[Music]
Crepe shop
opens. Two expensive guests have arrived.
[Music] This
is Calliope Morley from Please.
Ruin is here. Thank you very much
.
[Music]
Maybe that's how I decided to introduce myself.
Something happened to me
[Music] I
flew in from Austria two days ago,
and before I came to Japan to do this crepe collaboration
[Music] I was
looking forward to it! Hololive This is Kiara, the jewel of English [Music] When did I say that 1  Months ago 2 months ago 2 months
[Music]
Thank you, thank you, thank you, I
really
love crepes. I love sweets. In
fact, when I came to Japan the other day, I ate that Holo
Live crepe
collaboration. I
took Ame-chan and Gura-chan with me.
At that time, I'm sure it
was between Senpai and Aki-senpai, so
I ate Aki-senpai's.It
was really good, that empty space.Senpai,
if he could decide something for himself, what would he do?Oh yeah, that's
right.Amazing caramel sauce and cheesecake.The
best.
That collaboration is over too.
I bought an acrylic stand. I
think I bought something else as well.
[Music] It
might be a tin badge, and that thing. I
also got something like the clear file that I received. It
's so cute.
[Music]  ] I
really wanted to go, but I was definitely
a little
scared.I
don't think everyone knew, no,
no, I thought in a low voice and
left right away.It's okay,
today.
Let's
have a toast. Let's have a toast.
[Music] When I
heard you talking about having fun with crepes, you asked me what to eat and what to bring. I
was a little worried. Ah, I see, it's an
odd amount. I
brought a lot.  Well, I
just wanted to say how thankful I am, and it's a
really
nice big surprise
present.
Today, I asked you to think about what I wanted to eat, and
drew a picture of a grape. I'll
show it to you on the stream as well. I think it's like this.
Thank you in advance.  You
can eat as much as you want today.Then I'll
start with Chiara-chan's
crepe
Jajaan.What
kind of crepe is this?This is
grape.It's basically something like this at a crepe shop,
and when you order it, it's always like this.That
strawberry, banana, and fresh cream.  And
this is a fortune cookie with vanilla ice cream. It's not a fortune cookie, it
's a cookie.
[Music] It
was interesting to see the other members' drawings.
This cute sketchbook has a lot of
handwritten crepes written by the members I've been to. It's so
cute.  Anya's
Ori-chan's cap was amazing. I
tried to make it sweet and sweet.
[Music]
How many thighs? It's
more like thighs. It's more like her
arms are bent.
But this is Japan, and this is where the boobs are.
There are people who take fraudulent photos like that. I
saw that.  It's a cleavage that even an old man can create.It's a bit like that.If you're
a bit of a pain and
someone asks you to send me a photo of yourself, just
take a picture of it. [
Music] [Laughter
] If you
wear lace or something,
[Music]
[Laughter]  ] You
said you wanted to eat ice cream.Ice
cream The
crepe on it feels like it's already finished.The
crepe
looks like a cute top.It's
super cute with ice cream.And the
chocolate cream
sauce is really nice too.  I have a little bit of
chocolate sauce. Thank you.
[Music] I
hadn't eaten anything, so I was waiting for a while.
[Music]
[Laughter] I
hadn't really eaten anything, so I
went to the game, so I hope it's
okay.  It's a reward.
[Music] It
's a dinner crepe. I
mentioned it a little bit in today's membership broadcast.
But I like the
salty type of savely crepe. If I
don't eat it first, I
feel a little strange. For example, if I
eat a sweet crepe at first,  I heard that if I
eat a savely salty crepe later on, I'll feel
a little weird.Well
, if I
eat a salty crepe at first, it'll be a little weird later
on.I think I can eat a lot of different kinds of crepes, and I can
eat both salty and sweet ones, so I
thought it would be a good idea to try it.
[Laughs]
My friend says to check in often, so
I often check in too.I'm sorry, I
guess.
I
asked you what kind of crepes you like, and what kind of crepes do you like? I asked you
something about that, and I
wanted to ask for some potatoes that I forgot. I have potato salad, so
there are some fries that helped me out. Also, baked sweet potatoes.
Add baked potatoes.  There's
also lettuce in it. The
pronunciation in English is completely different in both Japanese and English.
This is Calliope 5.
[Music]
If you have it, I definitely want you to include it.
Please
[Music]
[Music] That's
right
[Music]
Bad.  I'm Nut
Festival Crepe Knot The festival crepe contains apples,
blueberries, bananas, strawberry
sauce, fresh cream, and
cream cheese.I was thinking of adding ice cream,
but since it contains cream cheese and fresh
cream, I think it's a bit too much.  I
think this is the best. It's a colorful
fruit that has all sorts of fruits in it. It
looks stylish. I came to eat a lot of it. Awesome [Music] Looks delicious. It also contains cute blueberries. Yes, it also contains blueberries. I want you to see it.
[Music]
Frozen strawberries are
not in season,
right?
[Music]
A little
sour
About 4
This fruit festival Bataan mat festival
Strawberries that don't have crepes in them are not
included They
are here
[laughter] It
's just for decoration
Even though I'm looking forward to it,
Autumn-senpai is my favorite.  After the decision was made, he
said something really nice. I
think the sweet autumn crepes are so appealing.
[Music]
Alright, senpai, it's going to take 40 minutes, but can you
make three crepes?
Leave it to me. Well,
first of all.  Let's go from the side dish crepe.
[Music]
[Music] There
's green too. I
like it. Japanese cucumbers and
those Austrian cucumbers look very different. They're
thin, they're thick, and
they're even more like that.
[Music]
There aren't any spots. [Music]  [
Music] The
difference between zucchini and cucumber, next to Austria, which is slippery over the moon
[Music]
Vegetables
I really understand it, I know it.
That's right, you
know my cooking. It looked
really delicious. I make it often.
But
what, next time?  I want you to
make some kind of home-cooked Japanese food instead of those crepes.I want you to make
good food, not restaurant food.I
want to try your senior's curry and rice.It's
definitely delicious.
[Music]
About 1 year 1  You've been saying this to me since before I got the impression in 2017.
[Music] Do you want to
do that real thing with a camera?
Let's do it
[Music] Let's
do what we want to do
[Music] I
know, I know, but I might have never done it.  I
don't know.
What kind of system did you buy?
Gather resources [Music] Create a road to create your own land. The
person who creates a big city and gets 10 points wins. The
person who created the most proper land wins.
[Music] I
can destroy enemies and things.
[Music]
[Laughs] I
thought it looked like an HPM that I wanted to kill.
[Music]
Wow, that looks
super good.
[Music] You
should really show this part of it on camera.  I think it's amazing. I want to see something.
[Music]
[Laughter] I
can believe it, but
[Music] It's
not suitable for just one animal.
like an anime. You
know it. You
don't know it.
[Music] No
one.  I don't know,
but
what do you say about that Nishiki?
[Music]
Nishiki is really friendly
I guess he got used to it right away
[Music]
[Music] He was
really quick He's a
professional It
can't be helped, it's okay
Please go ahead, problem.  No. I'm going to
eat Calliope.
[Music] I'm
going to put in the amazing crepe starter. It's amazing. I don't know where to go. I'll
take it on the spot. I
want to add this and my Instagram-worthy stand. It's
nice. It's the
best.
[Music] It's so
nice. Thank you.
[Music]
Well, if you send me a photo there,
of course.
OK, I'll send it to you. I'll
make two or three more in the next 30 minutes.
[Music] I'm looking forward to it.
Anyway, it's really
nice. I need to
check everything, so it's all in.
[Music]  ]
Baked sweet potato I'm going to
put it in now
Sweet sweet
potato It's the world I confirmed It's nice
[Music]
Today's baked sweet potato
Thick baked sweet potato
[Music] I'm
selling it as it's ready It's already made and it's ice cream It's
frozen.  It smells amazing, it's a mess.I
went to Starbucks two days ago, and
there was a Frappuccino that Starbucks was selling for a limited time.It tasted like a roasted
sweet potato.I
tried it, and it tasted
surprisingly good.It was
surprisingly interesting.The Grilled Sweet Potato
Frappuccino
[Music]  ]
But it wasn't very tasty.
[Music] It wasn't
delicious. Thank you.
I
see. I'll
take it. I'll eat it. The
crepes have started. Be
careful if you don't like the sound of eating.
Ring
[Music]
Amazing.
Wallet
Potato salad  I think teriyaki and teriyaki
go really well together.
[Music]
Have you ever put a cucumber behind a cat
?
[Laughs]
[Music] It does
n't react.
It's a legend. It's a
cat legend. I bet they'll be
surprised
[Music]
Or do animals look like snakes?
Those
two cats keep coming and going. I'm
curious.
Only one of the cats is a girl, and she's the most genius. I
see. I see.
Since the beginning of this year,
one of my two cats has
started jumping on top of that door handle to open it, and it's really
bothering me, but I
wish they would stop.  Yeah,
lock it and
don't add any reductions. Well, basically, I
keep all the doors open all the time.
Even if it's the door inside the house, my cat
would open the door to exit the house, so
that's no good.  Okay, I said
[Music] It's
heavy. It's supposed to be heavy.
Even if you drop it on the first floor, it won't open normally. But it
can't be opened without pulling your own body. But it will
pull. That's
right. It's very
smart, so someday.  Yeah, I'm sure you'll
understand.
[Music]
The beer is over.
There's still one more time. I
'd like to try the same one as you.
[Music] If you
pronounce it a little like a baby,
and if you pronounce it gently, it'll turn out that way. I
think it's cute.  Thank you for your support. The
next step is to call it wawa.
[Music]
Calliope
says ``Giwawa.'' These days,
[Music] It seems like it's
a little strong.
Thank you.
[Music]
This is interesting. Just now, Callie-chan
was drinking Japanese strawberry beer.  It
says it's a strawberry beer, but it does
n't taste like strawberries at all, so it's not strawberry at all.
[Music] Is
that a place?
But I like the basic design of this package.
[Music] I
mean, I've heard the word ``wheat'' in German.
I don't drink beer, so I don't know much about it, but
is it barley juice?
[Music]
Well, we're drinking the same thing. Calliope, I
don't drink alcohol.
What are you going to do now? [
Music] I
'm making my own crepes. Fashionable
[Music]
Fun I wish
they would add a little more strawberry
[laughing] '
Cause there's more
[Music]
[Music
] No, [Music] That looks really
expensive I'd
like some vanilla ice cream
[Music]
Expense
Let's add
it.
By the way, the key point is 20 minutes left on the simple time counter.
[Music] I
want to take a photo before I wrap it.
[Music]
This is going to hurt.
[Music] I took it. I
sent a photo to Nice. I
posted it on Twitter as art.  I do.
[Music]
Yes, ice cream.
[Music] I'm
super excited.
Can I get a small spoon later?
Thank you. I
taught my senior a really good English lesson a while ago.
[Music]
Beans
English I
remember it, so it means. I
remember it. What does it mean?  If you watch a long series all at once,
for example in one day
[Music]
Even if you're a regular user, please use it.
One Piece on Netflix Yeah,
I watched the movie. It was a really good movie.
I don't know anything about One Piece,
but this Netflix.  That dress was truly divine. I was
really interested in it.
Nami-chan is so cute. Have you noticed how cute she is?
Recently, I've
been able to see Kiara's casual outfit,
and it's the same color as Nami-chan's.  It
's a bikini top.
That's why it looks like a Name-chan cosplay.
[Music] I
hope everyone has noticed.
Thank you, Flash. I
get a lot of compliments on how good I am at taking pictures, but crepe
is difficult. You want to take it off from the top.
That's nice.  Maybe
No Fresh
Flash Off I
'd like a spoon
[Music]
This crepe shop is busy
Thank you
[Music]
Other characters
[Music] My
favorite One
Piece I
don't know, I don't know, it's the
worst  I think that person is
really interesting, but I think Luffy is the main
crew member and Brook is right now.Skeleton
Bits.I
like music, so I definitely like it a lot.I
just made Kari-chan's song from Volume 106 of One Piece.Yes,
thank you.It
was fun.
Good, I
did my best [
Music] I'm
really happy. Can you
hear this ASMR?
[Music]
But the sound is small.
[Music] It's
soft.
[Music] The
crepe is a panther.
[Laughs] [Music
]
Yo.
[Music] I'm
looking forward to it. Fruit Festival Butter  It's made of
fresh cream strawberry sauce.The main
ingredient is cream cheese,
fresh cream banana,
blueberries, apples, and on top of that
is strawberry sauce. It's
okay
[Music] It's
okay. It might be crazy. [Music] It's
super delicious.
[Music]
[Music]  ]
Thank you
Banana Banana and apple There's also an
apple in there.
Should I put the apple in there? Should I stick it on top or
sprinkle it inside?
[Music] It's
better to see it from above, that's for sure.
Cutting the apple.  How do you cut it
and
slice it?
[Music] I
know this. Have you ever tried this cut?
[Music]
[Music] If you
cut it this way, there won't be
much left. You can eat almost all of it.
Music]
Beautiful,
amazing I
want you to make Austrian apple dessert. I'll
send you the recipe next time.
[Music]
I like it.
[Music] Are
all the comments true? [Music
]
[Music]
Me  Parents,
senpai, there are only 9 minutes
left.Strawberry sauce,
that might be it.There are
quite a few of them.Hololive 1
[Music]There are
a few people in the 2nd generation who are pushing me a little.I don't know
why, but I do
n't understand.I'm
sorry.  What are you doing?
Even Mio-senpai. It's
hard for
newcomers to understand why you're doing this. Is that Subaru's car?
[Music]
[Music] I
'm in the ambulance.
Thank you, thank you.
[Music]
Thank you.
This mom is...  Out of all the things I've tried, it's my favorite. It
's the best. I'm
glad I
like crepes. I definitely like sweets.
[Music] Some
JP members also like
sweets, but side
dishes. Crepes are the most popular side dish. It's the same as always.  That's
right, that's why the diameter is the largest,
but it might just be Hololive. Yeah, most of the normal
crepe shops and girls probably have the
sweet
strawberry variety.
Americans also
only
want to eat sweets.
[Music]  ]
That's right.
Crepes that are as unhealthy as possible.
[Music] They
're cutely made.
Crepes are originally from France, I guess.
[Music]
Crepes served on fancy plates are
completely different from the crepes you order in Europe and those in
Japan.  There are a lot of different things on the tap,
and the way they are rolled is different, so I
think the differences are really interesting.
[Music] I think the
crepes at Boranchi are simpler and more
crispy.
[Music]
Most of the crepes are quite simple.  But
both are good, but if I had to choose, I like Japan's Harajuku-
style crepes the best
[Music] There's
really something about Japan.
Even if it's not desserts, it's foreign
food. It's
amazing to make your own in Japan.  I
feel like I'm going to add some flavor and make it my own. I'm
going to make my Japanese version, so I really like experiencing the differences
[music] There
might be quite a few. We both made this.
But there's that Austrian crepe.  Well,
actually, it's
called nose chinken.
Crepes and crepes are thin,
pancakes are thick, right? Hara-
kun is between them. The noodles are a
little thicker than the crepes. Oh yeah, yeah, that's right,
I can make them too. Let's
try it out.
I'm still eating.  I'm
eating slowly
[Music]
Thank you for making the
collaboration
[Music]
Round and round
I love it, it's wide
Don't you burn it?
2 minutes left 2 minutes
left I'm still eating I'm still eating Post-
stream
[Music]
Or
No, it's not like this  I thought I'd buy something with crepes.I'm
not the last one to use the gas in the kitchen and just put a griddle on it.I
have electricity, but it's a bit
weak.Okay,
do your best, do your best
[Music]
[Music] I'll
make use of my cooking experience so far.  The bar has been raised
[Music]
[Music] It's
really good
[Music]
[Music] That's
great. Let's
get started.
I can make French toast. I'm really
good at it.
But I feel like it's hard to make it like this unless you're in your own kitchen.
Come on, hurry up.  When will you come?
People might say it's because I'm from Japan.
Ah, I'm already in Japan, so please
come.
2 members always
say, "I'm going," but they don't come. I'll be
waiting. Let's go eat.
[Music] I'll
post the last crepe I tried on Twitter
[Music]
So today
was the Autumn Takamori party.
Thank you, Senpai. Thank you so much. I
think I'll be able to sleep well from now on. I
'll still eat it when I have a chance. I'm
busy so it's really early.  I look like a Japanese
office worker eating crepes.I look like an office worker.You can
eat crepes with one hand,
so you don't have to work.I
make them anytime, even when I'm busy.Come and eat.
[Music]
Please subscribe to the channel.Thank
you in advance.  Thank you very much.
[Music]
Later today, we will also broadcast Corone's Neo's birthday,
so please take a look. Well then, the
crepe shop is
closed.
Thank you
[Music]