thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
hey look you know what let it be said
that we tried man I grinded in this game
you've been here really too we've been
practicing as a team yes we've been
doing pretty good we weren't doing well
I don't think we lost yeah we had some
good battles yeah we're too strong
together
I feel like the BC buff
[Music]
MC for today so let me introduce you to
the stream today's stream if you're not
aware is the free Pokemon World
Championship
events
[Applause]
yeah yes thank you huge thank you for
including thank you very much thank you
exciting go first Pokemon unite World
Championship to be held in Asia we'll
start tomorrow from August 11th to 12th
in Yokohama I mean the Pokemon unite
category teams from all around the world
will fight for their championship and we
will also be fighting for championship
against Indonesia and JP
representing team Hollow en and who do
we have it is serious yeah very serious
here for our team I am serious fauna I'm
taking the Pokemon Wiggly tough as a
rule of support we also have Miss
Calliope Mori would you like to
introduce yourself hi everybody Morkie
here um I will be playing as uh Garchomp
jungler
um I will be jungler or I uh I will feed
I mean mid later mid later sorry sorry
mid later
I will be mid laner excuse me
Iris Would you like to introduce
yourself uh hiris is Iris I will be uh
using glacial and today uh glaceon's
wearing very cute clothes and I will be
bottom today
[Laughter]
so we have takanashi Kiara
hi hello
um I'm representing every European out
there who is currently awake at 4 5 or 6
a.m I've been staying awake but I'm very
awake still so I think I will be fine
let's come buddy muscle I'm doing alola
nine tails because yeah what else
but it'll be great it'll be great
to have Amelia Watson
um
Amelia Watson number one detective today
I'll be your tank yes rely on me please
stay with me yes I'm going top with uh
Kiara yes yes
my bodyguard yeah pretty much right
bouncing around there it's only a little
bit of time left before the world
championship I'm sure everyone is cool
Championship oh wait yeah well for today
there's only two a few minutes
going down
so how about we watch the PV together
okay I don't do a little countdown and
we can all share it on our streams okay
I hope I don't blast your guys's ears
the start one yeah yeah
first one
three two one go our summer starts now
[Music]
I love the animation yeah
you broke the budget for this one
[Music]
isn't that a legendary
exactly
[Music]
all right
I did not recognize that this Pokemon
and I met you yeah
oh yay what do you guys think wow right
that was really cute
it's fun to show anime
streams yeah
corrections I know
uh let's move on over to the event
overview I believe we're ready yup
that's the slides okay okay
but I'm not ready I'm ready oh wait wait
the slides uh the the the slides right
okay
wait a second wait a second yeah
differently
[Music]
and we thought that that was a good idea
because you know yeah
stop so can you find out for us if this
is accurate right now and we'll just
talk over it for now yeah I have a
Pokemon unite World Tournament is a
promotional event for the Pokemon u9
category on the world championship 2023
oh I have a whole lot of English and
whole life Indonesia will battle head to
head to settle who will shine on top
hopefully it'll be us
the three matches will be JP versus
Ian and the match will follow the WCS
rules therefore Mewtwo will be banned oh
wait are you guys showing the slides
sorry yes yeah
yeah wait wait it feels like it's like
black
[Music]
it's okay for me yes reopen and in a
case of a three minute pie the team who
scores the most can be crowned the
winner oh okay try for points
tournaments go
the winner wins the winner wins the
winner wins
wins and
we all get I think there's there should
be like something right consolation
prizes
mm-hmm
next slide oh I think first slide yeah
okay oh speaking to prizes speaking of
presents
the MVPs each team will be awarded with
like real physical prizes the wcsa
official uniforms which are not for sale
cool and if you were pushy wearing the
Pokemon units Hollow air and other teams
will be awarded with 2D trophies
according to their placements
[Music]
yeah they'll think we're the winner
I really want that shirt though yeah
I know well speaking of the shirt or
characters in game are also wearing this
shirt which you can also purchase
yourself from the shop the digital
version in the in-game store
we are going first seems like it
apparently okay
that's great that's amazingly ready for
this oh well trial by fire here we go we
are doing good just remember how we were
playing okay yeah remember
don't overthink it just because just
because it's the JP okay his JP team
it's fine
pretty darn sweaty though yeah no
problem we can be sweaty too just gotta
get in the mindset yeah
precipitation
here in the other participants for the
tournament from JP we have okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
makes sense
okay we have um
[Music]
be full but they're cuteness they're
scary
they are scary I mean we're supposed to
be lore wise you know like gods and
myths oh my God we should be pretty
darned right guys
including one one one human girl
the most mythical of creatures I know
in Hollow Yen I've really been wanting
them well I guess we have we got on me
we have a British
hearing your British accent you don't
bring it out very often
serious I wish you would let your
natural accent shine sometimes
it's okay I'll try it
okay
[Music]
so these are our clothes
can we put away the slide can we close
it okay
as mentally prepared as we thought
[Music]
I was still debating on what Pokemons
how do we get into the rooms oh they
will send a code and we will input the
code make sure not to show it on stream
I love how the order of the matches it
makes it seem like the whole alive JP
and ID are like the the finals
yeah
and I get to sleep early if yeah I mean
yeah I can sleep at night probably stay
awake anyway though
okay
[Music]
please just say Maury and I will
yes if we're losing your lane matchup
you know who to call
the code will be provided to us yes
I think we're also going to go into
meets the rest of the
should we do we wait until they are oh
it looks like they are they're going
okay okay
we go there wait are they
is there a Lobby already the all regions
Channel okay it's like oh oh to produce
it for introductions okay so do we move
too okay we go we go let's go
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
yes
I think that's why thank you Kiara thank
you
um
[Laughter]
can you hear me
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
we've been practicing believe in
yourself I'm proud of you
climbing the Rings
you can beat let's go JP and ID team
um
[Laughter]
what happened anyways yeah
I feel the motivation gaps but it's okay
oh no I'm motivated motivated me too me
too
[Music]
yeah because it is
I'm looking forward to seeing your good
fight battle thank you
and Tim okay
can I ask you
[Applause]
already started right the gong the
gongling
yeah there is
one year
you can't do that to me
foreign regions
[Music]
the food you ate before is it the food
we're about to eat food don't be nervous
we'll be fine food just gotta Focus your
food are you hungry some food I need
some food
[Music]
yeah we're the first two matches and
then they do the finals amongst each
other
you know if they screw up big time are
we good is that the code okay
quickly
yeah that's your code okay I gotta hide
okay I hide yes hide the code I'll be
search
I searched the lobby
I'm in the lobby
oh I think it said something like we are
supposed to be
uh
uh like a top
or at bottom like there's a specific
order they want us to be in really
yeah it was in the in the like
explanation thingy but now that the
order is changed I'm confused too but
maybe we're in the right spot because I
think it said for the first one and Ian
down for the second one
[Music]
let's go with that yeah
remember not okay and now we can show no
panicking allowed okay no panicking play
it safe play cool call the Cali as usual
okay wait so are we gonna go for top
objective first or bottom or are we not
gonna decide we need to be aggressive I
think
should we decide on that beforehand yeah
yeah it might be situational depending
on where the others are
um okay
um I should be high enough level at a
certain point where I can kind of guard
the bottom and then also take out the
bottom objective by myself if I do the
jungle correctly
it will be good stay out of my jungle
please
they start to stop us and they get our
first
our first uh
goal down and then they also get an
objective we can try to go and steal
their Farm in the jungle okay
await your command completely
um struggles against aggressive players
so we really need to play aggressive
okay
okay we can show the screen now right
yeah yeah yeah yeah
aggressive but safe
it'll be fine it'll be fun I wonder how
our team comp is I wonder if it's
let's focus on levels though for sure
yep
um and then
um
can we try to be not like screaming all
the time because it will freak me out
yeah okay okay yeah we'll be calm a
calming collection just like we're
playing against the bots so that we can
also hear fauna clearly when she wants
something from us oh they have a Glaceon
too okay so Dragon Claw is the meta but
I'm going with earthquake so that I can
take out the bigger Farms of swablu and
alteria so and also attack from a bit
more of a distance who's going who's
going Bottom with me I'm going behind
him okay
better than their Glacier
you got this no problem here we go have
confidence
let's go just like practice it's like we
practice just slap oh God my hands are
so sweaty already
pop this really quick we'll use it again
later
this one
I am useless until level five well we'll
just poke a little bit
okay let's go and get this they're
scared they're scared come on playing
safe they're playing safe
don't let them steal it don't let them
steal it
is okay I think they did
going back
yeah
who needs more help bottom or top
oh go for the middle one
[Music]
Nice Nice kill okay
yeah yeah
this thing traps you damn okay yeah
I'm gonna quickly my Steel
Kelly
it's nice
yeah let's go
score
steal the farm hold on oh scissor
scissor dude
okay I need to love this dude's almost
dead though oh damn it should we go
I'm lagging pretty bad
she on his back
shoot okay hold on no one's dead right
now right
should I join down there
[Music]
um
I think it's my internet
I'm safe
okay hopefully it passed and doesn't
come back
yes I do okay
don't attack yet
we're gonna go for bottom yeah they're
going for bottom should we should we
interrupt I think we should try to steal
it
okay let's try steal it okay
um
okay good we'll just change try not to
die
don't die
let's go
okay let's not play too impressive yeah
I mean I'm back Play Safe Play Safe come
back if you have to go back cool oops
all right that's fine
I know me too my heart's thumping if I
had my heart rate monitor now I'd be
dying right now
um
kind of want to grab Center form again
hold on oh actually yeah
you think they're going to steal it they
might but we could grab it we could grab
it
let's go top
okay
boobs maybe I shouldn't have I broke
down thing sorry
it's okay let's go over here okay we're
coming we're coming
it's okay no problem yummy
it's fine it's fine don't worry don't
worry
I can't really fight uh
okay just uh be the bouncy person
okay let's be bouncy I'm gonna back up
yeah ideally we don't want to fight on
there
there yeah if we can I'm trying to get
out but I'm lagging I can't even oh no
I'm sorry it's okay we'll be fine
oh God I can't I can't get out of here
all right I'm coming I'm coming
oh they're scissors you're gonna pop it
real quick hold on can't do anything
hold on okay
mm-hmm
sorry about that guys I will be back
okay let me get over here and help
nice
actually
bottom Glaceon scoring bottom okay hold
on um I think it's about to go bottom
should we I think someone's gonna
brought them
too much
I think I think we need to farm a little
I think we're focusing too yeah I'm
trying to find them okay yeah uh he's
bad girl they're trying to kill me all
right hold on yeah we can try to get
them ready
too low level but I can hold it I can
hold her you can try to hold bottom yeah
wait what level are we is everyone
higher than us no they're Nine and Nine
yeah
behind me
I'm gonna go back to bottom
is good
I don't know who's who who's who I know
who I know
yeah we shouldn't get should we go
bottom because we have a new hand right
now okay go bottom oh they just got they
just got ready guys okay let me please
okay hold on a sec no worries we're
coming back
no I should have known they were down
there I was not paying attention to the
map
thanks guys I will be there in a second
oh I need to be a higher level
no worries okay
[Music]
oh shoot they're totally uh I'm
dead okay
hold on
I'm not high enough level yet yeah we
should be careful about team fights I
think I think we need to there's like so
much left actually we should oh God okay
get ready we should defend I think okay
should I go down or up I'm going up I'm
just gonna get a buff really quick okay
we are going up yeah but we might need
it
right now already
is going so fast stay safe
okay we all go in at the same time we're
all here we're all here I think we
should here let's go let's go
100.
okay I have something to score uh we
should defend if we can okay oh they're
they're totally up there lyrics
[Music]
I don't know
it works no it doesn't work
they were playing the long game waiting
yeah they were I know where did they
come from
um
oh no there's like three of them oh God
I'm dead I'm dead I'm dead oh damn it
[Music]
I don't know we just have to stop them
from uh depositing points and we can
still put it we might be even right now
[Music]
um
it's true I'll defend I'll stay and
defend if you guys go okay I have no
points I don't know if that's enough to
go over I was willing to risk it for a
biscuit what the hell got me at least
they hey I distracted them where are
they right now I think I'm out of this
game no they were all the way to the
right at their home bases
they know what they want already yeah
yeah it's rough yeah
nice try nice try we did good we tried
it did I think we did well I we had a
handicap because I was not handing it
but uh I uh was lagging really really
really bad yeah yeah
next match
we'll get them next time
good job good job
I'm proud of you guys I thought that was
pretty good yeah if only we got if we
got the recoils yeah
I knew it's closed it was close because
so
it's kind of rough yeah anyway let's try
it let's try it maybe check chat for one
second yeah I I needed far more I'm just
going to set my presence right now
Ambush
um
so we're leaving the lobby right
we're playing again immediately
immediately warmed up it's true but my
hands are shaking I know my controllers
controller sweaty
I'm sorry oh is there already a room is
there really a room
another one
what about now Chad
I thought it was just super quiet chef
[Music]
okay wait do we still have a chance
right yeah okay
yeah we do we do we're only behind 200
points as long as we'll see how ideas uh
against Jason but they saw us fight
oh
I know they know our cards yeah okay
that's true they watched that is true
they have that
okay I had a fun time watching damn it I
think I know and I thought we'd be in
that position yeah
yeah I think in that one team fights
where our weakness
because we weren't arriving all at the
same time yeah yeah gotta make sure not
to start and I was doing this morning
before everyone arrived oh whoops I'm
sorry wait hold on is this the wrong
oh they went to the wrong one
um yeah I will try and help if I can but
I really need to try to focus more on
farming yeah yeah you're a late game mom
so you can focus on farms and we can
just try in the
try to defend yourself I'll try to help
if I can though yeah yeah Kiara since
you're looking at the time a lot um oh
yeah we just need to remember so seven
minutes for subjective unlocks and then
a two minutes Ray closes so around like
30 seconds or a minute before that we
got to be prepared to go yeah like at at
three hours three Thirty don't use your
oils okay so even for wrinkles
when there's yeah 330 left okay
[Music]
how do I move my position wait
over here are we supposed to be bottom
this time I think yeah they were all on
top so
it seems like it but I don't know
[Music]
you're saying fauna
oh yeah
okay
um
yeah I I get so tunnel visioned and I
don't really get what was like after I
get to a certain level I'm just like
what should I do now yeah I think just
stay with the tea yeah we should stay
with at a certain point yeah
I have to also focus on leveling in the
beginning because Evie is weak as hell
in the beginning and yeah I have to wait
until I get to like at least level six
or seven to get ice shard
yeah I think it too
we were focusing a lot on fighting them
and we probably should have just been
staying back and farming yeah yeah
we can try that too okay okay okay
[Music]
maybe she was only using it for that
stream I don't know but they were going
with like a pretty pretty
meta-ish I think I forgot
I've got your back show the screen I
forgot about that okay okay I'm glad
you're back so cute I'm going to focus
on being the strongest
good buff
[Music]
whoa
good work no laptop No I gave up on
Lapras
[Music]
I think Lapras is too too weak for this
comp
and also also because lappers did not
have much outfits yes
I really don't like zorark
oh yeah yeah
I think she's juggler yeah I think she
is oh God we're gonna have such a bad
time
confidence up
okay okay all right all right
I believe
all right I'm gonna be the strongest
right now seven minutes yeah three
minutes beware
all right yes
three minutes what happens in three
minutes we should be ready
okay what 3 30. don't use your own how
long does it take for the ultimate oh it
depends on the character yeah it depends
but you'll be safe if you win 3 30.
[Music]
I want to get that formed
steal it I think I stole it nice
scared
I'm going back to heal
oh okay
they're being very aggressive yeah they
are
good
[Music]
hey I'll come down to grab well you guys
got the foreign
[Music]
should we go
they're too strong it's okay it's okay
we still need to level one we're doing
okay in the middle
yeah just try to play Space don't die
and Farmers I'm coming to pop
they're not okay
speed up I need to keep farming actually
I need to focus on being the strongest
I'm gonna go for Middle Farm
yeah yeah
I think they're all going for top is it
just me I think I feel like oh they're
here
Iris do you think you can hold your own
down here they've identified
I could I could I'll try I'll try you
can you can go up I'll I'll try to just
hold them back I don't know if I could
die
zero scary
Thailand bot run go down don't fight
right now come come
oh that was close that was close yeah
I was gonna help them I was gonna help
them but never mind oh okay
lagging again oh no oh gosh yeah
okay we'll try to hold them off top yeah
just try to hold them off and just try
not to die and get it I want to score
I can solo this
no
oh no should we go down here
all of them okay oh nice we should go
okay all right they're gonna they're
gonna take the objective maybe we should
leave one person bottom shoulders
okay yeah and I'll try and farm at the
same time I got it actually I can take
it
points
yeah yeah we should try to defend
um but we'll have extra Farm after this
oh God I died
I shouldn't have sandwiches
yes
yeah they're really coordinated they're
much more important and they are it's
okay we still have the Rayquaza there's
a center Farm a few more minutes left
till Rayquaza and we can take it okay
make sure to farm the Pokemon in this
Lane in the Top Lane there will be bonus
mons of uh spawn oh because they didn't
give birth yeah okay oh they're getting
their Farm they're getting out up here
oh okay nice
yeah they're on the top Lane I'm also
top but all of them yeah they're all in
Top Lane it's scary
[Music]
like anyone
okay
alarm time time there's no I don't see
any form at the top right now yeah I got
the one on the bottom jungle okay
should we go
just run run come on oh no they're
they're trying to kill me they're oh
they killed me
this is scary
how are their levels doing right now
all right let me see uh I'm still a
level above we're in it I'm gonna go to
the bottom
I think we should all just group up and
bottom right now
let me know if you need me somewhere
come down
I think it's fine it's also fun okay uh
we should probably go top okay
I'll wait for you oh wait they're all
down in the bottom Lane are they okay we
could just go top though Kyle is bottom
line they leave they left solo
everything yeah it's pretty strong okay
or try not to I topped my score okay
yeah okay do we want to go aggressively
for once maybe maybe next we can get it
here
they come
oh oh no
oh gosh
[Music]
are you kidding me
I love being useless to my team all
right closet Rayquaza yeah yeah okay it
was because of the leg let it be known
let it be known that was because the
bag
all right well let's just aim for
Rayquaza and see if we can make it count
okay okay
saving all their stuff so yeah you can
try to win I'm saving yes
oh we're really struggling yes
actually hold on
[Laughter]
okay
yep
um right just get ready for Rayquaza
okay yeah yeah I still have my ALT
thankfully
we do have a lot of points we could put
in remind me and someone to stay and
defend I'm not sure because I don't know
I feel like all of us can just go
request yeah I think they're all gonna
go I think they're all gonna go Rayquaza
yeah oh they're probably getting the
bottom objective yeah you can't get that
in time
they're definitely down there
oh no no no
no
okay
I mean get him get him get him okay nice
nice
okay don't lose all your HP to the
Rayquaza because they're gonna show up
here
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
do your best kind of score
I'm so sorry I'm so slagging so bad oh
God they killed me
here I got I'm gonna pick up the points
yeah yeah
thank you I need help Callie oh I can't
turn it on I'm coming
oh they're all guard they're guarding
the middle I'm they're all guarding the
middle maybe you can go top top is empty
the topper the one is empty
[Music]
all right come in
now
leave there's no way there's no way oh
nice let's go yeah oh oh okay
[Music]
okay let's see let's see
yes nah there's no way did we I don't
believe you I didn't get to turn in
because did we actually I didn't wasn't
able to get turned in
[Laughter]
[Music]
nice job
wait we're doing the doll yeah is it for
every match I think it's for every match
right for every MVP yeah let's go okay
I'm so happy I'm proud of you guys
I think we did really well we could have
won two yeah yeah it was really close
you guys know if they sell this shirt or
no I didn't think so
um
[Music]
I'm so sorry
if we maybe got in second please
hopefully we'll see after the next match
if they tally up all the points
how does that work so like if and
deserves
if ID loses then we're first I don't get
away to get less than like 300 points
which is unlikely unless JP is
we'll see
okay
download the points oh
I want to spectate are we able to do
that yeah yeah I'm gonna set up once
fauna makes the room we just join a
Spectators first okie dokie
on me
too much excitement
[Music]
and we did good nice job yeah we won a
match yeah I'm proud of I know we did so
well
our practice is paid off
I'm glad that we practiced a lot yeah
I'm glad I grinded like like 10 11 hours
yesterday
yeah it was worth it
you too afana thanks for helping us
learn the game yeah
I wouldn't have been able to do it
without you thanks for playing
also thanks for the the tips uh chat as
well to improve my jungle game I feel
like that second that second game was
much better
yeah yeah good good uh and strong
middling game let's go
Ian Strong Man another one the Kyla was
scary yeah she is scary she she just
comes out of nowhere and then bam bam
bam bam
[Music]
can we get a run back with JP now let me
try it again yeah
[Laughter]
uh I know Kiowa you you want to sleep
yeah no it's not because of that I'm not
even tired even though I've been awake
since it's straddling
[Music]
happy yeah now we get to sit back and
watch back and relax yeah no matter what
happens we've already done
our part
we've done our part yeah I'm really
curious to see how these aggressive
teams play against each other so wait
for us to get first place if it were to
happen
um then
what wait wait so if JP wins then we def
then JP definitely gets first place
right um ID wins then there might be a
chance depending on point difference but
they can get like 800 points
it could be a close match with these two
teams
yeah I think because I don't know I
don't know if we'll amount to uh Mike at
third place because of our Point yeah it
was pretty close third place or maybe
yeah oh it is
we still we still
we fought we won yeah
yeah and then the JP match was closed it
was pretty close we just kind of slipped
up at the end and yeah I should have
been stronger
but uh the Ping was holding me back
it's the pain
yeah hey the lag really got me the last
match okay we're starting
oh we're starting okay game starting
okay I wonder how spectator looks yeah
we'll do it to fly around probably ah
wait I need to show oh that'll be kind
of cool I think that you I think that
you can I think we get to just fly
around the camera did you guys know that
like on the edges
edges of the what you would call it the
the map there's like this Magnemite
holding a camera yeah it's so cute I
noticed it yesterday it was adorable
cameraman cute
who do you guys who are you betting on
[Music]
um
yeah
yeah JP was not very aggressive so you
might have it yet ID was very aggressive
yeah
we will see though because they're both
pretty strong
[Music]
it will be exciting I know I can't focus
though my adrenaline's too high yeah I
never mean to chill
chat who do you want me to to focus on I
can follow someone specific
I want to see how she jungles that good
question I mean mid lane yeah
Kayla whatever Kyla was was Middle Lane
right yeah okay Chad says because JP got
a break between maybe they've you know
recovered
yeah true
so cute
the baby baby no they're so cute so cute
that's so efficient I didn't know the
flower was like a starfish looking thing
in the beginning
oh
a starfish it looks like a starfish you
know the red right you're right starfish
with the flower or like a star fruit
yeah
yeah they seem so determined I know oh
my God
they're really going on
go for it
you can do it yeah they are they're
playing aggressively well yeah
the most important that was the level
going oh okay okay now higher level than
Kayla right now
Focus
yeah did push pretty hard to get in
there no Okay so
let's go there Sheila's grinding she's
back in the rotation to get the Buffs
again back in the mines she's level six
so is Glaceon who's playing Glaceon uh
[Music]
right now okay
they're strong
Anya's chilling
Anya no
um
[Music]
instead
Logan
[Music]
oh boy you can live though she's turning
it I mean they're scoring yeah they are
scoring yeah they did a good score they
did push them back
we can see the point difference
they don't show the point difference
when you're actually playing yeah they
do yeah they don't glad they didn't
honestly I think I would have choked
yeah
oh yeah dude she's going for regular
going for the top yeah
he defended really well though
this is exciting I like spectating I
know me too
let's go
go where's she going it's dangerous cool
well there's three there's three enemies
coming
oh this is the hot spot down here oh
here they come oh
um oh they're aiming they're getting
they're going for the regime oh ideas
I know right that's so weird it seems
like JP is winning but yeah
he's been picking them up hitting some
pills yeah some boring they've been able
to get glasses
that was a good move
foreign
[Music]
or up top
yeah it is well Cuba's going for the
bottom they're going there yeah ID has a
plan for me
I feel like they would be very good
communicators the ID girl so they're
gonna yeah with their Minecraft
serversy
everybody is
they
really need help up there
oh no
Last Hope is Rayquaza I would say so
we need to come not too big still yeah
the Rayquaza can still turn turn it
around but us being third place is
probably already set in stone yeah
[Music]
we might get second place
is it by points or is it by games one
I mean if JP wins this then I think by
points we'd be okay but if they get
Rayquaza what is what I mean
she's going for the registered
oh yeah
it's super coordinated as well I was
waiting to snipe it
one minute
no yeah we'll see how Rayquaza goes
that's the main fight yeah for all
sharing for ID for a lot of reasons
I think how coordinated JP is I'm
feeling like proud that we yeah
together pretty good against them to be
honest
I should have aimed my old better
hmm I'm proud of us we think we did well
yeah they're already considering how
yeah our last minute our grind was I
think we did pretty good yeah
[Music]
20 seconds if only in our practices our
enemies weren't so good so so I know
a lot of them
yeah
they're really they're really going for
Reggie Reggie like you when Ray Claus is
gonna yeah they are respond really soon
interesting yeah yeah you're just gonna
go for it after they got it oh yeah
they come here comes everyone
she's gonna get it oh oh they cooked
yeah one Japan member the other three
they're three oh there's three oh okay
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
this is gonna be so close
so close yeah Kyle is the only one
guarding I think and everyone else is
going offensive
what is the right answer for this one
I don't know
ID defend Maybe
yeah
it's a close match yeah no idea
[Music]
keep running
oh
no oh my gosh
they got the points in yeah oh gosh so
if he's gonna try and score these points
[Music]
that was awesome that was so good
wow
I know good matches a really good man
yeah right it's like clothes for
everyone that was amazing wait so
everybody won one match yeah yeah now
it's all according to points oh shoot
well guys we did our best yeah
me too we did well
I mean look at how scary and chaotic and
crazy that battle was like it was pretty
insane
going up against these girls is quite a
challenge huge
that was huge
nice job MVP great job Japanese signs
[Music]
and all peku and only were the MVPs yeah
Ollie was MVP
everybody did well
yeah I am I'm proud of everyone I'm
proud yeah everyone knew what to do
pretty much yeah there was nobody that
was like fumbling around like I didn't
practice yeah yeah
I can confirm I did practice alone
it was really fun it was fun that was
really fun yeah I think I might try to
play more this season to hopefully get
to ultra
actually this was I feel like we all got
closer you know yeah it's really like
[Music]
yeah in general yeah once you know what
to do you just yeah if you're not too
sweatya
questions
[Music]
do we go and then I think we joined them
on the main Channel
and we must capture the slides again yes
awesome excited for that it will go away
yeah it'll be fine I just need to
repair yeah for the chat asking we don't
know the final tally yet we don't know
the winner not yet we do not know math
then you may know
all right don't say unless we don't want
to know we want to stay Oblivion yeah
exactly
yeah if you can do math you're banned
you can't be smarter than the fifth
grade us first grader
I think we will at least be in the top
frame I think so
yeah
we're on the podium
gold star for trying if you think about
it like the Olympic bronze medal is
something very something very proud
an honor it's just like that right yeah
that's big of an honor as that
I'm proud that we won a game I saw so
many people say today we were not gonna
win it yeah
[Music]
they're gonna walk all over us yeah
we've been training we've been working
but I was ready to be the most beautiful
carpets there to be no no wrong orange
carpets you have to be a flying carpet
yeah it's going to be a flying one where
am I flying to Flying to Victory
pad
Underdog prevail
Well Chad did you guys enjoy watching
that did you know what was going on all
the time it was at least fun to watch
yeah I never knew this could be so
sweaty like these kind of games yeah
yeah yes yes
like this like you know and I see like
tournaments going on and whatnot I look
at it and I always like oh no they're
just
spamming skills mashing is
it's just like an MMORPG I was like oh
that was fun but I don't why is
competitive now I get it yeah
when we like joined this I don't think
we any of us expected it to be that
serious I did yeah I didn't know I
thought it would be more it would just
be a fun
[Music]
just a fun fact
this was friendly yeah friendly
competition
but I'm really so proud because I think
we trained enough to make it like
interesting matches yeah
[Music]
um really
it wasn't too one-sided in any of the
badges I mean yeah the thing is like a
lot of Japanese and ID members were
already like really well practiced in
this game right I've seen a lot of
master
um ranks so you know yeah we just
started playing a lot of us just started
playing it yeah like four days ago yeah
yeah but we put in the work it was
playing in my dreams like last night
yeah
you're playing pretty late last night
yeah did you win in your dream or did
you lose uh well I was just like
attacking stuff in my dream but then
when I was trying to fall asleep I was
like running around in the game and I
kept running into walls and it was
really frustrating like I was like yeah
oh no
oh yeah I get chased a lot in my
nightmares just like here in Pokemon
unite
so it was a nightmare no no oh I wish we
could just play more while we're waiting
yeah
remix
[Music]
I'm happy with the way we perform yeah
it's so much more fun to like play with
like friends and like VCS and when
you're it was so frustrating yesterday
when I was like yeah you know queuing by
myself and then like yeah the random
would like you know leave me in the in
in the area alone and I'm just like why
and everyone's at the top in the
beginning I'm like what the why don't
you do that I'm Central okay I'm Central
I'm jungle and then I wait like five
seconds and then right before the match
starts somebody else says I'm jungle and
I'm like are you kidding me I might as
well not even do it
yeah I also had troubles playing alone
soloing regileki so many times why why I
was like why don't you girls wanna go up
there and get that objective why not
[Music]
they were just there to steal it after I
already got it man it feels bad man
feels bad but this feels good man yeah
like playing with the five stack yeah
yeah I still I still don't know if the
held items I chose was the correct
answer though I didn't go with like the
most standard build I went with I chose
something else for the because I wanted
to make myself less squishy but I'm
still very good I was still really
squishy so I'm just like maybe I should
have gone all offensive I don't know oh
they're going up now yeah I think it's
time okay the final piece of the results
okay
[Music]
wait a sec
one moment gotta set up the slides
slide okay
[Music]
hold on hold on
I got it thank you
[Music]
sorry this wasn't supposed to play this
I'm sorry I'm sorry how do I turn it off
oh my gosh sorry
[Music]
oh God is almost done thank you for your
good bottles
already
yeah
it was amazing
are you ready for it
[Music]
okay
yeah
[Music]
oh
wow
[Music]
[Laughter]
do you eat a cheese where is IDs
[Music]
[Applause]
let me know you were sold
um as a leader in leader please here you
are sold
I'm really proud of everyone many people
doubted the ENT but I hope that we
showed you know we showed our our
abilities today I think we did I'm proud
of everybody
[Music]
um
it was really amazing amazing match yeah
as a leader only time please tell
yourself
[Music]
[Laughter]
we can see a really good teamwork
communication thank you so much
yeah
thank you so much
I'm really glad you enjoyed this much
[Music]
meet us
many balls
[Music]
maybe always down
thank you
and not only this so I don't know
everybody
in the JP lesion MVP is
[Music]
thank you
so much
is MVP yes
great leader you got an MVP in the first
match and you really supported
yes yes
yeah you go to MVP and you contribute to
the comeback comeback Victory bye
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you
so much
[Music]
oh so we on the stream now or something
soon
give me a second hold on don't disease
when we left the slide thing you played
it did I play it yeah one more slide we
need to show one more slime oh one more
slides really oh okay okay okay
okay one second
let me pull up the slide
my time
because it slides it's not not the video
oh okay okay okay
[Music]
if this one was so exciting imagine how
exciting the actual one would be I know
right Pros you can also do predictions
right now
and then in the game if you get
predictions right you get prizes
Lee that the team uh Peru is absolutely
cracked really really yes okay no no I
don't know
I predicted also on a range
go
wait is there European oh yeah there are
European teams I should probably cheer
for them
go Europe go Europe let's go let me
remind everybody and did the Pokemon
unite category of WCS will happen
tomorrow
and here is a slide of all the
participating team members on the
Pokemon Knight category will be streamed
on the channel listed in the description
tomorrow 9pm November 11th AST
I tomorrow
in of course you can predict in the game
we're just going to get something for it
right you will win prizes if you guess
correctly yeah so please check it out
please watch the stream and cheer for
your favorite team
and we'll see you all tomorrow yeah we
will yeah I think that wraps everything
up I'm really proud of you guys I think
we did really well yeah really
considering considering like you know
how much we didn't really know yeah much
in the beginning
yeah that's why yeah
it makes a lot of sense
thank you I want everyone to get MVP
though
I think I'm really proud of us genuinely
we might have got third but they were
closed matches they were good I wasn't
like it wasn't a huge Point Gap it was
totally exactly it was it was pretty
close I feel good about it
with Matt shall we play the ending PV I
guess we should okay streams all right
yes then jump away yeah all right thank
you everyone for watching thank you for
watching thank you thank you so much for
the support it was really fun we're not
where are we are we muting during the
video yeah no do you think we can talk
through it okay okay
let's do three two where are you guys
wait wait wait wait I'm not ready yet
hold on hold on all right we're good
okay I'm ready ready okay
three two one go Pokemon unite recently
celebrated its second anniversary allow
us to introduce them congratulations
yeah first oh this map
yeah this looks fun oh cool I didn't
even try that yes I wonder if it'll be a
just as sweaty
yeah
the extra strong Mewtwo oh there's some
new Mobs okay too strong is not allowed
strong
via an event happening now and starting
August 17th you could get your Mewtwo
today which allows Mewtwo to mega evolve
into Mega Music
I didn't know Mewtwo why Mewtwo was this
like high knife
compared to eggs
different size difference was pretty
different world championship series
prediction events all players can
participate
unless you get all your predictions
wrong
imagine imagine
participating in this
mixed into the real teams I gotta put
that in too in Pokemon unite plus we're
also holding a second anniversary prize
machine
this is a great chance to get popular
Hollow air for Pokemon like Pikachu
stylish please join us
second anniversary
cute
yeah
[Music]
yeah thanks so much for everything you
guys that was fun yeah that was fun
thanks too I'm gonna be happy thanks for
inviting us for this thank you very much
a lot of fun yeah I'm really glad I was
able to take part in this and experience
this type of game yeah
fun training with everyone yeah I'm glad
we were able to train in the morning
yeah yeah it helped I think it did rise
and grind you know
it's my first first type of this genre
game yes it was fun Danke Schoen
[Laughter]
I believe that's all we have for today
we can let everybody get some rest yeah
we tried our hardest
thank you thank you thank you very much
thank you good job I have to go record
now okay okay I also
see you all okay thank you very much
thank you for
believing in us thanks
[Music]
have a great day
bye
[Music]
thank you