​​​ ​Hoof, hoof, helloof!​ ​​
​​​ ​konbandododo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Say your greetings together with the hololive members!​ ​​
​​​ ​hololive menbaa to issho ni minna mo aisatsu shite mite ne!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ready, set, go!​ ​​
​​​ ​nunnun nunnun​ ​​
​​​ ​How are we doing today? Tokino Sora!​ ​​
​​​ ​minna genki? Tokino Sora​ ​​
​​​ ​Nya-hello! Sakura Miko!​ ​​
​​​ ​nyaharo Sakura Miko​ ​​
​​​ ​This moment is key! This is AZKi!​ ​​
​​​ ​konazuki AZKi desu!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sweet bites! Yozora Mel!​ ​​
​​​ ​konkapu! konkapu! Yozora Mel!​ ​​
​​​ ​Haachama-chama!​ ​​
​​​ ​haachamachama​ ​​
​​​ ​A-quality day! It's Minato Aqua!​ ​​
​​​ ​konakua! Minato Aqua desu!​ ​​
​​​ ​Choc-on! Yuzuki Choco!​ ​​
​​​ ​chokkon, Yuzuki Choco​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, hello, I'm Murasaki Shion.​ ​​
​​​ ​aa, konbanwa, Murasaki Shion desu​ ​​
​​​ ​You listenin' to me?​ ​​
​​​ ​tte kiiteru?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey!​ ​​
​​​ ​neeee​ ​​
​​​ ​Hiya-peko! Hiya-peko! Hiya-peko! Usada Peko--​ ​​
​​​ ​konpeko konpeko konpeko, Usada Pekor​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay! Hel-Rushi! This is Uruha Rushia!​ ​​
​​​ ​iei! konrushi! Uruha Rushia desu​ ​​
​​​ ​konpeko konpeko konpeko, Usada Pekor​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey! Don't talk-o over me!​ ​​
​​​ ​iei! konrushi! Uruha Rushia desu​ ​​
​​​ ​cho, kabusetekunna peko!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahoy! Houshou Marine here!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahoy! Houshou Marine desu​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh, I don't really have a standard greeting, you see.​ ​​
​​​ ​aaa, watashi betsu ni kimatta aisatsu toka nai n desu yo ne​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh? Come on, Cocochi, introduce yourself!​ ​​
​​​ ​ee!? Cocochi! chanto jikoshoukai shite!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hoof, hoof, helloof! This is Tsunomaki Watame!​ ​​
​​​ ​konbandododo! Tsunomaki Watame​ ​​
​​​ ​Sup, groupies! Behold your Towa-sama!​ ​​
​​​ ​konyappi! Towa-sama desu!​ ​​
​​​ ​The hololive members keep coming. Next up is...​ ​​
​​​ ​hololive menbaa madamada iru yo! tsuzuite wa?​ ​​
​​​ ​Lamyoohoo! Yukihana Lamy!​ ​​
​​​ ​konrami desu. Yukihana Lamy​ ​​
​​​ ​Good afternene! I'm Momosuzu Nene!​ ​​
​​​ ​konnene! Momosuzu Nene desu!​ ​​
​​​ ​Brrr. I'll persevere-Risu!​ ​​
​​​ ​purupuru~ ganbari~ Risu!​ ​​
​​​ ​Moon, Moon, Moonafic!​ ​​
​​​ ​Moon Moon Moonafic da yo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh! Yes, sir! Iofi, sir!​ ​​
​​​ ​o o o! Obisa no Iofi!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, I'm Mori Calliope, I bring death.​ ​​
​​​ ​atashi ne! Mori Calliope desu​ ​​
​​​ ​Kikkeriki! Takanashi Kiara!​ ​​
​​​ ​kikkeriki, Takanashi Kiara!​ ​​
​​​ ​Of course the two of us come together!​ ​​
​​​ ​yappa watashitachi futari setto ni naru n desu ne​ ​​
​​​ ​Shut your mouth, stupid chicken!​ ​​
​​​ ​urusai kusotori! damare!​ ​​
​​​ ​yappa watashitachi futari setto ni naru n desu ne​ ​​
​​​ ​All together, here we go!​ ​​
​​​ ​saa minna de issho ni!​ ​​
​​​ ​S​c​r​e​a​m ​o​u​t ​y​o​u​r ​f​a​v​e​'​s ​n​a​m​e​, ​h​i​g​h ​a​n​d ​l​o​w!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​ibun no oshi no namae o sakebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n no oshi no namae o sakebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n ​n​o oshi no namae o sakebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n ​n​o ​oshi no namae o sakebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n ​n​o ​o​s​h​i no namae o sakebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n ​n​o ​o​s​h​i ​n​o namae o sakebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n ​n​o ​o​s​h​i ​n​o ​n​amae o sakebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n ​n​o ​o​s​h​i ​n​o ​n​a​m​ae o sakebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n ​n​o ​o​s​h​i ​n​o ​n​a​m​a​e o sakebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n ​n​o ​o​s​h​i ​n​o ​n​a​m​a​e ​o sakebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n ​n​o ​o​s​h​i ​n​o ​n​a​m​a​e ​o ​s​akebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n ​n​o ​o​s​h​i ​n​o ​n​a​m​a​e ​o ​s​a​k​ebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n ​n​o ​o​s​h​i ​n​o ​n​a​m​a​e ​o ​s​a​k​e​b​o​u!​ ​​
​​​ ​All together, here we go!​ ​​
​​​ ​saa minna goissho ni!​ ​​
​​​ ​C​a​n​'​t ​h​e​a​r ​y​o​u​, ​y​o​u ​k​n​o​w?​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​nnan ja zenzen kikoenai zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​n​n​a​n ja zenzen kikoenai zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​n​n​a​n ​j​a zenzen kikoenai zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​n​n​a​n ​j​a ​z​e​nzen kikoenai zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​n​n​a​n ​j​a ​z​e​n​z​e​n kikoenai zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​n​n​a​n ​j​a ​z​e​n​z​e​n ​k​ikoenai zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​n​n​a​n ​j​a ​z​e​n​z​e​n ​k​i​k​oenai zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​n​n​a​n ​j​a ​z​e​n​z​e​n ​k​i​k​o​enai zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​n​n​a​n ​j​a ​z​e​n​z​e​n ​k​i​k​o​e​n​a​i zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​n​n​a​n ​j​a ​z​e​n​z​e​n ​k​i​k​o​e​n​a​i ​z​o!​ ​​
​​​ ​All together, here we go!​ ​​
​​​ ​saa minna de issho ni!​ ​​
​​​ ​T​h​a​t​'​s ​b​e​t​t​e​r​! ​L​o​v​e ​y​o​u ​a​l​l!​ ​​
​​​ ​i​i kanji! minna daisuki!​ ​​
​​​ ​i​i ​k​anji! minna daisuki!​ ​​
​​​ ​i​i ​k​a​nji! minna daisuki!​ ​​
​​​ ​i​i ​k​a​n​j​i​! minna daisuki!​ ​​
​​​ ​i​i ​k​a​n​j​i​! ​m​i​nna daisuki!​ ​​
​​​ ​i​i ​k​a​n​j​i​! ​m​i​n​n​a daisuki!​ ​​
​​​ ​i​i ​k​a​n​j​i​! ​m​i​n​n​a ​d​a​isuki!​ ​​
​​​ ​i​i ​k​a​n​j​i​! ​m​i​n​n​a ​d​a​i​s​uki!​ ​​
​​​ ​i​i ​k​a​n​j​i​! ​m​i​n​n​a ​d​a​i​s​u​k​i!​ ​​
​​​ ​(hololive)​ ​​
​​​ ​O​k​a​y​, ​e​v​e​r​y​o​n​e​, ​o​n​e ​m​o​r​e ​t​i​m​e!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​a​a minna ikku zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​a​a ​m​i​nna ikku zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​a​a ​m​i​n​n​a ikku zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​(hololive)​ ​​
​​​ ​s​a​a ​m​i​n​n​a ​i​kku zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​a​a ​m​i​n​n​a ​i​k​k​u zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​a​a ​m​i​n​n​a ​i​k​k​u ​z​o!​ ​​
​​​ ​All together, here we go!​ ​​
​​​ ​saa minna de issho ni!​ ​​
​​​ ​L​e​t​'​s ​m​a​k​e ​t​h​i​s ​a ​w​o​n​d​e​r​f​u​l ​e​v​e​n​t!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​utekina raibu ni shite ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​u​t​ekina raibu ni shite ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​u​t​e​k​ina raibu ni shite ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​u​t​e​k​i​n​a raibu ni shite ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​u​t​e​k​i​n​a ​r​a​i​b​u ni shite ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​u​t​e​k​i​n​a ​r​a​i​b​u ​n​i shite ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​u​t​e​k​i​n​a ​r​a​i​b​u ​n​i ​s​h​ite ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​u​t​e​k​i​n​a ​r​a​i​b​u ​n​i ​s​h​i​t​e ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​u​t​e​k​i​n​a ​r​a​i​b​u ​n​i ​s​h​i​t​e ​ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​u​t​e​k​i​n​a ​r​a​i​b​u ​n​i ​s​h​i​t​e ​i​k​o​u!​ ​​
​​​ ​All together, here we go!​ ​​
​​​ ​saa minna goissho ni!​ ​​
​​​ ​R​a​i​s​e ​t​h​e ​h​y​p​e ​l​e​v​e​l​s ​t​h​r​o​u​g​h ​t​h​e ​r​o​o​f!​ ​​
​​​ ​dondon moriagatte ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​don​don moriagatte ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​don​don ​moriagatte ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​don​don ​mo​riagatte ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​don​don ​mo​ri​agatte ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​don​don ​mo​ri​a​gatte ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​don​don ​mo​ri​a​gat​te ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​don​don ​mo​ri​a​gat​te ​ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​All together, here we go!​ ​​
​​​ ​saa minna de issho ni!​ ​​
​​​ ​L​e​t​'​s ​c​r​e​a​t​e ​u​n​f​o​r​g​e​t​t​a​b​l​e ​m​e​m​o​r​i​es​ ​​
​​​ ​w​asurerarenai omoide o!​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​urerarenai omoide o!​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​u​r​erarenai omoide o!​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​u​r​e​r​arenai omoide o!​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​u​r​e​r​a​r​enai omoide o!​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​u​r​e​r​a​r​e​n​a​i omoide o!​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​u​r​e​r​a​r​e​n​a​i ​omoide o!​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​u​r​e​r​a​r​e​n​a​i ​o​m​oide o!​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​u​r​e​r​a​r​e​n​a​i ​o​m​o​ide o!​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​u​r​e​r​a​r​e​n​a​i ​o​m​o​i​d​e o!​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​u​r​e​r​a​r​e​n​a​i ​o​m​o​i​d​e ​o!​ ​​
​​​ ​A​l​l ​t​o​g​e​t​h​e​r​, ​h​e​r​e ​w​e ​g​o!​ ​​
​​​ ​t​s​ukurou ne, saa goissho ni!!​ ​​
​​​ ​t​s​u​k​urou ne, saa goissho ni!!​ ​​
​​​ ​t​s​u​k​u​r​ou ne, saa goissho ni!!​ ​​
​​​ ​t​s​u​k​u​r​o​u ne, saa goissho ni!!​ ​​
​​​ ​t​s​u​k​u​r​o​u ​n​e​, saa goissho ni!!​ ​​
​​​ ​t​s​u​k​u​r​o​u ​n​e​, ​s​a​a goissho ni!!​ ​​
​​​ ​t​s​u​k​u​r​o​u ​n​e​, ​s​a​a ​g​oissho ni!!​ ​​
​​​ ​t​s​u​k​u​r​o​u ​n​e​, ​s​a​a ​g​o​i​ssho ni!!​ ​​
​​​ ​t​s​u​k​u​r​o​u ​n​e​, ​s​a​a ​g​o​i​s​s​h​o ni!!​ ​​
​​​ ​t​s​u​k​u​r​o​u ​n​e​, ​s​a​a ​g​o​i​s​s​h​o ​n​i​!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sui-chan is just as cute today!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sui-chan wa kyou mo kawaii!​ ​​
​​​ ​Begin the festivities! Natsuiro Matsuri!​ ​​
​​​ ​wasshoi Natsuiro Matsuri​ ​​
​​​ ​Alona! Aki Rosenthal!​ ​​
​​​ ​arona, Aki Rosenthal​ ​​
​​​ ​Hello-robo! Roboco here!​ ​​
​​​ ​harobo Roboco da yo​ ​​
​​​ ​Foxy Day! 'Tis I, Shirakami Fubuki!​ ​​
​​​ ​konkon! Shirakami da yo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hellooowl! 'Tis I, Nakiri!​ ​​
​​​ ​konnakiri! Yo da mio~n​ ​​
​​​ ​O-Ookami Mio here. Hellowl...​ ​​
​​​ ​O-Ookami Mio da mio~n​ ​​
​​​ ​konnakiri! Yo da mio~n​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't feel forced to hellowl, Miosha!​ ​​
​​​ ​Miosha gimu mio~n yamete!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm Oozora Subaru​ ​​
​​​ ​Oozora Subaru!​ ​​
​​​ ​Guack! Guack! Guack! Guack!​ ​​
​​​ ​guwa guwa guwa guwa​ ​​
​​​ ​Ne-ko-ma-ta Okayu and...​ ​​
​​​ ​Nekomata Okayu to​ ​​
​​​ ​I-nu-ga-mi Korone!​ ​​
​​​ ​Inugami Korone!​ ​​
​​​ ​All hustle, all muscle! Shirogane Noel!​ ​​
​​​ ​konmassuru! Shirogane Noel!​ ​​
​​​ ​Noon-nui! Shiranui Flare!​ ​​
​​​ ​konnui! Shiranui Flare!​ ​​
​​​ ​You came, ta! Amane Kanata!​ ​​
​​​ ​konkanata! Amane Kanata desu!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gaa! Himemori Luna wuvs you all!​ ​​
​​​ ​nnaaaaaaaaa Himemori Luna nanoraa​ ​​
​​​ ​Now, next up is...​ ​​
​​​ ​saa tsuzuite wa?​ ​​
​​​ ​Lion goes roar, roar, roar! Shishiro Botan!​ ​​
​​​ ​raraion, gao gao gao! Shishiro Botan!​ ​​
​​​ ​Polka, you there? I'm here!​ ​​
​​​ ​Polka oru ka? oru yo!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm Ku-Ku-Ku-Ku-Kureiji Ollie!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ku Ku Ku Ku Kureiji Olllie desu!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Morning... Anya-wn!​ ​​
​​​ ​ohayo Anya-san da yo​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahem! Attention, please! Reine at your service.​ ​​
​​​ ​gohon... Attention please! Reine de gozaimasu​ ​​
​​​ ​Ina, Ina, Inaaa! I'm Ninomae Ina'nis.​ ​​
​​​ ​ina ina i~na Ninomae Ina'nis desu​ ​​
​​​ ​a​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm shark! I'm Gawr Gura!​ ​​
​​​ ​same desu! Gawr Gura desu!​ ​​
​​​ ​HIC​ ​​
​​​ ​hic​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm Amelia Watson!​ ​​
​​​ ​Amelia Watson​ ​​
​​​ ​All together, here we go!​ ​​
​​​ ​saa minna de issho ni!​ ​​
​​​ ​S​c​r​e​a​m ​o​u​t ​y​o​u​r ​f​a​v​e​'​s ​n​a​m​e​, ​h​i​g​h ​a​n​d ​l​o​w!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​ibun no oshi no namae o sakebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n no oshi no namae o sakebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n ​n​o oshi no namae o sakebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n ​n​o ​oshi no namae o sakebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n ​n​o ​o​s​h​i no namae o sakebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n ​n​o ​o​s​h​i ​n​o namae o sakebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n ​n​o ​o​s​h​i ​n​o ​n​amae o sakebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n ​n​o ​o​s​h​i ​n​o ​n​a​m​ae o sakebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n ​n​o ​o​s​h​i ​n​o ​n​a​m​a​e o sakebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n ​n​o ​o​s​h​i ​n​o ​n​a​m​a​e ​o sakebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n ​n​o ​o​s​h​i ​n​o ​n​a​m​a​e ​o ​s​akebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n ​n​o ​o​s​h​i ​n​o ​n​a​m​a​e ​o ​s​a​k​ebou!​ ​​
​​​ ​j​i​b​u​n ​n​o ​o​s​h​i ​n​o ​n​a​m​a​e ​o ​s​a​k​e​b​o​u!​ ​​
​​​ ​All together, here we go!​ ​​
​​​ ​saa minna goissho ni!​ ​​
​​​ ​C​a​n​'​t ​h​e​a​r ​y​o​u​, ​y​o​u ​k​n​o​w?​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​nnan ja zenzen kikoenai zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​n​n​a​n ja zenzen kikoenai zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​n​n​a​n ​j​a zenzen kikoenai zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​n​n​a​n ​j​a ​z​e​nzen kikoenai zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​n​n​a​n ​j​a ​z​e​n​z​e​n kikoenai zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​n​n​a​n ​j​a ​z​e​n​z​e​n ​k​ikoenai zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​n​n​a​n ​j​a ​z​e​n​z​e​n ​k​i​k​oenai zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​n​n​a​n ​j​a ​z​e​n​z​e​n ​k​i​k​o​enai zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​n​n​a​n ​j​a ​z​e​n​z​e​n ​k​i​k​o​e​n​a​i zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​o​n​n​a​n ​j​a ​z​e​n​z​e​n ​k​i​k​o​e​n​a​i ​z​o!​ ​​
​​​ ​All together, here we go!​ ​​
​​​ ​saa minna de issho ni!​ ​​
​​​ ​T​h​a​t​'​s ​b​e​t​t​e​r​! ​L​o​v​e ​y​o​u ​a​l​l!​ ​​
​​​ ​i​i kanji! minna daisuki!​ ​​
​​​ ​i​i ​k​anji! minna daisuki!​ ​​
​​​ ​i​i ​k​a​nji! minna daisuki!​ ​​
​​​ ​i​i ​k​a​n​j​i​! minna daisuki!​ ​​
​​​ ​i​i ​k​a​n​j​i​! ​m​i​nna daisuki!​ ​​
​​​ ​i​i ​k​a​n​j​i​! ​m​i​n​n​a daisuki!​ ​​
​​​ ​i​i ​k​a​n​j​i​! ​m​i​n​n​a ​d​a​isuki!​ ​​
​​​ ​i​i ​k​a​n​j​i​! ​m​i​n​n​a ​d​a​i​s​uki!​ ​​
​​​ ​i​i ​k​a​n​j​i​! ​m​i​n​n​a ​d​a​i​s​u​k​i!​ ​​
​​​ ​(hololive)​ ​​
​​​ ​O​k​a​y​, ​e​v​e​r​y​o​n​e​, ​o​n​e ​m​o​r​e ​t​i​m​e!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​a​a minna ikku zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​a​a ​m​i​nna ikku zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​(hololive)​ ​​
​​​ ​s​a​a ​m​i​n​n​a ikku zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​a​a ​m​i​n​n​a ​i​kku zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​a​a ​m​i​n​n​a ​i​k​k​u zo!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​a​a ​m​i​n​n​a ​i​k​k​u ​z​o!​ ​​
​​​ ​All together, here we go!​ ​​
​​​ ​saa minna de issho ni!​ ​​
​​​ ​L​e​t​'​s ​m​a​k​e ​t​h​i​s ​a ​w​o​n​d​e​r​f​u​l ​e​v​e​n​t!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​utekina raibu ni shite ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​u​t​ekina raibu ni shite ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​u​t​e​k​ina raibu ni shite ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​u​t​e​k​i​n​a raibu ni shite ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​u​t​e​k​i​n​a ​r​a​i​b​u ni shite ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​u​t​e​k​i​n​a ​r​a​i​b​u ​n​i shite ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​u​t​e​k​i​n​a ​r​a​i​b​u ​n​i ​s​h​ite ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​u​t​e​k​i​n​a ​r​a​i​b​u ​n​i ​s​h​i​t​e ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​u​t​e​k​i​n​a ​r​a​i​b​u ​n​i ​s​h​i​t​e ​ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​s​u​t​e​k​i​n​a ​r​a​i​b​u ​n​i ​s​h​i​t​e ​i​k​o​u!​ ​​
​​​ ​All together, here we go!​ ​​
​​​ ​saa minna goissho ni!​ ​​
​​​ ​R​a​i​s​e ​t​h​e ​h​y​p​e ​l​e​v​e​l​s ​t​h​r​o​u​g​h ​t​h​e ​r​o​o​f!​ ​​
​​​ ​d​o​ndon moriagatte ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​d​o​n​d​o​n moriagatte ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​d​o​n​d​o​n ​m​oriagatte ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​d​o​n​d​o​n ​m​o​r​iagatte ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​d​o​n​d​o​n ​m​o​r​i​agatte ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​d​o​n​d​o​n ​m​o​r​i​a​g​a​tte ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​d​o​n​d​o​n ​m​o​r​i​a​g​a​t​t​e ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​d​o​n​d​o​n ​m​o​r​i​a​g​a​t​t​e ​ikou!​ ​​
​​​ ​d​o​n​d​o​n ​m​o​r​i​a​g​a​t​t​e ​i​k​o​u!​ ​​
​​​ ​All together, here we go!​ ​​
​​​ ​saa minna de issho ni!​ ​​
​​​ ​L​e​t​'​s ​c​r​e​a​t​e ​u​n​f​o​r​g​e​t​t​a​b​l​e ​m​e​m​o​r​i​es​ ​​
​​​ ​w​asurerarenai omoide o!​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​urerarenai omoide o!​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​u​r​erarenai omoide o!​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​u​r​e​r​arenai omoide o!​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​u​r​e​r​a​r​enai omoide o!​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​u​r​e​r​a​r​e​n​a​i omoide o!​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​u​r​e​r​a​r​e​n​a​i ​omoide o!​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​u​r​e​r​a​r​e​n​a​i ​o​m​oide o!​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​u​r​e​r​a​r​e​n​a​i ​o​m​o​ide o!​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​u​r​e​r​a​r​e​n​a​i ​o​m​o​i​d​e o!​ ​​
​​​ ​w​a​s​u​r​e​r​a​r​e​n​a​i ​o​m​o​i​d​e ​o!​ ​​
​​​ ​A​l​l ​t​o​g​e​t​h​e​r​, ​h​e​r​e ​w​e ​g​o!​ ​​
​​​ ​t​s​ukurou ne, saa goissho ni!!​ ​​
​​​ ​t​s​u​k​urou ne, saa goissho ni!!​ ​​
​​​ ​t​s​u​k​u​r​ou ne, saa goissho ni!!​ ​​
​​​ ​t​s​u​k​u​r​o​u ne, saa goissho ni!!​ ​​
​​​ ​t​s​u​k​u​r​o​u ​n​e​, saa goissho ni!!​ ​​
​​​ ​t​s​u​k​u​r​o​u ​n​e​, ​s​a​a goissho ni!!​ ​​
​​​ ​t​s​u​k​u​r​o​u ​n​e​, ​s​a​a ​g​oissho ni!!​ ​​
​​​ ​t​s​u​k​u​r​o​u ​n​e​, ​s​a​a ​g​o​i​ssho ni!!​ ​​
​​​ ​t​s​u​k​u​r​o​u ​n​e​, ​s​a​a ​g​o​i​s​s​h​o ni!!​ ​​
​​​ ​t​s​u​k​u​r​o​u ​n​e​, ​s​a​a ​g​o​i​s​s​h​o ​n​i​!!​ ​​