e
[Music]
for
hello who are you people who are you
people who are all of you
people what do we what are you who Am I
who are
you I'm
Blue the vo is in my head what about the
voices in my head
[Music]
I have the strange urge to say something
that rhymes
with bble but I can't quite recall I
cannot quite recall what it is who is
that who is that who is that I don't
know who that is hi
everybody
hello what is this I don't
know who was that
I I I feel like I
no you're so
small when did you get so small I had no
idea oh my oh my how are you who are you
people I'm my name's
gura I I'm I am
Goomba welcome to my white
wall no don't step on us whatever you do
don't don't step on
us gur I'm gur who are you hi Goomba
[Music]
Goomba I have a tail hello how are you I
am
good enter
Nana Nana has entered the
room you want to see where we are I
thought you were blue I am blue unless
I'm color blind I don't know wait what
is color blindness what is this what is
that
[Music]
who
oo welcome to my chamber my chamber of
[Music]
Amnesia and
enigmatic
recollection entic recollection this is
the rubber room this is where they this
is where they' I guess we've all all
these other people are here in here with
me I guess this is where we go when you
don't remember anything not that I had
any memory of remember
anything look they're trying to break
out I wonder if it'll
[Music]
work look at all these
faces I want to punch this this one I
don't know why I just have such an urge
an urge deep within
[Music]
me you think they also want to punch
me wait everybody is talking now wait
pause wait
pause are you
guys anyone see the lights I wonder if
you can hurt people hey see hey you can
I do you know
[Music]
me no I don't think so wait hold on you
smell kind
of wait hold on my brain feels
foggy I can't remember anything dude do
you live in a pineapple under the sea
[Music]
wait wait don't look don't look don't
look wait hold on uh uh uh
uh don't worry guys the Men in Black uh
uh brain wipe brain wipe pause pause
Wait Don't Look Away wait hold on uh uh
you your memory has been your memory has
been wife you don't remember anything
I'll see you and uh please hold please
wait
[Music]
little jump scare it was
he don't fight
me okay okay she's
violent what
happened I was remembering things I
forgot it
again anyway
recollection yes I've never seen this
before have you I've not seen this
before in my life what could it mean I
don't told
no the last 24 hours as well I don't
remember eventually everything come
surely I can't stay as a blank stay
forever do you think I sound crazy
talking to myself I'm not talking to
myself I'm talk all of
you
isai could it perhaps be
isai maybe this is just the inside of my
head inside of my
head is it
[Music]
inside hello hello I swear you were not
so loud in my
head did you hit your now I think so did
you recover some of your memor I don't
remember it's kind of loud in
here
really I cannot perceive would you like
to join my corner I like the corner you
you like to join my corner I was just
sitting here thinking about how I don't
I don't remember where I came from but
that gives me a sense of peace I was
thinking of going into the
woods to create a new life a new life in
the woods I don't think there's
any's no you think what's
that I think it might be for the better
we're do you think he going to startop
eating
people prob the person that of it I'm
trying to get you in my right ear you
somewhere you don't want she's going to
leave my
corner I
see why would you get that
impression I'm supposed to be a cute
girl
right fig I don't
know funny messages in my brain fun
messages
don't
[Music]
know maybe the walls will slowly start
closing in on us and we'll be forced to
make a very fast
decision oh those letters she she's
already lost
it I wonder what color will all bleed
when we're all swished against the
insides of these
walls enigmatic
recollection you know how to
[Applause]
read something tells me it's good to be
able to know how to e
this hry
[Music]
uh
hello Echoes of Forgotten memories wait
Echoes of Forgotten
memories press the sneak key
who am
I the world I live
in and more than
anything the people I hold most dear
faced with
Oblivion I
feel
empty
relieved perhaps
distra I don't know
so much I don't know much I don't know
and yet and
yet I'm at the sneak
point that bright know it calls to me so
much I don't know I did I just say that
who just say that and yet the bright
light calls who's saying that in my head
hello
here hello hi we have to go towards the
light is it this the light light hello
light what is your
name I don't know it's
G oh my name is Jonathan spelled with a
G cool Jonathan Jonathan I just
saw where shall we head are we the
fastest readers I think so
I read
fast there people
here think Ice Ice Baby I hope there's
food over
[Music]
here someone's
hungry is this a
hole oh my God don't turn around it's
not a hole
[Music]
make we're dead
SI liestyle
Castle you there oh jeez I don't know if
anybody else can hear me in my head you
there what are you doing
here what am I doing
here you have the look of The Outsiders
about
[Music]
you wait could he
be quick send word to his majesty his
majesty
Heroes have arrived at the
sanctuary guards oh wait these are the
guards aren't they oh they are H right
[Music]
away Royal arience
chainers welcome Heroes this is the
kingdom of Lial and I am its king
King the guards who brought you here
have informed me that you remember not
but your own names what did I say my
name was again he's bald that's my
name he kind of cute oh you kind of cute
a side effect of travel between worlds
no doubt my name is
[Music]
Goa this must all come as a Sur tries to
you but hearken well it was I who
summoned you
here you see an unprecedented Calamity
now threatens our
world it has sewn the Earth with
corruption and driven us from our
homes this blighted land now gives rise
to creatures of Shadow known as
stains this Kingdom of liestal and its
surroundings are now the only safe place
left to us Litin
but should the Calamity be left
unchecked is only a matter of time
before it consumes the entire
world he walks he's so
tiny faced with this Prospect I scoured
the ancient text for a way to combat the
Calamity and therein I found one I know
he's not talking about me maybe he's
talking about
you say more little guy come
on the rich ritual of hero
summoning you who hail from another
world have been summoned here by me to
become the saviors of
Li am I saying his town R
lione huh only you have the power to
save our world you think you can hear me
when I'm talking to you
guys and so I will ask you I ask you I
you you who's that
you your
majesty what is
it a great host of stains has broken
through our defensive line no we are
rushing to a mounted defense but the
situation is dire Your Majesty we must
get you somewhere
safe veridus hi hello little green man
who are these
strangers somebody said my name was
daddy you can call me daddy little green
man I have a faint memory of another
little green man I meant
before little green
[Music]
man let's say you Heroes will you accept
this
Destiny there is great power within you
will you use it to save us to save this
world I don't think I have a choice me
to be to be no I'm so sorry I'm so
sorry I'm so sorry didn't me to there's
a little red man
[Applause]
too and another little little
guy oh my
goodness oh my
goodness oh my goodness
[Music]
yellow
hey he looks so
you
[Music]
like he still his television screen on
his
eyeball
he got a big head though
[Music]
a big book
too I don't
know I totally don't know
stop pleas
wow this must
be Li lielle where are
we am I saying that right forget
it is it called the phonetic
pronunciation lius weren't you listening
to them they were talking kind of
important all I heard was the stuff in
my head
oh yeah yeah so L the stains are
coming the stains the St you wen't
you was stains that are clothes or
something hello they just gave us a big
the stains are coming they can't fight
it off that's why we're
here I but all I heard was you're a hero
a selective her a big banquet like you
know to welcome the Heroes all we got is
this bread you can have some of mine
maybe
okay
your I can't give it I regret that you
must face such danger so soon after your
arrival as his majesty no doubt explain
to you our kingdom faces an
unprecedented
crisis oh dear a Calamity befs the land
leaving it the rift of life and infested
with the mon known as
stains not even the
mighty Castle can be safe anymore
sty Li style mayhaps it is too late to
save this world from destruction
nevertheless is it lifestyle or
Li they brought us here to kill us to
defend our King and our countrymen to
the very end Brave heres From Another
World let us go forth with Valor and
fight together together we fight
[Music]
fight fight fight for the King fight for
the
[Music]
king take them
down
the what do
it the laser beam
any damage not taking any damage maybe
we have to kill the uh little mini
guys oh what's that we
the hurt it hurt it hurt
it hurt this one hurt this one hurt this
one I feel remove the minis
[Music]
oh my gosh I'm out of there
okay oh I'm going to die oh dear oh dear
oh dear here please got Shields I've got
a big head and a big heart and I'm a
shark I'm help
me I'm helping thank you thank you you
saved my life anything for you little
shark girl thank you I will remember
this ow why do
you ow you saved my life again thank you
so much it hurts oh God prove that I'm
the best most helpful any there can we
oh there's another
onep oh this this way stranger oh
[Music]
hold your weapon and left click shout
Revelation which is the left is that my
Revelation
Revelation revelation
Revelation am am I am I pronouncing this
word
right
Revelation
um um revelation
[Music]
I I think it
worked oh God I appear to have blacked
out and I don't remember anything
hello hello is
there is anyone is anyone there are you
guys still there do you hear
[Music]
me you're now the voices in my head with
me you'll stay with me
right I think our Revelation spell was
too
[Music]
strong what do you think bad ending what
do you
mean what a
revelation the bad ending the void it
calls to
us oh
dear it seems as if though you may be
stuck in the dark
for a bit of time I guess we can use
this moment to
um to discuss but now now we
wait it's j it can't be J it just
started CL who's
gar wait I remember gar Gar is a distant
memory when I think about gar I see
red I see red and I think about blood
and anger
vitol did you ever meet gar is that how
you know about gar you have met
gar you've met
gar I see
you even have her
photograph I had no idea you knew so
much
about me how did you know all
that L is your o she gar is kind of
stinky she doesn't look very friendly
you read the
wiki there's blood in the
water I hope we don't meet gar Gar
sounds scary I hope we
don't it certainly wouldn't be good to
bump into gar or would
[Music]
it am I gar was dumb well I certainly I
certainly I certainly would be smarter
than gar don't you think
[Music]
bar is like a reflection a reflection to
me
hurah well if gar is seen is bad and and
evil and smelly and and
mean then maybe I'm the opposite of that
I'm seen as good and pure and sweet and
kind she lives Within Me
[Music]
maybe we all have our guardar inside of
us do you have a gar inside of you is
gar inside of you I think gar is inside
of you right
now I think she's just trying to get
out you hate
guard h
[Music]
Perhaps Perhaps don't let her control
you I don't think you have to worry
about her her getting in control is she
in the room with
us she might be but I don't think she'll
make it out I don't think we'll see her
this this time I I don't think
so it is it you see nothing I also see
nothing
[Music]
we're going to be seeing we're going to
be seeing nothing for a while I do
[Music]
apologize I think we saved the
day we can turn this off now I mean we
can stop speaking like that
um we can have some nice music some
chill
music um H what do we think of the
stains the stains what an what an
interesting name the the the the the
city the city
of
leyle home of the liis LI stands liba
stands the stains are hard to remove uh
yes suddenly their name makes a whole
lot of sense what are they staining
apparently the town the city of
lib lib
Belle the Le the lesbian no I don't
think it's that one Li
live
Libs the libs
the music inside of your head is too
loud
here I will
fix I will adjust until it's comfortable
for you do not worry do not fret my mind
Warriors The Warriors inside my my
[Music]
brain h
H you can see my eyes reading everything
I
am I'm quite good at it actually if I
can have a moment to to brag about it I
am pretty good at it and I proud myself
in being able to to see what all of you
are saying I've gotten real good at it
real quick haven't
I what else are you guys talking about
let's
see hi you may not remember remember me
but I'm actually your husband I've never
stopped searching for you since the day
you were taken from
me star Cruiser is that
true is that true does anybody else have
it's not true you wrote that Wiggy you
wrote that no no me Android wrote that I
think sounds like many of you wrote
that are you perhaps are you all a
husband wait R here is my
wife are we technically does that make
us one big
family there's so many of
us
wow wait think of the think of the
Banquets we could have all together all
all all the many of us
all the husbands and wives
together I have the urge to ask though
can I be the
dog forgive me forgive me for not
wanting to be the husband or the wife I
would prefer to be the
dog
woof woof
woof you can be my step brother that's
okay but I'm also the dog so you will be
the step brother
dog everybody else can also be the dog
dog if you want but I really just want
to be the the
[Music]
dog we might we wait I I feel I feel a a
summoning we
perhaps perhaps we are being summoned
back to the town of Le
leis
liand liestyle
can you be my mom your mom will be a
dog
wolf are we perhaps being
summoned I do think we are
[Music]
fall off this journey and you're going
to go to your
reti I
will ha
you we have
returned the darkness haunts my brain no
longer free from the darkness and back
into this large white room oh truly
whoever torture there's a shark where
sword
oh I'm so hungry there's a please please
she's going to eat
us a gluten she EA she's eating I don't
think she
eats I like red you like okay I
love I would keep my eyes on the yellow
one the yellow one seems to have quite
the appetite yes you hey she
you
seem yes really
hungry we could be the bread
Club I only have can we touch
TI red our swords
tip
oh what' you do
you I didn't steal
anything Thief it was the it was the
it was the
[Music]
God let me out of this my
food bread I wanted bread the all
powerful what are you yapping about they
all they won't let us out of these walls
man are we working together to escape
because of Forgotten
[Music]
memories who am I the world I live
in who am I and more than
anything the people I hold most
dear faced with Oblivion I feel
empty
empty empty
relieved
relieved perhaps distroy
distroy destroy I do not know for what
for what is this curse that has befallen
upon me so much I do not know and yet
much I don't know and yet and yet that
bright light it calls to
meall not within the walls I refuse to
return to the
walls I feel something
reel oh my goodness I just skin walked
in someone
reel reel
hello hello hello hello hello hello you
stink oh my goodness I'm so sorry excuse
me what did you say to me no I'm so
sorry no no sorry sorry so sorry what
did you say repeat I didn't hear you
what no no no I no no no I I was just
like I was just zoning out for a second
I'm so sorry I'm just panicking it makes
me want to go to the what was your name
what was your name sorry I am G here G
yes what kind of name is go yeah that's
a pretty bad name just kidding kidding
I'm kidding go nice to meet you nice
friend what is your name I'm m m my
memor is a bit
fuzzy wait it says fuzzy above your head
perhaps how can you read that I thought
I was the only
one I too can
read it says dumbass above your head
whoa excuse me what does it say above my
head
it
says you
are Dumber times
two that's a lot of words think can read
to I know more than you could ever
learn you'll have to teach me if we're
stuck in this cursed land for much
longer I know but I think we may have to
go towards the light first which one
there seems to be many that the the
light over there with Five Pillars of
light in the middle I see your sense of
direction is perhaps intact from your
travels yes I am meant to be Queen in
this Kingdom wow I know
oh the voices the voices guys
you there what are you doing here I've
been here
before you have the look of an outsider
about
you what could it
be quick send word to his
majesty the heroes have arrived at the
sanctuary right
away Vu I think we hit our head pretty
hard
welcome Heroes this is the kingdom of
and I am its king the guards who brought
you here have informed me that you
remember not but your own names h a side
effect of travel between worlds no doubt
no
doubt this must comes to surprise you
but hearken well was I who summoned you
here you see an unprecedented Calamity
now threatens our world it is so the
Earth with corruption and drives us from
our homes this blighted land now gives
you rise to creatures of Shadow known as
stains Skipper
Skipper the kingdom
of here I'll T ldr help help help help
us we're so tiny our arms cannot
possibly reach the swords of your
magnitude oh oh tall one please please
kill the stains before they eat all of
our
people how am I going to help the only
way I'm going to help you is if if you
tell me if your mustache is real is your
mustache real little
guy I'm so big I could just yank get
right off him
huh tall one the ritual hero of
summoning that's me I
[Music]
think you have the power to save our
world have spam Shi guys I am and so I
ask
you what is it a great host of stains
the stains are coming the stains are
coming no yes no yes your majesty what
fix it
no I'll do it make way little
men for
I I what was my name again what did she
say we'll save this
worldd outside of the castle Yeah yeah I
don't know how she knew that I needed
that endless loop I
it right this time thanks that's that's
a nice technique you got there we need
your help you I
thought a
hero special we looking for Heroes okay
okay who says that did you say
that me thank you my dad gave it to
me me of a different mushroom of a
different world you don't
say like the mushroom huh best you sound
just Heroes you must defeat the stains
or my family will be gone
why too powerful but fate hase save
us why you got a zipper in your back he
he was so romantic and
said don't touch
me I
report
is your what great great great grandad
he's my friend what are you going to do
send me to The Gallows if I I have a
tattle on
you tell the captain captain I'm call
Captain can't hear you from all the way
down here outside castle wall what is
that Ser me correctly you doing yes
we've been here
before what is this what you the whale
yeah you're some type of sea animal
aren't you like
fungus she looks pretty fungal to me
smells like it too I was about to say it
smells pretty Fung I think
there's walking about there's an
imposter of
foot these stains coming in hero hero we
need your help hero oh no the voice the
dialogue is reset
we will you help us
triing that please save my
family hero help us
hero
are you look awfully out of water to be
honest you're not the first person to
say that do you have any idea why tune
my ears to your voice oh wait I need to
listen Heroes I think you hit your head
pretty
hard ready to take the
enemy defeat the St
Heroes well perhaps she has a gar inside
of her as well oh anyway Time to Kill
the Boss don't know what that was about
maybe
find me it's time
I got
heal just put a bandaid on that boo
boo silly Archer silly Archer your turn
radius is that of a very large Jeep of a
very large forward
vehicle I I did not do it
Miss time
not over here and
help got a stubby little
tail the boss the big has a beam for the
he's coming
[Music]
down
go thank you don't hurt
are we
[Music]
winning look it's our
Min he's like a piggy
Bang watch the
wo last time going
get I'm
scared ow oh God oh God oh God that hurt
oh no
yeah get him the fuzzy one or did we
meet the fluffy one I don't remember oh
boy look at
[Music]
the okay we start
this revelation
wo the stain host has
been what does that
say
murdered routed routed
we thought bravely kind Heroes I pray
that you are not
injured the mighty armored one must be
their leader the stained King
fascinating Most Fascinating well I see
why they call you oh wait are you
British I'm sorry I didn't mean to say
that like that H well well I see why
they call you AO okay that's probably
for the better don't worry
[Music]
I like the one with the funny hat oh
wait a
minute we sustained minimal damage
thanks to your Valor our kingdom is in
your debt thank you I like the one with
the biggest hat kind of looks like a
shrimp on his head I must hasten to
inform His Majesty of our Victory will
you accompany me me of course we'll be
rewarded with a
[Music]
banquet Royal audience chamber
I heard the news though we called upon
you suddenly you Rose to the occasion
you have my deepest gratitude what
interest me most however is the strange
power you manifested during the battle
with which you were able to defeat the
stains that power May well be the key to
saving our world from Annihilation the
Trident according to the heroes the
powers came from like a memory okay when
they spoke the word
revelation uhhuh but once they used it
to shout huh once they used it to Route
the stain host to seems to pour our
power uh-oh Blain
Hood well that's brilliant is it so what
we supposed to do the next time of
stain's attack revelation we must
uncover the secrets of this phenomenon
if we are able to Prevail against the
Calamity many questions remain but one
thing is certain the kingdom of sty
still stands today thanks to you here
here so Heroes I ask of you once more
will you lend us your strength to save
lestelle from
ruin yes you'll join me right
guys
everyone right marvelous on behalf of
all Li STS I thank
you
nice when's the
banquet we are blessed to have your Aid
kind Heroes
allow me to introduce the four Great
guilds which are responsible for
ensuring the Kingdom's peace and
prosperity The Haven for the Curious
where knowledge and creativity are
valued above all the Scarlet
wand the home for Glory Seekers with
ambition and vision where closest allies
become fiercest Rivals the Amber
coin the sanctum of healing where the
spirit of empathy and devotion thrives
the Cerulean
cup the speaking of the righteous and
loyal where great threats are faced with
even greater courage the Jade
sword one of these guilds will become
your home during your time
here
ah I wonder who will be sorted with
Beyond this door lies the room of Truth
therein the will of the ancestor shall
decide your
guild oh boy okay we're going to get
sorted
[Music]
I'm nervous I'm nervous I'm
nervous
[Music]
okay okay drum roll everybody drum roll
drum roll drum
[Music]
roll a fear not hold on we have
dialogue introspection is a vital step
on the road to en mment excelsia as I
always say even higher I like that
guy time to roll the dice ape and seeing
some of you lot down at the Amber coin
Guild Hall let us save this world
[Music]
together the room of truth's aw a go
forth with
Valor oh God we're going oh God oh God
oh God I can't look I have to look I
can't look
the room of Truth step on the platform
and receive the will of the
ancestor
oo
[Music]
okay and so begin a journey to find who
I
[Music]
am Scarlet
w we got our
cloak Dawn the
[Music]
cloak arm with an wavering will seek to
defend the soul of
Jade I my oh my God the timing I think
that's all he has to
say oh no he's got more thank you for
joining the battle to save liall so soon
after your summoning at that you will
henceforth be working with us to mount
resistance Stones against the stains and
save this world hey oh what's up oh my
gosh are you also Scarlet one people
also where'd you get that feather cool
feather
man I like your Trident that's sick
thank you I like
your I like your wooden sword yeah it's
not a no no no I have something cool too
I have this this cool thing I'm cool too
I promise I'm cool hey I have a clo
[Music]
welcome what's you
have I have a cloak I have a red a cloak
I got a cloak a cloak oh I've got one
more thing hold on guys that oh you got
a giant like uh Christmas col you guys
check this out I got a f there I'm going
to tickle everyone's death
no oh that was sh speak to your guild
Guild Guild Master yeah this guy right
here rubius
rubius Ru good red like a ruby welcome
to the humble Guild Hall of the Scarlet
wand I Am The Guild Master rubius it's
the funny
HS
like we're going to crush everyone else
thank you for joining the batt to save
Li style so soon after your summon at
then you will henceforth be working with
us to mount a resistance against the SS
and save this world yeah you got to
right click him beh you to learn more
about this kingdom in which we live as
well as how to accept and perform Quest
go into town and you should find a quest
board don't to go there and speak with
the quest Master Prime opportunity to
explore it would beho you
okay yay thank you so much okay we got
to go to the quest board the quest board
we have to be in a party
fine oh maybe we should make a party
okay how do we do
that um I think oh wait are you two able
to join a party I can join let's try
let's try it can you attempt to invite
us to your
party yeah can it be hold on I need to
look at the tutorial hello everyone
everyone here with me right
now can I ask if you can hear everyone
or if anybody is too loud or so and then
just We join a party okay I'm going to
invite you guys I can't press actually
okay well we can always be on party how
do you accept yeah I guess I guess I
could
solo let me let me solo it you know yeah
how do I accept kind of sad but how do I
accept the party T accept
accept it's not like that accept uh let
me see uh except you click on you click
on except oh hey I'm in the party wait
I'm in the party wait wait wait wait
okay wa I'm going to keep Som I didn't I
I didn't do anything I just pressed
random buttons please please invite me
again uhoh I feel good about this Guild
something about
it does anyone know where the social
menu is wait why is people in the party
because she's been we people and I were
in the party from the beginning but how
do I like it says click um on the else
do we have when the
person
R to
kick
oh there go
Shori okay it's fine we don't have to be
in the party in the beginning I'm sure
it's fine okay yeah I guess see them at
the quest Bo follow you guys how about
that is myse tired do you guys want to
okay
oh yeah where's the quest
board actually I don't know we have a
map but is it this way I don't know what
did he say did anybody remember what he
said he said good job go to the quest
board speak to the quest
Master are are we
just speak to the guy I don't know where
we're going um we're trying to find a
quest
[Music]
board somebody completed it let's
go go to the quest oh wait
no oh speak to Quest Master how did you
speak to him uh how did you speak to the
right click oh okay I
think go to the and speak to the quest
master
[Music]
into
town our new
leader I think town
[Music]
is I I got to be honest with you I have
no idea where town
is it has to be this way doesn't
it I'm breaking away from the party I
just got I got to figure this out out I
got to figure this out I got to figure
this
out
town this map kind of sucks
[Music]
man
um oh there you are is that town this
way yeah yeah yeah we're we're all
heading this way looks like the The
Guild Masters or the quest Master's here
so I I'm leading the way but we we lost
you two so we're heading I see you my
bad I took off in the other no no
problem I I would have done the same
thing yeah where is
Shori she took off in towards the middle
Yi where are you did she uh well do you
think she made it to
the the quest area let's just go without
her she'll catch up okay okay okay this
[Music]
[Laughter]
way return to
us what's
up is it the front of this giant thing
KN in no it's it's going to be further
in the corner it looks like it's kind of
far away
I I'm looking at it on my map it's
marked oh it is I see it is marked yeah
you do have a talent oh I see oh God
that's a tree oh man that means we got
to walk the furthest to get to the
dining hall goodness I need to have
something it's pretty though I
guess okay somewhere in this house maybe
no no no no no sorry
[Music]
around he said here's the key good luck
this is the long way I'm so sorry I am
not being a very good Navigator I trust
you completely I'm so sorry the fate of
this Guild is in your hands to see the
text on the
map West Master Okay somewhere back
here oh my God it's that red Lady
Elizabeth hello
yes that is
I oh everybody else okay Quest board
Acquired and we found sh too oh
good don't know where is the side quest
we need to go to go to the to the master
matal I'm The
Apprentice let's the quest and speak to
the I understand
[Music]
Duty away the perfect job best
the side quest and speak to the quest
Master have the
same I am I
am now I
am
thees the oranges thees opposite we
going on a quest do you care to join us
not join you we are guil think we're on
the same Quest materials needed at
the materials needed at the
SM materials needed at the
smiy materials need I think somebody
needs
materials do
know the only one available on the board
yeah materals needed at the smiy I'm The
Apprentice at the Smithy and my master
says we're running low on raw materials
if you can help us gather some please
stop by the Smith I shall invite you to
the
party
everyone I think is there a way we can
fix our group chat because it would be a
lot less chaotic if we were the only
ones we could hear oh yeah there's
groups there's groups I don't I think
apart from just turning everyone else
down probably
not radio only party leaders
can is okay okay okay okay okay stand
still do not move I shall free you I
will K you from my
part there we go okay how do I get off
the horse where's the GU master and now
is it
[Music]
shift the
master click on it party is I to child
gu master was all the way at the
beginning I spent time with my horse
please show me the GU
Master thank you you're so can you help
Nissa accept the quest the AC the quest
I have to talk to the GU Master we wait
wait wait wait wait this is a I just I
my head I hit my head real hard this is
a lot to take in all at once holy
moly GA do you know how to can you tell
Nissa how to accept the invitation I
don't know since I you
invited it happened automatically for me
I don't I don't know I'm so sorry I
missed what you have said the quest
Master maybe F know fa cuz fa maybe oh
yeah I don't know where F went
though I think maybe she's helping Shi
with her uh to get talk to the quest
master ah I see I see I see to the guy
in the beginning so I guess we just
wait wait wait wait wait
wait and then so open your chat and then
you click accept yeah we got to go this
way I think we're going to use our horse
to
get nice idea let us ride oh mine
changed
[Music]
color Perhaps Perhaps
not I think maybe she's muted n are you
muted
hello sorry I didn't mean to mute I
can't open my chat oh okay but earlier
Shi said she the same problem right yeah
me and Shi have the same problem but she
got in somehow so she probably got in so
let's just wait until she comes back and
then you'll know how to be and right now
no one's close to us so it's not that
big of an issue anyway after you can be
in
a yeah she she said she just clicked
random buttons I tried to spam all of
mine but nothing happened
yeah if you do the right click on the
board it should come up if not you
haven't finished talking to the quest it
opens up Social menu for
trade
um so I'm not particular uh we know we
know how to do it I'm in the party guys
no worries we know how to do it it's
just
um uh we had we have a bit of
or error we've had a bit of an error
with one of the
uh members have
errors but no I mean it's just it's okay
for me we're
missing shor's in the game we're just
missing Nissa in the game we don't know
we don't know if she can if she can
join chat bug yes oh successfully joined
party okay okay okay we're in we're so
in we're so in did let's go do the quest
yeah
y where's the quest I'm so sorry good
question we need they need materials at
the Smithy so I think we need to go find
the Smithy maybe it's marked on the map
let me pull up my map again and see if
it says anything how do you zoom out on
this thing uh I don't think we can which
is
not particularly
helpful is it the green oh it is wait
wait bottom Green Oh you see it I see it
okay Cecilia onward let's go this way
following the
G this yes this
way yes thank
goodness trust
[Music]
me I think think I do
believe I hear
voices I I'll wait outside this place is
getting busy hello excuse
me pickaxe
oh
okay I do not have the required
materials weara from up yonder hasth
Fallen to their death hath Fallen
shall I wait sticks okay one two Scarlet
wand
member where is 345 three okay head
count 1 two
three we are missing four five 10 10 o00
I think that's very easy my
friend if you would be sent here we to
the completed
exactly completed it is just that easy
my
[Music]
friends
easy I have an
axe I think we need to you did it from
now on when you find complete the quest
speak to the
m did he say what we
needed collect 10 cobblestones 10
oh my
[Music]
is this is pretty chaotic I think maybe
we need wood wood 10 Oak cuz cuz yeah
let's go find want to craft some
stuff is anywhere good can we no is this
is this a crime to chop down a tree in
the middle of the town I'm sure they
wouldn't notice if we take a little bit
oh oh like one we sneak one
out uh what about that big tree do you
see that there the Town Center
Tree the CH tree the town tree it's been
here since the conception of Li Li sty
don't worry they won't notice it's so
big they won't notice if we take a
little bit of it yeah just we just need
10 town the tree that has fed this
Village for centuries ah it is now a
quest item is this
Oak where are we supposed to get
wood what about
here did you randomly get 100 coins by
clicking on him again and again no no I
have 100 coins and I think it said that
I successfully completed the quest but I
didn't do anything you hacking me put in
the cheat code
attacking I must be where do you guys
where do you guys see the quest sorry I
don't I I just still see the materials
needed at the Smithy but it doesn't tell
me what's needed because for me it just
says complete the site
Quest it doesn't say like oh a
child oh God oh God I didn't accept
reest yes I
did maybe maybe the map will tell us
again
uh
no that's
great you guys mind if
we did did you not can we go back to the
quest Master do you still need to pick
up the quest yeah but I think if it's
just wood then it doesn't matter if I
get the wood I can I can go yeah yeah I
mean we can't get wood from here anyway
so dude where are you not don't invite
her again we've been through we're right
here where are
you we're right here I'm I got fun on
the phone I don't know where fun and shy
are what that's true where are you
guys yeah where are they we got lost
we're at the blacksmith oh okay we're
coming back to you so stay there
okay
oh
okay oh they need material wait do we
bring
material wait The Apprentice we to the
despite proximity I don't think so yeah
10: how do I hang up with the phone
phone phone okay I don't know wait
you're still on the phone with me I'm
calling r r r r no I didn't even know
how you call me phone wait who are you
calling I don't I guess you wait I'm not
you I was talking I I got to figure how
to hang on the
phone okay bye
you we'll just go back to the quest m
Master okay they're at the blacksmith
just like oh they're at the blacksmith
okay we're closer to the quest master so
we'll we'll go there first so she can
pick up the quest properly and then
we'll head back to the blacksmith sounds
good okay so CC did you talk here and
then accept the quest on the board she's
gone oh
[Music]
oh there she is
hello yay
I'm just going to the quest real quick
to the quest you just need to you need
to talk to him and then you need to
click here to accept the quest on the
actual
born complete the side quest and speak
to the quest Master thece at the SM and
my master says rning raw materials help
us GA some place stop by the SMI
okay click to
order why can't I speak to this Quest
master I thought this was food I got
excited did you finish the
quest I did oh I have now finished
farewell ma where do you where do you
wait farewell maidens oh yes yes would
you like to um where did you get wood
from
[Music]
the that
way call
someone toward The City Gate there will
be an orb that will lead you outwards oh
my goodness we prank do we have to go go
to the Smithy first go out I I think we
can get the wood first and then go to
the
Smithy can we just accept all the quest
this way is out the wood and then the
Smithy can we can we yeah can we just
accept all of them at once I'm going to
see AC I I'm going to go get some wood
do you want to come with or do you want
to go to the Smithy I was going to go to
the Smithy to meet up with f
let's go get him cuz I just want to make
sure cuz I don't the others is this the
way call the others this is the way this
is the way this is this is also the way
I
think you correct it's this building
right here oh I see see wa somebody else
just did the
quest s all right
green did it work did not work you bring
over 10 oak logs there's a bunch of
trees not far outside the town that you
can chop outside of the town wait
outside okay let's try going
outside outside of town okay I think
maybe here this way this way to the
right do we got everybody we are
three ah well let's go the giant gate
maybe guys yeah I think the giant gate
might be where we need to go
three where are the other two I'm going
to make a phone call you know what this
feels like this feels like we're at an
amusement park and you lost two people
of your group we need the matching
shirts I'm making a phone call oh gosh
where hello hello hello where are you
guys now we're we're outside the town
chopping down oak trees for the this or
okay we we'll meet you there we're going
outside now too okay okay okay okay okay
okay good talk okay oh by the way good
all right go to another location
yes hey we're
here now we can get
wood and Scarlet
w we found you Scarlet W finally we've
been
reunited reunited at last feel it
does wow oh 20 coins wait far money in
this
game I'm tickle Master here your get
tickled yourse get I would like to farm
I would like to farm
coins right how many coins do you have
um
128 I got 171 W better do some catching
up you got some heavy pockets
right
ow this one is like a cute
bunny this one has horns and they kind
of
hurt why am I not using this to slay
about 10 of them
11 how much do you guys think we need we
need
10 15 that's like 25 % more three better
get to chopping do we each need 10
I think so I don't know my goodness oh
my goodness yeah you only need 10 you
only need 10 but each person though or
we're all
together uh I was I think we should all
get
10 oh okay we sharing I have some Spar
if you
want mayhaps my humble
opinion summoning egg mayhaps wh oh we
should probably run I think they're
after us uh they come out at night
revelation
reation doesn't
work wo quick let us return return oh
crap Scarlet
one red
team red team back inside everybody have
all their logs get inside the castle
Gates it's not safe out here come on
does everyone have logs we have
logs okay let's de everyone we do
Revelation we're
good how do we return actually make
haste
team how does when sumon the
gate she get
stuck
okay yes 1
2 again
yay blacksmith yes we can have horses if
we use a summoning seed egg that is
true you have a pretty horse pretty
brown horse must do it
myself the very thing she does not want
to okay okay shall we
go my
money thank you so much my M over there
if you bring the ra
material I made oh Cobblestone there
Cobblestone too many people are speaking
to him at once
ohow is this all of our money am I am I
using all of
our I do not think so my money has not
money I have your wood forgot how to
talk how much money do you have three a
wooden pickaxe oh try left sh richer
than you three ha I
mean M
completed collect 10 oak logs speak to
the black Smith Apprentice create a
wooden pickaxe at the
smiy I
see Plank okay okay what did he say
pickaxe he said wooden pickaxe oh wait
we need stuff for
it he needs sticks oh he needs sticks
Oak planks scks 20
coins the quest master and you have to
pay
YY May how you make
pickax it is not letting me got to make
the silly
items
um Timber how do you make a plank theith
it wait is this one free
[Music]
I have also created the wooden pickaxe I
have also created it I have not created
the wooden pickaxe how do you do
this um how do you have all the needed
materials is it all this wait is it like
regular yeah just regular so you do the
oak lock and then you turn it into Oak
planks and then you make sticks I think
you need like four or four each talk to
the guy with the
glasses yeah wait
okay I I think I think I understand let
me let me try let me try yeah yeah right
he going to ask us for a ah thank you I
did it thank you thank thank you and I
think now I I guess we just have to go
outside and get cobblestone instead ah
okay find the others moving
on great you did
it bring us 10 Cobblestone next yeah
okay okay Cobblestone that's okay we got
to get Cobblestone to finish the quest
follow me follow me I I don't I the
Scarlet wand where is The Scarlet
wand oh let us call
them call watch out watch out watch out
watch out watch out you hit me watch out
wait step out of the way watch out
leg watch out it was already
broken where are
you it's been a hdden run oh okay GA
narissa is outside getting Cobblestone
oh okay let's
go oh she said she's getting enough of
both of you should we go still or do you
want to wait here let's still go I have
to make one more phone call but let's
I'll talk on the
way okay thanks to
byebye oh we're doing things you'll be
hearing from my lawyer for that hit run
I got a picture of your
license I don't think a horse I don't
think that's a real horse
[Music]
anyway oh hi
hi I got enough for you too thank you I
got hit by a orse how do I throw them an
orse an orse uh yeah I think you have to
trade you have to left and right click
at the same time wait I have to
trade you can't throw this plus n oh my
God okay I'm sorry I can't share with
you after all maybe here I have some oh
trade with me sorry I can trade oh never
mind you're trading with someone else
I'm sorry are you trading with I'm stuck
in trade with Marissa hold on oh no wow
I see how it
ised me I see right click right
click no that doesn't do anything
TR you can only have
one what do you mean have you soft me
into a
may I go here sorry it'll it'll leave
maybe it'll cancel no you can be the I
will secure the last hits for you so you
can get all the gold make sure you get
yourb might as well Cobblestone if you
could I will off I
[Music]
go how many how many do we
need oh it's expired
TI let's go are you
friendly
oh it's okay it's okay that one was for
you do this have a
recharge all right did they go back in
no does everybody have their
Cobblestone I'm working on it okay
okay okay I am
ready M's going to get all this money
man
coins
Revelation dude you made a triangle t it
is is the
tep perfect for all your camping needs
you can probably light it oh light on
fire too a heal I'm not sure it might be
a
heal O A
heal an instant TP heal
oo
[Music]
okay okay
team go Scarlet
W yay now I guess we got to go back and
make something again yes something
cobblestone
wait is it this one did I go too far oh
that's not the right
[Music]
one there it
is all
[Music]
right you should be able to make you
stone tools to give it a
try so thanks for responding to the
question that's so cute please
it wait what are we supposed to
make eight
sticks I don't know wa are we supposed
to make
something or are we done with the side
quest now it's just says stone tools he
said that's all we
need but we might as well get some
upgrades though
yeah indestructible ooh
it was 100
coins do you need do you need money no
no are you in need of Charity no I'm not
in need of nothing Fair
Maiden well oh I'm so stupid the shift
is
weird I guess that's
everything and do we
return where did our other members go
did they make it
okay I I don't know
oh okay I guess not that
one I don't know where anybody
is I'm out of money okay I bought all
the stone stuff at least I think we
should return to the the quest Quest
quest Quest Master Quest yeah yeah oh
Quest Master this way he's this way he's
this way he's this
way make a group
call if we make a group we make a group
call we're still going to be able to
hear everybody
though party
call I think we're just going to end up
hearing double
double behind
byebye no come to the
to
the one and and a li
one beauty of finding the you from time
to time you're in pressed for time why
not have a look around town there a
mighty fine
shop shopping money
oh I don't have any
money none he didn't give you any I have
125 coins how many you you talk to this
guy if you talk if you talk to him he
should give you money yeah he'll give
you all the
money he's so supressed for time why not
have a look around
town give me money give me your money
you
little give me your don't hit him did
you press shift afterwards again okay he
gave he gave me the money he just
hesitated with all his goodness
do not Fred all I it was because you you
encouraged him with your sword I think
so too hello
sh where are you I called you we're
Gathering gather where did you find the
shopkeeper oh there's a
shopkeeper there's a Tavern I'm going to
go to the
tavern it's this way shopping okay it's
across the street from the blacksmith
that's pretty easy
you no we have locked eyes and we knew
that we were destined did you marry him
you married the king
that's oh my and they were
roommates oh hey what's up is she okay I
think she's
disconnected what make sure you got
enough coin ski a skipper ski a
skiper holy crap that's a lot to skip
dialogue I see
completed gosh victed a child in a
g talk to me I'll show you what I've got
in stock I want to I want to get lots of
money maybe we can buy stuff from them
and then we can sell it do not stop if
you ever need anything or if you just
want to keep me company that's okay I'm
sure fighting stains all day will be
hard on both your body and your
heart I like his top hat should be mine
are visiting the guild Halls we should
visit our Guild
Hall Vis the
gardens this way the children attending
to them why are the children working at
the Garden all right you guys ready to
find a lost
child yes okay is Nissa back hold on oh
she's let me ring her phone
call oh you can buy stuff from her
oh he has sweet
berries hey wait a minute I recognize
these song
titles not fiction oh okay okay we were
about to head there we're looking for
children
Marissa okay we we'll meet you by the
child the children they crave the corn
they yearn for
it oh all right are we ready
for we're going to meet n some in the
garden okay okay uh the garden should be
across there yeah
the my you sub the
quest going get need
you I don't know where the gardens are I
thought she already knew where'd she go
well this looks like Gardens we try it
does but it's kind of small for a
garden um
small people they can only handle so
much oh this kind of nice do not is this
the you know where the gardens are I
don't think this is a garden I don't
think so this is like a m The Garden of
betrayal I think this is the the the the
the the Jade Guild
Hall oh it is okay I think
perhaps thees these horses are sure hard
to keep up
everybody's gone where are we
going and they're gone bottom
right oh there's the child I see the
child do not fret
child I will find you child I will seek
you child oh child fear not fret not I
will go right toward you okay
oh I think I ran the child over fre come
and use them whatever you like did I hit
the K aces in
it what my job is keep an eye on them
stare away the birds and stuff if you
don't like gardening you can also try
building there's an empty lot just past
here where you arrows can build whatever
you like
arrows you and your guild mates could
work together to make a right speci
place to stay St bu any time if you want
to do some building
G oh can I tell you a secret did you
know there's a place in town called the
pit the pit mom says those kids aren't
allowed to go but I hear you can play a
really fun game
there sounds illegal terrible way to
advertise TOS children it's so fun but
you can't go you're hero they'll let you
in maybe you could go check it out and
tell me what it's like anyway hope to
see you again let's Rush there Mommy
says charismatic child able to loud in
front of five people very
impressive okay did we rescue him oh oh
finally he's finally talking to me oh
thank gosh to the oh thank
goodness it's okay FAA read it for you
let's run to the pit ladies to the pit
wait is this is this the way this is the
way I Follow the Leader oh
hello you think they finished all their
quests or are they just fighting each
other honestly I want to
know I want to see our Guild
Hall oh oh are horses allowed in here I
don't think they
are
okay lucky lady lucky lady I've got a
game for you oh says your new face don't
tell me you're one of those arrows who
save the town aren't you
she want to get rich I know it could
make you Fortune wait don't gu promise
it ain't nothing Shady look about how I
tell she something useful see I used to
run with the Jade show before I join the
Amber
[Laughter]
coin I don't know what he's saying I
can't read
this just point yourself at your M great
cck on her from there you can select
whatever to invite a te party a trade
with
her now we can adventure together swap
items and
coins told you it was useful didn't I
you'll thank me for when you're
adventuring yes uh I know you're very
important mission where C on you boo be
a lot easier if you add some extra coins
I'm saying give us give us the money
then you light to heav come down to and
play round or two Shake him Shake him
bro I don't care
just stop talking to me bro quite simply
I don't care shorten it this could have
been sent in an email shut up yeah
literally M let's beat him up and take
his wallet okay does he have one speak
to the I'll take his bow tie instead hit
him hit him excuse me wait we're
committing crimes against another guild
wait P it's a misunderstanding I what
are you doing here
don't tell
me we have
drama n shall breach the capital's walls
on
J oh no there and the Amber coin it's
okay you guys can go ahead without me
I'll just hit just hit Shi a lot J sword
guil yay I got it okay J
sword is that verish that's verish yeah
yeah yeah it is kind of sounds like
birday birthday salsa
exactly M
birday
oop to the greed man take me there this
at once we got
get myse cannot I feel like that is a
suspicious
the Gladiators Arena oh that's so cool
is this when we fight to the
death
theum where is this guy though don't you
die if you do that unless you're like a
vampire
probably
yeah it was all for a jol show
you know where you're going
dude yeah he under the
Coliseum I'm following know how to get
to him oh cuz they're the like they're
the fighty
ones fighty ones they're The Feisty ones
they're feral we don't know about Jade
those Jade members Miss I think this is
I hear the Jade members they're pretty
fighty feisty you don't want to get in
between them
oh they all look the same learned about
adventur has Bor have
turned I have not familiarized myself
with town at
all yeah same must be shaking suddenly
find yourselves in another
world oh oh you calling me
Calamity I was like what is this
sound our first priority is finding a
way to for gain your powers of
Revelation this world has a lot of
dialogue right it's horrible okay to
that end I just received word from our
Scouts for gaining a possible lead
investigating the
Calamity Mumble Mumble what's the
mission after this I saw they talk um
exit the Town Gate head to the Plains
and speak to a Hostess of the Jade
sword here
okay who has
this make haste who has
this may when you lead let's haste to
hastus he's
purple is it this
way I sure hope
[Music]
soing this GPS is kind of bad an update
very
quickly it's okay at least we have each
[Music]
other I hope we're all I hope we're all
gathered yeah same we have one
two well
um
let's
well I think we lost him hey there's a
bunny over here wait did we go too far I
think we went too far I think we have to
go back inside no no no he's he's in
here he's he's um he's
here where is
he
huh is he not on my map anymore oh he is
he's red
now a party call
well party call me me oh oh oh you can
do it horse you can do it horse I know
you can do it horse come on horse the
horse that's the horse there she is
she's right here oh hello
H hero you are arrived we have been
expecting you our initial Fays have
determined that the portal into the
runes is yet sealed with no way to enter
the runes we are at a loss for how to
proceed some have reported hearing a
strange voice voice but we know not what
to make of it the voice seemed to be
saying The Souls of stains open the way
I see uh what might it mean by that why
didn't you ask
right oh is this hus hus yeah ow it's
hus hero you are
arrived 1 2 3 4
five strange voice
The Souls of stains open the
way okay okay we have to kill we have to
kill 10 stains I understand that's
pretty easy that is the easiest thing in
the world aren't there more feel like
there's
more over here oh hello
ow don't you know who you're hitting I
am ow almost got me
why you sound like a
dog 10 coins give me your money give me
your
money what look there's something here
feel they not that many stains here
reached
it I'm going out to the oh wait yeah
there are wait a minute wait a minute
wait a minute spawn spawn
spawn H evidence we
wow this is the slowest better attack
ever oh
okay cleaning up the up okay that's the
end of the
world Wonder it's cleaning up the
stains
Revelation what is this even
do SC
I didn't miss okay maybe I maybe I
did three doesn't work yet we have to
find the power that's right we have to
restore the power of
Revelation
four also my Trident is on cool down
right now my my my what is it called
Oceanic out my Oceanic terror is on cool
down
yep yep
ow stop it I have not the coin to go to
the
aid
[Music]
hello I have a
key wait Skarlet
one mind what are our rules how many how
many have I killed wait for the Center
Bar okay who's who's the
Healer close wait do you need healing
like it's like destroyed no no wait can
you heal Revelation you're the
Healer I'm the Healer actually you just
full healed me you healed four Hearts
yes wait that's actually
awesome okay I won't use it on enemies
then that that would
make to
know wait
okay so you do healing watch out
watch what does everybody else's weapons
do I wonder open way I don't know she
always
tickles so we have a Healer we have a
Tickler we have a a mop
Revelation investigate the underworld
dungeon then speak to the Jade swword
Guild
Master I wonder how long this will take
hey a bird bird girl A Healer a
Tickler a mob see like anything that
says how many we have so
far ow I gu one to free yeah it doesn't
says but I think we can just go clean it
up Scarlet one clean it up I did it oh I
want to ENT H CL oh yeah probably says
that it's
complete do do the three of you think
that you will be fine without me and
Lady shiori
I think we will be we can do it we won't
let you down Scarlet wand we'll be we'll
be back we'll be back for the next one
okay okay okay we're sorry it's okay
thank you guys we can't wait to play
again I mean to fight together again are
you leaving my
wife we must we must
away yes we have who who's got the
fireball man what it is me the Phoenix
of the fires and the oranges what team
are you on hello lady of water Lady of
water I can put out your flame in an
instant with my
trop put out my flame you're on cool
down I know yes I am I know it because
I'm just used me Good Luck become wet at
least I can swim unlike you you wouldn't
know a thing you wouldn't know anything
about that about
me all right okay I don't know but I've
have a feeling I will know well how
about you prove to me whether or not you
can swim there's water right over there
this wonderful wonderful you for me
around over here sh um I I I get in
there it sure is dark in there there's a
diamond how about you go get that
diamond back into would you like a
diamond and if I sink what will come of
it I shall save you by then because I am
a hero oh good God something's killing
me
go on go on do not be scared oh she's
walking over water I'm in the water wait
what I'm sinking I'm
sinking oh this is nice so try
swimming I feel I
[Music]
can gura half drowned
wait can can I re re reenter the
stage for no
[Music]
reason ow hey man I just spawned in you
got to give me like a 10c cool down
period you got to give me like 10
seconds man I'm just I just got here I'm
being BM man get out of here get out of
here
got how do I get back
there okay now we are
three hello oh
hello hello
you wer there oh I'm back okay I died
but I can I'm back hello nice hello
shall we enter the
dungeon
okay I think I think I'm ready I won't
die again I
promise there's no water you next it
wasn't your fault it was the healer's
fault take any blame I know right wait
wait wait wait think the heer wouldn't
heal you one jober has one job couldn't
do their job yeah honestly I mean it's
well maybe maybe maybe I shouldn't heal
at all then maybe no without you let
your heals and where would we
be going to the dungeon wait where is
the it's here where is it it's on the
map oh oh okay okay
oh oh the
key
yes are we here wait good ide here
Dungeon battle music for the battle yes
are we
armed I sure hope
so do you have both your arms I hope so
I can't see them I'll have to take your
word for
it let me see you have both arms you're
good we're
good this doesn't seem like a dungeon
does it definitely not a level one
dungeon tooo Airy and yeah yeah
especially if for an underworld dungeon
this yeah I thought it would be I
thought it would be under the world this
feels very Overworld we'll see are we
are we the right level for
this level
zero level zero it's okay I'm I'm sure
we can cheese our way through it somehow
yeah wait what does your weapon do
Cecilia um Min is okay automat
assault oh okay is that
damage yeah okay DPS yours I think I'm
an
AOE that is an AOE that looks crazy does
that make me a tank you're a tank she's
a tank okay do
two and we have
one I think it also holds enemies into
place but I don't know if it heals them
too oh that's really cool wait let me
check do how do you you guys know this
this is like an item description or am I
supposed to know exactly what mine does
I no I'm guessing I'm guessing yes I
also I worried I was did I miss
something it's like a 10 page document
on the intricacies of the of the it was
the eth PDF not the seventh one oh man I
missed it oh ready to
enter ready
ready standing
bye wait do they wait
ready ready you are already standing by
for this dungeon do we need to kick the
others out oh no and it says two out of
five click enter enter wait don't enter
for me it says two out of five oh enter
dungeon wait I'm also two out of five oh
oh damn it a DAT yeah it says two out of
five it says gura is yellow am I not
cute are you not ready did you the green
one
[Music]
ready
ready status not
ready I'm ready up I swear I'm ready up
I ready up I
swear let me read the material thing let
me read the PDF real quick the 50
P it's just enter dungeon when you
approach a dungeon ready to enter
dungeon click on the green box on the
left and ready up if you're in a party
all members will to complete this step
you have the key I have the key
okay I'm ready kick party
members oh okay I can't kick the two
that aren't here
so when all players are ready clicking
on the diamond sword on the right will
allow you to enter the dungeon bring
over the enter dungeon button will let
you know if any members are not ready
hovering over the enter dungeon button
will let you know okay let's see um how
do we can we we can't make a new party
can we do that can we leave this one and
make a new
[Music]
one
okay okay let's try doing
that no yeah let try do that click to
leave click to disband
yes okay I left okay the party has been
disbanded okay let's make a new one
okay oh wait
okay inviting you both accept thank you
o accept Okay
we're and now we ready it says I'm
ready Scarlet wand oh my god oh we made
it we made it isn't so bad now this is
an underworld
dungeon it's still not really okay we
well under the sky imagine oh that's
lava oh there's a lot of lava oh don't
jump don't jump does the map work down
hereon this this one like starts
something the underworld a domain of
boundless oppressive Darkness as feared
as it is unavoidable it holds the final
resting place for every creature that
walks the Earth yet even in this realm
of the Dead there are those who live and
call it
home so we're just invading their home
essentially King out the
locals I guess weing the experience we
could put like a Starbucks here or
something oo
Starbucks I think we have to
jump um not that way not that way not
that way way not that
way scary I'm not sure
no
y
c maybe this is a baby level
dungeon if I die please don't make they
wouldn't they wouldn't go all out on the
first one
right okay first want to die um has to
do something
painful f
I don't know I didn't think that
[Music]
far wait not yet wait I think that
healed me did it heal you I think
so I think it did no I have a Healer
nice well fin
healed it healed me thank you very much
even with just three we've got a balance
party oh no oh a
checkpoint okay oh there's another one
there were we over there already though
or we couldn't access it
before I think we've passed the stone
monument before are we going in
circles maybe oh wait cool this way do
you see that big castle this cool wait I
don't I don't up
show up oh careful that's AIG job I
thought you got a new
GPU I bought a used one it's not that
good wait describe it with a FL
words Castle Looms in the distance with
the pointy spires piercing the heavens
BL red leaks Through the Windows I can
see it with my inner
eye yes so this is the creativity of the
Jade sword huh that's right we are the
creative team right and the smart team
Sky scarl one SC scet we we yearn for
the knowledge of geniuses creative and
very smart honestly very good
combination creative and
smart El you
need up who's oh God I'm getting a phone
call one second guys hello
hello is this
um
shark maybe depends what do you have to
sell
me uh sell no no no we're not selling
anything I'm with the
liian uh charity and we are looking for
donations for the uh
liian
um feels like I just saw for the first
time in my life oh my God it's a castle
guys the livian charity donation is
calling me should I give them any
money um we'll take a small donation of
Gold Everything my mom and daddy said I
can't I can't give you anything I'm
sorry The Blue Team M they told me to
tell you to call The Blue
Team The Blue Team aren't you blue San
cup says they have lots of
money and they're nice the chair
unit the donation I'm going to call you
back um they also more gold okay they
also said that your team is is
smelly hey they said that not us this is
the scar one team who's who's in charge
of your
guild seruan
cup I mean all right you're getting
written up I'm reporting
you
okay is in trouble
scary it's okay they don't need to know
they don't need to know is this going to
hit my am I going to hit my head no okay
we're fine we're fine we're fine we're
fine what's happening in the wait do you
think we can have here I I don't know
can we what no we can't use the
horses maybe horses are banned in the
Underworld oh Fair Maiden if only there
was someone who could heal me oh are you
in need of of healing oh I've
taken I healed thank you wait you guys
sound similar when you say
ooh ooh do we have the the green oo the
green oo the green O A we move really
fast she can't tell us AP
part my vision is blurring all I see
is a mumble jumble the fade of
[Music]
green the green ooze ah the artists are
going to like that one
when you say like that it sounds like
ooze like o o z
e the green ooze o the green ooze green
ooze very looks really cool though the
castle is really yeah there's a boss in
there I hope not I feel like we haven't
fought anything yet so maybe can you
imagine finding enemies during this
parkour
no I would die you're right what if they
flying on top of it oh no please no
parkour you should give them the ideas
for like next next time my short
leg you can do it don't give don't give
the devs any ideas they're
watching they're actually watching more
lav that
get my short legs man
[Music]
[Applause]
hello where are you where did you spawn
oh I'm at the bottom of the castle I'll
be I'll be with you shortly sorry sorry
about that you're at the bottom of the
castle you I see Cecilia hi I'm waving
do you see me hi hello I see you I see
you okay okay I'll be there in a sec
okay good okay I'll be back I'll be
man how do I run okay I was running I'm
doing the Run
button I got to show to them that I'm
not I'm not I'm not going to put I'm not
going to drag the team down it was a
mistake okay all I've been eating is
bread since I got here hit my head all I
have is carbohydrates oh the brain runs
on carbohydrates girl yeah but I can't
find my way up oh my God they're waiting
for me oh my God how did we get up here
before okay wait don't panic wait up
these phones have like MMS features so
you can send pictures of the credit card
they're talking about stealing credit
card what are you talking about stealing
credit card we're making a creative way
to make money stealing credit cards no
no no no no no tricking people into
giving us the credit cards very
willingly willingly giving them to us
yeah it's hello can you give me the last
three digits on the back of your I bet
you can't remember the last three digits
of the on the back of your credit
card I do because the other day I had to
put it in and then I kept putting in the
wrong one over and over and and over
again and now I Know It uh oh uh oh okay
I'm
F I thought I was going to
jump this is scary I don't want to
anymore you have to we're almost there
this make it to the top you can do
it oh a checkpoint if I get it doesn't
count for the whole
[Music]
team did everybody else already do this
are we we the the last ones I don't know
surely not right I think we the I think
it's just separate instances ah I
see I
see oh hello oh
inside okay is this where the boss
is oh no is this a maze
uh EO tank please lead the way pull the
enemies I'm the aggro pool are you
kidding me you're the
tank look at me look at me I'm the tank
oh look at me look at me I'm such a big
tank ooh ooh yeah okay yay that wasn't
that bad do I heal everybody with that
look up yeah I think so oh be careful oo
thank you for protecting us tank that's
my job don't fear do not
fear I've got a pocket and a DPS with a
very sharp
pointed I mean I'm on cool down no DPS
go DPS go you can do it go go
go uhoh uhoh the Healer needs needs
heals I did the Healer has no
heals why is he holding on to his
star we' got
geometry not the
geometry no no not
M oh he has a
circle wait wait wait oh wait do you
guys have keys I've got a circle key
keyle oh I've got a
star they're coming in waves
team they're surrounding us okay oh
thank
you uhoh oh nice wait Which Way were we
going don't I thought we were going
we're going this
way yeah this way I believe it's this
way oh
my Triangle
Man do not fear Triangle Man does
whatever triangle
[Music]
this way for
sure is it this way I I don't know uhoh
DPSS no there's too many use your AOE
it's un cooled down
waiting wait stay ahead of it stay ahead
of it CE call that
to oh God oh God okay
wait
okay thank you thank you thank
you
ow I'm sorry I wasted your heels I'm
sorry corner it's okay I'm no longer on
cool
down
okay wait one two 1 2
3 we're here we're
here wait is this it this
oh it needs oh can we like each put one
oh do we need
ke I have a key okay I put in this oh oh
nice
okay very
good excellent do you guys need food
this looks like food if anyone needs
food this kind of looks like Dark Souls
I don't like it yeah Traverse the white
light I know want to do this did we get
a save do we have a save point no
bonfire is lit this is hardcore mode
there's no save it's okay we can do it
first try Okay a hardcore uh something
something um great we can do this team
we got Scarlet wand Skarlet wand Scarlet
wand
Skarlet my God a checkpoint
that look cool that is
cool it's scet just like us yeah
actually
this another life expired leaving behind
a tiny flickering light assault
representing both a legacy and an ending
the veiled figure cradled in her hands
and with a hint of melancholy she
whispered is that the right thing to do
oh I don't know is it
I have to ask this mysterious veiled
figure who Could It Be Who Could It Be I
wonder oh I like the
chandeliers yeah fancy hit the hit the
chains and make it drop on the boss exra
damage I could put oil underneath so
they light on
fire smart this is this is the
creativity of red team ah and the
genius
yes we just build different and
everything here is red so it's like it's
made for us have you guys figured out a
way to remove like the in-game overlay
because it's like kind of
cluttery overlay you know how it says
like coins your party investigate the
other I just have it on there I do
toine I can with my increased Rend
distance is this a puzzle
oh guys this is ours we're the Geniuses
someone take the wheel okay quick
somebody else do it quick someone take
the wheel I believe in you guys what
what kind of puzzle is oh my god did you
play pets vets it's it's the pets vets
game oh it's like the ones around it
turn revers I hate these puzzles
y wait it seems like you know what
you're doing I
don't I feel like you're doing it though
I think you're doing
it I think you're just saying
that no no no oh
almost wait so does it like compare does
it do it from the the other side as well
or I got to look up the rules of revers
is it 3D I guess it is so if I touch
this one oh it is 3D okay okay let's see
how about this there's a there's a
single
oh each piece played must be laid
adjacent to an opponent piece the oppos
that the opponent's piece or a roll of
opponent's piece is flanked by the
opponent's piece of a new piece and
another piece of the same color did you
get it
yes it's just one
left oh never mind it's more than one
left
oh one uhoh oh okay let's just go move
with the flow so we so we activate this
one okay yeah yeah yeah yeah and then
this one no not that
one is it like one of those slidy
puzzles too okay okay and then this one
I think it is like flipping them on and
off oh wait wait wait wait
let's
go good job
genius the wrinkles are at least five
times faster than the other teams cuz
we're the smart on absolutely
100% now Sur that was the final boss the
puzzle and then the all and we win
right get
the Bing
wait the zombies we fought weren't even
stains do you think we're being set up
by this Kingdom to just like fight their
War for no reason yes maybe cuz they
weren't stains they were like ooh the
stains are attacking us they weren't
stains they were just people in a
dungeon there was just red
guys that's kind of
suspicious is this something is a foot
it's a skull I like this I don't I don't
like oh
oh oh dear it's
lasers rock and roll man
run um I don't know how we can take the
giant the giant
there can't
anywh oh um new checkpoint unlock was it
a scripted
death oh no I was able toay stay alive
on the corner of the stairs but then I
fell
down I think it was scripted scripted
rock
band
oh a
skeleton is he friendly he's hostile he
wants a hug give him a hug come on R
give him a hug okay okay actually wait
no wait no we don't do
anything
ooh oh o his bone crumb
did you
H wow
ow nice DPS DPS okay maybe we have to
use the bone thingy oh oh wait oh can we
make it grow yeah I thought so but he
was he just spawned out of it so my
mushroom did you
get
damage can I use my key on it ow I want
the I want the bone
key key give me give me can you attack
it or can you my R did you get one I did
not a bone crumb oh ah I'm dying
healer healer
help down you're on your own
yourself okay I'll eat we have to kill
him on top of the mushroom
oh genius okay
it
worked oh massive
brain maybe
again can we break these blocks and use
them
uh yeah come here yeah come here come
here yeah yeah okay
okay
okay I'm the tank I'm the tank yeah can
we feed it again I don't know yeah try
try bring it here come here at the
fou
skeleton oh maybe we have to fill we
have to fill all this and maybe then
it's like stairs or something yeah
okay ow I was standing in it
[Music]
sorry my
bad okay oh oh
right he's on me he's on me on me on me
on me
o okay is that enough oh we have to get
up there I think we did it maybe not I
think we need a little more
more oh
[Music]
w w wo wo wo W wo W wo w w w
WC Me You
O Okay where is he
oh there's a button there's a something
there's buttons there's a button oh you
can climb the vines over
here to get up really
[Music]
are there always buttons on trees
here oh there's a button the buttons
will show you the
way okay
everywhere follow the path of the
buttons okie dokie press the
button e a button want ooh another
button o another button o button button
oh yay a
button oh yay two more mushrooms to
grow I guess
we
[Music]
more come here there he is
I'm
dying wait wait I can heal you I'm the
Healer oh my God that heals full that's
really impressive actually that's crazy
this is pretty good power wait we should
try to see can you heal two people at
once do you not get healed by it too I
thought it was AOE but it might be I
haven't been that close
tension okay next time do you ah
let us know when it's on cool off cool
down again so we can do it come here
come here skeleton okay I'll let you
know do we have buttons buttons you got
any
ououou oh I'm going to die any
buttons oh oh it hurts it
hurts that's
all right let's see just how scary these
do you
mind okay I'm all cool down are you guys
damaged I can be I'm damaged okay pay
attention AOE baby yeah I got heal nice
I think we should be able to climb up
here oh my God can you
[Music]
not I'm climbing
oh there's buttons oh there's buttons
are we done I don't know if we have to
do the other one
too um I think we can get up on this
one yeah I do I
do c
[Music]
youc c youc wait she was slain by a
skeleton uhoh
oh the Healer was not there um
um how far back ring ring ring ring ring
ring see see where where did you where
did you
spawn oh I see you I see you okay I'm
sorry I wasn't I wasn't there to save
you from the
[Music]
skeleton we're we're stronger as a team
we have to stay together uhhuh mhm okay
okay I'll see you in a minute okay
byebye how do
we oh do we need the other
one no maybe
maybe how good is our parkour I
think I mean would they just make it so
that there's two of them but you only
need one would they do that that
no but maybe we need here you you work
on the parkour and I'll go feed the
other tree uhoh okie dokie there's a
button here but there is
no I can't click the block uh the the
tree we cannot remove the
tree it's magic tree with magic wood and
magic mushroom
[Music]
we need another
Branch we must have
more are the skeletons still spawning
for them
all they
are can I shoot this from up
here okay good to know it floats do
flip ow no luck or did you fall I did I
think we need
both yeah I think we need
both skeleton herey boy come here come
here come here come die come
[Music]
die beautiful oh is that good maybe
let's see I feel like that's enough
since
the need
heels you missed did I miss well I miss
myself hey man as long as the Healer
stays
alive all
right yeah come run the loop with me
yeah come on come on come onon I'm
holding it
skeleton all
right we're going to go this
way we're going to follow the
buttons and we're totally going to beat
the other two
first hop hop and then we go hop hop hop
and then we go hop hop and then we go H
hop
oh oh can we make that jump
[Music]
hop we have we've done
it you did
it we all did it
[Music]
immigr i'm green over here
they're doing green to Green
[Music]
communication you might need to go from
the other tree try the
left
wait
right oh oh no wait did
she hello
oh oh speed
running I just wanted I didn't want you
guys to wait any longer so I was like
you want I'll just skip it Scarlet one
genius that's that's why we're the
Geniuses
creativity okay that is for us suy
yeah to the Denis of the Underworld the
light elated eleminated by Souls was
vital they needed it to survive in this
ever cold and dark environment yet among
them there was a heretic who called the
Customs into question do we really need
to take others lives to sustain our
own is that how it works I think so no
there has to be another way and so she
stepped into the plane above oh she went
on a trip she went on a trip I wonder
what happened to her yeah what could
have happened happen I don't
know what could have happened let's open
this door and
find your power of Revelation has grown
stronger you've recovered a portion of
your
memories ah ah ah my
head it hurts I feel it I feel the
memories returning to
me look here to watch your
video but I will show you the video
later we will show you the
video should we do that now or I
I am down show it now where is the video
it is it is you can you may download it
from the announcements channel
oh need two minutes then to log onto
Discord oh
no oh
dear okay let's do that real quick okay
okay please hold as we access our
memories yeah it takes a while to
remember it's so fuzzy does it anybody
have any elevator
music oh I do you know I've got I've got
the music the F juke box oh yes oh yes
um please
hold okay oh one
second oh my memory is so foggy
guys have to remember your passwords
have to remember everything
I have finished accessing my memories
should I should I wait for you guys
or um let's let's play it together okay
okay a little bit more time my memory
download speed seems to be a little bit
slow my M my existing speed seems to be
a little bit slow
no you will get
there yeah that was a cute dungeon I
like the puzzles I didn't like the tree
stuff but I like the little triangle and
the maybe two too many trees but yeah
but the block thing was
fun yeah the light stuff was really cool
yeah and it looked super
impressive okay I am now due to my weird
memory setup I am transferring my memory
from one data machine to the other but
he said Cece's on Di up
[Laughter]
o
true it's funny until it's not until you
have okay oh God this is so slow this is
a big
memory well it's good
right faster if we get bigger
CHS oh yeah if you guys want you can go
ahead without love me I don't mind how
how how much longer for your memory to
download um so I'm currently at uh so I
have a stick and then I put
it and it's at 80% and then I have to
put it on the other data machine and
then this is really automaton technology
right here yeah this thing is like when
I was created they wanted like it to be
really secure you know so they they
didn't let any like my brain is split in
they yeah it's very complicated imimi
engineering very
complicated lots of gear and cogs
spinning around yeah but it's
uh
[Laughter]
um looking oh okay and now I will put it
here she's in the second
machine
yippe ah
the sun is rising it's almost there it
is
okay
okay oh
nice somebody asked if it was a floppy
disc no it's a oops it's
a hi screen it's fine it's
fine it's a floppy disc isn't it I think
it's no it's not a floppy disc it's like
completely different okay I'm at
90% okay
mhm nice well Papa thank
you okay okay okay
okay I got it I'm here I'm ready oh I'm
remembering so well are we are we ready
are we ready to
remember I'm ready to remember guys okay
me too
[Music]
it's a little big I don't have the AUD
pause behind wait should we get the
audio yes yeah she's talking okay I got
the audio oh it's loud okay
ready oh wait you haven't started okay
can we all start wait should we start on
three let's start over let's start over
Okay start over Okay
okay who's counting oh wait wait hold on
I'm not ready yet hold
on okay okay okay everybody
ready 1 3 2 1 go
[Music]
sorry guys but I keep
wondering
oh it's not muted anymore it's not
[Music]
muted is this the right thing to
do no wait
she she was the lady in the B was the
lady in the in the in the flame
attacks a cute what's going
on look at
[Applause]
that turn out we can also use people's
em we can do it we don't need their
souls at
all she's being called back Reaper
should help the
living not take away their future if the
others can't accept that that's their
loss
yeah oh she murdered them
all I'll do things my way
oo cool
[Music]
that was
cool
Mory some cool Reaper right there the
coolest it was her dungeon her under mhm
her underworld
dungeon oh no I don't want to go back
into the dungeon no no thank you I'm
good I'm good I'm good how do we go home
though yeah we need to go talk to Quest
[Music]
giver and
let's go fast with the
horse oh gosh okay but where you know
the way can we follow you oh I see I see
the map the map the
map no no please
ah you can't make me go back in there hi
Ena
bya oh I said
[Music]
no one two
three okay are you with me let's go you
say so
away
it's the voices in my head are calling
are calling for Kia
Mori get her
and then we go
inside
yes oh give the horses
names oh oh yes color or that was the
same mine a new horse every time mine's
been Brown from the
start yeah mine definitely changes
colors what
wait it does what
the for from the void every time how can
we get attach to our Pony that way it's
a magical
pony okay just a magical pony yeah
where's C
though here here hello okay here you
here
you here
here okay we made it we've done your
bidding Green Man
yeah what's what's say
you where's our
money please read for us someone I'll
read Brave hero I am hardened to see
that you have returned unharmed pray
tell what transpired at the ruins oh cut
scene lety oh no no we just explained I
see to think the ruins held such Secrets
a crystal deep within that when touched
returned a fragment of your memories to
you memories which in turn reawaken the
power of Revelation albe it at only a
fraction of its potential oh yeah did we
level up our power strong yeah at the
end of the dungeon in that white room
yeah now your summoning and the
discovery of these ruins should coincide
so closely there must be some connection
between the ruins and the power of
Revelation Brave hero seek rubius The
Guild Master of the Scarlet wand that's
us his Guild that's us gu has also been
searching for strange ruins in the lands
of Lial maybe they have discovered
something
oh my God oh my God we get to go to our
Guild we'll see our Guild now okay okay
well I mean this one's fine but I bet
ours is way cooler because it's creative
and stuff 100%
100% okay let's
go north rubius okay lead the
way it's going to be a broom closet
nuh-uh oh it's
here not that far oh look at it though
it's a big question mark yeah cuz we're
seeking knowledge knowledge CIA poti s
Scarlet
wand how do we go
inside I want to go
inside oh my God it's beautiful
that's sunlight
though wait I'm missing the quest I'm
sorry your choice of the power of
Revelation fascinating Most Fascinating
one might hypothesize that I don't know
how you pronounce that word that those
runes are the key to unlocking your
powers we of the Scarlet wand have also
been investigating near the Plains and
wouldn't you know it just off the coast
we aspired light with a striking
resemblance to Revelation good hero
would you be willing to travel to the
coast and Aid in our efforts there of
course members of our Guild are already
there heart at work I'm quite sure they
will appreciate your assistance good
luck and
exelia she casted
spells cast spells
[Music]
[Laughter]
Fireball it
now
yeah but I feel like mine was already at
full heal does it get much better than
that maybe the cool down goes SL bigger
TP TP
XL do we get
rooms yeah do we live here
[Music]
oh I want a room still cleaning up the
mess yeah like dorm room
this you think it's bunk beds was a big
table like so big we just I crave food
look you can't even see over the table
this little
guy he needs a boost to see he does
tiny
[Music]
cute okay I
mean I don't see any rooms but we could
just put our camp here we is a broom CL
thing I have I have instant tee you can
sleep summon Tepe
nice I cast summon
[Music]
Tee It didn't summon a little hard to
sleep in it if it's actually oh I have
some hide can we build it all here I
don't think
so let me see yeah can we build
stuff someone said we can build at the
Garden uhhuh yeah I think there's like a
house area but we're not allowed we
don't have the contractual like licenses
to build on their property ah which is
weird cuz we're part of their team but
oh well we have a lot of money we can go
see what they're
selling oh yeah that's a good
idea cuz I think
wait what about the pit do you think
there's like some death tournament that
we can partake in illegal gambling ring
maybe o that would be cool play some
dice that would be
cool okay we can check out the shop does
anyone remember where it
was across from the
blacksmith oh okay
where was that the
tavern oh the it was a it was oh wait we
have a map guys remember is it is it
labeled um yeah we have a well we have a
in our handy magical document we have a
we have a and um so we need to go to the
Town Gate Scarlet one is here why is
Jade SW everyone else's Bas is are
bigger than ours it's because our is
creativity we don't need a lot of space
to be creative they don't know about the
secret bunker or is mostly underground
the top part is compensating for the
smallness of their brains with the
weakness of their houses yes so true
okay I think
it's no
yes oh life beyond the C Castle Gates oh
someday I will know
[Music]
you The Bard
all I'll be The Bard hell yeah yes
please wa where's
CeCe here we are this is
thect and there should be the tavern
should be across here's the shop yay
money he has a Le a fashion surprise box
I fashion surprise box I bought it we
have to get that I bought it okay okay
let's see ready we open it on three yes
okay one 2
3 click to
choose oh een
what this is not fashion
what I didn't get any fashion at all did
you
guys I got St fashion what did you get I
got a construction supplies box I got a
constru supplies box wait this might be
good actually oo wait we get 64 of
whatever we I only get one
really I'm going to get some never mind
the gacha is
Bountiful hey guys what did you get I
got 64 Cherry
logs I'm making a pink house
pause okay I'm going to buy one more
black tight
head watch your
[Laughter]
mouth watch your mouth when you're
talking to me
Who you calling
pin you
very you point you do have a
point she has a point I've got a garden
for you to sit
in I will guard your garden oh no your
neck be careful it's going to break for
my shoulders the egg
could use that as a
weapon if you look down really fast you
can
SL forward with your face down
okay
charge no too
strong s that is impressive yeah it's
because your brain is so cuz you're part
of the scull and wanty it's all hiding
in my head please don't take off my head
you take off my head I'll
die I bought another
one oh you had the money I had 700 stuff
I only have 300 left okay wait I got
hats
again what we could use it to
impersonate another
[Music]
guild I could give you guys one of these
is back on the table
wait what did I get oh I didn't get it
wait what oh did you get I think it just
shows you what you didn't get it's kind
of mean like that how do we sell stuff I
see that was 300 coins I'm going to
cry it's okay you can maybe we you can
sell the stuff you get inside maybe I
didn't get anything
nothing consolation priz I did I did I
got a box that's right the box is
actually pretty good oh wait what should
I take from
it what' you say what you say what did
you say what did you say oh hello ladies
what did you say Greetings you say
something I the appointed point
change Point get it the Skarlet
wand I
speak we had a side quest and she took
over leader of our Guild W that's
cool it looks you're wearing a hat like
this it looks like you're wearing like a
red velvet cake on your head what is
your name blue creature it um um
don't
know she forgot you still don't
know hey you aren't you the one that hit
me with your
horse oh my God I don't there's lots of
horses and you are the one that drowned
her this wait a
second wait who don't worry I'll kill
over what what they do you hit me with
your
hor no no no no no no
no who right what Guild are you a part
[Music]
of please don't hit me with your horse
again we will never
know
aora yeah I have a question for
you would you want 6 22 Mangrove logs if
you tell us what color your guild
is really
here I 24 I'm opening I'm uping it no I
want I want the big hat or
nothing nothing it's okay goodbye you
don't understand wait let me reason let
me reason you don't
understand if I take this hat off I will
die so it's a it's a trade your life for
this
hat no that doesn't know her life and
the
hat I think I want the Hat anyway but
what if we give you uh wood
instead I I I don't I don't want a wood
I want I want this hat specifically well
you're not going to get it how about how
about I can offer you the opportunity of
a lifetime have you ever needed shelter
and you had nowhere to go well what I
can offer you is instant
tee anytime or place um any time or
place restrictions May
apply I okay let me tell you I'm a white
cat so I don't actually have a house I
don't need a home so I am okay thank you
but thank you for the uh for the offer
it was actually yeah yeah no but you
already took it you're now in her debt
true no no it
this how
it okay listen I have I offer you a
trade oh okay you give me 500 coins and
I tell you what you need to know I do
not have that kind of
money I can give you five no 500 and the
hat five best best I can give you 500
and the hat she's not to be reason with
no
hat no okay no hat but I want 500 coins
I give you five you don't have any
backup who's to say we couldn't just
quietly make you disappear
yeah yeah
quick what you mean hey that's against
the rule me leave me alone leave me
alone put her in the house put her the T
leave me
alone DP oh we already used the
DP H I need a cool down reduction on my
tee
stat it's okay who else is in the team
maybe we can ask someone
else is
that I don't know what team I actually
don't know the
guild yeah me either that's the problem
it's the yellow
coin oh blue cup it's the am te and the
green sword oh yeah
ahuh it's okay I'm sure we'll figure out
with time our
next and um the next time we meet her
will be plentiful do you guys do you
guys want to wind down in the Local
Tavern maybe you want to yeah yeah we
can go to the
tavern did we did we complete what we
were supposed to complete today I think
so I think so
wait there's a bar made wait a minute a
cute wait you can save the drinks on the
house on the house on the house he's
charging me 100 coins wait yeah where
where did you get it on the house the
left one set on the house well he hasn't
given me anything maybe it's just like
ad lip you know he's just he's just
telling me to talk to the bar
made night vision on the house
if you can really save the kingdom
oh I spent all my
money Goa what I'll buy you a drink I
like
how
Nam
money what would you prefer to drink of
choice be can we
loot like like Rob no no no no no no no
no it's
borrowing simply
borrowing yeah do they have anything
they don't have
anything or somebody else gone here
first true there's a
chest don't steal from citizens we
are we're saving their life
[Music]
do you think they made8 bit versions of
the songs you can listen to like this
here
non-fiction I wonder if these are like M
I mean um in the style of Li style you
know what I mean records right the
records yeah we can Farm gold
I could do you guys want to maybe try
checking out the arena yeah just
gambling there yeah you can do
that let's gamble the rest of our money
away yeah I still have
335 bought another gacha that was some
restraint that you showed I wanted to
save it for possible
gambling I have no brilliant
s God
genius I think everybody else is doing
the the thing we already
did are
they it says it says
duel o can we fight each
other okay the first participant presses
the door button whoever wishes to
challenge them also presses the Dual
button the first speaks to the arena
coordinator again after pressing the
start game button a countdown will begin
after which The Duel between the two
players begin you can also dual party
versus
party well in a party one representative
of the party should press the Dual
button representative of the other party
must then also press the D okay well we
not a party okay if you guys maybe you
guys can do and I go onto the steps to
look at you I'll be the commentator why
not why not you why don't I go on the
steps um to Cal oh wait wait wait wait
wait wait we should have green versus
green
no no we are team we're on the same side
just find another party to fight it's
just it's just some okay no need to to
do all this infighting right yeah no we
te
this maybe we should do one fight and
then do one with an opposing team
somebody duel me I'll Stand still I'll
be your punch
dummy okay you two go I'll I'll watch
come on man come on find a join come on
fight her come on I've joined the red
team could not find an opponent ah I
think it has to be against
opposite oh oh really you think so
you've joined the red team yeah we're
all on the red
team
oh oh okay I'm calling I'm calling
someone yes call them over wiing
wiing private call Who's
online are they all busy in the dungeon
oh they might be in the dungeon yeah
okay I'm going to I'm going to call H
okay so we one two three let's ask
I think Elizabeth and mor than the
dungeon I'm
try the other play is already no call
okay I'll try we could disband our party
and fight each other then oh that's a
good idea okay okay
goodbye
oh
red
blue seems
backwards 3 two
1 wait wait wait wait wait
wait we only have a wooden sword are you
kidding me where my Apple you don't get
an Apple now where'd you go stop
moving stop moving stop the Pigman stop
ow oh wait stop yeah sure yeah sure it
is the Ping it is the Ping wait wait I
going to die I hurt I hurt I
[Music]
hurt mhm
mhm well fought well
fought marvelous display marvelous
display now Fork over all your lunch
money
um I can't I'd have to trade you oh
uh I have
some okay
okay give me all your
money this is all I have what I don't
believe that it's all I I swear to you
it's all I have I swear okay fine was it
I'm scaffolding oh okay okay that's no
no bring the bring the scaffolding back
oh want my scaffolding this caus me 300
gold yeah
exactly plus oh wait hold on what if
[Applause]
we okay fine
fine bring
the bring the SC wait I'm thinking
though we could use this at some point
I'll use it I'll use
it what do you think I'm going to do
with it I'm going to use it to make
something beautiful no we have to use it
we
have we're on the same team only
fair it's only fair you lost it keeps
going down there okay fine
fine enjoy your wheat
seeds I will you'll see I'll be I'll
have a whole Farm soon enough I'll be
feeding all of the Scarlet
wands how do we um didn't cost any money
so I'm going to spend my last money on
one more flute box I think yay what
about the pit oh this is the pit this is
not the pit right this is the um isn't
there another no the pit is where they
sleep this was the pit there's some
shady
guy at the pit right yes yes oh right
you're right pit was
yellow okay let's see the pit is is is
the P Casino across from here oh it is
on this side okay lead the
way
[Music]
away a casino casino and then there's
also like the Coliseum what do we
have the broom
closet go
study the library
[Music]
P can we gamble
bookie can
gble make a b uh-oh well I'm going all
in on green green I got to do blue what
all in on green I got to do BL H how do
you do this how does it
work 40 seconds oh okay green is there a
roulette wheel or something
20 how do I do this uh okay uh you right
click him yeah and then press on the
make a b the golden button uh-huh and
there's a a window with four colors with
po
up what a window what happens if you
right clicking I have a hammer and a
piece of paper oh yeah Click put your
money in the piece of paper however much
money you want to bet just prep in like
100 or whatever how much you have and
then press enter and it should do like
a aing
okay nice you did it color Cannon is
firing where's the color Cannon where's
the color Canon oh there there it's is
it red oh the
wall uh-huh oh wait maybe not is it
deleting the colors uhoh wait I put it I
put it on blue like the last one
standing yeah
maybe blue blue blue blue blue green
greenen
greenen green
green green green green green green
green noen green Green there's no
way no
10 times how no that's not normal this
was a scam it was green
set they saw us walk in and we're green
and blue and they were
like wow that's that's
that's I can't believe this would happen
okay I have some more money let's play
again I'm
broke went all in on I'll give you a
little bit of money and then you can
let's bet one more time time
okay yellow oh
sorry there's nothing quite like bonding
with your guild members like gambling
gambling do you think do you think we
were oh push I think it worked if you
push the red
one okay oh thank you
okay what did you guys beted on oh
you're Bing green green I did yellow
okay
okay you bookie you better not cheat
this time yeah one more chance
bookie all right over oh God oh God
colon
firing please please I need this green
are standing how am I going to collect
all my funny
hats please M that's
good oh come on funny funny head green
green not I I
funny hats please I need the funny head
hold
hold hold yellow come
on goodby blue yellow green green Green
GRE green green green no it's blue is it
blue it's blue wait no it's not it's
green
green how much did you
make I got 300 bucks so much no
way okay I'm betting what you guys do
you guys are lucky
okay are
we are we betting
green I'm betting
green is it really going to be green
again
though of course always believe in green
how much for it's the strongest color
it's the color of life okay
okay I did 20 on green only 20 not much
fa there help I've lost every time
little old man I'm running out of
coins
okay I like the little tables it's very
cute oh yeah we should sit we should sit
down at a
table oh oh sorry s my bad you can sit
on my lap I don't
mind oh okay wait I can't see though I
might beat the table up wait you should
be on the on the front then I can't see
anything with your head on oh sorry oh I
see I see I see oh okay sorry
you no you go oh no no no you go no no
you go no you okay it's green green
Green it's going to be green
again you're very confident green I
trust your
confidence that is already gone that's
good sorry seriously
green has to be
green see I'm
seeing it's green it's green it's
[Music]
green see it's GRE green it's green it's
green it's green it's a green it's
green just your weights
yeah no way yes no way how much wait how
much did you guys make now I have 700
bucks oh I have 95 oh my
God
green green The Color of Money there's
no way it happens again
right it has to happen again I think
green you have to always trust in green
you have to trust in
green okay it's never disappointed you
so far I I definitely I definitely trust
in green
green I trusting green
too you wouldn't you wouldn't you
wouldn't forsake green would you for I
wouldn't I would never you wouldn't
suddenly like turn around and not go for
green right never never never after
everything it's done for you never
never yeah I believe
you I got to make some money back I sure
hope this Green Works
it'll be great
definitely 100 on red I don't have ah I
don't have the
money no you need alone it's going to be
green no not yet oh you're sitting
there green green Green it's green come
on green def green come
on okay okay red is again it's green
okay okay not
terrible
mhm now yellow just has to perish blue
is gone that's fine f is
winning yeah okay yes
I can't
breathe oh my
God green there's no way
[Music]
green surely it can't happen again
300 h
[Music]
are we green
again I'm going green yeah we're green
I'm going all in on green some money
earlier for now or no no no no no you
went to Green okay okay I simply regret
that I didn't put more on green I am all
it on green if this doesn't work I'm
broke so I'll put a little more in this
time if this doesn't work I'm going
to hold it again the members of the Jade
Spoon or whatever their Guild is called
yeah the Jade Spoon yeah
rients it'll be over for them
[Music]
yeah okay I'm starting to sweat I don't
know how I feel about this one okay
green it's green it's green green
definitely green
I
I okay see okay it's green green
standing
okay yeah that's still fine it's fine
mhm stay optimistic it's
okay my optimism is
wavering why no no no don't believe in
theing I believe
it's green still see how far apart they
are there's no way you can you can snipe
all of them see Goodbye
Blue
no I have to go my knees are weak I
can't feel my legs I can't feel my legs
I think the blood is draining for my
head I have I need a
loan you did this I'll be back I went
all in I'm
broke I'm broke um how are you doing are
you broke are you fine I'm at 700 that's
pretty good can I ask for a small loan
of 10 coins oh just 10 yeah just 10 I
just need
10 oh thank you
I'll I'll do you one
better
more 100 got an extra zero just for you
oh oh I am ever grateful thank
you but you will only spend it on green
right I will only spend it on
green how much do I owe you in return
what is the interest rate on this I feel
like oh it's just it's just 30
% okay oh my that's
all I feel like
the the like the
percentages are they like accurate or is
there a way to numerically game the
system based on like the numbers well
hold on how many times have we gotten in
the
payout is this cheating has to do
confidence it's all a a brain game if
you really conf confident and you
believe I think you can
win quit before they
win I think you can do it oh the house
always wins does it is it actually
rigged against us what color did you
guys do are we betting I'm betting I'm
betting I'm sorry fa I'm betting green I
went 500 on Green Oh my God
500 that's how it goes we lost last time
we win this time is counting colors the
same as counting cards am I going to get
thrown out of
here um they are very small and don't
bookie the bookie can barely see
anything so it's fine you're fine I want
to be able to
tell
okay okay mhm okay red is
[Music]
out okay very good looking good so far
far yes okay it's so green it's like a
hat it's
yeah an arrow pointing to the Moon okay
to the Moon the Moon is very high up
belongs to the Moon
green green this is 5050 through this
green to the Moon do we believe in it
yes I believe in Green Oh no
[Music]
it's rigged it's rigged it's rigged they
hate
us they hate us they hate us
specifically we're like 2/3 green and
they're attacking us for it okay I'm
going to go all in on this last
[Music]
one I mean we're do we're
do a green the
green green is is
do what about red no red is not do green
is do is a number it could be red though
no it could be it's going to be green it
could be all in on red fa it could
be oh it's 500
Max
okay okay can't go more than 500 that's
fine 500
how are we going to explain this to sh
and
Nissa oh well if we make money we won't
have anything to explain right true and
if we don't if there's like which won't
happen then we can say that another the
team we're burglaring us and yeah
yeah
Green Green please green please you
don't
understand yep it's green
clearly there there can only be
one this time it's a arrow that points
downward po down what does that mean
because you're going down the other
color
red
seeed I went all in red oh
no why
it's not fair it's going to be blue it's
not fair can't believe they would do
this us I'm drowning in the fountain
yellow oh no have so much to live one G
shouldn't be enough for this
please okay I don't have I don't have
that much money left I'm going to think
call it's going to be green this time oh
that's all I knew F I got no money I
actually believe this time we actually
do that's what you said last oh how much
is that last time I was wrong this time
we're do okay because it was yellow last
time it will absolutely be green this
time okie dokie it's all probability
really yeah I keep forgetting my
head I can't see
we can even go upstairs to the cannon if
we go oh can we tamper with the
cannon to make it so it's always green
we can talk to it very very you know
enticingly this do I fit apart to make
it green this time make it green green
make it green you know you want to green
green
green Green you love
GRE Color of Money color of nature love
color of
success color love green which is red
the opposite of green we'll see how this
works
green color of
leaves hurry NIS is
coming color of
everything never so
cute it's okay we're going to make it
all back green green green green green
green green Green okay okay okay it's
looking good you want green that's what
you
want I never doubted the green I never
doubted the green I'm sorry green green
green green Green
[Applause]
[Music]
yes never never a th000 coins oh my God
th I have nice a thousand
coins yay okay with that Victory I think
I'm going to go to sleep oh my memories
are coming back to me it's almost like I
have to sleep oh the memories of bedtime
memories ofies bed memories of my
comfortable bed with a pillow that is
cool on both sides delicious and a
mattress that's made of
money sleeping on a pile of money hey
what's my mattress made of I'll sleep in
my hat don't worry about it never
mind just flip it around and it's like a
sleeping bag sleeping
bag actually it's long enough for that
you look like a you look like a
caterpillar am I a cute
caterpillar or like a a pastry like a
cornet do you remember that scene in
Lucky Star where they're CH talking
about the chocolate chocolate you eat it
from yeah
yeah I'll accept that good questions
it's like that I believe but it was
really fun thank you for hanging out
yeah thank you I mean sky and wand SK W
SK and wand not green team red
team oh red team full of money red team
but red is the opposite of green so it
makes sense yeah it yeah it's like
complimentary callous so yeah okay see
you guys again for so we can kill all
the stains and destroy the Dungeons and
gambling good night take all the
money
my wait can we have like a slogan like a
battle war cry what's our Battle
Cry I don't know any good ones though
Scarlet W
Scarlet uh wait curiosity and
creativity creative
curious
uh wait on we have to come up with
something this is a bad look maybe maybe
the other two can come oh we have to
wait for the others right that wouldn't
be nice if we just yeah that's true we
have a lot of good ideas but we're
trying to be inclusive okay
green
green goodbye everyone
good
night good night
bye
ah good night everybody thank you for
joining on day one
of we calling
this it's Ian Recco or
inreco we'll see you we'll see you next
time okay keep keep an eye out I'm your
gnome
Garba good
night goodbye goodbye goodby goodbye
goodby
goodbye see you see
[Music]
oh