[Music]
hmm
my
[Music]
do
you
[Music]
do
oh
[Music]
my
can you guys hear me
uh hello test test
kick it again
[Music]
i need to check check
you hear me
okay good oh you hear the pgm too
you're the vision
yay
yeah okay do you even hear it it should
be quiet but i hear birds do you guys
hear birds
your birds
okay yeah birds yes and that they're
going like twenty three twenty three
three three
okay okay okay hello i'm starving over
here alone to say
[Music]
i'm one of the point of views uh how did
i do this
[Music]
merry christmas i started a thing a
little bit early don't tell the others
i just came in there and they saw that
this was like uh all covered in snow
look
look snow
guys
[Music]
okay okay
i'm kind of loud okay okay
i'm a little quiet wait wait wait wait i
can't i can't make myself louder than
this
i'll just scream all the time then
that's okay
uh
wait is this the right microphone wait
that's not the right microphone
yeah okay that makes sense
oh my oh my oh my god yeah sorry i i
wasn't on the vr microphone it's the
first time i'm doing it like this i'm
not used to it
you guys hear me differently now
it should be um
really bad quality
you hear okay okay at least it's louder
okay okay
i'm gonna try my best to capture
everyone today look first look at my
outfit mine my outfit is um
it's it's a cute sexy santa but it's
like with the with the new party dress
like the hairstyle from the party dress
i don't know why i'm bugging out so much
right now
and you see the the sexy neckline yeah
let me
calibrate myself
calibrating
okay
maybe i don't know oh god hunchback how
are you looking
i tried so hard to calibrate properly
yes
okay we gotta do it like oh i look cute
okay let's go to the others
okay
uh
[Music]
oh my god i'm feeling a little bit
motion sick today which is weird because
usually i don't feel motion sick um
there's christmas decorations up
everywhere
so even in this room oh i can quietly
hear the others already they're uh i
think over at the bar
getting drunk already
look at the christmas lights wow
and oh yahoo is wearing a christmas hat
[Music]
oh they're all having fun over there i
think
are they
[Music]
hello oh my god
yes
[Music]
hello hi
hi gooda
[Music]
oh
i showed you my mistletoe please respond
oh okay you want a kiss
brony
[Music]
oh my
god hey let me put down the camera right
here
or or maybe
maybe
[Music]
oh
do you guys know this feeling when
you're at a party and there's so much
going on and you feel awkward because
you don't know
who to talk to i know exactly
[Music]
but i don't think it is
i don't want to hold the trick i want to
help the kids get drunk let's get
[Music]
that was
[Applause]
your nose should have been glowing
[Music]
there's presents there's presents to
open later not this
presents did you give me your hands
braces
i like presents but there's more so the
candle is nice there's never like a
piece
don't do that that's really nice
[Music]
are you going to cali's room no way
that's not kelly's room
[Music]
pretty lights
i stole cali's drink i'm sorry
you left it with me
thank you for holding this for me i
really appreciate that
thank you kiara i didn't want it to go
to waste yeah what can i say
what can i say
it's me on christmas listen man
why did they do this to me
you look so sick
it's always the sexy outfits it's always
the sexy rules of the play
the shortest way to set the outfit
yeah that pose it fits perfectly they
should have given you like santa pants
like really bad
oh yeah yeah then it would be perfect
you know
oh my god
excuse me that
didn't mean to give you a fight
what's in that drink
you know a lot about them
[Music]
yeah it's something too strong i think
a little too strong oh well
oh goodness the only alcohol that i've
drunken in the past five years is a
christmas punch santa we'll see what uh
i could do okay
look at her being beautiful
doesn't break
oh oh kelly kelly
kelly let me do like a full body uh
thingy
from bottom to the to the top
delicious
the helicopter in your heads
nice spanky kelly
[Music]
let me do a full body thingy on you i
wanna do like uh
i wanna i wanna show your your outfit
[Music]
cute
[Applause]
yeah i already went there it's so pretty
i love i love how my room looks now
oh this one
oh oh my
god
[Music]
um
yeah yes
of course it has been snowing a lot
recently
no no no
that
must be the gross glochna the biggest
mountain in australia
gross glockner how do you say it gross
globalization
it means big bells
oh here
is so good
[Music]
i'll take the cookie i'll take the
cookies
she ate it
and i haven't done a full body shot on
you yet let me go from back
oh
[Music]
oh yummy that looks really good can i
have a bite too
[Music]
no
i stay still nice feel yeah something
was something was in the cookie and um
all the money bring it up for you i'm
censoring it for you it's okay it's a
sensitive spot
[Music]
that's right yeah i've got this cookie
now i run this town baby where am i
oh
[Music]
that's weird
even when i go to self wait let me let
me try to fix this chat
one second what happens if i close the
stream cameras
i don't know what you guys will see if i
close it but just give me a moment
[Music]
oh my god what did i do
my drinks gone okay
you guys see now oh
just my view okay
[Music]
how does it work again
settings
i swear to god i'm gonna make you pay
for that um
come on
it's not up to you to tell me that it's
time that i've stopped
[Music]
is
where was the elevator again
[Music]
oh
that's why i don't see myself
i will believe i will give you a signal
and then you all go to ten
[Music]
don't press any buttons yet but you can
press the button for here winter world
not yet but
okay now i want you guys to count to ten
starting
[Music]
okay
nine
ten
[Music]
oh
oh i see it looks normal to me but when
i do like when in front of the mirror i
couldn't see myself and with selfie
camera i can also not see myself
oh you could try to do the respawn oh
wait i can see myself again
now it works again in the mirror i
didn't see myself
[Music]
oh
sorry guys this is so awkward i'm so
sorry
i'm so why is there an egg
[Laughter]
so
[Music]
let's just let's just um look around huh
we're on a date oh look at what bales is
doing she's all alone too we're making
the biggest destruction
oh
[Music]
no
how do you guys do that
[Music]
yes
oh that looks nice it looks cozy
[Music]
let me put you here
no i want to push you here
sit no stay there
stay there why does it always come with
me
stop coming with me
[Music]
damn it
it used to work like this
[Music]
dmca incoming
the lyrics how did you make
[Music]
i'm on top of the world oh my god why
this makes me so dizzy what the oh
i was on top of cronies from the
[Music]
everyone will have to
look at them play like little children
cute
oh what what what
[Music]
what happened
why does it still come with me
[Music]
oh my god
okay this is how we're gonna do it now
tonight
yeah
mirror is here
before do you know how to like i can't i
can't pick up the
camera anymore
it's like fixed at a fixed position i
don't know if it's the same as last time
[Music]
um
i picked it up again
let me look
where is the money emoji it pizza
just you know oh there's my money
everywhere day-to-day life you know
we could do a nice vlog in my life
[Music]
yes always always ready for that wait
let me
[Music]
wow
let it go
[Applause]
[Music]
oh you know what you get for christmas
tiara for being such a good phoenix
nicole
[Music]
small cali small cali handing out cold
to everyone you get a piece of coal oh
and you also get a piece of coal fauna
[Music]
oh
this one the finished sauna oh no this
is
yes oh my god i think i can oh my god
whoa let's get hot
sweaty
don't watch that wear the blinds okay
don't look guys we're in the sauna
oh the camera came with me again i i
left you there for a reason
oh thank you
i can
[Music]
oh
please it's hot of course
of course ladies
oh my god i'm so down here
[Music]
except for bae she's naked
oh my god
yeah
i'm so sorry i'm such a bad camera man
i'm so bad at this
[Music]
thank you it's hard to handle it's
getting pretty full in here
[Music]
[Applause]
there she comes oh wow depends on how
good your bait is
oh it's my it's my but you know the
perfume commercials where the ladies
come out and they're like
[Music]
this is a slimy shark
but let's see did you see that video
where um like a shark is like attacking
a human in the water thank you and then
the human he turns the shark around uh
so that the the nose of the shark is
like turning
downwards
and and and that way i had full control
over the shark can i do that with you
no not tommy wraps
like turning the cat tonight
wait a second
you think shark people are told no
no no but when you attack someone could
have must take control of you
so that you don't hurt people
good i'm so bad at this camera thing
oh my god being so bad
i can't pick it up anymore
what are they doing
oh my god
you just gotta squeeze squeeze harder
okay i squeeze it okay i'm in the water
oh good good good
good good out of the ogra of the water
what is the wisdom
[Music]
yes
that is the wisdom having no wisdom
that's the real wisdom
right hey is that mistletoe
that didn't
yeah
i'm gonna jump again
[Music]
pants girl that's really classy
i like that
boy why did you put pants on me
oh i just noticed you have those
shoes
you have the elf shoes that are like
they go like upwards at their tippy-toes
[Music]
monster
blue seeds
i'm swimming
in the
since finland is known for their lakes
awesome
australia
at least finland
we don't have an ocean
sad oh
[Music]
it's fine yeah
because you're hydrodynamic i get it
[Music]
hmm
are you a skater boy who says see you
later boy
she wasn't pretty enough for him
now he's a superstar slamming
if i knew how this camera would work
[Music]
i am going to do dog
to
formally apologize for my
terrible camera skills
i'm sorry
i deeply humbly apologize
i will try better
i will try harder
sometimes i can pick it up and sometimes
i can't it's so weird
let's look up them are you broken
oh no why why'd you guys see that
nothing's having a great time thanks
chad thanks chad thank you
i really want to go ice skating too in
real life
oh
[Music]
thank you
oh hell yeah
[Music]
um
hello yellow
get low on christmas
christmas
[Applause]
[Music]
oh yeah sure of course anything from my
fans
yeah of course
you betcha come here
come a little closer
there you go capturing the good stuff
we're washing my hat i figured you'd say
that get low
get low
i want to get low too
oh my god
let's get low
oh good eye is over there alone why is
she always alone
why is she always alone
[Music]
thank you
oh she already knew where we would go in
the future oh it's a taco
[Music]
[Applause]
cute tacos
wait
[Music]
yes i guess i'll do one too
all right over here we got the snow
pieces if you guys want to add some
additional snow pieces to your snowman
we got a whole army here
uh
snowman cool oh my god i'm already
drawing oh no oh how can how can i get
rid of no idea uh
is there an eraser
i don't think there is or an eraser why
is
let's draw from the other side
[Music]
okay
i will make a snowman for you guys
can i like
wait i'm left-handed
[Music]
special eyes
it's not exactly on top of it
um
but that's okay
can we make bunny ears
let's make pickled ass standby
[Music]
thank you i'm drawing pickled as senpai
yeah you gotta look at it from a
distance
thank you oh sure
[Music]
[Applause]
is it time limited i don't know maybe
there's a limit on the angle something's
wrong it's disappearing oh don't take
them
it's working
[Music]
but it's disappearing
i tried
cute is there carrots
carrots
i don't think there's any carrots
there's hats though hats
she's bringing me a hat
oh what's yours what's that
oh long nose 3d 3d effect bam
what is that though
what is that
oh wow
that's art
i can't read does anybody else dollar
is she disappearing still yeah she's
disappeared
oh my oh my god what is that
what is that
wow that's beautiful indeed it looks
like a sled
[Music]
what is this cute
yeah
my
wait is yours disappearing too for those
gradually or is it
not it's kind of disappearing yeah okay
well um beautiful things don't last
forever i guess
oh
cute
oh nice hat nice hat
oh wait is that oh she got a sign
and big boing boings oh callie
oh those are heads oh my god those are
hands oh really sure oh really i'm not
sure about that why are the hands in the
front where the boobs should be i mean
because she's holding her sides down
i'm being killed by my shadow self oh
boy
that's what it is oh no
oh no
hey what'd you just draw there
what did you just draw is that what is
that what did you just
oh oh mittens thank you sana thank you
more mittens for my hands
are you drawing something cursed
no
let me take a look
oh that's actually really not cursed
that it's cute
that is adorable it has like pian eyes
but
[Music]
wait why is everyone drawing bunnies
is that supposed to be a bunny
oh
true okay can you stand right next to it
we'll compare it
yeah yeah 100
you need a ribbon in the middle
[Music]
oh i still have a pen in my mind
oh we can draw in the air too who is
that that's you
it's me i want to scribble
they also sometimes just
bump against your furniture and your
walls
yes i'm trying really hard not to bump
into it but yes
yes i do
where's my pen huh i lost my pen where's
my
[Music]
i'll draw something
i will draw on you
hi you got to stay still though hi
all right
[Music]
i'll give you big long twin tails
and
the things that you always wanted
[Music]
i need to switch the camera i don't know
how uh
it doesn't switch it doesn't switch it
stay good
we all knew this game i'm sorry
i got it i got it i got it there you go
hi john just needs to be a good angle i
am like that like that
hi
[Music]
okay pen is where did it go i lost it
again
it was in the geometry of your hand
okay uh
let's let's get painted on
i'll i'll stand uh here
[Music]
okay
you're gonna be my live model
are you ready i'm so ready
[Music]
camera good
yes
draw me like your french girls
i think i've been playing too much uh
mario kart because i think i defaulted
to making it look like wario
oh wait that's not gonna work anyway
there's your hat with a w for winner let
me see
can't believe it
w arms
i'm just worried sometimes
in this model
[Music]
wait i wish you could take my camera how
this is oh it works oh my
god welcome wario are there's my hands
this i just i just
uh yes no they're little stubby hands
that drive really fast and drift somehow
in that stupid little yellow cart that i
just can't get the room
are you practicing mario kart for the
tournament
i am hilarious i am for the past three
days or something i need i need you and
enough to
win for yeah
[Music]
on the yoshi island where she stays
behind and then gets all the way to the
top even though she was last place
no
that was so good super advanced that was
she's really good at keeping her cool
yeah like
yeah she's i admire that i gotta do that
keep the cool
the reaction cool yeah
yes thank you for drawing on me
thank you
um
[Music]
wow
is
again thank you for joining my song what
was that again you need a song name yeah
simple and clean from kingdom hearts oh
yeah i sang it a couple times in my
cutout okay that's right that's right
that's why i know it
dang that is i'm glad you know
[Music]
you're making a pickle are you making a
pickle
i was gonna say what are peccary's
friends called because
pokemon wait let me show the chat oh
that's over here
i'm so sorry i ripped it out
i ripped it out
[Music]
i immediately recognize them
they look cute
that's a good description i think you
have to look it up
[Music]
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes um
that looks
going on here she's making a pickle like
uh
[Music]
yeah right oh some part of it is
disappearing now it's a little bit less
cursed i think oh no is it disappearing
i thought it was disappearing
eventually
[Laughter]
that was what guda drew on me
beautiful
yeah that's pecora
oh what's left of her
oh my god so many scribbles this is so
cool what it who did all of this
who did all of this
so messy
of course i'm the one who's head so
messed up
thank you oh my god but i want to go
chill in the cage
wow this is art right this is what they
would sell in the museum or not sell but
show off in the museums
what do you call this contemporary art
what is contemporary eye
[Music]
i love this i love this uh location by
the way craps to
the creators
it's gorgeous
i like how it's like a really
serene and calm
snow area
i would totally go here for a vacation
by the way everybody me and nina have a
song cover coming out on the 22nd
just uh
putting some ads here i'm just gonna
walk don't forget about it guys don't
forget about it
oh they're still singing this
let me try the hat on
[Music]
look i got a new hat on top of my santa
hat
oh that's my that's my door
[Music]
merry christmas
merry christmas merry christmas
[Music]
thanks appreciate that
when we look at chats
[Music]
chad you want to see me dance
i don't really have good music
need some music
can you twerk two sparks yes you can
i forgot how spikes goes how to spark
school again sing for me
jumping around having fun except it's us
there's the keanu frogmoves
but as
well yeah
[Music]
how long the seasons are
i believe that we're anime girls
crazy yeah he had like how many
christmases
enough of that you guys don't want to
see me dancing i know it
you guys want to see the other cute
girls
[Music]
things over here every single episode
all right
[Music]
you took me by surprise crony i still
ain't ready to hear your lies
man they say that time flies imma show
you what that's like when we play fall
guys someday would you like to
collaborate
seriously no hate at that time we can
have a real debate so what do you say
crony my man
[Music]
[Applause]
not
this time but next time you're going to
get me
what happened to callie's drawing no
fall guys
[Music]
sky is tall i mean am i wrong holy
you are so right it's a dome today
off the dome
can i draw something on you small fries
fall guys
take me to mcdonald's and get me a small
fries
wow she's on fire
on fire today okay all i did was drink
some water
what are you drawing crony are you
kidding me
i'm drawing a bear
for yourself a teddy bear yeah a friend
flip you need some friends smile
it's now a reindeer
kitty ball
damn
[Music]
i know
[Applause]
[Music]
wow
i am gone from the selfie camera again
i want to take a selfie
[Music]
they do magic stuff uh there's only one
other note hello hello
[Music]
weird until it is
i think they did this because the
creator is from finland i heard
i heard so the 3d modeler is from
finland and they wanted to recreate
their homeland here and show how
beautiful it is because apparently the
people of finland are very proud of
their country and how cool they got the
sauna they got like reindeers and they
got the northern lights it's beautiful
let's go finland
oh that's a beautiful star yeah
i
[Music]
gingerbread i know the word for
gingerbread too actually what is it
peppa pig
[Music]
sorry
i disappeared again
[Applause]
[Music]
pixel holo ian
glitch that's funny
sparkle oh
wow
[Music]
blueprint nice
okay cool stuff cool stuff yo
but how do i get my model back
damn it
um
[Music]
i i i forgot which one is the front
angle at this point
[Music]
this one
you look like such a shark girl whoa
whoa whoa
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's a snowman that's not a real
person
she doesn't care for that one she goes
for the tree
following this is a documentation
i am who is that guy again from bbc
what was his name again chet
steve no that's not the one i mean
what's his name
david attenborough david
chef oh ronald mcdonald
i see i see okay thanks for that
comparison
okay look whatever whatever
i'm still not there damn
do you know how i can get my body back
you don't know it do you
get that body bag
get my body back
[Music]
no no sorry no
no respawn where do we switch but
recalibrated
[Music]
it's been 84 years man
merry christmas hope has ascended
[Music]
where is everybody where is the oh who's
there
good as good as always alone
this is uh david attenborough from the
babysitte
currently we see a shark it's not
natural habitat grilling soap sausages
oh she has noticed me
[Music]
um sure
thank you so much mate
thank you give me that wiener uh
yes please thank you
that looks a little bit too burnt but
i'll i'll take it
i'll take it
it's the best one is burn
maybe not maybe not completely burnt but
i mean i guess it could be like
something like a blood sausage
i'll take oh i can only take it with a
stick but okay ah
this is no no i want marshmallows i
don't want marshmallows hot chocolate
hot chocolate
is hot chocolate
with marshmallows with marshmallows
yo
if you want hot chocolate let's let's do
it
yeah i'm glitching am i all right let's
go kanpai oh my god help combo yay
[Music]
i was at a christmas market
um it was nice i i drank i drank two
different sorts of punch
and i draw i drank like a orange
children's punch and then i drank a
different different one where was that i
forgot
i forgot how to say it so yummy
and i ate they had they had like a
raclette
so i ordered oracle it was like a bread
with uh with bacon and and fresh
uh
recollect cheese poured on top of it
wow
fancy yeah very fancy
but it was cold as hell over there it
was so cold
oh yummy i want some real honey
uh yes uh christmas markets are so
expensive oh you found the marshmallow
on the stick
marshmallow
i actually i gotta be honest i i'm not
like a huge fan of marshmallows but i i
i like the
the thought of grilling them
what is your wisdom
what are they made of
ah
i think it's like um what is it what's
gelatin
oh oh
i don't know chat might have to tell you
i know that jealousy i know that
gummy bears are made out of the most
disgusting stuff
well because gelatin because gelatin is
made it cart what cartridge cartridge
cardboard cartilage right cartilage what
the is cartilage what is that it's
like
for humans it's like the bone that's in
your ear or like uh
acid and cools it's gelatin oh my god
the hooves of of like yeah
oh my god
[Music]
keratin
if i move like this it won't fall off
the sacrifice to the fireplace oh sit
down
i want to sit next to taco
oh
[Music]
people
it's hot now everybody's here
wow
[Music]
you're wearing a similar dress to me i
didn't see that
yeah it's kind of like make a mix of my
party dress
[Music]
yay
hi girls a sandwich hello i'm the i'm
the
[Music]
i already drank all the hot cocoa i'm
sorry
you drank it though i drank all
[Music]
oh
does anybody have any christmas
[Music]
merry christmas
yeah you guys want to hear it yes
[Music]
uh here's my story
once upon a time
in a snowy village
by the north pole
there was a very large man named santa
claus
a red outfit and a red santa hat and his
only joy in this in this lonely cold
dark and despairing world was to give
presents to the little children
essentially he was the giver of all
things hope related
however hope
that iris is
someone else could not
i don't know
the fact that this
this
gentleman is it here giving away
presents and hope to the children
his reindeer taking him away into the
night
suddenly something very strange happened
it appeared that there was a sabotage to
his sleigh
and some of the reindeer were cut from
their reigns and santa was left to fall
to his death but
who was it that came flying out of the
sky to ride on his reindeer and take the
remaining presents to the children
[Music]
i
again
[Music]
anyone else have any stories
make a story as you go around things
we've used to do them in improv classes
so everybody starts off
someone starts off making a story then
everybody adds like a sentence to the
story
didn't we didn't we do something like
that for uh the last christmas something
similar it was a mad lib oh yeah we
created the story
with the candy g string remember
[Music]
wow
how do we play how do we start it i want
to do it
somebody start
and come up with an intro to the story
so like
just start up a story that you would
write and then
say next and then the next person will
continue the story so who wants to start
does it like a word
[Music]
there was a snowy night and a giant
snowball fell down the mountain and came
to life
and upon its giant head rotated
mistletoe and
large lifeless eyeballs
and a tendency to consume the flesh of
humans
and suddenly
poisoning up
suddenly
it grew very muscular snowy arms
a very
thin leg
and started marching towards the city
next
it began its slow yet motivated march
toward the city however it need not walk
because after a while something akin to
a ceiling fan emerged from its head as
it slowly was pulled upward into the sky
and made its way towards the waiting
homes of many children
and families across the nation
next up sana
okay
the
helicopter
it did realized that
its body anymore
because nobody is perfect
the body fell off
from the fat so as a helicopter as a
helicopter
the body popped off
and landed
on top
nice
the body continued moving on its own
without the head suddenly remaining
sentient on
excuse me
is this lore
[Laughter]
can't continue at the end
after yeah
yeah
oh can someone paraphrase the story for
me real quick
oh god all right so there was a sweet
little snowball that like came down
the mountain and then it turned into a
huge monster that looks like crony and
then it has a helicopter head and then
it came off and it plopped down on the
city and then it's body separated from
its head and now it's getting ready to
attack the city um
[Music]
an attempt to get revenge upon the head
the body looked itself in the mirror and
realized
then i never skipped leg day
[Music]
tell us your story it marched on
to the gym
to
not skip leg day but saw
saw itself in the mirror they thought
oh man
so beautiful
and they opened their feet
oh yeah
[Music]
yes open their mouths
it opens its mouth
it opens its mouth and the
and then
inside of the mouth
appears a little fairy a little fairy
dressed in santa claus close
and the fairy jumps out out of the mouth
and looks at uh not crowley the the
monster or whatever looks at the monster
and says
you are beautiful no matter what they
say
and words cannot bring you down
next mummy
[Music]
uh the santa ferry also reminds the
monster of how it has lost its way
and so it abandons its lands for revenge
takes up a modest job
[Music]
[Laughter]
and then it gets to
a familiar home and then
oh
[Music]
the big monster that turned into a new
cave
and then he turned a new lead are you
printing something and then he saw
he saw
cookies
very delicious looking stack of cookies
and milk
couldn't he couldn't
couldn't help but take a bite of the
cookie
the cookie was poison
yeah forget your happy ending
so he died
and
everything is all better again
what
was it better for
[Applause]
i'm not surprised
[Music]
the tree is helping me clean this up we
gotta get these balls out of here
all right
[Music]
i ain't got no balls
i'm sorry
[Music]
i think the ball pushed us away
how does she do it how does she keep on
doing it
[Music]
is
come around
[Music]
but every present is labeled so we'll go
uh i guess
i guess we'll start
merry christmas
merry
[Music]
baby
oh
[Music]
anyway this is for me bae this is my
special ornament for you i made it
special for you oh just the perfect
let me tell the chat really quick okay
oh we did a secret santa where's the
camera we did a secret santa where
everybody uh everybody was assigned one
person an en so there's 11 of us and uh
everybody made a design a sketch for an
ornament to be put on the tree and so
this is bay's ornament right here and
everybody uh made and designed one of
these for each one of us so cali made
this one for bank yeah
[Music]
oh yeah
it's a good idea
i could tell this was kind of callie
though
yeah
oh nice
it looks perfect look at how beautiful
okay
it's amazing all right next yeah
[Music]
inside
[Applause]
[Music]
who do you think made that one
it's kind of hard to guess huh
i have absolutely no idea
who could cute
i'm i made
[Applause]
[Music]
that's so cute
um
[Music]
yeah put it right next to the nightmare
fuel
[Music]
such a cute idea
oh
[Music]
wow
concept inside oh who do you think made
this one
i mean inside space
inside and then we're going to rotate it
i don't know how you made this one
right
[Music]
yeah
i said the camera did you make this did
you make this um
no i didn't i wasn't me
okay i was like can other people guess
it was it ina was it inaudible
[Music]
wait i can't woke up
sorry guys i'm having issues with the
camera right now to keep on switching
sorry guys shall we guys you're
[Music]
it cute the the face looks like the
paddock
oh
[Music]
oh no
did kiara make this no no i can't make
something so cute no
shush your art is adorable
thank you
cute
[Music]
no
no oh
yes please do it is your
[Music]
[Applause]
merry christmas
[Music]
[Applause]
is
let's see what's inside
oh wow
[Music]
oh
chad's seeing all these beautiful
ornaments i'm already feeling bad about
the one i made
i went for something fancy realistic
yeah
i didn't make it oh babies are so cute
[Music]
no i didn't make it
[Applause]
[Music]
snow globes are indeed nice
i like them too
[Music]
another box over here
looks like blue monster
oh
my god
[Music]
wow
it is
[Music]
oh that's true it's not rainbow just
make your rainbows a blue glass of stuff
cute you're gonna put it on oh yeah who
made it who made it
who made it
okay
no it wasn't me
who could have made this beautiful
little thing
[Music]
ami
no it wasn't me
me me me me me with me
[Music]
[Applause]
i was already worried about when i saw
everyone else's i thought mine was so
lame
[Music]
supposed to be like super glamorous yeah
honestly crony you you're so round you
could be your christmas ornament
[Music]
[Laughter]
put yourself up on the tree yeah
yes
[Music]
i guess
oh
[Music]
adorable here's a nice beard i wonder
how long it took him to grow that beard
1 000 years
and then it's cotton candy
is it fake
it could be a cream flavor is it i don't
know
it looks like cream
[Music]
yeah i could see that
yum yum you made this one whipped cream
oh my god where is
[Music]
there's not many people left
yeah there's not that many people left
so
[Music]
i know
you
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh god i opened the box by accident i
opened the box by accident here
oh she's a look don't look closer
[Music]
right
this should be santa instead would you
want to replace him
looking up into the beautiful night
suspicious you want us you want to
replace him with this no no no real
suspicious
i i i would like to take a day off on
christmas thank you oh
um
[Music]
just to relax sorry i opened one by
accident i'm so sorry
okay please me know how to close it
uh i don't think you can close it but uh
could i just close your eyes you didn't
see it what's in the pocket
[Music]
open the box
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
getting a good look at it
damn that's beautiful
i want that in real life can we sell
that as merchandise
[Music]
intimidating
watson did you like this
no i didn't make it
no
someone really talented must have made
that one mummy was the last one i think
no
oh i haven't really been paying
attention
whoa you made it
[Music]
still not finished work in progress
right
[Music]
very cool i would buy that ornament
everything
so yeah we need a whole set
get the clothes up here bubba bae is
graphic design your passion perhaps
thank you for the interview thank you
very much
is this a watson
like i handled mostly everybody's um
like stuff oh then i just moved this i
handled everybody's like uh sketches and
stuff and i gave them to the modelers
but i haven't seen this one so it's a
really really surprised
[Music]
the pasta
i think i know too
thank you really
handmade oh yeah it's crunchy throw it
like that
into boiling water and you get some
fresh pasta with no effort yeah your
hair is super soft yeah maybe the center
is just a big cheese
[Music]
merry christmas
not many people left
very cute
oh yeah so i know who made mine
looks like a me box
okay two cali here we go
open
[Music]
give me give me the sesame ah give me
this hold on
oh county made basically oh
[Music]
this is very well crafted is this from
sauna
oh no
really watson you made this
i made it
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh i fell down
oh only mine is left
yeah
hang it up on the tree hang it up
[Music]
man last year we decorated a minecraft
tree and now we're decorating a real
tree yeah this is an update
this is like rtx update
turn on the rtx yo
[Music]
wait who's left who didn't i don't i'm
not sure
there's only one person left right there
[Music]
oh my god i love it
look at that little christmas chicken
[Music]
irish made someone's too right
i was you
[Music]
wow
ah here okay okay big space right in the
middle
here in the middle here
here
yeah that's perfect
[Music]
beautiful
this is so wonderful
merry christmas
many christmas
[Music]
the freaking maybe there's a way to
move the marker stuff okay give me one
second yes
i'm sorry it wasn't me
of course not i thought
of course not i believe
[Music]
where do i put the camera here
drunk aunt on the phone she's swimming
through air
[Music]
yeah you could be that's all right we
could do it with that we could do it
with the camera even though it looks
scuffed in the mirror
[Music]
i know you didn't mean it maybe you
could sit down
i didn't know how to sleep decided
[Music]
oh callie's in the stream
yeah the tree looks fun
[Music]
let me fix the camera
the sun is so small sunny you can fit in
the middle right here or not on the tree
yeah
[Music]
nice
all right
[Music]
merry christmas
help
what's the number you got to call
ghostbusters no no
[Music]
thank you guys thank you for making the
ornaments and stuff she did
[Music]
yeah and we actually i have a small
announcement before our big announcement
so we can gather in front of the tree
like just like we were um actually
this vr chat world will be available
publicly for every community to use
[Music]
so you guys can come explore the studio
the halloween map the winter wonderland
and of course you know the default map
and we'll push updates when when uh we
need to update you know maybe council
can get some rooms or something someday
huh
yeah
friends there so hang out with your buds
and um we have another announcement is
it time yet actually fake announcements
i mean we're a little early we got you
10 minutes no problem
should we no
[Music]
oh god oh god no not me please i don't
even know uh the exact uh
[Music]
whole live title
home live english has created
a
special song cover of the classic
christmas song the 12 days of christmas
[Music]
in 20 minutes i believe that the link
will be up so you guys can watch the
premiere of it has all uh 11 of us and
uh yeah look forward to it today
[Music]
i have an announcement too
are releasing a song cover together on
my channel on the 22nd uh like it
depends on your time zone but for most
time zones is the 22nd december
wednesday we're also doing a stream
about it so yeah please check it out the
reservation is going to be up about 24
hours before
[Music]
yeah
it's our way of giving back to the
audience yeah
yeah yeah give back to you
and special presents that are going to
be uploaded to my channel
so please check them out there are three
of them they're a series um and also
during my christmas party um which is
happening
about
uh it's happening tomorrow it's more
than 24 hours though
during that party i'm going to uh give
you guys a small visual preview of an
original song i've been working on with
someone here
please welcome be there to check out
check it out it's gonna be cool
um
it's cool it's a cool song that's your
hand
[Music]
merry christmas everyone happy holidays
happy holidays
[Music]
i guess i just wanted to say um
i'm i'm really glad to have my friends
here
[Applause]
we can have what no and i hope we can
have fun more fun next year
[Music]
a huge shout out to the developer and
people and the vr chat team who have
been working like day after day punching
in hours getting everything working and
looking really cool and working well
thank you guys for giving this present
to us and also the community yeah thank
you team thank
[Music]
thanks to you my dude
i'm really glad you guys have fun yeah
the year is closing out and you know
last year we closed out with only the
five of us and now there's seven of us
so i'm really glad that we could do this
together and you know there's this whole
week there's a bunch of cool streams you
guys are doing uh so you know you guys
in the audience make sure to check them
out everybody's doing christmas streams
and stuff yeah so make sure to check
them out and happy holidays happy new
year thank you everybody for watching
[Music]
bye
[Applause]
bye iris
[Music]
much
oh
[Music]
do
you