ho
[Music]
ho hello and welcome to uh our Christmas
video of the 8th 8th
December hello today I think Merry
Christmas is the first
collaboration uh we didn't have any
collaboration videos yet so that's
special are you excited video I'm very
excited I I invited L cuz I wanted to do
a special video with
you thank you for inviting I'm very
happy oh no ignore my USB noises uh I
have some cable
problems should be should be fine oh oh
let me test this uh as you can probably
see we're going to draw something we're
going to draw Christmas ornaments onto
these templates with a timer there's a
time limit yeah H only the fastest yeah
fast but we're going to draw for each
other so after we're done we present our
Christmas ornaments to each other so RDA
is drawing one for me for my tree I
guess and I'm drawing one for for her
tree yay that's such a cute idea I love
it it'll be a nice surprise at the very
end so I'm looking for look at my bowl
yeah I will not I will look over here my
tablet is here my tracking will probably
not work when I'm looking over there but
that's okay so are you ready L I am born
ready of course you are you are the
artist after all oh yeah top right is's
ball uh bottom left is my ball okay so
here we go three two one
St yes we have how many minutes again uh
four minutes
okay okay it's already beginning do you
already have an idea of what you want to
draw yeah I know exactly what I want to
do M I'm
excited I also thought a little bit
about what I want to draw o I wonder if
they can already tell what this is going
to
be I wonder color
change of course you will have to hang
this up on your tree afterwards I don't
know if you have
if you send me yeah do I bu I made my
tree on the 1st of November
oh wait what Christmas what you already
have a tree standing in your home yeah
since the since the 1 of November but
it's a fake tree
right oh yeah yeah yeah I have a those
fake ones actually I don't think I ever
saw like in Japan people selling real
trees like Christmas trees only Fake
Plastic Trees really there really I've
never seen them oh you you never seen
them okay yeah no wait my color isn't
working wait why is it not
working fast fast fast my color isn't
working oh something changed here oh
there we go there we go some setting
suddenly changed to different option
okay this is already very obvious you
made your tree already no I don't even
know if I want to you know have a
tree oh
why M because it takes up so much
space a but it do be looking nice right
but this is the best thing of Christmas
decorating things around yeah I guess I
have
to I know it's a little Annoying that
when you have to store
everything back this annoying part oh
does this does this look good I don't
know if this looks good
don't worry oh we have half the time uh
so now it's already 2 minutes pass what
yeah oh gosh not so much time SS bad I
hope you will not be like disappointed
in what I draw for you I think you're
better so disappointed you're better
drawing fast you
know better than
me what would you do for Christmas what
will I do for Christmas is yeah uh I
think you know I'll stream like a little
bit but also my family is coming
over sure oh cute yeah my mom and my
brother will probably come over and
we'll just cook together eat
together
okay what are you going to do I'm going
back oh and oh yeah right yeah I'm going
I'm I'm going to go back to my family as
well how long how long I think like a
couple of weeks
Ooh Yeah couple of weeks O So New Year's
also yeah yeah yeah New Year's
also
exciting are you any do you have any
plans for New Year H yeah New Year I'm
thinking of celebrating with my uh
friends so
uh Christmas with my family and New
Year's with my
friends do you still have a lot of
friends back home that you want to visit
of them yeah some of but a lot of my
friends also moved away
unfortunately
yeah they all in different countries
now how do I make this more oh God time
is up I was how do I make this more that
specific time is
over a okay no this is
fine this is fine I did my
best okay we'll reveal it to each other
first I'll look at yours and then you
look at mine okay cuz I have to okay
send it to you on
Discord um okay I'm I'm going I'm
excited I'm excited 3 two one a
cute of course it's a can't
y it's perfect it's so round yeah right
they're so round I love hugging them
squeezing them cute until they can't
breathe anymore oh no no no no love it
oh it has like little dangling legs
hanging down yes cute cute thank you I
love it I I would love like a Christmas
chicken uh no kfp Christmas chicken
ornament from my tree like an actual
proper one made out of glass or
something me too
uh wait okay soorry I have to send it to
her on Discord so it looks
funny here I want to see I want to see
there you go this is what I did
course well what do you
think uh do you want my Hest opinion
yeah
H uh I wouldn't I wouldn't hang this
bowl on my tree why you don't have to
eat
[Laughter]
it but I appreciate it thank you you
know what that is you know what the
topping is can you see it oh yeah you're
so yeah of course say it out loud say it
say it pineapple pizza
pineapple M yummy my
favorite you're welcome n of course you
know my taste so
well thank you n for doing this with me
thank you hope you guys enjoyed day
eight of the Advent calendar continue
watching the other ones too and sometime
there might be all a solo video right
yeah
so thank you Merry Christmas
bye-bye Merry Christmas byebye