[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
sorry
i was stretching
[Music]
okay
i'm gonna cry
well well it is it is one of the last
key arsenal weapons and
i feel i feel like i have um
a duty to use it you know
yeah
[Laughter]
it would be
a waste or
you know it would be
sad if i were not to use it when someone
went out of the way to not only draw
this thing but also animate it
so who am i to say no to that
i guess it's inspired by because i said
i think it was my idea originally anyway
[Laughter]
didn't i say that
did i say was it me
it's gonna block a lot of the screen
uh
what if me and my leg go
a little bit over here
i
i don't think we can take the game
seriously
if i have my leg up like
i don't need spikes on my shoes this is
this is powerful enough
are you doubting the power of my lanky
bunk
did that hurt didn't it i can hurt you
even more if i wanted to
yeah this leg
um was provided to you by jt
aka
jt mations
um
thank you for cursing
all of us
i'm sure i'm sure the chat is very
grateful
that you have made this a reality what i
was thinking about adding another leg to
but i think it it gets a little bit
sensitive
let me show you
oh my god i'm moving everything wait
no
oh my body
so it would um
look like this
[Laughter]
this is how i am at a roller coaster i
don't raise my arms no i raise my legs
and i go like wow
wow
no actually no i hate roller coasters
um welcome everybody kiki
welcome to the stream um
so is this how
this how it's gonna be today
oh wait oh wait
this is how i am at a roller coaster
um
so today on today's episode of takanashi
kiana and yakuza zero we are
um
finishing the game
[Laughter]
the story end is waiting for us and
wha yeah i told you
yeah i mean don't blame me for
suggesting having both legs up
all right i mean if i move to the side
you won't see the other leg much
yeah so
[Laughter]
who should we blame
well i mean the two like uh idea just
came from i think sea foam boy and then
the the legs itself came from gt
jt nation so blame those people
too distracting
i don't know why why why what's so
distracting about this is it me
all right i'll go away here have have
fun
i leave my legs over there
i mean i gotta be somewhere
right
you're gonna be somewhere
i have an idea i have an idea
now stay with me for a while
stay with me for a while
stay with me
do you know what i'm doing
[Laughter]
i guess that doesn't work
it looks like it looks like a butt
oh i'm so flexible i turned around uh on
my on my bottom half of my body
um yeah that's that's my butt
i'm dancing welcome
hi guys i'm gonna
dance for you today um i'm gonna dance
hinotori
uh let me show you the kiki kick now
this is gonna this is gonna be a slow
motion kikkity kick so
oh
it didn't quite go
as i thought it would i i kicked so
strongly that i dislocated my leg
and my hip and everything but here here
it can it can kick on itself it can
rotate on its own
don't need any help
so um yeah
ah one more time
beautiful we're back to normal beautiful
this is normal this is normal now
[Laughter]
oh let me let me erase my
hands because otherwise it would look
weird now this looks perfectly normal
this looks perfect this is how all
things are supposed to be
is this why you're in constant pain
probably this could this could explain a
lot of things but why did the doctors
never notice that my
bottom parts were the wrong way around
man
it does look perfectly like a butt
though the black panty part it's
wonderful
all right well so
i guess i guess the leg
will have to go
i guess it it it would
kind of
ruin
the whole
mood today as i think it's going to be a
serious episode
um i do have some other stuff
now i already used something for the for
the thumbnail so
since we actually got some more things
recently
um
i won't use
the same as the thumbnails just so that
we can get
as much as possible out there we used
the legs a little bit so now
i have something else that i
haven't tried out yet
no um
this this will need some setting up too
this is going to be
um an invention
by eden exile and it's called
the schnitzel nader
[Laughter]
i'm
i'm not sure how it works we have to try
it out
is there a sound to this no no no no no
no it's not okay so we're gonna add oh
no
it disappeared
i did not loop it
it's it comes in two parts i'm i have to
assemble it you know
there we go
wow okay that's a bit too big
probably just like this oh
is this how it's supposed to look like
like this
oh
[Music]
book
well then let me change my clothes
uh
i guess
i guess we're gonna go with this
and here i am back again
oh my arm is a little bit darker than
the rest of my skin tone
i think i can fix that though
this this also takes up so much space
ah
would be too small
this takes up a ton of space man
but when am i gonna use it if not today
this knot is taking some too much space
huh
what what
leg was better
no they both take up so much
actually the leg took up less space than
this
put back the leg
what if we do both
wait which leg is the right one
transform here we go no this is not
that's not this is this is it
um
welcome
welcome i am perfectly uh prepared for
today i am armed and legged
[Laughter]
funny
um
we have another one
the final fantasy boss
excuse me
i mean i guess that's cool
i guess that that's a cool thing right
we have we have i have something that
might be
not so
not so intrusive
here
this is this is just
just me strangling one of those
screaming chickens
yeah that works oh that grip in
that hand you see that grip
holy
[Laughter]
[Music]
i think i'll go with this one
sorry sorry everything else i i will try
to find a use for you
somewhere else so
okay
now
to the
actual business serious seriousness now
oh i once again have not ended the game
properly
so
yeah we're not gonna
see everything
again we're just gonna exactly
continue where we left off
but we have to
do something here
the legs for the ring fit stream
uh
i i guess
i i suppose i i guess
it's anyway are you guys ready meena
don't be like damasca please show the
cutscene again
uh
you want to see the cutscene again why
did you not see it last time
i can do the following how do i get out
of this
i can restart the game and then we will
probably be able to see it again
how do i
uh
okay
should be fine because we basically
saved right before the cutscene
okay
let's do this
let's finish yakuza 0
today
[Music]
10th anniversary projection
there we go does this look okay yeah
okay
all right
continue
because also
it's go time
chapter 16 proof of love
where is where is kfb's proof of love
it's you guys being here every day right
that's your proof of love
she's regaining her sight
as i have predicted
correctly
[Music]
i need
oh i forgot the tissues but i'm not
gonna cry
[Music]
but it was too late
my
[Music]
um
foreign
not
really i was never able to do it
in her voice too not only in the things
she says
foreign
[Music]
what did she just stumble over there was
nothing on the ground
[Music]
um
let's eat first all right this is kind
of where we left off last time
this is it
she claims she's smiling around but her
eyes are telling a different story
better take it slow for her
okay oh no no escort please we're just
going to uh takoyaki where is takoyaki
over there okay slowly slowly
no very slowly
yes we're going extra slow
oh come on
just take my hand then
he would snuggle
come with me
did that happen because i was too far
away or no
this happens
randomly
um
[Music]
get
you're gonna fall down again in three
two
[Music]
yes so many people
foreign
and make takoyaki at home and get cozy
no
doesn't that sound wonderful really
they're gonna make me walk around this
block again oh my god in this
case
in this place really
oh my god oh sorry
you're good
it's to take me um one hour
so um
how are you guys
[Music]
we're getting closer
almost there
oh my god we're almost there don't fall
down
oh my god can you guys go in
oh
[Music]
i was thinking of that
one place
i think
yeah yeah
thought sagaba would be sitting there
for a second
[Music]
oh it's autumn
that's beautiful
i really like the cut scenes man
[Music]
that's korean
she's doing her best dude
oh okay
oh
sweet
already done eating
foreign
um
don't leave her alone don't leave her
alone oh that's a flag that's a flag
that's a flag that's a flag that's a
flag don't leave her alone don't leave
her alone you're stupid
don't leave her alone don't leave her
alone don't leave her alone don't leave
her alone don't leave her alone
you stop it have you not learned from
anything in this whole game huh
have you not learned no okay we are
we're ending the game here today because
i will not leave her
this is a good ending
forever together
hi hi hi you really wanted
takoyaki
ah
this is so stupid
i'm sure something's bad will happen oh
but wait um let me practice in case
something bad happens um we need to warm
up with the man in black
let me warm up
what what the someone
i'm gonna kill you
i'm
[Music]
you don't bring a gun to the street
fight like this you're stupid
do you think
[Music]
that's right
he's using the bat like a nunchuck
[Music]
when do we ever use fog
only use breaker in slugger
[Music]
was this
azure dragon spirit both say your
defense were in heat mode
what does that mean my my defense is
stronger when in heat mode you mean
blocking but i don't block this is about
blocking
those
i block nah
yeah i've been spending the whole game
without blocking
boosts the power of weapon attacks when
using slugger style
uh
any weapons also the one i have by
default the bat
is that the case
yeah
more damage sounds good
that's 50 million let's spend the rest
on fog i guess
wow
what do we have here ah you still get to
never health booth the more you marry up
and we're left with 14 million can we
buy anything with that here probably not
so close 15 million posts
so
the heat costs will rise while you
strike a freeze post damn
bam he's got style
um 50 million 50 million
15 million okay we have two for 15
million that we could get for breaker
i will remember that and also i quickly
i'm going to grab some
food here
oh wait that's still there's nothing
else
no no no i want a restaurant
nothing
except here
beef bowl you don't have that before
hmm
[Music]
okay we're gonna go this way
makoto is waiting
yeah she's she's probably gonna get
abducted no matter how
little or much time i spend
just my feeling i haven't been spoiled
but my feeling is just gonna get
abducted now
i wanna fight one more time give me some
money
and let me fight yeah yeah
nice the top of his hp
get up
[Laughter]
dude
but that won't save you from your
destiny
you know i believe in destiny
and your destiny is getting the out
of my way
so why do we want to eat
i will get food from here
[Music]
let's get some healing
have i ordered everything here before
i have oh well
uh okay that heals
[Music]
that helps me fully
wonderful
oh
[Music]
machine gun kiss was running uh-huh
uh-huh
so abilities for we're gonna spend it on
breaker
or either this one
or
this one launcher counter-attack when an
enemy breaks for your defenses
i won't
remember that this one i think would be
easier for me
after tapping
square
and
right angle repeatedly your enemy
[Music]
okay
we'll try it
wait but that means
that's that's like me just like chilling
somewhere
can they break my my post dough when
i
uh i'm just like frozen they probably
can right
by tapping once only right
squaring triangle
that was some damn fine taco yucky i'll
need some more
piping hot oh
i've got some popping hot takoyaki
and now we're gonna bring it to makoto
she's still there
now
i don't think she's there
she's not there
she's not there anymore
see it you see that little little peak
i guess you can have it now
is
[Music]
at least it was free
it's about time to go meet makoto who
knows why she gave me the slip last
night but she wouldn't do this without
some sort of plan wait it's already the
day at five o'clock
we didn't we'd just we would just
teleport in
okay
well that was fast
they want us to speed run it yeah
okay
uh where
where are we going uh ah empty lot okay
oof it's so far away
let's go
empty long sparky funky wait what was
that
uh
[Music]
eh i can't go
i wanted to check in
oh that's kitty only oh there's so
many enemies
but have we been in there with video
before
we have been like story-wise right and
uh
well what's
[Music]
okay
overkill
[Music]
his beautiful face
nice nice nice
i didn't steal the chicken there's more
than one screaming chicken on this earth
no no i'm not talking about myself
it's before
ah
why do people willingly attack you right
it's a very questionable choice
i was about to say
excuse me
all right all right all right here it is
ah
now we're fine
should be okay
i mean they won't let us go to the
telephone club so what else could i do
it's snowing
i have a bad feeling something's bad
something bad and sad is gonna happen
because when snow suddenly falls
that means something sad is going to
happen
mm-hmm
nice watch
don't read chad okay
uh uh
it's not makoto is it someone else
yeah
[Music]
um
foreign
nowhere
[Music]
um
all right there's a lot of people maybe
i should oh no no no no maybe this oh
[Music]
[Applause]
my god
[Music]
they interrupted my
did you get me i was running around man
okay you little little
[Music]
cleaning up
cleaning up nicely yeah yeah yeah
love me some aoe damage
what about my heat moves man where am i
oh where are my heat moves i don't
see anything activating
[Music]
uh let's do this one
okay and
ah finally
three million what a party
what a party man
um
bring me to my hotel
surah
yeah breaker need training to unlucky
wait i don't have a single
here
oh well i mean it's pretty good anyway
even then
little bunky
[Music]
that is
famous to be the place in tokyo where
all the foreigners go party did you know
that
did you know that
little punky
i'm gonna go
all the way down there
i mean i didn't did never go there for
partying like that but
i know of it
yes i'm back i am apparently turning
into a neutral senpai because i just
love your
beef bowl that much
yeah roppongi looks really
fancy they have a lot of
uh
modern buildings
modern
high buildings
it looks really
fancy at night time
is
[Music]
can't think of anything right now we
only gotta just start it
oh my brain is empty right now sorry
guys i'm hungry though i can tell you
that
uh some should i say wait a second maybe
i should say first at least down
um
i never don't know i have no doughnuts
today but i do have some snacks in the
fridge
most of them are kind of sweet though um
i kind of want something salty
you guys still have some stuff from my
wait i still have the the chips uh that
i didn't open
with the swedish snack box review
let me get the chips
nice
nice sweden to the skill
yes so i got um potato crisps with
pepper and leek flavor from ikea
see i'm taste testing them now
the smell is normal
interesting
interesting taste the pepper
i do taste that um but the leek not so
strong
oh
what the this looks like in pokemon
arcades
wow that is
pretty a fan a fancy
setup to do what we're about to do
[Music]
congratulations you finally got here
why is she getting yourself into this is
so dangerous
um
okay
[Laughter]
m
but
he's not gonna
even consider that i've been great
[Music]
um
i never learned i never do
[Music]
yo that's a beautiful piano
no one can stop me from my groove
oh
where did he learn those moves
okay
okay okay
i can do more than just dancing my
second favorite sport is baseball
[Music]
okay you
you i don't need heat moves
you'll need them
[Music]
this is a no blocking no heat move
uh play through
don't look at me like that you knew i
would
[Music]
yeah
she asked for too much
[Music]
um is she dead
i kind of saw her death coming
don't leave
so what happens to them lots
oh they were not impressed by her offer
[Music]
they're scared of my upper body
oh this is where chad is saying mad dog
unleashed is this it's happening where
he goes crazy i was thinking that
yeah that maybe maybe the
death of makoto could make him
change like that
okay
his love
[Music]
kind of made him go crazy
it could have been so beautiful they
could have had cute children
[Music]
i mean of course it's not only that
there's a combination probably of that
and him getting tortured and
yeah
probably but what do i know maybe we'll
get a deeper look into it
probably
[Music]
i love
the scenery yo if i go to
japan
this year i wanna if this place exists i
wanna go here
could be a hotel or something maybe
up here man that would be insane
yeah i'm sure it's based on something
that exists because like there's like so
many other things that
are pretty accurate
right
huh
where the are you
[Music]
am i supposed to be impressed by yours
you just look like another npc but that
entrance was like you thinking you're
something special you're just an npc
dude
suggested
there's a helicopter thingy right there
architecture of this place
yeah eat the back of my bath
yeah
hey get on your knees
that's right
almost at 10 million
[Music]
ow i want to try something
stop it i want to try something
[Music]
so how do we do um dance
i don't understand i'm tapping
i'm not sure
it was it was square and then triangles
this is square and then try it
if you could let me test it out
spam square and both of them
but he's just dancing then he just
starts dancing
[Music]
with a square
combo well that's not it
it's a passion
[Music]
why is he bunching him on his knees
oh oh that's not really what i
wanted
oh wait what was that
how does that work again i
forgot i don't do it that often bro
oh several times
[Music]
huh i don't get it it doesn't work
you're my punching bag buddy i'm testing
out things on you how does that feel
you're not even worth a serious fight
never saw that one before
that's a new one
nice finish
[Music]
are you alive
oh no she's dead
no she's not she's alive
bring her to the hospital
bring
oh no more
is
[Music]
um
oh
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
foreign
that was naive
is
no
no no no
i'm gonna help please
use your healing skill or something
unbelievable why are you guys always
just waiting when someone dies and
literally in front of you
[Music]
thank you
help kim thank you
that's what a really tiny one is
[Music]
i think he really loves her
and she still doesn't know his
name
[Music]
is
oh you oh what a
cliffhanger oh you might today
really
i don't care about kill you right
now
in general majima's story is just more
interesting in this game
[Music]
oh my god it's not the first time where
i'm like i don't care i want to see more
about majima
they cut him off at the worst times man
we didn't even have a proper boss fight
we only fought like several groups of
idiots
but that gives me hope then cutting it
off
at that point it gives me hope that she
might survive but
chances are low still
oh that was shocking that that shooting
taxi driver shocked me
oh
[Music]
me
yes
become legend
[Music]
oh
that's a nice um
review though i like that
become a legend
black and white finale oh my god
oh
we're still here
[Music]
huh
but that's a good thing she's alive the
lot
he's still here as long as she's alive
[Music]
she can't do
i went to the doctor
much
no way you're joining me guys the doctor
no way she's too hot
no way
ridiculous
no
no no no no
and which doctor in this world
which surgeon in this world
looks like looks so fabulous with a
perfect hairstyle
perfect makeup
which surgeon does that
not even the surgeons and tv shows look
like that
all right all right
all right
so
foreign
okay
welcome
egg welcome to the membership
kid you
foreign
um
[Music]
foreign
you guys are too calm right now
way too calm
um
okay i have to call back okay
i'm almost done
just a little crumbs
no
okay
could be a trap but i can't afford to
sit here watching the clock chick
if it's got anything to do with my mako
toys i'll take a chance um
time to find and pay for them
those are good chips
small package thankfully because you
know
if it was a big one i would take it
forever and ever and ever and
ever the map is showing us literally
every pay phone
okay
suzuki
hit you there
ah there's one here
[Music]
good old days when people existed
i don't have time right now
don't don't no no no no
moshi mush
set up but i didn't want to say it out
loud in case i was wrong
okay
um little asia
i wonder if this is before she got shot
or
um
probably not after because like wouldn't
he be
busy with her right now like i don't
know
probably right before or so
it's that lady
ah you know what you know what we'll try
to do this side quest quickly
are you okay
you guys wanted to see the cyclist i
know
uh oh sorry i'm sorry for causing a
scene in public too it's okay
uh yeah
very much yourself what do you think
after watching that i'm not cut for this
line of work am i honestly you do seem
to be too caring and gentle to play a
dominatrix
i find it very hard to berate someone
especially a client it just feels like
i'm being rude
understandable
but i would think your customers want
that
if you're so hung up about berating
someone why are you even working as a
dominatrix
since i was child i could never rebuke
anyone even when my friends betrayed me
i laughed it off and forgave them i'm
still like that today but those
relationships i built on swallowing my
feelings were false they were shallow
i realized i had no real friends not one
person with whom i could share my honest
feelings
i took this job to transform myself into
someone who can tell people exactly
what's on their mind but now i see that
i'm not cut out for it
that's quite a leap of logic to make
yeah
but i don't have the talent to be a
dominatrix
a chicken dog other chefs are really
left dominatrix
a baby you always dress like that oh i
beg of you please make me a slave
um um i'm sorry could you huh
oh he's dead you got something to say
kinky lady
oh no i'm sorry
what the hell these days of what you
were supposed to be royal and some
s m queen you are
you're saying you're bad for christmas
uh
i'll say it for her don't loyal in front
of the club you're bad for business
stay ahead of this you squealing pig
you can't act all tough when you're
trotting out of an s nym that i didn't
come out of it
i'm not a customer i just got lost your
news and
don't order me around bacon boy
little masochist piggy worms taking a
punch in my right i know how to make you
feel real good then
okay
okay all right
sounds like a good warm-up
uh two weeks way too weak for me not not
you're not a match
[Music]
so convenient all these things so close
to me
[Music]
no problem
so am i your dominatrix now huh
oh damn this master kisses to have you
supposed to like getting your ass back
and you like it apparently so thank me
pay me
i said i'm not a customer do i need to
pound that into your skull again
they said pick a safe word before you
ask for flogging if i see you around
here again
you're dead meat
and maybe she can learn from me is this
what's gonna happen
i'm just gonna learn from my
from my my way of talking to these guys
excuse me
sorry i caused a big scene fighting in
front of your club
no no that's that's okay thank you for
telling those men what i want to say
myself
and um
could you teach me how to punish people
people
yes the words you said to send those men
scurrying that was amazing i want to be
like you and berate people the way you
do
wait i don't know
i want to change myself please help me
honestly realistically give me a
break but okay
she's desperate enough to ask for my
help even though we just met she must be
serious about wanting to change
not sure how i can teach her how to
berate others but if she thinks she i
could help okay i'll do what i can to
help he wanted it he wanted to help oh
you will thank you my name is aya i'm so
glad i met you
man i want i don't know where to be in
that's true for now though there are too
many people here maybe we go to the park
okay
park
the park okay
i need some privacy right mm-hmm
oh this park oh dear
that's where i lost makoto
well we're at the park now what
i'd like to try walking for a session
with you
there's still people around
how does that work s m is about
play-acting a certain kind of fantasy
it's a form of role-playing but it's not
what you would expect
i think i could gain better insight into
s m if i were to practice with you i
want to act out a play session with me
taking a dominant role in you the
submissive
okay
did you say i have to play the
customer's part
yes kenny osan i want you to play the
role of a ferolly masochistic client
and as we do this i'd like you to give
me advice on what i should be saying is
a dominant yes
um i did it but please i want to change
if i can't do this i'll end up as a
quiet little person for the rest of my
life
she's laying the guilt on fake
i can see her point though
it would do i you're good to learn how
to breathe rage others with
authority all right i'm fine nothing
weird though great thank you very much
kiyosan can we start with you entering
my chamber
okay
[Music]
may i serve you today
why
yes please do
yeah that's not right
i'm not fully into my reliever so i'm
not one to talk but i you're a
dominatrix
yes i'm supposed to be
before you can really dominate someone
you need to understand what it means to
be a dummy matrix
with this sort of thing the beginning is
crucial the first words have to lay out
the rules you're the bus
yeah assert dominance
basic and how should i respond to the
client's greeting
well that's just
i would say this one who gave you
permission to speak pig
i see you don't even treat them as a
person that does sound like a dominatrix
i wouldn't know how a masochist thinks
but it's probably a turn on for them
okay can we do this from the top again
all right all right
[Music]
mrs may i serve you today
who gave you permission to speak
pig sorry
i know i told her to do this but what am
i doing
so so how are you going to serve me
today
please tell me what you'd like me to do
as snl comes in many flavors i have to
get the client to tell me about their
particular kink
got it but i don't really have anything
in particular
i guess not
and then just in general what do you
want woman to do
to you can your son tell me
um
what do i want you done to me nothing
really comes to mind so just let's play
the master history um
[Music]
i want to be whipped
with whipped cream whipped cream please
is that right kitty son i never would
have guessed yeah
i don't really want that done it's just
an example
besides that's the wrong response for
dominations
i don't
telling you their kink makes them
vulnerable you need to come back with
the right response to maintain trust
i see then how should i respond
this one
i'm the only one who do that for you you
know
probably this one
go with i bet you'd like that you
pervert that will go
oh that sounds very much like what a
dominatrix would say that's perfect i'm
learning so much from you already
even in casual conversation you should
be working in an s m flavor
okay can we try this again all the way
from the top cut
scene three
mistress i would like to be whipped
today
i bet you'd like that you pervert
i'm sorry
what am i doing with my life
very well we shall
begin what are you guys doing
wow miss your clothes are so pretty
[Music]
are you having fun can we play too
guys this isn't uh we're not playing you
see um
wait are you calm down
how could you expect me to stay calm now
please can we no think about it when the
tree dominates
dominators take advantage of any
unexpected situation to enhance the
session
we are not going to use children to
enhance our session killer
i see that does make sense no it doesn't
well then what do you propose i say
anthony
that i use back in control
in this situation with kids watching
what would the dominator say to mr
history client
um
uh
maybe this
one of the top two
number one okay
you should go down him with their watch
and you get humiliated
oh i see being seen could be a big
friend for massachusetts
pointing that out would make it even
more thrilling and
titillating for them these kids are
gonna go home afterwards and ask their
mommy mommy
what's masochist
what is that
what's a dummy matrix
oh my god
but now you're getting it i understand
now can we pick up where we left off
and of course i have to walk in again
[Music]
on what are you talking about
the boosters
come on admit it you like this don't you
they're watching you being humiliated
oh oh this is actually pretty
humiliating
i don't get this game you're playing
grown-ups are weird i'm tall
okay yeah better get out of here
i'm so sorry i wish i was just training
but i caused the embarrassment in the
process uh-huh
i think i lost some dignity and long
longer things but it's worth it if it
helps you change i am
thank you kitty son can you come with me
to the dungeon
i want to give you something as my
thanks what am i getting a whip
[Music]
sure i'll go with you to your dungeon
we could have done it in here all along
but okay
i think i left my bag somewhere around
here i should have something that would
make a good token of my appreciation
you bring your personal belongings into
the playroom
are you john you've got a client he
requested you personally i'll send him
first so get ready okay
i'm still here yo
uh
if you got clients coming and i
shouldn't be here
no you're right but this should this
could actually be a great opportunity
i'm going to put what i learned from you
into practice kyrgyzstan and i'm gonna
be watching
okay
[Music]
um
sure
are you turned back
why is he so naked
that's the guy who told io she was a bad
dominatrix and he still came back
oh you i want to see how much you've
grown as a dominatrix since your last
time
okay
now mistress may we begin
go on who gave you permission to speak
how dare you utter human words you pick
such insolence
squeeze
cool
please forgive me oh and good mistress
you're fantastically gorgeous today
squirrel please only confuse me some
more oink-oink
i don't understand you oinking your pig
in human clothing why would i think to
listen to the bleeding of
animals it's so unreasonable oink more
more
my client seems to be happy
so what should i subject you to today
please mistress i beg you to whip me
then while i like humiliatingly
expose you step on me with your penis
points
i bet you're not that pervert
yes mistress i am a pervert
you must be only a pervert with back for
humiliation from a girl your daughter's
age with a pervert pathetic
scream
no i can't take it all
excellent just like i taught her he's
heating it up too that's how it's done
i'm getting really uncomfortable back
here i need to move a little
did you hear that
oh damn it they hurt me
is is someone there i'm busting you
hey
you don't work here do you
are you chad who is this guy
remember what we learned in the park
girl
i decided to have someone watch you be
humiliated well don't you find it kinky
oh whoa
you like it don't you big
your floppy body's on display for
everyone or at least this man to see
please degrade me a total stranger
watching me in my mortual shave
oh she applied what i told her
good going arya she's got a real knack
for this
[Music]
so stupid
oh well i think she got it down now i
don't think she needs my help anymore
congratulations
thanks for the playstation are you done
are you chun no your majesty queen are
you summer your demeanor was truly regal
and your behavior the height of haunted
scornfulness you were utterly
magnificent
oh really
you've grown immeasurably since our last
meeting mistress i feel truly humbled in
your presence please allow me the order
of loyally requesting you
how do you even consider straying i'll
allow you to keep requesting me you
pathetic swine
you hear that campaign
don't stray away from me
you
beautiful cute chickens
i'm a bad dominatrix too
are you you nailed it
thank you it's all thanks to your advice
video son
i just hope i never have to do anything
that awkward again
well here's a little something to make
it all better please accept it
a fur belly warmer i thought i would get
a whip
how we're gonna use that i guess it's uh
it's um armor
i think i've gained enough confidence to
make it as a dominatrix now
good for you ayo thank you kid your son
i demanded to visit again as a client
next time i know someone will pleasure
you with her whip
no thank you
yeah i'm not coming back for that
nope
what does he want to do with this
no
i could go here um forgot what that was
can we before before before we're done
here you know forever can we go karaoke
wait where the is the car open here
one more time okay while we're here
hello
[Music]
oh we have some time
probably
oh i need to use my money for the
abilities to remind me
hmm
what do we have
[Music]
i've never done this one
and uh
really
let's do this one
and then the other one
[Music]
why is it not kid you singing oh god
is
[Music]
oh he's got a nice voice
hey
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
i actually did pretty well for my first
time
everybody say woo show love
it's that karaoke pro there
and you're quite a singer she's called
miku hatsune miku
pink sticker thank you 7j
that's just me customers like you
brighten up my day
i'm singing but of course i will sing
again
recently this game has been feeling
making me feel a little bit
depresso espresso so
we have to sing
the one and only
the one and
oh my only
[Music]
i sing for you i sing for you
m
[Music]
wow
me
[Music]
i'll kill you
i feel you bro
i'll feel you
it's gonna be okay quinoa
i know you lost your job because ichiban
took over the heroin protagonist role i
know i know it's tough
but you have to move on you can't be the
protagonist for every game you
know
you can't be like done
one more
time there was a piano version playing
in the background
it's time to
take a break
which one
judgment maybe
last one
that meant
that
is not
[Music]
is
ah
[Music]
wow
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
those teachers
[Music]
hey
not so bad though
you might not get cutscene for
interjections
really because this stuff i'm singing
okay
no no no we're done we have to go back
to the main story
and
also i wanted to do abilities we have a
100 million
[Music]
what is there to get
power surge 2 increases the power of
your regular attacks and heat access
when using the brawler style
put up your guard again right after an
enemy breaks through it
[Music]
no
i'm not doing those what is this
extends the distance of your quick step
stability drop on the energy deep within
you
to withstand attacks that would normally
knock you down
hmm you mean this my is my poise
stronger with this
dropping the energy deep within you
to withstand attacks i would normally oh
that's nice oh yeah with heat we found a
sec a third bar
really
[Music]
or we can get a bunch of smaller ones
like this one bra mastery spirit but
boosts the damage of your
counter-attacks while in heat mode
[Music]
we could get several small ones
like this one as well pop a brow mastery
wrap
i'll search is more damaged
now should i get power search
always an effect
yeah okay
whatever
i don't know
there goes all our money
there it goes
i hope i hope it will come in handy also
i didn't put on my belly wrap
defense nine blade nine fireman
wow
oh do i have to do it ah instead of gear
how much is this
well it is better
it is better so okay
in the first slot now the hotel all
right we did
important things now
we continue the main quest
i'll be knocked down easier
anyway are we close to
drugstore
yeah i wanna i wanna fill up my
inventory
because we're so close so
this kayoke pub is called amelia
it says in japanese of karaoke amelia
amelia
america pub
that's why she is singing
in there i wanna go in
yeah
amelia karaoke is based on
all right
okay now we can go
now we can go but should i say
when was the last time i stayed outside
[Music]
oh
i have no time for you right now
ah
if only if only
if only their timing was a bit better
they could have a beef bowl in here
together
okay
now
now the weight is over
the weight is over the weight is over
the weight it's over wait so much
only four telemoves damn
and there's a lot now
oh
never a problem to find one all right
here we are huh we're going in here no
we're going in here
oh hello sumimasen
just passing through
there was a saving point here anyway i
forgot
i hate this alley
okay
story time
thank you elder antonio
achida
oh
um
banana
she was shot he just said it
um
[Music]
will
m
is
[Music]
um
thankful to you
oh okay sorry i'm yawning so much
all according to k-cock
i will
hopefully use the legs again
maybe in a game that's not so serious
right now
i guess there's really nothing more i
can do i should meet up with nisiki for
now if i head to west park i'll run into
him eventually okay
uh
wait now is the other place closer
oh i don't know
i don't know
[Music]
found my way out north is closer god
damn it
all right
that's okay once we're outside we can
run fast no worries oh men in black
hello
um
[Music]
really don't like fighting with you
so much
[Music]
like i feel like fighting one-on-one is
still like manageable
but against a group
and noise means so much
[Music]
foreign
when i get up from the ground
[Music]
oh wait
wait don't
huh
what did i see ah ah it's on the heat
with itself
[Music]
huh
i love it
that really reminds me of japan dudes
like that old dudes standing around
randomly practicing their golfing or
their baseball moves i see that
a lot in japan
this is gold it's cold
disco inside of the yakuza game is the
only disco
i will ever enjoy
um
even even when um people are around and
we thought it was a little bit awkward
but
hmm what have we not eaten here yet
we can only have one
[Music]
dancing has not been a more prominent
minigame outside of yakuza zero what
how disappointing
what that's my favorite thing here in
this game that was so much fun the
dancing arc
[Music]
foreign
waves and waves of people incoming
[Music]
style
please don't stab me please don't zap me
wait a second
i don't have heat moves on this one
either do i
let me get the trees
[Music]
don't resist
don't resist the tree what the
two times excuse me okay okay that's
freaked out
i'm being absolutely bullied here
okay okay not funny not funny not fun
[Music]
actual just happened here
are you seeing this guys
[Music]
unbelievable
what the was that
uh
should i is it worth getting those 10
million where was that again
uh
where was that
i don't know where it was
this one
now what
yeah 10 million is i get pretty quickly
from fighting
what
you only allow me one path to get to
where i want to go
oh oh oh okay
i am what is it
where are you
i guess they want me to go
straight over here okay
now
all right
oh the pgm is really dramatic right now
i like it
it's making me feel tense
that's how it's supposed to be at the
end of a game
no
i'm not dealing with you now
no no no how far do i have to go
ah now here i could i could
how many of the little do i
always have to deal with
[Music]
i know i know there's a money option
throwing around money but i never i
never used it i don't know
i don't want to run away from a fight
i'm a real man
also all of this gives money and money
means
abilities and you know
i might be kind of you know behind on
that a little bit so
[Music]
no
at least it's a fistfight review
[Music]
finally that pops up uh so little these
days why the i don't know
that's spanish island kinhaken
wasting my time wasting my time
oh
[Music]
scooter or something
or bicycles
give you on a bicycle
almost there
heal
oh no i'm fine i'm fine probably
[Music]
how many times do i have to do this
come on
yes
[Music]
yeah i'm sure there's fanfictions out
there shipping quinoa and cooza
the last one please last one
no more of this afterwards
okay i know you enjoy this both of you
yeah
i am planning on killing you
dying
um do you have something weak
no not really
oh wait this was one
this was weak oh well
[Music]
oh god
here we go
[Music]
i haven't gotten a single hand
let me go
[Music]
um oh oh
save me
the music is nice though can we just
vibe to the music
[Music]
what's happening
i missed
okay holy sh
yo
soundtrack
[Music]
it's gonna take a while guys probably
take up all my items
[Music]
for sake
oh man
okay
[Music]
is that that keeps popping up there we
go
[Music]
okay okay now we're talking
ah what the
me
should i change my style
[Music]
i think it's okay
we're just gonna always i think grab him
and then put him on the ground otherwise
he keeps on interrupting me in any other
situations
i'm just gonna repeat this
no you killed my heat buddy
you you
you you you you you
really
[Music]
did i win or lose
from a
no take him take him
[Music]
beautiful
almost there almost there almost almost
there almost there almost there
what happened suddenly he was dead
it's bar it wasn't that low what the
happened
my hits were too strong
you're an old man kuzette it's time to
give up to the younger dude
in the town
the time
i think he's a masochist he's probably
uh
a guest at that s m club
foreign
do i have to fight monty moon
[Music]
how do you know
is it written on my face
oh
foreign
[Laughter]
i would like to but you keep on stopping
me
i think that was the last time
um i guess they want me to fill up on
items again before i leave
uh
but the convenience store
uh the drugstore is over there
uh yeah i think i'll go to a restaurant
as well
[Music]
we need to be prepared
he just told us we're going to hell
basically
that sounded like
it might be true
um i said we're going bowling after
we're done probably
because so many people keep on asking
for the bowling what's so special about
bowling i don't get it
why is there only one drugstore in this
whole city
all right
no i do not know
an interesting ending
now once again since this is the only
thing nearby
i am once again going to eat
no don't tell me don't tell me no need
to tell
i'm ready now
[Music]
tomorrow by the way it's garlic phone oh
my god
finally the long-awaited garlic phone
club you guys need to remind me
when i end my stream
that i need to make a thumbnail for
mummy because last time um i knew she
wouldn't participate so i didn't make
one for her
but i think this time she wants to um
i i mean she was gonna participate but
she wasn't gonna stream because it was
time for her um
uh and it's still a shitty time for her
at this time but
but um
i think she's gonna stream so i need to
make uh
a thumbnail
huh
you're telling me to make a difference
point of no return yesterday
okay
i'll make one
it's the end game
oh my god
we're in guys
i did it
okay
wait so what why um uh explain to me
sorry because i skipped a few messages
because i didn't realize he would say
something important
what do you mean i can switch to majima
now can i end the story as majima is
that my choice like if i want to end the
whole thing with majima or with kirill
so i can prep monty moon
oh
i don't know is he prepped
where is majima anyway right now
hey
on the final time i can decide stuff
[Music]
i can take a taxi to osaka or
my last day on earth don't say that magi
might won't be your last day
ah
i just
know i think i'm fine i just want to
check the items my has a full inventory
so
tbh we're good
you know let's do this
hold tight makoto
sorry for the back and forth
oh my god the sound is dying so let me
fix it okay
i'm ready to end it that sounds
depressing
[Music]
oh
wait am
i if this is a blocked scene and i can't
record am i not allowed to show this
what
what does that mean
i can't show it
i i don't think there was such a
restriction
for streaming the game
yeah pick what i said if i showed it too
probably
it's probably fine right yeah you guys
say they showed it okay
that's a weird crump
oh
oh those are the guys who beat me up
when i was depressed
oh
oh it's time baby
can we kill them now
[Music]
i'll teach him a lesson please
very good beautiful
beautiful
that's what i like to see
no disrespecting majima
oh yeah
hey
[Music]
um
is
[Music]
foreign
don't blame it on the girl
[Music]
i'm angry
i'm very angry
[Applause]
they are doing the groundwork for us in
the cutscene
you want to fight
[Music]
okay
let's fight
let's do breakdance
i wanted to fight
nice ship nice boat nice boat
what's happening
this is uh
it's makoto
come on
are they killing the ship
you want to take down the ship
come in your footsteps asmr
making an entrance
foreign
[Music]
career
wow wow that's a big yakuza war
damn
what's the doctor she's here
she's way too good looking
[Music]
thank you i didn't want to deal with
these idiots thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
good luck with the rest thank you
oh so much new music
i thought they were taking care of these
oh there's a fat guy with a chair
oh i missed it
yes
i wanna take the
i gun to take that gun on the ground
i wanna pick up the
[Music]
help me
i'm so glad i don't have to protect me
shikido
[Music]
saw that one coming
he's not even using it to shoot he's
just smacking them with the guns
my god these guys are
not very nice
[Applause]
so
with that katana in his hand is he is
still not killing people
oh no my battery level oh no
i'll connect it soon
[Music]
is he still not killing people
what the actual foxy
hmm
i would love to help you nishiki and do
a badass heat move with you but
the game is not offering it to me
he was shooting
before oh well
[Music]
um let me look at my maybe we have um
something we can talk about
let me look at my memory
[Music]
i don't have much but
um
[Music]
i also ordered
the full collection of sims one
all of the sims one games
yeah
um i i ordered it uh second hand though
um like i bought it off of like a
from like a website where you can buy
things off of other people secondhand
i hope i hope it will work
i looked up like how how that is with um
cereal keys
supposedly should work but
yeah i hope so um yeah
i saw that a lot of people have
problems
oh
on windows 10 but there are definitely
ways to overcome that so no
no worries i'll make it work i'm sure i
can make it work
i just need to
follow some steps i already watched a
video
because i really really really wanna
play since one
[Music]
actually pretty difficult
it's like i think i said it before but
it's like hard mode for
oh
it's like hard mode
for sims
going okay i'm going okay is there any
more items that i missed here no
okay but
don't you dare hurt money she can
where is me
are you guys excited about
some sims 1 action have you guys ever
played since once
it's so nostalgic man
i'm so excited
[Music]
my age
i'm gonna play with all the expansion
packs there's a lot of fun expansion
packs in
in sims 1.
sorry
how do i drop a weapon that i'm carrying
when i don't want to use it anymore oh
sims 2 was great too i especially liked
um
i especially enjoyed the university pack
from sims 2.
they had university in several sims
games um after that but
because you like someone i think my
favorite was still how they did it in
sims 2.
[Music]
they tried something new there was like
kind of like an open world
okay
herbs no i don't think i ever played
herbs um but i played the one on the
challenge
the weird one where you like
in the middle of a desert in like some
casino or something
uh i don't know what was that one called
you played that one
i never finished it though because i
don't know i think i had some problems
understanding
the game
drop that
oh oh hello
what's about to say there's no one here
it's so nice of them to give even mpc
some dramatic entrances
[Music]
his name is a little bit too close to
mine i don't like it
i don't like that
you're faker
oh
he just smashed his head on the rail
of that fence yo
[Music]
[Laughter]
i look like me with my legs up
he's imitating me
trying to make fun of me or something
and
[Music]
this is titanic now
oh oh oh i see you're watching me
makoto
the doctor must be like what the
did i get myself into i'm just a normal
doctor in a normal hospital what's going
on this ship is on fire
what's happening
what's happening oh dear um what am i
gonna do about you
no
no no
how could i not have had that happen to
me huh
oh you
okay okay okay i'll take that off of
your hands
you're welcome
hello
oh there's a whole line waiting for me
is there someone using a gun again
the fucker's in the back right
excuse me
oh what is this place i can't fight in
here
okay
i am very focused
[Music]
no i actually want to fight this other
god do i have to fight all of them
we have to take them all down
[Music]
all of them okay
look at the money raking in though wow
before of course i knew it
can we just can we just skip these guys
and go to the gun guys
[Music]
i can't i can't i can't even block it
no no no no no no no
what how do you how
[Music]
guys
shhh
you you with all my heart
who the is next
[Music]
so many chairs here
oh you can chair vp
[Music]
you just have to look
to where the enemies die
[Music]
blind
before someone says focus
i won i am always 24 7 pushing
r1 just for your information
what is that move
[Music]
no
what is that it keeps on disappearing
[Music]
i hate this so much i hate this so much
finally one is down
i hate back
seaters i hate
[Music]
just play the game yourself just play
the game yourself just play the game
yourself just play the game yourself
just play the game yourself and just
play the game yourself
i'll give you that
[Music]
useless
oh you so much
[Music]
so sick of this
i hate so much
so many fakers in this
[Music]
what the game is the matter
what the actual
[Music]
just ended already
off no not more god people
no
[Music]
how do you block this for all the
in the chat who say block it how
do you block it
how do you block it
yeah right you can't flock or
dodge bullets tried and relax
no stay safe everyone but
sake
[Music]
i mean i mean i mean
they only give me useless items though i
want royal
i want royal
is that hard to understand
ah here we go
here we go boss fight
we're gonna lose my mind here
it's better than royals they're not are
they not selling that in the shop
well if it's better than okay
oh
really we're going to manjima now
[Laughter]
[Music]
sorry sorry i will not reimburse you for
that
while i'm dancing
oh
and one left
[Music]
good night good night my friends
i don't want to be the only one who's
blind anymore you're welcome to the
party
interesting
no no no let me think
oh wait there's a sword
oh no i couldn't take the sword just a
chair
[Music]
legal books
here have some legal books in your face
[Music]
i'm sure you all smoke so here's an
ashtray which is what i'll keep the
office nice and clean right
[Music]
now
is that a weighing scale on the ground
our big boy won't even fit on that
i know that's where the that's the
protest where the the thing was on ah
the thing in the vases that i destroyed
oh yeah yeah yeah
are you scared now that your bodyguard
is dead
here's a
horns from you know who
i can smile again i can finally smile
again
i'm gonna miss any items
okay
wait where are we going here
oh no but let me take my nails
oh yeah he's singing no time to lose
me when playing rpgs no time to lose no
time for cyclists
i'll catch it like a flower bouquet
oh my
i hate stairs
[Music]
i might not be my favorite style
huh
[Music]
no let me oh
you
[Music]
i was wondering yeah i didn't notice
i think it was because i was so used to
kirill for a moment
i give up no more heat moves no more
heat moves
i'll do it without
tight spaces
are indeed
a little of an issue when using a bat
uh thank you for the welcome greeting
what the
unbelievable
[Music]
i'm losing my mind
i'm trying to stay away
oh beautiful
um by the way i just realized
we have a hundred million again where
did that come from oh yeah from
finishing the chapter i said i think
um
these things
yes
i want to keep on losing my heat right
now
guns are for cowards yes
you tell them
wait instead of that
[Music]
a counter attack when an enemy breaks
the defenses
get some heat moves
launch a bombastic flying kick to
deliver additional punishments when
enemy runs off the ground
while bounced enemy is in the air
and also sounds very difficult to
activate what is this
[Music]
it calls rises when you attack an enemy
reduce the rate that the heat goes for
drops over time
makes you immune to standard
proliferation from what guns standards
ah
if it was real guns
tornado thrill
utilize torque to fling a weapon lying
near your feet you'll need a good eye
for one-handed weapons
okay
okay okay okay okay
uh 38
the rest is
50 million everything's 50 million
yeah everything's 50 million though
it's auto frail kind of almost
hey what's it supposed to
push circle
and it's not really auto throw um
four
not 50 million
ah
that's haunting
i'd rather save my money then
ah
mastery see which enemies have guns
or knives concealed on them um
pull out a dagger
[Music]
those two kind of work together
so i would see it
i have to hold something
l2 or press r hold l2 or press i2
and then go behind him
and the triangle
[Music]
it's
it's pretty cool but
now i'm gonna save some more
let's say some more get to 50 million
again
okay okay okay okay
nice
but now there is this item down there
isn't that a small item wouldn't that
wouldn't that work
it was it wasn't a breakdown style
though
oh you killed all of my heat
you
eat this bad
maybe a little small i thought that was
pretty damn small all right so
no no
um
[Music]
okay
any items here
no
who no time to lose
no time to lose
oh it's looking fancy oh dear hello
hello hello hello any gun people we
don't want any gun people here
we want a fair fight
who was that what was that was that a
gun
was that a gun
[Music]
it must be someone in the back that i
don't see once again
can i go through
where is the gun ah
[Music]
oh
ah
he won't even let me get up man
excuse me i'm not ready to go to the
toilet right now oh hello items
he keeps on moving forward i can't help
it
infinity
get up get up get up boys
[Music]
decapitation
take it outside no no no no no no no no
no no no
no have a meat shield in front
of me and you're telling me that it
shuts me
[Music]
now what the is the friendly fire
man
don't don't don't no no no
cancel pencil
don't let him see me
okay
now we can talk
i was so close to dying
you're the last one
congratulations you're the last man
standing
[Music]
oh i see you
oh
shot
oh there he is
gotta be very dynamic here
there we go there we go there we go
there we go
i would like to dance on stable ground
can we go to the middle now
[Music]
all right
takes a lot of practice you know to do
tricks like that
dangerous
dangerous corner
they are mummy pinatas
[Music]
that's all you are
you pink
your pink your pink
and the next floor is ready for me
get the stamina royale
[Music]
oh have you reached the uh top level
oh
foreign
that's exactly what i'm here for
how did you reach
um
foreign
[Music]
the way he speaks man
naked
threatening
the style
was that
um
are we doing this boss fight first now
because kevin was also right in front of
him
boss fight
come on
[Music]
oh
nice soundtrack again
naked man versus naked man boss fights
always have to be naked this is a rule
with yakuza if you haven't known you're
welcome i'm teaching you
only the most accurate knowledge
in yakuza life yeah because i'm from the
nyakuta and i just know how it works
why are they bulking me there was
nothing there
[Music]
i can take some more hits
no it's getting close
[Music]
right
nice
[Music]
and go away
get some of that healing item oh
let's go significantly
i'm just healing myself significantly
see it's like night and day me fighting
with you versus me fighting with
majima what the hell
hitio's fighting cells are just not
really my thing
oh buttons buttons buttons buttons
okay
that was better with magic
slugger
what is the difference
no i like all of the styles that majima
has but i dislike all of the styles that
kale has
the wall he can't uh move backwards he's
getting all the hits
i'll fall
oh oh oh oh okay
why is it taking you five years to get
up
one question though um you know i played
like a dragon first
and the fighting system was completely
different there obviously
um but from what i know this is the
normal fighting system in yakuza games
right
so the others are like this too right
now
my question is
in that case
does kirill also always have these
fighting styles that he has
does he have different ones
only this end in kiwami not always
he fights the same way
[Music]
almost done almost almost almost almost
there we go
same gameplay but different style ah
okay i guess yeah he learns maybe
story-wise the dragon style after this
oh i should connect
always wanted to beat up that stupid
face of this guy
i always wanted to
yeah i know you can unlock it here too
what i was saying he probably
story wise
learns it here and then later always has
it
[Music]
um
a
foreign
[Music]
lucky
where you gonna shoot
i don't know why you did that but
respect thank you wine
and i hate people with guns
i hate them imagine i killed him reminds
me to do it
wow
holy
this dude is
foreign
like the way he's being treated and the
way he looks like he reminds me of from
game of thrones the guy who was
protecting cersei
the big big big
scary knight
yeah gregor clegane yeah the mountain
yeah yeah
[Music]
wow all right at least he does not have
the gun anymore
tell me what you got best hitman in town
let's do a little dance
wink boys that's
that's good for me
nice start
and a nice start almost a new start
oh he's on fire
he's on fire
i'm running out of
medicine
i hope i won't run out of it for real
nice nice easy easy easy easy
weak bastard
i want to learn that
buttons buttons buttons buttons
was so fast
the problem is if i stand still to
activate it
it's uh
he hits me
i can't stand still but only
yeah
it only is ever there for like a tiny
moment when i run around and disappears
immediately and then i just do a normal
triangle attack
all right
doesn't matter we don't need it
we got you up against the wall
oh
so much for the boys
i'm good though
i had these i saw it popping up that was
nothing
dear lord
there we go finally
three other times
[Music]
oh nice
oh my gosh that was longer that was
longer yeah it was longer i was so ready
nice place to fight it looks like tails
have arrived right now
[Music]
ah he's moved there's the heat movement
he moves so close to grass
i hope i hope that after this we don't
have to do anything with manjama anymore
because i'm running out of healings
[Music]
i saw heat move again now it's gone
no it's gone
[Applause]
he runs like naruto
[Laughter]
oh yeah
okay
and now back to kitty
who is about to kill you
not really he doesn't kill people
[Applause]
and she chose as her husband another
dragon
this is
a poor doctor
yes i just noticed
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
m
foreign
[Music]
um
oh naked
is that a dragon too
ah
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
listen up
he still needs the color what the
did he not add color did he not have
time to finish his tattoo
it's just could i ever see his back
before
you know that's getting in
will we do it after yakuza zero
working progress yeah hadn't had the
time yet
um oh dear oh no
what are we gonna do huh oh hell
oh hell oh me oh me oh
[Music]
i think i think we need the
best style
um because yep
because he's on the fence
maybe a single hit but
not much more
[Music]
get some hits
holy i don't have much left
oh
a health boost wait does that give me
more hp
for a while
so it only heals
okay boost sounds like it's gonna give
me more
thank god thank god
[Music]
holy
get up get up get out get up
retreat
yeah yeah that's enough that's good
enough that's good enough this is all i
can count on
this is all i can do
hold for a little bit of heat
to get like two hips in
dropping
which button is it gonna be
uh whoa
hey that works actually pretty well
the point is going through the roof
smoosh it yes
[Music]
what's wrong with you
looking good i have a chance
yeah yeah keep on repeating that i still
have to keep don't do it again
do it again
[Music]
okay
uh which style is good now i don't know
i wish we'll keep this
yes yes yes yes
yes baby
and that's really
the only strategy i have
[Music]
oh i did it again
that was an open window for you when you
didn't use
get it
well he doesn't want it anymore he
doesn't want that anymore he's seen an
alphabet
okay well that's okay i want to charge
my heat anyway
oh
[Music]
have i grown i feel bigger than before
[Applause]
feeling he was about to do something
cool too but i stopped it
oh
[Music]
oh i think it calculated this happened
because there was only a certain amount
of hp left oh
okay
whoa that was close though
um to keep on fighting me forever
hmm
thanks guys thank you
mama
nice
oh
um
wow
[Music]
leave me alone
but maybe not peace of mind
okay
you want to do it together
you better leave me alone dude
never try to fight me again okay i'm the
only dragon
[Music]
foreign
but that guy is never gonna stop
look at him
at least put him in prison or something
[Music]
foreign
okay
it's not satisfying
[Music]
foreign
um
huh
hmm
um
[Music]
foreign
no
[Music]
m
foreign
see you through me
[Music]
foreign
my
[Music]
um
one month later
jojo clan officers assembly
[Music]
foreign
um
wow
foreign
he's having um
some issues dealing with that
he's about to cry it's okay to cry
yeah santa is respectable so
i
prompt he seems to generally
being
a decent guy yeah
so
[Music]
when are we going to see making
oh that's uh
huh
hmm
foreign
[Music]
okay
that's an idea
hmm
foreign
is
[Music]
foreign
hey
[Music]
you want
is
[Music]
sugar
um
[Music]
m
we do have a lot of money yeah
[Music]
oh wait
this is look this is his look
[Music]
i hate that we're so friendly with him
after all of this
[Music]
does management still feel like he needs
to be nice to him because
he's still
traumatized or
did he just like forgive him or what
don't get it
[Music]
he was never bad he was bad
um
[Music]
this new look is so edgy
holy
[Music]
i think i preferred the long hair in a
ponytail
you know
[Music]
um
ah
[Music]
what's gonna happen are they gonna
nice
ah
[Music]
origin
he looks so scary now though
[Music]
this
she knows he has an ipad
huh
no that's
kind of what you created by the way
talk talk talk
hulk
maybe she realized now without talking
um
it's taken care of don't worry
listen
of course what else
[Music]
is
um
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
yoga
suck
hmm
[Music]
lunch
he deserves some love to
give him some love
it did so much for you
[Music]
post credits scene
skip
[Music]
hmm
i need to teach you how long is this
gonna go can i get a tissue
speed run
[Music]
okay
i don't know what to say
i
[Music]
hmm
can i rate the game now
no wait cutscene might come now
well
i can't read that flash those are my
family patreon georgie mom became
guardian of the fairy tales clan german
seda but soon falls from
captain shintaro grace
assumes the fact of control of the
family leaving dojima to languish in his
glorious past
on a stormy night in 1995 a gunshot
rings out from the dojima family office
that will reverberate throughout torture
clan history
with that spoilers i don't it's okay i
don't really understand what's written
here anyway
[Music]
it's not it's not entering my brain
don't worry why are they writing
spoilers here though
are they assuming i already played the
other games which came up before it is
is all of this a spoiler okay
[Music]
he enjoys a long disabled reign about
eastern japan no that's good for him
good for
him good plan
[Music]
i did read it
this guy is gonna be at the table right
now hold on
[Music]
when do will he understand that pink is
not his color though
that ash rose is not his color
[Music]
my ranks of videos
no no i'm not gonna read oh no no no
that sounds like a spoiler that sounds
like a spoiler
[Music]
under the i guess of sarah and to clean
the rear alarm
and dramatic revitalization today the
new emblem of camelot stands proudly on
top of that story lots the millennium
a millennium tower
that i entered up with ichiban
portal mazzama rejoins the shimano
family as his captain where his ferocity
earns him the title of mad dog shimano
[Music]
eventually becomes an unpredictable
pillar of the torture club
[Music]
there's a lot of mentions of 1995.
the
pieces
oh well
don't think about it don't think about
it
[Music]
or
but that was not the scene that you guys
meant right there's something else
[Music]
we did it under five hours
and even uh did some
a side quest and some side stuff a
little bit a little bit
[Music]
i'll tell you my thoughts after this
after the last scene
and then oh and then we're gonna play
bowling
i guess because i kind of promised it
even though
after this i'm not really in the mood
but okay
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
bump
[Applause]
[Music]
one of these people
well these people maybe maybe
we're the one who decided to
give me that like a dragon sponsorship
because that was uh
en apple's marketing
[Music]
whoever it is thank you
how long is this gonna go should i just
tell my feelings now
maybe there's something important in
that cutscene
[Music]
okay important okay okay okay
is it because nishiki and
[Music]
in the last uh
that is important
and this is an important conclusion
[Music]
blah blah
i'm glad that we
did see
um
basically the whole um
creation of majima as he is today
because in the beginning of the game i
wasn't sure if the game would provide me
that
so
um
that's cool that i got to see that
because i was wondering about it ever
since we started the game i was like
that's not the majima that i know and
and then i was wondering are we gonna
see
are we gonna see him change into that or
not and we didn't get to see that so
that's cool
um
but
i'm gonna miss i'm gonna miss the old
magic one now
the old majima was
it was such a sweetie i mean he still
seems to be sweet at his core
[Applause]
judging by how he just acted in that
last scene there
but
from the like his outside is so
different now
like i don't mean his clubs i mean like
the way he presents himself is so
so different
[Music]
foreign
that's me playing by the way
yeah
it's me playing every car alright is it
coming or you have one more song
i think it's coming
oh
he said michael to bring flowers to oh
should bury him here
[Music]
nice flowers
damn
m
too reasonable
[Music]
um
uh
[Music]
to be repaired
i made music
[Music]
and you're telling me you're not
marrying majima
girl
[Music]
making another huge mistake in your life
what a man
and i know i understand you know it's
dangerous to be with someone like that
but i feel like he out of love he would
stop
and he she would
help him heal
oh hello oh yeah
hmm
you
[Music]
uh
i miss the old one
i mean that's funny and all but
wait who does that money belong to
better be adding that to both of our
banks or do we have the same bank
account no there we go we're both
getting it
[Music]
um
i'm not no i don't know maybe this is
not the reaction you want
but um
even though the imagine i got to know
first was this one
somehow
yeah what the is
16.31 percent
you're telling me with the full
game
i am just at 16.31
[Laughter]
wow not even not even 50 not even 40 not
even 30.
damn
um but yeah um
even though even though the first module
i got to know was the crazy one
now i'm like yeah
it's very regrettable
um
and i am so upset that they didn't get
together man
i genuinely believe
that if majima would have
stopped doing all that yakuza
eventually like he doesn't have to stop
it right away it could be like steadily
you know one by one
um like he would do it for the person he
loves and she would provide him the
happiness that he needs
to
heal
from
the suffering that he has been through
and i think she would have fallen in
love with him properly too if he would
have given her his name
i think it would have it could have
worked out so perfectly
but instead majima chooses more
suffering
and gives up the probably the one and
only
girl in his whole life
that he felt true love for and that he's
ever gonna feel true love her in the
future
i think yeah no not about fixing no just
like
giving him a chance to heal and feel
love feel loved
um
[Music]
create new one avoid overwriting all
right all right here this one
is black
i mean i'm probably never gonna use my
save files ever again after today but
it doesn't really matter but yeah we're
gonna play bowling now
[Laughter]
we're going to play
bowling
and i will also tell you what i thought
of the game also compared to like a
dragon uh wait which one what the
[Music]
premium adventure why premium adventure
this is before
oh someone supplied me
oh wait no no no no i'm going
no
anyway my closet there we go
don't know how to close games
still
ps5 so confusing
okay
premium adventure
as you go around no restrictions from
the main story
but it implies still um before the end
of the story i just can switch to
characters i suppose
okay okay
[Music]
free meal adventure
uh
[Music]
uh how are you still using uh wearing
his old clothes in premium adventure
mode you can create gameplay data data
using the phone in your hideout you can
use this gameplay data to start a new
game
moisture is music
what's going on
i can change clubs
did mommy not leave the radion oh dead
girl
oh that girl no
don't turn it off
you don't even know how to turn it off
oh he did
[Music]
is this a side quest
or does this only happen after the game
if you enter the game again
we kick off the show with shout outs to
our faithful listeners by writing up
their postcards
[Music]
to the postcard
this guy is as cheesy as it gets i need
to turn this off before he gets in my
head
thinking driver son hi don't you call me
a son i listen to your show all the time
hell to you too and thanks i have a
girlfriend i adore but this morning at
breakfast we got into a huge fight that
doesn't sound like a complete part of
anyone's morning
the argument was over what kind of
condiments to put on the sunny side up
egg
why would anyone argue about something
so stupid
oh if they're dating for a long time
then oh why am i not moving
there we go it's lagging
i use soy sauce like any self-respecting
japanese man but she used tonkatsu songs
can you believe that well i really like
tonkatsu's song so
oh man sure
maybe i'll try that tomorrow for
breakfast
everyone has their preferences since
then we haven't exchanged a single word
some things are important enough to take
a stand on maybe so but some things
aren't so important either
yes what do you put on your
i'm ex
travis son you're making a monstrous
boo-boo fighting with your girl over
something like that i think you need to
apologize for being so saucy whoa
by the way i put ketchup on my fried
eggs
that's okay
what is the deal of this radio show
they'll actually read stories that
insane on the air
oh would you look at this that's the
first fruit postcard we read on the air
from the thinking travis sound
congratulations the thinking travis son
will have a fantabulous prize heading
your way i'm not saying what but it's a
it's worth a cool million yen
a million yen
oh i'm already too bad too sad but
that's our show for today folks all
right and see you next time
what in the world is going on if they
rate your if they read free of your
postcards in the area win something
worth a million yeah we should do it
hi girl
marina
where why are you left the radio one
oopsy doopsy what a scandal nanny nani
cards
is she the one who was sending the
postcards why do i keep on stopping to
move
i'm moving
on my camera but not on my pc
i think my internet is itself
right now
don't mind me i'm just sniffing my
screeching chickens
legs
in case i'm going to put them in the
desk drawer please feel free to use them
kalu really wants that 1 million
anya had the same problem might be
youtube
no i think that's my internet
if there's something i can write about
maybe i should try something in a
postcard anything from certain sub
stories
oh write about the experience of the
postcard access the desk to submit
topics to the radio show
oh
no no no
and then i'll get one million one
million is nothing though at this point
of the game
okay i'm bowling
i'm fine with what i'm wearing i don't
care
um
where do we go blowing where is that
does it say bowling somewhere
[Music]
big purple
oh this one maybe i'm bowling okay
i'm bowling
bowling
i'm gonna go bowling haven't been
bowling in a long time maybe i should
go booming with my friends
[Music]
i said this before but i can barely hold
the bowling ball like even the other
ones for children
i'm having trouble holding up
this one
oh no left
i think it's going me too
me too
all right is it in here
no is it in here
is it in here
where do i enter
i have to enter from the side
we deserve
some you know
[Music]
that's so cheap oh my god look at my
bank account
wow
holy
how many frames what does that mean
i mean how many
i guess three for now
enjoy it again thank you
just do free
get those pins uh set direction with x
and the power
position select ball adjust pin
okay it seems easy
oh there okay
[Music]
wait it actually went pretty well
[Laughter]
i saved it
all according to cake
[Music]
oh okay okay now now now i am serious oh
i can change the ball too
ah they're different heaviness
oh well i'll go with the golden one
oh it's faster
masuku let's go straight let's go
[Music]
oh yeah
i am a natural as long as i don't have
to hold the ball
we good
right baby
come on come on come on come on come on
come on how often by the way do i have
to play this in order to get whatever
the hell you guys wanted to show me
strikes in a row
oh no
what no three strikes in a row is what i
need you're kidding me
okay well i had one yes
well it's manageable
yeah
a friendship no no no we ain't got no
time for friendships in this game
um
[Music]
wait
does it not matter if i get the strikes
now as if i'm not a friend with her yet
friendship is the thing
oh
huh
what about the strikes
i can invite
strikes don't matter now
what
she gives me a quest to get free strikes
in a row it might take forever
okay so i just um
continue playing and playing and playing
and playing for now
okay ten frames i don't even know what
that means
oh i gotta
control
let's stop
show me what you got
[Music]
how simple
i need i need one of those weaker
weaker balls
i'm still rocking it though
i can always save it you can always save
any situation guys remember that for
your life
remember that
how do you get both of those
oh nice guys at least
not bad
um
i
i don't know if i can get
only strikes though
[Music]
maybe a tiny bit to the right a tiny bit
i was
okay
and it's in the middle
go go go ah you almost
almost got that one pin down
so okay while we're here i guess i'll
try to tell you about my thoughts about
the game
so
personally
i
i think all in all in general i am
spam enjoyed
like a dragon more
um
[Music]
i don't think it's only because of the
vowel system i like both vowel systems
to be only honest i
i like them both
they're just very very different so
um but i think the oh i think like a
dragon hat just
more charmed in the story and in the
characters
and in the side quests like the ones
that i did were
uh generally funnier i would say
i know i didn't do much in this game
when it comes to cyclists but the ones
that i did do
i think like a dragon was although
somewhat
okay but i didn't see two crazy side
quests that were like you know the baby
the baby sat question like a dragon
you they didn't i don't think they were
able to top that
even the s m one
i wanna flip my hair back right now to
show up how cool i am
yeah and
um i like the whole you know party
system
and like a dragon a lot it's like having
a whole party the whole game
uh or like at least the first half of
the game
playing this one
i was thinking like
what
when when am i gonna meet the the other
party members
i was thinking that eventually
oh
come on
i was thinking eventually i will get to
have like a cert like kind of somewhat
somewhat of a team
but apparently
not
[Music]
i like the song
i don't think it matters that katie's
story spans over a longer amount of time
like they had they had good story here
too but to be honest like majimas was so
much more interesting to me
like for me
the
the protagonist was majima
and i don't think i'm the only one
who thought so
not too much that was too much i wasn't
even necessary going to the right was
not necessary
but yeah as i said i think both fighting
styles are
fine so it's not for me it's not about
the
the fighting system even though i had
some troubles in
yakuza zero
every now and then
um
i i remember i had troubles as well
with
the fighting system
in
[Music]
ah nice
like a dragon because you gotta be very
very tactical and uh strategic
in that one like you don't get much
choice to do something
and it's really important to decide am i
going to heal now am i going to attack
or what am i going to do
and if i attack what who do i attack
and so on you know
even if i heal i'm gonna die next turn
and so on
yeah let's go just straight
nice i'm just so good at this
um
yeah no i think
in general i prefer
like a dragon but this game was great
too i'm gonna give it
i'm gonna give it dumb
[Music]
what rating am i gonna give it
difficult to
rate someone
something a game like this
only slightly only slightly only
slightly ah
hey
well
it would probably deserve an 8.
oh
it more than that doesn't need more
no
but it still doesn't get all of them
okay
how much did i ever rape like a dragon
with numbers
[Music]
oh nice that is absolutely straight
let's go full power
strike baby
huh
that was too much power
there's no way i can get both of
those
there's absolutely no way
ah
don't know about this one yeah
whoa
that's a beautiful split
oh thank you it was on purpose
nice look at that
yum yum yum yum yum
your bowling phone was as good as ever
wait we're already friends what the
huh
they already said friendship
wait are we not friends yet do i have to
max it out well that was half that gave
me half
does this give me more friendship if i
do a ten then uh free
you're gonna say with it does that help
just do three frames
okay same amount okay also somebody said
invite a friend so
ah i can only get this again oh that's
okay though
who does majima get to call or can
majima not go bowling
no it's nisky
hey could i cancel the game you can
enter in an insta exit
you mean without playing
beautiful
beautiful even if two pins are standing
so beautiful
hmm he said i'm amazing yes i am
yes i am
no that's okay
go straight go straight
[Music]
get that watermelon
huh
[Music]
[Applause]
now you're just making fun of me
[Music]
uh
two
yeah yeah that's
you're making me nervous get out of here
no way that he strikes again he's doing
the same thing
whiskey you want to be bros forever you
better be nice
give me my strikes
switch into a 16 pound
and he knows he's bowling i never switch
i never switch balls
you must know what he's doing huh but
you didn't get this one
dummy yo
i'll keep i'll keep my six pounds
i'm going nice and easy
all right
i'm gonna go straight
huh
[Music]
[Applause]
i love those close-ups the whole
time
[Music]
i have it
i don't have one is enough
[Music]
i might be your opinion but i'm pretty
good at going straight when bowling
[Music]
what you got
dare you i dare you
no don't don't strike don't you dare
striking
very good feeling good very good
very good
wait oh my god we both went 19 and 28.
so if he gets under 48 then
yeah
all right
i'm winning though yeah there's no way
especially looking at that ball holy
kind of disaster
does it this is why you're never gonna
be a dragon
uh-huh
beautiful he through
because he loves me right yeah
don't mention it bye bye
nice okay so i leave or should i talk to
her again or like we only get like
friendship once every time i speak to
her right
once i'm once every time i walk in
all right let me go in
and talk
[Music]
how does that work
you guys said i could just leave
i have to challenge
inviting someone isn't affecting me
quit
i mean
just
cancel
this right now
okay
oh
i can also just throw everything
how do i leave
ah wait what which one click this one
but then she'll see that and she will
she'll be like he doesn't truly love
bowling
she'll see that i'm just a fraud
see look at her face she's like i know
what you're doing
i know what you're doing
you're just a fraud
frozen together leaves no explanation
i just need to let out some frustration
okay so now we're gonna challenge you
play with me
you really got time to play with the
customers here i don't think so
sounds unrealistic
she won't get what you want to see why
am i missing something else
if yes and tell me so i stopped wasting
my time
i need to do the real estate story now
the hotel okay so i am wasting my time
okay
read the super chat
i will be reading super chats after this
thank you
which one the pink one
but you need to first beat best the
sleazy king in the room
no no no
yeah
oh well
you guys asked me to play
bowling and here i am playing bowling
huh
don't tell me this breath doesn't bring
you happiness huh
no i'm doing this for you chad i'm doing
this just for you look at her laughing
at me
with high heels
she's bowling with high heels oh no
she's
girl you work here don't you
oh and now she's gonna if she gets nine
now then i'm actually impressed
oh she just said
oh girl
oh what a disaster
she's pretending to be bad because she's
on a date i don't think i don't think
girls need to do that on a date
uh on a date like bowling pretending to
be bad bowling
you don't need to pretend if you're
already bad
can't help that emily
you can't pretend to be bad if you're
already then i'm sorry to disappoint
meanwhile i'm doing this on purpose just
to keep
one thing alive
because
because i want her to have some hope
if i would only be striving here then
she would
see no
no hope and we don't want a hopeless
girl do we
oh emily
how bad are you gonna be this time
this could be
oh it's so heavy it's so slow
oh my god
someone help this girl
ah the only reason i could see
why she would be pretending to be bad is
because she wants to do you know one of
those things where
like katie would hold her from behind
and then show her how to throw the ball
she wants one of those romantic
scenes
i see you girl
ain't gonna happen though
my heart
is with makoto and majima oh
where are my glasses where are my
sunglasses
where are my sunglasses oh
power
and i did it again this is beautiful
this is on purpose
my my most beautiful split
i'm just trying to look cool this is
just piano style
[Music]
like my legs boy
all right
but now now that everything is over
now that the seriousness is all gone
i can put up my leg right
i'm relaxed now
anybody relax
[Music]
wow
[Applause]
[Music]
um
that doesn't save you though
unless you're gonna strike now
then we can talk
[Music]
the shoes
don't quite match
what do i get what do i get for winning
your bowling ball was great oh there we
go
your bottom looked as
lovely as ever when you
my butt
excuse me sexual harassment
i'll have to stop coming here
that is exactly what i was gonna say
um because it's a waste of time
apparently
oh you see for yeah okay so it's free
strikes but even if i do it
it won't uh
have the effect that you guys are
waiting for i guess
and free strikes is tough man
uh
doesn't it won't happen right
oh
try it
i don't know everyone's saying something
different
i mean
we can
try to
wait we need we need the free strikes
and we need a maximum friendship and we
need the real estate thing
right so
it won't work
laser boss sounds very sure about it
i'm hungry by the way
i'm getting hungry
hungry
oh i'm really hungry
let's go with new skin
[Music]
what
is that a possibility
huh
keep on doing this
sandwich i can't make a proper sandwich
toast is not good for sandwich unless i
make depends on what sandwich i'm making
if i'm making a hot sandwich okay but i
don't have cheese
[Music]
no
i i went too strong by accident
i smashed that button
asleep
i believe you i believe you
but let's beat this girl anyway
see what kind of
oh what kind of flirt line she's gonna
throw at me after this
i'm curious
it looks like a colorful taser on mobile
[Music]
a spare a spare we can do
she's winning no she's not winning oh sh
she doesn't deserve that
[Music]
oh
she really needs more practice
even i who came here for the first time
i'm better at this
what are you doing
what are you doing she's just
trying to get style points or something
by starting on the edge
girl
[Music]
this
she's challenging me
there's no way she can win will
i get more friendship points if i let
her win
emphasizing the letting her win
[Music]
unless she gets a strike
i'm winning this
[Music]
go go go go go go go go go
yeah she makes weird noises when she
froze
but nothing
compared to me probably if i would throw
a bowling ball like that i would
probably go like
because it's so heavy
let's go
uh
girl you need to stop wasting my time
i'm so hungry i'm gonna eat you up
oh
i'm so hungry but i don't want to eat
chocolate
i'm going to get sick
[Music]
wow she was winning both in ground one
and two
oh and all that lady
not bad
by the way we'll soon have a challenge
for our customers i'll keep you posted
right she didn't flirt with me
an event is scheduled to take place
i don't know
ah i stayed no no no no no okay well um
sorry guys
yeah
and but that means i have to do
something in the real estate right
yeah
i'm feeling doing real estate now
no no no no
no
yeah i can watch it on youtube
it's not much of a difference
i could go wherever i want and do
whatever i want to do that's right kid
you you do you don't let anyone tell you
that you can't do something don't let
your dreams be dreams kitty that's the
spirit yes
if you want to smoke on the streets
right in front of the bowling alley
you do you if that's what you want to do
you do you
hell yeah can you let's go
right so i will
i guess
safe just for the sake of it
[Music]
okay so everybody
thank you very much we'll be reading
super chats after this so you're welcome
to stay if you want to but thank you
everybody for watching my yakuza zoom
role play through especially the ones
who have been here from beginning to end
thank you very much it was once
money guy it was once again very intense
um
interesting story
you know you know i prefer like a dragon
but this was great too
i gave it a good writing
and i'm glad i learned some of the
beginnings
of this general story and also that um
now i understand a bit more what kind of
person kid you is because women like a
dragon
when he showed up i was like huh
okay
so what's what's what is it about him
that everyone loves so much and i mean i
understand it a little bit now um i
think for someone who has not played the
other games
um
the point did not come across 100
percent of what makes him so cool majima
is still cooler
i guess there's probably more to it i'm
sure that there's many many more moments
that make people love them in the other
games that make
uh that create a good reason for why
people are idolizing him so much
um
yeah
yeah yeah but i i think it was it's good
that we played this one
um
yeah i'm fine with it
i enjoyed it and i'm glad we picked it
up
it had some beautiful graphics too
i loved the cutscene the cutscenes were
great
they looked really really nice i like
the the skin textures and all that
[Music]
yeah so thank you everybody for tuning
in supporting me helping me get through
the game and also being patient
um
when i was a little bit bad at the game
sometimes but you know i
i had my good times too let's not forget
that there were some times where i was
pretty
pretty decent i would say
um
actually i had one one
death
where
like one proper death only where they
gave me the easy mode
but that was unfair like that was so
stupid those stupid protection
missions
are ridiculous
those are
oh those triggered me really hard in
this game they were i think generally
tell me if i'm wrong because it's been a
while but i think generally i had more
moments
of rage and anger in yakuza 0 than i had
in like a dragon
right
i cannot remember
me raging
in like a dragon at all
i can't remember at all
[Laughter]
maybe that's why
i like it more maybe my memory is like
like this like is i have a positive i
have mostly positive memories about like
a dragon so
so my it's influencing my
general
view of the game but i think that's
not bad or so cause like i mean if the
game makes me rage that hard with some
stupid missions like those
those
protection escort missions then
yeah
i wouldn't say that's that's
so something to blame me for
[Music]
but yeah i'm also sorry that
uh for the people who were really really
um
into
or like expecting me to do
all kinds of different side quests and
all that i'm sorry but you know
um i'm a stream i've said it before i
can't spend
months with
a game you know
uh i know it's only 16
imagine this how long did we play it one
month
imagine i tried to do 100
it would take me
a year
i have to consider that kind of stuff
and you know
the
you know
even with this i was playing it two
times a week
and six to eight hours
per session
so i have to think about the fact that
the more side quests and the more mini
games i do
it's
gonna
yeah take up so much time um but the
ones that i did i i enjoyed especially
that disco game and the karaoke game and
the the chiaba cabaret minigame and all
that it was a lot of fun um
so it's like you know a sneak peek into
the games into the mini games and
cyclists everyone who wants me to play
those already played it themselves and i
understand you want me to enjoy certain
things but um you can't you can't force
that not i'm not i'm not gonna have the
same exact experience as you did when
you played the game
um but
i i
i like your game okay so it's not like i
dislike it just because i didn't play
some side quests or whatever
i just want to say that because some
people get really really worked up over
me not doing certain things in a game
i will play the game how i want to play
and don't worry i enjoyed it
a lot
yeah
you can see
that i'm enjoying this by just you know
the fact that i went past like a dragon
i did not drop the whole yakuza
uh
series i continued playing it mm-hmm
eh
bacon ahead 15
and there you go
there you go
pekko that probably had the same font
that you know there's not not that much
time like you know to do
much more than that as a streamer
you could assemble at less percentage
than me so that tells you something
oh
no no well i don't think this will be
the last game um but i'm definitely
gonna wait couple months
uh until we play another yakuza game
because next up we have wind waker
yahoo
wind waker i'm excited for it um not
immediately next week or so um but soon
enough i'm gonna
take a little break for some small
things again
um maybe
maybe dip into minecraft again
um
but wind waker is gonna happen soon once
i got my wii u and uh the game itself
mm-hmm
yeah
and once i'm able to capture it properly
i need to test that out too but it
should be normal should be easy
yeah i'm not sure what to do in
minecraft but i keep on thinking i want
to revive it like we can do some stuff
like one block and all that but i didn't
want to do one vlog with eno you know
sick right now um but
i'm gonna find some
ideas on what to do in minecraft
um maybe you guys can help me oh by the
way one question uh
sticker sheet
or postcard
let me do a poll
sticker change
sticker sheet
i didn't say i said sticker sheet
no context
tough choice yeah because i'm thinking
stickers you will probably use up
but at least then it has a use but
postcard is uh
i don't know will you really
use it to send it to someone you just
want to keep it done right
um
you like to display postcards yeah i
understand some people might want to do
that yeah it's more
[Music]
i don't permanent okay i'll think about
it it's pretty 50 15 almost all right
all right then
um
i'll go into an intermission try to find
some small quick snack wait i have some
pieces from my pizza left over but i
would have to warm it up and then eat i
guess i'll keep that for
i should keep that for after the stream
i think
[Music]
i'm not gonna
get fooled by the rest of my pizza
though
um
[Music]
i'll just i'll just make some
i'll just make some something some extra
side um that i have in my freezer okay
so i'll not eat yet i'll try to
get through it without maybe i'll eat a
banana i'll eat a banana i'll eat a
banana that's a good idea okay
i'll see you later
oh
two minutes
okay
[Music]
do
i am
um
okay
banana is gone
[Music]
yeah
okay that will
stop my hunger
for a little while dodgy banana oh no no
banana
oh no
oh no i didn't even think about that
guys you've ruined the banana for me too
bad it's already gone
guess it is it is a symbolic way of me
ending the series by eating a banana
i'm just trying to honor
the legacy of touchy banana
um that's
[Laughter]
right
um
[Music]
what am i doing i want some music
how about
today
this one
[Music]
okay
just a little dance
yes
what do you mean what the hell huh are
you shocked because i am too cute
[Music]
understandable a lot of people have a
tough time with that they don't
understand they think they think you
know they don't like me but what they're
really feeling is
they're so confused and overwhelmed by
the the love they feel for me
that it makes them feel that they
dislike me
it's a very confusing situation it's
like a schroedinger's
piana
schrodinger's love
for schroedinger's kiara
it does happen to a lot of people
i wish i could help them but i'm not a
doctor okay
[Music]
and but if i was i would be hotter than
that doctor they had in
yakuza zero
i was thinking by the way
um
i think one more reason why
[Music]
like a dragon was
i liked more i liked that one more was
because it had more of an impact to me
because i think there were generally
more emotional scenes and
i just felt
more emotions during like a dragon
um so it felt stronger to me
not that this story didn't have
emotional moments on all that but
not it didn't have so
many and i feel like like a dragon had
more
[Music]
i think it had more
you know there were some shocking
moments like certain gunshots or
um
i think the whole homeless arc and all
that
i don't know it's been a long time so i
barely remember myself but
um
[Music]
like a dragon is way longer
was it way longer
i guess so i feel like we spent more
time with it yeah
i like the group dynamic yeah i think
that helps a lot that adds a lot to
something like that to a game like that
yeah the writers are very good
[Music]
no even if it was not an rpg
even if the fighting style was the same
as before
um
it's not only that
yeah
i think
[Music]
there's more than that but but but no
hate no hate i was just saying
maybe that's why i enjoyed it more
because there were more emotions and
more more emotional moments and just had
more
impact
12 hour stream i had a 12 hour uh lad
stream really wow
damn
yakuza is like jazz the emotions are
more hidden i need to imagine what's
going on
now what i definitely think is that
because this really even though it's the
beginning of the story it released after
a lot of other games and
i think it expects you to
i think the game expects a lot of
rather than a lot of newbies um a lot of
people who already know kitio to play
that game so
you go
if you go in there knowing kirill then
it might have more
of an impact on you
as a kid you fan than for someone who
doesn't know kitty
yet
i understand that
yeah that's what i'm thinking all right
all right we're gonna read super chats
guys
and then i have to make uh the mummy
thumbnail i hope i have a psd file
for
uh
yeah otherwise i have to recreate the
whole thing which will be a pain in the
ass i hope i have a psd i hope so
and
um
yeah
oh my god it's saturday tomorrow i have
to make my schedule tomorrow's sunday
um
schedule making i think there was
something else that i forgot that i was
going to do
tomorrow
what was that
let me
[Music]
all right i'm gonna start scrolling we
finished
the
super chats from the previous yakuza
episode is that correct
so i have to read the ones from the
drawing stream oh thank god i actually
came pretty far yesterday
good job me good job i'm sorry i had no
real small talk with you guys today
um
sorry about that but i'm gonna try to
spend more time with the super chats now
okay
good job pasquiada hell yeah good job me
oh i could have i could have picked up
the marshmallows as i said i might do if
i'm lacking
stories to talk about could have done
that i forgot about that
yeah that was uh that was a lot of story
so
it's okay it's okay
[Music]
yeah i was pretty invested too i mean
i'm gonna be
honest um
some parts in the end
with the whole yakuza talking blah blah
blah were a little bit uh confusing and
complicated to me
took me a lot of
concentration
[Music]
i got adopted as a kid
grandma should enjoy yourself playing my
favorite game oh you mean yeah cause a
zero is your favorite game or just
yaguza games in
i'm general take a cough drop already
just in case
yakuza just like that yeah there's a lot
of big talk yeah um
bureaucracy exactly politics and so on
yakuza politics are
confusing
[Music]
overall
the whole
the fact that the whole story is
basically wrapped around this one
lot
sometimes it made me feel like
is this really
is this really necessary to
[Music]
could could this have not been dealt
with
quicker and with less drama
[Laughter]
there's one stupid lot man
[Music]
such a big deal for one lot
yeah
yeah is this really necessary
[Music]
um
recently
when i um step out of my streaming room
for a moment
um i find
smoothie
in the cat tree in the hole in one of
the holes
sleeping in there and i go
to her in my intermissions and i pet her
and she goes like
strap really strong purring
why i'm saying this is because i'm happy
that she's using the cat tree because it
was originally in my office and you know
they like to keep distance from me
nowadays when i stream because i'm so
noisy
because they don't want to disturb me
so the the cat tree in here was kind of
useless because when i'm when i'm not
streaming i'm not in this room
and they are always with me in whatever
room i am so
they wouldn't go to the category in the
office but when i was streaming when i
was in this room
they wouldn't use it either so now i
finally moved it
to the living room
and it seems to be getting great use out
of it also when um i'm cooking the
the cat tree is in a space where they
can see me when i'm in the kitchen
so when i'm cooking they also chill on
the cat tree and they look at me
[Music]
and uh yeah
it's much better over there
yeah yeah
and it's nice to see her uh sleeping in
the in the cave thingy
of the cat tree because
up until now
even when they were using it before
uh she would only sleep at the very top
she would never sleep in that cave
but now she's finally using it as as a
cat owner you know cats reject a lot of
things
they they don't use a lot of the things
you get for them so as a cat owner when
your cat actually uses something you're
getting for hair
it feels like a huge accomplishment
it makes me feel so happy that something
i got for them is getting use out of it
um
it's so
so rewarding you know
[Music]
we have an understanding
this must be what it's like for mother
and child
you mean humans
i think i think for humans children
generally use stuff more than cats do
even even if they are often like sick of
their toys okay
i think cats are a little bit more picky
than humans
[Music]
i did buy another like small cat trader
to put into the office anyway because
sometimes when i um for example make
thumbnails or
when i'm
just longer on the pc without doing um
streaming work
there's some other work sometimes to be
done and then and then smoothie likes to
stay close to me
and chunkers too sometimes
so i thought maybe a smaller cat tree
would be nice next to my table
not the big one just a smaller
one that's like approximately the height
of the table so that when it's right
next to me i can pet smoothie with one
hand because it's on the same height
big thinking big brain
yeah my cats are so loving it makes me
so happy
because my previous cat when i lived
with my mom
my cat really did not like me
i tried to make her like me but
yeah it was partially my fault but also
in general our cat was just not so happy
i think
[Music]
i really regret it now thinking of it
now
she was not mistreated but
like i mean
i was just a teenager
i still am
i was just a teenager so
you know i i i did not
i think i don't think you can nice movie
i don't think you can like expect for me
to take good care of a cat like perfect
care like i don't even know i wouldn't
even know what
what needs to be done and all that but
[Music]
of course of course i am teenager what
do you mean
[Music]
if i say i'm a teenager and i am a
teenager
no
no no no
no no
no
[Music]
let's read super chat from yesterday
is rubbing her soft body against my leg
she joins me when i do super chats
[Music]
now she flopped herself i need to rub
his belly one second
then he wrapped the seat coming
yeah
[Music]
um
i'm carrying her over my shoulder
baby
who's a good baby
[Music]
you so oh
you're too soft my gravy cat
[Music]
i can't let her go
i can't
[Music]
who's your good baby
take it all in
[Music]
i love it
i love
[Music]
it i'll let you go now can we cuddle
later
okay
i'll let you go okay
i'm gonna let you go
okay
she's just chilling on my shoulder
i'll let you go
[Music]
she said goodbye
did you hear that
maybe not maybe it was too far away
[Music]
it was more of a angry goodbye though
she was like
you better you better be done streaming
soon mommy
goodbye
[Music]
go mangle
my sweet sweet baby gives me so much
happiness
so much happiness thank you for the
pinky oh my god thank you
[Music]
all right let's start mystic has fixed
thank you
you need a nickname
dude you need a nickname your name is
too long now
[Music]
hey antonio
doc
you changed your name i saw even on
twitter you changed it thank you for the
rainbow
and i was going to deliver a cake that
definitely didn't have a key baked in
uh-huh
to a harp
harbor
what you would work
against me
i never expected that from you what but
instead i decided to re-watch the stream
from eight months ago where you showed
up the features of the usual room and um
you're especially cute today uh-huh
yeah i better be especially cute today
for you
you have a pinky as well a stunning
potential like yourself deserves total
respect and loyalty did i mention you
look especially cute today so fetch let
me pour your cherry coke i'll make you
some gills that you know all the things
i love
how about an orange super chat to match
that lovely flowing hair over here and
then here's a bouquet of edelweiss i
picked from a biome i don't want by
me that's what i said was there's no
other way to say firemen yes
you say yellow also because you have a
golden voice warm like the sun that's
actually true i mean it's all true of
course of course it is
finally since i'm not working we're
gonna dedicate like yeah because the
general run he's had a long work week
and is working hard to see your document
now you hold up
you saved yourself doug
you saved yourself that was
dangerous
[Music]
you know how to get yourself out of a
situation like that huh but but but but
i am i am a bit shocked i must say that
you even considered helping someone in
the usual room
i thought you were
i thought you would never
go against me like that
but
you didn't do it okay you just
considered it okay
all right so a kiss for general mwah
thank you thank you soon
looking forward to seeing all of you
at dokomi
that are you gonna come to probably
difficult right i don't expect any of
you guys to come from different
continents don't worry about it i just
just want to know because um i want to
be prepared you know
want to be mentally prepared for who's
coming and who isn't but you probably
have someone to take care of so
um yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
if you can't come that's totally fine
but make sure to watch the twitch stream
then
of course i'm coming again yeah you cra
you crazy you're crazy you're crazy
oh yeah that's okay that's okay
understandable
i would love to come when i have to save
my vacation for japan oh yeah well i
hope you can
get there sometime within this year i
hope it for myself too if i had more
vacation time
uh yeah i'm so spoiled now because i can
take vacations whenever i want
i
i know i guess you guys have vacation
days too that um are you already used up
or you need to plan it wisely when to
use it up
[Music]
yeah yeah
that's okay
thank you
it comes naturally should i call you
doug hood now it will be difficult to
get used to it thank you doug for the
rainbow i'll try to say doug
[Music]
yeah
i might not be streaming on twitch on my
own but well the convention chooses to
stream on twitch
so sorry guys this is the one time that
i need you guys to come to twitch
all right
[Music]
smoothies back suddenly suddenly some
softness around my leg why are you back
baby
you go sleep a little bit more
[Music]
no more
it's so nice it feels so good
it feels so good like some fluff against
your naked leg is just
the softest
oh
ascending
cyrex
[Music]
felix sound thank you for the right
super chat am i late oh shoot i'm late
well at least i made it gonna watch
tincher draw until i fall asleep in the
oven
it's so warm and cozy in here yo felix
do you want to be my test subject for an
air fryer i could try to put you into an
air fryer
you really seem to be enjoying
um yourself in
hot situations so
thank you the right person
for my
experience you felix for the right super
chat
i'll hit you up once i got that air
fryer
yeah we stay in contact
[Music]
uh he'll he'll survive it feels fine he
he will be fine he's going to be fine
robin the hood
as ref junction
no i didn't order it yet
i didn't order it yeah i'm still like
i'm sure i've been ordering too many
things these days
but i'm pretty sure i'm gonna buy it
eventually
actually i am gonna see
my mom
next week
[Music]
by airfryer give to mom
oh yeah my family is gonna get together
for
uh easter
i'm not staying over but i'm just gonna
it's still gonna take up a whole day um
because i gotta travel
for that
yeah one she would like one i don't know
i don't want to ask you directly because
i wanna i would want it to be a surprise
maybe she's watching now though so that
would be
that would give it away
but then generally she doesn't watch my
yakuza streams
[Music]
we do easter as in we see it i guess as
a reason to
get together but it's not like we really
like
we might do some traditional
food or whatever but
um
we're not a really
religious family no not none of us are
religious so um
but still i mean you still celebrate
christmas and all that even if you're
not religious right so i mean it depends
not everyone obviously a lot of people
do
but i'm still doing the promised uh
easter stream next week the one where i
wanted to paint some eggs we're doing
that because next week did you realize
next week is easter
on easter sunday
i'll be doing the easter egg
painting stream
[Music]
tamagoto
yeah i said last year already that i
want to do that but i couldn't
i didn't think of it in time for last
year's easter i think that was the
problem i um
yeah thought of it too late
[Music]
and i i was saying next year next year
next year we're gonna do easter egg
painting
yeah it's already april
[Music]
it's already april
ah that reminds me
i wanted to
set a
date um
um
oh well uh where was that patsy duncan
mother control thank you for the pinky
hello kiara today i'll give you some
information you said you don't know
where to watch korean clips before but
this time a fan created
korean site the whole life oh you
used whole i've thought kr
[Laughter]
yo
whole i've got kr so please much decide
if you're interested damn
that means whole life could never use
whole life dot kr if if we wanna
hold on okay all right let me see that
sounds interesting
oh wow
it looks like a proper
news website
let me translate to english
it's showing
a broadcast schedule is this is are
these the ones that are currently
happening or
no way that all of them are streaming
right now
[Music]
not sure but okay
latest article
wait articles
there's someone writing
articles about what everybody's doing
[Music]
who's writing this
whole life indonesia is ionda rhys
to broadcast accounting to commemorate
the second anniversary oh yeah indonesia
members have an anniversary next week
the the first gen members
[Music]
who's writing this
website
oh there's a korean discord
[Music]
clip footage view more so this is korean
clips only
needs more chiara clips i see no kiana
in the first page
where is all the kiana
i see
veils i see it
mummy
[Music]
i see
veils a lot of
crony
cobble
[Music]
here's one
me talking to cat
a video where store manager kiana heals
while just playing with a cat
oh that's after oh that's after tatty
banana died i think and i went
i was so sad i needed to
go chill with my cat no no
oh
whole live member introduction
recommended illustration
it looks so proper
[Music]
and those are direct links to twitter
nice in the fan art section
yo
nice
well done
um but that leads to the official whole
page doll
the whole live member introduction
good job wow
link is homelife.kr
whole live.kr
amazing
i love that
i might check the website to look for
korean clips sometimes
in the chamber of truth
i am let's see duncan
[Music]
008 free come on nina for the pink super
chat hello
today is my birthday i would like to
give you my present as a birthday
celebration oh
i will support to you streaming future
have a nice day p.s your hands look
prettier than the picture
what
you mean
you mean my glove hands are prettier or
even oh what do you mean thank you
though happy birthday
thank you
[Music]
congratulations thank you for watching
my streams
happy birthday stay healthy and happy
and thank you so much for watching even
during the shitty hours
i appreciate it a lot thank you for
being part of kfp
korea
and strawberry
[Music]
foreign
monica
[Music]
thanks for answering my question no
problem
thank you
just woke up hearing you talking about
handbook so what is your free size no
personal use of course
[Music]
yeah i don't know if i can say
it must be
accurate right now
i can't say it
i can only probably roughly say s and m
or something like that
[Music]
high fructose corn syrup thank you for
the pinky poor cobra being bullied about
her hair and kids saying her mama is a
chicken and her daddy's a pangolin
well
no it's not other kids
saying her mama is a chicken it's
herself saying her mama is a chicken
is she calling
her calling a penguin is she doing that
sogaki
that girl
i mean okay to her gents okay
but to her senpai
where is the senpai respect huh
huh
this girl needs to learn once we collab
she's just still
she's still you know
there's a distance there that we have to
keep because there's no collabing
allowed at the moment so she probably
thinks she can
you know be a little kusogaki
but once
that
space once that wall is gone that's
protecting her
then she has nowhere to hide anymore
[Music]
lefish thank you for the rest of the
chat hi to you too is that all you
wanted to say really really really
thank you very much for your support too
generous though
thank you
happily
speaking of donuts i have a joke what do
you call a donut place super popular
with foreign visitors
tourist attractions
i don't get it
i'm getting
miniature pin shot down come sign it up
for the of the chad i like kobo's
cheerful cats phrase would you please
read this in kibala version
let me be your sun shine
what
let me be your son to shine ah okay one
more time
it's your service let me be your son to
shine your day
i hope everyone has a happy day
you can't use the word shine and ah
yeah if you write shine
it means a die in japanese yes yes
did that work
she does have a cute catchphrase yeah
um
i think it's good she has something like
um don't necessarily need one but i feel
like it's it's a cute something for me
that's kikkity key it's kind of short
but
it's nice to have something that only
belongs to you
and that other people can also
remember you with
thank
you robert carney thank you for the red
super chat as well this is the last room
i'll be able to see
for six to seven months so since you're
my favorite whole live girl you get my
first red super chat wait you don't even
get to hear my answer robert carney are
you here or are you gone already
happy early two-year anniversary also
you act like my little sister is cute
are you gone
six to seven months
at least i know you're coming back
well take care i hope whatever you're
doing is successful thank you very much
i'm waiting for you
okay
bye bye take care
thank you for supporting me
don't forget me okay
play johnny thank you for the pinky more
donuts potential
i'm going to turn into shinobu from
bakimonogatari
she really loves donuts there's this uh
illustration of her
in a bathtub with donuts
always eats donuts i'm gonna become
shinobu she's so cute
she's so cute i love shinobu alan
dankeshin unity chat danke shin foreign
your art style fits kobo so well the
sketch is beautiful so cute by the way i
have a question how do you use
marshmallow i didn't understand enough
gotta keep my heart hitting questions
for later it seems oh dear
uh
it shouldn't be so difficult like i know
it's a japanese website but maybe try a
google translation like the the one that
translates the whole website
but generally you just write the
question and send it i even had it so
that you didn't need uh
an account
for it to be logged in
man it's pretty simple are you right and
then yeah i guess there's like one big
button
[Music]
but don't worry unity chad if you have a
question you can always ask me anytime
if it's a super chat then there's a
chance i will answer it without a
marshmallow
[Music]
thank you though thank you
next time jarrah dances and iron warrior
duncan in rpgs of class systems what's
usually in your favorite class to pick
and why for example i really like
classes that feature animal companions
like a summoner oh
well when it comes to mmorpgs i used to
always be the healer
um but then for example one time in
final fantasy 14 i tried the one with
the
with the shiny
little fox cat whatever thingy
[Music]
what's happening who the is meow
stable
why are people spamming that the person
is dissing me is that a twitch streamer
or
samurai yeah summoner um
and when it's not an mmrpg but a normal
rpg game then obviously you know being a
healer is doesn't make much sense um
uh but i'm so confused um
yeah with uh i generally if it's not
here then i like to keep my distance
with uh
either being an archer or using magic
i don't feel so comfortable
being super close to the enemy so that's
also why held in the ring was
a little bit tough for me especially
because elvenar is difficult on its own
and then having close combat
but in diablo i went archer right
being a freedom gundam i don't know what
you mean with that i probably won't know
until i use it myself
[Music]
but you asking me that question makes me
want to play
another mmorpg i want to play every more
peaches
sage
never need to get close
yeah i heard that using magic
makes ellen rings so much easier
but no i'm good i'm not gonna try it all
over again as a magician and then i
wouldn't even feel like
[Music]
what the
holy what a story you have dog food
w008 free dancing
what kind of late snack late night snack
do you like oh late night snacks i
when i need a late night snack
it's often um chocolate some kind of
chocolate cookies
[Music]
i do eat that a lot
besides that
recently i've been eating ice cream a
lot more
yeah
too much ice cream
mm-hmm i might eat ice cream again
tonight
[Music]
oh thank you first and favorite whole
i've remembered big supports and love
now in the future thank you
sir
on a film set or commercial effect they
are made from mashed potatoes mixed with
makes a lot of sense because you're like
well mel's realized yeah that makes a
lot of sense i mean i never thought
about it but looking at
ice cream from commercials and all that
but i'm very aware that also a lot of
or maybe let's say 90 of the food that's
on packaging
is 3d
even though it looks super real
90 of the food on packaging is
just made in 3d
yeah on the pc
yeah
did you guys know that
you need to flex my knowledge
[Music]
and jim tracy dangerous in the game and
create dungeons
and that's why it never looks the way it
looks like on the packaging when you
take it out
free for free
thank you
greetings to brazil
[Music]
and eva
of course you can join kfp
and i'm waiting for you
gotta work hard
and get strong eat your vegetables
to get strong to work for kfp
denise duncan five chickens in a pretty
dress
thank you for the pinky we practiced
long for this day oh but
i mean that is a pretty dress but
i would
i would not okay well i mean okay no
that's fine okay
gonna dance with me
all right
[Music]
all right i'm looking forward to it
you guys are cute sarah dankeshen
[Music]
but i won't ask for a head chef position
yet but can let us be free of the jokes
i thought i redeemed myself but if we
keep making jokes and they're leaving me
in a vegetative state as writers of the
main like carrots
what
oil
general what's happening what's
happening with all those puns
it has nothing to do with you when i
talk about you know lettuce in a burger
recently that's just
that's just me generally saying that
it's necessary i'm not trying to um hint
at you or anything
[Music]
but you're welcome to
add lettuce
and salad to your burgers
chronic thank you soon
night bunny thank you soon thank you
l is not a ducation for the red zipper
chant i think i think of this as an
empty subject because i don't know what
to say
oh
[Music]
thank you
all right why did you not write anything
in your super chat what the
what the you being so generous but
then you have nothing to say
what's the matter with you
think harder listening think
[Music]
next time next time you better write
something big
into it something mind-blowing
did i have your kiss ellis
here's one this one ellis
inca raven thank you
leon
oh my god the screen went black the
moment chickens escaped the free range
farm ah
but my friend tony got his little
computer should i ask him to restore the
ball tech problems nothing again i think
i know what you mean is that when i made
the screen really really tiny in lbs
in minecraft
i think that's uh
well is that so long ago that slowpoke
makes a joke about it
thank you for the membership welcome
gd duncan the gamer criticism
motion function
[Music]
that looks kind of
cute and uh terrifying
graphic adventure game developed and
produced by killmonday game swedish
indie game studio
[Music]
reminds me of alice
the cat is so cute
oh my god the eyes of that cat
that game looks so interesting
[Music]
did anyone ever play it before yeah no
as
a horror game an idea
[Music]
oh
can you go
duck
thank you thank you that was pretty fast
and i did read quite a few non-red and
non-pinks too
now we read the ones from today
the weather forecast for this episode
predicts depression and sadness i only
cried
[Music]
one stone yeah
when majimo walks away no one majima
gave that dude
a goal with makoto now that me i'm
so so
you know
[Music]
you for the rest of the chat here's my
paycheck please use it to buy some less
smelly calf
no it's just watching friends there's
nothing to do with my cat food no no
thank you though spanking time
i'll sing the song for you now smelly
cat smelly cat what
are they feeding you
smelly cat
smelly cat it's not your fault
oh
[Music]
i love phoebe and i love the actress so
much um
there's this other show from the same
actress lisa cadreaux
that i've recommended to you guys before
but it's really hard to find a place to
watch it
but i want to recommend it anyway web
therapy
[Music]
web therapy is so funny it's like
really
a simple show but the dialogue is so
good and you guys
need to watch it please do please please
please please web therapy it has like i
think four seasons
remember watching one episode you need
to watch more
ah
lisa kudrow is
great
[Music]
yeah
there's also a lot of um
[Music]
improvising in that show because like
there's outtakes and you can see that
they really uh
they just go with the flow a lot in the
show
there's some points that they will
always follow of course but like there's
a lot of just
super funny
improvising ad-lib that the actors are
doing and it really shows that they have
some skill they know what they're doing
so good it's not apple to me
oh
well i don't have apple today but if you
guys have apple tv then it's gonna be
easier to get
[Music]
it's so good i really like the concept
of it
[Music]
it's basically her
um the whole show
exists only like in one screen like it's
like
it's like um someone recorded the show
by
recording someone's desktop you know
what i mean
you need to watch maybe a trailer or
something to understand but it's
basically happening all
through the point of view of a computer
[Music]
yeah and uh with webcams
i mean different computers different
point of views like that like by by
seeing other people's webcams
but in general it's just like
like not a real show it's like just it
all happens in the in
in the screen recording of a desktop
yeah it's really cool
that means it's low budget but
i think they poured all the money into
the script
your boy stephen adams
dear sanchez give it a pinky
here let's say you are sent to a world
where all mice have been replaced by my
sized fishbox
[Music]
wait aren't you always the one who sends
these weird ideas fishbook known as the
children of gooda would you take the
time to meet some of gooda's 20 billion
children or go back to your own world
right away
i would go back to my own world right
away
because what the no need to meet
her any of her 20 billion
fish
mice sized
fish folk children
dear lord what a weird idea is this
something you dreamt
[Music]
how do you get these weird up
ideas
[Music]
yes my mighty leg thanks for the pinky
i could put it up right now but it's on
the other screen i left my leg somewhere
else
patsy duncan
joker0195 dan kishan a capitan oh i
could yeah
have you seen those memes of um
people cabardoning someone not with
their hands but with their legs
yeah you can do that with my kikkity
kick
true
ladies love dancing for the pinky damn
bird you sit like this
totally
what you don't
you don't sit like this
we need to start stretching girl
sloth
you lazy's sloth i know you're lazy but
you need to stretch to keep up with me
uh-huh
[Music]
oh
your boy is even adam's duncan
uh rice or free duncan
you're also coming too
ah if only you could bring food then you
could bring me those
english crisps
[Music]
potato chips
oh man
gd danke 7j thank you for the pink
uh sticker actually you sent two in a
row almost
i'll give you a kiss for that oppa
are you ready
there you go you deserved that one
sending so many super stickers thank you
very much
[Music]
thank you full catcher
sensei
[Music]
thank you for the pinky let's go
where where where are we going where
were you where where are we going
where where are we going
was that maybe the beginning of the end
or so
thank you
for watching until the end
[Music]
panda running
oh yeah the last chapter probably
panda running gaming
jt mentions
7j more super stickers
so many pink super stickers 7j here's a
kiss mwah for two more pink super
stickers thank you
[Music]
your
you know what humans die when they get
shot
yeah i'm also
thinking kelio knows that and
he decides not to kill anyone
[Music]
although no is he really aware of it the
the whole uh car
uh chasing thingy where he was shooting
everything
they died
they died definitely
[Music]
no
i see what you're doing
thank you say rick that sound
around
your thanks for the pinky good job
kenneth but other deserved stuff
yeah well
[Music]
he did bad things
very bad things
but he seemed like
a better person
at that like in the time we met him like
he he changed so
i think
you know
many of the things are of course not
forgivable but
he still
became a better person
so i i was i know him as a good person
and it was very sad to see him go
[Music]
no i'm not forgiving him
but i was sad anyway because i knew him
as a hot
guy
a good looking guy
who
was
pretty charming to me personally
[Music]
who's pointing a gun to margot's head
well
well he didn't kill her
it did not kill her
i share your sentiment thank you
they're all yakuza in the end yeah
they're all yakuza
like the the way i despise sagala and
then you guys were at the end like oh
he's fine he's fine i'm like no he's not
fine
saga is a piece of for torturing
majima in the end they're all
people
they all did some stupid
horrible
except maybe kill you
maybe
[Music]
and they try to
you know find an excuse for it by saying
oh it's my honor or whatever the
um but in the end they're all
all
committing crimes
squid coyote duncan
jacob 47 duncan daisy duncan for the red
super chat you now bear the spirit of
it's you not yakuza
[Music]
how come just because i cleared the game
or what
thank you daisy
i've always been a true yakuza
[Music]
and i even have some people working for
me they're called chokers and smoothie
yeah they're pretty badass but they
follow me loyally everywhere i go they
follow me i go to the bathroom they
follow me go to the bedroom they follow
me
you know you you wish you had such loyal
underlings
[Music]
peter one two three leo doctor jen
i give daisy a kiss
here's a kiss
[Music]
mr kazmig's duncan
my typhoon thanks for the pinky another
rpg down thanks for playing this even if
the combat is rough in places the story
and the world of this series is amazing
and it was great to enjoy it with you
even if uh i've played it this many
times
oh you played it more than once it was a
blast every step of the way with you
thank you taipan for watching
yeah there were some frustrating moments
in the combat but overall it was a great
game i agree
i'm glad i played it
and this way i got to know more about
yakuza many many times wow
wow
but
are all of the yakuza games besides like
a dragon
um like this where you have no real
group to fight live is that only like a
dragon
is it only in like a dragon
[Music]
it is so lonely man i really liked
having a group of people with me and
like a dragon i'm
[Music]
will hopefully be out next year so you
can have a party again you think they'll
do it again
i wonder they won't go back to kyo
i guess also wouldn't it or maybe
i wonder if they're doing a story from
before like a dragon then it would make
sense to
go back to kitio but if they do like
a story in the timeline afterwards
i wouldn't mind seeing more of ichiban
like a dragon is the norm now they said
dead
and they said they continued ichiban's
story yada cool okidio star is over for
real
oh
cool so maybe we get like a lot of games
with ichiban
just like hide you holy then
wow
then at least for ichiban i've been
there since the beginning
foreign
i just started getting to know him now
but for ichiban i've been there since
the beginning so i would feel very
special if
if
something big comes out of that
[Music]
seven is an epilogue
wow
excited i hope a new game comes out next
year then i want to play it i want to
play it
i want to do more of ichivan and with
that whole
group
dynamic and all that
sweet coyote
[Music]
their story will continue
their story you mean including makoto
jim tries jim tracy duncan they came and
created 17 thank you for
another pink super sticker thank you
[Music]
thank you and
i just beat this game last night oh and
watching you play was the most
entertaining content i've seen have you
been playing alongside thank you for
playing this amazing series and hope you
have a fantastic day stay beautiful
queen thank you
have you started it at the same time as
me and just try to keep up with me
[Music]
where did you start like before that
i'm good that we ended it around the
same time
nice we're in sync almost
thank you very much for playing
alongside and and and
supporting me with such a generous super
chat thank you
hope you enjoyed it as well
hopefully you got more percentage than i
do did
16 can you beat it
[Music]
foreign
mom
[Music]
how could i mean i will give you a kiss
to majima if that's okay
[Music]
pain
pain majima pain gordo
he deserves one he does
he deserves some love
i wonder if he ever gets loved
and peace of his mind
jammu rudenko robert carney thank you
for the uh pinky ah
rabbit connie
i guess you're already gone you just
were there at some point of the stream i
asked for you like a little bit ago and
you weren't in the chat did not expect
to have time to see you but never late
never later than ever that's also that's
a fire fit you got on
thank you robert i don't know where
you're going
but i'll miss you
thank you for being here
you better come back it's a promise
um
[Music]
a bit more
um
congrats on finishing yank is a zero
attention what an amazing play for it
was i had so much fun watching you play
this game love thank you really
i hope i didn't sour the mood sometimes
when i got too angry
at the fighting system
i hope maybe you guys at least saw it as
funny
um
or so
thank you right ghana
for um
staying with me through all of it
[Music]
i did okay
it was fine okay thank you good to know
here's a kiss for you
on to the next adventure we go i hope
you'll enjoy
and zelda adventure as well
kevin lee donkey shooting dog hood thank
you and your boy steven adams duncan
[Music]
been really invested in them spending
numerous late nights love the game's
storyline and of course your reactions i
have a question though does the phoenix
boss fight include stripping up the
shirt too
[Music]
that makes me think i'll count to you
with a question are there a female
yakuzo
in general maybe but how about in yakuza
storyline are there any female yakuza
of course i wouldn't say that's an of
course
[Music]
i feel like they would uh
not accept
ladies in general
[Music]
not really right
remember one from yakuza too
i mean we had we had um
who was the lady with koreans or chinese
then the mafia that that cool lady was
with
and like a dragon but that was a mafia
right that was not yakuza
i mean was the japanese yakuza that was
korean huh
mm-hmm
that was a mafia
although where even is the difference
yakuza just basically japanese mafia
isn't yakuza face like a japanese mafia
just a word for japanese mafia
[Music]
right yeah
there's no
[Music]
nothing really that is different i would
say
i'm about to have set the hole yeah
because what what what what
[Music]
they might not be happy to hear you say
it well um you guys gotta protect me
when they come from me okay
when they come for me for what i just
said then you guys are gonna protect me
i hope so
and very few women who are acknowledged
are uh are the wives of bosses who are
referred to by the title
uh
anisan
[Music]
well that doesn't really sound like a
thing
playing a big role though no
no no no
but
must be a very special person to make it
as a female yakuza
to be accepted
probably really only if you're a wife
not as a
random
lady
but better to stay away from that anyway
yakuza is more progressive yeah yeah we
accept ladies
in fact only cute ladies only ladies no
no boys no no not
[Music]
um
what we do is uh cat fights and all that
you know
only cute girls
[Music]
is
foreign
[Music]
just some guy with a mustache thank you
for the pinky when i love you but she
doesn't step and go with you
hashtag only much more things
[Music]
after playing this game or a different
game but probably was this game right
ah understandable who can not fall in
love with majima after playing this game
such a sweetheart man
no
hmm boohoo seven to three dankeshenkaya
butter dankeshen salubrious beats duncan
but that also proves the point again
pecora was also more infatuated by
majima than barkido right
open the mic thank you for the thinking
the tattoo one apart uh got to be the
most sad part for me and really touching
my heart
can't forget that heartbreaking scene
anyways congrats on clearing 16.40
16.41 of the game thank you are you
making fun of me are you roasting me
yeah no for me um i cried even stronger
at that moment with makoto and the
doctor yeah
the tanji banana death scene was tough
too but
the last one was made me even more sad
because it all it meant that majima
would not get the love of his life
and will continue suffering
even though he deserves
just
great things he deserves kindness and
love and
someone gentle
giving him a hug
[Music]
i'm also
100 sure that he would be a great father
to a child i can totally see him he
would be such a cute dad man
maxwell the three stancation right ghana
dancing kevin lee thank you and karpov
sergeant and mary pippin
the best thing about finishing a series
review is seeing about seeing what you
get passionate about major my makoto
would probably have ended up together if
this wasn't a prequel
oh
this wasn't a prequel i mean if this if
they would have made this game
like as the very first
game thanks for the journey and see you
in the next one thank you
yeah maybe we can just have them date in
in my brain only i'll make up a world in
my brain where they
are together
i'm falling art no really it's not about
me wanting to date much i just want him
to date someone and be happy and have a
family
[Music]
elemental colors duncan
and yeah thank you for
telling us that it's not gonna work out
i believe you so i gave up
make it in sims
oh
that's an idea
and i know the ears don't anthony webb
duncan made believe that in the game of
creation but i
just realized i'm a bucket of delicious
fried chicken or did it happen today
must have been pretty traumatizing to
forget the experience but not enough to
forget about how cute you are
no you didn't maybe it just didn't hurt
maybe
it's it's not that painful it's all good
congratulations right that means a one
year one year membership i think
thank you very much for staying so long
i hope you're not sick of me yet i will
stay awhile longer so you better stay
too
thank you
[Music]
for
thank you for the pinky
i watched you from debut you weren't my
favorite at first but you look i was
also not my favorite but your love for
the community openness and energy
changed my mind here's my first super
chat for my first and only oshie
oh i did end up being your aussie
for my birthday tomorrow can i get a
yellow an employee number
yeah
i need to say your little to you
even though it's your very super chat
and your birthday you belong into that
smm s and m club in in yakuza 0.
you seem like a little masochist
your little
your birth your employee number how come
you don't remember it you know what your
birthday number
so stupid your employee number
uh you say tomorrow
uh
your employee number will be
nine
zero five
cause that's your birth date
what a coincidence
how does that happen
it's like a miracle of all the numbers
you could get it's your birthday
number
nice
now don't forget it anymore okay
now noonan
does that mean i am a chicken in korean
but my name is
in germany says wait my name is trap
i hate you
the koreans are not laughing so maybe
they maybe i didn't say it so
so well
so they must not have completely
noticed what i just said i see one
person laughing
[Music]
oh you're changing him into a shorter
one why lib
why lib what does that mean is that now
it's just your name your nickname
it is much shorter thank you
i like it dominique
it's monkey duncan
and i saw a few more laughs
they're sleeping mostly though ellis
thank you for the red super chat
oh sorry i skipped one i'll get back to
it this won't be anything big but i'm
just gonna
say i can't wait to see your dog on me
[Music]
you will be we will be there too because
this time i will be there till we go to
kfp people oh for future yakuza streams
here's an advice dodge more
just kidding i dodged i just didn't
block i still love your stream so much
thank you
gonna be there
the lord maryam
i'm so excited all you guys will be so
there will be a cat
in the audience
i can't calmly perform when there's a
cat sitting there
i have to stop performing and then pet
you
um
that'll be quite a distraction
thank you
i need to roll more or less yes
rolling would have probably actually
helped me dodging many things
like oh my god i could have rolled
through that uh for those gunshots
yeah that would have been nice
thank you ellis
a case
for you
thank you i'm looking forward to having
you at dokomi
please
look forward to it and enjoy yourself
there
not lou thank you for the pinky quick
question can we use the usual room to
sleep off hangovers
no
what the hell no
the
use your bed
usual room is not supposed to be some
kind of spa
it's not a spy retreat for you
so why are you drunk
you're on your shift
[Music]
you better not be drunk you better be
talking about separate cases
we'll wake up without legs
yeah if you'd use it for that you might
wake up without legs be careful
[Music]
i have black friction
and this is
i'm sorry the thought of nyakuza having
the chance of the kfp clan and the taco
clan culminating in kiara and inna
showing off their feelings and taco
tattoos as they get into a cat fight
i'll never leave my mind
that is a long sentence
but basically you're imagining me and uh
inna
fighting with tattoos on our backs
we are
we are known yakuza uh i mean
we are in yakuza but
ina has no yakuza clan so it won't
happen but you keep on imagining it have
fun with that font
nina's tattoo could also be on the
front of her
body
it's pretty flat they're good surface
for
doing but
probably might be painful
[Music]
[Laughter]
that just means she has
more you know space to
although even even when you have big
boobies i i think i've seen people have
tattoos on their boobies before
but that must be so painful man
i don't know is it painful
maybe maybe
maybe the more boing boing maybe the
less painful it is
[Music]
i guess you guys can tell me nobody here
who's tried it
then you may believe
[Music]
looking for the top down
hey
i know
don't don't point it out so directly i
know
and lo naivety
oh one more refresh
oh
dragon bunny dancing also dokami from
belgium oh cool
bring me some belgian waffles i wish you
could want food
but okay oh
belgian waffles
but i hope we have a good trip looking
forward to that
question
[Music]
all um i'm done reading super chat
hallelujah thank you for the pinky
for the membership thank you
oh uf mod also became an egg
about time
[Music]
it was about time
congratulations thank you for the
applause thank you guys i've made it i'm
finally um caught up again
only to tomorrow
uh fall behind a little bit again
because i don't read super chats after
collabs like that
uh i will read it of course eventually
but not right away
um
but that's okay it won't be that much
garlic phone all right i think i'm gonna
eat food first and then make the
thumbnail for me may hopefully don't
forget
don't want to forget
thank you jacob's monkey you're not
sneaking in there you cannot unless you
unless you have committed a kfp crime
uh-huh it's not that easy
don't forget the movement from now
doesn't help you telling me now
good job clearing your backlog thank you
yeah
everybody on twitter a little bit later
perhaps i'm probably not gonna forget
because i got to put up my own
reservation anyway it's probably gonna
be fine and you can see nora thank you
black fortune
okay for mario okay chill chill chill
thank you
yay
finally finally finally we only waited
about a million years
[Music]
thank you
secondhand thank you and jkh with the
references
where where how did he do that
huh yeah you were ratting him out
wow
oh spanking time and jake edge monkey
are never going to be friends again
wow next whole talk when
i don't know
i don't know i don't know who
give me give me some give me some time
to just
wait
wait it out i'm gonna wait it out
keeping kiawa here what do you mean
i'm gonna go also you can't do much with
those membership messages i'm not forced
i don't need to
read them
you can't keep me here with those
no i'm not ready to ask back when i
stand by
i i feel like
i feel like i want whole talk to become
even better before i invite her
i don't know how to improve it even more
but um
[Music]
thank you guys very much for
watching
the series i made a playlist by the way
it took me a while but i made a playlist
like uh one or two days ago
um if you need to catch up on some
episodes or you want to share it with
someone else there is now a playlist of
by yakuza 0
[Music]
play for thank you not applicable thank
you
no no super chat time is over no no no
yeah i'm going to warm up my pizza and
stuff
so yeah thank you jason duncan
the chicken i was holding earlier what
do you mean earlier
i wasn't holding a chicken today
[Music]
oh that one was not a real chicken don't
worry guys i know it can be very
confusing for you guys but that was not
a real chicken
no no no no you guys are the real
chickens
[Music]
okay i'm gonna go now pizza party
and in germany we say avida scene
brandon duncan blackfish and duncan
i will pet the cats yes
of course i always do
every damn second i'm not on my computer
i pet them i pet the out of them
making that applicable function no no
[Music]
it's the final
countdown what about
in less than 24 hours garlic phone the
whole totality is happening make sure
to be there
[Music]
thank you venged me thank you
skye duncan thank you you thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
see you on the next adventure
[Music]
oh
palm
of course it's going to be tuna of
course
man the reactions on twitter were insane
[Music]
i call that pizza discrimination
it's good it's really damn good
tuna corn pizza
some people tried it because of me and
said it was actually really good
yeah
yeah yeah
all right bye bye
you're just jealous that you don't have
pizza
jealous
[Music]
how dare you call me nerd one month
i have pizza i have tuna not putting
them together well you're missing out
missing