[Music]
do
like i always forget to hold it yeah
hello everyone
hello sorry for the delay we deeply we
deeply and humbly apologize for the
delay
but the game made it a bit more
difficult
to do the walkie-talkie thingy than i
thought so we're just going to discord
uh
push talk yeah
so we'll just pretend we're using the
walkie-talkie because we are the same
it's the same button so it'll look like
we're using it in-game
except we're actually on discord which
is better anyways because the vice voice
quality in this game is kinda
[Music]
but i mean that sounds normal because
it's a walkie-talkie of course it can't
be perfect quality
yeah that's true that's true also
oh we haven't had a amethody collab for
a million years i mean i met a mary
[Music]
yeah uh sorry to keep you guys waiting
but this time we're playing we're here
to we no we we we're here together
apparently there's free games with that
i thought there was only one so we're so
happy that we could play this one
together a man
yeah cause they're not like
chronological or anything
[Music]
oh
oh god damn it all right uh well oh yeah
what
i was saying i'm happy i'm happy you can
play this game together on them
me too yeah i think that way you're
pretty good at puzzles right
[Music]
i wonder how you got that image i i i i
mean if it's
like a normal puzzle you know like a
classic uh possibly in the classic
meaning of like putting one piece and
another piece together and then another
piece and another piece
that's that's the most puzzling i can do
oh okay well uh you know it's kind of
like this except it's a little bit more
guided
i think the good thing is you have
experience with this game like with a
previous one i guess so you'll be my
guidance
yeah i'll i'll i'll help um she's moving
her mouth but i can't hear her
tell that hello you can't why can't you
hear me
no i can hear you i know i can't
maybe you talk didn't didn't talk to me
on purpose but
i'm trying to change my discord settings
that uh
chat chat i don't know if you noticed
did you know do you notice something
different in my voice like i
i don't know maybe
probably not unless i tell you i don't
know
oh yeah yeah oh hello testing can you
hear me
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah hello i hear you okay
now i don't hear you i just see your
mouth moving
okay are you pressing a v i'm pressing
it
oh yeah no i'mma help me adjust my
microphone settings
and i thought you guys maybe will notice
the difference i personally didn't but
i just have bad ears i guess
[Music]
you're supposed to hear a difference
i don't know no i don't know
maybe who knows maybe they'll be able to
tell
i mean i don't hear you are you talking
to me hello
hello hello
[Music]
hello will you scare me continuously yes
i think it's just me i think it's just
because
i don't know it's funny but now now when
i when i now when i uh
oh okay are we are we ready to start the
game oh i freaked out let's go
okay let's go uh we'll probably do this
in two parts guys because
it seems to be like eight hours long the
king
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah well yeah
you can hear me right i can
let's go loading checkpoint
it's so annoying to push a button i'm so
used to not pushing a button
i get well too bad
[Applause]
very scary intro i'm so scary
good morning good morning
all right from now on i guess i'll just
talk to you when i really want to talk
to you and otherwise i'll just talk to
my chad all right
okay no cheating hey okay okay
no cheating and we'll we'll see about
that can you hear me in game and in
discord
now i can only hear you uh in discord
i guess the voice in this game is just
broken okay yeah
yeah the thing is i can't hear you
either it was like
really weird what's going on in this
[Music]
game
hello
yes yes yes hello oh my god hi
over over
hey you're uh your jacket's orange
that is uh perfect how that i can't even
remember three buttons this is gonna be
difficult so
this one is talking
uh you're pointing at me
yeah i know what was the winky one how
can i wave again
wink oh xxx
okay okay okay okay i got it three
buttons not so difficult
if someone's asking us for help i'm in
uh for help for what oh oh outside i
think 47.45
well then i have a lot of things open i
got it close all right one second just
give me one second hold on
i'll give you 10 seconds oh god as many
as you want actually
oh god as long as i can spend more time
with you over
um let's just let the dude outside die
unless you're staying here it's really
cozy
yeah this is nice why would we leave
i'll i'll cook some soup for your tomato
soup is that all right
uh that sounds nice that sounds good i
want something you got it girl i got it
i really gotta turn the graphics down on
this game
[Music]
by the way before you guys say yes obs
is in admin mode
it always launches in admin mode now
[Music]
this game is not very well optimized the
microphone settings don't work
why is it lagging
turn off motion blur
okay okay i guess we go outside
all right i'll follow you you know the
way right
no but okay let's go probably here
this is just this talking can we talk
back to them
[Music]
i only see you holding a walkie-talkie
uh
interesting
[Music]
oh so what are we supposed to do we're
stuck at the first class already
oh that's a puzzle that's supposed to be
puzzled i don't know
[Music]
the game looks better right guys though
i'm a little bit lucky
to fix that i'm just pushing the buttons
[Music]
okay uh we're gonna find a way out of
here
okay maybe that door
that was not the right door where are
you where are you
where are you there we are
let's go get an axe like in minecraft
and just mine the wood
all right one second
i'm uh i don't know someone told me to
tell you to fix your stream what's
what's going on over there
my my buggy gpu
is being garbage right now wait i think
i've
solved the puzzle
okay no i didn't but i got it i got the
wheelie thing that i probably gonna put
on the door
i have one too oh oh there's ah there's
two doors that
don't have the wheelie thingy i put it
in place i think yours has to go to that
other door to this one that i am now
pointing at oh yeah i tried doing that
but uh
i couldn't put it in
i was able to put it in the other door
that opened up maybe in there there's
another door and then there you can put
it
oh you opened up oh wow you open this
one
yeah oh there's a big car
it's a cute one oh there's some levers
but they said i should have messed with
them
who said that the ghost
oh don't listen to them
why would you listen to the game oh the
star opens
it's like a snowmobile oh it go
outside already nice oh it's so pretty
yeah it's snowing wow it's romantic
hey how did you put that red thingy in
because i have a wheel but i don't know
how to use it
it gave me a prompt it only gave it to
me at that specific door though so
i think it has to go into a specific
door yours as well
[Music]
okay yes it's still laggy
the game looks fine to me so it's just
obs i guess
it looks fine to me
extremely laggy it's really not that bad
though on my end
it's choppy i don't know why it would be
choppy
[Music]
i'm on the roof i'm in how'd you get on
the roof
a jumpy dumpy that sounds dangerous
uh you know with my super mario skills
anything is possible
i can't
[Music]
she's gone okay she's a phoenix she'll
be back
it didn't hurt enough unfortunately i
don't think you could take any damage in
this game
wow yeah all the landings are so soft
like
it feels like i'm landing on sukkah
hey we need a green wheel see one
anywhere okay i'm just exploring this
beautiful scenery can i go in the ice
no why not i want to go i have a
powerful
stream you guys it looks fine on me for
me i'm both on stream or
like uh the game it looks fine i don't
know maybe it's a youtube thing because
it doesn't even obs doesn't even say
that i have any dropped ramps
yeah i'll reset the stream at a lower
bitrate
[Music]
oh hey have one of the wheels i put in
uh next on the roof
[Music]
nice
wait oh you put it up there nice
yeah that's the first person that you
found oh wait no that was there already
right
was that wheel there before you put it
there i put it there i put it there
you guys it's exactly the same as it was
before it was it might be a youtube
thing because i don't know
the game okay we gotta find more wheels
uh yeah we need a green one
okay i will find it uh
uh the game doesn't give me very much
hints unfortunately like i don't know
what to do guys
i can restart obs i guess
yeah the game doesn't really give you
that many hints in general you just kind
of have to like figure it out with what
they give you
okay i don't want to run in on low
[Music]
settings
yeah we'll just turn everything off this
music reminds me of outer wilds
you know it's still laggy
i'm i'm a baby on on top of the roof
there were like some buttons you could
push as well
maybe that's like somehow connected to
the thing below here where you can also
push buttons maybe one of us has to be
at the top and one of us has to be
uh in this room over there that's a
that's a really good uh that's a really
good point yeah
let's try that all right okay here i'll
go to the roof
okey-dokey maybe maybe it's too early
but
let's let's try it out okay
all right i'm up here okay i'm gonna
push the buttons
can you just tell me if anything changes
or does anything
[Music]
oh yeah i see it changing so like the
length of the wave is changing
oh
oh i hear someone again
[Music]
right now or before before now it's not
anymore
yeah we basically got rid of that dude's
voice
i hear him again yeah can't go back our
recording is yeah
so that he told us before 47
oh 45 did you also push something at the
top or
yeah i changed it all right
so now we hear him again 47 45
whatever that means coordinates can i
press f3 in this game
[Music]
like in minecraft yeah
maybe we should look around a little bit
more because we still need uh
one we need one wheel for the
gate and then a green wheel for the
uh snowmobile garage door
i can't find no more gates uh gates uh
you can't wheels them can i open uh
drawers no
[Music]
yeah i don't know i don't know we're
supposed to do this is where the other
game
let's start oh it found a wheel okay i
found a wheel oh it's a green one
yeah i found it next to the uh next to
the fireplace
wow nice
[Music]
okay the snowmobile looks like it's
ready to go maybe
oh nice
ah so says we shouldn't be fooling
around
oh okay i guess we're not ready yet
let's try to find one more wheel
[Music]
maybe it's in the sink
maybe up here i think we're looking for
a red one
could be hidden somewhere
uh i really can't get that
wheel yet because it's like a gate
yes we can't do this part yet
maybe we have to respond to the guy
first maybe we have to
figure out i opened i opened the door
oh which door uh the gate outside
oh uh cause you could only open it from
the other side so
you had to jump i found a rail
oh wait i'm coming but it's like oh i
see something i have to warm it up
are you supposed to be over there oh
okay never mind
did i do that lag around
i don't know you're fine okay
i'm gonna warm up the wheel at the
fireplace i know that sounds weird but
it has ice all over it
oh smart good thinking
i don't know if it works now
all right so we can hear the guy
and then maybe we have to communicate
with them
the warming up doesn't doesn't wink
[Music]
do you see the ice on the way no no all
i see is a walkie-talkie
that's interesting i'm holding a whale
that is not just my imagination
uh the the tundra is making go crazy huh
no no a little too cold for phoenix
oh i can place it on the fire under on
the
what's it called on the cooking style
stuff
now it's melting the wheel is melting
something up yes a wheel that will be
our soup tonight
nice
i'm looking forward to it okay
a red wheel goes
on this gate outside there's like one
section over here
that we can't get to might be this one
oh but this is blue
is it tiny thingy blue on the inside uh
yeah yeah it looks look maybe maybe it
looks like it yes it looks like it yes
yes
i should open this one raja i'm on my
way
[Music]
open oh
what is that
shouldn't be fooling around later on is
touching up i think we got to figure out
the uh frequency thingy first
okay let's hold on guys i'm gonna fix
something really quick
i'll be right there i found something
that i have to investigate
we're a little bit blurry but this
should help with the leg
okay
what was that i saw something on the i
have
acquired another wheel where are you
finding all these oils
on top of the roof oh
this one's red so maybe that goes into
the door inside
oh yeah i could think that i saw prompt
on the wall
yes yes it works yeah maybe it's just
lagging here because particles particles
really freak me out
all right nice work well what the hell
is this stuff
oh coordinates oh we can't mess around
with any of this stuff yet
oh but we have coordinates
47 45 what was it 40 yeah
45 47 then
45 37 no not sure anymore we should
listen again
uh okay i think i messed with the thingy
so i'll go
back up to the roof and fix it okay
yes i know it's like it's probably
better once we get to a different
section of the game
actually seems better when i'm outside
for some reason
the like isn't as bad
i hear him i i hear him i hear him
okay not anymore not anymore
all right so uh i don't know if we're
maybe we're supposed to match the
frequencies or something
let's try yeah hold on i hear him i
hear him no
yeah i hear him out there out there he
only says out there
like a robot try to speed up the
frequency
or like uh
[Music]
i hear him he only says out there though
he's like repeating
oh uh okay try to make the frequency
like longer i guess
wait a second wait i was like super long
now
oh i hear out there out there out there
can we get like one bigger or
uh only less now
yeah i don't know what we're supposed to
be doing maybe
maybe down down
i heard him for a sec i hear him
yeah but leave it like that leave it
like that our coordinates 47
45 okay 47.45 wait let's let's swap
nine by echo beta four
what four eleven some oh my god that's
so much information
write that down write that down forty
seven forty five
nine by echo
[Music]
all right go up to go up to the roof so
you can see the different frequency
stuff and then
we can try matching it i don't know i
think we're supposed
[Music]
okay
i am indeed yes all right uh we're gonna
try we could try to match it to one of
them i tried to do it to the
red one i think or the pink one
uh what do you mean
so i control the green one now check
check the different frequencies up there
you should see different colors
oh okay i only see green oh yeah yeah go
to the next one
oh okay i see red uh-huh
okay i don't know i was gonna try to
match them
and pink okay
okay then uh let's yeah okay
let's let's match them okay
um okay so i see i see i see
and this one is really really like big
so let's make it smaller
oh oh no wait the other way around okay
we have the master green one to the blue
one okay
bigger begun begun become bigger
bigger bigger okay stop
that's right that's right more and more
uh oh i see it yeah
wait i hear music do you want to come
baby
[Music]
oh yeah but you don't want to listen to
music i do i don't wanna i don't wanna
i'm coming down
i hear it it is indeed the chicken dance
dance my chickens
dance dance i'm going back up
okay okay hey this looks like the moon
[Music]
so uh you guys aren't giving kiara the
answers right
oh yeah okay we'll be matching the red
one now
so small small small small small small
very small small small small small small
small small small
small stop maybe there at one bigger
oh and then uh uh not so wide
exactly yeah a bit more a bit more a bit
more
[Music]
do you not hear anything yet
that's that's so something i can make my
chickens fall asleep better
holy crap music
[Music]
all right then let's do another one okay
okay let's do blue one the blue one is
very very uh
narrow and very very tall
mhm i think a bit
maybe one more narrow and one more
taller or two more
a bit more taller
uh yeah one more and then a bit more
narrow
uh not no more no more tall one one less
towel
yeah and then a bit more narrow i think
[Music]
did you write that down no but it's
repeating so i think it's okay okay
[Music]
i can mess with the i can mess with the
thingies oh what does that do
but we probably have to refuel the
snowmobile so maybe somebody has to be
on the other side but let's do the
coordinates thing first because i feel
like
we're more able to do that
okay all right i'm in the coordinates
room
all right maybe you want to repeat some
of the coordinates to me
okay okay wait um
okay we have to both do this at the same
time so
we might have to write it down
[Music]
can't be write it
i'll let her i let her write it down
[Music]
sorry for the delay it's cause uh yeah
the game wouldn't let us select our
windows sound devices and we had to
figure out another way oh this is
otherwise and
coordinates written down okay
there's a lot of coordinates yeah i
think there's four right
oh one two three four five six
six actually okay well we'll we'll play
someone
there's actually three pairs right
there's two
there's charlie and better we have twice
and then there's delta and echo once
each
okay well i guess okay the numbers are
what do the they're they mean on here
see
all right so i can move it to the side
and you can move it up so
okay oh we're doing charlie 753 first
[Music]
or wait tata's dead
yeah so charlie charlie 753 is the third
one from the top
what oh yeah yeah i see it
okay and then what's the second one with
charlie you said beta145
uh the second one is beta754
oh okay i see it
all right you
wait how do i keep us i don't i don't
think we're uh
i don't know if we're supposed to keep
up there but i think that one is um
scott's hut do you see that all right
let's let's see what the next one is
uh delta 195. okay i don't think we need
to use the machine
we could just do with our eyes delta 195
and the second coordinate
that's that's uh from the bottom the
third one
no no 195 yeah delta 195 is from the
bottom the first one
yeah and then we have echo169
okay that is from the left the fifth one
okay i guess that's the radio tower yeah
that's right send signals and we have
baga 481 oh that's not the radio tower
it's send signals
that's the fourth one from the top
with charlie 447
ah that's the kiss from a rose
i think where is it yeah that's the kiss
from the rose
okay so we have the the tower the kiss
from the rose and what was the first one
oh uh scott's hut okay okay
all right send signals scott's hut he's
from a rose i don't know
what it was oh i thought was first so
yeah the close
should we go there first but the closest
is the tower i think we need to refill
first but now at least we have wait oh
yes
but we can't go back according to
charlie 753
by vega 754 zelda
does this mean that they are in the
middle of that because they gave us
three coordinates
free places and then they that would
mean that they are at the ancient
structure
but i don't i don't know i'll trust you
on this one
okay okay
um i'll go to the far away fuel
thingy the levers and then you stay on
the one
inside okay okay
okay so uh on the fuel levers i don't
know if it's fuel
i'm just gonna call it that there's yeah
uh
each thing has like a each lever has a
number so there's five
seven eight four seven
eight uh so i guess just tell me the
levels for it maybe
i have minus eight minus four minus four
minus eight minus four on on the three
levers but on the
on the thingy on the big
tank that's oh that's now it's filled up
oh actually i think we had to get into
that green line huh
ah to the green point okay then low one
or do i have to do so i probably also
have one or something
how is it now oh wait
[Music]
um
we're still a little bit a little bit
above green
so oh uh what were the numbers again
uh minus eight minus four minus four
but like i turned down minus four and
then it went down
uh a little bit from nine to eight
but we need to go to six
all right so that's even like
apparently math is involved so let's uh
oh no wait where were you originally i
forgot where that place was
and the gates yeah over here
ah there okay yeah
okay so maybe um
okay it's math so it
i saw you dashing how did you dash oh
what shift
oh thank you
ah okay so i think if the maximum number
is nine then maybe put like the
oh okay i see so we have to get the max
yeah yeah okay i get it
do you get it i don't know if i can
explain it i
i totally get it i totally get it
okay uh add um
i just just add try adding uh i don't
know
i'm not good at math but essentially
the maximum number on this one is nine
and so
i can only minus four twice and minus
eight once
you get what i mean excuse me the
detective watson isn't the maximum
number
actually 10 is just not written there
because they can't uh put in so many
numbers
yeah you're right you're right exactly
that's true okay and now it would be at
what six
[Music]
uh i didn't minus anything but yeah if i
minus four then it'll be at six
oh no wait because i think i put more
than ten in so i think you can only see
ten but technically
all the other numbers that you put in
also affect it because on minus four
it goes to eight oh
and yeah because the numbers i put in
right now are eight and four
i understand i understand i understand
it's it said eight now you say uh yeah
cause i minus
four yeah it took out four
wait to which number do we want it to be
again not 10 right
we want it to be five right at six at
six a six
okay we want it to be at six and it's
now at
eight yeah after our minus four it's at
eight
what about now it's at five
is that not good no it's gotta be at six
okay uh
um i'm not good at math i'll let kiara
do this one
i believe in you chiara
thank you
[Music]
just add adam add a random number
okay
minus four
okay now it's at eight
because i did mine oh wait hold on
wait
oh wait
[Music]
[Laughter]
what number is it now
wait
i feel like i could do it but i just uh
i'll be by these numbers
all right don't mind us any numbers yet
okay just put it set it to no no minus
okay
okay i got it
all right do two minus four
done what are we at
ten you did both minus four
yeah oh wait do i have to put it down
around
oh wait one second one second okay try
it again
uh okay we're now at the
fort
i thought i did the math right no i did
not
hold on hold on once again
i get it
okay do minus eight and minus four
actually i don't think that's gonna work
but
okay uh
oh there are two sevens oh okay um i was
trying to yeah okay wait one second just
do uh
minus two fourths minus two fours
[Music]
for some reason i was confusing seven
was nine did it
oh yeah i get it we have to pinpoint
yeah the one
uh in the middle the try and we have to
make a triangle out of the three
destinations and pinpoint it in the
middle which would be the ancient
structure yeah we gotta triangulate
their location the ancient structure
okay do you know the coordinates for
that because i probably have to put it
in the trunk
uh yes i do uh c six
two four and eight five two one
uh what is a charlie alpha
oh wait wait wait
always goes back yeah i think we have to
be fast
wait what is it again
are you controlling something over there
i'm just putting it i'm putting it up oh
there we go
oh maybe let's do the same time
yeah okay
that was nope not there
all right i'll let you move and then
i'll go up
stop okay
i don't know maybe the second one
overlaps the first one
okay okay everybody out there maybe
we'll stop at the second one
oh it wasn't enough
sorry what sorry i was uh i was uh
roasting my chat
oh uh it won't let us get in yet
everybody
somehow okay
oh or or it wants us to make
uh let's let's maybe it wants us to make
free circles
yeah yeah and just put all the other
ones probably it resets after we make a
third circle and then they're like ah
those are wrong
so it says let's make a circle there we
go oh wait we actually got the right
okay
okay let's go try to get started the
tower first okay maybe
got it okay another let's get the house
okay
ah you're right
[Music]
we put our brains together carrot we got
one big
brain up
[Music]
oh we forgot to open the gate i think
it's fine
[Music]
moving on to the next puzzle
i'm gonna like get stranded it's scary
it's not as laggy right guys
oh do we have to figure out that's a
snowmobile
uh it looks frozen over i don't know
let's warm it up with our passion
rabbit rub it and maybe we get on top
oh here's i guess this is
a little bit it's like an abandoned mine
i don't like the atmosphere
just pretend it's minecraft okay
i'm sure our uh comrades are here safe
and sound and we're gonna save them
they're dead amen didn't you realize
that they're dead
uh it looks like we got an elevator it
looks like we got another elevator and
another elevator and another elevator
and then uh two more elevators
that looks like a lot of fun
that was irony
hey i'm on the elevator
i'm i'm stuck i'm on the second platform
can you can you bring nothing down
because i think i'm bugged
yeah all right i'll come down you
oh wait okay i i when i crouched i was
able to go down
here so should i go up to the other
elevator
uh i don't think you can get in on that
side but i'll see if i can try to help
you get in on that side maybe there's
like a control or something
that rail i went up i was able to go in
okay well i can't go this way because
there's a rail block away never mind
all right well i can't go this way do
you think i'll die if i jump from here
i don't think so about it everything's
very soft
i'll go up one more
i know it doesn't go up anymore
ah but i can go down
okay so the the uh elevators all have
different symbols on them it looks like
oh
i think yeah i found the toilet
okay that's good to know thank you
you're welcome
oh so i'm like stuck up here
oh can i help you
um maybe oh my elevator moved by itself
what did you press
oh i pressed down i don't guess i'm in
the right elevator here
uh because a lot of the times i think
with
some um you want to move out i'm taking
you up
uh nope it doesn't go any oh yeah okay
oh you went down with that
now i can't get back first i went down
and then i went up no
now it went down oh this is the other
way around so if i go down now does
yours go up
yes it's going up wow it's like
weighted so when one elevator moves the
other one moves
well then okay i'm
whatever makes me go up can
go no more me lady mine too yeah it has
buttons on it but i can't
okay uh all right let's look at the
symbol is there a symbol on the
on that one uh you mean on the ground
yeah like on that elevator there's like
a dynamite
yeah okay uh mine has a dynamite
there's uh one with rails and gold and
there's also
um a diamond one
okay yeah uh i in order to find the
other ones i have to move this elevator
though because i'm stuck
okay yeah that's fine do it okay
[Music]
i want melon i'm gonna go cut some melon
later okay
i'm in the one with the with the mine
cart
okay oh should i
move it oh oh yeah i'm going up okay oh
it should be going down there yeah yeah
all right okay maybe i can move one for
you now i have one that's uh a pickaxe
nope i can't get in it never mind ah
wait
i guess i can't get into that one either
at the moment so
oh i think we have to do something else
first there was one more elevator
yeah probably okay i'll go back down
what's an elevator that uh what's a
different elevator you can't get into
um
[Music]
checking over uh currently cannot
uh wait but that one no no one
can wait
oh i am
[Music]
i am going from the very top to the very
bottom
to elevator with diamond okay
all right i can get that one
oh sorry is that on your level now
yeah but this one it just i mean this
one just lets us get to the uh
other one hold on let let's look for a
different one
okay i'm looking for one that
uh has like a dinosaur eating a diamond
if you see anything like that
okay
what you doing uh i feel like i
got myself stuck so i'm checking the
surroundings but i think um
by moving the elevators
uh yeah i think we have to undo
something
okay what elevator can't you get into
right now um
right
the dynamite one can you bring that one
down so it goes one up for me
nice um now i guess
i'm going up oh i can't go up anymore oh
yeah
can you can you make it go up
okay uh no i guess so let's go down
[Music]
oh no yeah hmm i didn't
oh wait wait wait wait wait
okay
[Music]
yeah i'm back at uh i can ride the
minecart one
and i can go on the toilet and i can not
ride the pickaxe one mining a diamond
i actually wait if you can ride that one
are you able to get into that one hold
on
one second i think it's at the top so go
back into the
dynamite one and then take me to the top
and then i'll uh
okay let me go back down yeah let's try
them this might be it even though this
is where we were before but maybe we
missed something
for a little bit okay are you ready all
right no
uh i'm at the minecart one okay
let me know when you're do you have a
minecart one
uh yes yes yes wait uh
ah yeah can we go up with that
oh now i can get in oh never mind that
was one too high i think
oh okay uh are you in the in the
elevator
yeah i can go up or down
ah i think you have to move that
elevator down from the not not the one
we're currently in
but the the the
yeah the oh no
i think yeah we have to move it
oh wait i can pass it never mind
i am at the very top now okay
and i see i see two elevators but i
can't i can only go on top of them
oh which what are the symbols on them
one is the the the pickaxe one or the
other one is like a
um a a drag
a dragon head oh yeah yeah yeah okay
all right i don't know if i can get on
either of those either but i'll check
yep no problem i think i'm stuck here
all right uh the only way it can get
back down is through the dynamite
elevator
uh so i guess we need to find a way
where
uh you're in the mine cart one and then
uh
you can use the diamond one
yeah yeah yeah yeah now i am however
stuck at the top so you you would have
to
bring me the minecart one back up that's
right
are you in it yes i am in all right i'm
out
me too um
so on this level that we're currently on
the mine the pickaxe
elevator is two two yeah i think two
levels of
no one level above me one level i think
the only one i can access uh might be
the
dinosaur one but i don't even think i
can get to that one either
brain activate
uh maybe maybe we have to go one more
step back
hmm
[Music]
sure i said we gotta get on top of the
elevator at some point
okay i'm on top of the
i'm on top of the uh dynamite one
oh okay wait on top of
any elevator not any but like sometimes
we might need that
oh oh wait you're on top of the dynamite
one
it's okay i'm moving it down so your
ears goes up does that help you
uh not really
wait bring it back put it back down all
the way
okay
okay i'm in like a different area now
i'm on top of oh
okay i'm crossing over wait
i see the dinosaur elevator but it's too
low okay can you
oh man i'm right by the pickaxe one but
you can't move that one huh
oh wait if i'm if i move my elevator
back up the pickaxe one
should be accessible
no no no no current no no
i can i can access the minecart one
again
boys to the minecart one okay hold on do
you bring up back the dynamite one i'll
try to get on top of the minecart
okay you should bring it up
okay
all okay uh now the minecart one can you
go back to it
i think we're getting it we're getting
it uh yes yes yes
i am in the mine cart uh go up so
mine goes down i guess
all right now go back uh go back to the
weekend
[Music]
um
i gotta find a way to access it so i
guess i gotta find a way to get maybe if
i go on top of the diamond one okay
we're gonna go back to the beginning
oh but i could
[Music]
i can go on top of the my top right now
okay
right now maybe that does something can
you go up or down
well i'm on on top of it so
i i can't control it uh now it's going
up okay
see the platforms above you like a is
there uh
anything that you could go up to oh yeah
maybe one more
up yeah
i'm here again oh
okay but maybe maybe that's that was
maybe that was necessary for some reason
i think there's probably like one
elevator that's in the midsection either
on your side or my side where you can
access
the uh mine the the
pickaxe one yeah yeah
let's go from the bottom and then we'll
try to see if there's any that we can go
on the top
of the elevators okay okay
uh uh can you bring me back the minecart
one so i can jump on it or in it
upside down uh other way around
are you inside oh i'm on top of it
oh sorry can you bring it uh yep yep
and then back up again thank you
okay so we're going down
um
you can do whatever i'm off too oh
okay are you at the uh dynamite
yeah i can go in okay you
uh bring it because well right now i
only see the top so i gotta get in
okay oh we're back at the uh
okay so on your first one at the diamond
are you there
diamond yeah back at the bottom
is the same for both of us so then i was
thinking that if she could get on top of
like a certain platform
oh yeah diamond just uh no wait my
minecart
how about you get on top of the dynamite
is there anything when you go on top of
dynamite
oh good idea can you bring it down uh
actually yeah the other way around
one more yeah yeah
i am on tap
okay well i can't go up anymore so i'll
go down
oh yeah i was here before
ah but
it's confusing maybe we should swap
sides you want to swap yeah let's swap
it's better it's better that way because
then we both have seen like uh
okay how do i get out of here are you on
the den are you on top of the side of my
one
um i never mind come on okay i'm out
don't freeze to death i'm if you need
some heat just cuddle the phoenix
okay oh hey hi
all right enjoy thank you you too
all right swapping ideas swapping uh
perspectives
now i can see what kiara was dealing
with over here
getting some new knowledge a new
viewpoint all right so dynamite going
okay it only goes somewhere going down
maybe i should go back up to the top and
take a look
[Music]
i have absolutely no idea watson oh
uh hold on i'm at the like where we
started i'm getting a new vantage point
of the whole area
all right so i can go in the diamond one
and diamond one leaves the dynamite one
and dynamite leads to
the minecart one
and then this is the pickaxe one which
she can't get to
because why is the pickaxe one anyways
is it this one then
but how can we get to that one if nobody
can get to it i know maybe this is the
dinosaur one
oh
okay i'm gonna try to get over to that
area over there because it looks like
there's some stuff over there that might
be useful
i'm going back can i just jump from here
uh
[Music]
can we do the dynamite one of my dynamic
uh yes i'm in
[Music]
okay uh can you bring it uh go down i
guess
okay that's the minecart one
this also is minecart one so there's one
twice which means we have to use it
either she goes on top or i go on top
and then we have access to the pickaxe
one with the pickaxe one neither of us
have access to
neither of us have access to the pickaxe
one
right because it doesn't move unless
it's
unless somebody else moves it uh but
there must be a platform that she can
get to
with the diamond one that i can't get
[Music]
oh there's a platform up here okay ah
okay okay okay wait uh go up can you go
down i guess on that
okay
going down
yes yes i am now stuck but probably you
are not you can go back you can go back
okay access either of these this is too
high this is a dinosaur one
this is a pickaxe one but is there a
platform down there
maybe this way
i guess i can't go this way
i need to find a way to get into the
excellent
can you bring the diamond one back
maybe i missed it oh yeah wait
[Music]
did you say diamond or dynamite i'm
getting confused it sounds so similar
minecart sorry i said it wrong my card
okay minecart you want it to go up or
down on your side
uh up on my side okay
uh the opposite
[Music]
how do we get to the pickaxe one maybe
she can only get two on her side but
when i was doing it on that side i
couldn't figure out a way to get out
uh go down oh sorry up yes
in minecart yes
okay go back to the dynamite
go down
sorry i'm getting really confused my dad
and my dad and my daughter like yes i am
uh do you want to go anywhere kiara i
could help you get somewhere if you want
i i would like to have the diamond one
uh
go one but
actually i have no idea
i'm so stuck um
[Music]
well so the diamond one is currently not
accessible but i guess the diamond one
really doesn't matter
because that's just that's just the one
that is like
the basics so if i go up
maybe i should try to get on top now i
did that before didn't i and then i went
into nowhere
oh god but but we can try i guess
let's see minecart one is probably what
i think when i go
can you do the the dynamite one and get
it one down now i gotta get into it
first
okay okay are you below it or above it
above it this is confusing
can you can you get in yeah yeah yeah
i'm inside okay
okay um so
okay can you bring it up on your side
yeah
uh oh sorry one more uh back back
oops yeah okay oh let's let's go
anywhere
oh oh was i here before yes okay now
that's just
okay uh uh down
one more is that possible oh
it
can now is um i can now get on to the
pickaxe one
you can get onto the pickaxe and i can
go over to
the dragon one which is currently not
here but not a little
yes i can get onto the pickaxe one what
and i do something wrong and i can
i can get onto it and i can get in i
mean i can get onto it if you
if you were to move it but i can also
get into it
can i get into it yeah i lays out
because i can walk by foot i can walk
uh if i'm uh if i go up then uh i could
yeah no i can't i can't get on the way
down into it oh
this is progress i think yeah i must
have not seen that i guess
oh sorry
so what do we do i want to go go into it
or on to it
because we want to go into it oh no but
wait if i go huh
oh i but i can't control it on my side
because i can't get it
okay then i'll then i'll go i'll go into
it
and and then i'll move it up on my side
first to see what happened
oh yeah yeah well done i'm about to get
on oh okay
you want to get on top of it i can't i
can't go
higher now but oh yeah you get you make
it go down nice and i go up
and now we go up again nice
and now right chris now
now i can get on top of the dragon no i
can go into the dragon one into the
dragon
i'm moving around let's see what happens
progress no wait i think yeah on your
side i was able to go
on top of it before so if i go up then
you should be able to go into it but
you have to wait i know the other way
down there
can you go into it now hold on
uh oh shoot i need to to get to that
side i need to
i need the pickaxe one back again okay
crossover progress
you need it you need it back yeah yeah
how would you flow right now
[Music]
i guess i missed something when i was on
the other side
oh wait what no no no problem anymore i
think
you wanted you wanted to go oh no wait
i'll never mind
pro i know no no no problem no
problem no problem
can you get into it yeah uh i'm crossed
over now i can access the dinosaur one
which i can get
nice i'm gonna get it
do that yes i am in i'm inside the
dinosaur
okay we're together then should we go up
but uh when you go up mine goes down so
oh but that's okay
that's okay because i reached some
no that's uh that's the only one wait
hold on okay i'm out
wait and i'm out i'm at the door
okay okay
was that it it only took like 40 minutes
or how long have we been here
oh
go all right
all right one more time okay
all right three two one go
oh wow that was quite difficult yeah i
think it's just because when i was on
that
i think like in the house and here as
well we both made progress after seeing
each other's point of views
yeah yeah because it's a little
difficult sometimes to like describe it
oh okay there's your tent for you and me
oh yeah well i think this is was the
previous people who got stranded
we could warm up by the fire buy out our
clothes
we don't need a fire we have a phoenix
right there
that's why i haven't frozen to death yet
all right we're gonna look at
the next one what is it is this a riddle
again there's a turn style
there's a lever there's a gate
oh come on another riddle
everything's already over here
[Music]
oh hey there's another turn style here
yeah
let's use it
oh maybe we have to i don't know okay
let's fix this oh i'm going the other
side
how'd you get over there
oh hey some stairs there's a gate here
a red gate okay so we have different
color gates there's one
yellow one blue uh
one red i pulled a letter for the red
letter
um one went up oh yeah it opened up one
trigger to get down i can close it again
well then let me see
okay i think it's oh do it one more time
all right i'm on the other side so i'm
at a turn style here
okay oh
what is
this is where it came from this is where
it came from
wait can you hit the red lever again yep
one moment
[Music]
we need a blue liver
okay there's no blue levers huh
no no all right
try exploring around with the turnstiles
and see if there's a see if you can find
a blue one
okay i see a yellow lever on my side but
i can't get to it yet
[Music]
i wonder if i need to turn styles so
there's eyes here but
if i could just turn one more time but i
can't because there's ice
i wonder if the ice thaws
is there nothing are you stuck like is
there nothing on your side
oh yeah there's nothing here can you uh
activate the red lever and then um
i guess you know yeah through it
i like the ambience here
[Music]
okay so we need a uh
oh then i'm checking one more time wait
a second okay
i found something i found a tunnel oh a
tunnel
tunnel of love
[Music]
what's down here is there anything down
here
yeah around it didn't work the little
fingers now
i i'll move the red one again so i can
explore as well
[Music]
i can see stuff through here but i don't
know what i'm supposed to do with this
i can't reach it i found the blue
leather
oh i see you hey
hi there okay you found the blue one
hold on just stay there
okay i pulled it do it again
is there any way for you to get back to
the red one or do the blue one one more
time before you go
uh okay
all right i'll do the red one and i
don't need a blue one again
[Music]
okay okay okay
excuse me
all right now the blue one when you get
back to it
uh for that i think i have to move the
red one again that's fine that's fine
okay
breakfast right hopefully
we need to find a way to get to the
yellow one
um but i guess i could control the blue
one and the red one for her she's like
in a good spot to get to the yellow one
and we'll do a little swaparooni
[Music]
uh wait all right let's swap sides you
go in through the other one
uh we have to open the three gates okay
i see you you're you're at the
red level now uh
no i can't get there i think i can get
to the blue one first
should i should i pull out the blue one
again
oh hey we're at the same place oh hi so
maybe you s you s
you you you should stay here i'll stay
here and you do what i was doing
i think you'll see something that i
didn't
[Music]
um oh yeah okay
uh blue leather please
blue lever again
[Music]
yeah but wait wait uh oh wait a second
i want to see something a blue lever
again
[Music]
okay okay okay so basically when i turn
the red one
uh and and you turn the blue one then
over there the only one that's left is a
yellow one
yeah yeah there's so there's a yellow
switch there's a
i saw a yellow switch on the left side
but i couldn't find a way to get to it
but maybe i just did it wrong so
maybe you should try another controller
guess i'll put the
red one back i guess
i'll probably have to mess with it
because
[Music]
i'll put the red one back up again i
guess i don't know how to get over there
this is gonna take a while again
to be expected
why are some people saying hi at the
same time hello
[Music]
can you do the blue one
but you can't from there on you cannot
get to the red one in any way
oh maybe try that although i wonder if
you went here before
you did
uh i've been there on that side but uh
hold on i gotta reactivate the blue one
[Music]
activated the red one beautiful
cara is like a cheeto uh
this is such a maze do you have
access to both the blue one and the red
one at the moment
oh where did i go
[Music]
bye
confusing did you see the yellow switch
because uh you can see it through like
all the holes in the wall oh i didn't
see
oh maybe yeah maybe it was somewhere
there
is that the turnstile that's stuck at
the rock
[Music]
oh
no
i'm just running around like a crazy
place and
trying to understand this place i don't
think i can show her because i think
the levers have to be activated to get
there just go through the
all the red and blue gates and tell me
what okay blue please
red blue
[Music]
oh
no problem no problem
okay
what i did before
[Music]
how come sometimes i can use it
sometimes i can't didn't i use this last
time
[Music]
oh
hey did i do this before why am i so
confused now
my brain is uh are you not able to reach
the red one
no i can't because i think uh oh yeah
i want my something up there i think
they have to help me
are we are we both stuck then i'm
if you leave everything the way it is i
can push the red one myself
and probably go back no no no i can't no
no no
but i pulled up the red one
i think you have to help me on this one
with the turnstile just go on the other
side and use it
where i'm right now i can turn the the
i can pull the lever over the red one
oh wait yeah no i'm stuck
oh okay okay
[Music]
what's in i'm there
oh what kind is regular
the european version of it oh
that's like different chocolate or
something yeah
yeah chocolate tastes different and
they're a bit
thinner and the cookie tastes a bit
different too
but i kind of prefer it it's called
mikado
so i think yes apparently
two sources of um the ancient ones
um you have like one we we're not really
i don't know if it's true could be wrong
but we
we don't really have to go in together
one person should kind of stay at the
levers i guess
yeah and eventually we
we would be able to reach the yellow one
yeah and then and then once the yellow
lever is arranged that would open up the
yellow door that is next to the red
lever so then i would be able to
move on as well okay well i'm getting
stuck
in between the blue and the red level
okay i move the red one can you move now
[Music]
oh can you move no uh
i mean no uh it's just the blue one i
guess
[Music]
okay this one as in
the levers okay
okay all right stop
stop okay i'm stopping but where are you
mom i'm in the middle at no level you
want me to move like all their heights
should i move letters yeah yeah yeah
you're on love okay okay
i need red but i can't get to red now
because there the blue level was pulled
uh wait
can you get out
[Music]
uh i guess so oh yeah i guess so yeah
can you pull the blue one
wait but i think i messed up
it's so confusing
wait wait bob okay okay you get now
now now
uh yes yes uh uh okay can you can you
pull the blue one again
uh i don't know if i can get back if i
do that
um okay okay i'll pull it again i'll
pull it again she'll be fine
okay now i can pull the red one okay
okay
and i can i can also yeah no
i can't only i get it now all right can
you do the blue one
if you can get to it no you can't get to
it i
we have to turn the turn style so i can
get into it and then get out the other
side
i think i turned it the right way
i can't i can't i'm at the i'm not the
blue one okay
i opened it or you close it whatever
all right i need you to get back to the
red one if you can
shoot should be possible
yes yes oh finally okay i don't we did
something great though before
because we were both no okay never mind
i can did i go the wrong way
[Music]
okay wait wait wait don't do that yet
oh i'm in it's you
[Music]
you gotta push it back
[Laughter]
turnstile which gets you to the yellow
switch it only has three sides right
just like this one and there's
a rock blocking it and uh because
there's a rock
blocking it it means that it has to be
turned a certain way before you can go
through to get to the other side
right so i think if we if i keep going
around
or if i turn it the correct way and then
get into it on the side you're supposed
to get into it then i can yeah
enough to get to the other side
probably yeah
[Music]
hold on wait
i think okay so it should be turned all
the way
if i want to turn it two times then it
should be you guys i'm not doing it
right i'm doing it right right
so right now there's one two three and
then this is you know
if it's turned all the way if it's
turned all the way
ah then i get into it on the other side
okay
i see now all right one second i gotta
make one more loop and get into it
again hold it okay why wow i'm gonna
is releasing our full potential
[Music]
okay oh
uh is there any way for you to get to
the blue one
um perhaps yes if i turn it back the
other way
uh i'm last time no no
dammit i'm currently uh stuck uh both
the blue one and the red one are closed
for me
all right i'll open it or
[Music]
yeah okay
maybe
[Music]
my banana red one is closed yeah cause i
have to open it in order to
come over here can you get back
okay okay so i open the red one for you
uh but now the blue one ah wait i guess
you have to do it again before you leave
yeah uh uh okay okay cause
uh okay did me moving the blue one did
something for you
yeah it opened the gate for me and now
i'm in between
[Music]
oops is it we're at the right position
now i think yeah it's fine
okay we're getting it we're getting it
[Music]
okay uh did that do something for you
uh hold on a second if i turn it this
way
i have to make a loop it's going to be
there and then if i turn it again
right so i have to turn it twice to the
left and then get on it from the left
side
and then go and get out or maybe
wait a second oh yeah and then get in it
okay
all right i figured it out all right i
gotta get it
now can you do the blue one again
uh only if i do the red one first that's
why
yeah okay on my way
[Music]
i figured it out i wasn't looking in
chat
even if i was you guys just confused me
most of the time anyways
okay all right now do it again and then
go to the red one
[Music]
okay
okay red one activated
okay i'm at the yellow switch what
okay a door open for me okay
now i don't have to touch the yellow one
anymore i think now we can go back and
figure out the blue and red
i am now in a place where the red one
would need to be opened
but yeah okay uh
do you have access to the blue one or no
no i am past
the yellow door
there's like a tourney door and then
there's a another red gate what it looks
like
looks like that's uh the end like the
the exit but i guess we both have to
come here
yeah i'm stuck
oh that's the place where we uh that i i
see
from here i see kind of see the place
where
the blue lever is so and the yellow one
is gone
so in ah
now what are the little doors for uh do
you have any access to any levers at all
uh the yellow one i guess
oh my god well i got through i will
check if there's another lever no
you're just to leave me behind no not at
all
not coming back coming back okay
okay so in theory the door is open here
the path is open
so i need the red one and then the blue
one to get out
mm-hmm the question is just does that
mean
if i go that you'll get stuck and then
i'll get stuck again
uh
[Music]
yeah no i if i do the red one
i i i will have to do the red one again
is it okay yeah
okay okay okay
[Music]
can you come over no but i'll go around
oh okay uh cause i have to do
how are we doing it
[Music]
yes
one more time oh yeah and then the red
one
another one
i guess i'll go through on the other
side
hello
[Music]
is
oh so i guess this is the ancient
ruins is it kind of looks like it
yeah i think so okay so there's no
bridge
but there's a star on the ground
probably good to know
you just did you lose your gun on it
your gun is on the ground here your
pistol oh yeah
oh this is a flare gun ah
oh they were they were trying to find
help yeah so maybe they're taking uh
they're taking uh what's it called a
shelter in the
ancient thingy oh i found a pattern this
might be useful
[Music]
what is this all right so this star
pattern here that's the one that's on
the bridge and so i guess the comet is
the one that's on the other side of the
bridge
so i guess the sun is before the star
like if we check over here
check over here
oh yeah oh wow wait what the heck this
wasn't here before
yeah pull the lever you gonna do over
time
[Music]
i did it one more time does it do
something no
try moving any of the symbols on the
thingy
uh oh
okay i moved something
try moving some by the comet
maybe i'm not supposed to be looking at
it or something we're both
[Music]
okay i just moved a bunch of them
randomly
all right i'll go back out oh wait let's
all right hold on
i'll report back
sorry okay so right now the bridge
only has one square that has the star
and one square that has the sun
oh another one appeared in front of me
the moon just appeared in front
oh
it's okay i'm back
so whatever you did there you brought it
up and then it it dropped again
actually did nothing oh
maybe it's times do they slide back on
their own
uh they reset after a while yeah
okay
okay i see the way that it's connected
[Music]
okay
i actually didn't oh there you are i
didn't really see the other side yet so
check it out
[Music]
okay i see that's how you died
did you die yeah yeah okay um
[Music]
okay i i'm not sure
what this is supposed to tell us so
there's a star in the sun
at the bridge ah does that mean that
in this pattern we want um the sun into
the star
also at the bottom uh actually i don't
know
yeah the bridge starts off with the star
and because the comet
is on the other side i'm assuming that's
what's on the other side
how do you know what was on the other
side did you see that i'm just assuming
that that's what's on the other side
because if you look at the diagram
like uh the comment starts in this
position
oh and there's a gap in between the star
and the comments i was just assuming but
i don't know
we can i guess we should try to start
by trying to get the star and the sun in
the right position
right
it does it's the only thing that the
lever does resetting the
oh this thing here probably
all right so we know the one that works
the moon comes up so it goes
so i guess the star and the sun are
already in the correct position so the
moon has to be
moved into a different position oh
are we just guesting then well i mean
it's not really
guessing because it's like a process of
elimination if the star and the sun are
in the correct location
let me see if the sun disappears when
you move it
no it doesn't move
[Music]
yeah it's like trial and error yeah
okay well so the moon is at the very top
now but like
how do i know what else i want there
just trying randomly
[Music]
you remember when i died where you the
moon was that time
we
you died you died when uh
i just died again
whatever you did to the sun one uh you
just moved it and it
yeah it killed me how how
how how how is that possible what why
did i kill you
did you stand on the bridge yes maybe
i'm not just supposed to stand on it i
don't know
let me see if it happens again
oh my god
okay because maybe it's supposed to be
like we can stand on the star one
because it's connected to two sides and
the sun one is only connected on one
side so it just falls
we can't see yeah yeah the next one is
there
yeah yeah you got ah um
ah wait maybe while you're moving that
if you move the right one in the right
position it would be
connecting itself to the star bridge to
this
uh sun bridge piece and i would see it
here yeah
yeah okay i'll move uh i'll move some
around and you tell me
okay you look like cookies look yummy
[Music]
i think about this
although i'm gonna reset it really quick
[Music]
ah i i
feel like i i don't know if you already
understood that
and i just didn't understand that you
understood it
but like see when we stand on the maybe
it's not about connecting
not not not about the fact that the star
was connected with the sun and that's
why it's
uh not falling down but like
maybe the star is in the right position
currently that's why it's not falling
down and the sun
the bridge part does not fall down
because the sun piece is not in the
right
well that's what i thought first too but
i don't know why it wasn't
clear
can you move the star thing it doesn't
do anything huh when it when it's moved
i can still stand on the bridge i guess
i'm moving a bunch of stuff around
no no changes um okay i'll move this
star
is that one not locked
the star is is locked in place no yeah
actually
okay that's why that one will never fall
down the first piece of the bridge so
the star is already in the right
position perhaps
[Music]
i can't maybe maybe that's
how it works could be could be wrong but
but
yeah so
so the sun
would have to be moved into every single
position and we will find out which one
is the right one
uh and for each each position you put it
in i have to try to stand on it to test
it out
okay okay then let's try every single
position
once you change it i'll stand on it let
me know i changed it
that was incorrect
next position please okay
all right i changed it okay
that was that was correct and i see the
moon now we have to change the moon
oh my god okay but in order to change
the moon maybe maybe have to change the
sun again just keep the
oh wait the moon disappeared okay okay
just remember the place where the sun
was at i guess okay
yeah okay okay okay
[Music]
all right try the moon does that wait
does it connect
uh it's currently not connected um yeah
the sun appears when the sun
is next to the moon but when i move the
moon to a different spot there's no line
so maybe just something else has to be
on the other side of the moon
uh not sorry if i understand the
sentence but what i know
is that um the moon piece is currently
not showing up because it only shows up
uh if the sun piece is in the right uh
right position
so currently i have two pieces on the
bridge but when the sun was in the right
position then i had a sun piece a moon
piece of the bridge as well a third
piece
i put it in the same spot but uh it's
not appearing now
oh oh there it goes oh yeah right okay
okay okay
uh yeah so i see the moon piece again
like
oh i have to stand oh wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait can you
put the sun there again where it where
it's correct
okay so now i'm standing on the sun
piece when i
don't move anything
[Music]
okay i understand oh my god no way did
you move the sun
no i didn't touch anything how does it
fall down again
it didn't do anything it just reset i
think it resets every time you die
all right okay so i am standing on the
sun piece
and the moon piece is in front of me but
once i get a walk off of the sun piece
then it all falls down okay okay just
guess i'm like locking it while i'm
standing on it yeah
yeah so when you stand on it there's
there's a line appearing between the
star the sun and the moon right now so
maybe if i
get the right well then i gotta lock the
moon into place i think
hey are you standing on the sun one yeah
ah the someone fell down but i'm back
i'm back i'm back i didn't die you you
you oh you got me back from the dead
is the moon one up the woman is still
there but i'm too scared to step on it
yeah don't do it yet
oh oh something
locked real
[Music]
okay i'm gonna move the sun one
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait i stepped on the moon one i think
it is correct
i i see the planet one the the one the
planet with the
you see the snooze around it yeah
okay oh it's it's locked it's
i think it locked itself okay can't wait
oh my god oh my god something
okay
interesting interesting things happening
here
i i i still i i was pretty much
i was walking up the bridge was complete
for a moment i think
and i walked over but i think you moved
something and then the second piece the
sun
disappeared and
and then and then everything disappeared
i think
now now i only have the sun and the star
again
i think i went to finally i went too far
but
uh we got very far because after the
saturn saturn and
one more thing showed up but
let's try to get the bridge going again
because it's all reset
um is the sun in place yeah i put it in
the same spot oh there it is okay
okay now i see the moon do you think
it's safe to step on the moon
um yes i am on the moon i see the saturn
[Music]
okay
okay yeah leave it like that now it's
locked i think
okay i see the bridge but it's
not the when bridge came up the sun
disappeared
so that means that you wouldn't be able
to pass over but oh probably i have to
pass over
oh never mind when i try to pass over
even though it's connected it uh yeah
eats me
okay okay um i am on the moon again
and i am on saturn and now the thing
the bridge comes up but there is
something that needs to be done
uh the sparkles something like those
sparkles
oh yeah it's not oh wait it's is it love
is that one
okay i'm gonna move them okay
okay i i fell down
all right hold on don't get on it yet
okay
actually
[Music]
i'm thinking i'm thinking
you're resetting my progress okay excuse
me
sorry it's okay
okay we almost got it they say we had
one point
i see it okay i'm just testing around
[Music]
all right
now it has to be connected
but i'm gonna move one of them i feel
like one of them should be moved before
everything is connected
[Music]
so like i'll put this here temporarily
and then
i'll bring should i move the
comet or the stars i think the stars
connects to the galaxy after the planet
which connects to the moon which
connects the sun which connects the star
but then
i can't connect the comet somehow so
maybe if i bring the comment
to the maybe if i bring the
comment to the
over here that they can all like kind of
be connected
i'm gonna leave it like this and then
put this back
and connect this here connects to the
planet which connects to the stars which
connects to the galaxy
it doesn't work i think i have to go on
the bridge in order to make it work
because nothing's happening here
okay okay okay i'm going on the sun
yep and it makes this the moon show up
and it locks in place so i walk on the
moon
and it makes the saturn show up and it
locks in place so i go on the saturn
and it makes the bridge show up with the
sparkles and it locked in place so i
walk over there
and i am i'm just this time i'm not
disappearing don't
uh so what happened is i'm now standing
on the sparkles on the bridge
uh but the sun disappeared okay
wait can you cross over to the other
side completely oh
yeah uh i can step on the swirly whirly
thingy
but then something else disappears too
it seems
uh but i am on the swirly really thing i
think i have to go on the other
side so then i move something for you
probably okay
so on the swirly whirly thingy i'm just
missing it seems like
one one or two more pieces to connect me
to the end
okay uh you have one on your side
no no no i am
[Music]
uh yeah so i'm on the on the swirly
wheelie the black hole
ah wait wait wait wait wait wait uh wait
wait wait uh
ah okay this ah that was not oh my god
that was
close okay okay the swirly wheely thingy
the piece i'm standing on right now
has is it looks like a bridge that
splits itself into
and um in total there's three
signs on it the first one before the
stairs split up in this one piece
uh is the is the sparkles the stars
this one is locked in place this one is
fine if i go up
left on the splitted bridge oh wait that
went that is one piece
oh my this is this is different pieces
okay the sparkles is one piece
but it is it it turns into split up
stairs
and when i go up the left side it is
connected to the swirly whirly
and if i go to the right side it is
currently connected but not locked in
with the comet so i would reckon that
the swirly whirly is in the correct
position but the comet is not yeah i've
moved it around
okay you might die
okay scared
[Music]
okay did anything change um
no the lock on the right side of the
comet is still
uh open oh hey you're there
now you can make an image of that um and
on the left side
yeah uh yeah yeah
the the swirly willy is still locked
but the comment is not so nothing
changed okay
all right i'm gonna move some more stuff
brand
[Music]
i'm trying to i'm trying to think like
uh well they're all supposed to be
connected to each other i guess
but
i don't know where the comment is
supposed to go i guess it's supposed to
lock into place somehow maybe the comet
should be here instead
but i can't even get over here i think
[Music]
i'm it yes
have you noticed that
when we don't understand each other
we understand each other the most
[Laughter]
thank you thank you see that that was
the case when we played uh
uh uh keep on talking and nobody
explodes oh yeah yeah yeah when we spoke
in english we didn't understand each
other but when you spoke in spanish and
i spoke in japanese we didn't understand
each other
somehow but did anything change because
it looks like the comment blocked into
the thingy
okay wait i'm gonna reset it locked in
yes yes
it did oh when i stan oh my
when i stand on the comet it brings up
the
moon eating the earth
oh yeah okay the double okay okay got it
yeah
[Music]
i see
okay it should be locked in now
oh sorry uh did it reset
um it is it's not logged in
uh i feel like i saw it logging in for a
moment was that just
on it
[Music]
yeah you had it locking in for a moment
but then it unlocked i think some
some position in between uh yeah no no
it's locked in
when you step on it it moves almost
there oh the rest of the birds pretty
much
disappeared okay but we have now
uh in front of me we need one more piece
and in front of me
is uh already wait a second
oh my okay already locked in in the
right position was a moon
and in front of me is the sun and it's
not locked in so if we move
lock in the sun then i'm on the other
side of the bridge
[Music]
a chris chris and moon chris christian
crescent temporarily i think
okay i'm going back on the safe piece
okay i'm i'm on the
okay crescent moon is locked in
the sun you said you need the sun uh
yeah the sun needs to be locked in
um i'm gonna go on the comet
just for safety okay
let me know if you haven't moved uh i'll
wait i have to be on the
no i think i have to be ah wait ah
in order to lock in the sun i think i
have to stand on the crescent moon okay
what it yeah okay i have to stand here
if you ever
uh if you are about to move the crescent
moon let me know because that's probably
when i'll die
okay i'm not going to move across the
moon but i'm going to move the double
okay yep that's that's uh
okay
nice okay the stairwell came up
okay i'll is there a right side and the
wrong side
i'm going on the right side again
because we went so far with that one
oh but okay so currently
um the sparkles is not locked in with
the comet
oh okay
okay i'm gonna move the moon
okay
[Music]
okay oh
yes the the double moon that came up
it's not locked in though
[Music]
okay
ah okay uh
the crescent moon is back and locked in
place
and now we have the sun in front of me
which is the last piece
that needs to be locked in oh
okay all right i think i know
i like i have to move stuff around but i
think if i move stuff around you're
gonna
[Music]
you're gonna fall interesting
interesting you're on the which one are
you on
i am currently on the crescent crescent
moon
[Music]
what can we like prep what you are about
to move
uh if we go like back on like can you
prep that beforehand
probably the last yeah probably okay on
the sun okay
like if i am for example on the double
moon i think if i go back it resets
though
does it no okay
okay so i am now on the double moon
is there any way you can prep it while
i'm on there or should i stand on the
comments that's awesome
uh yeah you should probably step on the
comment instead
okay okay i'm gonna move the double moon
okay
how do i get the because if i put the
moon here then i can't get past it
like i need the sun to be at the end
here no
but i can't get the moon there
i have to move some stuff around i don't
think it's uh
i need to get the moon pass or the sun
past the
doesn't have to be a position it just
has to be in the right order no but then
when i connect it here
okay okay
[Music]
no but the sun has to be touching the
moon
[Music]
okay maybe this is it i see you just
locked in place the comet with the
double moon
uh yeah try stepping on it now all right
i'm stepping on i see the crescent moon
and locked in
i move over and the sun comes up
[Music]
okay i stepped off the whole bridge is
gone let's see if we have the same thing
on the other side
oh it's so it's a whale
yeah i think it would have been hard for
me to tell you how to do the other one
that feels good oh my that was that was
a damn good job amen
nice thank you thank you
[Music]
thanks for being so cooperative i i hear
scary laughing on
it please join me
yeah i already regret it
i'm scary
where are you where are you woman oh
uh okay i guess we're not in the same
area
uh but i'm in a room with a bunch of
books on the floor that are circled with
glowing arrows which are pointing to
different books and there's also a grid
in front of me with
four stones uh five stones and it says
abcde on the left
and one two three four five on the top
so it's a grid
okay okay what about
uh well i have uh okay
uh i have two posters uh
pieces of posters which also has like
numbers and
two seven six five ten and then on on
the right place so there's
in the middle there's a minus and on the
right side there's a3 e2 b4 etc
on the right side the poster has uh
different combinations
and then in the middle i have um
like a like a monitor and a screen
uh with abcde
one two three four five and i can
operate it and
move like five dots
okay and that thing is on top
of a wheel with four elements
fire uh water uh
earth and pikachu um
so i guess if i operate that
uh oh i just saw a new pikachu
appear on my board yeah i did something
oh you connected that for some reason
okay absolutely no idea what this is
i know i think i see well
so for example ah i understand
i understand i think so
i have i have two poses right um
one of them has a bunch of numbers
five numbers and the other one has the
other five numbers so on the right side
i have for example one but on the other
poster i don't have one so
we're gonna probably start with one and
that one is attached
to d2 so on my thingy here i think i
first have to do a d2
um i have to point like one of the
elements on my monitor screen thingy on
d2 let's try that okay
i have a fire on d2 yeah oh yeah okay
that's that's there yeah
wait so that continues number two would
be
uh a3 what's on e3
nothing right now
okay oh wait is that it uh you just put
a b3 down is that so simple it can
it can't be
okay number three is b1
well there must be something that you
have to do too b1 is already there
oh i don't know there's probably
something involving these books and then
maybe the way i can
uh wait that was free so
it was a three a four is there e5
do you have any any idea what the stuff
over at your place does
uh yeah so the only thing i could do is
connect between the grid that i have
with all the elements on it
and then i can't interact with them but
there's glowing circles and
arrows which uh one circle is like
circled around a book and then pointing
to another book that's circled with a
glowing
uh arrow so each book has different
numbers on it so one is like four
to nine oh five to one
three two two ten oh maybe it's a code
maybe like uh it's opposite so like if
if
on your thingy it says like a
a5 or something it's actually a one
ah you mean for example if my if my
number one
says d2 then on your book it says one is
with what number
so that would mean that the first one is
not
d2 but what it says here for five which
is c3
are we overthinking
but that actually sounds
i mean i can't think of what else the
numbers would be for but the thing is
like it goes all the way up to 10
like it says 10 is 8. uh so i don't know
if you have anything
like that like that high
[Music]
mine goes up to ten
um okay let's can i reset this though
um it doesn't have to be done in a
certain order one second let's do it
but yours just says like one to two
stuff like that right in the books
i'll read all the books so it says uh
six
to seven or it's nine to seven i can't
tell which is the right way
uh three to two five to one
ten to eight and six to four
okay so if we have one at d two
on one of these
and you said one to five which is c
frame
maybe it's a math maybe it's a math
problem
i can change okay we also have the
problem and those have elements
how the hell how do i know
which one is what element oh god
[Music]
huh we're gonna be stuck here forever
ah we'll figure it out
i try some stuff but my grade only goes
to five so i can't
i don't know what to do with that
[Music]
what does your poster say again what is
it what do the numbers say
uh which numbers i have a lot of numbers
uh
for example one and one is d2
two is a three i think i misplaced eight
two uh a3 there we go
and um three
[Music]
three is b1
whatever is there okay so i guess if
it's a code
and the arrows only go one way then if
it's one then it stays one but if it's
five then it becomes one
see what i'm saying can you repeat that
over um because the arrows are pointing
in one direction then maybe the oh
the numbers which uh
or at the start of the arrow so if it's
10 it becomes eight
but if it's eight it doesn't become ten
you know what i mean it just stays that
number
oh my god is telling me that i'm wrong
hold on one second
what's this saying
i can't read it gollum alexandra
yellen
you guys think that's important or maybe
that's just for the next
puzzle
yeah this is like uh some chemistry
stuff huh me too or
ah okay ah
actually i i think i at least figured
out
one thing um that's the thing of the
elephant elements because i have these
four elements and i can decide which
point which piece that i
place would be the elements um
but it starts out it starts off with d2
the first one
number one which is already placed on my
screen and that one starts out with fire
so since the arrows only go in one
direction
the next piece that i place would have
to be um
green stuff veggies oh
so number two was a3
and that one is currently electricity so
i'll turn it to green okay okay okay
okay okay
so maybe first of all i just put every
every little thing
every coordinate in place and then we
can try to connect them
okay okay
i really wish i wish i could talk to the
chat right now
too bad too bad i had to hide the chat
because you guys the back is eating too
much
i want to figure it out i could figure
it out it's just uh i feel like i don't
have enough
to go off of right now you know
and if i'm just going off of what i see
it's not really too much i can make out
aside from that it might be a code
and i said that's wrong
maybe this is one of those times where
you know kiara's gonna do something
first and then i've gotta do something
it's not like i can move the books i
can't interact with them
is there a way for you to reset
everything i did
no
you can't just take them all off um
i can once i placed one i can change the
number
but i don't
what if i place like everything oh
oh okay now everything's full
how do i get rid of them though i cannot
get rid of them anymore so i guess it's
okay to have extra ones on there
oh you're oh you made them disappear
how did you do that i just tried to
connect stuff
i'm just clicking random stuff
oh wait i'm sorry i figured i'd have to
remove them
okay
okay let me try to remove everything i
have like coordinates and stuff but
there's no indication of
what element should be in what um
i kind of seem to have it because the
first one starts with fire and so
the second one i go with green the third
one i go over yellow the
fourth one i go with blue but i kind of
got stuck at the fourth one because the
fourth one is already set
in place with green even though it
should be blue and that's why i got
confused now
but i'm trying to remove them again the
ones that i just placed
so maybe for her coordinates since she
has like she says they go as high as 10.
maybe if there's a coordinate that's 10
i connect it to the one that's eight
there's a coordinate that's i don't know
if this is nine or six
connected to seven and if there's a
coordinate that's five then i connect it
to the coordinate that's one
because it's not like uh sometimes with
coordinates there's numbers on both
sides but
there's only numbers on one side so it
could correspond
okay um
okay everything that is on it now is uh
there from the beginning i can
not move them or i can also not change
the color
oh okay
ah can you ah
can you tell me
uh the numbers on your books again
the first ones okay
the four to six uh three to two
five to one ten to eight
four four nine to seven
or maybe it's four to nine and six to
seven
i guess after we figure out what we're
supposed to do with them then we can
test
if either of them are wrong we just
switch push it to
[Music]
what did you say for four six right
yeah six but it could be nine because
it's kind of i can't really tell
it could be nine
[Music]
uh
i can hear kiara's brain from here
okay okay you know what never mind um
but i'm i'm not gonna care about the
elements just yet i'm just gonna put
everything in place now okay okay so
it will take a little time and while i'm
doing that i guess
if you know which ones to connect then i
guess you could already connect them
okay please as you're like
okay one d2
already in place
number two is a a free
i placed it now
oh sorry
okay uh that was number two
two okay now number three b1
already in place number four
e5
already in place
number six b4
uh number seven
e2
placed it
ah okay so the the coordinates that
you're putting in are numbered
yeah yeah yeah yeah number one to ten
yeah oh okay
all right have you placed all of them
yet or no not yet
okay number eight number eight okay so
one connecting up the number
of her coordinates to each other so like
our hourly already placed as well
so number nine i don't know about the
elements or anything like that
um a4
placed and number ten
be free okay i placed all of them
okay now i need to tell me
uh which okay so we gotta connect these
books to each other so we'll do five to
one first so
whatever the fifth coordinate is to the
first coordinate
so c c3
to d2
[Music]
wait i forgot one oh apparently yeah but
not you see
you're free ah
can you unconnect that because i don't i
think that was
okay okay now now it should have all of
them
okay now we're doing uh
three to two three two uh b
one two a three
okay now let's do ten to eight
and don't be free to
e1
uh
b3 2e1
is that even possible okay i guess i did
the first one wrong what is a
five two one a
c three two d two
oh whoa uh
now wait we did
did five to one we did three two we did
ten to eight
now i don't know if this is seven to six
or nine
uh sorry i don't know if this is nine to
seven or six to seven so i guess we'll
try let's do
uh nine to seven first
uh a4 to e2
okay that's probably not it let's try it
okay let's try
six to seven
b4 to
[Music]
e2
okay now um four to six
or four to nine i guess uh
four a5 to
a5 e e5 to a4
e5 to a4 okay so uh
both those last two i just did are blue
which means i think the elements are
correct
so i guess for the other three uh they
should be different elements
[Music]
okay ah
ah is it perhaps
because that one is set in stone and
it's green
ah so it's opposite okay
so yeah whichever one is red then put
blue as opposite
so like for the fire one that's
connected to the lightning bolt just
turn the lightning bolt to blue
okay can you connect it again
[Music]
yeah and can you connect the other one
again the
bottom left to the middle red one okay
oh yeah
okay because the first one started out
as green and i
the one that i set uh i can change the
colors and that one has to be red okay
so that one started out as a pikachu so
the next one has to be blue
okay connect please yeah
we did it our brains are so big oh
my god okay i you know the problem was
in the beginning i thought that i
already had to figure out the elements
from the get-go
but i could only figure it out once the
connections were made then it was easy
then it made sense but i tried to figure
it out too early
yeah yeah whoa where are you where are
you on me
oh uh i see there was a creepy clown
that i saw
what the you have to bonk that
clown
i'm good at bunking clowns what the hell
okay well um hold that one second
i'm gonna stairwell and i'm carrying a
candle oh never mind i'm going into a
deep tunnel
that's in the in a fireplace
it's creepy
probably have to come down to you oh
i'll save
okay well i'm in a room let me know when
you get to your destination
oh i have a ride i see you
oh man i have a cut scene
no it's mine
oh wait that's not you
would you have a different cutscene yes
what have you
done
okay i met the guy that's like lost in
the tunnels and he told me to
make an apparatus to go to work
okay well i uh wherever you are i'm in a
room
that has some water and like a big
pattern that has these little orbs that
are connected to like things that look
like batteries that have
two stripes on either end which are
different colors respectively
are we in the same room is that what it
looks like on your side
i am oh my god ah oh what the hell
i think something's happening i think
the water is rising yeah
i jumped into the water and then that
turned on the
lights oh okay well there's scary music
so i think this is timed
oh no hey what am i going to die
we don't finish it on time probably
i'll i'll take all those things oh my
god okay uh what the hell
what oh my god what what what
i can't change anything on my side but i
could probably tell you okay
okay there's like there's like a bunch
of like thingies
and i okay there's a lot a lot of
weight lifting thingies that each have a
color and i'm supposed
to put the ones with the right color
into the right position
yeah uh the fuses fuses i guess and i
have to put the fuses
into the into the right tower thingies
now i have for example green and red but
i also have
uh blue and blue and i have red and red
and i've only
okay okay so i i see green and red and
to its left it's connected to blue and
orange does that help
and it's right it's oh wait okay uh
which one is connected to blue uh not
blue blue it's just one blue stripe
and do you want to know what blue blue
is connected to
i want to know what red blue is
connected to
red blue is connected to three different
ones
uh the top it's connected to blue blue
to the bottom it's connected to blue
yellow and to the right it's connected
to just one stripe
why are they connected to three oh my
god oh my god
i'm not gonna get electrocuted
what is uh what's connected to the to uh
yellow green or orange green whatever
that is uh
one yellow stripe one red stripe and a
blue
green and also one blue stripe
calculating oh what's up here is the
water rising
at least it's not for me i i guess i'm
safe maybe kiara maybe it's dangerous
for her right now
i feel so short in this room um um
um okay um
i see some connections like the towers
that i see
the electricity towers or whatever those
are uh
some of them have fuses already in there
which is why i was asking you
why what is connected to orange and
green
however orange and green has like a wire
on top of it that connects to
one tower with no fuses and the other
wire connects to another tower with no
fuses but only two so when you say there
is red things connected to it oh my god
okay when you say there's red things
connected to it um
three things connected to it i'm not
sure like why is it free
four four four
ah okay okay you say four colors are
connected to it
four like different uh units are
oh okay maybe i have to try maybe
is this frown uh can i wait when
something happen if i put the wrong one
in
tell me uh one of the colors again
that's in red green or
orange green uh blue green
it's yeah in that order blue on the left
bring on the right
when you say blue on the left and green
on the right is that you mean that's
that's
on one fuse blue on the left oh
how are you what do your towers look
like
like are they in a certain pattern or
are they just
oh my god
well the pattern is that they're
connected with wires at the top
and there's one two three
four five six
yeah this should be eight probably uh
um oh my god
is there really time running
i don't know which one was this you said
blue you said blue
green or so but i don't have a fuse with
blue and green on it i have blue and
blue
i have green only i have blue only maybe
that's something
okay i placed it nothing happened maybe
that's a good thing
yeah and then go to another one that's
connected to orange green and then we
can see what else fits there
yeah the other one that is connected to
orange screen
um i guess i'll put the green one up
oh what happened what's happening what's
happening nothing's happening oh my god
wait this
oh i just realized the
thing in the middle um which is sparking
with uh very dangerous electricity is
getting closer and closer to the water
oh once i put the green one down
wait did it wait wait no okay that's
slime that's
that has i guess nothing to do with the
where's the fuse it has to do with time
okay
i'm about to die probably yeah well
at least we figured it out for the next
time
yeah yeah yeah you know
i never died before for like
electrocution as a phoenix
so this is gonna be new for me i don't i
don't know if i wanted to make that
experience but
what is connected to uh blue and blue
uh red and blue uh there's a blue blue
a blue orange and just an orange or i
don't know it's like orange yellow i'll
just call it orange
okay i'll place blue blue okay
wow oh my god can i put something here
what is done
well i placed when i placed
okay i'm dead your journey has ended
that was quite a shock are you kidding
me
it's not fun wait wait does it start oh
it starts from where
we just were okay okay
i'm pretty sure yeah
so what have we learned
we learned how to connect them
are we sure about that though because i
had a lot of leftover
fuses should be fine i think
it'll be like a process of elimination
thing
okay yes i'm in the water okay the timer
is on
okay we also learned that ahmed doesn't
wait i guess at the end i have to pull
the lever here and see if that
lets me out okay oh i'm taking all the
fuses
okay well there's no way that the first
combination that we tried is correct
though
because it gave me a bunch of different
colors and
and yeah i just picked a random one
well uh but it sounded like only
one could fit in that particular like
whatever you're putting it into
so that's why i thought well if it can
fit then that must be it
but i put a different one in there now
where previously i put in green or
something i think i put in
red now and then it doesn't there's no
reaction
i guess as long as it maybe maybe
because um
it's about the way it connects like i'm
looking at a double blue one that
connects to a red one that connects to
like two different ones
so maybe it has to go via how it
connects i don't know
ah uh wait a second uh is that maybe the
correct one because it goes green to
green
green i don't see any green to green
uh but from the ones that are connected
to
or yellow green which ones were
connected to yellow green
a single red blue and green a single
blue
and a single yellow
four different modules
do
kind of just like uh you know it's
pretty chill
got a nice water feature in the room
you know i got a nice view of these
electric dads
pretty cool uh oh i don't get to die
that's pretty cool too
i don't get the pressure um is there any
oh my god yeah is there any ring
connected to oh god
can we switch places no we can't it's
too late
is there anything related to yellow
orange whatever color that is
that's just a yellow just just a single
yellow yeah
there's a blue red there's a blue
orange there's a single blue and the
orange green
look oh man
i i i just i don't i don't see a pattern
i don't
i don't know which
sorry can you repeat all those colors
again okay uh
red blue blue orange
uh orange green and blue
[Music]
i'm supposed to be telling her but i
can't really discern any pattern here
between these they're in the shape of an
m like mcdonald's
you know maybe maybe there is a pattern
for it
well there's four in the middle of a
circle maybe that's helpful okay do you
have anything like the structure the
pattern wise is there like a circle
ah
circle circle yeah like a
i don't know how they're placed but uh
so the the way that mine is there's like
four
inside of a circle and then five
outside of the circle like on the border
of the circle so maybe
if you have any like uh in the middle of
an area
maybe that'll help
i feel like i'm confusing her
she looks happy about something
um
[Laughter]
i wish we could swap sides
let me see what happens if i pull a
lever i'm probably gonna die
oh oh no
it corrected it doesn't mean it was
correct
oh my god oh my god oh oh oh oh
i saw that connected up until a certain
point doesn't mean up until then it's
correct but i'm about to die anyway but
okay
wait remember that orange green one was
like all electric
it was like uh it looked like it was
gonna break
does that mean it was crazy
[Music]
i will remember that i put orange here
and
blue here connected to the okay
so i guess it didn't continue here
because i didn't have anything there
i would not crawl down like this random
tunnel i guess it's the only way so you
have oh
oh sorry i didn't push the button what
is connected to the orange green one
uh blue green blue red and
just orange
simply orange
i tried peach fanta okay oh
i don't i feel like i didn't have blue
green blue red and just orange
one more try you can do it all right
it's good you kind of had it well really
lever at the at the start and let's see
what happens
okay yeah if it doesn't connect anything
at all that means that in the beginning
that the last pattern we had was
actually correct oh
okay maybe because it did connect up
until the point where i stopped
putting in uh what's it called again
[Music]
fuses
okay i wanted to pull the level all
right let's see
ah oh okay okay yeah that means that we
were
on the right track so only blue blue
um like shocked like uh
oh yeah i also saw like connection being
made here
actually the connection not being made
even though previously when i had the
fuses in there the connection was being
made did i put green in there let's see
again
um i'm pulling the lever it continues
it continues electricity
stop wait does that mean that i put the
wrong color in there
nothing's happening on my side
oh
tracking is so good
like when she's thinking you could
totally like oh that's kiara thinking
you know what i mean
how pretty
oh okay okay i saw oh
so i saw a pattern between the single
blue and a single orange
and then when it got to the orange green
it stopped
why did that one
[Music]
uh okay so up until there is correct uh
so next i'll just i'll just put
something something random in there
oh
okay tell me the colors too okay so
it went from blue single blue to single
orange to orange and green and then it
stopped
so there's either blue green or single
red
pulling the level okay i'm watching from
the start this time
okay it starts at blue it goes to orange
and then it goes to orange green
and then it goes to red oh it connected
yeah the red one was correct i think
yeah yeah yeah it went
i need to connect with that we're
probably gonna die again this time
but yeah uh so from red it either goes
to blue blue
or blue green i'm guessing blue blue
because
blue green is between uh no uh
ah that one automatically connects to
one that was already placed there which
is red blue oh okay okay then blue green
uh do we have anything connected to red
blue
uh a single orange blue blue and a blue
[Music]
orange
was just bad timing i think because i
don't know on my side it failed at red
fail it read what wait someone tried the
same
when you tried to wear the same thing
again okay but when you trigger it it
goes from like blue orange to like a
different to like a
orange and then to orange green
and so like i could see the path of the
electricity going and so
it goes from blue to single blue to
single orange to
orange green to red and then something
was disconnected at the red one
oh okay wait wait wait
yeah we get free fried chicken for
everyone
okay so sorry it was a single blue some
orange and orange green and then
i think it was single red yes
[Music]
and that single red either connects to a
blue green or blue blue
which is interesting because the wire
connects it to the tower
is where the pre-replaced fuse fuses
which is
a red blue but i can connect it to one
one more tower that doesn't have a fuse
in it
and i have left the following colors
orange orange
green only red red blue blue and green
red
yeah i think i would go yeah
out of all those patterns i think only
blue blue is the one that
there's a red green but not a green red
okay let me try again maybe it was
really just the timing the time was
already available
over pulling leather
okay blue to orange to orange green
red
[Music]
because i can't i cannot remove the one
that's already pre-placed
but i guess the blue one is wrong after
all um
so yeah i'll just put the other ones in
let's see what they are again what are
the ones you have i have orange orange
uh green um uh
blue blue green red
okay and red red none of those
okay interesting yeah
i don't know those are on here oh
but not green red wait i want to see one
more thing one more time
maybe red red
yeah it just does the same thing
uh what connects with the red blue one
uh either single orange blue orange or
blue blue
single orange blue orange or blue blue
yeah i don't know what it looks like on
her side so i don't know which one
connects with the orange
green one uh
either blue green a single blue or a
single red
[Music]
but blue is where the electricity
started the single blue so i don't think
maybe it's supposed to go blue to orange
to
orange green to blue green to red to
blue blue
uh repeat that please we're about to
dive
away but uh uh well it starts at blue
and then it goes to orange and then it
goes
to orange green and maybe it's supposed
to go to blue green and then to red
and then to blue blue
well i don't uh have a blue green
i'll try blue blue that goes i don't
know i don't know
maybe we should start on a different one
one more try wait wait no those are
connecting fine i think
orange green instead of red yeah yeah
that one was not quite oh it returned
though
interesting why did one this one return
[Music]
maybe we should start well i don't know
it must be the wrong path because
if it stops at red and it doesn't go to
blue blue and it doesn't go to blue
green
next time we should probably start on a
different one other than just a single
blue
well i don't know how it works on your
side but we might have to just start
from a different
area like a different path oh do you
have a green oh sorry a red green to
start off on
oh yeah
okay we could do that because the red
green only connects to two it either
connects to a single blue or
a blue orange well okay
okay well i'm gonna wait until
i die and it happened a few seconds i
was coming what if i jump into it
oh all right okay i didn't just walk
through that thing but that doesn't kill
me okay
but this kills me sure sure realistic
it's okay
okay maybe this time we can do it yeah
yeah maybe we just uh should start at
the bottom of like the electric nodes
that i'm looking at
it starts on red green
red green okay either blue orange or
blue
[Music]
i wonder if i get electrocuted too if i
stand here at the end
or if i stand here when she presses the
lever
testing
[Music]
that seemed to connect fine yeah but it
stopped that uh orange green but yeah it
did connect
yeah yeah i didn't put enough anything
after that so
uh what do we put into red green can you
once again tell me the connections
please
connected to orange green are red
blue green and yellow
okay i have uh from those i have red and
yellow
just a single red or a single yellow
yeah i guess single red
let's do it actually do single yellow
sorry
okay and then from there tell me what
you have
okay put in should i test it again i'll
test it again
where did it oh i think it worked oh
yeah
oh my god i'm just missing the last one
last one this so i have something that
should be connected with
red and blue
blue okay i have blue blue
oh my god is this it
pulling the leather oh yeah there's also
yeah there's also blue yellow you can
always try different ones
grenadine connecting collecting and
[Music]
we should have started from the bottom
from the top oh meow meow
i think you have to maybe open the door
for me hello mio hi baby
oh wait no one i i got through okay
i don't know shook me leave it on
that'll do one more
[Music]
i wonder how far we are like from
percentage-wise
this one looks complicated so maybe we
should leave it it looks pretty
complicated oh
well of course chad says one more
are we like if we do the next one would
we be halfway through
island chat do you know that chat
do you know that
i remember well i've seen a little bit
like of
i don't know how to do this one but i've
seen a little bit of it in like a stream
before
but i definitely don't remember how it
works
i just don't know which channel says
we're like 45
or so why why don't mine
ah
[Music]
we are at chapter 7 out of 10 but it
gets harder
but that sounds like we're pretty much
like even if the other one
three last ones or four last ones get
more harder i think we might be fine
um yeah yeah let's leave it at that for
this side
okay uh i guess it's saved here right
if we continue can we just leave the
game no
it should be fun because like when you
start uh you can actually start on any
chapter so we'll just start
on oh we'll just try we'll just start on
chapter seven next time again okay okay
hopefully all right
wow i feel partially very stupid and
partially
a little bit smart i think he did great
i think he did a good job
uh not as good not as great as my uh
detective investigator we both got stuck
at certain parts like i think at the
beginning you really figured out a lot
of that stuff
uh maybe not sure
well i think oh wow what is this
next week is probably not possible to
continue it so
maybe the week after oh sorry guys it
will have to wait a little bit
until this continues because i'll be at
dokomi next week
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh but you and me uh
we will be soon seventh and eighth of
august actually i think just one day
but in uh the second week of august oh
yeah the first week of august
i know it says
yeah yeah uh 14 15 13 14 15
on one of those days yeah you wouldn't
need i don't know if it's all of those
days to be honest i don't
even just one day yeah
uh we are uh which convention was it
uh orlando maybe
oh yes yes
apparent so uh check it out if you're at
the convention i guess
yeah then uh okay you have two
or one hellotalk this week
i have perhaps too
oh oh yeah oh whoa it's not it's
one of them is not 100 the um
yeah the public information yet but
people already kind of guess it because
i already gave some hints
oh should i not have said that no no no
no problem
it's okay i'll probably announce it like
tomorrow i'm sorry no no no no no no no
absolutely no problem it's like i i
could probably
already say it no problem all right oh
well thank you ammo for playing with me
i'm glad we're
glad we finally play something again we
gotta do it more often well with this
game
we'll do it at least one more time at
least yeah it was really fun thank you
for playing with me
thank you too and
i think i'll read some super chats i
guess
so i'll i'll see i'll talk to you later
okay goodbye everybody enjoy your kiara
super chat reading thank you guys for
watching i'm gonna head out
goodbye bye bye
bye thank you
okay and i say goodbye to you guys chat
bye
thank you guys for watching i will read
uh the super chats from today's stream
probably on super sunday
but uh the next few streams i will read
the same chats of okay
i'll see you guys tomorrow bright and
early for uh i don't know actually what
it'll be for
but i don't remember see you guys then
mario oh detective diaries yeah i'm
gonna open up a marshmallows tonight i'm
gonna post it on twitter
i'll see you guys there okay goodbye if
you guys want some more content uh
kiara's new super chat readings are
pretty fun
so goodbye thank you for watching
i'll see you guys tomorrow uh think of a
good question okay
okay bye
[Music]
do
don't forget guys ina is also live now
with a resident evil 7
and i believe uh let's have our right
monitor hold on i'm opening it now
she does you guys can check that out too
okay thank you for watching
goodbye