[Music]
hello I'm not a
I'm I know I'm
together
we
hello are you ready for the second day
of seven days to die second day
for the day in the game I definitely
think is not day two no no uh but that's
okay because even though it's day two
for wow we're going to
hopefully help help maybe get strong i f
some zombies yeah should we keep going
let's get going right away
here
okay
by okay I think we're ready to spawn
done spawn
spawn creating player
why is that kind of
scary it sounded scary but it's not
scary that's not scary H let's go join
everyone you do not see any trucks
around
here yeah let's go join up with
everyone okay maybe we should go
everything into my inventory on
[Music]
accident welcome
we woke up on our bunk
bed we're going to help but we are uh
babies and it doesn't look like
anybody's El at our house it's clean we
have a new what I figured maybe
everybody mov do you want me to come
pick you
up it's night
time no it's 4:00 a.m. you're fine yeah
uh we'll be strong demon dogs we're
going to go and find you I should stuff
with if you if you look at the map and
zoom out like really far you can see a
bunch of our names on the map and that's
that's new house location okay we'll go
on a quest zoom zoom zoom oh okay that's
not that far it should be that bad what
you trying to do okay I'm going to go
towards the the tier two quests the in
the
desert is anyone learning how to lock
pick no oh I think I would like to okay
here go thank you but why lockpick when
we can just Brute Force open
everything apparently there are safes
that that won't work with I had to lock
pick
one so it might be nice to have we're
going to go on our journey and then once
we everybody oh is it okay I see at the
old home here there's a bunch of
magazines and animals and stuff are
those L yeah you can use whatever are
they can I take everything old home or
is it still being used um we're going to
we're going to go back there for the
raid so maybe leave some resources but
whatever you need you can take okay yeah
something you need we'll go on our
journey then okay and then we'll come by
if we have a
questions lot of Quest at the trader if
you want to get a
okay okay we will
[Music]
okay I took
everything that's good though because we
don't really have anything so we need to
take some things right I don't know if
it's okay to use all their magazines
well if there's a magazine that sounds
particularly interesting I think it's
okay H that sounds really good a repair
man Farming Farming Farming that's a
magazine we want what about this one
craft tools cra harvesting tool oh that
sounds like it works well with farming
yeah BS maybe
notu sounds
strong that sounds
good what what kind of magazines are you
big boy
h i
sound it doesn't sound bad M they just
trying to the game just trying to SC o
this looks really fres
Honey
[Music]
coffee I'm going to take the
coffee
[Music]
wow are we no clothes
probably let's check our
clothing oh we have clothing if you can
call that clothing we have clothing
pumpkin is that a pumpkin it's a pumpkin
[Music]
I'm going to take animal F yeah I want
to take
it
mushrooms
cereal wait that's Acorn green Acorn wa
is w I thought there was kiwis blood
bag oh
[Music]
oh
oh who's bu I was kind of wondering too
bble box bble box oh this is the junk
box I'll leave the B box let's go take a
look at our box oh there's more boxes
here
too oh
okay we're looking oh muss those are
ours M right they're just going to grow
back so we might as well pick them now
did I get them we got them yeah my
shs they could to go back right so I can
pick them right
[Music]
oh okay and then let's go see other
depressing
box our box is good
oh those are our items we have some
water oh you're right
yeah is it cleaning supplies what's that
scw I feel like our box is actually
better than I remember it to be me
too to the point where I like did
somebody give us some gift right okay
well it's 6 am in game you know is my
gun or that gun I that's our gun the
pipe machine gun I don't know can I
combine them I don't think we can
combine
guns okay they built you a door we we
built ourselves a door right yeah yeah
yeah that's our door still
there okay okay well I'm going to repair
this maybe we can try crafting some more
better clothes
better weapons maybe we the
[Music]
magine oh read the magazine
right
use yeah oh there's two of them oh
another one what if we use again yeah
okay and then other
Magazine see coton okay that's what I
wanted let's craft clothing because we
have to make a long journey so I think
this is our clothing no
yeah I think this is our clothing okay
can we make anything else better I
wanted to
make probably at the new home there's a
farm or
something and then we can make the C
Farm
exra f
H okay what about our clothing we have
clothing this is the best we can do okay
what about our weapons should we get a
better weapon good it's daytime
okay I have a feeling I should be
careful
yeah let's close the door okay we're
going to make our journey now
pumpkin I want the
pumpkin oh this is smart zombies aren't
that smart oh
gosh back up back up otherwise it going
to oh I'm so confused okay I'm confused
by the door so now I'm standing am I a
zombie okay where are we
going no no we are
going where did everybody go oh maybe we
have to zoom out more maybe oh oh that's
where the home actually is here
maybe are we really oh are we sneaking
we're sneaking right now oh is that
where the home actually is oh they left
then let's go there
here how do I set this
yeah okay I now it's showing I think
we there we
go let's find interesting things it's
bright and
early it's good
weather oh look there's so much coton in
here let's not get too distracted
though yeah no broken legs let's be
careful now is not here to save of us
no I'm not going to get distracted
okay yeah it's not that far we've at
least been kind of around that area
before I'm not going to get injured
uh
yeah so we'll be good we're going to go
straight there just a little bit of a a
walk to start the day out you know
yeah oh water is okay because I'm not
injured and we have stamina I'm
sorry as long as we have stamina it be
nice to have even more stamina oh this
is M there's a
mailbox is there anything in it magazine
can be in the mailbox
really no
empty should I follow the road or go
over the
[Music]
hill immediately distracted I just
remember that you know mailboxes are
good
there
yeah it's so nice we're going to be
careful
careful careful okay don't lose your
[Music]
be careful why you're going to fall here
I'm not going
to careful oh there's a house there it
says live is it a live
house I'm I'm not going to it getting
distracted I don't think want to any
zombies I think everybody clear out the
zombies I don't want to meet the
zombies we're almost
there can I make it across
this down here a bit
more where oh there's a bridge over down
that
way we could cross here we could cross
the bridge I'm going to cross here
uh-oh
okay did they need to build build a
bridge
then am I starting to run on the
stamina well it's probably cuz we're wet
huh maybe I think so I think you're
right
M we have an umbrella on us this is the
farm where we found a gun before
a I'm going to catch my breath on yeah I
think this way we're going to dry off a
little bit I wish we could just shake
all the water off
here can't do that almost
there Bob's
Boys the boys is here I'm
going yeah we're sorry doggies right
[Music]
now oh I can't walk without sprinting
I know oh I guess we can join the party
I
guess it's fine for us to join the party
right I think so where was that again
yeah is this how I join the party I
think so we Jo
people yeah I don't
know I'll
[Music]
try so
spooky I we're almost
try this is good
yeah course
nice we're almost
there huh this wasn't that long of a
journey or anything at all huh we didn't
even see a single zombie this is
good click the other envelope from
car I want to go in the house
oh wait where is the
house hopefully it's going to be okay
cuz they on the quest I don't think
probably we should be joining the quest
right now where is their house maybe
their house is the really nice one
there that one oh is it it's kind of
close to the way point we put down the
way point isn't exactly put down we're
just like they're kind of around this
area right
huh wait is it this house we in this
one that's
it okay you sure yeah the door is open
open there's a fire
burning that's the
bun do we have any water oh there's a
tree in the house ah now it do storage
why the doors open
H why is that door open I'm closing the
doors door then that's all very
[Music]
good I want this to be our room
magazines and craftables it's magazines
and craftables room then and that means
is that flashlight for us or is that oh
one left on the
ground that's a flashlight I think he's
left for
light I guess when it's night time a
night time night
time
box can we make another bed
thing the bed
roll put our bed roll in that room by
the be
box what are you doing I'm trying to fix
the door oh here oh we could put it in
the corner there I want to put it
here bed w h fiber I don't have okay
that's not too hard
though so this house is really
big fiber I'll put I'll get rid of the
way
point goodbye way point goodbye way
point there
okay P
time enough
yet getting of all the I think we got
enough now can have a bit more what if
there's a zombie
though no zombies
we should save a way point here anyways
though so we can always know where the
new home is a
true
[Music]
oh the house
doesn't I think it's probably
different
impressive w
a okay let's go food and
Medicine oh there we go
oh
[Music]
okay here yeah let's put it down right
here that I want to put it in the corner
there
right here
yeah you have to spin it spin it
oh in the corner how do I spin it it's
good there just like that right it fits
perfectly in the corner spin spin spin
spin yeah here
perfect
there perfect
yeah little
corner oh huh why did you punch our bed
I don't know I tooking that at soft or
something yeah I'm making it
softer
okay should we save that as our spot I
think it saved no I don't
[Music]
know well once everyone's back then
we'll join the chat together with them
for now what's this I would like to do
fire B what's that what's
that do collected water oh is it
full I can't
tell well I won't touch it we won't
touch it we don't know exactly what it
is this is where we want to
be can I make more of these boxes
are they ready to go should shiny M you
should take the shiny ones shiny if
they're ready yeah jump back up those
ones they're shiny really green ones no
those are really yellow ones oh super
[Music]
corn was that right was that
okay
huh mushroom
ah is this how you harvest
properly I don't know I thought the
plant would come
back oh this is the that's right Kai
said to go and get a bike that's
probably not our bike I'm going to try
it I don't think she meant to take this
bike let's go get our
[Music]
own ouch i r it into a tree
I guess it doesn't hard to just take a
test ride right yeah I'm just testing
[Music]
it if call some comes back and she's
like oh that's great M you got a
bike I'm just leting her to ride
okay can we go fast it's a bit
tricky do you think you want your own
bike
then I feel like
oh my stamina doesn't go down oh okay
now we want our own bike then oh my bike
has its own stamina oh B
stamina I see let's go park it back in
the
back it's go parking time how do I get
off this is those parking spot with it's
good here sure yeah it's fine okay guys
I'm IED to go get lots of quests and
there was the the police don't went with
no before then should I ride the bike
there no cuz she said to get the quest
that has a
bike it's
dark weather's not as good
anymore oops I'm fixing it oh no no are
you fixing
it I don't think you're doing anything
go Dad can I not fix it I don't think we
have sticks to fix it
a I see yeah we need to go to the trade
into to build quests I want to do
farming oh today is a good day to stay
inside need tree
Parts is everyone going come home
soon they're really far
away look how far away everybody is
we're waiting for them to come
home
[Music]
oh at least if the rain stops
soon don't have an umbrella I clothing
doesn't repel the
water storm is not good okay
[Music]
it's to stay
inside coming home
soon we look at the map to see where the
traitor was and then once the rain stops
are you you want to open soon a c be
zombies that come home they're coming
home soon
[Music]
I don't know if I like our new home it's
definitely more fancy the layout's kind
of interesting I like our bed M can we
look at our map and we should find where
the trailer
is a it's so close and then if we go
there we'll be safe M let's go to the
trailer right now it's not that far it's
just down the street H it's only noon
yeah it's just rainy
[Music]
much in
here let's get going to the
trador a trador is safe until night time
yeah cuz it doesn't like us staying
there
right let's go
M be okay oh we're wet now yeah
but it'll be okay if the tra
us it'll be
okay it's just down the roof look at
that I want to make sure I'm going the
right way though
yeah hopefully this is the right
way I think everything's going to be
empty
here yeah
oh did I get stuff I don't
know I
wouldn't I go faster than this go down
are we going the opposite way I don't
know can we put a way point we should
put a way point we should put a way
point I think a wayo would be good
is say Compass way point hidden so I
kind of have a feeling that maybe way
point wasn't
yet there good enough this way okay it's
getting sunny don't use the torch
because the zombies are attracted to the
heat oh it shouldn't be that hard I
thought feel
though if I was a zombie if oh what's
that
yeah do we know how to use a
compass do
we it's
okay Instinct you know
yeah good down we should probably go
towards it that way we can do the quest
so it might be a quest to get a bunch of
coton you know I want to make
clothing
okay I have to make
sure
okay yeah okay why do you want us to do
again that's
lot no never
mind hello B holy [\h__\h] I thought you
were a zombie I'm not a zombie
witho I see your inventory the drill
[\h__\h] what your have
[Music]
what did I want from you again well you
better get your ass to crack a book cuz
you're dumber than dirt what was
that let's go do the quest have Quest
into the bird supplies we're working on
that
now ah right right right right we need
to head to the Rally Point
is it marked on the map
no maybe an x on the
map get rid of this
one Rally Point zoom zoom zoom out ow
ow ah it's over here over there let's
put a waypoint there I don't think we
put a waypoint there down
yeah way point was not
set how do I set
it let's
go that way
okay we need the shovel for this do we
have the shovel in our hands oh
no good sh
thank you that would have been bad if we
had it then I didn't have the shovel
still you're aiming for that
yeah let's see no
zombie keep on
going keep on
[Music]
going oh Shiny Rock
H A Day 21's
dangerous okay we need to get strong
before them then
huh oh I wanted
them let's focus on getting over there
it's a little bit further away than I
like so you said it was close
it's close but it's further than I like
it to
be oh I have to go up this hill yeah
it's a little
skary that looks like we could break
break
something let's go this way
yeah chicken get the chicken get the
chicken I got the chicken y y chicken
I got the chicken yeah
yeah
helpful what's here what's over
there wa oh oh that's where we need to
go
hello oh we have to dig in this area
then dig now dig right here dig okay
let's dig here
am I doing
it ah it takes so long with the shovel
if we just had a CLA
then
yeah no yeah
yeah is it
waking better get comfy
how far do we have to do
huh to do piece by
piece
okay we guys sit here then hope no
zombies come here oh
wait I S
now
okay how much do I have have to dig Did
the whole
circle you're getting closer to the
treasure
a pretty far
down maybe dig in the a made the nice
sound I don't know
[Music]
this sounds very
Sandy
yeah I'm
thirsty did we bring the water with
us no treasure yet
H
oh just a little bit more
[Music]
oh wait
yeah be careful that we can get out
that's what I'm worried about
too okay
oh I think we can still get out B
bow b b hey guys what's going on we're
digging a hole you're digging a hole oh
great doing some quests yeah okay I I
would love to come be a part of your
quest if you don't want of course yes
I'm going to go to you and help you guys
do a bunch of quests thank you get you
up to
speed I drink water really quick let's
make our own party
okay okay so so we should probably leave
people's party
and let's
see um I'm going to make Kiara the
leader of this other one I don't
know okay now I'm inviting you to my
party
okay should join K party don't get
distracted you're digging a hole don't
worry about it I will go find
you how do we leave the party we're in
right
now yes okay definitely do
that and I will I will come to you on my
bike we bored it for a moment so oh we
found
oh okay those are all good stuff did I
take all this stuff I took the stuff
I got a party invite from you guys okay
I'll accept it now we're in the same
party I think there's a zombie that
found us oh no do you guys have any
weapons I found her look it's a gun gun
gun okay there distance where'd she go
where she go where'd she go there she
is maybe maybe I don't need to shoot her
I can shoot her I going to have to send
her away
die oh no no bullets violence other one
other gun another gun other gun violence
is the best way no no bullets okay I'm
running hello running is also okay
hello I I I I I I saw you but then you
running away from me stop running away
from
me Chi CE you want to get in our
party I just I just spawned and I tried
I keep running
for you keep getting fur away stop
running there there you are there is a
zombie you like the
zombie you look
strong we yes I very strong I'll protect
you don't worry hide
behind together and get you guys strong
this is on the hill I took your Tower
okay I'll kill her for you okay stay
behind stay behind stay close but not
too close I tried using my gun but it
wouldn't work hope it doesn't have
bullets oh boy she looks very plasticy
oh she's not going to
roll oh no hit her hit herit
her is that the only is that the only
weapon you have or we have guns but we
have bullets okay okay is that I
couldn't tell was that just normal Stone
axe okay let me give you Stone ax okay
that's behind you behind you there's a
big
one okay okay wait come with me here
I'll I'll drop it at this smaller tree
and then you have a spear which is
better because you have more space thank
you between you okay and then aim for
the head yes head is the best oh I had a
spear oh you just likey
aim for the the x is to to make stuff
it's like to repair and
stuff he's saying we should stop no keep
going keep going he likes it Hees it he
loves it
it get him get him get him I don't know
if I need to hurt him that much okay
should we go to you Kelly or I'm on my
way to you guys I have um a special club
for you
oh very effective just try and hit them
in the head with it is it okay if it
go I got
scared here you go this is a very
special Club it's a level five oh thank
you thank you it's my nerd glasses I get
lost you know what F you guys need one
of these nerd hats because get you a ton
of exp during I thought you going to say
because we're a big nerds so I can't
believe you say that to them I can't
believe it that is maximum silliness
right there kie can you invite me to
your party yes
absolutely okay now I'm going to invite
why can't I invite you that's weird very
strange oh foko you guys are the leaders
so you have to
invite be the leader for once okay invit
invited okay quick make some call some
shots to your Tower why yay we were
working on digging and then we got
scared and ran away oh oh look at Tokyo
Tower it's so impressive it's so
beautiful Tokyo Tower Tokyo
[Music]
Tower the to next to the American it
look
different oh boy Toyo
Tower I don't know if there are going to
be any good quests in here Lo here okay
okay let's do let's do quests so that we
get stuff digging the hole it didn't
quite finish off maybe no we did it says
hold land claim block at the top zero
out of one so I have a feeling we didn't
do it I think I just have to build
one hold we have to
help okay hold
the yeah we're going to see if we can
make you guys Little Nerd
get with the
ra um so for the raid you guys um guns
might be best just because we have the
spike Fortress set up and uh but but the
thing is when the zombies run into the
spikes we don't get exp from it so we
prefer to shoot them if we can the
spikes like the last line of defense I
will be going out into the the the
center of the fight with my bat it's
very strong but for you guys it might be
good to choose a gun okay and um but the
club is also helpful so should I place
my land claan block can you make make uh
clubs uh yes you can make them yeah very
e with wood easy no no I mean the you
said you have a very strong one do you
have like a special one oh yeah I gave I
gave um one with the chains to them I
can make level six I believe no level
five clubs will you will you mind me me
later
for yeah I want I want to wh cuz I I'm
not really wait wait where are you going
turn
around okay look look at the M look at
the top left do you see your name and
Callie's name I hear Follow the arrow
turn around turn around oh we see see it
this way way okay and then on do you see
the arrow oh God just stay stay turn
around look at
me we are faster than the zombies run
with me this way I've lost my
they are very slow just keep running
okay and follow the blue arrow that you
see on the top of your map and where kie
is that's like it's the arrow and then
we can follow her here here CeCe here is
a a level five club for you for me the
next shotgun I can make is a double
barrel oh man I need to keep reading
shotgun weekly um also oh there it is
nice here are some bandages for you guys
guys three C here's two it's not that I
don't love you any
any let me get you another one you go CE
you all right yeah those are for
you yep you can take these too it's also
for you CeCe oh for me okay now you
have mom so ready okay okay okay
okay okay now let's go do some quests to
get you guys
get you up to speed SS good how many
Quest have you guys done n we have whole
land claim block
yeah okay gotcha we were digging I think
we fin did we finish the DI the quest in
the upper right corner does it say go to
the trader oh we did that one we have
land clean block and then it goes Place
land clean block we didn't need to place
it but I think we want to place it in a
good Place why I don't
know um it's getting to be pretty late
so I'm not sure if if we'll be able to
turn in the quest
todays good in the morning
[Music]
okay welc to trainer trer I'm thirsty I
need an old drinky hold on little
rink um the IDS are holding having
there's some dog food in here in the
vending machine you want some dog food
dog food yeah the dog food dog food
unless unless the dog f for you guys
yummy Yumm how do I hand him
stuff go talk to him talk to him he
didn't we agree he mean by the way he
will he will be are mean things to
you I don't know if he wants any of my
quests
oh he wants to give you quests don't you
worry he definitely does but he's just
kind of a mean guy so just get ready for
oh I see choose a
reward gun machine machine
gun machine G Pockets we have a pipe
machine gun pipe machine gun pipe
machine gun pipe machine gun bundle yeah
I want the shotgun though no no no no I
want the shotgun shotgun M
yeah should I ask him for more jobs
fetch yes you want to you want to get a
job right fet let's fet clear
zombies fet fet closer is better a bit
farther hey Jerk you need some work or
what let's see I have some level two
quests that would get you guys some real
real good let's do okay can we only
accept one Quest at a
time no you can do multiple oh okay then
we'll do this fetch one let's do the
second with thumb up so if you guys want
to follow me I can take you okay thank
you shall we shall we go let's is it the
one on the map that I see as well is it
yours or is that the different one 43
424 so met away 400 and yep right this
way that I'm headed y
oh right behind where's the tip or he
doesn't deserve a tip he's a mean guy
that D's a bul ignore
him told us to wipe the smile away yeah
that's not very smile wait are you guys
crouching are we probably oh no we are
oh we are okay with the
sword we have the
couch yeah we'll do a couple quests um
although it might be night time by the
time that we finish this so we won't be
able to turn it and we'll see um until
tomorrow and then we'll get you guys
prepared for the raid and we teach you
some stuff okay let's see if we can make
you some strong armor too your armor
what level is it careful coming down
this hill one okay all right I got
you be careful be careful just just kind
of carefully scale the wall I like that
adrenaline maybe that's how we survive
in the zombie apocalypse we all addicted
to Adrenaline yeah it has to be it's got
to be what's your what's your your
favorite way to get
adrenaline mine is cough that's not
that's that's not
okay what's
you um uh shaking a soda bottle and then
like opening
it that's bad
but can you do that inside or outside
yeah you like cleaning
no all right
[Applause]
Ready's here getting my party crony oh I
have to do that crony get yeah you got
to invite crony there we go should we
place the L block or what's this yellow
arrow here
[Music]
for uh it it'll start the
quest I will start the quest
now all right now be very careful these
zombies be a little
stronger
win they they awak in
here yay nice did it so much more damage
now right now I know how to turn that
off why why why I don't know that's
really horrifying I wish I could turn it
off hang on maybe we can break it no no
it's it's here's there's a there's a
valve
here I'm just C to be honest what's
going oh he's just doing his job guys
stop can't he's not
[Music]
helping zombie oh
wow problem zombie nice y big
exp feel free to you know look through
all the stuff and loot whatever you want
those look good
let's see nothing in
[Music]
here all right let's see what we got in
here oh this is a nice
room okay
[Music]
upstairs baby come down the stairs and I
will attack you died from one hit she
look good
though wor you'll be fine see you're
doing good good
job yeah you that
club good doing great with that club
nothing oh we got to climb up here oh I
hate this one climb up
where I'm Too Tall a biggest enemy the
honestly freaking rope I
can't jump up the oh this fight
fight oh my gosh the zombies have off I
off there the
friend I can't I'm on a stamina don't
worry don't push
yourself the trash someone take it take
I can handle it I'm just
dizzy okay do you have to have food or
water uh I think so yeah let me just
really quickly heal myself wait actually
I have food I just need
water I'm num n n chicken
yummies right we're almost done I think
we just need to do a little we're just
missing a couple a few
more all right not a lot of goodies in
there I think this one also gets turned
off somewhere just oh oh oh
here okay we can jump into this
hole wow zombies can climb wol now we're
looking for supplies ladies so everybody
has their own Supply C have to find help
help help I'm going to die I'm going to
die help what's going on oh I went
theall and there's like a bunch of them
and okay okay okay and the door is
locked and I kind get out it's over
we're good we're good don't
[Music]
worry why is he so strong I'm out a
Salina okay you got this you got this
just C him around it's okay he's
nice use the first items that us all
right so the area is clear it's okay
we'll do another Quest don't worry it is
we'll do another
one I guess it was
time for her to I get it that's very
silly that you said
that uh I found my items my supplies
everybody's is in a different place so
look for an orange marker on your screen
that has like a a bag icon it's orange
search for
that we haven't seen an orange marker
yet there it is it's far we should use
another
Bandit it could be upstairs or up in the
the attic there are a couple different
places it could be but try and track it
you guys your dogs right you can track
it oh Myst oh we found it nice it was
right here by the orange
marker nice who would have
know that's
crazy how about you did you find yours
mine's downstairs one sec
okay oh no it's like middle it's not
downstairs I wonder if it's in the attic
I guess no it's like in a
vent oh yeah there is a vent world ah oh
my God don't worry all the zombies are
dead no I got jump scared by The
Voice Hi nothing can hurt you hello
hello hello I'm sorry our fallen
soldier it's all good did the mission
fail because of me or no no no
no it's just that I don't think that you
can get their rewards sadly but we can
oh no no that's okay that's completely
finey what are you
me I'm fighting with a bone knife
oh nice I wonder I wonder how that I
wonder if it's a strong enough weapon
against these zombies um let me see
maybe I can make you a club uh that
might be better I can give you a level
five club that will be a bit stronger
for you um I don't know what You' been
putting points into whether it's been
strength or whatnot but this will
probably help you more than the knife um
the the the level five wooden Club we're
going to the
[Music]
club this one right
here BL okay I found my Satchel
thingy a then are already done the quest
then yes so we can go back to the trader
now and turn in the quest and maybe get
a new
one did you uh grab your backpack crony
you got everything yeah awesome let's go
back then let's go back to the trader if
we can figure out how to leave this
house oh it's uh it's this way I think I
remember kind
of um PA the exercise yeah yeah it's
just this
[Laughter]
way here it's supposed to be this way
but then the door the game me neither
it's fine now it is night time though so
actually we can't uh turn in the quest
instead what I think we should do is we
should make a run to the new house
Provisions to take to the old house okay
oh oh oh oh KY I've shotgun weekly you
you use shotguns right oh yeah yeah yeah
I need that okay put it on the floor
thank you all right read oh I have some
shotgun shells too oh if you if you're
not using them I'll gladly take them off
your hands I just love collecting
things yes thank you you're the best oh
I have one more here you go another I
can
this is big all right maybe I can make
some for you guys too if I have enough
stuff so let me look it up double barrel
shot if we die then the mission will
fail so we got to live yeah that's kind
of that's kind of that kind of I mean I
get it but that is kind of the difficult
part I
think I'm very over cucumber though so I
think it would be nice to go back to a
house don't really mind which one I
think we should go back to the old house
first though okay okay okay to collect
materials and then see if we can craft
some stuff at the new house so just
follow me follow
my sounds good yeah okie dokie you know
we only we had
bicycles the bicycles come from
quests after the raid we can speedrun a
bunch of quests if you want I think
actually shouldn't Ki be able to make
bicycles now I wonder I wonder if she's
the if she's that she has like I think
the thing is you only need three vehicle
magazines and I think she had like 10
but I think the problem was often the
not having a workstation for everything
right yeah now we have a workbench
though yeah workbench right right so I
think so we could all have bik bikes we
could be a biker g bik y that'd be cool
there something making sounds maybe we
canot okay wor just keep running you're
faster than them for now are we faster D
is kind of low even at night I would say
yeah even at night they just get faster
but you're still faster than them
okay why are you starving cuz we can
kill you don't kill us no no then they
fail the
quest all right we are hungry we are
thirsty but right now we're just kind of
option we had to eat and
drink we got food at uh the new house
house okay we'll collect some materials
here wonder if I can make guns for
everyone maybe Kiara can make some stuff
too yeah just walk uh are we splitting
up wait wait where are you going I have
no idea I have to check the map okay
okay turn around follow my marker it's
it's to the left uh there a bunch of
bars and it shows some arrows that are
pointing look for the one that's
pointing to my and just follow that
direction okay
follow Cecilia Cecilia probably knows
how to use the the thing yeah I'm just
sticking to the road so that we can have
visibility
screaming it's okay keep going I'm a
Sal it's okay it's okay why did it start
attacking the car that's
weird I was always standing in traffic I
hate this oh cars
disgusting our cars kind of weird if you
think about it I've always thought cars
are kind of weird because it's like a
house but outside of your house and
people look into it but people act as if
it's like their private space but it's
not really because I can look into your
car you know yeah unless it's looking at
some's house
too if we eat or drink something then
our stamina issues will be soft yeah you
can eat or drink do you have food or
water we have Mony water uh coffee
coffee yeah but you might get Tummy egg
let's wait until we we have some coffee
we can drink that do we have anything to
eat we have
mushrooms yummy can we eat eat mushrooms
I also have some water and some Golden
Rod tea for you guys over here and
there's also going to be some food in
the house just when you approach the
house be careful it is very fortified
okay there are there be spikes to not
run into the spikes yes take a straight
path into the house I think at some
point I think it was yesterday started
just breaking spikes because she was so
sick she's like I'm done with
her no what do you mean just don't walk
into
them spikes yeah me we a really job we
did yeah we worked really hard for those
spikes you know how much wood is needed
for them yeah insane it's impressive we
very careful not to get hurt by them or
when we're opening the doors we're
struggling a little bit crossing the
water okay this way okay I have a lot of
ammo so I'm going to drop them off here
I don't want to die in the water I think
I have some shotgun parts
somewhere
materials I'm going to make you guys
some better armor maybe I bet Kiara can
still make the better armor Al together
though yeah it might be nice to have now
unless it uses a lot of important
materials just so that we can like
survive until we meet them again and
then maybe tomorrow when we all like
hampered down in the base and starting
maybe she can make us some yeah can
IIA do we jum did I use you as a rock to
pass oh gosh I'm sorry don't hit
me I my button guys I'm not a zombie I'm
an a it's different I'm
alive wait you can be used as a a
Crossing block over the water yeah that
is true I can't
float where do I put the armor parts um
oh you have armor parts that's huge yeah
okay maybe a nerd hat then I would hold
on to that if I were you okay um and
give it to how many parts do you have by
chance uh just two okay um and bi has
four I wonder if you go first I'll close
the door because if you use those you
can make armor kits if you have sewing
and duct tape as well and you want to
make those because you can get stronger
like pieces of armor and clothing so if
you can try and use those armor parts
with sewing and duct tape and put them
together you can make armor kits try and
make some of those if you can I think we
have armor parts in our box yeah tell
what what is armored up is that is
should we use that or should we use that
or should we give that to um it will
basically make you able to make better
level armor but the thing is we can
probably like me or Kiara have been
reading a lot of those we can just make
you really strong armor instead I have
three I can give this I have one armor
part you have one armor part okay put it
that will help I think that will help
Kiara just definitely let her know here
that you have an armor part help you out
I'll put it behind you magine oh that's
a magazine have a magazine and
mechanical
parts that's I'm going to give those to
K cuz I think they'll be in better hands
with her machete
PLS I haven't really decided what I want
to go into I think I want I think I want
to go oaba I have I found something it's
called Bob rolling we store items and
maybe like bar balling like crying
balling your eyes no like like brawling
brawling
brawling I don't need that bring the
egg uh
hey fire Almanac Fight Fire with Fire
Fire based weapon effects s oh
cool are you guys under are you guys in
your little room yeah the bunk bed okay
I've got some food for you oh thank you
here I take these and then have some of
the Golden Rod tea as well because this
will cure disent having did I just
destroy something by accident oh no I'm
sure you're fine don't worry about okay
I'm sure you're fine let's have the
golden R
te oh it looks like mky water but it's
not that will be good for you it looks
like murky water it is not though should
I use it right now I don't do we have
this
c um if you don't I mean it's still
probably it still will cure thirst we
have some murky water that I really want
kind of we need to maybe I should learn
some cooking skills as well to boil some
water and
such let's see I'll put stuff
oh I was reading vehicle
Adventures I can make
bicycles please make us bicycles all
right let me see if I can figure it
[Music]
out I'm just going to put all my stuff
into the shared storage so that people
can take it yeah we should do the same M
Jam because we don't really know what's
what so honestly yeah that's a huge help
because for example if I want to make a
shotgun I need duct tape some people may
just have duct tape lying around you
know I have one duct tape I put it in
here I don't know oh yes let's freaking
go crony you're a legend thank you wa
put it where I can make a shotgun now
yeah in the materials box it might be
full but if it's full maybe see if
there's something that you like in there
okay
AB you have one magazine that we're
probably not going to use let's put that
in there put stuff
box this is also ammo do we have ammo no
let put some of our weapons in the
weapon I'll take one if it's free this
one's pretty full materials oh we have a
lot of feathers you can put the feathers
the feathers like pretty good C so I
feel like it might be a good idea for
them to put it in the Shar container if
they're not using it like seeds for
example oh seeds yeah seeds need to be
in the food crate yeah it seems like
some people uh they have their like they
have stuff in their own boxes so maybe
we can ask later yeah good idea
animal I wish we had one where it's like
this is the garbage box cuz I have so
much stuff and I don't know what to do
with this you know what I'll put mine in
two oh you know if you have no idea
where to put him just put it here I'll
organize it I love organizing yay thank
you okay I'll put I'll put I'll put it
in here put any random stuff and I got
you buddy alcohol I don't
know oh take this oh this what does it
sound
bad I understand the need to organize I
agree with it let's put in there which
one's this food food so we can put our
mushrooms in
here there's animal F this one too is
animal fat and material and item or food
I put it in food cuz it's like like
animal base
but yeah I don't really know like what
else you use it for but
yeah we also can head to the new house
as well and see what's going on there
there may be stuff that will help us out
over there too okay I'm going I
recommend that we do that since now it's
about to be morning yay y the new house
is right next to the trader as well so
we can
turnest that one here's some murky water
m
yeah I was going to bring that to Bieber
I have six murky water to have her boil
it I don't want to anymore you can take
mine two then okay please oh wait I took
I don't want I
want yeah let's put those away nice
and some beer at this time of day I'm
predisposed to try and hit people oh I'm
I'm drunk in
game that's it's just like me two hours
ago yeah it's all blurry
oh wait whoops I put my club in
the the weapons
uhoh okay you may need it you can put
the also we we have these but I don't
know if we need those we could put them
with that coffee this this
materal coffee material oh
maybe got a lot of good stuff actually
I'm not going to take it though I'm just
looking at it take it take it steel
no mechanical part as material Ste only
o I can make a land mine
cool that could be yeah I mean the the
whole like trap stuff sounds fun but I
guess it's not that useful if we want XP
so I'm not going to do it but it's
fun yeah for
fun okay better
maybe I'm going to head over to the new
house whenever you guys want to want to
come over um feel free and I'll have
some stuff for you I think I'm going to
try and make armor for you guys there we
together yeah if you would like to come
with guys where did you
leave okay you can you can drive for in
front of us no worries raid time so we
will
here oh wait can I interact with your
bicycle
we both I'm figure out if I can make a
bicycle for you guys because bi has
handlebars but we need like a chassis is
what it's called a bicycle chassis I'm
going to see if we have that at the new
place Oh I thought you could make it out
of like iron or
something oh can you you might be able
to meal in the ammo section have had
some
food I want to go to the new house so I
can make armor for those guys
right now we're hungry though we also
don't have stamina don't go in the water
Cory you have to you have to let it go
we got to go we got to go sorry sorry
yeah I'm
sorry be right
there you have to it will never be a
perfect system it's okay okay okay okay
okay okay
it's a perfect
system okay I got it it's okay to be
okayish system as long Astic okay
AO eat something you won't have to wait
to hit
that yeah I'm still I still believe
you're the only one that knows that that
thing I think everyone I mean we'll see
once you get to the new house you can
check you can check the boxes yeah I've
already like sorted all the boxes in
that in that old
house yeah you you'll get to live your
dream with a new one as well oh sick
yeah new house is full of good materials
that's why I'm running over there really
quick to grab some stuff and then we got
to go back and make our I don't know if
we need to fortify the house I will say
that during one of the earlier nights
there was a zombie that jumped and it
could jump like 10 m so if those zombies
attack us they will get through our
defens only to fight is the thing that's
fine we can fight we can fight it's just
cutting down the numbers with spikes
might be very
helpful oh we might also maybe at least
uh we for and I maybe we should go to
the trader to give back Quest okay
should we just head over there now then
new house yeah yeah yeah the red one so
that you if you die nothing bad
happens oh yeah make sure you turn in
that Quest it is right next to the new
house than yeah yeah it's true it's
pretty
close so cool so the old house is just a
decoy yeah we use we use that as our
fortification so I think I'm not sure
why but I think it's so that in case we
die and lose they don't destroy our all
our items and stuff yeah it's not our
main base of operations it's to pull the
zombies over there you know we have two
houses basically yeah I I have a
question we're starving so we ate a can
of salmon but it didn't really do
anything we're still
starving that's kind of weird I feel
like well if you go to the trader he's
selling a lot of food and you'll get
money for your for your quest okay okay
so you might be able to grab some food
also if you come to the new house I
think that there's actually a ton of
food at the new house just kidding come
to the new house please we're almost
there an
eggs let St for the new house at the new
house it's right where I how do you
think you can make boats at some point
do you think that's the thing I'm pretty
sure that's possible it would be weird
if would be cool to have like shotgun
amm thirsty now thirsty
and then we just drive around in boats
and run away from the zombies yeah
little ship that's
awesome shotgun that would be nice all
right crafting shotgun
now the new house
yeah we stop at the new house we got
some then we'll go to talk to the
traitor CL oh 15 armor parts yeah looks
like we we will we should
armor for you guys but I got to ask if
it's
okay here and we're cooking three bacon
and
[Music]
eggs welcome so check out the food and
the food crate oh okay the food uh feel
free to look it's in the cooked food and
Medicine just take what you need okay I
don't know if there's much food in
here there should be enough if not
there's three bacon and eggsit are
cooking right now on the okay maybe I'm
can we try cooking eggs is that's
something yeah there is a lot of food
there hold up yeah click click on the um
there there you do need to cook a little
I don't have the skill oh I can make I
can make t meat let's make the
meat oh yeah you can also just take the
the bacon and eggs that are on the the
stove and eat those
okay I should help you
[Music]
a take you're willing to bacon an
egg it's
[Music]
making I am so slow my God no
worries what I just got a big pop up and
said I was dehydrated guys don't forget
oh stay hydrate hydration
check hydration check is
important okay I'm going to make another
shotgun to get how come nobody check the
cover eat my meat oh did they not is
there stuff inside the covers yeah
there's a book here it's going to take a
minute oh
nice no
one oh it's for
cooking cooking it it's going to take a
minute and a half at the bottom that's
there yeah maybe one of our chefs could
read it but our chefs needs to cook a
little more
[Music]
food oh really can't believe it I would
love to do some supply stuff that would
be what would you like to do in this
world cron would you like to cook would
you like to what do you want
before I I don't know if you guys have
any need for collecting materials but I
could probably do that I like that too
material colle
yes I don't actually yeah I think we
always need materials right Callie isn't
that like always need stuff to make
stuff so if you guys like going on like
little excursions and and it does happen
naturally when you do quests where you
will go to places and you can scavenge
that right right uh there also farming
which might be important but I don't
know I think s is farming but I don't
really understand how farming Works
Scavenging is really helpful I am going
to are these
things the thing like for example I'm
going into healing and I want to heal
but like everything I need I need uh
like aloy cream for it and I need Aloe
Vera and there's no aloe vera in the
world andless I haven't seen it at least
unless we Farm it
ourselves tra has oh the trader has it
okay got to go see the new
Trader the new Trader okay yeah she's a
beautiful girl
give these to what with these trees
going into hello I'm
home okay we're going to head on out
we're going to go to the Traer
Traer where are
they is it is the where's the forge
cie oh it's here I found it I found it
okay uh waiting for a shotgun to be
complete oh it's done okay uh F please
where are you guys we are going towards
the Traders but we're not that far oh
you are okay let's both go to the trader
together okay okay we'll be at the end
of the road here okay if we
here I have a little something for
you oh heck yeah okay we'll head towards
the Traer right now we're a little bit
slow I think so Mr Fix It hey guys I
have a little gift
what here you go um this should help you
during the it should help you wait
and then
here give you guys let me give I don't
know how much you guys are going to need
so let me for
now here's 65 ammo thank you do I need
to load it in the gun probably you press
R to reload it
[Music]
a ooh I think I found I think I found
something that I want to do if you want
to if you want to join me with that I
need oh yeah
I need five forged steel five I need
five duct
tape five yeah find glue and cloth you
guys I'm sure that'll get you the duct
tape you
need heck yeah cloth you can make with
the cotton right is there anywhere we
can do like
Farming Farming is a bit difficult in
this game yeah I think farming is super
comp some I don't I don't really know
how that works also it takes really long
there no no gratification there it's
like can you put it in there I'll wait
[Music]
years now let's oh
Ser I wonder if there is anyone has duct
tap here so he's going to give you um a
gift for completing
the you can choose whichever one you
want and get the hell out of here maybe
crafting skilled yeah they're just
really good oh I can do it now get a
little
so cornbread's really good and yummy you
can buy some of that but also at the
same time you know fauna and biu when
they do want to cook they they make a
ton of a ton of cornbread and such
so want to much your money on it it's up
to
you he doesn't let me know I can do all
the side jobs like if there's like
nothing to do like aside from you know
looting places or whatnot if there's
anything else you want me to
do I don't know if I got any magazines
anybody
wants well which ones do you have Sol
and farming explosive magazine I'm going
to go and loot houses and see if I can
find glue well you know K wants hammers
so just put it in the books box okay
let's talk to him again he doesn't have
any jobs I don't really know what other
jobs there are to be honest corny so
it's kind of like just do whatever
gotcha yeah yeah just just just do what
you want to do you guys want to do one
more quick
Quest he doesn't have any you want to
come to Cory two Quest two Quest should
we check our own quest list you don't
have any do we have our own Quest oh
that's right one second I've got a bunch
of we didn't use our skills or anything
yet oh please yeah allate your skill
point and actually I would recommend
putting them into shotgun and strength
okay oh God the DAT is turned
red
strength strength is a shotgun there no
food I'm going to
die let me uh let me hit him up let me
ask by by no food drink I don't know how
many points we have we don't have
anymore oh do we use them all
up okay so go to Rally Point is that the
quest you're
doing okay see that okay okay I think we
can do one more Quest and then we need
to regroup with the others and prepare
all right they're coming home they're
getting ready to come home our cooks are
on the way
okay it's going to be a bloody day I do
want to mod the shotgun but I don't know
what mods I
have have to look and see I'm sure I
have one
oh actually we have a light I know going
fast for a
bit just fixing stuff in the house cuz
there are a lot of damage stuff around
here nice nice extra 4 it all right
let's go let's get
moving try using that shotgun yeah let's
try using it on the shotgun practice oh
really but what about my
bullets you'll get more bullets maybe
crony could learn minor skills do the
bunker
mining yeah be a miner it's loud I like
dig some
holes oh I love being a hole digger oh
yeah only for the most sophisticated I
feel danger grinding
croner how should we get down from this
hill or you guys just very carefully
slowly walk down okay just yeah very
carefully
you won't break your leg this game the
fall damage is like you have to really
be jumping pretty high up okay um but if
you can scale walls so easily in this
game see we broke like before and that
was a really bad experience oh no yeah
oh yeah g it was a bad
experience we got stuck in a storm with
da being the da was a good part the
storm was the bad part yeah course
let me know when you guys are there and
then I'll come back yep I'm I'm there
I'm waiting at the exclamation point
Okie doie I don't think I've done a
clear quest to this house yet maybe but
I don't know nice I'll wait for you guys
here I we eat it's say you need to
eat eat down
let's eat the sandwich sandwich oh is
that a sham sandwich yeah just get ready
to drink some Golden Rod tea after don't
eat it I ate it okay I think we drank
our tea too do more tea I have more tea
okay we're going to drink the te I
thought that was the one that made us
sick
a I don't know it just look like a the
quest no because he has not here oh I
don't know oh okay I'm coming okay right
I'm right here what's in the
house AO plant there's an AO plant in
the
house part PL on
Al it's a nice place let's look in the
cupets already thinking about stealing
it huh why not a third base would be
nice but I think it should be more in
the burnt Forest Area or maybe the snowy
area all right snow area
[Music]
use the gun my gun you
should yes fire
away there's a food Pile in there if
there's any
goodies sorry I thought you were I'll
give you a
bandage this is a Time some oh my god
did someone shoot are you kidding me I
had did I have full health who how
happenand I think I hit you in the head
but here's the thing you have to
understand you didn't appear on my
screen until half it's okay okay BL
let's blame the Ping blame blame the
Ping it was the Ping it's okay maybe I
just jump I jumped into I will admit I
fall but that no no no no don't worry
don't worry it was probably me I I might
have just jumped into your into your all
right let's push forward me try and stay
away from my friends beating up zombies
he's behind the
[Music]
[Applause]
door yeah beat her up beat her up yeah
he's up he's
up no problem
okay let's eat the food we're hurting
here all right there's one in the
washroom
hereid can take care of
that I'm going upstairs there's a bunch
of dudes
here let's go help
kill should be
okay
after I don't think shot the best the
best weapon
oh he's not done wa wait oh he's ouch OU
ouch ouch okay he's down why nice why
why you
sp why is he get her get her cron oh
nice oh I found
glue glue more shotgun parts make more
shotguns for
friends shipping crate dog food strength
mod oh batter up for
me let's see there's some there's some
dog food in here if you want dog food
dog let's hit this hit this yeah just
hit
it this will enhance my strength I think
that this will be
good just letting you guys know I'm
installing a strength mod on my hat
because I really think that it will help
you get be smart cool and
strong did we do it we did it someone
wants an intelligence model give it
maybe maybe Kiara could use that nothing
yeah all right we did it
guys nerd hats have been requested I
hear yes we just finished a quest we're
not too far from the new house but we
probably need to start working on
getting ready for the raid
anyway so we're going to go turn in a
quest and then yeah we have some hungry
folks here I can now make him on level
four already but I will need four armor
crafting kits unless you want it on a
lower level oh the nerd hats yeah yeah
um they have they do have some armor
parts um I might actually if if Loko
wants to make a level one or so uh nerd
hat I'll take it and I can give them
mine because they need exp more than I
do but we'll see we'll see how many
armor parts we have cuz I think I think
that there was a bunch in the crates at
the house but you might need that for
I'm I'm parts we have here and
there I think bi had like four in her
personal chest at the old house so I was
going to ask her about those if she'd
like to make a
donation I know I I got a couple too I
just I don't know if I can make a level
four nerd hat Maybe three is fine
yeah yeah how do we make the level one
night
H yeah I mean there's some extra stuff
but the most important thing is the
armor crafting kit um I'll make you
actually you know what I'll give you my
level two I think nerd
hat uh or wait wait wait wait wait wait
you yeah donate to the animal
shelter new armor and I'll try and craft
I think I have enough cloth to craft you
guys some better primitive Armor high
level I
also youo problem we
knowledable I actually have a ton of Mag
to give Tiara
yeah I need more duct tape do I have any
duct I have two duct
tape okay that'll be enough I'll see if
has use make duct
tape we're still using the old uh base
right today for the attack yes okay hey
Chad does this increase I'll C you this
doesn't increase B congratulations
here's your reward glue glue we should
ask for glue right to make duct tape
glue yes we need glue as much glue as
possible it's not shotgun I figured as
much okay get the magazines oh that's a
food
bundle workbench oh wow another
workbench that's a big reward money oh
they're giving you a workbench don't
yeah yeah it's a reward for
aass
nice then we could have two next to each
other because again we can't use it at
the same time it seems right okay I
grabbed it nice
no we don't have any more can K can you
make a
bicycle
oh you should be able
to it's a matter of we don't have the
parts is the thing yeah I would need the
parts but if you do enough quests you
get a
bicycle yeah
keep okay okay let's
leave quest uh let's
go uh should we go should should we go
to the old house now or the new one or
maybe zombie coming up behind yeah okay
okay let's go to the old house and
make just check the spikes we don't have
to make more but maybe we can like fix
the ones that need
fixing yeah or should we stop by the
trader first since the Trader's nearby
one more armor okay okay okay okay and
then we can get some stuff there oh
there's some air drops oh oh that's the
sound is that the sound
yeah back to where
is this
where
okay
[Music]
there our inventory is full again so we
should go do something about it
that's why okay I now have an old level
two nerd hat that somebody can have and
one new level four nerd hat that I'll
give to Fu thank
you how about how's crony doing crony uh
crony CC you guys probably need some exp
right yeah yeah I can live without too
you know if you
I can even more crafting kits then I can
make more nerd heads okay okay I I'll
see if I have some and I'll I'll I'll
I'll but right now I'm too I'm very a
bit far away if you can put it into a
chest somewhere get uh I'll put the nerd
hats that are like free to take into the
armor chest in the new house nice thank
you I mean if there were spars would
love it but otherwise you know actually
it's okay well there's still enough time
I can probably still make more I just
need more duct tape and stuff I wonder
if someone supply drops G's kind of
close I wonder if she's going to get
him
wow it's fine you need to focus on
getting
ready we want to focus on getting ready
but we're not sure what getting ready
isly
B UPG your armor I'll make you some
armor I said I was going to do it F me
I'm going to make a bunch of armor with
cloth thank you we have a cloth I think
maybe if you can give me some cloth that
will help me if we do have cloth I oh we
have fragment fragment oh I see I wonder
if you can make a full cloth with the
fragments you can craft it I
think thank you I think cloth fragments
are fine I'll take them
okay this house is so
cramped we need a bigger one we need a
Bigg three thank thank you oh perfect
this is actually yeah this will be great
okay I can use that okay we can make
more so we'll make more
yeah if it's
helpful oh oh oh oh uh Cory you should
buy lucky loot sorry guys you should buy
lucky looter let's put our magazines
away lucky looter it's like a I heard on
a guide you really shouldn't do
thaton why
not it's called
luyer but if you want it go for it go
for it no no no no no okay okay I just
read it and I was like this would be
good but if if the guide says no then
don't do it okay never
mind away a lot of things I have a
feeling we're not going to survive
night don't say that I think we'll be
fun if somebody has to die we will be
the one who
dies that's heroic but you know we won't
die just stay in the back a little
bit we defin be in the back naturally
because we're scared
but a paper paper magazine let's put it
the old house which is this follow me
okay what else do I have I I
follow I follow you something something
baby maybe put it in here
there is that does it go that way I call
you you into the deep see baby someone
me
up you know
it come here come here full in this room
not insane I'll give the CL they're all
of different levels but it's better than
what you have right now
so I made another nerd goggle level four
so um give one
to okay let's put this stuff on you're
going to give you're going wear the nerd
hat though maybe someone else okay yeah
wait wait but I think hi is here so we
can take no wait are you who's we're in
the in the new house CR in front of you
yeah uh yeah one of you Cecilia crony
fight for life for this level four yep
okay take take the level two one of you
can take the level two one in the chest
no actually I think I think you'll
benefit more from having
take I'll take the other one armored oh
wait I can I can probably still make
another one if I get more duct tap no no
no thank you fragments
too I have the the fragrance
here behind us behind us
you
is thank you
thank you% what it look like now should
I drop the Primitive Hood then yeah it's
a level five primitive Hood who wants
the Primitive Hood maybe give it to um I
think CeCe needed it oh no I I have the
I have the the I have the head K I made
now this okay I'll hold it for
now do we have water she has a level two
making some better stuff let's get water
PL oh we have a lot of plant fiber oh
okay nice big big
news yes we do that's
a is time make a gun okay okay okay we
should the rod and fles ner hats unless
they give me ingredients B too thank you
very
much
okay come here I got some better armor
for it's just higher level armor yippe
here you go yippe and the hat I think
somebody else has the very strong face
mask who's not using the very strong
face mask look we have the that one the
strong the Primitive Hood yeah if you
could give that to crony that would be
crony here it
is yippe yipp now you're
fortified yay
look at how strong we
[Music]
are you wear a baseball bat there's a
baseball bat in here oh I have a forge
ahead if someone needs that put yes yes
please please here I'll it I see you I
put it on my feet okay in my on my
bottom see what we look like
Bellows head by the way
these
sorry no problem it's so cramped in here
also get a little bit of a little bit
more medical stuff so like maybe
everybody take like a couple medical
things let's take some medical
things which one am I making I don't
have any medical I'll take one Med kit
for
me painkillers or
[Music]
something you should probably boil all
the murky water so I'll do that I also
have some we have
some okay can you like just put it all
we have glue we should put the GL away
hold on crony hold on a sec let me give
you do we have a magazine box in this
space as
well yeah books yeah yeah books are here
right in front of the fire oh okay
thanks C use
[Music]
oh oh
thanks oh thank
you you didn't have to it's okay I have
magazines for you a lot oh thank you
where's where's do you have any more clo
frag chance yeah they the I have
10 oh really
yeah I
[Music]
have and this is 17 behind you K yo yo
thank you
[Music]
yo you got to make the armor for
us the armor
okay we give can for the armor parts
yeah oh yeah armor parts will also be
useful for a lot of things okay we only
had that one so and maybe we have some
more back maybe you should use this
Kelly oh yeah I have I have a since you
do shotgun I have a thing improves
weapon handling while moving or firing
from the hip because the weapon becomes
more manageable enclosed quarters oh
really interesting let me see let me
grab that from you yeah I put little
hands on it what am I doing right now
cuz I don't use a gun you can use it is
this here and I think we can put the
mods in the magazine section too because
um they're like all learnable stuff so
yeah that's
I think might use this CU she uses a
pistol oh okay okay I'll give it to her
when I see oh she's here Cecilia we
found some ala seeds I don't know if
that helps at all but um I would need
like actual alivea but it's still nice
for the
future don't know how the farming Works
to honest we do have a farm here yeah we
kind of notic we took down a super corn
and can I scrap can I scrap all the
level one primitive outfits cuz it's
taking up space in the armor section I
think so I think you can scrap that yeah
scrap it let's it pretty sure we have
these things
probably iron in my
[Music]
cook unless it's something important and
it's not I have another workbench I'll
put the workbench down somewhere
else so
blind don't punch it yeah I am pretty
blind there it is what if I put the
what's a pipe rifle good is it bad
okay uh do you guys have murky water
yeah oh yeah you put it all there okay
I'll boil all of them then that'll be
good nice there's a person standing
there call is a pipe pipe pipe pip pipe
rifle good can I use that uh the only
good pipe weapon apparently is Machine
Gun okay
but if I make a shotgun find enough
Springs uh Springs Springs I need seven
springs for my new shot uh machine gun
oh dang it you're not using the AK more
um I was using it it was so good
but I can already make something better
now at level why don't you give it to
somebody else maybe if you're going to
make another gun oh there somebody else
use machine guns now I wonder I don't
have any guns yet have you skilled into
anything no no you haven't skilled into
any weapons no cuz I can't
peek you can't pick oh yeah I'll do it
now I was waiting for well I we didn't
need for the first round and I didn't
know so I'll do it now okay I'll go into
I don't want to do anything
like maybe
I'll I'll be right back should this
one do we know when the zombies are
going to get
here I wonder have you put points into
anything have you picked oh I put them
all into Str strength okay you know what
stage okay I'll go I'll do that too
at the house the
house oh lucky I should started
organizing this chest too it's kind of
getting
messy blood Mo starts at 22 by the way
ladies nobody wants robotics no the
Nerds I kind of wanted to do robotics is
that fun you should you should there are
tons of robotic magazines cuz no one
wants to learn it
so take is there something wrong about
learning
it it's just it just seems complicated
but I'm sure it's not that
complicated all right I've taken the
food I want to
take what do we do with the freaking
Duke's Casino token yeah WEA
robotic turrets are amazing yeah people
recommend making turrets
but nerd stuff but then we don't get XP
that's that's the only thing that I'm
worried about that if we go do you think
do you think they count as like I wonder
I wonder maybe chat knows if they count
as exp mhm yep turrets give exp they say
okay I used don't like skill points to
make it yeah use your skill points okay
we should probably head back to the
house uh pretty soon pretty
[Music]
soon let me see maybe we should all get
everybody in the same voice chat let me
go I think I'm
stuck I think we can make it down you
got up here we can get
down send a
message I'm going to go head
back okay I'll read the I'll read
the robotics then see what are
they I'll go to the house
too well I don't where did you say the
robotics
was what was that what was the robotics
thingy uh magazines in the books crate
that's here either that or in the old
house there are a ton of Rob I see I see
there's a good amount yeah I'll go to
the old house
yeah that was so s
what was
that all right old house quick way point
okay
gu yeah cuz it's almost time yeah okay
let's go back so exciting yeah oh God
there's still stuff to organiz it's okay
it's okay you can do next time next time
it's okay and once the raid is over
we'll still you know can go on for like
a tiny bit longer I think but I I won't
I have a different stream I'm doing but
okay yeah if you want to stick around I
think that having the server open for
like a couple more hours is probably
okay we just have to keep track of when
the raid is going to happen you know
okay now the raid is happening
in very soon very very soon so
yeah it's happening in at 10 p.m. in the
game so in like 10 10 minutes huh yeah
can so by yes we lost track of you there
you are there you are see me on the map
yeah I'll show you anytime you can't
find me look at the the left hand side
and you look for my name and there's an
arrow where I am same with any party
member
yeah why is it so
Misty we're going to the Silent Hills
baby oh no no but then we going to have
to stop talking talking to each
other it's
over would be kind of funny someone does
a silent hill in the place where they
just don't say anything en time
stream they they don't they don't
elaborate they don't explain they just
quiet oh a storm it gets super foggy
when it's close to the blood moon and it
starts storming oh I see that makes
blood moon I think this miss you uhoh
the zombies are
coming oh no I want to go home we're
going home but the zombies want to come
to our home too I don't want okay heck
yeah it's time to die time to die in
style little swimming lady make
sure
uh make sure that there that you have a
bed roll at the old house
something or the new house wherever you
want to oh we have a bed both so okay I
don't know how it works I think you have
to like intera it'll be the most recent
one oh okay we'll interact with our old
one then we justad idea I think that's
the best way okay spawn near the
backpack there cilia
imig hey that's me have you decided on
your choice of
weapon I want I think I'm going to go
stick stick
stick no no club club club oh really you
just want to focus on one I feel like I
don't know if anybody else does this but
I chose like one me and one PE pew pew I
think do you like the assault rifle do
is it fun it's fun for me it's like I
don't know much about guns and okay then
I'll go with that one okay uh I can give
you I can hand you down my old uh the
one that Callie gave me
is that if if you are using clubs and
you want to level both your your shotgun
and Club strength at the same time like
they shotguns and clubs use the same
strength metric so if you wanted to use
shotgun might be a good idea cuz you
could min max it a little better but
okay I'll I'll I I think I'll do one
skill in into because I don't want to go
since the weapon is already melee then I
want one that is a little bit further so
I'm going to go with assault rifle for
now but I can do I can change my mind
with time I think one point is not going
to
I would like to hand me down please now
are you in front of me make more SP uh
no I am at the old house right in the
I'm
coming okay so the horde is starting in
three hours is should we all go to the
vc1 then yes I that'll be a good
idea jumping
over you see one let me see one
why not in our room I don't
know we have to close the door first oh
oh take your anger out I put it down
let's go join them once we put the bed
down
okay spin
there try
again okay
so the back door is
closed uh let's
see
[Music]
thirsty okay the
front I'm going to show up last minute
again uhoh
oh r
a go let's put
magazine some shotgun shells in the
magazine and ammos s
spot okay and
then oh
nice this
is oh what is that all right higher
quality shot the shotgun maybe can we go
up to the top of the and shoot from
there oh are you using a pipe Shotgun by
chance uh yeah so I already gave uh the
double barrel shotgun that I had to F
but I wonder if I can make a shot a
shotgun double barrel quality one let me
let me look it up right
there there's a lot too I have shotgun
parts I just need five forged iron duct
tape and spring I'll see if I can if I
can make something for you a thank you
quality I don't want to hurt myself get
H does anyone have
wood I have wood the beaver has
wood can can you
can I'll just make some more spikes uh
that I'll give you I'll also like help
repair the spikes yeah okay so you kept
some wood because you'll need that in if
you want to some okay okay I'll go zie
can't get on the RO I'm so
hungry to go back
starving house try try and then I'll
bring you your your rifle nice thank you
okay I'm going to reput the spikes
outside be careful when coming in and
out of the
house okay
was there any fortification added again
or is it same as last time same as last
time I don't think I think it's GNA be
fine I don't know if I can go in time oh
gosh uh run run bicycle
bicycle It's a
Sky it's so
nice
minut ow I think I'm going to die
actually you know what I can do I think
I can make you a pipe shotgun that's
higher quality it it won't be double
barrel but it'll be a higher quality
pipe shotgun oh thank you I just have a
level one is the thing so okay I can
get level three dang it hold on a second
hold no you don't you don't have to like
straighten yourself CU I already have
the club that you gave me so oh yeah it
is a pretty it is a good club um okay
let's see pipe I just need might not
work from the roof why
not this is
does anybody have a ton of glue let me
see
glue are you in the old house or new
house uh either one I'm oh I think
there's some yeah in new in the new
house yeah but depends on where you are
it might take you a while yeah we have
other guns maybe other guns will be
suited better I I just left a while ago
I'm on the way we need you don't go too
far what about in the inventory wait are
you making it
for uh what about that
gun maybe we should we can check the the
boxes here there's a bunch of maybe we
can find maybe if bi has glue I'll just
pay her back for it later oh yeah bi's
got five glue never mind all right bi I
owe you five glue we might be
overpreparing
again we might be fine I mean over
preparing is better than
under only three pipes I wonder if we
have more
pipes pipes uh and then new house
there's definitely some
pipes
okay I might have some I'll
check oh
no she's going to die pipes you sending
her she's going to die pipes what do you
mean
pipes why is she so
confused pip okay
okay okay okay okay somebody
[Music]
has um I need them for a pipe shotgun
I'm making for crony actually I'm
stealing them from biu sorry B I owe you
six pip you don't owe me anything just
take it G get to the base hurry I'm
trying but I went the wrong way drive
faster use your bike go through the
river you don't have to go through the
path go through the river
try harder don't shoot me when I get
there please I'm not going to try really
hard not to I might enter with the
zombies oh oh then we might we might
have promise I can't promise anything
shoot me don't shoot me I'm almost
there we have 60 bullets so let's make
them count
okay yeah you guys will be fine I'm
going to show you I made a little
okay I'm I'm going to take the
roof ammo oh my God this shooting
platform is so good thank you thank you
now you're welcome you're
[Music]
welcome going to shoot you no shoot her
shoot her no it's not too
late it's dangerous dangerous the button
else have any pipes any amount of pipes
at
[Music]
all okay it's okay man we can make you a
level three I can make you a level three
shotgun well we know when the zombies
are here they they'll be here in 20
seconds oh the weather is so beautiful
it makes me want to
sing okay okay5 ammo as well to help you
out crony all right oh thank you where
are you I
probably going surprise for everybody's
facing that way face the other way see
okay here you go here is your gun and
here is your ammo oh my God didn't have
to what the heck that's a lot oh my God
use them well but remember you only it
only shoots one at a time yeah yeah so
just be ready for that I'll make
town oh boy here we go oh God here we go
uhoh good
luck oh
gosh God this easy easy
easy kinky can you one here for me wait
a minute
okay can't jump so
high
party are not best at
yeah thank you there they
are no on the field right I'm going to
throw Molotov not on the okay what be
careful just
[Music]
watch oh oh they spit all theb they
spitting e SP pretty
far okay seems like no one's attacking
the house from the side yeah I'm
watching the other
side what the heck what the
heck I got
SP look in the house in the house the
house the
house are they in the house
all why did I get SP on I forgot to put
my bed roll in here I'm leaving oh my
God it'sing like crazy
[Music]
okay that no way a bit
lagging
so you almost you ow don't hurt
me uhoh at
those oh they're going to break for the
SP
soon
get the back the
[Music]
back
it you're doing it you're
doing on the left side the okay okay
okay us I don't know way I'm looking
I'll cut this tree down too while we're
at it for more wood
what about the natural
uh Hill Z on the hill on the hill uhoh
on the bridge on the bridge zombies on
the hill zombies everybody the front of
the house now again the hill the hill
I'm going up the stairs how do
you the hill down the
stairs see if you right click to
activate it and then throw it with left
click
oh good
behind oh yeah backwards okay
down the would kid
you oh there was a bomb I didn't even
know
that yeah but it was very very
Li all the birds are
on
bird I'm this P not that strong it's
okay okay get him get him
down okay I'm putting spikes on the
front I'm not going to shoot you I think
you're taking them down am I taking them
down there's a big one there oh no it's
not oh dear good job hurts I think they
broke they broke F on this side am I
helping I think so just keep on shooting
am I helping I think
so someone's I can't reach I can't
[Music]
reach okay I'm going to try putting down
more
spikes we have to be closer enough to be
able to
beat the bird
he's in he's in wait he's
in oh
he I think let's try to
rep need toal we need to
heal
okay time right now down time healing
and food inside in the food chest
okay oh they're coming they're coming
from the left side left side
healing oh I'm going to throw a so don't
go in the field on the left side yet
okay my
M this is definitely different from the
first
nights yeah it's getting a little hard
nice
fire oh God so many of them are broken
you doded it you doded it all right I'm
going to throw pipe bombs also on the
left side so don't don't go out oh watch
out watch out watch out watch out uhoh
uhoh make it go I saw right in front of
me there's a lot going on on the left
[Music]
side oh nice make him go boom yeah make
him go boom
have I make the
brid don't worry don't worry we'll be
fine what's this they're starting to
come a little bit from the left be a
bit it's a lot on the left back there
they are get him get him get him what
out he's spinning he's spinning oh my
God take down down down yeah reloading
reloading get him get him get him right
there right there you
again nice weo have said the fight on
fire by
himself oh nice get him get him I think
we got
him anybody over here down
below I'm out of ammo soon there he is
there he is
where are the repair kits do we have any
here the
South get him there's the big one the
big
[Music]
one I'm helping I'm helping get him get
him get
him yeah
oh no don't break it through out there
using her fist she always does jumping
the
F I'm bonus uhoh uhoh he's down he's
down so
brave
go out of am probably go
out die
watch
out do not shoot shoot the N okay no I
watch out behind you the big
guy oh oh oh back
back I don't know if we hit him I think
I did
we need to beo I don't
know
reloading
wow should we go backwards
get him get him I'm
trying that him
down on the
[Music]
field I think we almost out ammo
too I'm
scared who's who's outside right now
besides fauna oh fa just went in
I'm
[Music]
in
miss something damage to me I don't know
what it's almost
over bad not too bad it's not
bad I'll make some more
spikes get him get yeah yeah
yeah it's the big one oh
there OneWest
Southwest uhoh Won't Let You
spit no
spinning going to do it okay it's okay I
won't let you spit yeah
[Music]
oh joyous Day to
Die s Days to
Die shocked face what are
those nice
do
it what's going on
open we're letting them in the house
now we're letting them in the house are
they in the
house are they is it
done music stop suddenly until 3 i i f 4
a.m. seem it seems quiet
now quiet recoup everybody okay
recoup oh it's over for real oh
man it's quiet too quiet it's too quiet
that means I don't think it's over to L
Happy song or something
[Music]
how many bullets do we have left if we
don't have any 79 really is it over two
out of 79 how
many I don't know it feels
over but the but the the the the the the
the the the sky is still
red and the Happy song isn't playing
what's
happy can't touch
we drink Dr
[Music]
water well too quiet wonderful we've
done we've done it I think next time
maybe one more row of spikes because
they do seem to be breaking through now
yeah just one small row yeah I worry if
we're going to I I wonder if we're going
to have more like flying type enemies as
well if that's a
thing only a few Birds they W that more
ammo also there's iron spikes that you
can build now uh better [\h__\h] it's not
over it's not over not over it's not a
bad feeling
you yeah did I scare you guys a little
bit such a
[Music]
troll a little silly sometimes it's
getting
rder I think it's not over
yeah I heard it's over there was a
lightning yeah it's over yeah apparently
you can you can uh get fredom all before
4: a.m. we were just back yeah we were
just okay free waves that makes sense
okay yay we did
[Music]
it it felt more intense than the first
time yeah yeah the first was B
anti we just got so much
[Music]
stronger thanks to everyone we didn't
die we helped maybe maybe good job
helping you did you did you
did you guys are doing great how do I
fix the spikes oh gosh oh gosh not with
our B not with our body I'm going to die
I'm stuck on the spikes oh no
can we heal now we're going to die let's
maybe maybe
[Music]
fix let's heal
let's die mhm I hope it's over cuz I
already left and went far away oh God
yeah yeah it's over it's over yeah it
should be done I think speaking of uh
how long may we be online today 4 hours
total again or um I would I would be
very happy if if we could if people
could not play past uh 45 minutes from
now okay okay sounds good okay of course
we'll play again tomorrow
course you know just to make sure that
everybody's got enough time to level up
and such and do a bunch of quests
together I think shotgun ammo and uh 762
ammo in the old house so take that
before you leave the old
house we need to end here for today but
if anybody wants our our um what's it
equipment cuz we have a good the good
ner right oh yeah you can borrow to
someone else I guess yeah I'll drop it
for now
okay
thanks ah I I was going to drop the
other ammo and
the let's check the current St game
stage how I drop it fa is the one that's
furthest in game stage
50 what did I do how did I this what's a
game
stage punching things punch I not been
very much I wonder if I have the debuff
or
something huh if you want to grab the N
goles again oh yeah I'll bring it into
the new house okay
[Music]
okay I hope it gave you some
levels nice go our bunk bed everybody
looks so nerdy look at
thats should we put our levels into
strength
again what weapon are you enjoying using
shotgun
shot strength is probably best for that
okay strength for shotguns
I want to take some of these materials
like iron stuff from the old house to
the new house since we have a forge over
there good
idea thank you we'll see everybody
tomorrow byee okay thank you
byebye Som how we survived at first wa
hor zombies but was than to everybody
else's help huh yeah
let's more hopefully we at least didn't
hold them back maybe we helped a bit we
ate some food but you have to eat some
food right that's all we took
waight
[Music]
b w let's head
back
okay bye
thank you so
much happy we're able to
survive another day a few days in seven
days to
die well we'll be back again Tom
tomorrow you do well yes thank you I
really like just surviving going around
and Gathering things and making things
together everyone it's really fun
especially all together with everybody
too we did receive a lot from everyone
so maybe we did a lot more receiving
than giving this time but hopefully next
time it can be a bit more helpful yeah
so but we did give C some of the clo
fragments yeah I was happy I could help
she so
many
[Music]
yeah fun but maybe let's take a look at
our next stream coming up our next
stream we're going to be part
of bra
battle and this year organized by
m Channel well we become the fluffiest
and fuzziest and L part of s j bra we
have to solve some puzzle
problems some concerns and wores that
the real Min Senai has and hopefully we
don't get voted
out it's going to be really chaotic and
will there be a translation for
English
[Music]
unun we doing our best to keep up
you very fast we can keep we can keep up
and speak really fast so that we don't
get found
[Music]
[Applause]
by we'll do our best okay we're really
nervous but we'll do our B it's going to
be very
chaotic yeah and
wow we should look at our our schedule
still our schedule still where where's
the old
schedule just show the the new
schedule old schedule okay okay for the
rest of the
week
dad W two more early in the morning it
says at 4:00 p.m. but it's going to be
at 3 p.m. m p with the doggy pack we're
going to be playing some B guys
guys know we with the to with the doggy
pack a little bit yesterday with our big
1 million thank you so
much but this time I'm so excited
because we get to play fall guys again
together so well wi if you've never
played before please go and download for
guys it's a free it's a really really
fun apparently you need to update so
we'll make sure we update too let all
update you know not we're all ready to
go so I let's do my best just having fun
if if you fall well that's fall guys
yeah but after that at then 9 9 a.m. jst
or 500 p.m. PT we'll be playing more
seven days
today I hope we can get really nice and
strong to do more
questions kind of specialize you know oh
FL can do this you
know at least hopefully we can GA stuff
yeah yeah
baa kind of seems like nobody really is
that confident at farming or wants to do
farming so maybe that's something we can
do maybe you know we'll see how the is
yeah plant
yeah we
see new schedule new schedule
shall we take a look at
[Music]
it next week it's a big busy week
for but starting on
Monday morning follow by the
semifinal semifinal to 7 days to die and
on Tuesday we have our final day what
kind of Adventures wa for then
H and then
[Music]
morning but
Thursday it's been a while but we're
going to be playing all together with a
we're playing
FIA apparently there's been a lot of
updates yeah we haven't played in about
a year
right so uh hopefully it hasn't got too
scary but there'll be a bit of an
announcement so please look forward to
it too my I'm really excited for it I'm
excited for the
announcement and finally we have a
morning but early and Saturday morning
at 3:00 a.m. PT or 6:00 a.m. ET we have
a very special collab with
P we're really really excited for this I
know is really early in the morning so
if it's a little bit roughly understand
but it's been something that's been in
the works for a little while we did and
we're going to do our best what channel
is it on it's
on but you know if
like that's okay too so we the archive
we're going to do our best too and then
Sunday at 3:00 a.m. will P be there P
will be there on Sunday PT at 6: a.m. 18
no really early
morning going to be participating in an
animal Tower T we're going to be
stocking some animals and hopefully
we're the best animal stalkers it'll be
soon I don't want to lose to S by but I
don't know that they invited us what's
animal Tower what is animal Tower is it
animals and you stop them into a tower
into a tower and we want to build the
biggest tower because we want to win
I think that's about it for that one it
sounds like a lot of fun
[Music]
is it seems simple enough right right
yeah
so maybe both if you're half awake I
think being half awake is about good too
yeah yeah and then at 600 p.m. PT on
Sunday we have a super chat r
thank you so much for all your lovely
messages we're really looking forward to
be able to read them and you know just
kind of share our feelings some more so
thank you so
much thank you for everything we now
over 1 million subscribers here on
YouTube thank you thank you love you're
able to take a little bit of a moment to
be able to read all your comments
everything too and we we'll be sure to
take it as easy as we can this week like
we said you know it's a really busy big
week for us we have some very early
early mornings
too yeah so we're going to make sure
that we take care of our barkers as much
as we
can yeah
[Music]
and so much for all the fan art too
everything it really made us so happy so
I will continue to keep our eyes out for
them thank you Mom thank you and that's
our next week coming
up
right
wow best get ready for our
next thank you so
much I'm for the wol the AR today your
for is B pipe shotgun
B thank you
[Music]
oh