[Music]
n
oh
[Music]
I'm trying I
it's Journey away years
[Music]
no no it's not it's not Halloween you
feel it's well this is uh this is
different because this time we are
releasing our very first fle original
song
[Applause]
[Music]
n
la
[Music]
oh
I'm I'm trying I can't
[Music]
all right guys want to fight
hello we back we're so bad all five of
us in the beginning let's
go y pumkins are a little loud oh yeah
yeah yeah I I made us a lot of chickens
but I needed it for the arrows and for
food oh true true ah I want to give you
guys a tour of what happened but okay
yeah Kar did a lot of [\h__\h] apparently
show us the chicken pan it's kind of
loud in here oh get out of there get out
of there save yourself they're
aggressive chickens they eat people okay
fre them free them I'm free how could
you do that to them chicken chicken C
now in where there were villagers before
uh feel free to you know deal with the
chickens however you
like kill them
all hello you in the
water hello that scared
me wait come with me
Kuba as soon as my mouth starts working
I'll be right there I ordered a new one
it's coming today I made this house it's
beautiful Airbnb for future villagers
o and
yellow wait it's really pretty in
here come Callie come Callie there's
even I'm not going to miss out look my
there's so many pandas there's like
what's in the bows I think it's
oatmeal it looks like the Yum
y Grandma's oatmeal don't say it
cool oh hello You Like It Amy what you
like coffee with your
oatmeal ooh I already have some I got my
morning shot o so basically you can see
we have beds now because we found a
sheep and we got sheep it's one sheep a
single she a single sheep if you need
can it it like and yet
Tois we have about eight pandas mitosis
it's important we have to and each one
of the blood line what it's
called can we Harvest our meat G no no
asking can we I'm not asking permission
I'm just saying can we Harvest
is no yeah in terms of food I got bread
now as well feel free to can I harvest
these now yeah of course the chest has
seeds if you need more if you want to
throw some away wait smart you put it
above yeah I hope I hope I W did you
think of that or did your chat think of
that I thought of it I'm a
genius whoa smart your do your neck hurt
from holding on to that massive
brain seriously though true true though
wow wow wow
okay and then if you remember the old I
mean it's still the same myth house but
it has our colors now in terms of beds
and some more
decoration oh I want to see did you put
my bed next time Big Sleep No you don't
want why did you no we no fine fine I
understand no it's fine a corner pillows
yeah I got wait I got double pillows
double pillows oh no I'm fine with this
I'm good with this why you seeing double
pillows
[Music]
nothing what else do you make
k a if you go let's let's go behind the
um Chicken House Co I have something to
show you I can't believe my little
Merchant pen became a chicken
house the chicken poop cop yeah we have
po portal now I didn't go in yet but we
can go in today cool don't we need some
golden stuff though good thing we saved
all that gold
check out that chest over here dang it
you already did it that's fine all right
that's okay we're fine we're fine and
more CH there's also the Eyes of Ender
that we need yeah turns out we already
had enough of the Enderman eyes so I
just made pearls I made some eyes out of
them so yeah yeah yeah yeah look good
that's like the most important stuff I
did and some decorating here and
there yay very nice even' very busy nice
rain is popping off rain is always super
loud in Minecraft oh my uh shaders
aren't hold on a sec let me get my
shaders popping off cuz I got shaders
Lads oh shaders
shaders oh do you want to know why you
are a genius without knowing
it the I was like I was mining my own
business yeah yeah yeah um and then a
creeper popped up a creeper spawned
right and because you're so close to it
automatically it it goes off right I
stepped back but it went like and then
bam and it exploded in this whole
construction that you made and I was
like yo bit it's going to all be
destroyed but the water took the
explosion and therefore nothing exploded
science okay it's as if it was on
purpose that put that water there
totally she's a scientist and she
doesn't
scientist all right I'll do a little
more organizing I'm I'm kind of stuck
what the hell I can't get out how kind
of to organize all our for us it's very
cool of her that she does that you're
doing that help yeah take take this take
all of this then thank you oh my God
yeah you're welcome please I can't click
on some of these things how does it feel
I live to please why can I
not is it the when are we go into the ne
I want to go in I'm
stop we need we need armor and shut the
up
that's wait what what do we do what
what's going on turn the weather down
the weather to shut it pad oh no is
somebody stuck oh
no wait get a is there a trap door oh is
she fine opening it leave it
open ah no I I think wait am I like
crouching but I keep on pressing it to
like release it you got to come out this
way somehow I legit cannot move that way
oh thank you thank you Freedom Yoo she
free and in terms of armor um we don't
have that much iron uh I don't think
we're going to be that lucky in terms of
arm want to dismiss we have a bunch of
we have a ton of emeralds um oh we have
a block of iron why not crack that bad
boy open here I'll crack that I don't
think we'll all have full iron armor but
we can we can like partially get dressed
up mhm sounds good to me is it still
better to have gold we don't have iron
but we have
diamonds
Diamond putting on the diamond armor now
and then dying in the
ne true that's going to be me don't give
me
any 27 diamonds from a block of diamond
here so now we have over 64 we have 68
diamonds not bad lads not bad oh okay 68
diamonds all right all right yeah 68
diamonds sick mhm wait how many 68
diamonds holy moly yeah we have a fat
stack of them but I mean I think it is a
good idea to save for later we're
rich ni money money can't believe we
have more diamonds than
iron ah yeah that really doesn't seem
it's because I I used uh most of the
iron to make an
anvil oh do it and tools we've been
making a lot of iron pickaxes that's
true okay those are necess those are
very necessary they are they
are but yeah that's how it's been going
so um the the thing is we have already
enough enough Ender eye thingies uh to
open our portal so we're not going into
The Nether to really get Enderman or
Blaze anything we already have all all
we need but we're just going in for fun
and we can get more NE Wards and blaze
rods because with that we could make
more potions that would definitely help
us wait what if we die though are we
risking losing
resources uh well if we die there we
drop the stuff unless we die to magma
true just don't die in the magma just
don't die don't die bring Stone oh
should we bring some should we bring
some gold so we can trade with the
pigments IDE I was thinking that might
be fun but I looked at a sheet of like
percentage what you can get and it's
like going to be such a waste we could
use the gold for golden apples that
would make more sense in the end but we
can take a some we have a lot that's
what I was thinking wowo let's just not
take all oh I made the wowo yeah that's
pretty cool that's cool K that's cool I
want to enchant something oh that was
the bow that was enchant Ed but broken
but I fixed it with the Anvil yeah and
then I named it
wowo
w we're going to need feather falling
for
later if you die in the nether you
should receive a punishment oh that's a
good point a punishment can I make with
one of these for endangering the team's
resources sounds good what is said
punishment we should make um we should
make a diamond sword with a power three
enchantment oh go okay okay oh yeah we
can share it we I think we should at
least bring a bow and some arrows so
that I can take care of guests I got
good bow and I got some arrows I have an
idea use INF arrows if you die in the
nether you have to be slain on stream
for Shame by the Power Three diamond
sword that's a that's a good idea you
die double you die in the nether you die
in real life exactly in Minecraft SL for
shame Minecraft is real life in front of
everyone here people are saying that
power is for bow what if we just did an
Infinity enchantment on one of the bows
instead do do we have Infinity we do we
have Infinity we have levels that's the
question that's excellent question you
can't make a diamond bow right that's
not possible you can only do
a does sound nice though cuz we have
limited bow or Arrow resources yeah why
not both yeah why not power and digging
will get um well it would take a while
anyways to level up like a villager
right it had the right stuff yeah cuz
all could sweeping Edge though is
sleeping Edge us a
sword it gives it like kind of an AOE a
little bit like a bigger bigger swoop
and and there's loot too if if you want
get more stuff with always go for it go
for
it everybody's listening
to you guys silence nothing nothing
listening to you where where's the music
box go bra I moved the music box to the
house because people told me that
parrots would dance to the music and
then I tested it out but it didn't
actually work even when I removed them
from the bed I want to see no no I think
it's like a newer version Oh wait now
it's dancing it didn't like the track
it's
Dancing Yeah okay where'd he go oh he's
outside oh my God oh my God oh my God oh
my God oh your own one oh yeah like let
them dance bring him into the
disco dance
bird
cute yours doesn't want to dance what's
wrong with him do
something po with a stick do
it maybe maybe this tune is just not it
maybe tun to enhance different tun
Boogie birdie Boogie oh
yeah he's doing the cre the Bodacious B
Infinity arrows he wants to escape he
wants out so bad oh God okay a I'm
excited not quite his
Tempo not quite his Tempo let's try it
out oh oh oh oh it does shoot Infinity
let's go let's go Infinity arrows
audacious bow no should we take that
into The Nether though cuz we need that
for the end what if we lose it yeah
maybe not we'll store it in the weapons
chest weapons yeah maybe at least bring
one bow and a couple of arrows though
for the gas I I got one bow and a couple
of arrows okay okay I think I think we
should at least have like Stone
weapons at the very least
definitely what about what about should
we do one piece of diamond armor per
person maybe maybe maybe I mean as long
as you don't fall to Lava it should be
fine cuz it'll just drop whatever you're
wearing and stuff
so so I got gold helmets for everybody
so let's do I don't know maybe the chest
piece for yeah chest piece would be good
good
idea okay okay I'll just make some Stone
I'll make a ton of good weapons for the
end okay I'm going to make the chest
plates for all five of us so don't don't
take diamonds or so Okie
doie right before the stream I I I ate
uh some stuff that was sitting out for
like uh maybe almost 12 hours
now you do
that what what was it
snack oh no what was just it was just a
single rice cake oh that's probably fine
but I don't do that like meat or
whatever CH how do you say it
toi to oh
to oh okay it's fun okay as long as it
was meat or dairy right uh I had meat in
the you in
the K you're going to be fine you'll be
fine wait Kelly Kelly wait Kelly huh
Kelly
here than you I won't die I
promise I might die I might die I'll do
I'll do my best I'll do my
best okay everybody's got a p I guess I
should make
some rainbow fren call it it's a big
ring okay the music is kind of loud
now should make some pickaxes too oh
yeah mhm I have them iron one I still
think iron pickaxes are for the best I
think I think we for normal mining we
can use the stone ones but if there's
like a resource like gold or something
we can use the iron one mm good
[Music]
idea ni everybody gets a stone pick you
get a stone pickaxe you get a stone pick
or I have have then we should have
enough food
oh this is so exciting is it it's like
we're going on the field trip y oh my
God for school field trip so what we
need from the nether by the
way just going in adventuring yeah
normally there would be things that we
could use uh from there but we already
have everything thanks to mining
endlessly so we're just going in for fun
for field Tri like increased chance of
diamonds or no no diamonds but we can
get more
gold and make golden apples and we can
get never wart which is a little little
plant which out of that we could make
portions to help us resist the dragon
that we're going to fight uh good and if
we find we can get blaze rods what if we
make a portal inside the nether does it
go anywhere like if oh oh usually yeah
you make one and it goes further but I
wonder I feel like they would have
blocked it for this mode I'm not sure
I'm going to bring some obsidian to it
experiment okay there's a fire charges
in in the cool things chest if you need
the fire charge for cool things chest
I'm sorry I didn't hear about thisan
chest it's also in the coolsan is it
right here
[Music]
oh and the fire oh we don't have we
don't have sugar cane do we no fish no
we don't ow ow something we
need cuz if we had sugar we could make a
lot of pumpkin pies that would be nice
food yum yum yum yum nice idea wait fire
charge is that what I'm getting uh yeah
yeah yeah yeah to zap it on it's only
one time used though okay okay I brought
an extra just
case iron more iron oh there's a fish in
here fishy fishy fishy fishy fishy
fishy we don't need more chests we have
so many materials I guess we can't we
shouldn't do that this is why your boy
wanted a trash can
listen we just have so many things oh
there's a lot of stuff in
here sure you organize it properly just
because we have a chance to die I think
going in with half armor is going to be
okay we can help each other to not die
protect each other get that gold home
W yeah so when that big floating
jellyfish man dude guy comes like
shooting balls at you and stuff like
that you're supposed to hit it back with
a sword or do you slay him with a bow
and AR you can hit it oh there's another
bow here with infinity bous bow oh yeah
I put that in there that's that's the
for the that's okay okay yeah it's just
I'm making a bunch of weapons to get us
ready for the end so we'll use it then
just the Bodacious bow yeah someone can
use the Bodacious bow when we fight the
Ender Dragon what does that mean bod go
oh have you should we at least make a
shield oh the pant the Panda's free the
panda it's a new panda
panda new we should at least make a
shield we can oh yeah sh is important
make Shields oh yeah okay somebody it's
like it's just one iron purse so it
should be
okay hi Panda what are you doing I'll
make shield for everyone okay
Tas by the way K Bodacious means nice
body Bodacious Bonk all right I should
know what it means yeah I just said
that here's your
Shield thank
you oh thank you thank Goomba here's
your I looked it up it can be excellent
admirable or attractive yeah I guess it
is oh yeah nice Dictionary look up there
a man here's your Shield I see my pen
before I go make a baby make a baby then
wow a bab baby why you're double
shielding oh
oh it's like the anime with thei girl oh
I didn't know you could do that damn
let's go okay having murderous try
harder make
eaten taking our
resources we could use that for
something but the pan for eating them
the bamboo cute must is this to murder
what it's just a b bamboo look how cute
they are
Banda I love Banda it's for morale boost
all right we need that we're going into
The Nether to die we ride on their backs
like what if could we ride on them into
the nether like that would be cool me me
no no they're just cute that's they're
purpose died for a second let's go
hooray come on OB I'm going to make one
more Stone
Pickaxe mine has also been dying
H OBS what's wrong with you stop is it
OBS or YouTube side OBS is drunk for me
right now that was OBS but often it's
also
YouTube need some sticks then we can go
I'm pretty
sure guess what I'm making after the
stream wait guess what I'm making what
do you I'm going to make a chocolate
chip Skillet cookie
yeah it sounds kind of yum wait what's
what's the skillet part that sounds like
a like a steak thing it's like a it's
like a a like a cast iron thick heavy
bottom pan pot thing and you put yeah
put the cookie dough in and bake it that
way and then you put ice cream on
top we're invited
right no it's single serving
sorry that's messed up girl you can't
just tell us about it and say you can't
have any come on I putting the dough in
so that it fills up the whole Skillet
like a pancake or yeah oh so it's like
it's like a cake kind of what you're
making yeah little bit yummy damn yeah
that's a good idea give me the recipe
later please please please please please
yeah do I need a skillet for it some my
dad um I guess it would be easier that
way yeah okay time to buy a skillet you
just use a cake pan probably oh yeah
yeah a cake pan a small one though if
you want singles in the oven or a cake
pan on the OV oven it's in the oven okay
yeah there's a restaurant that serves it
it's called they make they call it
Pazuki
Pazuki pazooki what they serve Skillet
cookies
yeah for what the hellc
me free
string string string
oh the the chest is full that's a lot of
stuff that means your boy isn't doing a
job okay hold on a sec call my brain was
like breaking yesterday when you were
gone and I had to sort things on my own
man that was rough rough rough rough
that's all right it's just cuz you have
the configuration down like I do if you
figure out where it all goes it' be fine
fermented spider
eye Mory handles it
though yeah I'm I'm useful it's just
just not super entertaining is
the sorry everyone watching my POV I I
don't really not really doing much here
besides organizing okay does everybody
have enough food by the way there's
still like a watermelon and bread in the
food chest if you want yeah I got the
food okay you're having a great time I'm
happy take it take it take it take the
food take the food I'm sure chat will
watch paint dry with with us if it comes
down to it that'll be inter
interesting stream watching paint yeah
they would especially watch it if it was
drying on your
body good point maybe it's a good guys
we we got we got a situation
situation where' everybody go what oh
no what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] what oh no excuse me what the what
why is there two enemies anyway
I led out I'm
scared damn that is like last phase
Pillager uh dare attack damn that was a
super unlucky why there so many still
here're still
here should I log out it's okay there's
only like four of them left what the cuz
they're scared they're [\h__\h] what they
came all in one damn what that's why
they attack in a group cuz they're
cowards got one crazy those those
traps did you see those traps yo on the
ground TR traps yeah the traps that the
the Pillager was like setting up while
the Vex that was insane oh really that
was very I saw that in Full full
4K I got caught by one come here buddy
smells like chicken in here get
him as there's chicken in here get down
here coward oh sorry ow please I feel
like we're hitting each other more than
more than we're hitting
the I think so yeah I think so seems
peaceful great job guys crazy nice one
ready smelly um I'm ready think ready
the shower let's go oh I need to grab
girl has to get her 1,000th block no it
was purposeful no going to force you
helmets with the golden helmets oh
they're in the chest behind the house
house here here here
here at the portal
okay I think my mouse is dying but I
can't find the charging oh that's why I
only only use cable
tools I used to but I have a lot of eggs
here we go those mouses mes mice we're a
little too
heavy wonder I must release my where is
it see
nothing oh well if I die my mouse
dies let's go M let's
go okay okay so uh goal would be to um
find a Pillager just for fun did anybody
bring gold for that a villager I mean h
not a villager uh uh a piglin
piglin did anybody bring some gold just
just a little bit no no okay I'll bring
some some hold on I'm duplicating my
friends I'm rening space in time just
I'm just going to bring dropping my bird
off a little bit of gold just for fun
okay um I feel like I'm playing
dollhouse the other goal would be
finding one of those Forest play
sometime gu so Forest it has the ne wart
for
potions and if find a fortress that
would be
sick actually hey I found the corn yeah
what wait don't J with me man no I'll
I'll play Barbie dolls with you girl
anytime let's do it Barbies
Barbie I love dollhous my weapons are
kind of dying I kind of need to fix it
can I fix it move my friends around a
little
more damn it there we
go
moved one second I'm ready to
bring yeah I brought like 20 I don't
know okay uh building should we bring
bring some building blocks to make paths
perhaps I think we'll be able I I have
some
Cobblestone okay I got some End Stone
too like one one stack yeah yeah I was
scared for a second cuz it was like it
went so quiet for like 5 seconds I was
like did Discord
die no it it went super quiet for like 5
seconds on my end I thought this died
even like Minecraft sound died I was
like huh but no it's just me I'm I'm
just being scared of my
own is coming we're here okay and I
think we can go I can bring one of the
okay I'm ready come to the ne portal if
you're
ready giv me energy ready to go wait
before we go in we should take a picture
in front of it sure if you say so sounds
good to me stand in line whose bird is
this whose birds are these they're going
to get in and yours and mine I thought I
thought you was going to sit in the
house we got to get that cat out hold on
we'll get
it guys I feel like we're going to get Z
sority photo
girl did you kill it where'd it go I
don't know where the cat went
but my bird get your bird where is he
he's in front of the portal he's going
to go in by himself oh no he knows not
what horror getting photo bed don't lose
the bird in the never that would be so
sad hello have you seen my bird he's
about this tall and green it was on your
shoulder last time saw I'm jumping no
the other bird the green one oh I jumped
it's on your shoulder it's
on guys I'm
scared come on come on come over sorry
sorry struck by lightning with the
bird hold your hand if you get struck by
lightning while you're is on your
shoulder do you guess cooked chicken as
the item that's messed up like
Aero like the Birdman or something like
that your origin story is you were
struck by lightning when you had a par
your and then you turn into the parrot
Man
scary okay Darkwing Duck yeah something
the M man thank you guys hry for the
wait whose cat is that should let them
sit so they don't follow you into
another oh [\h__\h] maybe
mine yeah it's your cat in the boat but
that's the bird boat so okay it's
sitting okay all right let's go good she
okay
cheese hello hello wow leave it to you
cameraman leave it to you I got it okay
then what shall await us on the other
side we shall see it's so
dramatic cool let's go the donkey's for
me careful you don't fall there's a lot
of
lava the donkey went in let's go
bringing
alive he burns alive wait is he really
Burning Alive hold on a no put me back
don't worry guys he's gone he's gone I'm
tripping what is this portal spawn
that's messed up wait where are you guys
are up there what how'd you get up
there what hold on also it's super
dark gas who's floating hold on I'm am I
stuck in the port wait let me try this
again what is the ser so
borked hold on no please please let me
go let me join my friends okay I think
we're good oh there's all it's all lava
actually let me turn off
that's the hole Kelly I'm here I made it
I was just tripping count you had some
weird mushrooms stew we're fine better
yeah be careful of your paths you may
not be seeing a hole but there may very
well be a hole dang should have brought
block anybody bring a ton of blocks just
go back and get a big stack I'll get a
stack two stacks okay
some oh there's Soul Sand over
there we need those for uh time to be
useful let's go nether W growing
let's yeah we have a lot of Soul Sand
but more NE W would be nice and finding
a fortress would be sick wait we got
nether w a little bit yeah oh then we
can totally grow them already we should
have we should have planted them on the
soul standand oh we can duplicate them
okay well then don't don't take away the
things the few things that we
have okay now we're good let's keep an
eye out for the Fortress oh wait uh
coordination Cords Cord it'll slow you
down what are the cords okay I took a
screenshot of the
cords okay wait one two three four this
is not a very nice SP we're missing I
brought blocks I'm here I brought blocks
I think she went back yeah okay I'm here
should we go that way to the next
platform fa wait I think I found
something what what it's a
fortress already are you sure it's a
fortress it's yeah you see to op zoom in
with optify it's bricks it's
Fortress wait where
over there over over where I'm
looking I should go this way see that
far let's go it's a [\h__\h] right over
there okay well now we have a goal
that's good yeah we need to make a path
over there let's go I'm at the
Builder the blocks give you if you need
more blocks let me know I've got a ton
let me turn I hear a Gest I'm scared
it's okay it will be fine need more
block fall off here if you give them to
me oh yeah sure here you go oh I hear
him he sounds
hungry thank you he does sound hungry
that's okay it's right over there it's
right over there it's totally going to
see it's okay no wor it's fine it's fine
you got to also remember um how we got
here I have the cords no worries and I
mean the Fortress is so close I think
we're going to find our way back fine
we're so
lucky so lucky man but I'm glad so
scared oh why did I not okay I didn't
get any of those okay making the path a
little
longer or a little wider wait if you dig
another what is this red rock with a
stone pickaxe do you get them or do you
need iron you should get it it's just
like dirt basically it's this this
realm's dirt in it's Ence yay Ena does
this remind you of something
recently you and being here I feel like
I had more gear last time okay hold on
is let me go
past okay did YouTube die again for
anyone that's why I made I made it
really
bad we'll fix it when we come
back word on is
YouTube you're not fine falling down
like that on the one block path where
the other side is lava
o you're not fine you scare
me no my God it's fine it's fine it's
fine no worries no worries mama I didn't
mean to put this down
m
m flash to the
it is a fortress no way yeah lucky us
that's nutty looks like the eye of
Sauron goodbye load of the Rings watch
along let's go oh full extended oh oh
yeah I've done that actually before with
members oh well remember when I got sick
in Japan when we were doing our 3D watch
along 3D uh debuse I uh when I got sick
I did uh Lord of the Rings extended
version watch alongs with my memb
one after another oh my
God okay I'm out 4 hours yeah the good
stuff make a little
stairway make a little stairway can you
catch me I'm actively making it worse
okay hold on what can you catch me oh
you made
stairs that's a lot less Roman in Fe to
tonight oh let's go fun I helped I did
one BL rotk
Ronin RK stands
for oh how do we get into the we have to
go up dig in yeah I think we're got to
go
up it's an M from
Moy oh
mo can't go in through the
bottom I I think we'll have to go up
like this is just like the the pillars
of it yeah the path seems to be above
and then the main part seems to be
further uh over at the end of of that
that those pillars there all right well
if everybody mines some uh nether rock
then we could just like boost ourselves
individually you know what I mean sure
oh yeah like a big like elevator yeah
okay I didn't bring a normal pickaxe I
only have the diamond pickaxe just in
case so okay well we I'll leave it to
you girls to to
mine yeah I think I have enough oh dear
easy I'll start and make a bridge
careful there's like lava right
everywhere yeah there's a lot there's
aot
everywhere yeah careful there's lava um
all over the
place out the we we W
everywhere I think I saw her
blind I saw her blind no
really right over there her blind's
going to kill us her blind
oh we can get some levels from
this oh you ah you making like a a
circle circle stair great like a little
platform for you guys to uh build up to
about 40 blocks or something like that
okay can somebody also give me blocks
done okay I've got quite a big stack
I'll give you 64 Q thank
you do you want me to go in and Scout it
out yeah we need a
scout but then if we want to go back
already went up just I guess we get rid
of the blocks we made up I
guess
uh yeah that's how the elevator works
just mine our way down again mine your
way down don't worry if you have to use
a diamond pickaxe to get down it's fine
no no no I I'll use my
hands there some dudes okay they're
friendly we have gold they respect us
why not just build
stairs right somebody says make a spiral
staircase yeah right thought that that's
what she was making I'm already up here
so you know I'm good all right all go
then right beneath this is kind of scary
doesn't it I hope this is enough blocks
yeah it should be fine wait race you
race you race you oh God it's so
bright got a head that's not fair okay I
got 30 uh here oh yeah thank you you
just okay just should be real careful
okay making me nervous here with the
think they all went back to me wait
let's let's did you can drop the whole
stack yeah wait wait wait let's go over
here then I'll give it to you oh so this
is a fortress
T oh never I like the sound of the
stairs oh wait what are these nether so
do it is that what you're supposed to do
here yeah we taking it over be careful
though very dangerous very dangerous
dangerous can we fight them with stone
swords do you think we'll win
totally if we find a blaze
spawner it's going to be a little bit
rough we rush it we don't give it a
chance to spawn and then we rush it yeah
yeah
yeah sounds good team we just need a few
blaze rods just for fun we don't need to
you know make the whole spawner our
ours just you know oh yeah if we if we
end up getting wither like two more
wither heads we can spawn the
wither oh a side
quest I don't know about this ooh more
poisonous mushrooms for poison mushrooms
oh
sorry where you going dude sorry left or
straight uh girls Democratic vote please
left or straight straight cuz it's are
we going to get lost uh uh no I have
some torches oh me too me too you should
put torches like on one side each so
then you know which way to go
back oh yeah good idea going in a
straight line I think it'll be okay okay
that's a good way to Mark oh but
actually straight is a dead end we could
go oh then never mind left is good okay
come on come on we're going this way
it's so quiet in here so
far did you just say
that oh my God bye Kiara a big one
there's some stairs here I want to go
up W what what possibly could go wrong
it's so quiet here this is a cal before
the photo photo
photo where is every
wither where the
skeletons I
like this is maybe also dead end do they
have like chests and stuff here to raid
uh yeah they should have some chests
yeah oh sorry dead
end my loot Goblin oh
why run back inside run back
inside Retreat Retreat Retreat par it
just yeah you got it
gon
anyway go tell them to be [\h__\h] I want to
hit the thingies don't risk it for the
skillet
biscuit it won't kill you hold I'm just
trying to hit it wait wait wait yeah do
it do it girl where is
he dang it it should die yeah let's go
go yeah fall yeah you suck yeah yeah
yeah we got
it okay back
down and then this this
way yay it's so empty but the bricks are
so nice I want to take some bricks
home somebody else choose the path but
this seems to be a good sect
this stairs straight oh there's a thing
there a spawner there's a spawner there
oh nice rush rush a rush it's
scary what IDE Shield if you block the
fire it should be fine you just put a
torch oh just put a torch on it Go Ena
go goo go am go
Callie me oh he's very strong oh he's
very strong oh he does not like me sorry
yeah B the potato
fries it spawned behind you too okay got
it kill him kill
him nice well done ladies that was easy
did he drop something do we need
to oh nice uh I mean if we find more we
can want more right oh or we can build
this thing where it's like you can like
block the line of set and just hit it
from like down here M that would be nice
if we knew how to do it do you know how
to do it if anybody has the torch you
can put it back on
now nice on fire nice hit oh I got a
blaze rod too be nice from an exp I
guess you need more rods for the eyes of
end we already have all the Eyes of
Ender chat that we need
actually we're just doing this we take
the Ender Dragon now I don't have
I mean we could
but maybe a little more diamonds yeah a
little bit we should go in with a bit
more armor at
least I mean we have enough Diamond to
make armor
for I think so everyone don't you
think we have like a stack plus a more
no we got to drag it out at least one
more day come
on yeah torch guys torch oh you pushed
him into me
sorry it wasn't
me okay
okay today is never day and the next
time we can do anything have one
so and I used all mine oh I have oh okay
okay oh yeah yeah you listening yeah
kill the
end oh but I I thought we want to fight
more oh yeah sure we get what do we need
do we even eat it just it's just you
know for fun
it's okay we finish Minecraft Minecraft
and then we just find a different
different thing to all do together
fine am I using the wrong oh sorry this
is the wrong I'm such an idiot I don't
know how to Y I was doing basically the
more of these things we have the more
potions we can make like OverWatch we
will not be playing OverWatch together
I'm sorry OverWatch isn't bad no I don't
think it's bad either it's just not what
I want to play play with you
guys why
not why not OverWatch hey is this what
you need this stuff ooh skin tags wait
where are you too are you where are you
and some red stuff turn I'm a sniper
where did everybody I'll Just Fall o
free lav oh free lava oh this good yeah
pick them up good good someone's going
to have to this out of here cuz I got no
clue where we
are but where are the skeletons is it
like bugged why are no skeletons this
random random spawns in the Fortress a
dead in my chat Kara oh speaking of the
Dead a lot yum I should have brought
milk damn it why did we forget about the
milk de be enough oh oh oh no oh no good
oh no oh no I'm going to die first one
that dies get spanked by the diamond
sword goodbye what happened
bye up my look like that where are you
uh I was a little I I was a little bit
from dying oh there's another
one yeah milk would have been good oh
and there's a place too I think I might
die that's not great did you find my
stuff yeah I picked it up okay good
bring some maybe retreating is a good
idea
okay yeah those those the the curses
they put on you they're no
joke yeah I was really surprised by that
I can't believe I survived you behind
you you behind
behind
ow I just want to get the chest o nice
chest
please
armor nice what's in there don't worry
all my all my moves are calculated got
it all ho it is dark I do wish I had a
torch oh there's more nether or here
blocks I had to build my way up I got to
build my way up
again uh if you follow the path uh I
started building oh I guess you don't
have any
blocks I'll be fine I'm bringing
blocks but no gold armor sorry I have no
shovel a ladder we're going to make
ladder now
not in there okay here we scary found
the entrance you guys hello where
where's everyone my I was looking at
that chest over there byv but there's
nothing in there oh really okay yeah let
where's everyone else wait won can you
backtrack okay you guys come back come
out of the chest area Okay is he is he
going to attack me hello the entrance is
here but there's also this unexplored uh
part here go deeper we go deeper we wa
fora oh it's just more chest it looks
like oh is he going to attack me more
chest to be looted iron horse
armor golden we do have a lot of horses
a quite a few to ride into battle
valiantly I'm standing at the
staircase scared he won't does he not
care about the gold tell me tell me chat
tell me chat okay all right I got
everything in the
chest okay we're going back up let's go
get
Kara
k w you're going to get me yeah you're
alone I thought I was just going to go
back to
you you're actually coming back do we
need anything here I feel like we got
everything why you want to leave
already what I thought we were going to
do the Ender Dragon no we're not the end
no
not no today's never day don't end our
beautiful time together so
early wait what if we made like a like a
like an arena and we have one each one
of us has to fight the Ender Dragon one
at a time o that could be fun a true and
we
watch watch you just watch and die yeah
and back seat each other damn oh what my
BL sounds fine oh uh
I think it's a good idea
my oh boy I might indeed need help to
get back up we're going a
Coliseum Coliseum sounds good
huh yeah I do Coliseum you guys think
you could beat a bear in a fist fight
speaking of Coliseum no no no
no can you there was there was a thing
like that like a game called M noi it's
like you can get a title for beating up
a be when you're 10 years old wait I
think there's that in in Witcher as well
you you fish fight a
bear can you start bu oh you don't have
any blocks I I have a few a few I was
going to say you can start building
stairs up oh my God there's a guest over
there guys I don't feel very spe spe up
got to goon I'm trying
Ena you are the
distraction I think
it's okay okay go go go go go go go go
okay maybe I can help build two maybe
not there's two're almost there we're
almost there
guest me speed
speed we here careful
girls I should have bought like a slime
block or something so I can just jump
down down okay emergency B
oh I do have
votes I don't know if I can do it with
this ping though now we just stairs why
why why do I not have problems with the
Ping I'm so
lucky okay what if you're coming back
then I guess hell oh hi we're here we're
right up here okay let me see hold
on you can get in the boat and dive off
the edge oh all right that's thing
okay can we
tandem what does that mean uh two oh
like a tandem bicycle oo girls I got to
go like AFK for a second but I'm just
going to log out for a moment wait okay
I'll I'll beb don't be gone too long I
miss
you
okay W okay all right I got a I got two
boats
nice are we are we just going to boat it
let's try it let's try it let's try it
boat yeah that could be good get cie
okay if you say so okay aim do not aim
for the lava I wait am I in the front oh
[\h__\h] dri I can't see I can't see the
bottom I can't see I can't see I'm going
my Houston you're clear clear W clear
for
launch let's PR here we go oh nice it
works
wellow we lived I I mean I knew it you
didn't doubt me for a second did you of
course not I was just joking jokes jokes
jokes oh
[Music]
W did it work I'm just going to put them
oh oh
oopsies okay let me get out of the
way I have Mario Kart DK Mountain on
Loop I'm losing my mind nice in the
background
yeah it is pretty hype though I have
your battle
Tunes battle jungle
music so that we're here and kar's AFK
we can uh test by putting um a obsidian
portal oh where are we going um where's
it to the
unknown wait that's what you titled your
stream isn't it title drop title drop
title
drop but if it's one block on the other
side then what if we spawn nowhere do
you need a
pickax well then I have KS Diamond one
I'll just use
it
oo I'm
[Music]
telling don't be a title tail girl this
is tall
enough uh
is it three it's okay it's it's going to
be a 3X3 it'll be
fine okay hopefully this works those are
weird noises who wants to go in
first careful you might spawn into
nowhere wait maybe you should leave your
stuff
first I'm not going anywhere oh I guess
it doesn't work oh yes it does oh wait
wait no just us just wavy and then it
just stays like that forever oh oh wait
what a
ooh oh I'm wibbly wobbly where did you
guys go I'm going to Bar I'm going to
barf I don't know everything
I'm god I think I'm in
heaven do you guys have any blocks um
there is nothing I just is this why they
call it Sky Block I I spawned underneath
the portal and there's like a little
obsidian platform that catches you
there's nothing else I have some blocks
I'm getting bar give you some blocks I
can't really go anywhere okay uh just
chill any it's walk
off I have to walk off no no don't don't
don't walk off don't walk off this is
really wobbly um let me see if there's
so shift you made up a portal oh uh
don't come in okay be a good idea to
come in it's just really hard to place a
block right
now did you did you did you make a
portal and you were like in the middle
of the sky oh middle this guy right now
oh that's fun that's so
fun can you can you get up do you have
do you have blocks I don't have any
blocks I got some I got some here drop
it on the other
side what's happening I want to
see hey can I come through come through
okay okay we have enough enough platform
this to stay okay all right I'll just
mind some bottom oh mind Saving Private
or what's happening here I've got five
blocks to help you oh my God wait
so um what's the plan to be here what's
the purpose of being here I'm trapped
restart the
trapped restart restarting the
challenge we're trying to save lot
oh no what if I what do you mean she's
there what how is she she's below us why
wait where are you at there's a obsidian
platform underneath the come come on
come you see this here what what does it
mean you see
that okay I just made another portal at
the bottom never
mind what okay so we go back into
the I'm already on the other side there
was enough blocks to just make another
portal all right you guys go
first okay I'm coming in
[Music]
hello well that was that was good for
science right so we know that if you
make another portal you'll be again in
the middle of the sky the middle of the
sky here I can give you back your stuff
hold on I'm going to oh break this
portal so we don't go into it again mhm
yeah why not what a strange silly thing
all right here you go
this and this one oh I didn't pick it
[Music]
up I guess that's our portal over there
I think you have the chest plate
now it's mine now two chest plates no
what do you need two chest plates for
why not one for Monday and one for
Tuesday oh a all right so are we going
back in cuz we I think we pretty much
got
everything well I mean yeah we can go
back but I'm not letting you go that
easily can I make all my friends really
wide wait what if we dro the dragon into
a portal like what we just did and then
he falls into the sky out
yeah kind ofs can you build another
portal in the end I don't think I don't
think
so but then we can break the portal and
he's stuck in the void
forever oh you can't build a portal
though okay interesting is that what
Chad says yeah the dragon kind of flies
though so it won't have fall
damage not a hold H nether doesn't work
in the end a a that's too bad okay then
let's go back to the to to the real
portal and we can still do some stuff
though we don't have to end it here that
would be so sad we still have to collect
materials
or weapons and that kind of stff yeah we
need M Diamond let's just endlessly mine
because we need some diamonds and we
need maybe if we find a villager that
would be nice and I me if you want
something to do you could build
PPP more organizing chat doesn't that
sound fun do do we need that well we
need nothing really but um you know make
a bunch of cool this time I'm going to
be a weapon Smith what I can build
together yeah yeah hell yeah
all right I'll look up a guy on your
head sounds fun small child don't come
we trade gold I we didn't do it but we
could it's not these though the it's
like the
normal
L welcome home everybody my not yet hold
on are the pandas okay yeah did they did
they uh perish so sadly
they're okay dang it they're starting to
get so many you might need to expand
their
territory or call some of them I thought
you ex execute idea if you need me to
execute your pandas I'll do it for you
why are you so eager oh yeah I there's
one loose Panda that's not part of the
pack
right what I'm going to put this
horse armor on a can I put on a donkey
I don't think so sadly unfortunately
where did all the horses go oh there's
one horse all right I shall do some
organizing wait that's a
donkey so that we can mine more CL
enough wait did all the horses
die I gu there's a skeleton
one hey yeah we had like so many zombie
hores I know that one is like
underr oh a broken music disc why is it
broken
why um I'm stuck in the right guys
watching a zombie spawner farm
tutorial let's go can I help I want to
help me to work yeah we can help let me
absorb information first absorb it yes
okay learn and then do the on way ton of
dirt blocks by the way if you want to
expand the forest I don't really think
expanding the forest has much of a
meaning now though but I mean we can
still farm and get more trees oh we can
get more apples actually from the trees
oh yes yes apples would be nice
really you can take that as one of your
side quests cool okay side quest yay
nice nice nice also there's a ton of
coal in this fuel chest over here kind
of
coal yeah all right expand the forest
then I'm going to gra grab some dirt and
then we're going to expand the forest
have fun I'm chopping down the forest no
no my don't call The
Lorax it's okay it's just you're
chopping it down to make it
bigger it all has a purpose it all
serves a purpose I'm not quite making it
bigger I'm just getting more app okay
good that's fine too uh how does how
does one plant apple trees oh apples are
a random drop from these
leaves got to punch the
leaves yeah you can punch the leaves and
or just you know let them disappear on
its own and see what you can replant the
trees as I'm going to create a forest
that branches off from where we're
planting a ton of
wheat it's going to go this way here's
the path to the forest go
go come here help me where are you
[Music]
putting you to work Kuba oh okay either
sword or mine oh not Birch Oak only wait
that oak trees okay yeah I'll sort I'll
sort have
fun have fun finding the
rightest I was going to get a
snack um just so you know in the storage
room area I've uh I've separated things
by how the chests are actually labeled
so if it says nether chest that's blocks
from the nether if it says ocean chest
that's blocks from the ocean oh yeah so
they're already like pre-labeled that
way nice yeah and then the ones that are
in the regular storage area have signs
that say like the top chest has these
things in them the bottom chest has
these things in them that kind of thing
n yeah oh good job by the way GL we got
some heart of the Seas but it's like so
useless I thought you could use it for
Atlantis but got to make a whole
ocean no I just need a little bit of
water I can put it I can build a conduit
and and it's cool
yeah it's useless yeah so
sad but it's
fancy I can build it anyway
oh yeah if you're up for it I mean it's
useless can you build under not
underwater or is it only underwater
Sprouts go uh I'm looking at your chat
for the
answer
um only water or also under
water try to make it in the fishing
pond or in the dolphin uh
pool how much water is
necessary then the the dolphin can can
swim even faster if it has the conduit
he's not allowed in the he's not allowed
in the conduit pool he stays down there
in the stinky dolphin confinement Zone a
that's where he belongs yeah he bit me
what oh yeah okay well he bit me yeah
true he's a little
[\h__\h] yes little shits the
aquarium I'm stuck again I feel like the
grass should spread from there DOL John
yeah that guy
sucks hate do John
it'll grow okay I can't go that way what
the
Helly all right start mining cobblestone
cuz we need like
a we have a cobblestone maker that g
made
right how many you need okay what we
need what do we need how many one second
one
second I'm making the my myy you guys
all right we need 20 stacks of
cobblestones one stack of trap okay okay
we already got a C
[Music]
do I get paid
over let me check how how much
Cobblestone we have in the other chest
right this is I don't know if I does it
have to be
Cobblestone specifically uh I guess it
doesn't it just needs to be 20 stacks of
something oh then we should have enough
stacks of things right all right let's
we'll make a cobblestone stack cracked
stone bricks stack chiseled stone bricks
stack I can't can't ride zombie
horses they'll fall apart they're
rotting in the chest by the cobblestone
generator I'll put U put like full
stacks of stuff if you find any okay
goodidea 20 you want yeah we need 20
we're so ready for this there's so many
stacks in
here empty
hands one two
Golden Arrow spectral Arrow 1 2 3 4 5 6
7 8 9 10 There's a Zombie 11 12
Stacks my a lot of zombies are oh
there's a really a lot of them spawning
okay just like again man I don't think
you need to mine at all we have enough
stacks of things I you forgot to light
up the new area really might yeah yeah
that's what I was going back to do I'm
sorry we just need two more stack I
added them just now when you left oh
okay okay we're done all right SC
stop
okay this many look how much you thought
two zombies Max wait wait but there's
only 42 on that one you need more no no
no no that's enough this we have that's
not a full stack no no that's okay need
to be a full sorry full St dead beat I
swear to God dead beat I know I know
I've seen the a of my ways okay KO you
did all of that wait red sand sand is
going to fall I that's fine no it should
be okay we're just going to be stacked
up okay okay okay I have too much stuff
look how efficient she
is maybe I should then trees get
together there why is it so slow anyway
can it not be faster come on it's my
ping always the cursed ping
pong oh what's my chicken St there what
the hell get out did you spawn there oh
you have a new family
now a little fall
down so
close count the stacks goo try counting
the stacks why don't you count them for
me why they're over 20 you count them
yourself I need to complete this one
stack okay it's for your own development
right let me finish oh no the Finish
it's unpaid anyway doing it for the sa
okay there okay what 3 6 9 12 15 16 17
18 19 2 22 23 Stacks but at least now we
have extra o
yeah what the hell because what if
somebody dies who's died the most here
what's that noise who turned on that
music
me it's a broken
scared me it's a broken one I don't know
what what it
is oh God it's a spr
[Music]
faster no why do you do that know hey
stop coughing come
get cover your mouth cover your mouth
spreading
germs it's like an audio book it's a
voice pack it's a voice pack oh I don't
like this voice pack I didn't buy it I
want to refund my money
back that's not quite my
Tempo my Tempo I'm
scared he's running faster Kiara run run
run run behind you behind until he kills
you y That's spooky how do I get into
this dolphin Center I think it's over
where is the
dolphin it better still be there he's
gone I he died no
way he must have despawned or so because
like why would he
die we need four carpets four carpets oh
yeah yeah he did oh my God I thinking I
should probably go share the
Sheep again it's fully grown M but four
carpet should already be possible with
the yeah stuff that's in there yeah the
only thing iron cuz I need I need five
oh wait what is it four Hoppers but we
only have 11 I think we can only make
two let keep mining it then we have two
Hoppers
now oh we do somewhere oh yeah yeah okay
have enough while I wait for the forest
to grow I'll organize oh there's a
chicken in there we got CH the rest of
the iron wait Dolphins can
drown yeah what
I guess they do go up for
air wait I feel so stupid right now but
I think I
do
yeah imagine being a sea mamal and
drowning couldn't be me that couldn't be
me okay I got the
carpet oh there's a Sher box
noat are you perhaps
[Music]
Gill and I say sounds like a gill
issue good one not he's
happy he's happy that you met with the
one and only Phoenix mommy come on
chicken let's go consider yourself
blessed come on chicken come on time to
go it's time to accept the new world
you're
in come on
get
moving y he should be grateful we're
going to be like feeding him and stuff
yeah or killing him we are no we're
going to be killing him this is you know
he doesn't need to hear oh just giving
him
free like hope before you know the end
well yeah that's how the meat gets
really good is that you don't tell them
that you're going to kill them we're
done with this series I promise to my
chickens I'm coming back to the server
every day to feed them every day I will
every day commit I might not stream it
but I will open the server every day and
I'll come and Fe every before is so much
bigger okay isn't this Ser we're going
to get shut down though anyway I'm going
to pay to keep it open just to feed the
chickens all right well I'm ready to
start if anybody wants to help okay I
I'll come too I want to learn how to
make
it okay I'll still work on the trees is
it like version specific does p yeah
yeah it said it should work for uh
version 1.14 and up oh wait I got to ask
chat a question chat should I build the
um mob spawner XP farm uh should I build
it like at the end of this Atlantis
Road or uh cuz it's close to spawn right
or should it be further away from
Spawn what to spawn or far for needs to
be BG far away is better okay well you
might um I have slabs I can build a
little bit further wait how many blocks
away live 2D is bugged no it's not I
just changed how they
look what' you do what did you do to us
nothing nothing I just you manipulated
your images a little bit it's fine don't
worry about
it oh is this your for expansion
pack k o we yes it is MHM I'm working on
the my my it's going to be a really
big the Mor's
let wait you can put melons in the my my
yeah the melon
Mor I got some here thats good oh hell
yeah mhm damn you should make like if
you ever do like a charity stream again
or so maybe plant some trees to make a
Mor o that's a good idea
yeah every every uh Super Chat that we
get for charity plants a tree in
Minecraft in
Minecraft yeah wait what no but then we
take the money then we take the money
from that and then we donate it to plant
real trees okay yeah okay real trees
real moris we want them real moris
really we some Dimensions with that
oneing di Manion bucks for one tree
all right I'm at the end of the Atlantis
uh okay thing if anybody wants to I'm
coming I'm coming is the only normal one
well yeah she's the only human out of
all of us so I thought I would leave her
image untouched is she do is she she's
British are
hum Goa is so I can make them for you
four
carpets we have
it there dare
wait where did everybody go wait hello
going to I'm bring extra slabs I got to
I got to extend this place a little bit
extra slabs com iing slabs okay go is
making them I'm here anyway I'll make
them nice I can't believe you can just
make a PPP that's so cool yeah what the
heck imagine having the brain capacity
chat I make PPP your name has to be also
ailia wats
only she is
capable oh I made a lot why isn't it the
the P then I don't
understand previously his property
because it is previously yeah true that
was already a PPP and I guess that was
pip should we just talk in abbreviations
from now on thank
you
why is in yes why oh ah oh stop that
would be maybe a joke stream idea just
only talk in in
abbreviations could be fun sounds hard
BRB getting more mushrooms too
LOL right I'll need you guys help in a
second hold on I'm just this really
quick maybe we can expand the forest in
time to go watch how the PE he is made
almost done f
r FR F
FR for real for real oh
stop they're actually oh my God I'd
never last that kind of stream
SMH I can't think of so many need to
make some
notes TGIF ladies w
though it's not tgit t TG TG M TG is it
TG I don't know is it Monday Tuesday
Wednesday Thursday Friday Saturday
Sunday it's one
wow I just rot the
dony okay let's see what she's doing wow
the weekend's here feel like I'm going
to
fall can I make a wall around here Amma
yeah maybe fences would be good or
something wall
KCK off BRB um
GTG got okay I will tame that
horse
him I wish we I still can't ride this
horse it's just the donkeys maybe I'm
just not meant for horses a no horsing
around youa no horsing around
donkey donkey
full myth Shrek watch along
when oh man we've seen it so many times
k k you and I have seen it together we
watched we did a one and two watch along
we watch both them need to get the
others in on this yeah we watched both
damn Marathon at my place yeah in the
beginning honestly it felt so short Don
I know
shre shre I'm always down for a shre was
along why is this name Shrek what do you
think you're M now donkey could it be a
reference to a German word of surprise
which is I'll look it up right
now I am surprised I
amre why is he called shre I knew that
was a
j girl related to the German Shrek
meaning fear or
fright you hit the nail on the head oh
my God that's why I brought it up cuz I
thought it kind of sounds like and you
know ogres they surprise you right with
their look so you're
like oh Shrek lore new Shrek lure just
dropped y there Shrek lore yeah years
later we're still getting new Shrek lure
what a world e that makes me so happy
that that I speak German wow you
donkey donkey me I'm donkey or no I I
think the donkey okay good nice how tall
is get shreked idiot Shrek is probably
like 8T tall block of iron oh yeah he's
pretty big he's a big
guy yeah oh my wait Shrek is based on 7
feet Fiona would be 510 as a human and
6'4 as an ogis oh she beat
ogis they call ah female OG ogis hot not
gun NGL
NGL hot what in what way K would you
like to elaborate girl
win yeah where's our ogis in lot of
English no no no it be cool she have
like an alternate form she changes at
night oh for all the night streams okay
that's cute yeah yeah yeah see see see
some people in the in the chat are like
hot y see there's something for everyone
here I
see you guys like an ogre lady h
I think they don't not like an over
lady why not what's there not to
like okay I'm going to oh yeah you do
you sure bunch of iron bars you're just
joking you're not serious about it I'm
going to put you in front of an ogre
lady and you're going to be
like help K like that don't out them
like that
k i be careful here cuz I got to build
down somehow I don't know how I'm not
opposed to ogres see they're fine with
it
with water that's why they're myy
fans wa ogre outfit next who's going to
do an ogre outfit not me ogre onesie
with little Shrek ears on keie it's got
to be you come on you have this whole
like Shrek thing throughout your whole
streaming career here no not really it's
it's just a little
J just a little tea hopefully I don't
die doing this go
go catch you Boulders gate three ogre oh
yeah oh man B this gate is so good I
wish I could have played the full
game yeah have you not played it on your
own no well I I did a little bit right
like simultaneously when we did the
collabs but then I felt like doing both
is kind of rough and then I left it to
the collabs only but then you know you
know what happened to the collapse so
and I was like ah I don't know
continuing now alone is a little bit
felt a little bit l i get you I didn't
realize that we had actually finished
act one oh yeah we kind of did yeah we
just didn't like we had to do like one
thing and then it would have been
finished I think right yeah well oh
maybe I thought we already did it and we
didn't realize we passed act one we were
in act two oh for real yeah that's okay
though yeah it's hard to do a really
long Ballers gate play play through just
a long game meanwhile nusa yeah Nara she
did the whole thing she's crazy I
respect that several times I also have a
friend who's played balers gate six
times with mods six
times my
god oh you can play it differently every
time that's the amazing thing about
these kind of games yeah I love
that for the
part okay what do you
need uh hold on we're going
to I need to get
water just grab a stack I guess we can
do sand for this one one because it's
fine we're going
to it do be
fine 20 up I'll be right back in any of
these like Corners
thingies yeah good at going AFK now that
we need
her Sloss please put me in charge of
golden apples I promise I won't let you
down wait uh oh yeah am I the
boss yeah well I kind of figured since
you set this whole thing up count 21 cuz
I don't know I I count it but I don't
know if it's right wait if a block is 64
and then it's
403 at the end of it cuz I didn't count
wait is there water down there how are
we going to get down oh oh you got the
water oh is it going to it's just
temporary yeah okay oh shadowy spots
suspicious hold
on oh I can go up with
the with the water
ah wobbly water oh shoot funny free I
was right
okay
ni uhoh I'm going to go to no I'm going
to shoot it I'm going to sh maybe we
should sleep you want to sleep you can
sleep let's sleep all right good night
oh God good is out in the open though oh
AFA we have to defend her I'll try where
is she okay at the future PP I got an I
got a bow but it's not coming closer
right now come on where are you go at
the
future oh over there oh beyond the
pandas
gotcha oo
cool I can fight him too I fight
him I'm going to waste these arrows like
that we have we can use infinite bow
yeah nice good idea I'll have it hand
so hit
him hey okay yay now we can sleep Arrow
cancel it's fine it doesn't matter let's
go sleep yeah doesn't it not matter oh I
guess a majority of players can
sleep
yeah hey Chad how do
I no it's not set the majority but uh so
this n we'll we'll
await good ey in our bed hey girl we
started having a sleepover party without
you
[Music]
a no
no which item oh okay thank you chat I'm
not much of a bow Smith but I'd like to
become
one oh did I just see her move I
[Music]
imagine yeah back with the abbreviations
it's not really an abbreviation I
guess I wonder why it's like why it's
like zzz for sleep like where did it
start oh not much of a b yeah not much
of a
boson I feel like at least G is one of
the few ones of these onop which are
which is like the same all over the
world like you know how for example uh
bark bark and woof woof they're like
different in different languages but z z
z is like same
everywhere says since
1918 yeah it's it's been used to
symbolize
[Music]
snoring who decided it who who decided
it uh no one really knows but it just
started appearing I guess in Like Comics
and newspapers I
suppose it's kind of like you know like
Comics have like The Zo like those kind
of things zap
Zipp so now we're just like chilling
here oh goo's back gooa can you like
sleep with us in our beds sleepover
party come over gooa oh sorry sorry cuz
it's because uh one of those Phantoms
spawned and you know we want to be safe
up there when we work uh wait you didn't
protect me what if it me we did we
protected your honor we killed it and
then we ran away after we we killed one
which means another one could have
spawned
totally are we all sleeping in the right
bed oh I saw
you
hey oh good
[Music]
morning
with did the forest grow did the forest
grow chicken dang it oh this grass is
really
slow is there a way to make grass grow
faster
everyone wo
gr faster ah the grass you need to
connect it to other dirt blocks and it
will just yeah we just got to wait for
this cuz it's going to start going yeah
okay well I'll wait then play the
WFT really a lot yeah thank you so
much bone meal a bone meal is for trees
that's what I'm going to start doing to
get apples uh afterward after the forest
is ready let's go to the PPP while we
wait we can go watch them we don't need
the corners we just need like to enclose
this water area I me
wa can we make a clay
brick clay we have a ton of oh yeah I
was thinking we should use some of the
clay stuff that's a good idea yeah feel
free there's tons yes yes go
ahead make pretty
bricks wait can I make too many no okay
you got a cook clay oh it
requires yeah oh oh we could pick up
some lava from the never so we can have
endless you know no coal for the thing
but instead lava yeah good idea yeah
lava Farm kind of thing that was one
good thing about going into the never at
least let's
go yeah it's a long
process let me put these back in
here so this is the
PB oh I that will require me getting
more I was getting suff I guess we can
get rid there's like one side that needs
to be sealed so the enemy is full in
here right goodbye
fish one more right one more oh yeah I
got it oh you got it okay she got it
she's got it h Fight Club yeah looks
kind of nice actually as if we
purposefully made a nice pattern nice
design yeah good design skills yeah
totally on purpose
M
premeditated wish I could give it a
home looks
nice Temple of
PPP I don't know we need to do something
eventually yeah get him
C watching watching nature do its
thing huh what does that mean
how can we help now Amy uh I'm just
waiting for this water to disip hold on
oh wait I have a sponge but it's wet
actually it's G it's gone already damn
it okay well now we have an extra
bucket oh sorry where did all the other
buckets go all right one second I got to
watch this video more sorry you guys are
just waiting for me okay okay it's just
cool to look at to be honest
I'm so excited we're getting does this
count as react
content not if you're not streaming I
think or like taking a video you got to
react to it live on some video for but
then what about watch alongs wouldn't by
that metric watch alongs not be react
content cuz it's not on stream yeah it
but yeah but you're stream like it has
to be showing on stream oh no no no I I
don't mean it needs to be showing on
stream but I feel like you should be at
least not doing the watch we have to go
back up there somehow we need ladders I
think content for us ladders we can make
yeah I shall make we need like 20
something
okay 20 laders let me guess you make it
super dark in
there uh yeah we're going to we're going
to build a platform up there
[Music]
cool live myth reaction I should have
checked out how
ladder damn it
wait wait wait wait
wait okay okay we're good we're
good I'm eating like rice crisps they're
pretty
good are they covered in chocolate or
just blank sour cream and
onion I was thinking of different kinds
I think okay I got a I got uh almost two
stacks of
ladders okay
going to throw them at
you wait here uh
[Music]
oopsy scolding requires string doesn't
it I don't think we have that much
string I think we need
scaffolding yeah should be okay okay up
she
goes we are looking if you guys grab
some uh some blocks we need to make a
platform on each side so it'll be like
uh
four platforms extending on each side
the top wooden eight yeah at the top I
have some what are they called half
block
slab do it like how I did here but on
each
side slabs
onal oh sorry blocks or slab blocks or
slabs oh um blocks blocks huh
huh I got block
wait you work I thought that they don't
spawn on slabs no don't use wood just in
case if you don't have any other c
jfyi um that only counts when you put
the slab at the bottom of the block for
example cuz you can put them both in the
top and the bottom position so just for
your Minecraft knowledge thank you do we
extend it this
way it was the bot
jfyi jfyi I didn't understand what you
meant there for a second I get it no you
know yeah how far is it
again uh eight blocks long two twoo
wide s eight nice this is some real Sky
Block kind of [\h__\h] let's go now this is
react
content feel danger oh you want some
walls too am with
that uh yeah yeah we're going to encase
everything in a two block high wall for
now say you want a side of walls with
that yummy walls go back down for more
blocks oh shoot speaking of going down
any commentary for this re video I think
it looks like a propeller right now like
a you know helicopter yeah what water
down okay give me a second I think
there's water in the uh in the chest
over here the Sher box oh wait I have
water never mind she's doing the water
landing oh I'm just I'm just making
elevator make a water elevator
Minecraft's insane oh there goes the
Torches call
torches wait could we make an actual
functional water elevator we have Soul
Sand right what else do we need yeah we
can I don't think we really need a I
mean unless there's something else cuz I
don't think this needs a water
elevator oh a kelp oh okay I think I saw
havep though mhm we got so much stuff
I'm going to go down it's my first uh
space right when I jump in the
water uh huh shift is it shift if you
want to go down it's shift yeah gocha up
oh yeah hello I'll put some
torches on the fences maybe I'll
help Kelly are you coming back to finish
the wall or should I finish the wall I
mean I was going to get more blocks but
you can finish it go ahead okay I got to
watch the rest of the video
okay oh I had two
torches this looks cool I like this PPP
we should give it a new name I think P
was actually
cool what's it stand for
previously Armor's property oh could you
if we have enough buckets uhhuh I need
three more buckets of water three more
buckets okay I have one I don't know
where all the other buckets I have all
the buckets because I filled them with
milk thinking we need them when I went
back
but I just wait I'll I'll go pick up
some water watch out I'm coming up you
mind if I just I'm on the ladder I can
bring one but me you know I actually
kind of want to make a whatchamacallit a
carpet sorry I'm just a little a carpet
what do I need a
carpet
wool no how many
WS what okay two wo
okay I don't like opening
doors oh you want to just jump over hey
hey hey I four buckets of water four BU
I have one you can bring bring one to uh
I
okay KP is silly guys what you guys are
silly you guys do and now we're going to
um said with trap doors I said what they
were saying I just said it out loud a
now you're pointing fingers at each
other s they started
it so we're going to do it like this and
then
gotcha sides and it's going to be on
both Sid this side okay sounds good oh
oh wait like
okay I'm coming with the buckets I just
went up the ladder and realized there's
no opening there wow perfect now no
delay in going over
fences hi are we pouring the water here
in the middle uh no no no it's going to
be at the end of this of the Halls that
we're standing in right now but uh maybe
you should pour
it I think we can't make a w f until we
get another deep only have
one this is not a
sheep this is a
sheep it is a sheep don't tell it
otherwise it's going to
cry don't let him
know it's very much a
sheep
okay it's white it's thick it's
fluffy mhm honestly I didn't even lead
it there it just like went over the
fence somehow and suddenly was there
it really wanted to be with the Sheep I
wanted to give it some
company the PO I need another I guess
can I make this jump yeah we're supposed
to both sides sorry water pushes
you w if you fall down one half
heart not bad that's that's how it's
supposed to work it's like exact amount
oh so I'm you can kill it zombie
now nice test tested it for us how do I
get I putting more water so it's going
to push you good to watch out ah watch
out don't worry I got washed away out to
shouldn't break the sand I think she's
not
Gill meow is car stuck down there no I'm
I'm made my way out oh is it downtown so
The Hoppers already working I can tell
you that you got your stuff yeah no I
didn't die but like I broke a block and
it went into the hopper ah okay nice see
Wawa tested I did I did waa approved it
was on purpose according to
kak can we get a translator not thank
you thank
you nice
o wo the view from here is really nice
you can really see what we all made
together a all right damn it's pretty
big
wao that's a good oh I can see from here
too nice it's te posing be a shame if y
all
slipped she says
Sing she's not going to push me off I
couldn't
reach points finger
[Music]
oh oh it's
working kind
of wait don't spot him in yet I'm in
here yeah send enem the enemies wait
pause pause the game wait pause the game
I got to figure out how to get out of
here doesn't matter what side the
enemies oh look a sper elev please okay
wait it's working wait what it's working
oh yeah go down go down go down go down
go down there go down down in the I got
to put the water in they won't go down
unless I do that is that airing
maybe a bad idea to use
say yeah guys wait who died wait k
died wait did all the Hoppers and chest
blow up oh just a
ho okay let me go grab Oh that's oh I
got to eat I got to eat I got to eat oh
God you have a bucket of fish
oh God oh God he's going to need some
repairs for
sure that was so good I saw like G die
and then I saw the sand falling and then
I slipped and I fell off with the sand
falling we need
the cuz you put it in at
me yeah I got it it's okay it's
so the middle Midway
is it's okay it's okay I'm staying down
here man can't blame you that one going
up there PPP giving
PTSD sounds about
right but hey you know at least we know
it spawns
monsters Karm mod K mod I'm not K mod
this was fun I I enjoyed every single
millisecond of
that I think it exploded in the
middle so maybe need some repairs in the
middle yeah that that creeper would have
either exploded up at the top or the
bottom so maybe the top would have been
better we'll maybe he launched we just
need to fix the sides the water's out
now uh yikes I'll fix I'll fix the
bottom if it could light up first maybe
at daytime might be a good time oh yeah
maybe we should okay sleep more stuff
will
spawn really I'll put torches up there
right now okay okay just L the work in
progress sleepy my time yeah sleepy my
time
the beds are being
used sleepovers are nice see you
sleepovers all right there's already
stuff up there spawn so I'm just going
to go to sleep hopefully they'll die
there are monsters nearby we can't sleep
oh there's
zombie kill him hey idiot stop watching
USD hey you hit my panda it's fine he'll
live oh wow okay wow all right he
punched me back so you know what we're
even we are even
Steven even Steven even Steven who's
Steven the even freaking weird freaking
weird zombie outside wait the even sleep
yeah did anyone pick up The Hoppers or
maybe n I'mma do you have my stuff I
have I have your stuff
cool do you I have the Wow Bow Wow Bow
oh no the Wow Bow sorry yeah I think wow
bow sounds nicer
so or you say
w let's just call it w bow like wo this
is a bow it's called a bow it's not
called a bow wo okay so it's a wo
bow yeah okay oh there's Hoppers missing
and we don't have any
iron I think we have some
missing yeah I only
no they they br oh no so recently I
split up an iron block that gave nine
iron I feel like we should be able to
make some more yeah we have 17 ingots so
we should be able to make a couple more
yeah let's try yeah it's just five per
Hopper so we just need 15 iron and then
you put a chest in the middle if
somebody wants to build it yeah okay
sure why we don't should I make the
Hoppers how many Hoppers do I
need uh we need three we have a million
chests so just take
we have a ton of chests yeah oh okay
yeah there's plenty
we I'll get these trap
doors you got the chest Cena or do I
need to grab some I got the chest I got
the IR too three Hopper leave it all to
you and uh me see if I can I want to
mine a little bit I'm going to
mine why we will find some more
iron
boy Japan bro
three okay shiku well actually if we
make pppp our iron is actually Sol cuz
some of the zombies or something drop
iron bars oh oh yeah oh yeah yeah
temporarily we can get more iron yeah
there's some a lot of good sides to PPP
so I think it's good that we get
it okay I'm bringing the Hoppers
over nice more iron surely yo if we
could make an iron farm though that
would be amazing but it's not really
hard to do yeah we need at least one
vill yeah Ah that's at least two would
be nice so we can just breathe them here
and I was trying to get one yesterday I
was like mining endlessly but they just
don't show up they've got to show up at
some point so I'm going to keep trying
okay I put the hoppers in the the
shelter box nice thank
you nice
Hoppers hippity hoppity you are now am
his property yeah me me I sir no the
hopper
oh oh Kitty see that's a good sign we
got a kitty cat wish you were a villager
but that's
okay new
cat more
cats is this white
cat oh I wish I had I wish I had face go
fishing Ena go fishing bless do we have
a fishing rod there's a fishing rod
somewhere we have string to make
one is it is the fishing rod broken the
one we had before uh no there should
still be one
there bucket of salmon was
tight tight is that oh is that German
yeah it is really it means
Health oh Health yes just Health be
healthy dummy yeah can I get your help
over here on this side yes so all the
sand fell cuz the bottom ones so we got
to rep put this hand I got sal
sal is pissed maybe we won't use sand
just in case it breaks
yeah we got other
blocks we have
Str that should be good
6 hours later SpongeBob there's a
fishing rod oh there it's Caren stick
that's not a fishing rod oh wait there's
a fishing rod beside it is the top like
blocked off or can I still get like
build up there no you can get up there
okay there's a a letter to get
out oh wait WR BL I'm not blind wrong
block here wait don't start from the we
got to get up here
honestly I feel like I've learned so
much about Minecraft just from this from
doing this though it's not standard oh
yeah give me one fact you learn oh like
I didn't know about the grass thing
right guys but what grass thing you know
that you need to have like a grass block
connected to dirt that like leads to the
you need to have like one grass block
and then it makes more grass blocks I
didn't know that there's Speas at the
top I didn't know that either
uh just knock them off I have like no
weapon because you got my things but
I'll try yeah I put him I put him in one
of the chests down here when you come
back okay is a ging watermelon St oh was
another yes I'm so sorry that was enough
a cre you're not allowed to go back up
there banishment she just attracts them
she attracts creepers can't be helped
M
me de
deal deal was there no uh Diamond chest
plate within my
things oh I have it you have it oh let's
go they sh I'm going to take it
off I'm coming for it put my diamond
chest plate into the final chest box oh
that's a spoter spoter monster more
string give
me swear to God just die monster I don't
ow you don't have any armor on you don't
oh
no oh no you don't have any armor and
you oh
Noe oh my god oh thank you oh
oh you know next time I I see you IRL
I'm going to do the thing where I hold
something high above you and you will
jump and not be able to catch it on
[Music]
in I uh I was trying to fight something
and I fell let me pick up
those it's okay Watson you're doing
God's work don't worry about it it's all
good my helmet we here to assist like
there's um there's a lot of obstacles in
the way and uh by a lot of obstacles I
mean
somebody you mean all
the work work space what what do you
mean what
nothing nothing it's fine we're doing
good it's a hard head Zone not a hard
head Zone hi
Captain right shouldn't die again but
fall Pi up my stuff oh well it's f ah I
took it what it wasn't really I think it
went into the hopper there you
are your diamond armor in the other one
you
oh you can't eat it okay I can't see you
white catle where are you point
them I need wait I have your helmet too
wait I took a different helmet thank you
that's actually I think that is possibly
not even my helmet but yeah oh okay CLE
please if you put torch under sand it
breaks automatically
oh speed
Strat bone meal bone meal how are you
supposed to get it underneath this sand
cuz good keeps falling good
question yes come for the
fish fish yummy fish where did all the
bone meal
go we have no bone meal M maybe
somewhere in some chest still I can't
see the cat Kelly Kelly in your light
colors chest cuz I see no other fee
there than light colors there's nine
bone blocks that you can turn into to
bone meal here this okay cool yeah know
that's supposed to be end chest but I
guess you don't get those things in the
end never mind yeah like the
Sandstone so I thought it was just your
light colors chest
whoopsies okay ticks uh it's time you
know it's time there's many orders all
made by
me
so oh hey I can kill them one my head
with this okay never
[Applause]
mind my is hungry feed
us just keep falling all
right sorry KP love you though love
you you know I love you great CLE
okay I'll also get this C
okay okay I can now save you I need more
seeds why are they running gr why are
they trying to
escape get you out of there C I got to
leave in 20 minutes oh okay has it
already been so long maybe leash long
has it farewell how long has it been 2
hours
oh God it's getting dark again okay
sleepy time go torches okay sleepy
time let me know when it's ready for
sleepy
time stuff will spawn while we're
sleeping right yeah probably
but probably
torches I mean if you leave if there's
no water it'll
burn oh yeah but the creepers don't burn
do they do creepers
burn uh wait do they not I've seen them
walk around during daytime I don't think
so they don't they don't
burn and spiders also don't burn I think
I got framed for a chicken masker
yesterday what did I do yeah well
yesterday I was like you know slaying
some chickens to get feathers and then
the chat uh like I can't see the AI chat
thingy but the chat told me that the AI
was saying that Mory K be brutally
murdered the chickens and that's why the
chat is
sad I had nothing I mean if it died I
probably had something to do with it but
way they are trying to make
it wait are you girls in bed someone
stole my bed what who keeps on whistling
by the way what the birds yes the birds
so loudly
are you waiting for me in bed yes
okay just dropping some eggs really
quick
okay no no God damn it chicken
chicken AR chaotic okay I'm here oh let
me take a picture
CS I need all of your guys' help to just
finish it quickly that way oh yeah okay
we shall
do all right what you got to do c Wasson
uh we're going to connect all the
corners to make to right now it's like a
cross right but we're going to connect
the corners to make like a big
platform and then uh yeah so we'll need
a lot of stacks for
that
materials I'm going to stay enough
materials just don't use sand cuz it's
going to fall
wood uh did someone use
sand well yeah probably not wood ah
okay yeah we can make slabs out of the
cob stillone right uh no not slabs I
think block
okay is it safe up there right now yeah
okay
what's the percentage drop rate for
apples guys okay low it's low we just
got to wait so we got to make it into a
platform yeah so connect the corners
like uh like here I'll do like a little
sample like this all the way to the next
corner and then fill it in ah okay yeah
oh the
window to
wall all right we'll get to planting
then
you good to go by you're trying to say
something no no
more if if anybody has
uh somebody could go down and make more
cuz I I ran out of platform or um trap
doors I don't know where they went the
rest of them oh I got some how many I
can make some more well it was a full
stack so I don't know probably like 30
okay I got you am I'll make them now I'm
already here
okay thank you
yeah let's see okay doors
teamwork all the wood I can find
[Music]
cute 30 or
so trapo
cute Pik time
what did you photograph us and you have
more block without my
conent
illeg okay I'm going to sell
it to the highest bidder did you get my
double chin you might no I took it from
quite above so it should be flattering
okay two blocks don't worry I'm also
worried about my double chin
we'll make acaia ones it doesn't matter
what kind of wood it is right
Amy uh no
okay aaia AIA sorry stop stop that okay
B whatever it's
called paparia papar
Pap okay what
else uh okay we just s on trap doors and
then hold on I'm watching the rest of
the video to see what it does next it
looks so
beautiful looks so proper so colorful
Patchwork this whole island is
Patchwork right I'm going to just like
us yay do Patchwork family all right so
now we're we're doing the wall it's
going to be two blocks high so if you
have more blocks more oh I didn't bring
any
uhoh yeah need to go down to
I think maybe maybe an apple will drop
I've almost got enough we got 21 trap
doors I'm just chopping some wood cuz we
do not have enough
wood I'm Mor I'm gred init sorry that's
wrong what I fell I I made a one block
too early I
think I'll replant
them
okay I just want to see if we can get an
Apple just one apple get those apples
those
app we open yeah it seems like it okay I
got to help so that should be
enough an
opening uh wait do we need openings oh
wait maybe not should we no we we'll
close it all okay yeah I just need you
to get yeah
okay so I have 30 but it's 10 of each
different type of wood so it's not
really consistent but it's enough yeah
it doesn't matter cool it's crazy how
much more efficient y'all have gotten at
Minecraft compared to when F myth first
started yeah we're Pros we're pro Gamers
now we've gotten better so now we're
going to seal it but it's going to be
like this like this and then we don't we
don't need this extra block up here
really doesn't want me to help guys how
do we swim it's shift right you guys can
start building off of mine if you want
to you don't
another space so thanks guys oh yeah I
was such a noob I played Minecraft for
the first time after I joined Hol for
the first time in I think I played
Minecraft before but it was back what
2009 or something really really early in
Minecraft I only
[Music]
Edition am I the only one who I have
another Quest For You C who yeah let me
know what I need more torches to light
up above the what we're building right
now I have oh yeah okay I'll go grab
some
right here never mind what I was go up
top for now and just put the Torches
down up there here I'll drop them light
up the what we're building right now
like what we're putting
down stuff doesn't spawn what is Pocket
Edition
on the iPod Touch
[Music]
IP touch Minecraft for everything I
watched a video recently where somebody
got uh Minecraft running on a
calculator no way that yeah that was the
first time I heard a Minecraft zombie
and I
cried scared me so bad that's cute I
never had an
iPod a
jelly oopsie
see torch I only had normal MP3 players
the ones with the USB stick it's a lot
of torches it's okay never low on
torches
again do you want to know how many
torches I made many I made about 400 wow
wow what are you doing I know we so
we'll never need torches again they're
all in the wood they're in the wooden
box but I'm going to give some to
Amy okay I'm out of blocks
again Callie said how many
yes when you go down there can you can
you close up on the back of the at the
bottom yeah you know that one there's
like one uh wall that the tall wall
That's not finished yet okay it needs to
be finished I'll check it
out ah that one okay
mhm okay here you go Amy
your torches oh two walls actually no
get a few more blocks actually we're add
let me build up once
again yeah no it's okay it's okay I'm
getting something else side quest failed
successfully what the apple quest I made
too many but that's okay torch Quest oh
no no no the Torches yeah I didn't make
too many don't finish it all the way
cuz uh should we no it's okay I don't
think stuff will spawn in here oh not
well iess fancy put some torches for now
okay all right now apple
quest it's going to be so
colorful should have had should have
made the whole thing in those fancy
terracotta
blocks oh yeah I don't think we had
enough though yeah he's okay I'm going
to make the backside like are you good
um o creep cre but it's water finish
there's like
a
here
uhhuh see there's like one wall That's
not there's like two walls that aren't
finished down there uh oh
boy I'm sorry it's okay it's okay it's
okay nothing much has been destroyed uh
the chest and Hoppers are still there
yes yes yes okay that's what's important
I thought would you know die in the
water such was not the case okay all
right well we just need to finish the
yeah those tall walls down there I'm on
it I'm on it I'm on it I'm on it okay
upstairs she's on it I'm on it
lit on your on your way up there's like
one that's halfway built if you could
finish that one too I'm on
it okay doing both at the same time
watching you we'll be done pretty much
here you guys probably want to move out
of the way cuz I'm going to start
putting well actually I'll wait till
she's done to put the water so she
doesn't
well oh no no do it down funny funny you
die there'll be water right oh wait k
look look to your left there's I don't
know if you can reach it but there's
like a little Gap there oh okay I can
reach that too oh they're watching
[Music]
me I'm being judged doing it okay yeah
do a good job what are you dropping are
you dropping trash on
me oh another there we go nice and then
I don't know how you're going to get
down uh look HM fly I won't be able to
place these last blocks though cuz like
I need to I think we can place it you
shouldn't die if you drop from here I
don't think let me let me get over there
first in the middle and then I'll like
replace it and you don't have a pickaxe
nope oh wait maybe now I do I Apple oh
thanks I'll go here and then bong and
then I guess I'll die I'll die no here
guess I'll
die that was a really genuine guess I'll
die jump
bye I survived dig out just uh I'm just
waiting for the death the death text to
come up at the bottom you guys want to
get up here cuz I'm going to we'll take
out the Torches but now I'm going to put
the water so don't want to get in the
way oh it's night time and sorry whoops
I'm going to mine my way out and then
I'll fix
it yeah
wait wait don't take the Torches out yet
yet oh sorry sorry sorry
sorry not a single god dog on oh okay
okay okay wait
chest oh are they in the
chest no okay I'll bring some should I
use shears on the trees you guys shears
no it doesn't work for apples like uh it
shears are the most efficient to get rid
of leaves but it will not drop apples
when you do that I see so I should just
use other random things yeah just a
sword or something my bird is up here SC
me yeah by Bird
Bye it's
gone wait it should the water shouldn't
be flowing all the way down I don't know
why it's doing that we can sponge it up
maybe yeah well if you bring up some
spudge use a
hole which chest is this sponging I can
find it I can find it but I'm just
replacing the chests really quickly
oh creeper creeper watch out no it's
l it didn't
blow we got to put torches down up
[Music]
top oh oh oh it's okay it's not it's not
too bad oh wait it killed my parot oh oh
there's zombies just log out just log
out I understand
you know to you know get to log out and
then should I go to sleep okay I'm out
yeah everybody else just go to sleep
sorry just got an apple
okay oh no bird dead oh no all the
parrots are like going instinct They're
All Dead all right I'm going to sleep in
dond Watson's bed
Instinct that's not how you say it in in
English right okay you're good you guys
can go that
we come back extinct
extinct are we good mhm yeah there's
probably going to be mobs there oh yeah
oh yeah it's
working zombie zombie be like two apples
I'm starting to get apples
nice she's on that Apple grind farmer
yeah chami love apples just got to
finish wall again and uh need sponge cuz
I don't know why the water actually
don't need sponge I just
yeah o
drown drop that trident baby come on oh
get try one of these
days yeah probably not block to fix the
anything anything can to happen uh I
might need a couple more blocks I have a
couple but I don't think know
yeah I can go get more wait I have I
have n it's not
enough okay I'll go grab
some who died up there my
bird oh the person died why did you
bring your bird up here he followed me
oh no
and well now he'll never follow you
again
bring this block of Quartz should be
enough I think I don't see anything is
it gone can't be gone oh so if I farm
the wood the leaves drop the stuff on
their own like app and what not oh okay
I didn't know
that we do need more wood we're going to
have some colorful ceilings
yeah oh
oops it got picked up yeah yeah yeah
yeah what you doing
goall I should leave this one I didn't
want it to go over the edge but uh yeah
oops we good yeah hopefully I'm going to
try should I should I uh PL this
here I can try ceiling hole should I
plug
it uh not yet hold on okay
I left the Hole by the ladder so we can
get up
here sponge found the
sponges all water but do we have to
place a sponge at the source or just
anywhere no no I don't we don't need it
it's okay he
SpongeBob SpongeBob
spob
SpongeBob German
version yeah so in English it's Square
Pants right in German shamov means um
sponge head oh Shram more trap doors
here Spong you close up could you close
up this water I have trap doors like
just put blocks here to get rid of the
water oh my Lord
Bob but where are we putting blocks to
get rid of the water where top bottom no
don't worry it got
it oh B have some
oh I'll take these
okay
Spong sponges
bubes
spes you in a funny mood sing German I'm
fine I'm just
tired cool no feel continue continue to
practice this is probably like 5 minutes
away from being done and then wait I
must I must leave yeah I was think
I must make my grand exito
no wait goba wait let me sing to you
really
[Music]
quick there you go that was for you F
thank
you
okay
I'll thank
you have a nice
evening getting rid of the we're getting
rid of them yeah we can just make a
bridge like
thisum
yum how can I help
so I think we're done let's go do we
need this wood down here maybe we can
get rid of it so I'm going to have that
empty
chest wood oh getting it okay and the
one below wood just wooden is there
something below okay no there was a hole
but okay we're good all right uh see all
over I'll leave first okay yeah yeah I
have enough to steal it
okay down
okay I think we
have all right should be done
yay fine now we can Farm
exp thanks for working on random stuff
from the let me check the rest of the
video just in
case what about this water go it's going
to go away oh it's going
down there's one chap there that's not
closed
should we
check what what was it chat says there's
one chapter that was not closed but not
sure I thought I what that
was oh I heard chapter well it's working
yeah it's it's working fine
creepies oh oh they exp are they going
to be not exploding okay uh they
shouldn't I don't
know good oh yeah oh we can get gun
powder from here and then with the
gunpowder I can make bombs and with the
TNT I can get us some um never
ride I don't know why they're
exploding or not exploding but they
they're like making noise going to
explode are we
safe can we put a trap door or maybe and
then like put it
up I don't know I think it's okay cuz I
I uh I think we're just seeing us cuz we
were too low yeah oh okay
okay nice it's working great there's so
many of them W and we'll get a lot of
bows too
y heck yeah this is going to be super
help oh get away so scary but it seems
fine is make sure you're not make sure
you're not standing on the Rock while
you're actually
on
yeah
nice ah the carpet's are gone are the
carpet supposed uh are carpet supposed
to be there am yeah H where did those go
I have them in my
inventory where'd they go
all I can play B them in the on I can
try
difficult difficult but it's working
without them what are the carpets
for I think it's just supposed to help
like cushion the fall or make it look
nicer
oh kind of difficult from this
angle uhoh I think I hit you sorry oh I
think I think it was the enemy felt like
it was the enemy person me okay damn
damn that was
crazy so um maybe no carpet was fine
maybe
oops Dad do we need the
carpet it's working really
nice security oh carpet is for the EXP
to not drop into the
Hall
my oh and so creepers don't see you and
explode it's better so enemies are
higher and don't see you as
easily okay so it's like two two
different mechanisms how are we even
going to fix it I don't even think we
can right now all right maybe here here
you keep somebody keep give me the
carpets
oh there's a
[Music]
witch yeah from the higher angle you you
could place it probably we can good
weapons now the EXP F yay oh well
yeah we can get the EXP enchant things
yeah I got it yeah I got oh you put you
put a carpet up above okay all all four
with power three oh no I got rid of it I
got rid of oh
okay yeah I think I got it ouch nice
nice
completion good job thank you Amy for
leading us through it you
thanks actually I think we should block
off the side a little bit because there
is a chance we get hit and
then which side like just on the side
like here on the on above the uh or we
can just put fences
cuz yeah yeah yeah oh okay come check
apples later I'm what what you naming
this
one
uh uh I don't know chat do you guys have
any ideas spider
clog oh it's
spiders
[Music]
oh okay something
dropped nand
nand yeah I saw in the video they said
you can put um like carpets inside to
stop too many spiders from spawning oh I
don't know oh pretty I like the design
work p should you want to call it PPP
ppp2 or VIP
or
um myth mob maker somebody says oh that
sounds
cute
the previously Lost am's Property you
guys just want to say PL
a MM what's mm come on
please okay
M I like it it's just ours no one else
yeah it was working great until there
they go oh nice maybe they'll despawn if
we go away yeah let's sleep let's well
it's working yeah thank goodness for
that Yay good job
everyone nice job team yay oh yeah we
should add that power three enchantment
to the Bodacious bow true I've got
enough
exp all right sleepy time feel things
have gotten a bit disorganized here
though so I might need to fix that
I'm coming I kind of want to make an
enchantment table but we would need
books to make a powerful
right probably but it's it really that
hard to find but leather I feel like is
not too hard to fine well we have plenty
of leather cuz we have course our cows
and stuff we can breed and then you know
but it's a paper out of this world we
haven't really gotten any paper like
things yeah how do had like fre pieces
of
paper but like that's it here it's
working C look go tast it y my turn oo
okay I'm excited go reap some Souls G
yeah yeah yeah I've been waiting for
this o there's a bunch of them just
don't Crouch when you're hitting them
cuz the creepers might see you a gotcha
so so don't Crouch gotcha yeah oh
there's so many time to die
dummies oh there so many there's so much
she's reaping oh my god well I think uh
they saw me all right this is I there
goes the XP fall wait it exped no we'll
fix it and as long as we just like stay
further out get out just get out just
get out get out get
out oh no I hit Watson oh God it's it
never we just got to as long as we were
like one step away and and killing them
it was fine so we just got to you know
save
I don't think we can fix it don't youy
dot dot dot me it should it should be
able to you should be able to go up it's
okay it's okay call close that's how
it's supposed to work so it's okay it's
a design
flaw tower defense game now I'm glad I
tested it before someone else hurt thems
okay well what we can do is block off
the area and then just like build kind
of around it so we can hit them from AF
that's the best we can do if they keep
yeah but somebody has to go in and like
fix like we we can block it and then I
can fix it if we can get blocks in there
seal it but they're going to be
constantly spawning
yeah oh I have no arrows that's oh the
creepers there are a lot of them it
should be one XP uh or one HP one HP I
mean this is one way to farm XP right a
different way all right I just every oh
here uh who here Ena I'll Trust Ena to
come in and uh fight them cuz they're
one HP I just need to get in
there on my
way yeah
B nice all right what are we
doing if I are they shooting at us yeah
yeah yeah I I got to get in there so
just go and we'll kill them they should
be one HP except for the spiders creeper
it's okay they're they're low okay okay
probably get one hit godam it
whatever all right just keep keep
getting them as they fall I'm I got to
seal it a shooting range yeah all right
all right it's it's sealed for now it's
sealed for now oh I'm not okay okay I
wonder yeah is it supposed to be kind of
lower do you do you think um like cuz I
feel like yeah they saw me and I was
like as I saw them I was like oh I bet
they can see me but it was too late
we'll fix it needs to be lower there one
hopper I think it was working fine when
we were standing like one or two steps
behind like further
behind
M maybe put like a fence or something so
we can't get too close by yeah maybe
that'll work yeah okay like here's the
limit where no no
touy damn
that was good stream
content well it was my turn to blow it
up I everybody had blown it up before so
yeah we did we did blow it up several
times in the process don't worry bonding
experience uh I need the Hoppers but I
don't know where they went they're gone
no again destroy I I bet we have some
more I have one I had one so I put it in
already okay I'll see if I can find
another one
I need like a slab or something oh there
you go I have 60 free slabs if you need
them I just needed it to put the carpet
on
here okay is there ore and we've only
got two iron but let me see if I can
find some
more uh iron block would be nice come on
Minecraft Gods I've really been testing
the team today in give us an BL
yeah there's a hole in this side it's up
there I get
it get
that see oh there up there
oh oh got
one why can't I
place oh cuz there's a slab there oh
okay I see nowo I'll just wait
till this is theam around feather
falling four nice that's really good and
then oh it's loud mhm uh so if we put
Gates right here well we need we need to
make more Hoppers I don't know if we
have any more yeah it's okay we we'll
work on that we'll just leave this for
now and then yeah I'll find more
iron we'll fix it we'll fix it carpet is
easy to get yeah
yeah there's there's a block right above
so we can't put the carpet there
yet um okay let's just go get the uh we
just need the Hoppers and then put
the put the um no no no yet we just need
the Hoppers and then we can fix it up
okay okay for now iron iron
iron we thought it was finished but we
finish it a second time
yeah and new and improved yeah oh yeah
we learn you know
it it's okay slow and steady slow and
steady do win the race
oh I'll a bit to see if we the box is
full right now um cuz I was trying to
find some iron it's the one thing
there's so much stuff obviously we're
going to get so many blocks we don't
need
mhm need like two fences or three fences
that we can make it safer which we don't
have any
wood wait we don't have wood we should
have I I just farmed a bunch of wood
actually um I'm going to put it there's
a a storage chest um oh I have some wood
too in here I'm putting all the wood put
it in the wood chest iron trap doors are
more durable and can handle a Creeper
explosion
guys there's a problem with that we need
iron yeah yeah we don't have what do
they mean like cuz we already finished
the top part we don't it's not a problem
them exploding there there's no trap
kind of low on iron we can't really iron
trap yeah that's the main
thing that's why we got to make an iron
we need a villager we need a villager
please if we could get a villager that
would be a game changer M only need two
V Villers that's the game changer yeah
need to get lucky
twice
yeah it's okay we'll we we'll be fine in
the end yeah we'll be
fineous yeah we'll just need to get some
iron freaking from
the but oh I got two more carpet does
this also drop water m
B is
awesome let's see if it drop trying to
use up some exp before I inevitably die
and lose it
all have what is that oh of course I'm
look for more apples for now I'll let
you guys do the mining I really should
organize those so they can do more
mining please please Ka sorop please oh
yeah oh yeah whoopies I am carrying a
lot right now ah one moment
sorty sort OPI
[Music]
sorty there's my
dirt let's see cute fish oh pink P well
that's kind of nice cuz we don't have
any pigs oh let me that out of there
come on come on yeah good job
good job who's a good piggy you are yeah
you
are I'm not sure if I can drag this into
here you need help or is it too
full yeah if you can get like if you can
grab like a or something and then like
drag
them the the but I think as you said
weat so yeah just just bring the cows to
the other side come on follow me ESC
yeah they seem they seem too thick to
escape
anyway okay we sure do get a lot of all
right we're good we got the
pig oh freaking random ass zombie oh but
this one's did you come from the nether
oh I think it
did oh oh no so I'm going to introduce a
new mechanic we're going to have a chest
that you guys put things that we don't
need in there like rotten flesh and such
and then I'll take it and I'll throw it
off the side when it's full m yep that's
what we going to
do free
gold more gold for
example I don't know where to put
anything here so if you don't if you
want to throw things away one of the
Sorting chests oh wait I can't throw it
off the side never
mind you can't unless it was a Shuler
box such a dummy yeah just put it in the
Sorting chest it's
okay it would be such a good idea though
trash can this is why I wanted to make a
trash can we can't though we can't
because that would be Iron add never
thing that's fine they can visit us I
don't even know let's see visitation
hours are currently open you don't want
it just throw it off the
side this high priority
is five five iron per Hopper right
more
sorting put it next to sand then remove
the sand oh that's a really good idea
actually for a trash can cuz we have a
gazillion chest it's too
many iron please please show yourself
the good thing is that at this point
where it's All Phases combined sometimes
there's iron blocks like full iron
blocks okay just like how there's iron
Emeral blocks sometimes so you know we
can get lucky
sometimes there's always that
possibility like my inventory is very
full even though I'm dumping everything
like okay
don't put that in
there I win I
wi i
w although the more we mine the more
pickaxes we're going to use going to
just mine with stone pickaxes I guess oh
I've just been doing that unless there's
a like a block that's hard to get mhm
yeah it's definitely the best way I'll
do it too after this one
breaks get a
sand all right I'm making a trash can
we're going to try it out wait is so
wait maybe chat was saying that instead
of carpet we put trap doors I don't know
if that has the same function on top of
the hop
first I guess the trap doors are a
little
bit maybe sandone
they're a little bit higher so I suppose
they would we we would be lower but I
don't know if that really you know
helps
yeah unless it's iron of
course but we have so many fancy blocks
but no iron so much terra cotta and okay
diamonds are nice what was that wait
what was that egg yeah what was that
it's a zombie something egg here what
was that I want to see drop it just
throw things off the side can use this
as fuel I'm trying to trying desperately
to make a trash can I need to just give
up all right uh let's see what was that
hold
on I think it was like a zombie
something egg oh I got it zombie zombie
villager spawn
egg is that good I mean we could track
hearing it but we wouldn't need like a
potion of weakness or something and then
a golden apple we have plenty of golden
apples we need a potion of weakness side
make that side quest side quest side
quest get the potion of weakness the
spawner we it spawn several of them no
just one okay but then let's say let's
spawn it in a safe environment in the
Airbnb okay I'm going to put this in the
precious goodies chest sick what a hold
it we have a chance I didn't know they
included these blocks
what the hell yeah it was in the chest
so like I guess the chest can spawn
extra special things let's go let's go
let's go nice one is a game
changer throw the trash in the nether
that's also possible
iron cooking one
[Music]
iron diamond and gold I mean if we found
the uh if we found a like a normal
piglin we could have totally tried to
have a traded gold for iron bars and
stuff but we find
one
yeah thanks for the yeah those piglins
all kind of yucky all of them were
messed up yeah they're kind of dead
they're
groy oh this a random
chest okay
yes are you
okay I'm stretching oh cute stretch
sounds nice right about
now more sugar
cane we finally got sugar all the game
changers now game is changing forever
now let's go this game will never be the
same now that
you we can en enchanting
table eventually but you know there's
some work that leads up to
that ah sponge stole the water yeah I do
happening often it do be happening often
cannot speak English finally sugar cane
let why we can make pumpkin pie too
yeah y Let's go
Team a win for us finally at
last it it's the it's the it's the bad
one it's the bad
okay um he's dead good job but the the
vexes are still around all right we got
to kill
them chickens protect me hey dummies
come over
[Music]
here nice thank you little
T got it for being my Refugee oh there's
one more
I got your stuff sorry I pick up come
here
[Music]
no where go yo why is he allowed to just
face through the freaking
floor go I have tra oh there there he
is some of your
things sword Prett much I think this is
your sword and then did you have an iron
pickaxe cuz I also have one okay here
you go you can just have it and then
thank you you
go anything else Granite oh here's your
granite and your
torches oh thank you that one is so
aggressive I didn't get it's okay I'll
just make a stone a pickaxe oh I gave
you an I gave you an iron
one no I did it didn't go oh it didn't
hey where' it go then no no that wasn't
okay I just I just make a stone one oh
wait I have your iron one on me oh you
picked it up
I have a block of iron I have a block of
iron nice we got nine I love that we're
celebrating over BL what happened to the
water that's what I really like about
this game mode because we we start from
the simplest things again and you know
we can't just use all these farms in the
Japan server okay I'll cook these two IR
or okay how many is that 14 oh we just
need one more for a hopper
yeah I wonder if we can decompose the
iron horse armor that' be nice that
would be cool if you could break it down
we can do that with our own armor but
not with the armor of
the
[Music]
sad oh yeah it would have only been a
nugget H I love nuggets but not those I
mean still it's it's more than something
yeah
also cuz we do have some other iron
nuggets probably need to check these
more often these
trees how long does it take for the
apples to despawn if they fall no wonder
long long long no oh despawn oh despawn
may be not so
long I keep an eye I'll come back to
check M
okay start with
those maybe this
one 5 minutes okay I'll be careful I'll
keep checking on them wait this used to
be a stone box
down all right
wood actually I'll make a chest that's
just wood from the forest
okay now the sponges shouldn't take the
water I think
oh another Improvement
made yeah
she what did you a little bit how did
you do it I might need some bread I just
put more trap doors and put the water
block a little bit higher
oh IR oh
iron we can fix the fix the Hoppers now
yay
that okay guess I need to break some of
these leaves down right I'll make them
oh we already have enough we already had
16 oh oh wait really yeah I thought we
had 14
Maes math is hard all good math is hard
for a myth
math math class with myth we released an
English language book before now we're
going to release a math class book oh
yes oh is there any more car oh wait we
can already make a potion of weakness
cuz we already have fermented spider egg
or spider ow oh yeah what you mean for
the villager oh but we need a yeah yeah
but we need a potion making thing I
don't know what that
oh like a potion table potion mixing
table or something what is
it huh H maybe I should make a fence
around the uh around the forest I wasn't
really holding anything important I
don't think okay brewing stand op F op
don't fall oh we can totally make one
okay what did you lose
key uh I think the only important thing
I was holding was maybe two apples which
is to bad but is what it is damn all
right get
cobblestone a couple of chests too oh
well all right let's start making some
new
things not like we don't have materials
to make new things
yeah
okay cobbly
Stone so I got a cool potion that gives
plus one luck very cool it's all right
it was just two apples do we have any uh
carpet or wool make carpet oh there's
carpet in the uh shulker chest oh yeah
put I should have put some in there okay
thank
you okay make the brewing
[Music]
stand
nice I'll put it right
here okay we have
glass oh had glass in one the chest
Kelly were you still wearing the diamond
armor no I put it away okay come cuz I
think I'm going to put mine away to just
in case oh yeah no I put mine away don't
worry okay but it was a good reminder
for me to put mine away too yeah
anything can happen at any time I don't
know where mine went
water it's somewhere for sure for sure
probably yeah I just put it in the final
chest that we're taking to the the last
battle I've been hoarding stuff yeah
good idea I'll put it there too and the
gold golden helmet um so I can make I
got Apple see already getting new
apples where's the Sheep I got simply
adding
fermented spider I water bottle it's the
only potion I can without without Nether
oh I'm so excited Ena I'm so excited oh
hey we got a potion maker let's go oh
wait we need to get Place power no
problem I think we should have some
we've got that cover
okay make a splash potion mhm yeah I
learned recently how to make potions
too finally gunpowder we got gunpowder
from the from the
creeper
though where did I put it there's how
many do you need there's four here just
one oh okay here
those thank you
are there children playing outside
please be quiet and enas at a
year I'm so excited I'm so excited this
is not how I expected to get a villager
but it's it's a cool way to get V where
are we putting the Villager in the in
the house you
built well we might we making sure they
can't get out right yeah yeah we'll
close it off somehow okay we got three
of them so if we happen to have another
one more down the line we can use it do
you want to make it now
or I I want us to make it now as soon as
possible um we need a golden apple we
have pled go check the final chest
behind the uh the chicken Co cuz we can
already give him a job right and then we
can already have him start working on
like armor wa we can actually give him a
job yeah that gives us iron Emerald oh
yeah yeah
yeah it's it will be the the the problem
solver for
everything when if we can get enough
iron we can change his job and watch
more thing they can open doors can they
open fence
gates I think so cuz farmers do that
right no do they open
them what's a good way to do this chat
there are only that gives IR they buy
iron they don't give iron am I thinking
of like the merchant oh okay we'll put
it in a boat must be thinking about the
merchant
but if I have a
boat is he going to restart I'm not
going to make a million we can we can
put him in a boat for temporarily fix
things
okay okay I think we have more sticks
let's
see are are you here Kiara doing it wait
wait
wait yes I'm so
here spicy be enough let's find
out wa cool he already has a job does
he kind of hit hard you should stand in
front Okay and then you want to get out
of there it's a splash
potion okay me from my then I throw this
right guys do it do it I want to see
right
chat he's a map maker
lame
job okay I also got weakness and then
golden
apple
w magic oh he's evolving he's
shaking he needs a
hug gosh you cold there buddy once you
are not a zombie anymore we'll give you
a
hug first stop stop being so
green don't press B
he's dead he's dead oh it may take 3 to
5 minutes okay oh oh really okay we'll
just stand here and wait make him
uncomfortable I mean we should put we
should also get can you get a name tag
just so we don't accidentally them yeah
what are we going to name
him uh Shrek no that's a bad idea he
won't be green never mind we don't want
we can have a legally
distinct that is not
Shrek he's like a Hot
Pocket you okay sh with G oh man what's
going on are you
okay oh worry about it guys oh no I'm
good okay I made I made I made a
name actuallya need help again the same
thing I'm anticipating can he be named
something small and then uh you got you
guys watch over the Villager yeah I'll
watch him I'm a good babysitter
I I'll make another axe cuz mine's kind
of like
half
durability oh yeah idea
Stone oh he G he's got a name now if you
look at him nice
name shred G can I make it with d and
then we we should make another one and
also call that one shre so we can have
unfortun shre to together yeah shre
sh love shreds come on get over it
already walk it off walk it off shre
look come on I his mon fancy yeah get
him shant good idea sh hey that was Chad
not they'll have shs together yeah you
ready I'm ready I just need to seal it
off again so just need one
more Shing
I kill what's there and
then I want to see both what I do what I
doing I want to see
both they're too far oh there's
more shoot creeper watch
out also there's a piglin walking around
are you cool that something a piglin no
where yeah oh that one it won't attack
us oh creeper creeper
oh even if it loads chunks does it not
load people I wonder uh there's a hole
there on the side
shoot keep keep at it we'll keep at
it come on do something they're not
taking as much damage
uh falling on the
sides damn he looks like he's really
struggling I'm going to go get some soup
you better not trans super constipated
I bet he's going to trans like a tower
defense I know we need to back up it's
fine might e to eat come back okay
yeah go get your mushrooms to mushrooms
to 50% off go get it
now okay fall back fall back all right
Retreat Retreat I was able to fix some
of it but I couldn't see it all the way
okay y
yum uh I guess I'll borrow a bow and
some arrows I can shoot down first from
the
side power three let's use a regular B
he's
nervous that's okay he's got performance
anxiety I killed some of
him not while people are watching it's a
freaking Battlefield damn crazy it's
okay just give him a minute girls if you
need help let me know
okay I
think right yeah
okay do you think it really
worked for sure yeah it's the because he
has the swirly fingers around him it
worked oh he became
a wow oh it's okay it's okay a damn it
why not the other way around let me out
no leave bed I want to talk to shre
but he's got to change his job hold on I
ran out of stuff to seal it with I need
to you know how to make a what job shall
we give him ready okay I think the armor
would be last we can still switch his
jobs
afterwards whatever noice though he's
got to get
better well now yeah his his uh current
job is kind of
useless all right no I'm going to die oh
you can't change the I can't change the
job
okay I can't get the zombies there's
like one hole on the left I got to seal
up you trade with locks into a job they
say when we come
back um like in the back make L of paper
oh wait if we trade with him you can't
change after trading job okay but so
you're saying now I can still change it
once and then once we start trading we
can't anymore so now we can we haven't
traded with them what's the tool again
for armor um
makers what's the work table
thingy what was it a blast oven o that
probably needs iron right all right uh
we'll need to go around the back cuz I
got to seal up the left side all right
if you if you go in the front like on
the left you where the see where the
purple blocks are on the left side yeah
and then I'll go around on the other
side to seal it maybe if I make that
it'll teach me how to make let's do some
trimming let's go get the creepers first
I need some
cob no it's
not yeah I want
to oh
no there a lot more than I thought that
seems not
good wait was mine defeated
okay I was blowing up so my stuff should
be
around I had a totem life but I blown
off I was blown off the edge yeah
damn I thought we didn't lose that much
stuff it's just like junk that we lost
at least
for wait was Ena wearing the diamond
armor it's still there right I was inde
need I don't know if it's still there
cuz I technically was blown up by a
creeper and then could still be there
hopefully yeah where that's a alive
there's just like one hole that they
keep coming out of that I need to like
seal it but I can't get to
it yeah it should be at the base of the
farm if it didn't fall how do you make
it into a blast
[Music]
furnace is a skeleton over here snow
Stone
I the void claims another not feeling so
good actually get
him what's up is tummy egg oh I heard
where that come from where did that come
from that didn't sound good there
someone there's like stuff spawning back
here oh that's somewhere oh I think I
know where it
is looking for Cobblestone here torches
I think it's back here I'll be our be
okay
okay things haven't spawned here in a
while
so
Wonder bring cat against creeper can we
bring
cat yeah bring C I guess we could it' be
nice to have a cat sitting by the chest
cuz that's where they everything spawns
right there but I think I fixed it cuz
there was uh one block behind the wall
that didn't have
torches I got
it yeah bone meal guys sorry I lost the
bone meal when I invisibility potion
what's invisibility
potion o would that
work one potion of night vision and a
fermented spider we don't we don't have
any more fermented spider eyes how do
you make fermented spider can you make
fermented spider
eyes like if you have a regular one
maybe regular spider eye and then do
something to
it yeah Brown mushroom sugar and spider
eye oh we have brown mushroom I remember
I bought some from the the
nether oh
yeah oh yeah we have seven or eight okay
so we can make this and we got sugar
from the sugar
cane
nice cool okay and then spider
eye I'll just go over there with some
blocks and like a you know like kind of
like a suicide mission give me theil
potion and some blocks and I'll just
seal it up okay and then potion of
invisibility need a potion of night
vision which is
[Music]
uh o of night
vision nether war and one golden carrot
we do have golden carrots right yeah
yeah we do if you check the chest behind
the chicken coop okay
so one nether w we have lots of nether
W sand oh we do need more water
bottles oh be
quiet need
one yeah we'll make three three just in
case or later
okay one two
[Music]
three and
then three Nether
wart makes awkward potion and then we
add the golden
carrot was it was it uh glowstone powder
that made it last long I think so
right we have plenty of that if so yeah
you know for the extra
cautious you know stay stay invisible
long oh yeah oh glow stone amplifies oh
it's red stone that makes it longer okay
we have plenty of those oh plenty of
both of those yeah
somewhere yeah the F chest a lot of
chests around
okay okay we
got got the awkward potion so we add the
golden carrot the awkward potion
what the that's a weird name for
something yeah it's a it's pretty
awkward what the heck why would you ever
want to use that
potion
Wanda hey are you to you when you're
invisible shoot all right I'm going I'm
going with just blocks
and that's all oh what if what okay I
got an idea since the blocks blocks are
the the place you have to block is kind
of up above right yeah so why don't you
build a bridge like up above so the mobs
can't reach you and then you go get to
the oh get to the get to the hole
Yeah that
work that's by Archer well we'll have
we'll have
a
uh maybe if I can make a shield I can
tank some of the mobs I was able to
close it except now just the side parts
are open there's some side Parts open
was able to close the bottom cuz that
exploded
again um yeah I Can Build a Bridge I'll
just just build
Bridge I'll Le make
oh oh I realized I go soon the Apple
hunt wait that's not one that's a
beehive come on come
on don't fall off there we go and
now they should start despawning on
their own once I kind
of okay I have to go soon so I'll
quickly try and help out before I go
okay what do you mean you try to help
out you've been helping out all along
yeah no like like last like get
on the yeah stuff just seal it for now
and then we'll fix it another
time I dropped um ladders if you want
to I just need like a form of
Defense
yeah there's right now so yeah I get
you oh good it's cuz they they don't
spawn until you're close enough for that
to happen true app I have no idea where
it's working get another more
Stone now we've got three n you are wait
what do you call an a lady that has an
apple farm and collects apples isn't
there a nice word for that an apple farm
stress no nice your word
an apple
princess yeah no no that's not what I'm
thinking of I'll figure it out someday
okay you want well okay Orchard is
probably the the prop most proper word
for it an orchard R well I guess Arrow
would have been better huh Orchard I
just got to um get a pickaxe cuz I I
can't get in there to seal it
okay see this this for is really good
mhm okay at least the zombies are
burning once we get here it's good right
guys oh that's a lot of Creeper there
moreing out oh Jesus Oh you swimming no
I was swimming for a minute there it's
cuz my Forest is so
Bountiful Apple
Jack Apple we'll also get a ton of wood
at the same time
too I need to make a
it's okay at least I brought my
cat yeah y cats the creepers
away uh my cat's not doing anything with
the
creeper yo do your job it's like when
you want your your cat to chase a
cockroach or something in your house and
they won't do it yeah just because you
command them to if you're not there
though they'll do
it oh shoot I forgot to make slabs
sit down here
cat that's more than the pandas are
doing all right it's sealed off for now
so the ones that are here are the last
ones that are going to spawn the one the
I feel like they're still spilling out
from somewhere it's just my
[Music]
imagination like on the right like where
they're standing uh yeah they're just
standing there they they can't get they
can't uh fall that far
down
okay guys are still added oh my God this
is crazy we're almost done though we're
dead now this is crazy I should bring
them okay I'm going to go bring a
bow it just blew up
[Music]
the no I didn't have any items that was
just uh that was my Suicide Mission
okay
y there's only the really good bow left
oh use it use it it's okay oh okay oh my
inventory is not full I died with all
the weapons huh maybe I need the
infinity bow yeah Infinity bow would be
good for this okay I have one Arrow so I
can you can use theous bow if you
like yeah no it's destroying everything
and we should build it from scratch
again no we don't have to build we did
have to build the base again but uh else
is fine
yeah oh no no no no no no no are we sure
it's
fine I don't know how there's still
stuff's fall I'm probably going to die
right now
but oh no why have you no mercy why why
why that's
cruel there is a hole there is there my
mission
did you take there is all yeah okay I'll
I'll bring
the why are you
doing together we'll like you know snipe
everything wait is the Sher box con did
it blow up I think so oh no this hurts
so bad I want the
Apple this ghost
Apple okay it's a day full of different
rough Adventures but I'll be late yeah
all the the H we got to fill everything
in
right I'll just
no it should be yeah it's it's done for
now build it using obsidian we do have a
lot of
obsidian not that many well at least the
base
maybe like the the first couple of
blocks in the bottom could be obsidian
even if it's obsidian The Hoppers will
still oh yeah the base could be obsidian
H wait don't isn't there still a hole
over there we have to fill that in with
water you think that'll
work it's because I sealed it you see
where the bridge is I sealed it right
there oh that's why they kept sing at ah
no no stuff can't fall past that the
hole where the bridge
is uh the ones that were here in this
chamber I think they're just um they
were just a lot that had accumulated ah
okay yeah all right
right let's go
cat I mean do we even need an XP farm
for something I mean it's already
finished basically and there are
definitely uses good uses for it I would
say drop could be temporary iron and bow
and stuff arrows and for enchanting
things we does anybody have a pickaxe I
can borrow so I can fix the base at
least a few pickaxes no okay oh if if
there's obsidian though we'll need a
diamond one right no I'm not mining well
unless I mess up if I mess up I need a
diamond then we're in trouble here you
go well I got to head out for now okay
thank you take care than
foring thank you survive we'll try also
our our house is open I don't know oh
it's cuz of the
creeper oh oh yeah hey do you have any
torches k um we havean Tores I'll try oh
wait I got the shulker box guys I got
the shulker box oh hooray oh
nice okay now I can
leave uh my job here is done do you need
torches on me okay bring her to
torches byebye
guys
by
okay here you go on Torch
delivery thank you you're welcome
maybe
more I wonder how many golden apples we
should aim to
have many many yeah many many many maybe
honestly probably five per person would
be good too per person yeah okay sounds
good so 25ish
we're getting pretty close to
that this is so
sad I should at least make a wooden one
make a wooden one I want to make
obsidian fence Cobblestone here but ooh
a fence out of obsidian doesn't exist
sadly oh that would be really strong
though I bet yeah
oh
d d 32 bone blocks oh we'll have bone
meal for
days okay all right this should be good
for now okay
I will be your replacement for Ena so
let me know if you need something oh are
we going to fix it now oh I mean if you
I mean if you don't want to if you don't
want to then we don't have to um we
still we need Hoppers again because
again are they gone yeah four Hoppers we
need I'm pretty sure they're gone I
don't thinka had them Fu well if you
want to do something else on it then
yeah go for it we can pick it up later
yeah I we can fix it whenever we or if
somebody's going to play tomorrow or
whenever the day after I think I
understand how it works so if I'm
playing alone I can fix it I can try to
fix it uh you just leave it I'll Jo okay
I'll let you know I'll let you know I
almost got the
vision uh okay well it was it was uh
working for you
know um a little amount of time and uh
that was a good time
and this is fine too there was a time
when it worked and there is a time when
it doesn't work and all times are good
times yeah it's fine there's plenty of
other stuff we need to do anyway feel
like apples I think I'll make a second
floor underneath so that when this
explodes Again by any chance uh we will
not fall into the void yeah that' be
good like a little bit wider of a
platform underneath too I'll make that
I'll do that thank you just leave it for
now yeah let's leave it for
now okay I think um I'll probably go to
okay
I'm okay have a nice evening thank you
for being here
today thank you goodbye
chk
goodbye see you now it's me and kaop and
then there were two Mor op we're going
to we open we're going to grind a little
bit more Cali or what well yeah I wasn't
really planning on on stopping until you
know about when it's time for the 2.0
reveal so ah okay okay okay you want to
like raid yourself into that or what I
was thinking maybe I'll do that but now
we'll see what time is it like how many
hours it's about 9:30 so it's like an
hour and a half or so oh okay okay okay
still a good amount of time to keep
playing um I'm going to I'm going to go
check on my cats real quick
okay so don't say anything suspicious
while I'm you mean you're real cats
right but of course okay okay oh yeah
not the ones in the game I really have
no connection with them right now I'm
sure we'll get closer we'll get closer
surely okay I will be right back but
yeah don't don't say anything
weird I won't say
anything I'll just say sleeping
Chad what no no K help me please uh
please I need I need assistance I need
assistance oh uhoh oh that sounds bad
okay hold on hold on the timing we're
just going to fly away it's probably
going to fly away uh let's hide in the
house okay
yeah oh no is it did it shoot the farm I
wonder oh we can check on the damage
later yeah should be fine should be fine
my bow it's okay it's okay I only have
like two arrows I would probably I don't
know if I would have hit
it surely it's fine see hear sticker and
go away yeah you can go AFK because
you're safe in here
oh yeah all right I'll be
back you can skip the Hoppers and use
chest as bottom you only need that is
what I've heard oh maybe to Grant the
mobs yeah I guess so the chests will
pick it up right anyway Hoppers is just
more
convenient Ponda is
free at one Panda what about the
others they look
fine I think it's gone okay I was going
to say sorry I I don't even know how
much longer I'll really play because
maybe you have noticed I
have I'm feeling so good right
[Music]
now actually it's like it goes up and
down and up and
down uh oh oh dear oh dear oh dear no
the Potion No the potion make
no um I'll be
um giving cie a little bit more company
for a little bit longer but then I'll
probably dip soon as
well I think maybe you think it was a
salmon I don't know could it be so
delayed because it's been like 24 hours
since I ate the salmon but I was
thinking that too like was it the salmon
after all it didn't smell weird and it
didn't taste
weird but maybe it was like really like
on the brink of being good and bad and
then yeah I don't
know oh I got the stand okay maybe
[Music]
salmonella that's my dinner for today
though the second serving is my dinner
for today but I'll just eat the salad
and the potatoes because I have plenty
of it just don't pick up items
automatically you need Hoppers to get
items chest without you have well I mean
when we're standing there we'll pick it
up anyway right but it will be a lot of
trash I I want to you know get more iron
again and fix that but it's how much
iron did we already waste on that it's
kind of
sad can we not make a two Hopper version
instead of a four Hopper version replant
the sugar cane first
y I need some more one more piece of of
dirt right
somewhere there must be
dirt careful there's holes
everywhere but yeah I I want to I want
to play along and I want to play
energetically but today something's
wrong with my tummy and I feel like
wobbly when I when I'm starting to feel
it feels wobbly doesn't feel nice and
and I feel
[Music]
weak but the cats came to support me
they were worried about me it's so cute
having pets as emotional support it's so
nice it's the only oh oh does it need
space it's the only emotions support I
have at
home thank you Kos
[Music]
wa this is actually I just realized how
awkward this is I feel like I'm talking
to my chat only but in reality there's
another chat who's listening to me
right hi hi de uh sorry for telling you
about my Tommy heart
sorry it's like somebody's like it's
like I'm in a phone conversation and
unknowingly someone else is in the phone
conversation that I don't know know
about they're listening in and I don't
even realize
it and the tacos are here too well who
knows how many who knows how many are
still here but the tacos the tacos have
a history
of invading kfp but I don't
mind it's it's
fun they are spies within cas
[Music]
I don't want to wear this Shield it's
annoying wow wow w w w I wonder if we
can maybe we'll go to the end the day
after tomorrow and tomorrow will be one
more day of grinding the Villager and
iron and like whatever arm and so
on I feel like we could
probably YOLO
it it might even you know be fine but
why not just play it a little bit
safer right what do you guys think we
could probably yellow it right but I do
want to I don't want
to you
know I'm going to ask the girls if they
all have time the day after tomorrow for
the
end and then we'll
see b b b
[Applause]
b yoloing could be fun H well it
definitely didn't want to YOLO it
tomorrow because if we were to go to the
end today you know I would have wanted
to advertise it that way but I think
it's nice to like separate it in
different episodes The Never at the end
even if the never wasn't really that
necessary I think it's still good to
keep those things separated and then you
know announc it like oh my God we're
going to the end we're going to do it
final episode it's lady Ender Dragon
would be a waste if we wouldn't do it
like that in my opinion
yeah the first time y'all fought on the
server was already yolow didn't we at
least have like a full set of diamond
armor and I think we are decently
prepped because I feel like
Ena like very much uh
you know was very into preparing
us like making potions and
stuff is there any more holes oh hi KO
hi sorry my cats were just they were
just really
cute understandable I I know how that
feels ghost cat was sitting on the the
corner of the sink and I was like all
right I have to pet you for 5 minutes it
can't be helped understandable can't be
helped I wonder if many apples dropped
oo apples apples apples app Che apple
apple check no nothing all right that's
okay no problem hey the trees are
growing oh this broke why did this break
what the hell maybe I should try doing
some quests I feel bad I haven't been
doing a lot of quests and no apples are
good to
have yeah I figure once we get 25 that's
like one big thing off the checklist
right are you not tired by the way cie
not really damn really and then I'm
going to be up until like 1:00 a.m. and
I have a recording today and then two
other streams so it's a busy day I got
to be Ganky girl be G it's a busy time
but you can keep that reveal stream
short no oh yeah it'll be quick it'll be
like hour two hours or
so how I haven't just chatted with the
fans in a while yeah I I I told
everybody about my tummy hord oh no
we're suspecting the salmon that I ate
because it was expired and I cooked it
anyway no but it was only one day
expired and it tasted and smelled fine
so I don't know uh who could say I mean
I don't know I I I'm always worried
about that because I've been watching
especially when I was recovering from my
knee surgery I was watching a lot of
those uh videos where it was like
documentaries um or not really
documentaries but you know internet
videos where it's like this guy only ate
vitamin gummies for 10 days here's what
happened to his organs you know stuff
like that they do a lot about people
that eat like this person ate pasta that
was sitting out for one day this is how
she died yeah yeah yeah I I watched a
few of those too actually yeah yeah kind
of got into that hole for a while don't
risk it guys don't risk it this guy ate
gas station Sushi this is what happened
to his room oh don't trust gas station
Sushi yo what you doing what are you
doing it's already bad enough in regular
regular old restaurants that you find
Rand in Japanese you called that
jigo
jig jigu like your own fault oh my God
yeah that sounds about right okay it's
convenient I just realized for the blast
furnace I need iron as well so I'm just
going to mine I'm just going to
mine you may say the gas station Sushi
is is cheaper than uh than than regular
like nice restaurant sushi in America
but if you come to and you eat sushi the
sushi here the good sushi will be
cheaper than your gas station Sushi
say so come over here yeah if only I
like sushi then I would totally eat it
all the time you're not much of a fish
person are you if it's I mean I don't
like seaweed that much either but you
know there's like a kind of like a
Korean version of uh Sushi do you know
it it's called I think it's yeah I love
that I kind of want it for lunch that
one is wrapped in seaweed 2
and I can kind of
like ignore the seaweed because I really
like Kimba because it's with like
veggies and stuff oh yeah yeah yeah it's
yum yeah kind of tastes like the ocean
with the the seaweed I get
you I kind of don't notice anymore but
yeah I know what you mean oh
yeah stick if these ones leaning off the
side have apples I'm going to be so
upset got to make got to extend the
platform oh yeah well I think I think
the forest is all right on my end the
forest is in okay shape and
amount so why did this why did this
happen why did this
happen can't do it here or what I'll
just put it in the frood
[Music]
chest
okay wow I'm mining I have a workmate
who fell really sick after eating sushi
that was being served at work just
because it wasn't properly refrigerated
ra is dangerous yeah yeah yeah proper
Refrigeration is really important I feel
like I may have broken
the we uh the cooling chain in German we
say cool cool cool C cooling chain for
like cool C the cooling chain yeah you
know what I mean like the with the
cooling chain I mean like you know when
you transport food for example from the
factory to a restaurant and then it has
to be cool in the in the in the car and
so on as well so that the cooling Chade
is not being interrupted yeah so I feel
like when I got the salmon from the um
from the hellofresh box I left out the
hellofresh box for a little bit too long
but generally there's ice in there to
keep the fish cool but I when I when I
took it out I felt like it was actually
not that cool like the ice was not
really nicely placed so maybe the fish
wasn't being being cooled properly so
that could have also added to
it I could still know that's a
lawsuit that's a lawsuit I can't really
prove it and it's okay I'll survive I'll
be fine I know you like the hellofresh
stuff so well yeah sponsor you wait do
we still have a diamond pickaxe
somewhere um someone had it at some
point right I'm not sure I have it still
I just can't see cuz the inventory is so
full oh that'll do it gws
thanks hope you feel
better let's see Co me to infinish it
sounds so
similar come on come on come
on
who um yum
need more tools stone tools are the best
though cuz we get lots of
stone where's my C Stone oh we
go okay sorry I haven't been organizing
I've been on an Apple Mission it's okay
all right I'll see if I can do a little
organization real
quick
okay always in the market for more
Cobblestone okay by the way chat I did
not watch the new season's first episode
yet of gamer uh not gameer of Thrones
House of the Dragon didn't watch Dragon
I knew you do that maybe I'll watch it
today before I go to
sleep oh yeah does kfp are they also
watching along with you I mean I think a
lot of my viewers watch it
yeah but maybe not House of the darg
dragon dragon these not oh my God I
really don't like these kind of jokes
but it's like this culture is making me
say them I get you it's same happened to
me it's
okay it's going to happen I I tried so
hard to resist for the longest time you
know we all try to resist and then some
of us are weak and we fail yeah that's
okay we're too weak for this
environment trying to get stronger too
easily influence you got to resist those
silly
jokes oh well ask oh yeah I was I was
wondering if um since Kar is such a
Minecraft Master if she knew anything
about coblin
D she's already seen that clip hasn't
she dang it I mean I don't know if I saw
a clip but I know what you're you know I
know what you're getting to okay I'm
sure you didn't see a clip all right
yeah whatever cobbling
these
[Music]
nud damn she said it it was funny the
first time only and only about 50 %
funny what's this chest it seems kind of
like a mess over here which one oh uh
someone just started throwing random
things in there so I've been slowly
trying to I don't know I don't know what
they were going for in there not even
me not even me it's another sorting
chest now uh yeah yeah so I have a
couple
projects here couple different couple
side quests yeah little side quests my
own personal ones
but the apple one I'm excited about
because I'm like ah yes we really need
this oh yeah we do we do it's going to
be really helpful especially cuz I don't
know if we can really get like proper
armor and all of that and weapons for
all of us but yeah the apples will help
keep us strong and healthy I hope
so that's why I'm gathering them so
let's see all right I'll do a little
more
organizing were you able to change the
villagers uh thing H not yet because I
need iron for the work station for him
okay gotcha well if you want to keep
mining for a bit I've just emptied the
chest thank you very
very
yeah another
[Music]
nugget let's
see feel like I saw spider weip
[Music]
somewhere somewhere for sure oh well now
they're going
here can we plant more sugar cane for
the books H Kelly while you're waiting
for the apples to drop you could also
make another Farm next to the trees for
sugar cane in oh that's a good idea how
do you plant it you stick it in the
ground yeah dirt blocks and then it
doesn't even have to be like you know
properly made with a hole as far as I
can tell but it has to has water around
it okay water around it next to water
it's probably like with the weed right
that it needs um one block of water and
then you can place four fields of sugar
cane around it right in all directions
probably same with
wheat
soce yeah in any case if you get started
there's like two pieces of sugar cane
for uh that that you can use in the food
box okay sure but no pressure If you
don't I'd like to once I can figure out
how to do it you already have so you
know my brain's really small that's okay
uh sugar needs a block to touch oh it
always needs to touch water okay so H it
needs like you could do like rows of
[Music]
water you could do rows of water and
then yeah the sugar cane always has to
touch the block of water like be right
next to it oh I see Dam why why couldn't
you have been a villager why do you got
to be a
merchant so close so close get out of
there get out of there always
fing water
move you left you do it I'm right here
not you oh but as long as you're here
I'm also
happy it's good so I was going to put
the water in this trench may not
alone
yeah okay I think he's I think he's
[Applause]
gone oh and okay um I'm going to bring
up the topics that I couldn't bring up
when it was so crowded but Austria lost
against France of course 0 to one but
that's okay apparent I wasn't actually
watching chat you might think I was
watching but I I was taking a
nap and apparently Austria wasn't doing
so badly yeah they played really well
well let's go I'm proud that's good to
hear yeah cuz they always had this
reputation that they that a sucks at
football you could see the diagonal yeah
but wow that's cool they were playing
aggressively and they had the ball like
50% of the time
apparently and they were not annihilated
you know with like five to zero or so so
that's
good so maybe we have a chance in the
other
matches
congrats key sorry it's like so
unrelated to you probably did you fall
who did that what did you fall who
pushed me girl no it was the panda
probably wait is there a hole where's a
hole where' you no someone pushed
me wait where I fell right oh a spider
no why did that spawn what where is the
spider did it fall down too yeah and now
it's under where did that come from God
damn it that is
annoying away with you lit up enough let
me light up some
more where where exactly where you in
that moment I was right where I'm making
the what you call it I was going to get
rid of these diagonal blocks just save
blocks
but let's see that's
fine around the
aquarium I see well let's see how
about find more dirt blocks does it need
to be dirt or can it be any rocks or any
kind of whatever to put the water sorry
sorry bra can you ask the question again
my brain was
like oh that's okay so I'm trying to
make the Tren like a ditch for the water
does it need to be dirt around it or can
it be whatever should be dirt around it
so that you could plant the sugarcane
yeah but the the block where the water
is basically on top of can be anything
oh okay oh yeah sand also works for uh
sugarcane if you want to use sand
instead but the sand will fall down if
you have nothing underneath yeah that's
the thing all right well I found dirt so
we're good okay all right now we won't
fall again
at least I wasn't holding anything
important I'm going to go with you for a
moment to see if you need
help oh this is good already yeah yeah
you're getting it this kind of thing
you're getting the point nice
yeah cool I'm going put water in there
exactly you know how to do that like cuz
you'll need to like probably fill up
like even when it looks that like
everything's filled it's often a coup
yeah I'll help you out with that I was
building an onent at a certain point so
I kind of get it yeah oh okay the
experience is
helping this will be the main field and
then we'll put like some regular Stone
around it or something you want
to put one more block here oh yeah
definitely let's
see there we go just round it out yay
[Music]
nice okay yeah I like your PRS you like
my pranks thank you I love
them thank you so much for enjoying
them sometimes it's just a it's a force
of habit I guess at this point you
[Music]
know can't be
helped I need a prun emote you guys are
right oh yeah I don't think I was pling
like if it wasn't for you really you
taught me how to
clink yeah okay I think the first trench
is filled up all right cool and then
around that I'm just going to I'm going
to need to put a fence cuz I don't want
to fall I know I'll fall well maybe we
we could make another
line oh yeah sure we could do that one
more one more one more one more I like
this is fine I so like another line on
this side yeah like uh this this block
here you could uh
no actually this one yeah the furthest
one out because we can have we can have
um we can have sugar cane here and then
we can have sugar canane here cuz this
one will touch the water over here uhhuh
oh I see Goa so we should turn which one
um let's see and I'll bring some we
should turn which one into it so the the
line all the way here that I'm standing
on we should turn it into a trench oh
wait wait it's the furthest on the edge
that should become a trench and then you
make another line of dirt blocks there
okay yeah I'll just need more dirt we
just got to get more dirt blocks and
once we have more of
those we can do anything wait does it
need why does SU can be too wide oh is
it because there's no
water
yet ah so you really literally can't
plant it even okay I got 24 dirt
H
okay although water wait before you
place that
dirt mhm um I have an idea we got to
make it one more block wider but it's it
it won't be dirt I just want to place
torches in between oh sure
umbe it can be Cobblestone under the
okay cool then we'll put Cobblestone
under where the the water trenches mhm
mhm cobbly Stone Cobin
D okay so I was
thinking why not
make that's where you want to set up the
Torches that's pretty cute yeah and then
the next line next to that will be dirt
again and then water and then dirt yeah
sure okay sounds good beautiful
okay we'll do that right over here right
next dirt okay wait did
wait what what yeah ah wait no wait I
did it wrong I think I did it wrong it's
okay oh yeah it just needs to be moved
one over I guess huh yeah uh I mean this
could work too right if this if this
line becomes water water yeah that was
water no get rid of the the Terra Cotta
blocks again come on hold on I'm going
to get rid of the dir over here just so
you know I'm here so don't maybe don't
hit him
yet is that a merchant it's yeah it's a
merchant but like why'd he come here I
wish he was a villager not a
merchant oh what the heck would have
been more
useful ah dang it he should invite his
friends over that are regular
dudes
yeah damn it that's okay okay so now
that we did that
yeah this will be water then then dirt
again no no no I'm going to do it proper
okay okay what I'm what I'm getting rid
of now is going to be the Terracotta
path okay just hold on to that dirt cuz
we'll need it yeah I'm I'm picking oh
not again who
whoa no did you
what was that a spider or was that
no it was just me walking backwards all
right we really need to build some
freaking fences how many times have I
fall I should I should extend the floor
down there before
anything
yeah okay you wouldn't think that I
would be holding shift so good at it
when I'm focused on something I just
forget that's fine all right well it's I
had made new tools so that's good
but uh now our dirt's gone so I got to
find more dirt
I feel like in some chest there should
still be like randomly a chunk of
[Music]
dirt damn it son of a
gun you can change your settings to
toggle Crouch so you don't have to hold
it that's what that's right it's on
toggle it's on toggle
dummy yeah to be like that dirt Quest
right seven dirt seven dirt is good I've
got a
few cool and
then for the trenches we'll just use
Cobblestone or regular Stone too that
should be fine I'll go underground and
make you a a floor down there thanks
yeah pay attention to your surroundings
more pay attention it's
fine it's content Kelly oh God it's not
the kind of content I
make okay so here's what we'll do um
hi love you what are you looking at cat
what are you looking at oh hi guess I
could have gone down that
way oh o kind of hard to reach
not oh you're you're kind of making a
floor too there yeah just cuz I Was
preparing for the trench over
here
okay there we go
that
work Takami building time
y it's going to be great and then we can
make paper which means we can make
books yeah books and and we can make
more Foods we have more options with
food kind of hard to
reach Shi
I don't want to get rid of this
now okay
[Music]
maybe what if we did did
these okay and I think you have more
dirt so I'll leave that to you mhm yeah
leave the rest to me you can continue
with like apples or so app just sorting
mining it looks like it's coming
together this what this Panda doing here
you trying to eat my trees little dude
oh I'm underneath let's go how dare
you get out of my
Fields bless you sneeze thank
you thank you very much at least I'm not
holding any apples
yeah o
I wish he sold cool
stuff those Merchants they kind of never
do it's so lame E I was going to say how
do we level them up but if he never s
cool stuff they don't level up now not
as far as I
know no y your merch sucks my
dude the only cool thing about them is
that they normally come with
alpacas ah yeah but that guy is alpaca
list so yeah kind of no worth
huh no
alpacas no alpacas really no
[\h__\h] you know that image of course I
do what do you take me for silly I've
been on the internet for a little
bit it's just you know I'm behind the
times at the end of the day my internet
Days Are Over My like grand time of
being on the internet all the time is
kind of P at a certain point
it's hard to believe but it's true I
feel like now is our prime time it
should be right but it's our job after
all yeah well that's the thing is that
I'm mostly on the internet for my job
now
but I don't know if I if I didn't have
to be I don't know if I would be to be
honest like not very much not as much as
I used to be I was a quite a meme Lord
back in the day pretty intense M Lord
really all those memes are stale now no
one cares about them
yeah I don't know any of the new
stuff what blocks could I
use
diorite and the
side beautiful oh you're cobbling these
cobbles no time for meme homework
exactly also things on the internet just
they make me laugh a lot less than they
they used to I feel yeah maybe it's just
the time changing or too too grown up
too adult to mature ah I don't want that
yada people want to stay children
children want to stay children want to
get adult hood into their hands and we
want to get back to Childhood
times that that is how it feels often
yeah I will say yeah I don't know I also
feel like my brand of humor is extremely
niche in the first place so it's like
hard to make me laugh these days I don't
know I don't think so ah it's pretty
Niche what would you describe your humor
as it's like it's so specific it's like
a very specific kind
of humor some of it is also the the
darker the darker part as well is just I
can't really I can't share
it I don't want to is that [\h__\h] up
well you know I feel like the dead beats
don't want me to say things that are too
self degenerating or too like morbid oh
and that kind of stuff well but morbid I
mean you're literally Grim Reaper and
they're skeletons how can you not be
morbid out of the edge see here we go
it's a perfect
example oh yeah it's fine it's better to
hold back a little bit and don't be too
degenerate
I'm making you a second floor under the
forest
too a thank you no accidents no
more oh and I was going to make a second
floor under the PPP p a mmm it's
mmm I really was the Joker all along
yeah you wouldn't get it I wouldn't get
only watched that one
Joker mov what was it again is it the
super serious movie with Walky and
Phoenix Chad we didn't we watch it
together actually chat help me out I
don't know which one was
it Joker that's a title literally Joker
okay that's the one I watched 2019 one
yeah what do you think of it I loved it
I think yeah but that's only like a tiny
bit of of the Joker Batman Paradise
he Woodson's
back yeah I don't even think the Batman
appears in that movie where's where's my
question mark I
here oh my God it's
the maybe she just wants to to work on
work on it like on her own the b or
something can you get out of my business
sir she couldn't get that Minecraft out
of her mind she couldn't stop thinking
about it
yeah it's the Minecraft brain
RT a once you get into it it really is
pretty fun yeah that's why I felt like
so sad when you were like I'm not going
to play Minecraft again because I was
like I feel like you can definitely
learn to like it you just need to get
into it the proper way without suffering
too much you know like cuz that's going
to give you a bad experience mhm but I
feel like have a good time with it
yeah I'm having
fun good yeah I just had to like relax I
feel like I was I got too stressed out
by it which is the opposite effect that
it should have right yeah
exactra you put too much pressure on
yourself on
maybe I don't know I just know I can do
better where are the apples there's like
this one corner of really tall trees I
know we're going to get an Apple out of
this but I don't want to climb up that
high
mulai you know I will probably fall down
why do you drink a potion of invis why'
you drink that invisibility potion yeah
CU it's getting dark that's what they do
a
it's their defense mechanism yeah like
turtles they hide away in their
shell I get
it it's the turtle
hurdle Turtle hle if you want to hurt a
turtle you got to get over the turtle
hurdle whoa whoa whoa whoa you're very
silly whoa a silly person that was quite
it is dark can hear yo Monsters can't
spawn in trees right and I mean if it's
too dark there then yeah oh o I mean not
in the tree around the tree oh oh around
the tree yeah but it should be
relatively lit up
there cuz I am like deep in this tree in
this tree's guts right now
oh then you're probably
fine oh yeah digging around
yeah yeah yeah
yeah why would I want to hurt Turtle
exactly don't hurt the
turtle turtle is already being bullied
by colon
Senpai SM small t
house
house no no Senai that's not
funny I mean maybe to maybe to us it is
but not to the turtles that's not fair
Turtle had it come
in turtle is trying
okay oh this looks like a
watermelon this is nice terracotta and
I'm using it for stuff like this but if
this was a normal Minecraft playthrough
I'd never have so many of these kind of
blocks ever like especially the
beautiful terracotta with the patterns
damn yeah I feel like that's it's so odd
that they show up like this I know and
now we have so many of them we're using
it for stuff like this yeah cuz those
don't just show up in the randomly in
the world you have to make them right oh
no no no they they do show up I think in
like in the
[Music]
desert I thought that was just like
regular like one color terracotta shows
up in temples but not the fancy
patterned ones I thought you had to make
those it's like no it's like
a what is it a desert some kind of
dungeon in in the desert so to say right
right guys in some starches yes but not
a lot yeah there's not many of them oh
and the Ocean Floors too yeah mhm oh
interesting but I guess maybe you you
can also make it yourself
yeah many ways to get it but I feel like
normally it's it's too much of a
b not all but they're so Prett I'm just
go make some golden apples to appease
myself okay we have a bunch of gold we
have plenty of gold
thankfully for days the choice of blocks
to use is getting smaller and
smaller I think that's a good sign it
means the stuff that we're we're mining
has a use mhm we have 11 golden apples
so far oh getting
closer that's pretty good H getting the
work
done nice and 35 diamonds so far it
would be nice if we had more
but it's good I'll put some of these
terra cotta blocks we bless thank
[Music]
you
whoa you can roll your tongue fine huh
yeah but not the way I want to ah oh
should be's specific way you want to do
it yeah the Japanese
way that
thing can't
okay
yeah does take practice I feel it would
help my P by impression cuz she does it
a lot well she does
she goes
[Music]
like like that
yeah the tongue
roles it sounds like she's rolling her
G's I watched her play and NAA one of
those like you know you know all those
games like the one where you need to get
up high what was that one called again
climb no only up or yeah only up like
all those kind of games
the one with the stone
Rec yeah and I have no sword I saw her
play one yesterday today yesterday
mayday mayday that looked kind of
medieval that one looked oh yeah
actually kind of fun Watson watch
out maybe I'll play it are you Watson oh
yeah Al too that's ala four that's the
name of the game oh ala four yeah oh
yeah I've heard of that game before Oh
yeah she was throwing chickens I was
like hey
yo you have chicken in your back your
backpack so cute oh and then there's
Medieval music
so that does sound kind of fun it does
look like a fun
game I was like H well I I have too many
other games I need to play right now but
it did look
fun yum yum
potato potato
you know what's the best way to make
potatoes what's the best way in your
opinion okay explain it to me you got to
line it up for me lay out so you you
peel the potatoes then you cook them
once they're done cooking you um like
kind of melt butter in the same pot like
you pour the water out and then you put
the butter in and once they're all
buttery and all that you add parsley or
you can do it at the same time I guess
chopped up parsley like a lot of it so
it's like buttered parsley potatoes it's
so good it's what you normally eat with
schnitzel wow that sounds really yum
potatoes are
yum potato do you think potatoes are
vegetables Kiara of course they
are but they're like starches what about
corn is that a vegetable too of course
it
is huh okay but like if you eat it it's
not like good for you three apples in
one tree oh let's go Sor that's a good
apple tree that's a really good apple
tree I don't want to cut it down I grow
some
more flavored mashed potato packets yeah
it's not as fun as cooking though
right corn is a green but it's still a
vegetable no what the hell I mean I
guess so I guess the way that I think
about it is vegetables are are like
healthy things that are like good for
you right potatoes are not really good
for you I mean it maybe some part of it
is not good but still isn't it like
mostly
good um not not really I mean I it's a
starch like it's all carbs like if you
eat a ton of potatoes you get fat you
know I
mean but like if you eat when I think of
vegetables it's like those aren't things
that really make you fat but do they
have no vitamins
I don't know do potatoes have vitamins
in them guys and fiber yeah fiber
there's certainly good parts about it
right you just got to not deep fry them
oh I see I like grilled
potatoes yes yum yum yum yum oh the
Skins do the Skins have vitamins in them
oh I see yeah cuz I kind of been I don't
know I've been avoiding potatoes these
days cuz I'm like oh yeah these aren't
good for you so potatoes do not have
fiber okay but they got other stuff like
nutrients
sweet potatoes are better that I did
know my trainer told me sweet potatoes
are nice but I don't like cooking with
them because they're usually like so big
and
so oh yeah so big and so hard and it's
like really hard to cut through them you
know to chop them
up I don't want to say it but okay it's
it's just how it is okay it's how how
sweet potatoes are no it's true
definitely they're so yummy though I
sweet potato fries those are
I thought I heard
something are you okay yeah yeah should
be
[Music]
good that's fine was very scary did oh
am I still here did somebody end up uh
the lava I wonder I might go to the
nether really quickly oh yeah it is like
right there
yeah going to go grab some lava buckets
for uh efficient
furnace
cooking nice idea you can make a blast
furnace now oh my god let's go I guess
so yeah we have enough for that yeah cuz
we have so many emeralds so oh wait wait
I should oh there's like horses and
donkeys in here in the nether
oh yeah they kind of wandered in there
didn't
they
a let me just bring this just in case oh
I already wear
it can't you just make armor normally at
a crafting table though or is it
Enchanted armor you want to make um or
something like that um well the thing is
we have I think more emeralds than we
have diamonds so if we make our own
diamond armor we're going to use up all
the diamonds and maybe not have enough
and also BL furn yeah and if you if you
level them up enough then they might
have uh armor that's already Enchanted
and might be some cool stuff I get it
interesting it's a bit more this is all
new stuff to me
so you're learning you're learning you
can use emeralds instead of diamonds
yeah yeah basically yeah and that's
pretty much the only use we have for um
emeralds you
know oh can I get yeah exactly cuz you
know we're not really we haven't been
very lucky with merchants and stuff do I
have
go
[Music]
D there's still some over there oh
apple
apple got the four apples that's pretty
good there's another one damn
it living on the edge for these
apples there's so much lava here but
it's like so
far I got it
M oh nice it's working there's another
one up there but they're going away so
that's good the Apple will fall
down new
axe
okay thank you physics
[Music]
Gast
CH gas
g somewhere y don't bring him in here
he's too fat to fit through don't worry
but he might just spawn in our world on
its own he's a chunky guy you never
know okay okay okay oh wait oh no no
got two apples nice I bet we we'll have
this apple quest done by the time that
oh it's over today's session is over
y y
indeed get rid of this and then plant a
bunch of more
trees wait how am I going to get down I
guess I'll mine my way
[Music]
down oh yeah you're in the nether right
yeah oh am I up there
[Music]
okay need more
wood can't reach there it
is zombie
do zombie John
y he's looking for
you I'm scared that suddenly a lava
pocket will open up there oh yeah that
would not be optimal oh nice I think
they're
disappearing
yeah touch it lava touch it the lava
touch can't reach still don't touch it
don't touch it I want to touch it you
want m
can't
reach should I rather go to the bottom
what do you think
[Music]
guys
y
y it
it bottom
better this might not be a good way of
doing things here let me mine my way
down which one
is that one that one that one
okay the things I do for the furnace and
for efficiency I mean it's going to be
super helpful
though oh no I almost
died hey but you didn't though that's
what's important hey
let's go she lives I like the the
feeling of being almost
dead it's a nice
kick oh yeah oh yeah oh
[Music]
yeah all right I I guess I'll try to go
to the
bottom that's actually really funny hold
on
[Music]
oh oh this is the most effective way to
search her apples go that way what what
what way have you found to just Spam a
sapling with bone meal and then quickly
cut down the tree and then let the
leaves fall away M instead of letting
the tree grow to be super super tall mhm
and it's kind of annoying to chop down
and yeah m
hold on I think this is the best
way we found out what Callie's humor is
small tree no you know what I think I
think I know how I can maybe describe my
sense of humor but you probably might
still not understand it I was thinking
in like a comparison to like a wine or
something like that you know I kind of
like like uh oh yeah dry and dark yeah
dry and dark yep but I feel like I don't
know
it's kind of hard to express sometimes
it's very
specific
hilarious I can't explain why certain
things make me
laugh it's
odd okay tastes better with time
maybe but how do I build down when
there's nothing you know for me to make
a stare
guys maybe if I drop a [\h__\h] ton of Soul
Sand or
sand and then like stack it I know go
further further
where you don't you need sand yeah
that's what I was just
thinking mhm and
then shovel it away is this even worth
it right now this
effort dig into my Mountains to form
stair
yeah o o o
Callie o o
o oh he's zipping a rep please sir don't
I want nothing to do with you sir
please just use
coal but coal we also need for the
Torches but yeah okay it doesn't take
priority right now never mind
then oh God
oh wasn't this more before I guess why
you doing that am probably took isn't
that am's roommate uh
maybe me do some
sorting grinding a she's probably making
Hoppers right now let me see there's so
much Redstone oh my
God there's a lot of redstone falling in
here okay I'll do some organization
then oh my definitely is uh working on
fixing
[Music]
it that
fox that fox is going to steal
things yeah it's obsidian now I think
it's a good idea cuz like of course if
it's like fixed in a way that we don't
um
uh you know have any explosions anymore
then we don't need it anymore but you
don't know what will happen until the
point that we get to that point you know
you know you know what I mean oh true
enough so better to put some obsidian
there now so that it doesn't all fall
apart again yeah yeah much
agreed what am I doing what I I guess I
was trying to extend the bottom floor
vage oh this is the random chest I
almost forgot okay oh hey there's one
lava bucket I can sort
it I can sort this
chest
nice
cool guess that
works oh oh oh
[Music]
don't do
that all
righty what the Army
doing wait I got five oh oh wait am I
might be needing them forgot to put them
I didn't intend to take them I don't
know if am is watching this stream or
now and she's like oh
iron was my attention it's back in the
box now eight pieces of
iron dang
it okay oh quartz can go in there too
and then make a BL furnace no I don't
want to like in case she's like doing
you know that work over there and fixing
the Hoppers and stuff I don't want to
take the iron that we have
now once she's gone I can look at how
much iron we
have I see you Kelly you see me oh not
anymore now you're too
far oh I see you again hi making trees
happen
hello so close yet so far give me
Apple oh yeah we don't have drip Stone
no no we don't guys this version is very
very
old I don't know why this version had to
be so old they should update it
m is there a reason why maybe they can't
yeah it's got to be like the mod and I
think there's
other one block mods that also work with
newer versions and it's just the the
version that they got I don't know oh
but it's got to do something to do with
that oh yeah that's right 30 minutes
from now guys I got to do the reveal oh
yeah
so
2.0 yep I like it a lot I don't know if
else will but I like it a lot I liked it
you liked it there's a lot of movement
mhm and I don't think it's too different
where it's weird or anything like that I
don't know yeah I'm excited guys please
pay attention to her cheeks I think the
cheeks are cute my cheeks look at them
now and then look at them later
ah oh yeah actually I'm interested that
you say that I'm going to look
too what if you saw someone else in the
distance on their own Islands doing one
block that would be really cute actually
a I'd love that yeah like an
mm exactly I'll make these apples
golden that' be cool I think so
too but like then if they get too close
it's like whoa there buddy what's going
on getting a little too close for
comfort I just want to see them from far
away that's
all almost reached it we now have 47
diamonds that's pretty
good
okay wow does that also do we still have
iron blocks that we didn't unleash I
think that there's uh only one there's
only one so I didn't even bother putting
it in the
oven don't worry about the Torches guys
don't worry
oh boy I think we're at 18 golden apples
now
y we're almost done thanks for the
membership gift thank
[Music]
you tell your cheeks to stop looking at
me stop looking at my cheeks how about
that you can stop looking at my
cheeks gr dang you
[\h__\h] okay no blocks it's incredible
how many blocks are necessary for all
these things
[Music]
man so many blocks but we only have one
block well we started from that's the
amazing thing is like all this came from
one block you believe it I really love
it that's why like all these buildings
they just they feel really
special
mhm yeah we built it all together I mean
you definitely carried I will say you
built a lot of Stuff n no I put a lot of
like unimportant
stuff yeah only a few important things
only a
few quite a few but it's exciting
excited to see we can beat the Ender
Dragon oh we
can think so we're all adding to it and
with all our Mighty power we're going to
do
it can I make slabs and all of this oh
yeah
apples I know you want to grow apples
just gave me three from One Tree I know
you're there don't you lie to
me this Panda really likes this area I
don't know what's going
with why the ingame hunger is hitting me
uhoh
um we have a decent amount of food
though this time that's as long as I'm
like out here I just keep on refilling
my um my bowl with mushroom soup because
that's endless doesn't take up anything
and endless mushroom soup it's easy yeah
at least ingame kada likes mushroom soup
only in game though right you're just
not a mushroom person huh I like I think
I like mushroom sauce like if it if it
doesn't have any mushroom bits in
it it's just like is the texture you
don't like M the texture yeah but also
partially the flavor but with mushroom
sauce like for example for a steak or so
I think it's not as intense and it's
like a good balance so with that I can
tolerate it I feel like mushrooms don't
really have a taste to me I just like it
cuz the texture is like soft and I think
they do also they freak me out like when
I I did cook with them sometimes even
with hellofresh and then I feel like
they look like very terrifying like a
horror horror like a a vegetable out of
a horror
movie well there are quite a few
mushrooms in horror movies I feel like
the bottom mushrooms the bottom of a cap
you know those like it looks like a
filter like a air filter or something
yeah like to run it over my tongue
e what it's like a fun texture like
little flaps
yeah what when I wash a mushroom it gets
all slimy I don't get it why does it get
so slimy and
weird okay well I don't what are you
looking at dog I mean I guess I get what
you're saying I actually do have a bit
of uh trauma that affects how I taste
mushrooms so mushrooms um always taste
like pool water to me um and the reason
yeah but I kind of tolerate it the
reason is because um I was at a cookout
with a bunch of my friends one time um
and it was it was like we were really
excited to all cook together oh no we
washed them yeah they were all like they
were stuffed mushrooms they were
delicious and then someone was bringing
them to us and they tripped and fell
next to the pool and they hit the pool
water and then we were we felt really
bad so we're like oh we're going to eat
them anyway and so we ate a couple of
them and we didn't get sick and die but
you know they always taste like pool
water to me because of it what yeah
washed them in the
pool chlorine like you're still ass
them with it I guess yeah I think I
probably always will cuz it's a core
memory for me
but
yeah I'd never eat them again if they
were soaked in pool water but you know
when I taste them I just that lingering
memory you know yo where my apples at I
feel like we should we're due for an
apple now what's going on
here okay going on got to run for one
more small batch of blocks but then
more bone
meal okay yeah it's not worse than
bathtub Pizza in my
opinion
yeah the bathtu pizza yeah dang it need
an
axe yeah another core memory
[Music]
need to drink hey you just
got yeah everyone can do if you believe
in
yourself okay more blocks more blocks
okay more blocks what could I take this
time how about these that doesn't sound
good
so
nice I want to help I'm in mining I'm
almost done with my P mining Oh you mean
in the the one block right yeah she's
she's been mining probably looking for
iron oh I should clean up over there
okay I'll organize oh she would probably
appreciate
that
yeah C believe am she felt like N I
can't leave it like that after all
when she was the one who was like ah do
we even need the this do we even need
it it's like once you have something
like that going you just can't can't get
it off your mind you know I can't leave
it like that did you forget about your
stream in 20 minutes no I did not forget
about my stream in 20 minutes I
didn't you guys got to calm down calm
down we'll do it we'll be there
soon there about constructions yeah
that's a good way to put
it all right food time food Time
Forgot man I want to eat some McDonald's
right now McDonald's why I feel like
that would heal my tummy H oh yeah you
think it would cleanse you yeah a nice
tummy cleanse with some
McDonald's I want to eat some really
salty potato fries
yeah that's like drunk food I guess but
you would I don't think you'd know
anything about that but yeah yeah I am I
guess it does the same kind of thing a a
an alcohol
virgin you've never had any at all at
any time I mean I've tried several
things cuz people are always like oh you
should try this you should try this I'm
sure you like this one oh this doesn't
taste like alcohol at all I'm like it it
tastes so much like alcohol to
me your pressure oops sorry elit sorry
I hurt
you n it's fine you don't need it yeah
so i' I've tried sever of things I've
tried wines I've tried um I don't know I
don't think I tried beer cuz I already
know by the smell that I'll hate it oh
yeah beer tastes like dish water I can
imagine that I know that if I like
really force myself which is probably
what a lot of teenagers like do they
force themselves to like drink it
because that's cool and then they'll
like work up the tolerance against it
and then they'll end up liking it or
they just get addicted to it or whatever
I don't know oh yeah but I haven't hit
that point yet so I still hate it and I
don't feel like forcing myself to you
know yeah it's not something you need in
your life you already know you don't
like it so no reason to force yourself
cuz honestly I've been saving money and
I've been saving sanity oh yeah better
for your health too oh I got a new music
piece
better for my health exactly I don't
have like you know like problems
with getting drunk and getting into an
accident or something like that or or
having crazy bar fights or [\h__\h] like
that y bar fights kind of pop off though
at least when you watch them yeah but I
get what you
mean yeah probably I mean really
actually it is for the better you don't
need the change of thing
yahua I think so too yeah
I think so I like this track this is a
Bop yeah Waffle House fights for example
they sound fun to watch but not fun to
be involved in I'll participate in yeah
I'll watch from
outside catch me outside how about
that you remember that I do a silly
time my first tequila shot I didn't like
it you
mean tequila sucks tequila I like the
song Tequila tequila
oh this is nice do we already have this
CD because it's really nice I really dig
this one it's cute this is
cute it makes me think of
shenanigans between all of
us oh yeah it's new we didn't have that
one nice new
Tunes cute
ow oh sand what
the me and am hurting each
other no no no no no infighting I'm
sorry you good we hurt each other it's
okay what is love baby don't hurt me
hurt me don't
hurt no more no more
trying to identify the right blocks but
I'm too
slow trying to be efficient taking your
time and shovel my way
through every day I'm
shuffling oh I wonder how much more oh
yeah we're still mining okay I'll try to
be
quicker what is not too much in here
right
now chest
oh who needs
that
okay more things to
organize okay I'll try to organize those
myself thanks oh my [\h__\h] got 50
memberships are you
crazy I got dropped to 50 too you guys
are super generous thank you so much
same person maybe who who is it
okii that's a different person but still
hay Big Ups to you big UPS Big Ups Big
Ups everybody for the memberships you
guys have been sending wow so generous
yeah in collabs I don't really I can't
really say thank you out loud all the
time but appreciate you very
[Music]
much so true what am I doing what am I
doing what am I doing
why are you standing on top you can't
have anything in this chest
sir don't you even think about
it nice all right our final inventory is
looking pretty good gosh those chickens
are popping off kiari gosh what do you
what are you feeding them I know I know
they will not shut up chickens need to
take their meds calm down nice oh 10
more let's
go let's go question mark stop walking
out cave people still no freaking apples
that's said you you can
leave not
allowed yeah yours are pretty good thank
you oh it's so crowded in here sh
make more chicken out the eggs eggs the
a little bit eggs eggs eggs eggs eggs
eggs EG eggs eggs eggs am I right
Kelly
yep eggs eggs eggs eggs eggs eggs eggs
she knows what she's talking
about hey hey can't open the chest if
you guys are there oh God there's so
many okay
um like I said you got to thin out the
herd survival of the
fittest the chicken with your
[Applause]
sword this way at least I possibly won't
hurt the small
ones
oh a a
phantom that was weird why is it appear
now I think I maybe came out of the one
block but burning already no
worries
bur chill Chad
chill you know this is how we
do this is how we do this is how
we this is how we do it oh two different
songs Katy Perry to what's that song
This is how we do it oh yeah I don't
know who sings it but I know it it's one
of those songs
that was 50 Cent
really that was 50 cent no way backst
street boys question
mark
maybe Montel Jordan okay that sounds
more like it cuz two people said
it
mon that's a Bob I need to listen to
that again
properly yeah and then sing it and cut
open Mor KY clearly wrote it ah yes more
famous bangers why are you guys standing
up there is this like survival in
Instinct oh my God it's kind of making
me
sad I feel
bad this really hurts my heart just
saying kfp I'm not doing this with like
an innocent life
lightweighted heart or so this hurts are
you killing them yeah cuz I I I
multiplied them and now I'm like taking
them down bringing them to
the yeah you got to thin out the numbers
I'm here to witness the slaughter oh
we're pretty much done do you see how
there's mostly only children still there
wait there was more than this
yeah I mean at least more grown ones
yeah oh my I see my new one
strong happy to supply more murder
weapons you ever need any just let me
know okay no you can't escape what about
me it's cuz he tried to escape I had to
kill him I had to do it understandable
oh the panda is on top of
everything cute okay it's bread
time oh yes C lots of bread can you
please stop with
the can have a sword no I have no way to
defend
myself we
could sleep hopefully he'll
disappear sleep might be a good idea I
think I have to stop actually playing I
got to stop playing yeah
possibly
yeah it's 2.0 time let's
go at long last the
reveal oh I'm nervous only a little
nervous though I hope you guys like app
sorry I should end it too and then right
into your reveal oh only if you want you
doing from the right right from The
First beginning like from the getg go no
I'll chat a little bit we will chat a
little bit okie dokie yeah don't worry
about it take your time Okie doie even
if you want to keep streaming I don't
mind no it's it's late anyway I should
end it anyway especially if I want to
get up for
jackbox oh true yeah boss party yeah
yeah Mo place it's still happening right
it's still happen I I
think I think all good all good we'll
see I just need to check something but
um but yeah thanks so much for watching
everyone and please yeah uh look forward
to it look forward to tonight I think uh
we'll update you if anything changes um
but I'm excited and yeah keep watching
our adventures one block Minecraft
things are really
getting in possibly another are do you
think we can stream Minecraft tomorrow
too yeah I can try to wake up let me see
um I wish they they weren't lining up
these recordings day after day but
that's okay I think I should still be
able to wake up for it I think I'll be
okay I'll let you know though okay yeah
maybe I might not stream F too don't
worry about it I I don't think we're
going to the end tomorrow so it's not
like the big important episode yeah
that's the big one that we got to
coordinate on when everybody
get in yeah okay well I'll see you guys
later bye kiaa bye dead beats see you
guys shortly and yeah I'll catch you
guys on the flip sidee you're welcome
goodbye goodbye
peace bye bye bye byebye byebye
byebye can you still hear me yeah but
I'm going to leave just saying like no
no like obviously uh I don't want to
like have have you have social pressure
or anything like that just write into
your own stream please okay I don't want
this to be awkward like why is she not
obviously you R into your own stream
okay just making it clear okay I I do I
appreciate that thank you very much just
saying the audience you know no need for
her to do that because she has her own
stream so a thank you that's sweet I
appreciate it I'll catch you later okay
yeah have fun bye-bye see you soon W
peace does that make sense what I just
said I don't I don't know I can can't
really put it in the right words but
it's like weird
expectations I think especially cuz like
we're collabing and someone's ending
earlier and then like the others red
into me so it's like oh she's got to do
it too no no she doesn't have to just
making it clear so nobody feels awkward
about it you know what I mean
[Applause]
oh big
slime I'm a
booger
who I rescu the
Army am
hero am Amed
Gosling got to get some gravel because I
have so many feathers I want to make
some arrows because we ran out of arrows
protect the armor T HX you're still
speaking in abbreviations even the sorry
was an
[Applause]
abbreviation don't you guys have two
Infinity balls uh I think only one or
actually yeah you're right I maybe can I
do we have another Infinity book then I
could put it on the p on the wow yeah
this one's ah this
one if we have another one then I shall
do
that SM flame looting sweeping Edge
forting no we don't but there you know
there's always a chance we get another
one yeah
I only got four Flint out of that
wow
wow I of those Shenanigans do I still
have
sticks
villager I don't know if she's listening
but I want to type
villager we can make
babies okay oh oh she's doing it okay I
leave it to she's she's better at this
stuff probably oh my God oh my God oh my
God oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my
God it's baby
time oh oh she's boating she's boating
well I'll push him ah wait I think wait
a I'll get rid of the blocks maybe cuz I
think you
can't get FR yeah it's
better oh he wants to ah he wants to go
into our bed ah ah you get stuck in
theat ah he stuck in the boat well the
bird is dancing he wanted to go to the
bed but got himself
stuck
lol party
parrot
no that what that's not
that's not what she wanted to
do I'm sure it's not I'm sure it's not
whose parot was that
oh wa we will find a new one maybe okay
a that's kind of too
tight wait I'll mind the way for
you I'm a did she just like
glitch
through the
block the
[\h__\h] glitch in The
Matrix thank God there's a platform
below
whoa I don't know where the blocks went
maybe they fell down
too so wait his job what's this job
again isn't this like
uh leather worker no what is what is
this oh same problem he might want to go
to the beds no no no stop
stop oh no he likes the other
beds is a blacksmith
wait make armor or weapon
both how's it going here oh he's
sleeping break
bed in a moment maybe oh okay but if we
sleep he's probably just going to walk
out immediately are you ready for that
Amy are you ready for
that okay he's chilling he's
chilling push push
push push there yeah
yeah here we
go learn with bread does he actually
follow bread like how animals follow
seeds and all that is that actually work
I don't think so but I'm ready to give
him bread once he's paired with the
other villager but I got to make an
entrance well thank God I put an
underground there as
well
uh M
Mia no no no I I would I would have
opened up
no just had to boat him inside a little
bit more oh he's still chilling here
actually oh wait I have a boat I have I
have boat I has boat uh
oh okay he's in the
boat wait now I'm scared that I'll
glitch for you I'm scared I'm scared
okay it's only when it's like really
tight I think
okay whoa I went for the m Matrix for a
[Music]
moment okay what do we do about this
entrance so that
they
can't
get Phantom
John what you doing
there why
[Music]
scar out the kitty cats aren't
you I don't have any arrows
anymore okay she's fixing
that okay wait let's see uh trap door
mhm iron doors ah and like a like a
uh oh what what iron door trap doors
above door okay that's more likely
okay a trap door a trap door trap
door trap door
okay
under under here how's this going to
work where's my door didn't I have a
door did it fall
down
huh under that one diagonal looking
block
interesting just checking if my door is
down here H it
is H um well I don't need that many
wheat seats
whatever wait I can just walk up there
I'm still using my water
elevator oh my God I'm so excited we got
two villagers today
yo y it's happening the only one more f
we need is like iron stuff but even even
with
that okay so we can walk through but
they can't like
this start harvesting sugarcane oh oh oh
oh oh yeah it's growing oh wait it's
actually not finished I wanted to finish
it ah so much to do so much to do ah
[Music]
well you know what so much to do for
like tomorrow for example
right I
shouldn't I don't I want to raid into
cie so I hope she's not like doing
anything
yet let me just let me just let me
just loading screen at the M okay and
she said she won't like do it right away
anyway
so there so much so much so much what
was like what was no uh ah yeah I was
going to sort a little bit
away wasn't there a wood
chest feel
like yeah wood wood wood wood wood wood
random things
chest yeah okay whatever just wanted to
make a little bit of
space okay I'll do like only I'll finish
done sugar cane Farm really
quickly
and anything else that super important
not really I think I might leave it
there more
water yeah the Phantom I think it's
bugged it was like this before it should
burn to death but it just won't
that's enough water oh oh
well oh
[Music]
wellow okay looking smooth look at her
go look at her go when by the time I
stream tomorrow that will probably be
all fake
all
right it's almost fixed o she do be
listening that's all the sugar cane I
have but you get the gist you get it oh
no
got
time it's time to go yeah I don't know
if you guys are interested but I I
already said like uh previously that I'm
probably not going to do a proper reveal
for my 2.0 I might just like you know
show you like like on the side like this
is I guess this is my 2.0 for the 3.0 I
want to do it oh this doesn't
work what
the what hurt me makes no
sense oh you got that close to me oh
[\h__\h] no cat to protect me okay the cat
buff was
off all
right mhm
I want to play more
but it's so
over it's so
over just going to put some things away
call stream offine she'll she'll come
back she'll figure it
out what am I doing here cool
bows I to put put the diamond axe away
pickaxe in in case somebody needs
that and I don't know if anybody is like
reading this but I'll put up something
new
um get uh villagers to be
useful armor weapons
like level them up is what I'm saying
make
potions everyone they I'm pretty sure no
one wrote it I can tell you
that
oh okay
go
n maybe she's the only one day two
building digging mining I drank on the
job don't tell my bird boss I will be
punished how will I feed my family if
takiki fires me I won't know how to live
with myself tell my wife I love
her this is beautiful this is exactly
the kind of stuff that you know they
also wrote in like Hardcore
Minecraft she gets it she delivers okay
okay this one kind of shorter almost
died to a dolphin today I got the last
word idiot dolphin Baka dolphin day four
oh my God she's actually riding these I
didn't see her riding them at all did
she all Rite like three days in one go
so day for I've been briefed that we are
going to the never for the content I'm
not sure what this word means but if
it's for the greater good of the company
then I will accept the S Mission from my
employer without hesitation Shar out of
I return
go she couldn't take it when I said f
right probably she was like damn it I
need to redeem
myself okay yeah this is what I
thought yeah s this a riding right
[Laughter]
now okay okay
okay take your time m
take good
time I'm it no cute donkey chicken let
me set you free oh you laid an egg in
there wow already getting to work you
take your job seriously
oh it's got to be upside down oopsie
H they twoo fishing they fre don't
remember I think she just rote these
now they for suffering no suffer I mean
yeah honestly that's really really good
good
content but I feel
like I'mma just proof to us that she is
the the big Minecraft brain after
all yeah okay am it I'm going to log out
be careful about like you know being
alone don't get blown up or
something
careful live think I fixed it oh well
then I got to check it
out you going to test it something about
I'll take a
look
Yoo have you ever seen a PPP like this
before huh guys
nice okay we have Hoppers we have
carpets
this where are the
[Music]
enemies should get rid of the sky Bridge
a maybe one sec oh
okay is cie stream back guys is she good
yeah okay does need slabs on top maybe
that's what she's making right
now I have some slabs
though they're
somewhere they're like stopping
[Music]
somewhere like up
there mhm
what does that
mean what she
doing you
have
what give her slap you think does she
want
like it's working Amy seems to be
working oh did she just go up there and
open it up Ah that's where she
went
o all I'll let you do the
honor oh
god oh they're dying on their own now
not all of them
but
yeah oh
oh
wa nice I hear no Creeper explosion
sound
oh never mind [\h__\h]
hell no
no no at least I can't come
out um that is so sad I need to pick up
the I have to pick up I have to I have
to pick up the hopper at least
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] F [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I
think I picked it up no what I went into
into the hopper wait what Hopper ah [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] what no don't don't what clean your
inventory it's clean what do I do um no
they're not coming out it's okay they're
not coming out but I need to get the
Hoppers because so much iron went into
that again uh uh let me go get wait I
have I have arrows
[Applause]
but wait Infinity boat Infinity boat
Infinity boat she's back she probably
feels bad she wants to help fixing it
now uh infinity
boat cleaning up from the from the
distance would be good I think we we
really just it this the the way this is
built is fine I'm in in case you're
still listening we just really have to
take a step back just not getting too
close is the key and then it will be
fine this just you
know it's not bad it's it's not like not
functional or anything like
that okay see it's all under control am
don't worry it's all under
control it's all good it's going to be
fine your work wasn't for
nothing this is a long range
PP yeah thank God for the obsidian right
guys
so worth it all right hopper in my
possession how many two I got two
hoppers on maybe the rest is better no
was it two Hoppers
[Music]
originally four [\h__\h]
hell do you want
them B
you like we can just put a fence there
right and just attack from a step behind
the height of the slabs were the issue
you thought
so the slabs definitely helped in
keeping them from you know walking
out so wait I I put the hopper and the
carpet whatever I picked up I put it in
the chest if you no pressure If you
still feel like you know working on this
then good luck you can do it I think it
doesn't have to be like fixed so to say
I think all we need to do is put a fence
there for
safety so don't get your head worked up
too much about it
umy put slabs on The Hoppers put slab on
Hopper they say am just one more advice
I suppose
oh why am I
sleeping
yeah well good luck
Army you could try to build lower so
that you see its feet and the creeper
doesn't
see well I mean we've seen from a
distance it's fine even from like one
step away like while you you don't have
to attack it with a bow it's wait wait
shut the M let me put my bow back
let me put my bow back in case someone
needs
it bye-bye bye-bye
man yeah that's
good
oh don't worry I don't know if she heard
all all the things I said all the things
I said all the things I said running my
head running my head running through my
head running my head
okay guys uh I'll I'll R you to cie so
go watch her I'll go to sleep or
actually I'll eat some potatoes and
cucumbers no salmon for me I'm
scared have a nice uh day I'll see you
probably at K's uh jackbo stream and
then probably um Minecraft later after
mhm and yeah I had fun and I feel like
especially when it was all five of us
there was so much yapping and we were
like so excited and and had fun even if
the never was shortlived but still and
we did lots of teamwork and and we built
some cool stuff so I think it was a good
day yay so hooray a good day in German
we say in bye
bye see you tomorrow
[Music]