[Music]
n
la
[Music]
n
a
[Music]
kiak
yah
Pap K
[Music]
welcome okay okay I see Tak Tak yeah
everybody Welcome to the stream this is
origami stream
yeah and uh uh we're going to make yeah
create origami while
talking but it's more
special
[Music]
on yours it says myb myb
it we bought it at Amazon
Amazon when was it that you streamed in
this
CL maybe one year ago she streamed she
did a hand Canam stream and she was
wearing this and I was
like boy I was like I know these cloes
so I wrote to her and I told
her yeah I told her like after I saw her
doing that stream later on she did a Gak
stream and I told her oh I have to same
pajama we have to do off collab of the
pajama and
[Music]
finally uh before we started the stream
uh two of our not colleagues not s not
really uh two special people passed by
our
[Music]
room
and came by because they had a stream
too and we asked them if they can make
origami guess who made this
beautiful beautiful crane who do you
think made this
[Music]
[Laughter]
one why why do you think it
was why why why would you think
that
it
was it's
beautiful wow she was like I don't
remember I don't remember but she did it
like really quickly like
not very
fast said I can't do
anything so she
can
aan said the only thing she can maybe
fold is like um do you know this like
it's like a game it's like like four
folds that you like open close open
close and it says something underneath
she said that one she can make what do
you call that in English in in German we
say
H in German heaven and Oh Heaven and
Hell oh it came back are you
[Music]
okay yeah yeah heaven or and Heaven or
Hell Heaven and Hell
but yeah we don't have I thought
maybe is Japanese so she
knows no but we have gu and we brought
we brought U paper paper paper and oh
show your your yeah yeah yeah I
love bought nice origami I bought cheap
origami
oh cute the penguin is
cute cute very cute maybe a little bit
hard
yeah she she was like saying to me
boasting to me she brought a really
difficult one
very but I don't think I don't think we
make this
one
W but it
says it says two hours two
hours it looks
amazing
[Music]
a fox getting married in a
shu is it easy H
oops
and Chloe will be making the chicken
chicken K yeah there is a
chicken uh guide I don't really think it
looks like a
chicken and I make orca orca yeah I make
stinky
Orca for good smell
[Music]
stink depends on the depends on the
chicken I want I guess a
black
we have we have uh problem already I
can't take the paper it's the last page
it's the black one come on come on okay
okay okay and oh it's perfect cuz it's
white in the back black
okay no no wait wait noit wait you don't
anyway I actually um before the stream I
I went to get some uh snack for
us I need to
sneeze it's gone but I just want to say
I got uh waffles for
[Music]
us this is not all I brought waffles BD
I found
something when I was
ging I
know please open please
[Music]
open it's the same waffle
kitchen
[Music]
WAFF
WAFF so many
waffles
so
[Music]
Wu I love I love monin
WAFF
sorry
[Music]
so now we have oi pajama pajama and OSI
waffle y okay let's uh let's let's we
have the same First
Step okay okay okay we start folding in
half I think I think for me black is in
the middle a triangle angle oh and I
have talking topic oh okay oh it's not
so nice talking
topic and I want to write on the OBS
screen you can't touch I can't touch my
phone okay
H so there's one I want to hear about
this too cuz I don't know so much
about new
ah New Zealand New Zealand well I guess
not newand New
Zealand New
Zealand uh I know Chloe studied abroad
for a bit in New Zealand is there
anything in particular she enjoyed or
misses
uhand
[Music]
oh Shell
Beach
oh the beach is
beautiful yeah very
[Music]
beautiful maybe yeah yeah
yeah I guess so
so what about food New Zealand
[Music]
food big
size
[Music]
so the sizes the food serving sizes are
apparently also pretty big in uh New
Zealand I didn't know I don't
know
[Music]
for
oh
[Music]
nice
sorry okay
[Music]
okay
for oh okay she's not talking about NOA
she's saying that it's like a really
relaxed calm peaceful
[Music]
place it's the fault of the gloves
because it's more difficult with
[Music]
gloves okay okay
open wait step four open up the paper
trapped
underneath
difficult very difficult
chicken
[Music]
okay
Zealand one
year
[Music]
I think your English is really good no
no no
[Music]
no
hi I
am she she said she didn't stay a whole
year in New Zealand but she also learned
some English before joining H life in
like an English school in Japan and I
said yo your English is really good and
and I asked her if she wants if she
learned it for joining whole live and
she said no it's because she wants to
talk to to foreign foreign people
foreigners just like me
no no you can speak English yeah yeah
yeah very smart
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] okay
next yes okay h chlo
[Music]
Chloe did you ever
watch did you ever watch uh uh Lord of
the
Rings it says flatten the paper on both
sides into a rabbit ear fold with two
rabbit folds you have a fish base
[Music]
for
guys have you made a chicken
before go
[Applause]
gobe okay okay what am I make F fold the
top and bottom in along the dotted lines
ah ah easy easy
easy easy
J no no
wait okay at the top just the
[Music]
top it's fine it's
fine cool this is this looks like a
penguin right now h
maybe okay next door next step f for for
Chloe fold the two triangle flaps of of
paper over along the dotted
[Music]
lines will be kind of difficult yeah
we're making uh Orca and
[Music]
chicken
this
is fold the paper in half with the
bottom half over
behind
fold the paper in half with the bottom
half over
[Music]
behind oh uh I I don't
know okay uh for me I okay next
step fold the paper in half over behind
the okay okay okay easy hold
behind my step
[Music]
is yes
yes need a YouTube guide yeah video
guide better
[Music]
maybe
just half probably no we're looking at
picture guys pictures with uh
[Music]
sentences yes yes po
H this image is zoomed on the right side
fold a flap of paper over along the dott
line and repeat behind
[Music]
ah I think and for
me h uh ah okay
[Music]
okay
and I I I make
[Music]
tail I think the chicken that we like
the guide we have it looks really
weird looks
[Music]
good who knows that top part is missing
on on the
guide Mama freestyle
freestyle freestyle show
[Music]
face
face what do you want me to do make a
tiny inside reverse fold on the front of
the
face
[Music]
Japanese oh like this oh do you guys see
what's happening
Japanese yes yes Japanese blood coming
in
[Music]
handy okay
okay and
next faulty
entire make an inside reverse fult
inside hi along the dotted line to make
the
neck okay and mine mine is almost over
apparently like I have one more
step wait oh no I'm
done
[Music]
uh they actually have like goggly eyes
on
their on their guides but I didn't buy
any
huh I think you it looks uh
wait Maybe Freestyle
freestyle fre
freestyle bo boy boy boy
[Music]
what I'm making it worse I think I'm
trying to make it look more like the
actual final product
there's supposed to be goggly eye
[Music]
here make two more in side reverse folds
along the
[Music]
Lin it looks difficult with
gloves oh oh yes
yes or guy is here
yeah
end the
end make uh uh make inside reverse fold
up along the dotted
line this one hers is difficult a few
more
steps
[Music]
cool fold the paper inside the model in
along the lines repeat on the other
side
[Music]
chickens are more complex yeah than you
f it looks like a bird oh and then make
make face but why why looks so weird on
the
guy I don't know where the feet is and
where the the head
[Music]
is yeah let's the other way and then it
should be pretty much
[Music]
complete
do because in the guy the one that looks
up yours looks to the side and I think
it's better cuz this can be the beak
this
[Music]
is goggly eyes I don't have goggly eyes
but I make chlo eye here
[Music]
this is this is
b h it looks like looks um maybe here
too red or or orange
orange yes yes yes yes ory we have pants
yeah it's crying blood I thought so
[Music]
too
so no
P my hor is so fast
no
same this part is the white part
open freestyle freestyle freestyle
that's how we made
[Music]
it
nice
New Zealand accent is similar to
Australian
[Music]
accent right it's pretty similar right
no oh no oh no oh no
[Music]
[Applause]
so she didn't know any English when she
arrived in New
Zealand
yes yes yes yes yes yes ma positive
person oh yes
man
okay son asked a question
about units
oh frog
[Music]
frog FR
frog what's frog about
[Music]
that
go for what the [\h__\h] is this frag no
no okay
okay okay I have a question
hi
[Music]
for
hi hi
hi so we have connection like that too
because she is in Umi and with her is
goba and I am in h and with me is
not
[Laughter]
we only have one song now but
[Music]
yeah she said she I asked her if she
wants to join hon and she said well
she's being told that she has like a
bird head as well like a forgetful so
she's is like a bird
but I think she should she she she will
probably stay in Umi
hey yes I I talked with uh you know our
our sta yesterday k
[Laughter]
no good good we will make good things so
please wait for
hon here
honon okay next challenge ISU crane I
have recipe be for
Crane this is made by before she
uh we totally made
this okay this is crane I don't know I
mean I would say that this is the same
same recipe same
guy
[Music]
the chicken had 15 Steps oh the
oh the crate what I'm scrolling and
scrolling oh
my 5
52 POS 52
steps wait wait I go back to the
top 52
steps okay let's do together we can work
on it
together start with the white side of
the yeah so
okay but maybe in the chat there's many
people who made a crane
before you tell us if we do something
wrong fold in half
again easy easy easy
easy
[Music]
okay
half don't remember it was 52
[Music]
steps fult that flap back and squash to
Flap
down
squash but it becomes
[Music]
ugly
okay okay okay okay okay like this okay
nice
cool turn the model over we're going to
[Music]
repeat
behind
[Music]
squash well thank God I have Chloe with
me
Japanese Japanese skill
[Music]
issue
what's
happening make it for
[Music]
me okay thank you
okay okay and and then step six let's
[Music]
go what we doing okay okay okay
right
[Music]
okay you now have a completed square or
preliminary base with a few more folds
we'll turn it into a bird base fold the
side slab to the center along the
line
[Music]
okay
I asked her what kind of thing she wants
to do withi and she says Takaki party
and I said for hor I will do Yak to
party then but she said she wants to
join so I guess I'll also join the II
party
[Music]
fore please say
yese
[Music]
spee fold the top
along
[Music]
okay fold like uh until the point where
I folded the
[Music]
sides
or or
or like
this isn't this a
genius
genius oh you got me stream genius oh oh
continue lifting up and pushing the
sides along the creases you made in the
previous couple of
[Music]
steps
for continue lifting
up this
[Music]
is 15
do the same thing as
[Music]
me okay okay okay okay okay
I need to go it's so difficult the
cloves but I think this is what we're
supposed
to she ripped
it like
this I
[Music]
think
please make one at the same
time help
[Music]
me
for 15
[Applause]
calm down C
[Music]
down okay
okay 18
okay
[Music]
for this is Step 17 we're probably on
the
same uh yeah step now fold the side to
the center along the
[Music]
line going to make pedal fold on the
other side
[Music]
too
well yeah and then
unfold
[Music]
unfold okay
okay uh then
we drop this down Drop It Like It's
[Music]
Hot
don't think just do it just do it just
do
[Music]
it
for
[Music]
free free
souvenir
I don't know what she's doing like I
look over and it doesn't look like we're
doing the same
thing okay
[Music]
okay hey why is this so
bad
okay we make it prettier cuz really
looking bad okay it's
better it's
[Music]
fine her is like broken
okay
perfect petal fold the completed petal
fold at this point you also have a
completed bird base next we're going to
fold the neck and the
tail fold the top flap on the right to
the
center along the
line
[Music]
foreign fore fore
speech
[Music]
[Laughter]
speech call
[Music]
I love
you I want to show the pajamas more but
they're pretty
short
teach me let's talk English for a little
bit okay uh wait I get Talking topic
yeah
talking ah very very
different very
hard do you think there's something that
we have in
common
[Music]
not Pajamas not
pajamas no no no what about do you like
I think somebody wrote on my Twitter
that something maybe you like hello
project do you like hello
project
no I don't
[Music]
know she doesn't know hello hello
project or any other Idol much hey I got
one
guide no anime what kind of anime do you
like or game no okay first game or anime
anime anime SK anime SK anime in English
yeah
ti ti attack of Attack on Titan Attack
on
[Music]
Titan Demon Slayer no no noon yes Demon
Slayer Demon Slayer
[Laughter]
[Music]
turn the model
over
we're going
to fold the flap on the left to the
[Music]
center okay okay
behind something looks like boobs to me
and I don't know why okay so
[Applause]
[Music]
okay oh easy
easy to use English for when having a
fight uh shut up shut
up I hate you I hate
you you're stupid you are
stupid and what else uh you [\h__\h] you
little [\h__\h] yeah you little [\h__\h] you
little [\h__\h]
yeah
[Music]
uh what guys what what should she use in
a
[Music]
fight out get
out get
out and in the end you say I am so
sorry please come
back please
free be quiet be
quiet you want to fight you want to
fight you want to fight you want to
fight
fight yeah but I think you
can your your your English is beautiful
without my
help to fight you want to F fight you
want to
fight fight she looked at my eyes and
she was like you want to fight you want
to
fight is this how it's supposed to look
beautiful not not as beautiful as you no
no
no you understand what I said you said
oh very beautiful and I say not as
beautiful as
you she just replied like naturally in
Japanese
the Moon the Moon is beautiful
tonight uh maybe uh
very uh far far away yeah so far away
the Moon is far away yeah
because but no matter no matter how
far we can reach anything
together English flirting English flirt
okay focus
[Music]
focus okay okay okay M Sor
to okay okay okay cute very cute next
oh we can do dance
dance cute I want to draw like socks
sock like sexy sexy legs KN uh yeah KNE
High sucks
okay crease this well and
[Music]
unfold
fro
no
no onum is not sexy but is there
pornographic
[Laughter]
okay unfold back back to
this turn my we're going ah
[Music]
noig
okay
okay we're already at
come back come back okay okay fold the
long fin section of the
[Music]
paper okay
maybe lift the paper up inside the
model uh you already made and flatten
everything lift the paper up inside the
model along the creases you already made
and
[Music]
flatten sheep
paper paper no
[Music]
you make flat but it
[Applause]
broke
she's
[Music]
okay I will I will
Contin no
way
[Music]
um make another inside reverse fold
along
[Music]
the leg to the
back
[Music]
I don't understand these steps
guys what are you
doing
[Music]
okay it looks like the 44th step what I
have and then
uh okay so I think I have to do the same
here but it's like really
[Music]
[Laughter]
scary
she was like oh maybe maybe you're
supposed to like rip it but I'm like no
I think the meaning like of origam is to
not rip anything you're only
[Laughter]
folding no
no come
[Music]
back let's let's believe let's
believe
[Music]
for I don't even know
anymore yeah yeah same same same
[Laughter]
[Music]
same it's already the same thing I think
we're close to
the
for okay we'll just do this oh yeah that
looks
fore looks
good
turn the model over so we can
repeat why no no no no pH long P section
of paper on the left
[Music]
side
she got
it Chloe is smart she's smart
[Music]
foree
ohe fore
[Music]
foree
fore
[Music]
Force why is she so
smart
yeah I think she's smart yeah smart Ora
[Music]
yeah let's let's cho cho
cho
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's
[Music]
it looks like that dog uh the dog snoot
the long long dog snoot the funny one
that looks funny on pictures
[Music]
because
[Laughter]
for it looks like the the dog snoot that
funny but she made it like a million
times faster than
us
[Music]
beautiful we made chicken Ora
or okay I get I get recipe for for frog
she's goingon to make frog for me cuz I
really want the frog frog and I will be
like throwing talk topics at
her Teamwork because we only need one
frog okay step one step
[Music]
one
okay maybe
okay
[Music]
we have one more connection point is
that that we both participated in one of
the best sponsorships ever
[Laughter]
[Music]
for us uh we got one gift from company
vure connect one big gift then from each
member yeah for example H I give gift to
Ena I give gift to Ras and so on I give
gift to p andak p give gift to me and so
on so we exchange
[Music]
exchange I think not not for example Ena
give me Chanel glasses
wow and I give to laas uh finger paint
finger
pain finger
paint and I give to inan uh uh like a
maybe one year supply of oh one year
supply of k
k
and then there was also like fans uh I
[Music]
think
for I want to go to Hawaii too
beautiful but I wonder New Zealand yeah
Hawaii I think New
Zealand II very beautiful very beautiful
Hawaii II very beautiful yeah but New
Zealand New
Zealand so ah so I asked about Lord of
the Rings because New
Zealand because uh you know Lord of the
Rings was filmed in New
Zealand sorry Lord
[Music]
ofand
you can go see The Hobbit houses is like
on know in a in on a on a grass hill
inside inside the grass hill it's like a
cave but made like a pretty house it's
so nice I show
you it's so good it's so good fantasy
yeah fantasy movie L of the
Rings
[Music]
fore fore
spee
fore I want to live in Hobbit
[Laughter]
[Music]
house
she doesn't realize how popular Lord of
the Rings is because it's just like
Harry Potter is more popular in Japan
than Lord of the
Rings I'm trying to convert another
member of course it's worth
[Music]
it
it's ridiculously better yeah it is ba
is here of she must be Ed what what do
you mean
bailes you mean she's educated because
she prefers Harry Potter over the lord
of the RS ah ah what do you want I'm
going to ban you I'm going to ban you
fight yeah you want to fight you want to
fight what do you want what do you want
F come here come here come here come
here right now CL needs some ah okay
okay okay so you're on my side okay okay
no fight no fight no fight
misunderstanding
[Laughter]
misunderstanding misunderstanding corner
here here's the
[Music]
corner
push everything
[Music]
down for the the paper D around the
ex we are confused cres just like
you
[Music]
water fold the paper down along the
existing creases just like you making a
water
bu looks like it's connected but hers
isn't connected at the top hers like two
[Music]
flaps
fing which one is more Majestic of of
these
birds what's
Majestic help
[Music]
me maybe
maybe are
you
y yay I'm I I showed her how to do it I
just didn't do it cuz my hands are less
[Music]
nice I
help or you got me rat there surely is
there's like so many guyses on this
website there's so many
animals
[Music]
genius nice nice I
helped
[Music]
interesting yeah I thought we were doing
something completely wrong but we're on
the right
[Music]
track
Co nice go Chloe go go let's see if I
can find another question here let's go
let
go okay how about do you do you like to
cook oh yeah oh
what for
[Music]
example
is she really good she's she claims
she's good at cooking I
[Music]
wonder
okay maybe we have cooking in common
what else do we have oh I
[Music]
don't
for Sumer she actually she didn't I told
her to bring you know the pajamas so we
can wear it so we can just show it off
but she even brought the
pants pants though we're not showing the
[Music]
pants
ribbit
ribbit okay
okay four 24 yeah
24 fold the top right part of the paper
up along the dott line this will make
one of the frogs front
legs don't worry about the angle of
the as long as you get a shape like what
you see in the next
step
fold the left part of the paper up along
the dotted line to make the other
[Music]
front
[Laughter]
[Music]
for
okay yes yes yes frog frog frog frog
frog frog frog frog
[Music]
frog
s can who can get the Frog to fly
further so
ribit okay okay okay okay now from there
to here yeah
okay
ribit
pretty camera die welcome back hi
I'm gonna show her my frog um uh
imitation cuz she doesn't
[Music]
know look at the Frog imagine close your
eyes or look at the
Frog no
no car that's
frog and frog okay you're throwing no th
sound throwing up
sound
no no I'm not B
she
no that's the first time someone said
something like that
[Music]
no
okay get anybody can do
it that was supposed to be
S yeah I
[Music]
hate oh look let's let's put our things
[Laughter]
here
why is this so funny it's like it's
that's that's what an orca looks
like
okay okay
okay our beautiful
[Music]
animals
it's Orca yeah oh can Orca
stand no
no
wow we made a lot we actually made
plenty I think this is uh would be good
to end
it after this we finished the
waffles WAFF
WAFF she
got not
similar do you like Yakiniku I love
Yakiniku yeah I love but what's your
what if you go to what do you
[Music]
order
for
[Music]
I asked her like she asked me if I like
Yakiniku I love Yakiniku Japanese like
grilling meat but I asked her what she
orders if she goes to Yakiniku and the
first thing she order is like what every
other Japanese member orders always it's
tan so Tang tongue yeah you grill the
tongue of a cow or yuk yuk is a Korean
dish I think with like a raw egg on top
of raw meat
[Music]
but cow or horse yeah cow or
horse
[Music]
I order I
order I have for
har for 10 years I was eating harami
happily last year I go to Yakiniku and
someone told
me uh harami is
actually inside
part nice
[Music]
it's a stomach
stomach no no no no maybe
[Music]
no hormon oh I hate
hormon
bonding I know we
connect because we don't
[Music]
connect it is it's not really very
intestines like but it turns out it is
but
[Music]
yeah
for I
[Music]
understand
yeah let's go
sometime do you like to
[Music]
no no no
no okay okay okay do you like
[Music]
m
I love Sab it's a tonu
[Music]
place
well
I was like oh my God you're
right is the way to go f f nothing else
no
more
nice
[Music]
nice meat well okay I think maybe we eat
waffle outside of
stream this is this is my
[Music]
waffle and uh we will maybe hopefully
collab again even if we have nothing in
[Music]
common this is also scary the
[\h__\h] okay why okay and in German we say
Al Fe in
[Music]
yes I'm
inside byebye thank you
[Music]
guys I to thank you guys for helping out
and hanging out with us bye bye
byee
[Music]
no
sh
[Music]