[Music]
[Applause]
a
[Music]
[Applause]
n
a
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
a
[Applause]
n
[Music]
K
Kitty oh where's my
child where are you can you hear me
kitty
Hello I am not quite frogging yet so
don't worry you're not you're not in
danger yet there you go a Ribery
key I don't see your profile pictures on
YouTube but I've seen some of you guys
change your profile pictures and names
on
Twitter y'all are excited for frog week
yay where is my ocean
hey I heard there was frog here yeah
frog I'm starting to frog I feel it I
mean there is a frog here down down here
down in my uh in my little glass
container
it's open it's not contained so she can
exit any time oh it seems like I have
like with the new updated app I have
some
issues so it keeps on stopping to move
49 months thank you so much please don't
please don't do it please don't okay
okay yay I will probably have to restart
the app a million times today we'll see
we'll
see whack ass crystal Prison
it's not even made out of crystal
crystal would be would Crystal be
stronger than
glass
oh Tuesday afternoon it's Tuesday
[\h__\h] is it it is right yeah yeah it
would be stronger right yeah I thought
so thank you guys for the membership
gifts thank you everybody first of all I
want to say I'm
home I'm home with my cat
and this time it looks like I'll be
staying forever no for for a
[Music]
while I still I don't know when would
you say I'm completely recovered when
you still have a little bit tiny bit of
fum in your throat I think I stopped
having to blow my nose pretty much maybe
yeah today today I didn't blow my nose a
single time that's pretty good I was oh
yeah I mean I'm like yeah 19
195% healthy maybe
um yeah I I have a frog in my fruit
literally now when I talk I think I have
to cough more or um I didn't have to
cough at all before the stream so don't
worry if I'm coughing it's just because
I'm probably
choking
um I have frog in fro I like that you
guys say that in English too you you do
say that in English too right I'm
choking on the Frog yeah I got to let it
out I got to start
frogging right about now m
um I'm kind of nervous about this stream
it's kind of uh it feels like I haven't
streamed from home in a while in a hot
minute and uh I have a few things to
show you guys so I'm a bit like all over
the
place yeah I don't know I want to do
like some normal quick speed tangents as
well first of all can you hear the bgm
though can you can you hear the
music I like this
one it's I think fitting for the
dorkiness of the Frog you can hear it
okay I hope it's not too long I've
noticed so while I was gone I was gone
for 2 weeks uh in Japan but before that
I was also gone right in North America
for like in the end I think it was a
week it wasn't supposed to be a full
week but then my flight got like
cancelled right and I had to stay a few
days longer so I think I I may have been
gone for a week back then and then then
I was back in Austria for 24 hours and
then I was gone to Japan for 2
weeks
um so I was gone for a while and while I
was gone my
BFF my best friend and her boyfriend
were taking care of my place and then in
the second week my
my brother was taking care of my place
and I've
noticed um like they used my PC a little
bit uh on a different profile of course
um but I don't know if it's like my
cat's continuously stepping on my on my
mixer thingy on my streamer thingy or or
it's them or it's a mixture I think it's
a mixture of both my cat stepping around
on it and them using losing my equipment
but I feel like I can't get my
broadcaster back to the settings that
they like that it was on before so
things are kind of unusual for me like
um I I I I've been trying to record
something right yesterday when I after
arrived
uh um I can't seem to get rid of like I
can't seem to just have my voice like if
there's something playing um I can't
help but have it go through and normally
there's a setting that I know will make
things go through the microphone uh like
like background music or something
there's a setting for that but even if I
turn it off it's still there so I'm like
really confused I don't understand what
what is going on with this
thing so right now I'm glad you can I'm
glad you say you can hear the B Jam I'm
glad you say it's not too loud or too
quiet uh because I don't know how to
change things
really very you throw out the roadter yo
I I would love to throw out the roadter
and I would ideally go back to the goxlr
but um it's not supported anymore and
some of you guys
think think that the that the ghost L is
bad or anything it's not bad it's really
not bad sometimes I I still get to
stream with boo XLR When I visit other
people's places like Ena Ena was still
using the go and Kelly was still using
the gox and so on and you guys never
complain when I go
there I don't think it's different but
whatever whatever don't even don't even
get me
[Music]
started imagine changing a PP and name
because it's frog but couldn't be me yay
I love it though I love it I can't see
the Prof pictures on on on the in the
chat though but I I feel it I feel the
spirit
don't get kfp started yeah yeah like you
can get me started but don't get kfp
started so yeah uh I I yeah don't no
don't even get me I could like I could
like complain a lot why I need to golar
and why the roadcast is [\h__\h] it's [\h__\h]
why it was a bad purchase but it's like
hard it's hard to
know with these equipment thingies
until you actually get to use it if it's
something that you can work with easily
with the kind of work that you
do I started
no I started no so today will be kind of
a short stream by the way
uh I I don't know I I wouldn't say I'm
jet lag that badly like I I I I yes
yesterday okay okay okay okay I want a
tangent ah yesterday I I was supposed to
arrive kind of earlier but my right now
there's no direct flights to Japan which
makes it a lot more difficult but my I
didn't realize that my flight back to
Austria was a lot longer than my flight
to Japan which of course there's like
you know reasons because of globe and I
I guess just like what is the actual
reason of why that way from Japan to
Europe is
longer why why is it longer like I know
there's like some like earth physical
whatever reasons for sure the wind
currents earth
rotation oh hey even your guys' answers
are like
mixed winter is it when direction is an
earth rotation Earth don't say e don't
say e a RF jet stream was is that the
same thing as one of the other words
what's jet
stream something about that yeah and
then and then of course like still the
routes uh are not the usual routes like
the planes when going from Europe to
like somewhere over there in Japan or
similar areas they still have to go like
all the way around like I think I think
every every Airline kind of has to
change their routes for going
there which makes it a bit longer
but I when I talk I really feel the frog
in my Thro man
[\h__\h] um any funny airplane stories well
it's funny cuz I was just getting to the
like story about being the Lan again um
so my my flight
connection the to say lay over stop over
wouldn't even have been that long it
would have only been like 2 and 1/2
hours which is not bad but then in
total each of the single flights was
still so long on its own on the way back
that in total it was going to be like a
little bit like over 21
hours yeah that's already long I didn't
realize like when they booked the flight
for me I just looked at the stop over
layover times to make sure they're not
weird um and the flight to Japan was
certainly fine wasn't too bad I think it
was maybe like 16 17 hours mind you if
it was a direct flight I could get to
Japan in like 11 or 12
hours but it took me [\h__\h] 21 hours to
get back what should we try some
pineapple W who who well I I eat
pineapples a lot but I wouldn't say
they're good for my
fro
yeah so and then I was looking forward
to a short layover of 2 and 1 half hours
and I arrived at the airport was it was
Abu Dhabi by the way if you want to know
Abu
Dhabi really
interesting Abu Dhabi airport I arrive
like around midnight right and then I go
to the lounge cuz the lounge is quite
nice pretty big there's showers so I
take a shower quick one and I was going
to I I was going to take a little rest
there's relaxation rooms which is
basically just like a not very
comfortable looking
couch uh in not a completely cut off
room it's just uh like cubicles maybe in
a darkened
room and that you can have a blanket
there and all that and it it's a
relaxation room so obviously you're
supposed to be quiet and sleep right and
I I was hoping that maybe the walls
would go up to the ceiling so maybe that
I could record I was still hoping to
record the voice over for that YouTube
shirt that I
uploaded um because I was too
embarrassed I went all the way to the
like furtherest corner of the lounge
where there were absolutely no people
around and I was like okay okay I'm
going to record the voice over now
because I was going to record it before
I flew with the first flight
uh but then I had no time cuz I was
still cutting the video on my phone so
whatever I I I'll get it done in between
my flights and then upload it during my
flight my last flight so you guys have
something but I go to the very end of
the lounge nobody around and I I I I
pull my phone really close to my
face and I'm like I I start recording
and I
say and then I noticed even a relatively
low voice k key felt like it was like
not echoing but it it still felt like
cuz there was no one around me no one
talking it still felt like it was going
everywhere and I felt super embarrassed
I was like [\h__\h] I can't do it I said one
word and I was like I can't [\h__\h] do
it so I I gave up I
mean I think like because no one was
around me even the the further away
closest person to me if that makes sense
would have hurt me I think that's the
issue I didn't see anyone but I still
think like somebody could have Hur me so
I'm not going to be like talking to
myself on my phone like if it's a normal
phone conversation and I wouldn't be
embarrassed but I I would have like said
stuff like yeah k key I went to this
cute Cafe and had
om imagine if they say k key back that
would have been amazing then I would
would feel less insecure
maybe so I was like okay okay um in that
case maybe maybe the relaxation room is
really soundproof and I can do it in
there so I check and even if it wasn't
the case I would have just chilled a
little bit in there and I I check and I
get a room after a little bit of waiting
time cuz they were apparently really
full and I go
in I go into my little cubicle and I
already hear in the room right next to
me a family with a relatively young
child like I don't know I didn't see
them but the child sounded really young
the parents were loud and talking and
the child was loud
and whining I was
like yo this is supposed to be a
relaxation room I know I know like with
children it's hard but
like uh I don't know I don't know man
that kind of sucked that I I was like
like standing there and I was thinking
does it even make sense to be in here
cuz it's more quiet outside of this
relaxation room it's more quiet where I
just was than in here in the relaxation
room I'm not going to be able to sleep
here so I walk out and I say to the lady
sorry I there's no way I can sleep in
here because of you know H and she's
like oh okay and I leave so I was like
no problem anyway because my flight is
uh you know boarding soon cuz I only had
a 2 and 1 half hour layover right so I
go and have uh the the little shower and
then and then I sit down to just uh
chill a little bit and then I
see a [\h__\h] delay email I'm like
no cuz my first flight my first flight
from Japan to Abu Dhabi was 16
hours how is it 16 hours when normally
from that's in between auster and Japan
but from auster to Japan I can have a
flight in within 12 hours how is this
one flight 16 hours I must have gone
like quite around the uh
Globe the first fight was 16 I think was
it
16 now maybe 14 something like that and
yeah and then I get a delay for 4 hours
so instead of 2 and 1/2 hours layover 1
hour in I suddenly realized I have to
wait like extra 4 hours so 6 and 1/2
hours lay over 2 and 1 half totally fine
3 hours totally fine even even 4 hours I
could still somewhat tolerate I I would
not if I knew that this was a 6-hour
waiting time I would have not chosen
that flight if I if that was like
decided ahead of the time yeah so that
kind of sucked I was
like so I go back to the relaxation room
and I'm like hey
um hey if that family if they leave can
you let me know and I would like to have
a room again after all cuz my flight got
delayed and she's like yeah the family's
already gone I'm like what they they
were in there for like a really short
amount of time maybe they realized that
they are bothering other
people um but she said sorry it's
already it's already closed uh like
everybody's you know in the rooms it's
filled up and I don't have an opening uh
until like 2 hours later so I'm like
okay I guess I'll wait I'll still be
around in 2 hours so so I sit down
nearby and I get myself a [\h__\h] VPN
because Discord doesn't [\h__\h] work in
uh the Emirates I
suppose I I didn't realize that uh last
time when I was at the airport I was
like why is my Discord not working but
this time I researched and I realized oh
it's just not working because it's not
working but I wanted to check up on my
Kima Envy cuz kind of uu sent me a a
preview yeah Discord
crimes kind of makes sense yeah they
they they ban a lot of of things like uh
Discord and WhatsApp and so
on uh so I'm like [\h__\h] I really want to
watch this I cuz you can open Discord
and you can see that you have new
messages and you can see who said the
new messages and where they are but when
you click on them nothing loads it's
still like the old messages I'm like I
want to see this I see that kanu sent
something I I know it's the MV cuz he
told me he'll be sending them V preview
soon
yeah and I was like I I I need to watch
this and now I have so much [\h__\h] time
you know so I got myself a VPN after a
while finally I got everything figured
out and I watched it it looks pretty
cool so far it looks pretty cool so
far some glitching and all that needs to
be fixed and I said more dancing scenes
please
but I'm a bit oh God I go from tangent
to tangent to tangent can you tell h i i
noticed that like you know I was using
my exent suit that cost me what 12K or
something
12K and I noticed that like some parts
where like whenever I step strongly with
my leg it seems like my leg is like
wobbling and it looks honestly it made
me p pissed off because it feels like I
could have like that leg wobble it makes
it look like I recorded it in [\h__\h] VR
chat so that's really frustrating for me
cuz I I spent a lot of money and I tried
my best like I don't know why cuz like I
really last time I
recorded I really tried my best to like
fixate everything so that it all stays
in place and doesn't wobble wobble and I
had the impression when I was dancing
that everything was really like you know
set in
stone yeah thanks for Super
Chat I'm happy you're celebrating frog
week
to uh even with duct it no no no no you
don't use duct tape with that but um but
kind says he doesn't have that issue so
there must be a way for me to like
improve that [\h__\h] but I'm
[Music]
just so even those moves will just be
not shown as much in the MV or we'll do
like close-ups and whatever so you can't
see wait
what but K you can carry a beak
humidifier why are you saying this what
does that relate to but also are you
saying this because of uh uh was it Iris
or crony because I think it was Iris
yeah Iris saw me in the lobby in the
hotel lobby with
the
yeah yeah did she say that it was big
cuz it was indeed very
big yeah I I remember that moment very
clearly cuz I was like why are you here
are you visiting like one of us who was
in the hotel and she's like no no like
I'm actually staying here I'm like oh it
confused me hi hi smoothie thank you for
saying hi it confused me cuz like she
lives in Japan right but uh she got a
hotel room
too small world yeah honestly we kept
meeting people each other so often in
the lobby I met crony a lot like my
elevator would arrive in the lobby and
the door would open up and I would see
crony in front of the elevator door
crouching on the ground rumbling and
rumbling and rumbling in her bag like
fumbling and rumbling and rambling in
her bag what do you say how do you say
that like looking for her back on the
ground like not even realizing that I'm
standing right in front of her and she's
like ah she looks up and she's like ah
and I'm like
Ah rumaging that's the word that's the
word rumaging aggressively rumaging I'm
like nice to see you
again and then then I would like
randomly meet like girls checking out
and like Amy for example I'm like Amy
you're leaving and he's like yeah and
I'm like no no I'm man and I gave her a
quick hug oh God the tangents I'm not
supposed to
[Music]
tangents yeah there were a lot of like
random random
meetings yeah it was it was uh cute cute
to see
them n anyway I was really pissed off
cuz of the layo delay don't you
understand how piss stop I
was
yeah it was okay though it's okay I I
ended up like cuz the relaxation rooms
ah I didn't finish the story cuz they
said like wait 2 hours or something like
that right half an hour later or so of
me sitting there the lady comes up to me
and she's like you're waiting for the
relaxation room right I'm like yeah and
she's like sorry
actually actually they're all closed
until like 7 a.m. which is like which
would have been like half an
hour before I would take off I think and
I got to start boarding earlier than
that anyway and I was like huh I didn't
say I just said yeah okay but I was
wondering why did it change like first
you you said to me that it would open up
in 2 hours and then at that point you
tell me it opens up in like maybe 5
hours or so I'm like
H how how come how come that was changed
huh and then she said I should just go
to one of those like reclining chairs so
I go to the reclining chairs but
suddenly I'm freezing suddenly it's cold
as [\h__\h] in the
airport um and you know when it's cold
you just can't really sleep I tried
covering myself with my coat and I tried
sleeping in a reclining chair but it
just you know it just doesn't work I
tried curling up I tried
everything yeah so I was just like
dozing off for short periods of time and
then wake up again and check the time
and sleep
again and then feel feel how my how my
neck was
really uh tensing
up yeah wasn't the most comfortable but
it's okay eh the flights themselves were
pretty comfortable
and really good food I want to say um
this was ety head Airways I don't think
I flew with etad I flew like with
Emirates before for example but never
with never with ety head I think ety
head oh I have a great tent do I have
time I was supposed to look at
[Laughter]
frogs I just want to say no okay let's
keep it for one of my gaming streams no
no no no no no no no no no I'm supposed
to look at frogs okay I mean I don't
have that much to say about them anyway
it's
okay I just I've done a little bit of
research but uh okay let's let's reveal
um one of the things or two of the
things sorry I'm choking when I talk
what the [\h__\h] I don't have a cough
normally let me
drink sorry I'm
choking
it's it's the it's like the the little
bit of remaining
legum sorry why
why oh [\h__\h] okay okay let's do uh
reveal sorry I'm dying good that this is
a short one oh [\h__\h] I got tears in my
eyes F you
eyes
yeah okay I'll do the reveal now first
reveal
is help me first reveal is um
background [\h__\h] I'm D okay let's
just
t
it's so
nice please look at it while I drink
water froggy W is coming
out yeah
um
I'm not
acting oh it's
real okay so we have um holy [\h__\h] I
really can't
talk cough sounds like a froat at
frog okay so we have a nice little
background made by Eden exile for my
frog week thank you so much I
requested like you know habitat of
froggy waa uh with a little house
honestly I uh uh it's it turned out so
adorable but I don't really know about
the sizing I I please don't take this as
froggy waa really being this but I guess
it makes sense cuz she is pretty small
when she's in my in my office in the
container in the batl bow so I guess the
sizing m is it too it might be I think
yeah I guess it's too scale I I always
imagined her to be bigger once she comes
out of the bowl like just like it's
containing and holding back her size is
how I kind of imagine it but whatever
it's cute here everything is small okay
um I I I requested gummy worms cuz that
is now officially froggy Wawa's favorite
snack she has a little a little
um uh uh what do you call it again swing
it was on the tip of my tongue a little
swing I looked up like some some like
wooden small
miniature naturistic furniture and they
had these cute little swings I was like
I want one of these they look so cute
yeah and I requested the water to be
moving he did that looks good here in
the back you can
see and I requested moving fireflies
which are in here I don't know why you
can't eat them are they toxic actually
are they actually toxic for
frogs maybe maybe they
are I'm fine I'm
fine they are did we have this
conversation before I feel like we
did I can remove the tree stomp in front
of me um but it's basically the table
it's it's the table for froggi waa to do
her
business okay this is really lovely
right even though pretty much all of the
streams that froggy Wawa has planned
speaking of here uh all the streams that
froggy has planned our gaming streams
from now on Frog's Adventure a frog
detective spin
frog and frog song Frog song being I
think the longest game out of
these so I don't know how often we'll
get to use it
uh I didn't think of that I just wanted
a nice background for her I'm so nice to
her yeah I have
a [\h__\h] okay whatever stop
talking let's reveal H cuz it's I can't
I can't hold it back
anymore single gummy
worm are you ready stand back she's
frogging I already you might be
wondering it's frog week why is she not
froggy Wawa yet it's because I'm trying
to do like a segue into froggy
[Music]
Wawa
three
two
one wait let me take off the
bag
yay I fr frogged I frogged I'm I'm
becoming froggy waa she has me under
control I finally have like a cute Cape
yeah like a lot of other members have
capes you know somewhere you know like
it's saw you know I saw some like bear
capes and all that like cute stuff
fluffy fluffy capes winter capes but I
wanted a frog Cape it's so cute right
it's really cute yeah it's wobbly do you
see the wobble on the
eyes it's so cute the SC and I put it on
my h on my default on my uh casual
outfit of course cuz um I felt like I I
I have a lot of uh usage on it uh yeah
easy to use use
look you you see the
wobble just by looking at this you might
think froggy waa is here oh my God oh my
God the wobble oh my God the
wobble it
bounces okay and then we have like you
know cute little design here with some
Frills and the Frog frog legs or
whatever uh as a pattern I had like
several patterns to choose from several
like designs that they gave me to choose
from but I kind of like this one the
most so here it is yeah cute I'm so
happy with it yeah I can be a little bit
more comfy in this frog Cape from now on
even when it's not frog week but I would
say this is a nice introduction to frog
sad thing is I can't use it with my
short hairstyle unless I use up more
points for it and I had no points
left um but it works with the chicken
mascot it works with you
guys
interestingly I can have you guys out at
the same
time yay cute cute cute we're so cute
together cute right yeah oh wait I still
didn't do the Frog
thing I guess we we're probably going to
like I'm glad I'm actually glad that I
don't have so much time left so I can uh
excuse speed running
it okay then I want to uh tell you
remind you in case you haven't seen cuz
I didn't tweet it out yet I'm going to
Red oh that's that's the thing yeah I
have to redirect you I mean I can change
the time but I don't want to change it
too much this video it's coming out if
you remember I used to do kfp 101 like
these are videos that are kind of like
introduction into the waah wa
World wah wa
world uh yeah it's been a while though
we have done four episodes until now
this is the fifth episode and I think if
you're if you're somewhat new or you
just you're even around for two or 3
years but you just feel like you're
missing some knowledge or some like why
is this a thing how did this happen in
the first place um these videos are
really really well made thanks to cow
carrat scripting and directing them um
they're really well made they're really
inform inform in informal informal in
inform formative informative wa is that
a
word yeah they're really good they're
really fun and with this one you'll see
once again K carrat has uh added a skill
to his
repertoire uh AKA MMD yeah
informative so this is coming out
afterwards it's an episode about frogy
laa which we wanted to do for a long
long long long time but then I don't
know it didn't happen and now it was
kind of like perfect to time it for the
froggy waa week frog week frog
week I'm relatively new so this will be
informative yeah make sure to check out
the other episodes um it's been a while
since I last uploaded one but there's
been episodes about the usual room I
think there's been one about M
Zoo maybe has there no maybe not wait
what were other episodes usual room and
what
else
[Music]
wait what were the other ones about I
don't even
remember Casper oh yeah Casper and
Australia wink Ah that's free isn't
there one missing then hash is # W #
yolk is one oh
really okay okay and then now we have
froggy Wella so you can learn a lot of
things through these episodes please
look forward to it you'll be redirected
once the stream is ending in apparently
40 minutes
it is now 50 so I'm supposed to uh show
off my merch now because yes I have
finally made it happen I finally made it
true true because okay so so we can have
merch um we we have the right to have
merch for our uh birthday and then
usually you want merch for your
anniversary solo merch we're talking
solo merch and then you get a third
merch choice um that others often use
for their new outfits or whatever uh as
a commemorative thing uh but I didn't
use it yet for last year and I and they
asked me what do I want to use it for
and I'm like I don't know I don't want
to use it for my outfits I wouldn't know
what to do um but then I thought I can
make froggy waa b i really personally
want frogy W merch and I
think my beloved kfps also want froggy W
merch
so let me introduce you with the
beginning of froggy waa
week I'll be reminding you all week
about it we have froggy wava
[Music]
merchandise wait the big banner was
here
sales are beginning in less than 10
minutes wait where the [\h__\h] oh
here 3 2 one I am
ready
T frogy beginner merchandise don't
misunderstand um this is not going to be
like the starter merchandise fies that
are up uh constantly no no no no this is
as usual only available for one month of
free order there is no like special
signed edition this time cuz I don't
want to do it like for every uh merch
set
cuz uh it's a lot of
work and I've done so many last year so
it's okay I think but we have free merch
items and they are amazing do you want
to see them a hoodie yeah it was I think
called Parker uh and you guys some of
you guys saw it and were like what the
[\h__\h] cuz it was like leaked a little bit
early but that's okay I'm not mad at all
I feel I feel like you know it happens
no
problem
so ta wait I actually have this like let
me use
this okay let's take a
look you even even with the leak you
didn't see the items yet did you I hope
you didn't I don't think you
did make a bigger here we
go okay from akab Baba very very popular
famous artist uh for H live and you get
okay why is it already here purchase
bonus okay yeah yeah this is when you
buy the full set frog beginers merch
complete stack you got a sticker okay
it's cute it's cute you can put it
somewhere maybe on your laptop I like to
put stickers on like my PC and laptop
and all
that
t Okay Okay Okay so uh the wobbling
frogy waah K sayain wobbling frogy
waah uh it the middle part is shaky it
moves okay it's like attached with a
little metal ring so it will move around
Wawa will be wobbling froggy Wawa will
be wobbling it's a small key chain with
some cute tadpoles and flies I didn't
know what else to put there they were
like okay what do you want in it I'm
like I don't know um lily pads and flies
and tat PES I don't
know I can't think of anything else so
here it is and then we have a b blessy
oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God
oh my God holy
[\h__\h] I'm so excited um I don't think
I've ever done a plushy on my own
merchandise
before so this is the first and oh wait
never mind I mean I've done uh recently
I've done the chicken the kfy chicken
before
okay recently that was actually pretty
recently but okay besides that I've
never done like like a um a plushy of
myself the plushy has a gun yeah it's
kind of flat in reality it's not like
that's not really threedimensional but
the whole thing is threedimensional but
the gun is kind of
flat
yeah um but she's so cute I saw some
previews I hope we can provide you with
IRL pictures
soon I already saw some but yeah it's
really cute you can take the hood off
and she will reveal her fluffy hair
which is so cute it's based off of Mama
loon's design um you can tell I think by
looking at the eyes that it's a very
money
core it's so cute it and it's kind of
small but not too small I think I said I
wanted to be around the size of a dino
GAA so if you have a dino GAA you can
like have them next to each other and
they will be best friends
forever yeah I thought they will have a
good time together they'll hang out she
fights that dinura if you have dinura
and you get frogi waa make him fight and
make him cuddle make him do
both yeah isn't she so cute I'm so
excited I'm so
excited my little froggy
wa I really want to hold her as soon as
I
can and then we have the
hoodie finally kfb merchandise not
orange finally you can be supportive of
me without uh being
orange I kept the
design uh again not too like flashy in
terms of oh my God that's an anime fan
you can't really tell much there's a a
peekaboo Wawa in the pocket and it just
says frog waa on the arm um but the the
hood is obviously inspired by Froggy waa
with the blushing cheeks the ears so
those are um yeah they they stand out of
the hood
and it you can open it in the middle
that was very important to me I want
these things to be
openable I want you to have the choice
to open it yeah there's some some space
for stuff in the pockets and
and the hood is I haven't seen a sample
of this I think yet like an IRL sample
it looks kind of small
here but I don't know how it will be I
asked them to give me a sample
ASAP uh I
think I think I said I don't want the
zipper to close up the whole Hood so I
don't think it's doing
that yeah but it would be really cute
yay made with amphibian lever no no no
no no no so yeah yeah your wallet is
crying yeah I mean the plushy and the
the hoodie are probably more on the
expensive side in terms of like
merchandise more expensive than the
keychain for sure but they're once in a
lifetime froggy well menion ni and
they're really special and you can show
who your true or she is I guess move
this
in the future at kfp meetups maybe we'll
have some people who stick out a little
bit who are not orange but
green and thus we shall question them
why they are wearing green instead of
orange what is the problem with
you I think generally at conventions and
meetups and so on you guys should still
strive to wear your orange merch nice
because I love how you guys stand out so
much and how I can always be sure that
orange people are uh are Wawa people it
makes it very clear for me and it makes
it very clear within the community but
maybe you can wear this more like as an
everyday kind of thing because I think
it's it's it's very uh I mean I mean the
hood is kind of you know
but it's cute I think it has everyday a
peel it could be the sapl no no
no it's not you're not don't let me
don't worry it's still it's froggy
waa with this you can State your love
for froggy Wawa very clearly
M so yeah and there's a bundle sale
where you can have all of these free
items with the sticker or you can have
uh these items individually it will be
up now it's me night now for me at 8:00
a.m.
jst uh so it should go up now Link in
description jenma can you post a link in
the chat too really quickly no need to
pin it but just like spam it in there if
possible like copy paste copy paste copy
paste copy
paste if she's still
listening still not up oh it should be
like maybe in a minute or
so I think
you already did is there is there is it
there is it up okay there's no limited
edition so there will not be a case of
selling
out 44 not found
why give it give the server some
time give it some
time release the Frog yo it's up okay
it's up maybe you guys yeah there's a
little bit too much um um people trying
to access
it ah oh the link there's something in
the link that makes it go to 404 uh you
have
to ah I don't know what there somebody
said something at the end of the link is
like obstructing
the the
link maybe check that out JMA I don't
know the link is bad apparently
the last free symbols guys you got to
delete the last free symbols
apparently yeah it's on Twitter though
the link is on Twitter and also it shows
up in the new products yeah okay I here
here it is updated let's check it out oh
there it is oh that's a a nice price
99 for
me 99 just under a 100 for for the full
set I'm sorry these are just kind of
like expensive items to create as
merchandise um but they will be worth it
they will be worth it ah you can be
green no more orange finally the IE
sword that is orange just
kidding but it will be maybe a nice
change a nice change
[Music]
maybe
yum all right I'll I'll check with them
to send me samples again at ASAP okay
and then you can see but yeah this is
this is the
froggy just bought the full set thank
you get the froggy wa drip get the
froggy waa drip let's become froggy waa
together
EU shipping is by geek Jack yeah usually
geek Jack is the way to go for Europe uh
I think
yeah 86 lb is quite good for real need
is oh I'm glad you think
so thank you instantly order the FL
thank you so much my order is in yay oh
yeah yeah yeah uh maybe consider maybe I
shouldn't be saying this maybe I
shouldn't be advertising is this but I
just want to say it might be cheaper for
Europeans to use like
tensil T NS o or apparently something
called Zen
Market um yeah maybe look it up it it
will make uh it a little bit
easier
apparently yeah other Europeans have
tried it and say it is a good choice use
a proxy I hope I don't get bonked for
saying this I don't know if it's uh I
should not be
advertising but yeah yeah it's like a
shipping forwarder it you will you'll be
able to use a Japanese address and then
I think it overall makes the shipping
cheaper cuz they take care of it kind of
I think and then they send it to
you we heard nothing no you're supposed
to hear it though uh oh oh oh okay it's
okay Jemma says it's okay and Jemma also
says tenso is a good option Jemma
approved approv sticker
approve
yeah okay um I guess we're going to do
the Frog uh tier
list sorry I kind of lost track of uh
when I was going to do that I guess I'm
so happy about the merch I'm so happy
it's so
cute
I'm so happy let's bring back the
[Music]
table let's move it a little bit like
over
here and let me get rid of
the there we
go
okay
uh I I'm I'm I I I
don't I'm not this is like I feel like I
prepared like a presentation for
school
um yeah I'm not I don't know let's just
Let's Do
It um
okay
um i' I've done some
research uh yeah okay okay okay here we
go uh and cl now pretty class okay let's
start I guess with a pretty basic one um
I know everything about frogs so uh
listen listen up beginners of frog
knowledge here is a tree frog it's cute
it looks like a newborn human baby kind
of so cute but also kind of
you um I I like the texture that it has
is very nice very green too um the tree
frog is not just like you know one frog
no there are over 800 species within the
tree frck so I show you this but they
can look very different too but you know
out of these 800 species they are all
you know very different but what makes
it a tree frog you may want to know I
really feel I'm like in [\h__\h] school
right
now well I think you can see it here in
the bottom left on on its foot on its
back foot one bone in their toe in their
back toe is shaped like a claw and that
is the only thing that connects the tree
frogs while they they're they may be
very different from each other in some
ways but this is what connects them that
little claw okay besides that um the
tips of their fingers look kind of
weird yeah everything looks weird but
they're [\h__\h] cute and they use toe
pads to climb not all tree frogs are
that often on trees but yeah they they
can be on trees they like to climb and
they're cute but they're not very
you know dangerous or anything they're
not poisonous although maybe there are
some are there some po okay I don't know
let's just say there are not
any but they are um cute and and I guess
maybe they can be a nice pet okay how do
they taste you do not eat frog do not
eat frog wait I didn't even name
these uh a
obviously red is best uh this is worst
okay I forgot I
forgot let's put him
into just because he's pretty cute and
easy to keep as a pet probably um cuz he
thinks he thinks he's doing something
with that claw but it's really not that
efficient but let's just let him think
that he's doing something there yeah
next we have the pond frog which is also
like kind of same
issue um or I I don't know if it's an
issue but
uh they also have a lot of
species but so they look very different
they can look very different from this
but the P frog is also known as the true
frog and I
I must say what do you mean what do you
mean what do you mean with that how dare
you imply that others are not true frogs
even in German uh it also is like kind
of the same word like I
think yeah are there false frogs what
does it mean I don't like the things
that you
imply they're not poisonous by the way
they come in Greens and Browns so not
very like pretty either
necessarily but they jump pretty well
and they have you know easy movement in
water thanks to their webbing in their
back feet um which you can see here and
also he's not even in water so like
everything about this seems to be a lie
to me I don't know if you're really a
true frog cuz you're in grass and you're
supposed to be a pond frog so get out of
the grass now and go into your stupid
Pond like what the hell I don't like the
implications in makes other frogs feel
false and like they're not real frogs
and and this is just really toxic even
though it's not a toxic frog it seems
like a really toxic environment to
create yeah unlike the environment you
in the grass you should go into the pond
go where you came from bye-bye Pond frog
don't like you very
much not even making up for it with his
like cuteness there's not much cuteness
to him
M
okay I hope you're enjoying this so
far F frog next frog how about how about
um this one
tada this is poison dart frog wow eyes
are so reflective you might see my
credit card number in them got to be
careful
but this is a really really pretty
frog yeah but as you can probably tell
he's very toxic because he listens to
Britney Spears all day
um I would say out of all the frogs they
are probably the most beautiful they
look like the acrylic painting that I
did with Cali the other
day I mean he really kind of does holy
[\h__\h] maybe I should do acrylic paintings
like inspired by poison dart frog color
variations that would actually be like
kind of
Genius yeah it's so nice he looks so
pretty um they're so beautiful they come
in different colors this is just one of
many variations and they're super toxic
though but I mean they're still pretty
small and besides being toxic they don't
have much to go for them um but you know
what I found interesting is their name
poison dart frog not dark Dart d a r t
comes
from them kind of being used uh for blow
darts occasionally back in the day maybe
not now anymore but they were being they
they're poison not them like actually
sticking to the blow dart but no they're
poison I guess was somehow extracted I
wonder how you do that and then you put
it on the blowout and then you and then
you shoot your opponent and they die
yeah that's how they got the launch the
Frog that's how they got their name um
but it wasn't actually that common
anyway like just a just a few people did
that and it kind of got the name from
there even though it's not even that
common besides that they're pretty small
they're 1.5 CM uh averagely
don't ask me what that is in Freedom
Units I don't give a [\h__\h] uh you should
adjust uh also they live in a lot of
places like you know forests but also
other places so they're very versatile
and there is a golden poison dart frog
that has enough poison to kill 20,000
caspers AKA 20,000
mice which is pretty [\h__\h] impressive
but to a human I don't know how
dangerous he can be to a human for his
Beauty and his grace and uh interesting
facts I will put this one
in a tier or whatever this is a s a b c
d e or a b c d e f whatever you want
he's
here good frog a shiny variation yeah
really good frog frog really good frog I
like this frog it's a good frog do you
like this frog it's a good frog
guys next we have
a a frog this is a frog just so you know
this is a frog it's a rain frog
okay rain frog I think is this the
famous frog that people yeah it's the
meme frog right this is the one but he's
actually so tiny did you know that he is
under 1 cm he is so small that you would
probably step on him and kill him if you
were around him and that is so sad that
you look at him in this picture and
you're like oh my God this is the most
precious thing ever while also being
really disgusting but super precious
super cute and wobbly
and it's literally like the epitome of
blo um
but you would probably step on him and
kill
him for ferocious yeah he's a little bit
angry yeah um but even though they're so
small I found it really interesting that
they are born not as
tles but as
froglets what unbelievable that's a
thing holy
[\h__\h] yeah what
what how is that possible he is defying
nature on his own with his tiny little
body maybe because they're small they
can do that I don't know that's
illegal yeah they basically just hatch
his frogs they they do not um they do
not come out as tpes and also because
they're so small it's a little bit
difficult for them to make babies so
when they mate they have a little um
like um glue that they can eject it's
white yes and with the glue they stick
themselves to their
lady and that way they can mate without
like falling
apart and they can stick to their
partner and uh you know they they safely
make baby make baby which is not tadpole
but frog Le yes we have learned so
because of being
small I think very cute but also
very very much not a fret and which is
not a bad
thing small is cute I will put frog for
cute and
here cute
pretty good frog
but not much going for him although
actually by skipping the life stage of
tadpole actually kind of superior cuz
they're just like skipping some levels
there oh I sound like a certain
someone
okay
be
de sorry what's wrong with me okay next
we have uh this [\h__\h] he is big he's
[\h__\h] big look at him I I gave you a
picture where you can see how [\h__\h]
big he is what is
thish do you know it's a [\h__\h] chunker
yeah big [\h__\h] Chun oh lot he coming
he's a can toad he's a can toad toad
what do you mean this is a toad doesn't
look like me at all um yeah I don't have
much information besides he is big and
he's uh really toxic as [\h__\h] really
toxic even though he doesn't even look
so toxic and like it's like why are you
so toxic when you're already so big like
do you really need to be this toxic you
kind of like so [\h__\h] big you're kind
of like a lizard like how are you not
like a [\h__\h] crocodile
why do you need to be toxic why why does
he have such high skilled skills you
know stats what's with these stats man
doesn't seem very fair um there's only
one interesting fact that I can give you
it's that people apparently in Australia
especially I
think think but this is a myth a Hollow
myth people think you can lick this toad
and get high from licking the toad this
is not true do not do this do not try
this at home even if you happen to have
a cane toad at home if you have a can to
at home I would be concerned and I would
move out of this country because this
shouldn't exist frogs should be small
and cute this is basically a
crocodile um K TOS very highly ranked
with tiar zooo I say
no maybe big and strong
but actually I really don't like him I
really don't like
[Laughter]
him like if he at least had some fluff
like fur then the big size would be good
cuz I can give hug but he's not fluffy
so kind of meaningless to be so
big no I want
[Music]
fur oh a s ra thank you thank you for
the
pinky okay I have a few more frogs of
only a
few obviously I can't cover all the
frogs but just interesting ones okay
next you know what this is have you seen
before it's actually a pretty well-known
frog yeah and I like how his nails are
painted it looks so cute his looks so
cute I mean it's from the family of the
fire bellied frog yeah it's a Firebelly
frog fire belly he can spit fire just
like me no this is a lie I take it back
but they have pretty nice colors not as
nice as the poison dart frogs I would
say um but they're pretty nice and um
they like to do something called an unen
reflex which is funny because they say
this is a German word but but I never
heard unen ever before uh but they even
use this in English when describing this
frog the unen reflex is basically just
like them trying to look threatening
they like kind of like look upwards arch
their back or whatever and try to
threaten you whatever it's an unan
reflex not really interesting not really
efficient anyway I think but they do
that to show off their belly and their
fancy colors on their belly are supposed
to look threatening I mean yeah I mean
we all know if a frog looks like this
he's probably poisonous and then will'll
probably stay away so yeah show it off I
guess that is really efficient even to
to humans um but even though he's
poisonous he's very easy to keep as a
pet and he's quite popular to be kept as
a pet but when you keep him as a pet the
colors usually like you know they kind
of grow a little bit darker and more
subdued so to say
so he might not look like is if you keep
him as a pet well also he's always very
hungry he is very hungry frog yeah which
kind of speaks to me as also a hungry um
individual
myself I like this frog I like frog I
like frog interesting frog good frog not
as pretty as poison do frog but he's got
some other stuff going for him uh so I
will put him here too okay okay low tear
for me looks like budget
D kind of
true kind of true but I don't know my my
mind tells me colorful frogs have to be
up
here I'm very
biased okay we have another frog this my
timing is really good now actually I
realized that uh I have seven more
minutes this is really
good t
what the [\h__\h] is this guys really weird
ass
frog this is uh I like to call it the
following name which is not the official
name but it's like a common name that
people call it because it's just easier
to remember I guess it's the titty Kaka
frog titties and kakas titty Kaka
frog me and the
morning this is a titty Kaka frog why is
it titty Kaka frog because titty Kaka
that's a it's a it's a it's a lake titty
Kaka Lake and they uh these frogs only
appear a lake or river it's a body of
water yeah just like um just like coobo
um this this frog only appears in Titi
Kaka Lake yeah only appears there and
even there it appears really really
really really low low low low low in the
water this is water frog you never see a
frog above water frog is the water why
because frog like water okay this is
water frog but really low it's like a OT
ubo under water a submarine
frog and it goes way deeper than other
frogs too pretty impressive submarine
frog TI Kaka ubot
frog oh
yeah not much else to say besides they
have a lot of excess skin as you can
tell he's very um not skinny in that
sense he's still kind of trunky uh but
skinny as in there's a lot of skin there
and they can secrete a sticky whitish
fluid from their
defense um and that's pretty much it
he's just very exclusive he a a rare
oops what the [\h__\h] he's a rare specimen
okay but I don't know he looks I don't
like him much for his exclusivity and
his funny name I put him
here okay now we go to the best frogs
that there
are number one frog bird
of course is real frog exist
IRL uh nice frog frog bird is beautiful
I love frog bird I miss frog bird I
think of frog bird all day frog bird is
beautiful frog bird is the man who can
make all the ladies
SW he's very long and lengthy and tall
and that makes him very attractive
to
that's right froggy waa and I don't know
why I'm using this
fixture it's the one that I had at my
hand this is just froggy wa right
now and frog froggy waa obviously
together forever in love with frog bird
all the way up here love forever frog
frog yuua and frog bird I will never
forget the love that we share
yeah froggy Wawa kind of is um its own
tier the highest tier of frogs obviously
and the truest frog of them all more
true than the true
frogs and she is looking forward to
entertain you for almost a full week H
for this exciting very exciting frog
wink WN of froggy waa
so tomorrow we have frogs Adventure we
have a lot of little fun games and I
I've been planning for months now to
play these during frog weeks I I I asked
for permissions for these games a long
time ago uh frogs Adventure is a cute
one FR detective free finally that game
was already out last time I think but I
was like okay I I'll play it next time
so I still have something frog detective
is always fun we know this there there
is proof and spin frog is just a little
fun I don't
know dorky game and frog song I'm really
looking forward to even the the Twitter
of this game has been looking forward to
me playing it apparently they retweeted
my schedule they're looking forward to
it I think the Frog song might be a
really really really good game and it's
a bit on the longer side so I'm putting
it on the weekend to be earlier and then
on Sunday from AI waa will again make an
appearance on the Easter stream once
again we're we're doing an Easter stream
um members will know that I'm trying
hard to improve it in terms of like
content new games and all that I talked
about it in a members only stream uh
yeah H please look forward to it it's
going to be a VR stream not everybody
will be using VR but there will be some
games that are focused on VR and some
games that are focused not so much on VR
I mean you don't need to use like V art
trackers in order to play these things
but yeah it will be at midnight for me
uh and there will be Ian and ID
participants yay and now I already got
to go because I'm directing you uh thank
you guys for watching let's have a fun
frog week I'm going to rest my throat
even more until tomorrow I'll see you
for frogs Adventure please get the
froggy
merch and froggy will entertain you
hopefully while kiaha is gone goodbye in
when we
say
actually this uh week we'll be saying
Arab Dy okay okay okay byebye got to go
stay stay so I can redirect
[Music]
you