[Music]
hmm
hello ah welcome back
[Music]
all right today we're going to begin
our investigation our interrogation
of our prime suspects
i wonder where they could be
i've trapped them in a containment
cell and we will be interrogating them
um here are our prime suspects tonight
[Music]
one's missing
yes you can't run away
[Music]
holly
be back yes never leaves for long
i guess we'll start at the end then
[Music]
like creature what do you have to say
for your officer
it wasn't me officer i didn't eat the
chicken
you want to tell us a little bit no i'm
okay go ahead
shut up prisoner shut up
oh my god
[Music]
me
ah i have managed to
capture recapture the prisoners they
almost escaped
all right ina tell us about yourself
i am i am not a taco
i am 100 human i like to talk to the
ancient ones for
let me knowledge that down
next prime suspect
[Music]
get getting
but actually amelia amelia
i i don't think you should be
investigating me
i actually i actually think
you might have noticed that i'm missing
my hats
who stole my hats is that what we're
trying to find out today
who's maybe maybe that's it those are
the hats
who smell my hats i am not the suspect
since i am not wearing my hat
i don't know that sounds suspicious to
me
huh
next up we have the dangerous
not shark get up
[Music]
eh
she looks too innocent nonsense
and next up we have uh supposedly
death herself
um so whatever you think that i did
um it was legal in the underworld so you
can't arrest me
i hate to break it to you but uh good
luck
it's not going to work you all are being
suspected of being mythological
creatures
what do you guys have to say for
yourselves i agree
you're not going to deny it
it's obvious i don't think there's
anything yeah but are we supposed to
i want my hats i want my hat to wear in
my hat
[Music]
i'll put that in the key we will always
[Laughter]
i need my hats otherwise i'm naked
i'm gonna ask you guys a few questions
to gauge your
suspicion levels
[Music]
i would ask if that's all right but you
have no option
[Music]
first kelly
this is only for uh research
interrogation purposes um
could you give us a rough estimate of
cup size
um i don't know what that means what are
you asking me
i'm afraid i'm afraid that i do not
understand the question
if you could perhaps ask another one or
rephrase it
uh i don't think i have to ask anybody
else besides kiara
huh stop looking at me
i know exactly what her size is
you no you don't be sharing with us why
would you ever know that
it is it is actually
double b incorrect
wait no not like i even understand the
question
so whatever your answer was uh was not
correct
so nice try um i have touched i
know no you haven't no you haven't
don't lie to the people you're making up
stories oh maybe it was my teacher
maybe it was my dream i don't know that
is equally just as terrifying to me so
maybe we should
i dream about you every day callie don't
like that
don't say that thank you i absolutely
hate that
kylie you won't kill me for asking that
question right
[Music]
wait a minute i'll have to keep them in
the container tell a lot of times
no we can make a deal
all right next on our list of
interrogations
i know you have a giant fork have you
ever killed anyone with that fork
[Music]
suspicious with or without legs
oh well very suspicious i will write
that down
uh i also heard a rumor that uh
when you go in a pool you need floaties
is this true
[Music]
i told you that
who supplied you this information
it's just a rumor i heard
all right so it yes
it's a rumor i can swim
merry christmas i have to be very
suspicious
indeed next
up
[Music]
well will we start my investigation now
about the hats
ah not quite not quite
okay what is it then uh i saw your sword
during your debut hey does that sword
also double as a spatula
ah no you can't flip burgers with it
uh my sword
might be looking like a toy but it is a
real sword
so so you've used it before
is that a couple live
actually uh i
what's wrong with using it though i'm
protecting myself and protecting you
i protect the world i'm a good girl
i'll take note of that
please do and you said yourself that you
have
a bird brain
do you also have a bird body can you fly
well if i use my transformation belt i
turn into
phoenix and then i can fly but i'm not
so allowed to use my transformation belt
in this world so
right now maybe not
okay okay
[Music]
is that a bad thing ah well
if you're found guilty of being
mythological
yeah i'm not i didn't say anything in
the beginning i'm not
mythical or mythological
[Music]
no no no no no no no i am i have
a question recorded right here wait
didn't you say that it was obvious and
we shouldn't even be ashamed of it
like you were literally the one that
said that i mean
honestly like if she's going to arrest
us or anything we can just uh
especially you kel we can just kill her
that's actually a great point now that
you actually mentioned that
yeah thanks for bringing that up oh yeah
well container you can't get out
wow the lab is over we have taken over
no please don't kill me yeah it's our
show now
okay i'll let you keep on playing amelia
keep on playing
last one we'll let you think you have
the power
your bangs your squishy yes squishy
bangs
uh will you let me squeeze them later
[Music]
excuse me excuse me i must say this is
unfair treatment
why are you only suspecting us free of
any crimes but
not inna uh yes it is guilty too
i suspect i'm guilty okay all
all right now i have a few more
questions for you very suspicious
suspect
oh no that color
does it have a meaning the color you
wear
it's a secret
are you perhaps owned
only three
[Music]
last times um could you tell us your
shoe size
let's use slime
for a research of course medical
purposes i have to compare it to
footprints that found
at a crime scene
what what scale are we going by bananas
okay let me see let me see my hat is
um one banana
[Music]
don't tell her anything don't tell her
anything all right
noted noted thank you thank you for your
cooperation
everyone
we will now the second
installment of our interrogation game
[Music]
wow
all right to explain the rules the way
this will be working
everybody has questions two questions
and there are answers to those questions
now we will all guess
the answer to that person's question
when asked and
whoever gets the most points at the end
mommy let me dig around under my desk
for a second
shove myself a shuffle
it can't be yeah
i wanted to make yago proud i need that
statue
so if you know each other if we know
each other so well
you might be able to win
can we have you know draw the scoreboard
please
wait what what am i drawing uh the
scoreboard up at the top
the green one and now you had one job
hey amelia can you crank up the music ah
sure
drink up them tubes please yep got it
so i can bob my head just a little bit
hold on
is this the right one
[Music]
[Applause]
the jams have been pumped
i like it very much me too me too
[Music]
you know you had one job wait i thought
you know you didn't draw the scorpion so
i drew the school
communication problem
[Music]
i guess that's the problem when you talk
to brits
[Laughter]
sick bear i don't think so
[Music]
what a waste of a cute taco i i guess i
don't really like it
[Music]
oh yeah okay okay
let's begin the questioning
[Music]
okay
whoa
so what is my favorite
food number one takoyaki
number two cucumber salad
number three cup noodles i know i know
pick me pick me pick me pick me pick me
anything i know
i don't know i have to write it down you
have to write it down
okay gosh these beginners
oh that's tough
mine for one think it's cucumber salad
i have locked in my uh
[Music]
no cheating no cheating
oh wait totto wait you guys can see no
oh my god it's fine
[Music]
okay
there's a competition about getting the
least points right um
why would it why would it ever be a
competition for getting the least amount
of points
that's not how it works in what universe
does that make any sense
in big brain universe moving along
[Music]
okay oh do i delete that okay
manually right next next question
[Music]
how many chicken nuggets does kiara eat
per day
eh 5 15
or 53
i think she's trying i
[Music]
actually don't write it down and then
we'll oh yeah
[Music]
5 15 or 53.
chinking
[Music]
i'll have your answers one moment yes
i'll write it now kelly you should know
me the best we've met so many times in
the underworld
well maybe oh i was using the eraser
hold on okay i mean
i think i know i'm pretty sure that i'm
correct
that does not know how to tricky
questions
so okay i have
i've finished putting my answer in that
big review
why should i write down mine now no no
no just tell us
okay the answer is
[Music]
53.
i expected i expected nothing less
future franchise owner yeah indeed
um the thing is that's not the only
thing i eat but uh
you know uh i'm i'm a sporty type i work
out every day do you even lift bro
[Music]
can we go to the next question
all right
[Music]
okay
next up my questions shall i be the one
to ask the question
ah yes okay my first question is
what is calliope's favorite method of
erasing human life
first piano falling on the head
second medieval flail third
heat stroke at summer comiket
okay what was the second one i think
medieval flail
it's um it's a really interesting
contraption it's a metal ball
with many spikes on it
oh and what does it do uh you bashed it
into people's skulls
ah it's quite lovely
[Music]
aha
everybody has their answers in
[Music]
kelly be honest be honest here
be honest
okay the answer was two medieval flames
yeah
i know you so well telling me
ah i knew it i
[Music]
i'm honest i just knew that the most
the most aggressive way to kill someone
would be your favorite
[Music]
i guess that makes sense oh yeah you're
not wrong you're not wrong
so
[Music]
are we ready i'm ready
excellent okay
how many teeth does gouda have
32 55
or 28.
[Music]
i'm not good with numbers what were the
numbers again
[Laughter]
for 28.
[Music]
i'm gonna pick a random one because i
have no f
in clue when then down
[Music]
okay all ready keep in mind kuda is a
baby shark
excuse me i am 9 435
she's kind of old man
[Music]
you bamboozle us there
should i give points to people who ask
the question or no
no i don't think so good yes give us a
pity point this is hard
okay okay i think this is fine
i won one time i did
55 okay okay
wait wait wait but then shouldn't i have
two points now since you added one point
to everyone who asked the question
no i took it away i i added a point for
you for asking a question i think i
added one for eno too
[Music]
okay my turn
what is my favorite drink
i see
[Laughter]
[Music]
what is a white claw
you don't need to care about that we all
know what it is
drink of the intellectuals what do they
call it in atlantis
[Music]
i don't know what it is what is it and
i'm telling you
[Music]
hold on
oh girl you should get this one right
he's alright
[Music]
oh
my favorite drink
[Music]
[Laughter]
finally
[Music]
aside from the fact that it keeps people
alive but you know
ah he knows next
[Music]
okay what is my favorite
ride in amusement park
hey oh otter coasters
e ferris wheel three
drop tower
[Music]
i feel like carousel could be difficult
don't like any of those you don't like
fun
i like fun but like
live on the live on the edge
don't you fly kiara aren't you like used
to it did you
yeah but but the flying is like actually
like
fun and roller coaster and stuff is like
i'm gonna die
oh actually i guess it doesn't matter
[Laughter]
[Music]
this this is why
of course yeah we all have different
answers
okay the correct i mean i think
[Music]
the correct answer
yes i am starting to win the reason that
i chose a is because i imagined you
uh enjoying watery rides like floating
on your tentacles like an inner tube
that was the image that came into my
mind and i thought it was so cute
yeah yeah i want to go to a water park
again
[Music]
one of these was one of kiara's previous
life's
jobs a flight attendant
b idol c
fitness trainer
um
[Music]
shall i repeat yes
what did i do before flight attendant
idol fitness trainer uh okay
ah i know i do you really know yeah
sure you know
[Music]
i don't think and heal me
are we getting baited it's not the life
of somebody who's about to play it
feels like it honestly okay
[Music]
the answer is
all of them
listen to me listen to me
that is not what we agreed upon of
course
[Music]
i know that's the thing
i guess that makes sense though yeah it
may find a waste
[Laughter]
it's not totally unfair but still kind
of a
kind of a dick move
[Music]
so my next question is a very important
question
number two what is calliope
scythe made of a stainless steel
b plastic see
the bones of ancient demon lords
[Music]
what do you think
do you have your answers i do
okay reveal them to me please
[Music]
what's it called i can i reason my
answer
okay y'all i'll i'll listen to your
answer you
you just started out with whole life you
are broke deaf so
your weapon currently is made out of
plastic but it will be upgraded in the
future
hiatus that makes sense that's um
that's an interesting answer that you
get and very well
and very well reasoned however it is not
correct
let's try the s the answer is a actually
um i'm glad that nobody gave the really
eggy answer that was
c uh because that was that's absolutely
so silly if i used the bones of ancient
demon lords like my scythe would suck it
would be so terrible
like like bones really when you're
trying to cut someone's neck open
no it doesn't work very well so i've
seen the videos where they turn
turn stuff into knives maybe your scythe
[Music]
this is a hard one are you ready okay
it's time to test those brains in there
ladies
all righty i'm ready to go
and for all of you at home eh
question number two from guna
what is luke
is he a a fish
b an emergency ration
a c a high amplitude ultra low frequency
deep sea sound discovered by the us
national oceanic and atmospheric
administration also known as noaa in
originally thought to have come from a
marine animal no double
look stop it would you like to hear the
choices again
nope i'm good actually um do you do you
intend for us to write the answer
completely or can we just write name p
or c
[Music]
amplitude nope
ultra i know the answer hello
[Music]
but i have to get this one right
the correct answer the answer is
[Music]
wait wait so hold on a minute hold on so
you're telling me that um
you can eat you can eat that little guy
you like eating like
do you do you like you do that
yeah someone wasn't paying
attention in good history
someone was very busy
[Music]
i'm not going crazy don't worry it's not
like i haven't slept it's not a problem
i'm great i think all of us are running
on really low sleep
[Music]
all right now that conducts the
questions wait oh i have one more never
mind
oh my turn
[Music]
this question actually decides
everything ah
true depends uh
where did i put all my points into
a intelligence oh b
look c
melee is it not melee i always read it
as melee
it is melee it must be merely
all my life i've been reading it as
mainly you cannot come see
it i'd be really disappointed if you
were just a really lucky detective
so i'm going to go ahead and not choose
that one for the sake of
wishing to believe you're not just super
lucky
[Music]
it might it might bite me but
i once yeah
[Music]
it must be okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
it says
yeah you know what a for f yeah
don't worry about it be good the correct
answer
was a b look ah
oh my gosh what really you're just very
lucky
yeah um
you did that you pulled that [\h__\h] on us
you will not be so lucky anymore
you know who you're dealing with you
know who you're dealing with
i'm sure you're mythical creatures
please no
i'll do whatever you say i mean sure
like me me and eno maybe
but i mean
good is very cute but i don't know about
you
i don't know if you could actually
all right next we will move on
to our next portion
[Music]
are you going to draw with that because
we're in the drawing section now
yes cannot
[Music]
[Laughter]
no toys at the dinner table oh hi
can i bring tentacles to the dinner
table
i've got a fork what about
what about chicken uh yeah does look
kind of tasty
oh no she's too far enough
don't try it don't even try i don't want
to buy
but i'm hungry no i put it away already
that's not fun and with this appointment
all right the next section we'll do
should it be one minute or two minute
drawings
what do you guys think
30 seconds 30 seconds
i'm using a mouse it's not fair me too
fine i will nerf nerf my hands i will
use my tentacles
i couldn't find my pen the way it's
going to work
[Music]
is we will draw from memory no cheating
uh you can look at other people's art
while you're drawing for reference
but you can't look at each other okay
okay and you have one minute and we're
gonna draw one person at a time so first
we're gonna draw ina
and then chat will vote for the two best
ones it's not a popularity contest okay
it's about the soul in the art
i thought i draw myself too um
sure yeah do i just doodle
draw yourself all right let me put the
timer on
[Music]
oh god drawing with a mouse is so
[\h__\h] hard
[Laughter]
also i'm left-handed but i'm using my
right hand
ah i cannot capture
enos beauty i can you'll see
well you have a tablet how do you know
that you don't know that
i know you i see that i say it looks so
pretty it must be
tablet drawing call this pretty
yeah i don't know do you everything you
do is pretty
thank you for the compliment
[Music]
yes what was your favorite food again
cup of noodles oh
thank you i'm sorry i have kind of a
bird brain i lose memory in
like three seconds it's okay
uh i didn't start the timer correctly
but
i put 58 minutes 58 minutes
damn we'll call it we'll call it there
okay i'm done ah
okay now it's time for chat
participation
you can play god kiara
[Music]
please someone i need to win here good
uh
you mind explaining what that is
[Music]
the tentacles look like an explosion
behind her
[Music]
i don't feel like drawing the pattern
right now so i am just going to go ahead
and improvise and tell everyone what is
on the tentacles
now what time's up
oh time is up okay i will stop writing
let me link with a word
just in case hi
a lot of cali a lot of cali
and guys
do it for the boing boing
[Music]
i'll give all three of you points okay
yay
[Music]
thank you chad for cheering for me i
appreciate you very much
okay that still doesn't help me
i was going to say not really not much
changed huh
[Music]
yes
do we even have time to drill everyone
um yeah yeah it'll be a minute each i
think we'll be fine
gotta go fast okay next we will drop
italy next
[Music]
i can take some time off oh this will be
easy
yeah if you don't want a job you don't
have to all right start timer
[Music]
sorry i'll wait up it
dirty cheater
oh hello kelly i see we have the same
idea
are you serious
so i'm doing something right now one
[Music]
second
hey i'm back and what the hell am i
singing
what
[Music]
what on earth am i saying oh it's a
picture of you
five more seconds
[Music]
there's some nuggies in there too
i am not happy is that a novel falling
it looks just like here
[Music]
you vote for your favorite
favorite one i mean
the only one emilia
that's the only close one i don't know
what you mean mine is very very accurate
to you
no
[Music]
the only one who has respect for this
majestic phoenix vote for emilia
i see kelly
[Music]
mm-hmm i will take the point
thank you i know that you did not
deserve it i have to say this this time
i think i did you make me a big angry
i have to say it's fine you'll forget
about it in like 30 seconds
no i haven't yes you are
[Music]
oh my god
what was funny about that
[Music]
i good i'm gonna give you a pity point
cause cha
thank you
i actually what was i just angry about
that's what i thought just don't worry
about it it's fine i think there was
something i was angry about no
there was nothing there was nothing
continue drawing me please
[Music]
alrighty
okay i haven't seen your drawing by the
way but it will be like a fresh new
experience for my eyeballs as soon as i
look at them
is y'all calling again
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
we're busy
all right chop we'll put it to a vote
all right i will now look at the
finished art pieces here we go like in a
bonus point i'm the only one that i drew
your site
do i get a bonus point because i drew it
with a mouse
because that's it you gotta say
amelia is pretty accurate
i'll do it a different way maybe kelly
can choose to give points too
maybe no i see i see now that you're
just gonna be
i see suddenly you change the rules
what would that sensei say
[Music]
says that she spots a nasty cheater
so maybe we put it back to the chat okay
[Music]
amelia
it was not fair yeah i'll buy it
i think that the drawing is all right
yeah don't worry you also get
consolation prizes for participating
okay is that what i think it is is that
what i think it is no
no
i need a good point too because i feel i
feel like you should get a point for
trying
uh-huh tried your best
[Music]
you know what i'll take one for the team
i have many golden diego trophies at
home
[Music]
oh i almost erased the wrong
window i want justice
i demand justice
fine i will use a mouse for this one
okay you're better
you're the best out of us
[Music]
wait who are we drawing good up yeah i
mean time star
[Music]
just hands me that time is ticking
i will give it a surprise for myself
[Music]
you smell like a fish
make sure you draw me with big teeth
i'm really trying here okay
you have like the hoodie so bizarre
[Music]
oh my god
[Laughter]
blushy bless you oh yeah it works
this doesn't look like good at all
i'll be there
[Laughter]
hey i'll give you thick teeth i can't
bring something else so i almost know
something else
yeah i don't know what happened
this chat is voting i see a lot of of
course
uh
[Music]
i can't [\h__\h] sneeze drain
the thing is like i started laughing
because of how shitty my drawing was and
while i was laughing i was still drawing
and then i thought then the six thousand
likes
exactly while i was laughing
it was not on purpose oh my god
but i'm glad i won with this masterpiece
davinci i think
yeah you deserve it for something like
that
i could i could feel the soul
it had very
interesting characteristic oh thank you
hearing that from you you know makes me
very happy
okay now you guys get to draw me
[Music]
just give me the point
okay i'll start i'm sorry
[Music]
i just make
i don't have time you have 30 seconds
i don't think i can do this anymore i've
been awake for too long
so i'm gonna go simple on this one
[Music]
there we go 10 seconds left no
10 seconds no kelly that is good
[Music]
oh i like that one
oh that's good what is that
oh my god okay
are you trying to tell me something
this is holo e and i tried to like you
know
uh since you wrapped up the
collaboration i tried to put in that
spirit there
so since you were so nice and now you're
also doing the collab you know
uh as a big thanks and it's the
gratitude ah
you go in for pizza i just got it now
guys
it's just a chance i had to fly off
somewhere real quick
i'll join back in just a moment okay
before you
hear it you rejoin tell me before okey
dokey
okay um you get to vote
i'm supposed to draw a magnifying glass
but i ran out of time so
i used to have one bulging eye
yeah i gotta say i really like widows i
like this cannon
yeah i have to take hallie
yes that's illegal
it's a classic dog
smart dog now just in case i respawn
over all of you and i'm very big i
apologize
ah are you going to rejoin right now yes
all right
go to the only screen
oh come hither frozen
it froze oops uh one second
[Music]
bye
we're back ah yeah
[Music]
okay let the voting commence vote for
your favorite
what's up
[Music]
dude
thank you for liking my really odd
drawing
when you try pretty accurate all right i
think the chat has picked
two i see i see two a lot it's
uh good ass and
[Music]
in my drawing i am i wanted to i wanted
to uh show the truth
if you get what i'm saying
we now you don't need to just don't
worry about it
you now have the golden yago winner
[Music]
congratulations
[Laughter]
distressed honestly it's not like i
needed a win or anything
all right don't worry guys okay you'll
forget about it
it's all about the consolation prize
wait we got a consolation
[Music]
wait shouldn't i get the
most consolidating consolation
[Music]
can i give mine to someone else uh why
don't you want it it's a cut it's a kind
gesture
please don't touch my head
but amelia i just don't have a question
where are my hats a great mystery
to be sure we could solve that in the
next episode
yes so you're going to scream without
your hats until then
let's see about it maybe i'll travel to
different dimensions you get my hats and
then
i'll lose them again you know how i am
you
[Music]
she likes to decorate them ah i don't
know what you're talking about
i'm just very suspicious that's why
she's hiding her tentacles today
it is the weather we are having today
isn't it
[Music]
special announcement
oh yeah oh yeah that was perfect
[Music]
i already forgot give me one second
while i set it up
yay
[Music]
i'm waiting for this
i hate where are my hats
every chicken didn't i had to just have
them like a second ago
[Music]
all right um you guys
the link you can click on it
in the secret channel
[Music]
all right we will now watch
the voiced promotion video
bye exciting
oh my god well count it down and
you guys have it ready uh-huh okay
three two one
[Music]
i got chicken come to the shark's side
there you go the chip ones are calling
[Music]
it's elementary paint it
well i mean you saw the important things
[Music]
hello live english
okay um that's that's about it
i guess we'll have to say goodbye from
here like this
good is too small
can i can i make an announcement yes yes
uh i am doing my first
non-debut live stream in two hours keep
in mind i've been awake for over 24
hours
and i'll be streaming fall guys after
this for the first time let's see how
[\h__\h] insane i can get i thought i
said the effort
i was gonna stand
kelly how many adverts did you drop i
mean all right let's move on to the next
step
does anybody else hey that's nothing but
anything you guys have any other
announcements you'd like to
oh you go first gouda you go first i'm a
shark
um indeed
my announcement um is i recently
released a song
uh my first original song and today
i have a special guest coming to uh talk
about the song
and uh have a bit of a zatsudan chat uh
together
um and that is uh chiara
never sleep never sleep 48 hours here we
[\h__\h] go
yeah but she dropped another one
8 30 jst at 8 30 pm which is
i don't really understand jsp sorry um i
will post
uh i will schedule the live stream very
soon
and yes it is very well i mean if
if you're i mean it would depending upon
where you live but like i said i don't
really understand
somewhere in the world yeah the
underworld we don't play
but i will post uh i will schedule it so
everyone who is interested in listening
to kiara and i thought for a bit
um is absolutely able to come a private
uh making out session between the
timeless and the death
that will never happen
can i maybe i can just invite you to
someone else want to come
be instead i'll be there
you can't get rid of me now what am i
doing
all right that's all i have to say any
other announcements
no no no i'm gonna know okay thank you
for watching
our first collab stream i hope you guys
had fun did you guys have fun
thank you everyone yes i feel straight
from beginning to end
top 10 anime betrayals what are you
talking about
what are you talking about thanks
everyone
follow hello live en on everywhere yes
please
and use the hashtag use the whole live
english
holo myth and subscribe to all of us if
you want to keep seeing the stuff that
we're putting out we'll be doing more
collab streams and
all kinds of fun stuff because
everyone's talented in their own way and
we all do a bunch of different things
though
yeah yeah yeah
it's like that exactly
all right thank you everybody for coming
to collab stream
cheerios
[Music]
bye
you