[Music]
I still wonder I Was Made if I could
only see oh please
make me new
person perfect for you pretending like
it's all
just what I want I need
[Music]
do
you show me on a i you up sh I don't
even know what to do with this
man good
night
[Music]
night nothing with
see break me shake
me you never see what I want
what I need oh do
[Music]
you I don't even know what to do with
this Mir
[Music]
fall
in you make me fall in love
[Music]
you make me fall in
love fall in love
[Music]
there reflection going on there don't
the
I still I
was
[Music]
I never see what I want what I need oh
do you oh do you
[Music]
like
you don't know what to
[Music]
do
night you dis and and
[Music]
hey
oh
K
[Music]
[Laughter]
hello hello k
[Music]
good
evening I feel so hot so warm
here so
warm oh my God wa hi are you doing the
oh my God like the hard
thing oh my God KY
hi I've seen I think I've seen people
recreate that with me but can some
somebody recreate that with like me
reacting like that towards
kfp oh my God kfp
hi how Breaking Bad finally hit you I
talked about it
in I think yeah the beginning of my last
stream right my last half of XL stream
if you want to hear it I should probably
you know shut up about it already so you
just finished it
congratulations I just started breaking
so nope let's not break Saul poor guy uh
because of Saul no uh better call sorry
a little bit of a brain empty
moment because of
sa I can commit all the crimes I
want because because of Soul no matter
how much trouble I'll just get out
because of soul I won't get into
jail he's gonna pay my
[Music]
[Laughter]
bail oh I could write a whole song about
that he should hire me
yeah he should hire me me to yeah
perform a song a theme song for him
mhm what's wrong chunky wony what's
wrong um I have an
alarm that goes off in 1 hour 37 minutes
why do you think that
is guess
well actually one good guess wow decent
guess about oven oh another beef okay
I'm not cooking the beef
B that one is supposed to be with
mushrooms and I feel like if you take
the mushrooms away it's not much of a
beef Boron anymore also it was looks
kind of like
man I I'm just cooking some spaghet de
bologa but with red wine
uh I've cooked it for one and a half
hours so
far prepared everything and have been
cooking it slow cooking it I guess cuz
it said like cook it for one and a half
hours or two or three ideally the more
the better and I'm like
okay sure I guess I'll keep it
cooking then it will be done after my
stream yeah
yeah I uh I did some stuff before my
stream I was productive
baby I uh like my place like I cleaned
up
everything and prepped everything nicely
um before the girls came over right but
then when they were here the whole ret
thing created a big mess obviously in my
fridge and outside of the
fridge and lots of stuff to wash and all
the the bed sheets gotta wash that and
this and that so I was just cleaning the
whole day and getting things back on
track back back to its original state
thanks for the
raid would you and other members
recommend this you mean the game sure of
course of course I
would no
no no
did
ni good
I damn
it damn
it a
a okay it's time to retire
I hereby I'm
retiring I'm useless I'm
unprofessional I am
ashamed I am hereby ending my
activities as
me it's a second time just in a
different
way what happened with the copy paste
man why did it not
work why did why
why I apologize I'll do naked I'll do
naked okay I'll do it I'll do
it where is that Christina mon the
art barely anyone noticed
yeah but the ones that did are like
probably sharing it
around you little
shits
whatever
whatever whatever for people who don't
know it seems I have spoiled the next
Advent calendar video because it was in
my copy paste and I I I accidentally
switched links when I or didn't switch
them when I did the starting now tweet
yeah well it's okay uh yeah in Japan
it's already the 10th
so
yeah I just copy pasted it so that I
could send it to the Advent calendar
team to put it into to the website make
it
ready I'm sorry I'm
sorry but it doesn't matter right it
doesn't matter in the end it's coming
out in a few hours anyway and and it's
my calendar and I can do what I want
with
it I can do what I want with it
ah [\h__\h] okay calm down everybody calm
down calm
down is this the real link I'm going to
make a new starting toe
it is this is it double checking what
does it lead to okay it leads to my
stream all right ad Calendar's R yeah
yeah see this is exactly like why I
shouldn't have done it this year why did
you guys not stop me how did you not
foresee this my
uselessness uh anyway so I'm cooking
yeah okay
please um let me cook I
will uh stop the cooking in one and a
half hours I'll just turn off the heat
and that's it and then I'll come back
but I join and first thing I hear is
this it's
very very dramatic you just missed me my
naked DOA you came too late I just naked
doad my way out of my shame
shame
[Music]
shame but yeah how are you guys are you
chilling I'm chilling I didn't take a
nap today I'm I'm drinking Coca-Cola to
make up for the lack of nap and for me
already having used a lot of my body
energy today I went I went a little bit
shopping for
groceries
and
stuff Cola helps not much I
guess
yeah
yeah there's not much energy there right
now but which chilling we're chilling
we're going to play Path of Exile and
then we're going to Yap while doing
so I want to Yap let's y eating cookies
what kind of cookies is it Christmas
cookies is it Christmas cookies please
help me it's Christmas cookie please
tell me please tell me it's Christmas
cookies I just want to I'm just I just I
I need to make
sure I'm holding my breath yes yay
hooray okay I don't know what's wrong
with me I'm just weird I'm going to play
the game
Now is it going to be [\h__\h] loud is it
going to be is it going to be [\h__\h] no
it's all
right I guess it's all
right
uh goal to finish one I don't know like
I don't know how long this game is I'm
just I'm just chilling detected out of
dat GPU driver please up
no okay wow I know you couldn't see it
now now you shall see look at
me
Heisenberg wow my picture is so pretty
oh I look cool I haven't seen this
screen before I think that one looks so
funny this one also looks pretty funny
they all look kind of funny but this one
looks the funniest can you see it can
you see his nose say her name say my
name say my
name say my name say my isenberg be like
say my name say my
name if
you uh say my name say my name and then
I will cook
some
uh you're okay no I I need to stop
no no I
i i i revoke my perms for
freestyling I've revoke my own perms
hereby I've revoked my
perms I do not have the
right
yeah cuz I'm not good at it whoa what is
that oh right I wanted to look into the
cash shop is it safe to look into the
cash shop and uh now are the
titties
fixed can I
look then what I heard that no the the
bug is still
there damn it damn it as long as you
don't click back and forth back and
forth between the pages or
what I mean it's probably fine even if I
showed
him right
like YouTube YouTube's going to be nice
about it
right how do I get into the cash shop
anyway microtransaction
shop wa thank you for playing Pap Exel
Early Access when is the real access
you have no microtransactions to
display click below to buy some from our
shop what
where here
oh there's 29 armor
things where are the where are the
boobies how would they appear this one
looks
nice partially gives me
[Music]
me like vibes from the recent like the
armor pieces vibes from the recent Zelda
game uh and Elder
ring this one is very very
very d word the d word that I shall not
say oh my God what why would I want to
look like that what maybe as a whole set
that would look
interesting like these two
combined that one's interesting
too oh
cool back attachment variations what do
you mean variations is there variation
between though this one's cool too but
what about like a simple Japanese girl
school
uniform like is that too much to ask
for if you click there's different Tes
oh well this one's kind of sheesh
crazy that one's cool but I don't like
the head why
[Laughter]
[Music]
why that look would look like I don't
know a necromancer from outer
space
Oh can you any of these can you wear
them without the Hat don't use the Hat
oh so you you can you can just not use
the Hat oh okay
oh how much is 315 in real money how
much what's the conversion rate
here what are we
talking
oh 30
uhhuh so this is like what is this 45
bucks
this
one wow
expensive H yeah but there's no school
uniform so or like a bunny suit or wait
what the [\h__\h] is show me
that
oh what replaces the standard effect on
Portals you create with the albino to
toad King what do you
mean the portal turns into a
toad I walk into a toad or what what
does that
mean the Blue Portal turns into a
toad okay I'm me I want that
[Music]
what portal skins is kind of interesting
interesting
idea don't invite
me please tell me people got this
one oh my God
what oh my God it's so
big I I got to do the DND D again huh
okay she wanted not yet oh she's got a
she's got
a this is
ridiculous I love
it
o what what what does that what would
that look
like like on this one I guess I can tell
on this one I can't
[Music]
finisher effect oh so it's like when you
kill a
[Music]
monster imuse a weapon blah blah blah it
amplifies the deaths of rare monsters oh
[Music]
interesting extra character slot cursor
pack oh
cute hide out what do you mean Hideout
uh but it's utility skins only for now
Hideout area do do we get
like our own little Hideout area later
or
oh something for
guilds
M stash
tabs
what shut
up anyhow you need stash tabs e the tabs
are the Act important ones
what is this ah is ah is this like extra
space in my inventory too
or is it just like sorting
[Music]
functions uh just Das for your
bank storage in town extra space extra
space in your St oh okay well if I run
out I might want to buy
one they should make one but like okay I
I I I would say they should make an like
a like a bigger extension for your
inventory that you always carry with you
but paying that with real money doesn't
seem
right
so
oh can I look at
them
oh o
ew
interesting is this
just oh so you look
Speedy leaving blood Trails behind you
seems like a very smart
idea better call all though sorcerer
wand M cool looks good yeah these things
look cool I want the Toads the most out
of everything I want my portals to be a
toad this is what I Aspire towards I
think this will be my
goal okay
uh wait what the [\h__\h] thank you that's
kind of
cute now stop disturbing me guys
what were we doing uh travel okay I
guess I just go back to my
portal yeah that feels more like a
jailbird but okay like your name sounds
more like a jail
bird where are we we're in the old gum
farmlands and we need to find the
village the proper
Village oh oh
oh haven't we already explored this
beginning
part I know I know that map's reload
like re
reset I need to relearn how to
fight but uh have I seen this part yet
before buy the Frog now what what
do I have
but oh wait
no wait which one I think the pink one
is
cute wait can I not look at each one
specifically pink is cute though wait oh
there we go purple
pink green stinky
poison M
cute but this one's cheaper
why let me look is it just a color or is
it more than the color a the tongue is
different
too is it just because pink is more
expensive besides the tongue it's pretty
similar I wonder I want to see them in
action
I I'll get this
one 200 coins worth it 20 bucks now we
shall make a
portal how do I how do I make it work do
I need to activate
it do I need to restart the game I have
to equip it where is
it
okay oh
make
you it's so
big it's so big and so fat and it's like
melting and it's disgustingly
[Music]
cute I can get eaten by frog let's go oh
oh there's no animation of me walking in
and it's closing its mouth okay that's
lame I want to refund I want to refund
immediately well do the others also see
no they don't see my portals right they
should see them they should see my
portal at least you guys see my portal
I'm I'm I'm I'm in my toads don't
disturb
me I am not available right now do not
disturb me I am AFK chilling in my
toad leave me
alone they see the PO only went in party
oh I
see if I ever play online with somebody
from Hol then I want them to see my Toad
and I want to surprise them with it and
they'll be like what the [\h__\h] is
that I'm chilling I'm having a little
spa day in the body of my
toad
frog look at it
[Music]
cute
amazing frog slime treatment
yeah oh it's lovely it's a lovely day to
be inside of your toad so okay how did I
do things I I did left click and then I
did some right clickies here and there
wow that was
dooming and Chicken all the chickens I
feel bad for that wait you look kind of
weird Oh Oh I thought that's your head
but that's your
butt
hold
okay where are we going where is the
right
path
ew
cows dead stinky cows maybe we can feed
them to my toad do you think my toad is
alive I would like to think it
is Portal toad cute what are you guys
doing I didn't tell you to fight those
[\h__\h] stay with me protect
me yeah I feel like I already walked
through walked through all of this
before a scepter it's just
white guys today this is show like
whatever who cares but for the first
time ever I I I had the
the in the supermarket I had the lady
from the meat
counter
[Music]
and mint meat on request I didn't know
they could do
that I guess like in
in yeah the bigger supermarkets they do
that why is this breathing why is oh the
chicken wandering through
it I didn't know they would do that it's
a little bit more expensive I guess than
getting it pre package but at least I
can get the exact amount that I need
because all the package they maybe they
do that on purpose all the packaged ones
are like too
much so if you want to cook small you
got to get
it from the
counter dely butchers
yeah I got my meat freshly butchered
not
really I guess the the animal was not
freshly butchered but I got freshly
minced
yeah yeah and honestly it did feel like
better quality than the one from the
usual packaging because it wasn't like
like really annoyingly sticking together
and all that like all of it it felt
easier
to like take apart once it's in the
pot so I see I see I see the charm of
butchers yeah sometimes with certain
Meats when I make like bologa with
minced meat sometimes it's like really
annoying oh I'm not going to go in
yet sometimes it's really annoying cuz
it's like so
sticky weird texture like the flavor is
fine and all that but cooking the
cooking process is a bit
annoying right fresh but me are great
when you have the opportunity yeah yeah
yeah might do it more often
[Music]
now you can find una's loot here wait I
already did didn't I already
did didn't I already give it to her oh
what is
this uh some weird ritual happened here
oh look at those
bodies I
will pick it up pick it up stop
attacking stop wasting your Mana a corse
to serve
me pick pick pick it pick it up where is
it I
don't thank
you bro
we have a skill Jam let's get um I don't
know let's get the
arsonists up
up bad bad doggies who's bad doggies
these doggies are chasing
me yeah you can try to set up keyboard
pick up in the
option
ah like like hovering my mouse over it
but like pressing space or whatever to
pick it
up like okay not space obviously but
like any key to it seems really
counterintuitive but sure it's an
option that's see huh for
what what did I
say what did I say no hover just nearby
oh okay okay
[Music]
okay lost to do large amount why would I
ret talent I like how things are going I
think currently my my the way my skills
and everything are
distributed it's working pretty nicely
everything
harmonizing maybe could be better and
more
minmaxed but I think it's going well how
about the crop circles oh are you saying
it's like a eupo thing an alien
[Applause]
thing
spicy
aliens it reminds me GAA
tweeted
uh posted like the baseball
thing implying that it's like a
EOS sighting or
so what word did she use UAP what does
that stand for
unidentified Animal
product uh
unidentified
uh uh uh ah aial
phenomenon oh
oh
oh I find that
interesting identify the aern
Phoenix what what what do you want what
do you want do I need to give you my
password I have to identify
myself no I want to stay anonymous
let's go
in just going to go in
now many people believe there was
supposed to be an alien invasion
recently but those kind of people are
crazy don't listen to those kind of
people they always thinks like
apocalypse or alien alien stuff is
happening at any
time in New Jersy corner is a blaze how
why in New Jersey
you guys have a lot of um conspiracy
theorists there boo
Beed
B oh both quests are
finally moving on we need to search for
the seed of corruption and we need to
find Randy's tool okay
so this Village seems to be a goner did
we know that before when they told us to
go here did they tell us go to this
Village it's already [\h__\h] though or do
people think this Village
still oh my God what's with you no poor
dude somewhere on the right oh thank you
I mean I just started looking you missed
the way point
[\h__\h] I see it here though on the mini
map on the
right yeah I don't know it I I think I
kind of saw it when I entered but I was
like I'm going to go to the right sad
because it's going for the middle right
away feels
like too
straightforward
literally can you turn on show Health
Mana levels
[Applause]
options why they're on the left and on
the
right those are pretty big I don't
really feel like I need it over my head
if that's what you mean filash
oh still
alive would it put a number on them but
I don't really need a
number give
me okay I want I want the
thing let's try the thing is it an input
uh pick up item pick up item pick up
item pick up
item pick pick
pick must have missed something wait it
must have be it must be on left click
use bound
skill is anything else on left
click item pickup key ah here control
control that uh let's
do
H something that's like like right here
how about caps lock can
I no hey it won't let me do caps
lock how
about shift just shift for anything
else doesn't look like
it and you want it you want it I don't
know why you want it maybe it maybe it
is helpful you wanted uh
uh this one
right I why would I want
that that's just
extra
n it's not picking up
though oh is it because I have no space
possibly no it's not even picking up the
scroll of
wisdom enable it that's for picking up
items that's not for picking up items oh
[\h__\h]
oops item pick up key that wasn't for
that left click is for yeah I want to
change that but I don't see
where H I can't change
it well that's uh now I'm in a pickle
I'm in a little bit of a pickle in that
case what is
this right click this item and left
click a one St
maximum improves the
quality I'm trying to minmax my
inventory I don't know man damn
it [\h__\h]
all right through the toad we
go through the toad we go
happily it's my favorite thing to do
now
okay the Villager you must
why are you yapping at me I just want
you to identify items yes I like to hold
this
enchant un
no oh just that one okay oh wait and
this one maybe ah wait wait oh this one
has increased charges
woohoo now you're thinking with toads
I need a portal 2 mod that
oh how do I get rid of that
again it's not what I think it ah is it
because I it was
shift so what was I going to say oh yeah
portal
mod there we go for making all portals
to house you've caught me at a moment of
but that probably wouldn't work very
well away
there we go already
clean and now now I actually have plenty
of Scrolls and I don't use them at all
but I guess if I ever really need to
identify something right where I am then
we got it
covered decorate a never portal like
that yeah like make a whole
3D uh toad around it hell
yeah
cute
cute oh oh look who's coming for us a
spicy boss
monster just really really wanted an
autograph and
oh
my what is this like toxic Blood on the
ground what does that
do my power
to pick it up pick it
up Mama Mia that's going to really
trigger
me go that be go that speaking of dead
beats
I already saw this like when they put up
the reservation I guess
but I was honestly quite delighted to
see
that like
management thought
that they should have this like flow go
flow glow collab with
Cali I'm glad that they thought of her I
mean it's it's obviously it's kind of
like an obvious
choice like oh they they like to rap
okay bring the rapper
in but I wouldn't take it as such a
given because Ian members are rarely
involved in such official programs
especially when it's got to do with like
specifically a Japanese unit or
so so I'm just like really happy that
Callie
is first of all being considered and
acknowledged and involved in such a
thing I mean how can you not right
because she's obviously the rap bird to
think
of so it's obvious it's right there but
still I it makes me happy to see
that you know they were like hey let's
do a official program let's make it
beamed about like rap learning rap or
whatever and then let's invite Calli
because we respect her I like that I
like that s by respect baby and and not
just for Japanese members but also for
Ian members I like to see
that we need more of
that more more more
moreful like we have been also working
hard you know trying to establish
something here trying to make it trying
to do something
cool trying to make
history I'm on the right side this whole
time and I can't find the thing that you
said is on the right
side oh
well so yeah I saw the I didn't see the
whole stream but I saw them like
wrapping she she must got
rip damn it reminded me of myself very
recently yeah trying to rap in Korean so
I can imagine how much they you know
must have practiced and struggled trying
to figure out how to rap that fast in a
language that they don't speak this is
not easy okay it's not easy
that is not such a easy Feast
feet yeah feet but f e a t not f e e you
know what I mean you know what I
mean i' not want to do that it's really
really difficult it's already already
difficult to rap in that speed in the
language if you're familiar with it like
even I struggled here and there with uh
Callie's songs you know right
uh although I would say now I am a pro
at but then in a language that you don't
speak Mama Mia struggle struggle
struggle
so so so so
I need to understand is is slow glow
like as a whole supposed to be focused
on rap are they like a rap
unit is that their whole
thing don't think
so or like hip hop I guess
no could just be the
aesthetic not only rap but they have a
rap hip-hop emphasis yeah I was
wondering is it just for aiona or is it
the whole
group but okay yeah it makes sense if
it's like a hip-hop
Focus where do I if
I'm once I'm done with the sniper where
do I put all these stones
into like now these are already level
four right oh no they're not is a
Essence Trin is wait cuz I'm not using
them I don't want to I don't want the
extra
skills I don't want I don't want these
I'll keep the stone for now oh but is it
like once I get into this row I need the
stones to be minimum five like I need to
start with five or can I still like once
I'm in this row put a level one stone in
and then work my way
up oh it starts with
five so those level four stones will
become
[Music]
useless I don't want to use more skills
right now I'm pretty comfortable just
repeating the same two skills over and
over
yeah into the
to into the to
into the
[Music]
to
quickly time short make haste it is good
to see
you good to see you too beautiful lady
oh yellow
yellow o
[Music]
maybe I take
boot
mhm would you say these are better
there's less maximum
life but it adds also maximum mana and
gain two life per enemy hit I don't know
no yeah
grer life oh grants 54% of Life recovery
to
minions you wait phrasing does it mean
that if I heal 54% of that heal will be
used for my
minions or additionally and I still get
a full
heal who
knows I'll use it
it seems Shadow for minions but not for
you oh okay it doesn't take away okay
good good good good good
then shouldn't beue oh wait what is this
one uh skele ooh ooh ooh ah ah
ah level four skeletal Warrior minion
would have been cool um but uh don't the
plus one to level of all Minion skills
is too good to exchange
right put a transmute on it this
one maybe it will get me that again but
apparently I was really lucky with the
minion
skill
oops right click and then left click ah
oh ah allies in your presence deal 25%
increased damage that's pretty cool
but the modifier does that change that
again Pro a
okay oh minions have wait it added one
it didn't change it it added it
cool now I have increased maximum life
for the minions and my allies also have
increased damage
don't think it's better you don't think
it's better than this
one because of the plus one to
[Music]
level can I do it again
careful I have a
couple that's a straight up
upgrade level plus level one is one of
the best skills on a
weapon you can't add anymore I want to
change can I change
[Music]
Regal
orb do I have Regal
orb
Regal I don't do I different orb not
worth it okay
uh I'll get rid of this one
too all right then too
bad was a good one though not bad
see not
[Music]
bad got some good stuff
here it seems Shadows haunt us both
these are just some I will treasure
it
okay it
seems still the roll was good yeah hell
yeah let's put these back this I'm
putting this away
[Music]
too oops wait I have the decks now
should I ident identify this I know I
had free identify but whatever uh
evasion rating I'm going to get rid of
that it is good to see
you got to keep my inventory clean just
like my home and my kitchen oh I also I
I went and bought don't sell items from
stocket oh
whatever I went and bought um what do
you call it like a washing machine
cleaning liquid because I have my
washing machine for a couple years now
and I don't think I ever cleaned it and
recently I don't know if it's just
because I did an oopsie with the
laundry but the laundry was smelling
weird but I think I don't
know I think it's both basically so I
was washing laundry before the girls
came and then I forgot about it while
they were here so it was wet in there
for three and a half days or so
probably when I open it it smelled weird
weirder than usual normally when this
happens I just uh wash it again and it's
usually
fixed but when I watched it again it
didn't fix it the whole laundry still
smelled
weird but now I don't I didn't see any
mold on it but I do feel like probably
like
still something like or orb something
like mold had probably uh developed on
it I
suppose
sad yeah and then what I thought is like
not necessarily it might not necessarily
only be on the clothes and them sitting
around in in the wetness because I had
that before and it wasn't this bad so I
thought okay it's time to clean my
washing machine for the first time
ever how often do you guys do that like
put a liquid in for that and clean it
baking powder Americans love to use
baking powder I love that baking powder
culture that that you guys got
going literally never never oh yeah you
guys are honest huh once per year oh
that seems very very reasonable and
[Music]
believable I still haven't found any of
this Quest stuff vinegar baking s soda
not powder Bing powder and white white
vinegar yeah I ended up um using this
like proper cleaner for
it uh and also when I opened up the um
the the drawer where you put in
the washing machine liquid stuff oh um I
know I got to go to the left side but I
want to continue tanging without
stress uh I noticed that like when you
look when you take out the whole drawer
and you look like deeper inside as far
as I can it couldn't really look very
deep cuz no axes but I noticed there's
like some Decay black dirt where like
kind of like where where
the liquids would go
through and I I only saw like a tiny
part of it because like like it's just
too narrow and I
can't look there yeah so I tried
cleaning the part that I could reach and
see
um with a strong
cleaner and then yeah the rest of the
machine I just oopsie I just washed with
that liquid so hopefully it's better now
I don't know if it is there's another
checkpoint
there it's probably mold did you open
the L Dr no I forgot about that I don't
know where it
is
oh a smithing tools oh my God chill
chill Grace chill here have some CBD
here this will calm you
down or Snickers I guess would have been
fine too here Snickers CBD well that
would be a great collaboration Snickers
is all about calming down
right none
canose that was
easyd
CBD calm down have a Snickers a CBD
Snickers I've never had CBD
before too small anyway I don't know why
I did
that I don't want to like leave anything
behind
guys it's my problem
ring a new
ring cast
speed let's
[Music]
go
no wait a second okay to time to time
white items are aren't worth picking up
yeah I get it but I still I I don't want
to leave anything
behind I don't want to how can
iting I thought I had something to
identify but I don't makes fun of my
collection but I think it's I will
treasure it oh [\h__\h] I sold it
oops money is money
guys if you want to get rich this is
how pick up everything you
find easy
sell every single dollar every single
Cent it will make you richer yes it is
my secret and I shall share it with
you now let's go to the other checkpoint
that has the other stuff also you said
to the right but it's like this whole
like round around and it's more on the
up
left but okay I'm not going to I'm not
going to be angry at you for misleading
me I love
you what was I talking about about my
washing machine
right yeah I I'm uh washing something
right now again so when it's done we'll
see we'll see if that did the trick
hopefully hopefully
ow exploding Pig
what wait what was
there okay here we go the other fight
past us sticking oh what I'm not cooking
the noodles yet I'm only cooking
the E only cooking the sauce the heck
you should
burn Wich take you [\h__\h] my would be
executioner okay the
Executioner the Executioner is to be
executed I see I I I can handle this
[Music]
easy your time is I always need to make
sure that my CBD is working on him runs
out so fast
just and hit him with some
spikes little mob kill him kill
him oh what was that some Anvil drop
she
Justice he keeps on talking about
Justice is
Justice friends with him with this guy I
mean I don't know what kind of Justice
they're usually
into I'm
supporting hopefully not this
time just like
that W oh he's getting a lot more
minions oh
oh
done
oh and there we go nice nice nice nice
nice
nice oh there's still a lot more
coming little minions minions clean
up they're like we're here for the
Minion
ride we're the minions for the Minion
ride we we're working for Disney uh no
not Disney
Universal wait it's not here [\h__\h]
they're going to fire
us pick it up please thank
you a they're going to fire
us
no no woman are you still there oh I
shall save you if I figure out how to
reach you there we
go oh no hopefully this is not the lever
for killing
her there we
go how you doing was surely terrif Ying
I will not laugh at
you I will feel with you I will become
one with you that's how
how strong my feelings
are he killed Aon just killed him I I
don't know what to do I what did he do a
crime or something normally executioners
don't do that have to get out of here
for no reason
what did he
do surely there was a reason okay she
left so maybe I should leave too with my
[Music]
toad I'm just kidding of course of
course there wasn't a good
reason look at
him he's like ah
wide
open
cute what have you learn very
cute oh oh uh increase charges or 23% of
recovery applied instantly actually that
sounds
great but I I mean it's not really that
important because my Mana so far I'm not
using the
flasks either way I don't don't
mind but insta recover sounds pretty
good here comes the
airplane am I the airplane
then I'm the only thing going into his
mouth it is good to see
you oh wait I got like these too
it seems Shadows haunt us
both a small one I'll put in but the
level fives I can use oh nice look we
got new skills and more minions I can do
zombies or Frost
Mages um
this also says minion but I don't think
it summons a minion the bone spike is
itself a minion oh okay it's a bone
Spike to send nearby minions into a
frenzy as long as the spike remains
causing them to use skills more quickly
and oh it's like a
motivator a
cheering a
cheerleader watch the video uh okay pain
offering will impale one of your
skeletons to empower all your other
minions I mean it doesn't look much
different but I'm sure it's doing its
thing skeletal Frost
mes cast Ray zombie on a corpse to
create a powerful zombie minion they are
stronger than skeletons but only last
for a short time if you have power
charges you can cast
ra hold down the button for bone storm
to conjure a mass of bone spikes above
you upon release walk it too but just
[Music]
slowly bone storm
op very useful yeah okay then let's go
for
it I'm quite happy with my minions right
now still I would feel bad to already
like replace my War my my my skeletons
with zombies maybe
later okay
[Music]
here instead of bone
cage and then I can do another one
though maybe I will take pain offering I
don't know how often I'll use it though
like maybe only in boss fights it's
worth
because I don't know the other fights
are usually over in a moment
don't use Zombie zumbie B oh
really skeletal Frost
Mage yeah
yeah well we're probably going to get
like both in the end I'm going to start
with this
one put it on
E all right uh then
renley up
here this hooded one is here on your
honor don't take this as a threat but
it's your head if he turns out to be as
evil as he looks I guess I thought it
would be trouble but this is too
wonderful like obviously evil look a
prop bench here for you to be
evil okay
now I have a bench a salvage bench if
you find a p out there you bring it back
Salvage equipment items with quality or
sockets for quality and currency and art
Fisher shards okay don't really
understand that how's the
clearing but
yeah surely it will be useful oh lus is
here
crying for what it's worth my name is
lus I appreciate the rescue but
Amon everything I know it's all
gone it doesn't work worth much but take
this perhaps it will Aid you against
that monster I'll take care of it oh oh
thank you immediately I will have that
wait where did it go oh I didn't take it
I never take it
enter where where did you let uh
here I'll take the frost
Mage but do I I need that like oh wait
it's full
uh maybe into the archers again I don't
know Grim
Feast what was that
again is that
the that's passive
right
mhm maybe there's a skill you don't use
much no not really I mean
the bone cage
maybe yeah but I don't even have like
these
Spirits yet let's get it when I have
more spirits to give
away right sounds
good a Grimace also is using it yeah
I'll just wait wait for
more I'll just wait for
more all right Infiltrate The Manor
Beyond The Village this one yeah here we
go let's go in wait actually one second
do you guys mind if I go away for 1
minute to uh stir my
bologa and see how it's
doing well even if you say no I am gone
I am gone
okay I feel like it's finished so I
turned it off was already cooking for
like two and a half or 3 hours
yippee what were you
doing what were you
doing 99.1
VI it's a long time yeah it said like
cook as long as you
can so I
did you check the bottom if it didn't of
course I I I stirred it who do you think
I am
Yia who do you think I am I've been
cooking all my life
now I've been I've been cooking at least
very actively for the past 3
years how dare you ask such a
question obviously nothing sticked but
it became pretty thick so pretty thick
and I tasted it and it it tasted pretty
good I think from this tiny tiny taste
that I had so the food is ready we
sorry I just wanted to test if it
works
okay I will your my dinner is ready all
I need to do is cook the noodles cook
the
pasta hooray it's nice to have it like
ready actually surprised I had the time
to cook of all the other St stuff I was
doing man my kitchen was such a
mess such a big mess by decree of the
count of
augum all men must work a third shift
and continue exate little further
notice any man caught resting will meet
The Executioner's axe or The gall's
Noose did you see that just now
by decree of the count of
augum all men must
work okay it must be like out of the
game like an overlay I saw like the
moment it said by the by decree of the
count ofam it said like right there on
top of the speech bubble thingy I got
the riot games logo appear for like 1
second and then disappear and I was like
wait wait wait what right game
why yeah maybe the right client updated
I don't have it open but I guess it did
it on the side see I need to deinstall
League of Legends it's already taking
over my life in spooky
ways yeah not good not good not good at
all I have to uninstall it league is
infecting everything
yeah help help help I'm seeing Riot
ghosts where's my
aim those are
mine sorry I keep on trying to fight my
own minions they must feel so insulted
like ah Here We Go Again T are attacking
us man thank God we're skeletons it
doesn't hurt as
much Vanguard anti anti-che does that
a for a moment I really thought that
likee or so must be like a character or
so from from uh like League of Legends
and in order to protect themselves from
like copyright strikes or so or just for
the sake of the deal to put that name
into the game they paid them some money
and then they were like uh they they put
the logo into the game for that one
moment so that they had like the rights
to use the name of
ogam that's the whole story in my
head to explain the
phenomenon I think too
much I'm think too
hard Mama Mia
hey this one's
flying cortisol is that how you
pronounce
it
CTO did my hole just immediately
disappear I tried summoning it but feel
like it was gone right away
they I guess they attacked it so
fast this time I saw
it this time I saw it go
up only last for six seconds no but
legit I I didn't even see it for one
second so I feel like it got killed
right
away guys
tomorrow I have the lien
collaboration where we'll talk a bit
more in
detail about what they liked about
Austria and what we did what we
ate with some pictures we did actually
forget to take pictures a lot of the
time
uh especially on the first
day but it's okay because on the first
day we streamed and talked about the
fresh memories already a little bit but
yeah we were so busy with enjoying
stuff which is a good
thing but then I ended up taking plenty
of pictures anyway no
worries I also took some videos too
like in the museum
also when uh raden was
like explaining things sometimes like uh
I don't know like techniques and stuff
and history of certain art styles I was
like oh my God oh my God that's so
interesting say it again when I turn my
camera
on and then she just repeated herself
and talked about it and even more depth
and I recorded
it while um showing the
picture oh bone bone storm bone
storm museum curator
yeah oh my God that's so cool let me Tik
Tok
that no it wasn't for a TI
St it's for Twitter if anything or for
YouTube you know
me you know I wouldn't do something for
a Tik Tok I have not sunken that far
yet have some
respect pick it up pick it up oh I can't
I legitimately
can okay I am throwing away stuff now
for
once did you update yeah I need to I I'm
I'm doing it on my own pace
okay stop stretching me out
and yeah there's some some troubles with
the last
video so and I haven't had the time to
really take care of
it so please
forgive me
why is everybody asking me how I like
the
game again and again I like it
difficulty so
far is fine I died a few times last time
in the Stream to some bosses but most of
the time it's always very manageable and
still uh
thrilling how long is it though do we
already know like the approximate game
length in
hours by the way is this AOE the the
bone
storm
uh okay some are greatly
exaggerating but it's uh 20 to
25 two more acts for now oh wait is it
because it's early access so it's not
the full
game
oh do we know when they are planning on
releasing the rest of the
game there in a year oh but that's cool
we can like you know just take it slow
basically do do this one part of the
game now and then we take a break and
then we come back to it when they
release the rest of
it what do you mean it will be free to
play It's the game itself is free to
play so did we only pay for Early Access
oh but the cash stuff will still be
there huh that's amazing that this is
actually a free-to-play
game
oh
wow
damn this really doesn't look like a
lowbudget game so I'm surprised
true I also got the cash up money extra
yeah yeah they make a lot of money from
microtransactions which is like you know
people like to complain about
microtransactions but that's usually for
games where it's extremely pay to win or
for games that already cost a lot on its
own if it's on a game that doesn't cost
anything and also like if it's not like
in your face like Bam Bam Bam
advertisements
everywhere like this is very user
friendly no and I think
very reasonable to have
microtransactions when the game itself
is
free I
wonder they must really think that
microtransactions are going to be
enough to make enough money for the game
development is this a indie game is this
considered an indie
game no
okay yeah cuz it doesn't look like
one but they only make half of X out so
you guys told me there's no other
games so how does a company
become non IND
I think we talked about this before what
makes a what makes it non- Indie what
makes it able a yeah I know poe1
[Applause]
but oh it's owned by a 10 cents ah I
heard of 10 cents
before ah okay cuz they're not
self-publishing
feel like those blood puddles on the
ground are sucking my life aren't
they yeah they do
huh they certainly do I would say a AA
at this point wait why why what makes
the game AA and then a
AA is it the amount of money that is
being
invested continue top right okay I just
want to you know look around a little
bit
more thanks for giving me the general
direction
budget one of the reasons basically
[Music]
this is
a I thought you were actually arguing
seriously a a a is the car shut up you
guys correcting soldiers of a the
outside threat grows ever stronger
Whispers of betrayal Echo within my very
Halls we can no longer tolerate any risk
use lethal Force against those you
suspect of now play Speak carefully with
your men andure they are who they claim
hang any suspects seek out resistance
within the village and raise their homes
to the ground Wow we must send a clear
message leave no stone unturned not even
the Pebbles the Pebbles are in danger
they're going to be turned around they
have no legs and no arms how going to
how are they going to turn themselves
back around again the poor pebles they
have no
power we have to help them at least we
got or you guys got wings at least you
may not have hands but you're still kind
of doing better than the Pebbles who
have no limbs at all if they're if they
are turned
around God knows what will happen to
them they might just die lying
there they'll get
rotated get rotated
the Pebbles have laser
beams oh crazy here I come big bad
wolf crazy so maybe they don't need our
help okay take it back take it back take
it back let's not help them then
although like laser beams won't help
them from being turned around from being
rotated I do think they need our help
okay take it back take it back
orders are help
Pebbles to
survive and then pick them up and throw
them for fun use them as munition use
them as ammo put them in your guns yes
you have guns
now what is that
who that attack is crazy I want to use
it on a
boss I wonder if um contagion is
actually
like strong
I want to pick this up go away
puddle cuz I think one of these days
I'll replace it if it's not really that
worth
it it's a little bit annoying to always
like click on every mob trying to
get uh the CAG on
them I'm using it on the mock and it's
pretty fun can be one of the most FY
things okay well if you say so I don't
mind continuing to use it but if it's a
like very mid skill then I also wouldn't
mind replacing it but so far I
mean it's I guess it's working
well although I've never really played
without it so I don't know how it is
without ah
oh
uh so this in there where are we
going oh we're up here we're going to ah
uh how do
I I was supposed to type in minions to
make that glow right to see where we're
going
so we're going to go
left there we go almost
[Music]
there and why don't those puddles go way
faster I can't pick up my item
too much
clutter too much
[Music]
clutter uh 20% recover applied instantly
oh this is like a combination of the
previous
one I'll I'll use that but also
[Music]
so this one is for
life we have uh 54% life recover to mins
and 30% increased charge charges
[Music]
versus nah I don't want
that uh I think it's toad
time in
it I don't know why I identify if I'm
going there anyway
but sometimes you just feel like
it it's tote
time switch it
out what have you
learned
oh oh it's actually better can't use
this not enough strength what are you
talking about oh strength God damn it
should have spec into strength I
actually didn't care but I went for deck
oh maybe next time precise riveted M
nope nope
okay oh
no it is good to
[Music]
see I've collected I will treasure it
it's beautiful be careful at least we
can make una happy with those level one
gems now that we don't need
anymore amulet yo wait should I put the
thing on that makes it
blue was uh was was uh this one
right that was a support gem yeah I know
but it's like level one only so I'm like
why not sell
it sorry I was we have plenty of them I
mean not really but these are just some
odds and ends of
mine that's just a level
one I hope it
helps oh it's these ones I mixed them up
with the other thing
uh supports damaging skills blah blah
blah no supported skills remove 100% of
your maximum life from a nearby
minion oh so I'm I'm I'm uh sacrificing
a minion to make 40% more
damage okay
now sounds strong but I want to keep my
minum cuz I don't feel I have so
many like something sometimes I I feel
like you know I need more when I'm
fighting
[Music]
bosses energy Shield recharge begins
immediately and is not interrupted by
damage for 2 seconds when stunned while
use using support skills
oh I don't really like these what about
pain
offering minions from supported skills
have plus 30% to all elemented
resistances uhhuh uhhuh
uh uh-huh uh support skills have 40% 40%
more skill oh yeah let's do it
yeah okay you guys were right with
buying it
back uh okay cool
nice yippee now we have all the slots
full yippee
[Music]
ooh disenchanting gives the support gems
back
really pick it
up can try equipment
H yeah maybe one of these
times
oh oh what the heck is that a tackle
wait it's a t yeah it's a it's a it's a
it's a the squid tentacle tacle thing
he's under
there he's even more insane than when we
last
met it's a thing from The Cinematic oh
it was in a
video don't recall that because I didn't
see
anything damn you're
strong
aggro is so focused on me
this place is so
big was there a direct way down where
the hole was no right
oh oh what have I reached it the count
geonor this is very Diablo right
now this is very
Diablo uh
doesn't look like count geonor is
[Music]
here is this going to come to
live first ones hear our laments sanity
recedes ever further into the Dark
Shadows hover above us in the corners
watching and waiting what sickness has
come Among Us that so unsettles our
minds it sits poised to strike nowhere
is safe
what a
delightful candle MK the living right oh
he's made of candles
[Music]
funny oh oh my alarm I already stopped
cooking by the way I watched the uh
Breaking Bad Malcolm in the Middle
parody thing the like uh other ending
that they made so to
say
oh he's pretty strong and
fast let's try to
here
yeah I
more
W cool it was funny anyway I like his
acting uh well I guess I can't even say
that because his Malcolm in the Middle
acting is obviously like comedy acting I
was going to say his acting is better in
Breaking B but it's just like more more
realistic and Breaking Bad I
guess but yeah people like to compliment
I guess that we can play those two BS
which are so
different we can play them so well it's
true it's true
[Music]
yay he was underused in Godzilla must
have my own one of those I don't think I
watched
that yeah most definitely didn't that
was a good fight cool fight cool uh
[Music]
enemy oh do you always get this as a
drop 20 uh plus 20 extra life
nice ah nah our current hat is just too
good with the minion skills but
otherwise this would have been
nice in another life it would have been
nice I wrecked
him should check on your pass no no no
no no I already did like 20 minutes
ago and then I turned off the stove so
all is well don't worry don't
worry but yeah it's funny they talked
about how if uh
Heisenberg's Walter wife was actually L
from Malcolm in the Middle
then yeah all of this wouldn't have
happened I'm not too sure about that I
feel like
Perhaps
Perhaps it may have still
happened but L wouldn't she wouldn't let
herself be
so mentally abused and manipulated and
gaslit by Walter and would have just
left the relationship in any case right
away she wouldn't let him [\h__\h] with her
like that you
know that's the one thing although she
Mar may as well have stopped his doings
if she was there in that
world uh I found stairs that go down is
that where count geonor is or did I
missed him somewhere on this level
although yeah stairs down makes sense
because we saw the lower level
okay how do
I she would have grabbed him by the ear
and direct him to the
[Music]
police I wonder surely there's like
a not quiet but somewhat comparable
situation and Malcolm in the Middle
where the dad gets in
trouble and she stops him or so surely
there is something well not obviously
not like drug cooking trouble but
something like
that that where we could like kind
of you know see her way of thinking in
such a situation
it was
yeah I rewatched that whole thing in the
right order a while ago right like last
year or this year I don't
know I I watched the whole thing
normally I only watched it like in
pretty random order on
TV where are we
feel like it may have been up but I'm
going oh no never mind I guess not keep
digging oh we're still not on the level
though we need to go even
[Music]
lower thank you
do yeah yeah yeah you got the position
oh let's go three rounds of
interviews you got
it sasuga oh of
course of course you would get it I
would expect nothing left from
you you're a
go-getter not really uh I don't know if
you're a go-getter but I just feel like
you're are
very I mean I don't know anything about
you but I feel like you would probably
be very qualified for it and very
intelligent very deserving
so it was to be expected
oh my God Kopi
reference it gets a bit confusing in
these dungeons I don't know where to go
I always find my way in the end but I'm
always feeling very indecisive about
what direction to go
where are my minions
bro top right is a rule on pum yeah but
then you know I would miss out on stuff
like
this
yippe Callie talked about the 24 hours
stream again boss
uhoh uhoh I'm scared I'm scared you know
I want to do it too I guess I I never
talked about it on my
stream I I want to do something like
that too and if I were to do something
like that it would also be C for me my
choice of
partner um but I'm very scared of my own
um ability to do
that like if I can really nah I tried
staying up for 24 hours while
entertaining in the way way way way
past too far
past and even then it was
extremely rough by the last
hours you know how much I love my like
sleeping and napping
oh another
door wait is that where I came from
no what it's not going down is
it what's a little room it's the Count's
room I sense Oriana
knows and I cannot deny that which I
know deep down to be
true that fair villager an eternal
descendant she
knew at that moment when our eyes locked
we both knew what that you made for
other she clung to her children like I
would end them then and there oh I guess
not where going but how many others must
I
fear is my blood truly
impure Ariana assures me we can write
some of the wrongs of the past
she promises a way forward for augum a
way forward for the Clans and the
clanless alike
and a way forward for me can you read it
we must continue with our task why is it
so low I wish you could move it the
window that pops up would be good if you
could move it it seemed kind of cut off
there at the bottom
too Dam
it oh well uh yeah uh what about having
an AI K stream while you
sleep well I mean I did mention to Cali
like maybe for
example like some
parts uh one person can take a nap while
the others continuing to stream and yap
yap yap
but one big problem for me is I cannot
fall asleep in such such situations and
I'll be just more frustrated
because let's say I have like a 2hour
window when I know that I have such a
short time to fall asleep and that I
really have to and should then that
pressure in my mind will keep me from
falling asleep at any cost no matter how
tired I am I usually am not able to do
it and if anything I would be very very
close to falling asleep by the end of
that time frame and then it's then I
have to get up and then I'm like so
[\h__\h] pissed that I was about to fall
asleep and it took me two hours to get
to that point I didn't do it and now I
have however many hours of a stream
ahead of me in that situation where I'll
be continuing to fall uh suffer through
it
so I don't know it would have to be
longer than 2 hours probably but then
it's like I don't know feels lame do do
like me Cod on it do they when they do
their 24-hour streams I I'm actually not
aware do they take like sleeping breaks
at all I know they take like some
resting breaks right but do they sleep
and how long are
they a pre-record Ah that's smart yeah
pre-recorded stuff
uh they have pre-recorded
segments how long were they
though I think not but that means that
overall we would need more prep time to
make such pre-recorded
[Music]
segments but then I wonder like I don't
know yeah it kind of takes away from the
achievement of doing a 24-hour stream I
don't know in my mind it's like got to
stay awake for 24 hours and entertained
for 24
[Music]
hours ba did it huh I
see that's
crazy oh yeah she did it kind of
recently
right she also had a bunch of guests
right didn't really didn't really hear
anything about it
[Music]
mhm
H yeah I don't know what cie thinks if
she would like to do pre-recorded or
like
hardcore thank you I think it would be
good for my sanity to have some
pre-recorded uh
[Music]
Parts yeah we both of us already stream
so
much um let's see
oh nope
I've collected these over I will
treasure
it be
careful most worried about the health
side effects exactly like I mean I don't
think anything will be like long lasting
it will just be rough at the moment
during the stream and for the following
day when I sleep through it to to fix it
but
yeah
sket why can't I do it again oh
[\h__\h] I thought I could
ah damn it I misunderstood can I undo it
can I redo
it no huh cuz I already had that I
didn't realize
or I don't no I do right I I already
have it in my stash now I have two of
these so what I do with this can I sell
it or like un
un yes let's try this oh I can't damn it
why does it give me the opportunity to
do it when I've done it before no I've
collected these over time guess I'll
sell it what do you think how much
another one gold thank you pleas I get
plenty of them later
okay damn
it fruit a
told
H where were we where were where were
we you have 10
spare that's not that
much I thought you would say some more
impressive
number where am I wait this
part but yeah would you guys like to
see a 24-hour Takami
stream I do think
like if it's going to be like
somebody like if we're going to make an
Ian version of the mikona one then it's
got to be
Takami yeah all right we'll stop it for
you we'll do it for
you but I don't know if it's really
going to be the next time I'm in Japan
because no I definitely feel like we
need more prep
time got to have some serious discussion
up about it like what we want to do do
we want to do some more ambitious
things plan it out
better cuz right now nothing's really
planned where do I down
down yeah give it some more time maybe
after
Fest I don't
know oh there it is
death and
Decay
ow Oreo shake Oreo
shake man now you'll make me want to
drink an Oreo
shake why
[Music]
yummy guys is MSG common in supermarkets
in like your
country cuz
like I'm doing this cooking stream right
and
[Music]
uh I was told to put MSG into the thing
that I little cooked
but
like we don't have it here I got to go
into an Asian store but like for five G
I'm only going to be using five gr I
never use it otherwise I don't want to
buy like a big package of it if I only
need five
gram MSG is really uncommon I think here
if you uh like for home
cooking I never see it in any recipe in
now I looked at up like what it's called
here and all that so I I know I
know it it exists but it's just like not
really
common this is your chance to start
using it more I don't know do I want to
oh oh [\h__\h] this is like a bossy low key
boss it's delicious
if I'm not using it do you think it will
taste a lot
different buy small bottles you think
they they sell small bottles the
packages I saw uh like online when
looking it up the product they all look
big just use
salt so I use it as if I'm salting the
food and it's like salty but it also
makes the flavor stronger
right something like
that yeahi I
know okay I'm using the pole more often
than I thought I would so I think it was
a good good
investment all level
up
no nope she says I say yes girl yes I'm
full again
there we go beautifully
sorted another chest over
there sprinkle the leftover Emy on
kfps
n fried
fries yummy
[Music]
yeah I guess I could use it for a bunch
of P but is it like
basically I would use the same amount as
if I was like salting it if I use like a
tiny bit of salt I use the same amount
of
MSG it feels like
I'm uh artificially enhancing my food
feels wrong it doesn't feel natural
maybe
less stronger than small
son As Natural as any other seasoning to
be honest
really huh well I still have some time
onto the cooking stream maybe I'll go
buy
it maybe I'll try to go find it oh more
don't stop the Beast
hungers this is
like is he feeding it to use it as like
a attack later oh Arena the up
it's like this is like
Arcane what level are you uh I don't
know what does it
say who knows
really yippee 10% uh damage increase on
my minions
I am level 17 already wow oh hey there's
another door here maybe another room
yeah yeah yeah torture log
o should I read this there's no
voice even after 6 hours on the rack the
pro fost refuses to give me the names of
the men who escaped from their own
failed Coupe attempt does he not realize
the Mach ma machinations of shape
Changers are at work here I do not doubt
Conor's loyalty only his intellect the
shape Changers are obvious in their
tactics they are untrained in the art of
deception they fidget they sweat they're
constantly afraid of being singled out a
question that is how I identify
them they are less than human a human
being is Winsome even beautiful but
these creatures bely that recognition of
kin the closer I look the more I see
that there are no more than bones
carrying bags of Flesh under an oozing
membrane of skin peel away that covering
and the disgusting truth is revealed
they must be thrown into the pit and out
of sight let the seed consume those
flate
Abominations
n I'm going to take a fro candy I don't
know my throat is so um dry today
it's the dry season I'm surprised the
girls they were actually like saying
that their throat was like doing really
well when sleeping
here and I was like what usually during
these cold times my throat gets very dry
here but they said like both indoors and
out doors their throats were doing
generally really good I mean radin was
kind of [\h__\h] of course with her throat
but generally they said it just like
felt
good I'm
surprised I'm glad it was good for
[Music]
them yeah yeah they were like sometimes
like I I mean I can imagine that Tokyo
uh obviously like it's going to be way
more polluted air than over here but
when I go like back and forth between
Austria and Japan I don't really I don't
really
notice the air quality difference that
much I mean when I'm in like Austrian
mountains or so I for sure feel like
it's smells
fresh but I wouldn't like really pay
much attention to it usually but the
girls were like oh my God the air is so
good
here
really you
think
[Music]
H H okay here we
go Throne of the wolf are we beginning
already where is the boss
where's your boss this interop has the
power we need kill her and you shall
have everything I
promise no news this time I'll remove
your head myself romantic your
first ah CH chill chut the chill I need
to hello why is not working I'm pressing
e there we
go she she's cool all the first
one easy
play rabbit he's cool I like him for the
first
one but you won't get me you won't get
me down
never easy bra never
[Music]
oh he didn't w Wait
what oh oh
[Music]
W let's spread the plate come on come on
W
easy you with your good good
hit my minions where are my
minions go unish I stunned him
apparently
e open the cage release the if only my
minions could have gone all in in that
moment but this is fine I could charge
my bone attack
since you are too weak to do the job
cheerleading
on manipulative wh did you did he call
me a manipulative [\h__\h] wait you're not
talking about me right what is who you
talking about I I got to be honest I'm
not quite following of the
lore yet as of yet this feels more like
Side
Story know what the main quest I will
take out your hat my
hat I he said I will take off your hat
no don't take off my hat it will reveal
my helmet hair ah
[\h__\h] ah no I so close to killing
him the whole hat thing really upset
me that ice stuff you got to I tried to
like walk away from it first time it
worked but the second time it was too
close in succession and like too close
in
space this time oh hey his wife is gone
and the the first couple of mobs are
gone too this
time
easy death and
debit oh hit the direction
easy
break I think the first try was already
pretty good I could have done it
honestly if it wasn't for those stupid
ice
attacks oh oh w f yeah that is hard to
get out of that Circle that
quickly okay we got the
minions oh God oh God he's cornering me
stretching me out no again that one is
[Music]
rough me
first youare oh he's stuck he's
stuck oh no I'm so dumb doing worse I
think this
time okay time to dodge time to dodge
probably keep my roll oh no he's not not
doing the thing I smell your
blood and I oh no ah this [\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
I'm not sure how to oh no it's it's not
yet not
yet
ah you are hunting oh what the [\h__\h] what
what's going on what's going on that's
so scary that's so scary that's so scary
that's so scary what's going on that's
so scary that's so scary that's so
scary that's so scary I'm getting
claustrophobic [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
that's actually really terrifying
somehow stop it I'm so
scared wait please stop please stop I
don't know what buttons to push
anymore please okay it's chill it's
chill calm down calm down it's not so
bad it's not so bad strong Panic no
Panic I will take out your
heart okay see everything's okay oh [\h__\h]
not this part
a no no
freeing okay okay let's try to get oh
this this is the one this is the
no what he didn't even do the cornering
claustrophobic thing the first
time roll to I I mean I was trying but
like recovery time
bro and I also didn't expect him to do
it three times but I guess lucky number
all good things are
free
P didn't get his health that low does
wait what how does what whatever we got
to take it as it
comes I'll remove your head myself not
if I take yours
first first ones I am
R
it you will F oh oh
oh first one I didn't know that that's
what happens when you stay in that
line that's how it is
oh easy
play First on
you okay with your
life
[Music]
oh no damn
it what is that Circle over there go
away
[Music]
oh nice you dare mock me
yeah more
mocking more mocking let's
go oh God I'm scared is this is what's
what scary time is about to
begin please involve me in your PL no no
not this okay but I will be chill I'll
be chill I'll be chill I'm not scared
this is not I I didn't know I have
closer
phobia but now we
know how we know I've never experienced
this feeling before and you by the moon
no oh my God I I I'm going to die this
is killing
me I can't heal up effect fast enough sh
sh I'm panicking I'm really
panicking again okay we good my god
[\h__\h] desol leave me
alone on high oh
no I smell your blood it's always the
same SP the same
thing
no yes charging the skill killed me I
didn't expect this the Beast hungers try
to get some cold
resist
interesting um I don't know did I have
anything with that
whatever change your charm for the cold
you have in stash okay if I die again
thank you for reminding me I had a
feeling that I had something with cold
resist good to know this time I remove
your head myself not if I take yours
first first one's yo that's huge damage
right in the
beginning
first no no let me out let me
out let
me you're so mean you're so mean I said
let me out I want it out I didn't I
didn't agree with that little
rabbit no let me out I want to
die
first oh my God
that gives a good opening though when he
does that even if I'm not inside he
still takes time
to uh put an attack in
there in the middle oh
hello I get worse
somehow oh yeah good contagious
[Music]
spread no no
no really not much time there to get
out oh
uhoh
okay on high oh oh oh oh okay
okay I smell your
blood and I am
ravenous
oh uh no the air grows colder no
no
no actually I'm the
Imp this attack might be really
death and you be ruled by the mo oh oh
God no please end please end it
[Applause]
please your veins soon
chill agna shall slay
again no but it makes me slower if I
walk into the icy
stuff
[\h__\h] don't worry about killing them just
run
really you guys just like run away from
it I felt like challenge was to like
stay in the
middle no my minions are also not like
keeping up but one in circles around the
Mist he's
funny had to roll around for a bit
really maybe I'm fine if I do that then
but I mean okay I died again so might as
well go get my
[Music]
charm so what ice thing did I
have
uh what
do h used when you take cold damage from
it ah this
one but it only works one time and then
I need to refill it so won't this be
pretty
useless oh it has
[Music]
charges how many like it charges back
two times it's like still
nothing h
what I have a blue
one at this
[Music]
one h no that's the same but I can make
it
blue do I have another
one oh this this is no wait this is uh
for sockets
[Music]
so should I make it blue okay
trans oh
H so what does that mean it charges back
faster does it or does it not charge at
all until I come here to refill it at
the well or so now augmented
oh on kills I get charged ah so if I
kill his
minions what am I
doing what was the thing again
this
one recover six life when
you how can I
be it is good to see
I like to hold I will treasure
it maybe in the future we have like a
enemy that has lots of lightning stuff
I'll keep these for that
time might be not necessary but I'll
keep it for
now Al could also augment the rest of
your
gear oh huh
is this
augmented is this
augmented what did it do Target is not
magic
what anything that only has
one I think they all have more than one
right it all has amulet and
ring oh ah the lower one ah okay okay
okay it all looked like more than more
than that to me uh what did I just get
the increased cast
speed and Fire Resistance great great I
wanted cold
resistance this one gain two Mana also
[\h__\h]
unlucky yeah the line I I see the line
now yeah I see where we draw the
line everything else has it
right you might get cold rest there oh
see if you can buy a new ring from the
vendor H which one's tell Rings you no
not you you're the gamble guy right
feeling
lucky but you do have a ring a random
ring for
3,000 later
bro hello these are just some odds and
ends of mine you have uh no
ring she has a sapphire charm
and an amulet be
careful but I already have my own cold
amulet till next time
deceptor uh I don't think she will have
anything that has minion skills so even
if I try to you know augment it myself
to put the minion thing on there chances
are we're not getting that probably
oh
oops press that what
for on her sorry I was I like to hold on
to bits and pieces wait what where when
any that catch your eye when where
why ice runes and armor slot yeah if it
had
slots check the
scepter oh wait this one also has minion
skills
[Music]
yo but nothing about
cold but we might be fine now if I run
around instead of becoming
claustrophobic uh yeah overall it looks
better also level five Warrior minion
instead of
two oh I should buy it it's a good price
that one spoke to me as well Feast on
flesh ah what's this the last
gas how does this work
again I put this in here
yeah it
is no I already have the plus one to all
Minion
skills already had
it but the rest is really nice it seems
Shadows both good
Improvement okay let's see let's see how
that will
go I'm
scared hi
scared but the level five Warriors is
only the one that comes from the weapon
right so only one single Warrior is
level five no new this time I'll remove
your head myself not if I take yours
first
easy run little
rabbit you will
fter y
goodin of bone
oh that was a big
charge Spread spread Spread spread the
contan
[Music]
I'm very
concentrated killing for
us so okay I'm I'm running
here I'll do a I try to do a little bit
of damage here and there oh I didn't
know I had so much space Swift as death
I I really limited myself to the one
little patch that wasn't
icy cursed or
gifted bred and I see this is like much
better now your ve
CH agna shall slay
again freeing
I will take out your
heart no no please don't do
[Music]
it oh this attack I also don't like this
very
much
okay okay lots of phases are
uh uh survive but you probably do
everything again
so can't rest just
yet oh he's thring it again
[Music]
already the etern
pure with blood lust
empowered our asir
endured but soon oh I'm I'm definitely
doing
better ah they pushed me
let me death waited at the door they
cornered me I couldn't move for a while
by
power [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
M oh no oh unfair unfair unfair
killing I will take out your
heart accidentally Tapped Out up the
game for a
moment okay
okay
desolation
high oh wait I'm alive oh thought I I I
died I thought I
died I
[Music]
no not again you are
hunted F tooth and
Claw can't take this anymore under the
moon the pack suffered but
endured now in
tune no Tales were
told none new none
old go go go go go go go go Wobble Go
Wobble
goer what the [\h__\h] is
that
fre I will take out your hat my hat not
my hat anything but my head oh I did it
I I had to protect my
hat k your mind if only for a moment hey
you the
madness it consumed my
being
Oriana used it against me where has she
taken the Beast I found
messages from the desert the tentacle
beast from the V
yes find
kill
her but first
please st stop the madness As You
Wish thanks for the help let us return
to clearfell to make our
preparations o new St but I don't use
stabs
man pick it up did I
yeah
oops
yay yay oh you forgot your message thank
you I hid my loot is
it which button I'm not sure what now it
should show right yeah I'm never sure if
my keyboard is like English or German
and then where Z and where why would be
so I press both thank you for the
membership gift you did way better than
other streamers I've seen oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] thank you really I feel like you
know I definitely limited
myself um in the previous runs maybe I I
would have done it already if I didn't
limit myself to that one
area I really didn't think I I could
like cuz it also zoomed in like that
right and it was just this tiny
patch of non ice I just thought man I
need to stay here it felt so
claustrophobic I
misunderstood you did amazing thank you
people complain about this boss in the
world
chat
losers wait this is not the right portal
I cannot walk into this portal it's a
false
portal I should make my own
portal there we go it even replaced
it it's a trap need my own
portal I don't trust your portal I have
a toad yeah I don't need your sussy
portal all right here we go he looks so
cool from behind that dude
you look so
cool damn that cat really looks
nice wait one sec I have eight DMS let
me check it out
[Music]
okay congrats on finishing A1 oh what
did it officially say it's act
two you've done well
stranger no has a to Port yeah that's
the one thing I really thought I wanted
become part of our I had to buy it I
shall sing it
proudly the darkness that crept Upon Our
lands has been forced to it called me
and I have a feeling you will pursue it
to the end of the world it was Destiny
good luck to you thank you unaa you're
so
nice I guess well that vest looks really
cool too actually yeah let me uh where's
the guy oh you moved also why are you
guys rotating like that huh you making
fun of the rotated
Stones those poor stones Beast is
leaving corruption in its wake so we
have a trail to follow stinky Trail when
you are ready to part from this place we
can leave immediately so this is
actually I guess also kind of like
Diablo 2 where like all these like NPCs
they kind of go with you when you move
to your next main Camp so to
say
right somewhat
[Music]
only him oh oh I see I
see betrayal of corruption leads East so
East we shall go it seems fate conspires
to return me to the PLS of
V someone who looks so oh wait no wait I
guess it's
okay I didn't realize he would teleport
me right away attempt to control it has
ended in c e
we must pursue her to the plains of
vasti
oh we should find the merath
Caravan only they can lead us through
that harsh and they don't look nice
though we got to kiss their ass even
though they're evil for them to move us
to where we need to
go o rat
sand thank you Yuni for watching I was
going to say like the way he looks so
evil but seems so nice and helpful it it
I like that it's kind of cute and Loki I
feel like maybe it reminds me of like
Spirited Away the one
that uh like puts out his hand and asks
for money or so what was
it the hooded one no face yeah no face
looks
evil maybe is evil I don't know just
seems very nice kaashi well my lady
can't necessarily say that kaashi is
like we don't know that much about
kaashi
right can't really say he's not evil
either right if evil why hot more like
if evil why nice why so well behaved and
helpful
seem more naive than evil but very
mysterious in any case yeah but I feel
like there's surely other good examples
to to compare the the hooded one to this
Outpost seems to be part of a trade
route so we should be able to find
americ Caravan they are an honorable
people oh really I have no doubt they
will assist us wait it didn't look very
honorable in the trailer that you showed
me
H all right let's
go maybe that wasn't the
Caravan the weary traveler grows close
to the end of the path the bread ball of
the world The Verdant land of seven
Waters awaits was so excited sure to
have your toll ready at the gates cloth
gems metal and coin are talking to me so
much energy and
excitement what a happy
Stone cool what is that so the mar what
are you cooking strong minded women are
plenty I
approve she
approved yeah it looks like carrots but
I don't think it is carrots oh this is
our
well so this is our encampment
Zara let me look at you where's your
face you are seeking passage on our
Caravan we cannot travel anywhere at the
moment pic got some sick horns rout
ahead those look so heavy we are stuck
here time to what I can do she looks
cool I wish I could look at her from the
front but uh angle makes it kind of
difficult what a waste she looks like an
instrument should I blow into
it but you don't blow into the big open
part you need to blow into a different
hole maybe into her mouth if she opens
her mouth I blow in then it should
possibly go through her whole head and
then through these horns and then come
out
like
right ooh where her smile looks so
Barbie doll f
she's got a permanent smile issue some
people got resting [\h__\h] face she's got
a resting Barbie
face oh look at you little choco
bll you look like
you're very naked you need more
hair look like a unfeathered chicken
hey yo what's happening I will put you
down and now I hear
monkey wait a
second is that it did we look that did
we look at everything oh he moved he's
cute oh wait that's not a monkey that's
a hyena huh that what I heard I guess
they do make kind of like monkey
noises wait I still have stuff in
here wait do they have
a
uh oh never
mind I am lost what have you learned are
you already identified
oh uh yeah Spirit like oh actually maybe
I will take this also want to see like a
different look on me
I need more agility for this oh [\h__\h] oh
oh so much
decks oh this looks like a pretty
decent staff actually
but not using it who can I sell things
[Music]
too ah
here um I think I'll keep this
that stuff is good but not for you yeah
so
sad so
sad uh that's for life right
yeah and my
stash okay let's
go Grand was that bigger
oops I buy
back I buy back oh where where go oh no
buy back oh oh because I didn't sell I
uh transformed it oops we will'll have
to deal with this for a while now with
our not so strong uh flask
are you guys following me or are you
staying there nope they're staying there
oh
[\h__\h] wait is that a hyena uh
horse what the heck
hia did you say hyena am I saying it
wrong yes Cent sent Tower hyena
Tower hi Ena Tower it's like I'm saying
hi to a tower of
Ena or very long
Ena right okay you guys making me feel
self-conscious it's okay though
long Ina is
long I like this area the Red Sand is
pretty oh
iron no it's not really on purpose but I
don't see a need change how I say it and
it is kind of engraved there's other
words like
cassage that one is kind of on purpose
but it also sounds fancer the way I say
it I sound more
sophisticated don't
die
e biomi oh yeah okay that one's also on
purpose but it's also like if I don't
think about
it like it's been a while since I said
that word so now I would say it like
that if I don't think too hard about it
although you guys have corrected me too
many
times that one
definitely I feel very awkward now when
I say it in front of other
members feel very awkward
now you ruined the
magic it's not necessarily you guys but
like maybe people who don't watch my
streams too
often when they think that I don't
know yet that I'm saying it wrong and
they're correcting
me take the [\h__\h] gem thank
you come
on I'm just spamming my
attacks schedule always comes out as
schedule and it feels awkward what do
you mean wait am I saying it wrong to
you
schedule or is it your own
pronunciation I clicked on
both trying to click on the sometimes it
feels like the other thing works better
but then it doesn't so I go back to the
other way I do say properly okay your
pronunciation oh what you say
Skittle Skittles
what happened here
oh what is happening devastated
Camp I shall take all your money and
make you even more devast
stated deal
deal at least I saved
[Music]
you oh W wo whoo
wao don't worry I am here to
help what now are you guys going to
thank
me
[Music]
no
oh okay moving on check corpses all of
them this one didn't drop
anything no I already you didn't one guy
me I already had a feeling that's what
you
meant yeah I took everything from
them and even investigated the corpses
of their
friends am I the evil
one are we the evil ones
[Music]
uh what the heck where do I go
down did I go all the way up here for
nothing seems like
it are we the
baddies I love how that that that was
such a sweetie and she's so cute and she
actually saved my butt I was trying
forever to get day
nine uh like taken by somebody it was
empty even though like later dates are
mostly all taken but the ninth somehow
stayed empty because like you know a
couple members were like hey I can't uh
participate until like one of the later
dates please give me later
dates so I tried to put as many members
as possible in the early ones but then
the ninth kind of stayed open and you
know worst case I can always make a
video solo but I don't want to spam too
much of myself in there you know I want
variety I'm sure people want
variety so try my best to make that
happen and also like trying to put some
groups together also in case like solos
somebody already had a solo but they
didn't have a group yet and so
on in the end I'm still doing as much if
not more organizing than I did also back
then guys I said I said I wouldn't run
after people but I'm still running after
people very much so I mean I'm not like
for people who didn't answer about their
participation uh I'm not running after
them but I'm running after the people
who already committed to
participating and uh you know just to
remind them hey your video is up in like
24 hours so please submit it like within
the next 23 hours that would be great
thank you and so on so like I I'm still
very very occupied with it in my
mind and I was trying so hard hard to
find someone for the nine until the very
last minute or very last couple of
hours and in the
end it becamea because she uh she had a
solo plan for later later
later in the schedule um but she was
available to do it earlier thank God
thank God
sent me her video out of nowhere while I
was shivering and shaking and I wouldn't
make
it very
dramatic and then she sent the video I'm
like oh my God my hero My
[Music]
Savior let's go and she even made it
really funny and cute
yeah but today's video
is uh ready to
go so I'm
relieved mostly really things are going
relatively smoothly and I say I'm
running after people but it's not like
they're late it's just me reminding them
saying Oh uh 24 hours uh please submit
video don't
forget and now it's kind of like
matchmaking cuz like people the girls
were like oh yeah I can do a solo and of
course I can also do like a group if
anybody wants like a couple of girls
wrote that but then I feel like nobody
took action in like hey you and me let's
do a a group video except for
like you know one or two groups
so I was like okay I guess I'll played a
Matchmaker so I I put two two cute girls
together a popular combination of girls
you'll see for one of the future dates
but I put them together because they
didn't have any other group yet and I
thought it would be a great
match so I kept on
talking to them individually in their
DMS I'm like hey this state would you
mind making a video with this person I
think it would be really
good and then that person is like what
does the other person think and I'm I go
to them I'm like hey hey do you want to
do a video with this person they already
seem open to it it's on you and then
they're like yeah but not on this date I
can do later and so I go back to the
other person and I'm like hey this
person is in very okay with it
but uh not at this date how about this
date then I wait
another day for the reply so all these
communications they take
time and then this person is like yeah
okay this date's also fine with me what
does the other person say I go back to
other person I'm like hey this person
said yeah that date is also fine so can
you girls just uh talk to each other
now what the [\h__\h] is going on who am I
oh
you I was like who am I attacking wait
who am I attacking wait what what what
wa where's the main
monster all of them or this
one very
confusing went in there Tangen
thing and just did not
survive look at the oh wait what wait
that's not the boss where did the boss
go TR broke you wait what is it that
frustrating but it's an optional fight
right oh the checkpoint is just way
further behind it's over
here so is it like uh all of them oh the
boss is at the top of the hill okay so I
got to go to the boss right I'm just
going to ignore these oh no wait w there
he is there he is there he
is ah wait this is messed
up not
optional this one broke beo oh it seems
like it breaks a lot of people stay away
from the
wall you can't go up or they throw
Spears at you I mean they also throw
Spears at me when I don't go up though
though
right see I'm clicking and I'm clicking
here too both up and
down oh my God
it really doesn't want to be picked up
this one works yeah now it works
sometimes you got to go back and forth a
little
bit and pick up something else in
between how am I supposed to do this if
so many people struggle with
this
uh what do it where's my where is it
why isn't there a checkpoint closer to
that though I don't want to keep on
fighting those
hyenas fight him at the end of the
peninsula where is the end what do you
see as the
Endy C
Define oh level
up that could help a little
bit uh increased hit critical hit or oh
sure why not why not
yeah I still get the the XP each time
even though I die which is nice I guess
you can also
oh bro do you want to fight me from down
here catch me downside oh no they
started attack wait this works wait they
can pre kill them without me triggering
the
fight do they respawn when I go up there
though let's go guys can you also
goop wait minute you do too much damage
sir really really quickly I want to um
switch out my
uh ice
thingy wait she's cute I like your
outfit
where's my stash
here switch back to this I
mean we don't really get stunned either
but do I have anything else that makes
sense maybe they sell something that
makes
sense uh is that does that go into the
same
slot or is that a necklace thing no damn
it I could buy one of
these maybe this is I I mean maybe this
could be quite helpful to have for the
fight
um maybe I'll take this one and then add
the second one myself cuz it's quite
expensive that's not what you need what
do you mean of course it
is of course it
is it's the twoo faced one
right ooh life recovery to
minions m
could be good to keep my minions
alive hell yeah
[Music]
also uh wait I have both of this already
this is this I have on level
five we can upgrade this I
guess I almost had a new tier of spells
after you beat this boss there's
something to look forward to you're
trying to motivate me I'm not broken yet
I don't need to be motivated yet don't
take it okay I don't have it but don't
take it Feast on flesh so I trust
you and we got another support gem lying
around
[Music]
here I didn't really like what these
did I already took this I could
take this is also so the survival uh
sacrif sacrificial one I don't like
it yeah but this is too much I know
there's more options but I don't really
know like unless you have one in
particular that you would recommend for
I would say either pain
offering or bone
storm it's just too much to look at
I mean something like applying poison or
Arcane Temple o cost speed yeah
yeah scatter shot I do have
scattershot um lying around somewhere I
think but the arsonist already has
pretty good stuff in here
so ah wait the sniper is actually we
have a sniper out right but he's missing
his second one how do you open that
window again by the way just going to
get
my what was it uh chain
leret I'm pretty sure I
had it don't
I gee okay don't
I huh
did I not or did I sell
it
huh okay uh yeah I think I'll get the
uh
the what was it Arcane Temple sure
thank
you huh need to sneeze
again
uh oh hey we had the same kind of
enchantment on this one too would you
look at
that
sorry how can
I bless you thank you
cell cell cell cell
and you guys said something about don't
get rid of things with
slots do you still agree with that and
yeah it has movement speed should I keep
them we can put a second thing on it
movement speed is really
good
Sal wait but wasn't that a smaller
flask never mind okay God you stressed
me
out
um yeah no don't we want to why why why
Salvage this when we can use
them oopsy we can was it
augmentation or both I think
augmentation life generation per second
I guess I'll wear
them they have a socket too
so I guess it will be the first time
that we put something
in so I can put something in like this
cult resistance lightning
resistance
uh must be hug yay
uh does anything apply to this current
fight
though uh increased physical damage do I
do physical
damage wait ah on Armor it increased
armor evasion and energy Shield oh I
think I'll use this
[Music]
one I think I'll take this would you
agree my bones physical okay don't do
resistance well this is not resistance
anyway disagree I agree
agree agree to
disagree resist is better even if it
doesn't help
now he but which
one cuz there's so many different
ones probably not cold cuz we just had
cold probably there won't be any cold
any anytime soon maybe lightning or
fire lightning yeah I feel so too I feel
it in my
bones that lightning is coming up in a
desert oh hell yeah we learned that from
Zelda uh here there it
goes oops
sorry okay back to that fight that will
probably take me me a while maybe maybe
until I finally uh get it right maybe
we'll get another level
up we'll see we'll see I like how my
toad is parked there oh wait that's the
first time I noticed that he's got like
this toxic black mud whatever
going that's so
funny Would you share with the class
what's so
funny shall we do this
again
attack go minions go minions
yeah you know what to
do just a little bit of a head start it
won't make much of a difference anyway
I'm not ready for
this bro I'm trying to cast something
thank
you I was trying to cast something it
just wouldn't [\h__\h] cast
it oh I just noticed why they they're
they're ah they're like talking or
listening to the
boss that's why they're all looking into
that
direction okay you know what [\h__\h] it
let's go in cuz now I have like a lot of
minions I mean they die fast but you
know they're already
[Music]
gone whoa
oh my oh my oh my God what the [\h__\h] is
going
on I don't think I can win this
fight I but I'll take it
slow with my attacks I'll just focus on
always having my
uh my dots damage on
him I'm just going to try to keep the
distance and let my minions do the job
for me even it will take a
while maybe put a cheering pole up for a
little
bit just dancing around
all more highas oh that's
[\h__\h] but that could be good when
they're
dead ow [\h__\h] oh oh
home
more right
bro
bro oh my oh my my my
potion p pul
potion
potion potion okay I'm good I'm not good
I was so close I was so
close I was so
close oh I got the the the the no potion
situation was making me very nervous
there I think I did Super well
though I was in the zone I had a system
it's taking it
slow I'll do this again though
because my minions die so fast anyway it
doesn't make sense to rush
in [\h__\h]
potion this is the new bigger one right
though is
it guys can you start up at the top
throwing it at it throw something throw
something throw throw something Thro
where's my
arsonist all
right ow
do you see how we're
dancing oh I have no minions to attack
right now but we just got to we just got
to farm minions
oh God a that's no [\h__\h]
a
emerge emerge you
bastards emerge
get those minions get them going get
them cooking
[Music]
easy
Ambush easy that was an easy
fight I feel really cool right now
actually many corpses so I actually feel
really
cool that didn't take me so long at
all ah I feel really cool
I was not
broken
yay yeah it is definitely difficult but
I think it helped me to know that this
boss breaks
people that knowledge helped me to like
mentally prepare for it so they
yeah yeah let no one call my Oshi not a
gamer
exactly but cool fight uh like I got to
say oh even though this weapon is
floating continuously the game has been
offering lots of different variety in
attack
patterns and all all that kind of stuff
in boss
fights the bosses are really Co
cool mhm everybody is
different and does their own
thing yippe I'm glad we did that so
apparently uh oh that was the the
raiding group that we needed to take
care of
ah wait where is dark is she back in the
camp it's the the lady the old lady with
the horns
right I guess I'll go there but I'm kind
of curious is uh wait we already
explored here okay then I'll go back
through the
toad let's take not the town portal but
the toad portal
yeah yeah you defeated the me yeah look
at me sends us a fortuitous you know who
I AMC to say my name say my name May
travel with us in exchange for your Serv
as a jingu and you will have nearly the
respect of one of our own for as long as
you stay nearly only nearly
oh there goes the the bridge thank you
oh
take
thanks oh wait we got a yellow body uh
armor not wearable yet cuz not enough
strength
though oops
see you God damn
right presents exactly one reward yeah
give me more choices at least give me
the illusion of choice that's at least
you could do
ooh yeah that's cool I mean both fire
and cold resistance maybe is not that
urgent but at least it's a yellow armor
with a lot of different stat
I just need more
strength so I guess I won't be needing
that okay oh we got two level five uh
skill
gems oh wow this is the no it's not it's
not the next row you promised me another
row is it somewhere
else a decent singular choice for
reward yeah yeah I
guess
uh wait I can ah I guess we could do
contagion up to five cuz I do use it a
lot and then unearth up to
five yeah need to wait for level seven
gems
yeah spirit is better for you spirit's
nice you you want me to wear that over
the yellow
golden four stat
Armor All I guess I already I already
disenchanted it so it's gone
on did you beat the boss yet I beat the
boss like a boss I showed the boss who's
the
boss he now goes around here as a
mere low tier
enemy you cannot find him anymore as a
boss he's just low tier
now I'm the boss fight
me catch me outside how about that
thanks for the membership
really beat him up again well see that's
the thing I
can't he's just somewhere but he's not
where he once was as the boss he lost
his
spot he's uncool he lost all his
coolness C the gate I know I was just
chilling I was just
chilling whoa oh cooling Village oh
there's people here
oh oh cool we're just always always just
going to be here
now oh that's so
[Music]
cool that's cool that's very original
too unless I mean correct me if I'm
wrong maybe Diablo I had this kind of um
encampment but right now it seems rather
original
see the front Beast is on the Move
twisting the desert as it goes waking
ancient dead and unknown Horrors alike
the Countess brought it here as part of
some nefarious
plan I assume she has allies here I must
track them down and convince them to
give up this madness I just twisted my
spine and cracked like five
bones wait he looks this guy with his
wings that look like like that like that
Pokemon
anyway thank
you whoa what's going on here with your
crazy cash up stuff
guys our guys here what do you do go
there by the sound of your voice you
cannot be Marth it is always intriguing
to meet foreign Warriors her theirs of
War like I actually if I look at the
full body I wouldn't say so but just
this portrait am sham oh she sells okay
just her portrait makes me think of um
Wheel of Time warm night the scary
people that show up in the second
season which also I just wanted to point
out I did see thank you for posting it
in my kfb hashtag otherwise I wouldn't
have seen I didn't watch the trailer yet
though new season in when was it March
or so they got a new season trailer out
now yeah the the sh or whatever how you
say it the well is
fancy way
point this is a sick Caravan but it's so
wide I guess generally a desert is
pretty wide with no obstacles but
sometimes what if you want to go through
more narrow space
is not too long wait yeah time goes by
fast after
all this is like a ship this is like a
sand
ship I never saw someone
before like Envision and recreate the
idea of a ship in the desert like
this yeah I'm taking it slow I'm taking
it slow
oh wait I think I may have received an
interesting
message
ah my
friends oh you got a nice house here wow
why this is so
cool I am aalah the seima of the ardura
I care not where you came from nor what
cast you might have been there all that
matters is that you have shown yourself
capable in battle
Jing remain a friend to the ardura and
you shall have nothing but respect
armor that is that why you wanted me to
check out the front of the
Caravan when when you were saying oh the
front of the Caravan is amazing what you
thinking of this
woman or this part I mean this is also
pretty cool she
wow that bed looks Mighty
comfortable doesn't
it never
mind yo I like these Scrolls I like the
table like all the nice
patterns wow so the Beast has entered
the world once more we were following a
trail of corruption before we were way
laid and now we shall resume the hunt we
Marette are honored bound to seek and
contain corruption wherever it may be
found mhm it seems the sacred Duty falls
on us once more mhm the trail connects
to two locations but we don't know where
the Beast currently resides I am willing
to begin wherever you and your shade
thinks is wisest my shade oh the that
guy the evil looking one
you guess that's my partner
now this whole operation would be more
efficient if they were dead
oh well that's [\h__\h] yeah I I I I
suppose what I saw in that teaser was
true after all these people are [\h__\h]
and
evil so it was
them why are we treating what what
why I guess cuz it's normal like in this
kind of
society but like
bro we're
like involving ourselves with people
like
that I mean if evil why hot but come on
she jez there are no good guys in
PE we live in the society yeah damn how
many people is that 1 2 3 4 5 are they
all five 10 15
20 uh 25 probably wait there's like
maybe 30
35 uh 40 45 50 55 60
65 what 70
75 80 85
that's probably it could be 100 but it
looks like
85 maybe
90 you count
95 maybe it's
95 woman we have to talk about the
conditions out there their working
conditions are worse than at kfp
yes can we talk about it foreigners
often misunderstand the concept of the
seima I am no dictator and do not make
some pathetic claim of Divine Light okay
Emperors are for Nations filled with a
weak-minded and soft as history has
proven every time an Empire Falls and we
endure I am seima because others have
put their faith in me I don't know I
mean if you have slaves you're basically
a dictator to me because there is no
better replacement it is a role much
better by definition
bro
Glory but it is an amazing ship that you
have here if I may call it so travel the
adura Caravan to areas of the reported
corruption wait wait wait so what what
what what what do I what do I do for it
to make it
move do I go to my map and just choose
the next location or was did I miss
something oh okay
[Music]
uh Palani Gates
or
huh what oh wrong
map oh the T table
oh I have to click that
table uh yeah okay but still halani
Gates I guess or no this is level 17
monster level this is level 20 so we
should go here first I
suppose we could also go to the V
outskirts they're level 16 over there
doesn't seem
like the quest really needs me to go
there but
then this is just like optional I
guess but wait raft breaker didn't we
just fight that oh I came from the okay
makes sense then I shall go
here all right o oh desert looks
different here it's not red sand
no uh
where do I
here oh oh
goodbye into the modern
Quarry looks more
depressing not depressing seems have
been up to no good in the hills of M
yeah no you're you're right the lack of
color is a bit
depressing can I get a cheer for all the
sick chickens what do you mean too late
to help you I'm so on track with my
super
chats are you already sick
though yeah you're sick sick as
fire nothing less to expect from a
chicken of
mine nothing wrong with being sick sick
as [\h__\h]
yeah but yeah uh get well
soon you also download the flu don't
worry it it's it happens to the best of
us for example uh
quason so maybe you should feel kind of
cool also you know you guys talk about
how women supposedly Sy up their period
Cycles which we don't sorry to break
your dreams but if you find that so
entertaining you could think of it as
you synced up your flu cycle with quason
which
again is pretty
cool you have a connection
now you talk about it no I
don't I
just you know I'm not a baby I pick up
things then I talk about
it it's just how it is it's how the
world works and how the wheel
turns blacksmith swe
take
it
infection oh P up open up open
whatever whatever I will not run after
these items anymore if they don't want
to be picked up then I will not pick
them up
anymore uh yeah uh was that enough
cheerful like I feel like it was at
least
um a positive way of thinking about
being sick
too bad I am not sick right because then
you would feel like you're connected to
me if you're sick but we don't want the
laa to be sick no no
no leave me alone with your sickness
your germs oh checkpoint
SMY
poofy hi a she meow at me she woke up
she walked in and she did a stress
oh hello I think you were heard just
now g g g wants players to pick up and
choose since you always best medicine
then you're in luck that I'm streaming
today and ra a long as well a r oh a ra
long stream
I feel like we should take it and then
enchant
it on our own that flask what do you
think what was that checkpoint
for what is there to checkpoint me for
what's the what's the
point oh
baby oh she jumped offy
[Music]
you want to be with
me she wants to be with
me what made you choose to play as a
necromancer um because I'm
simultaneously to this playthrough
playing the ablo 4 right now and I'm a
fire
Mage
there so I wanted something different
but I also had to choose a female
character obviously so that gave gave me
the choice of only two classes if we
already get rid of the fire Mage I guess
I could have had an ice Mage or whatever
but
nah yeah I was also considering the um
what was it called the Archer
lady do you want to lie down properly
and not just sit
H baby girl you're going to stay with
me going to chill up here the ranger
yeah I was considering the ranger but
honestly like from looking at the videos
the video previews of the
attacks looks pretty
fun yeah I wanted to stream
spikes that was the main
goal
iest L me oh
much I feel like in 2024 my cats got
even clingier than
before especially in the past like half
year especially smooy got like more
accepting of when I
stream previously when I streamed she
would want to have space or like peace
and would go into a different room even
though normally she's clingy as [\h__\h]
but nowadays she's often in the room
even when I
stream it's so cute makes me so happy
she laid down she's Loy
[Music]
loafing you always goone to mysty yeah I
think so too I had a lot of
trips interesting a lot of trips this
summer
so I I do think she missed
[Music]
me haven't left my cat on a trip yet low
key
afraid they have someone to take care of
them then it should be okay hey oh that
I didn't even recognize this as a bridge
that I could walk over that's what the
checkpoint was
[Music]
for for that direction I thought oh
there must be a boss over there but
no you love me too not just my cat huh
not just my cat loves me that's good to
know our people have lived in the
shadows of the Junes for too long
countless Generations have been
forgotten will be
forgotten we are not faridan we are
Marth and if we were together the people
who wrote this then they will be forced
to acknowledge us the same kind as the
ones from the Caravan right must show
them that casting us off is a
mistake we must show them our
strength perhaps
we can one day rebuild keth itself for
all those who live in the plains of
vastii oh there're the people chain to
the front Okay well then I'm cheering
for
them secretly I'm cheering for
[Music]
them yeah doesn't sound very
happy another
one wao wait let me take that maybe
we'll get better results from that oh
level
up we got another level up oh oh oh
she's
oh she's curling up on like right next
to my
phone she's she wants to sleep right in
front of me this is the first like she
would come into my room more often
recently right when I'm streaming but
she wouldn't be like right in front of
me she would be like on the bed or on
the cat tree behind
me still like a little bit more distance
but right now even though I'm still
talking she's she wants to be right
there she wants me to have a constant
view on her cute she's my cheer
leader she's so cute I can always pet
her now she's in petting
reach but now I feel like I shouldn't
get too loud I don't want to scare her
when she's like
sleeping now why I'm holding back
[Applause]
wa Bristal
slash those kind of things I see them
flying around in the summer we call them
kni at least in
Austria I hate
[Music]
them they're disgusting and big they
don't do
anything but they are just too big take
get
up why won't you why won't
you there we
go I I hope they can fix that in a
patch like I'm clicking on it a million
times ooh another cult maybe this one's
even better than the other one it
doesn't even need strength to be
worn if only I could pick it up man or
is my inventory full now um I think it
would fit
let me rearrange a little
bit everything
okay there we
go take
it troll please take it I really want it
there it is
triggering
me is this like
uh remains of a
caravan o a
ring that's good we can make that one
blue we can make it
magic check my my settings it's just
because I have that skill on
on
um on the left Mouse button so I
constantly wants to do the skill even
though I'm clicking right on the item oh
see there's more of this
art yeah on that on that illustration
they looked very zombie like but in the
game they look less zombie like
so I think they're suffering quickly
but I want to keep it on there because
it's so easy to
cast and it's okay I take the
tradeoff I take it it makes it easiest
for the way I
fight wait what what happened with this
uh evasion rating maximum life lightning
resistance and physical fors damage what
do you think better than the other one I
have in in my
stash maybe not I don't know this
one this one has no armor
extra uh and it has different
resistances no fire but instead we have
for
damage yeah this one I can wear that's
that's what makes it automatically
better right I guess okay and then uh
how does this work again first this
one and then the double
face on the ring do we want to see what
it could
become Mana oh it already got two so I
don't need the orb of augmentation Mana
regeneration rate and increased light
radius I don't like it that much
I don't like it that much I
[Music]
think I can still Aug
it
oh
okay
oh let you see if it's one mod or not
what do you
mean that's still pretty bad
yeah I don't like it that much either so
we agree
hello increased armor and energy Shield
by
42% wow
it goes It goes now it goes by-bye last
uh arguments to
share it all goes too
late all right I wanted to enchant these
and
see what we're going to get
[Music]
uh mhm mhm I think this one
wins
mhm switch your rul tell your
tale speak
up you like the charges per second
more really
to what should I
do I really don't know the difference
that
well kind of the same 46 48 increased
recovery
R for long boss fights okay true
true all
right you guys are very welcome to guide
me on these kind of things
[Music]
and last but not least we got this gem
to give
away uh but yeah once again I'm
like what should I
do you some people keep on pointing out
raging spirits
but I don't
know because I don't have fire spells so
like fire area spell summon the spirit
stuff like that is always a
meme is it
H I
mean
okay oh but again I don't have any more
space and I don't know if I want to
change anything in my current
lineup we'll put it in here
[Music]
why do I still have this don't need it
right let's get rid of
it speak
up do not
wer
okay you can be an infernal later
you don't have any active skeleton
archers I don't really also look where
we are here
uh I think I'll do just generally
increased
damage um oh oh she wants belly rubs oh
my God yes
she's okay half of her body is on my
keyboard there you
go a she's so soft
okay ignore ignore Focus for
streaming um oh here
F1 yeah I'll go back uh where's my toad
here this is where I parked my
toad
okay wait
sorry got some DMS preparing something
for
tomorrow for the Austria re view
stream some pictures
by the way are you guys curious what the
silly membership stream
entails the silly hand scam stream don't
get your hops up too
high
uh but I feel like my original idea I
already improved and changed it a little
bit because I feel like the silly hand
cam stream words got some people hoped
up that it would be very silly but it
wasn't quite as silly yet as as you guys
were anticipating perhaps so now I
prepared some extra
content hand Shadows that would be
silly but no I'm not going to be playing
around with hand Shadows unfortunately
but yeah I prepared some stuff it will
need some setup because I think I'm
going to be uh doing it
oh in the
kitchen just a little bit more
space and can angle the camera in all
directions all kinds of directions
none can oppose
me um but yeah uh basically I picked
something up in the Christmas
Market uh that I want to show off in in
the memb
Stream I saw something and I was like oh
my God I want
this so it's all based upon that one
purchase what's a Jacob
lder I don't know what that is so
probably not a whole stream for that no
as I said like it's more now because I
feel like you guys were looking forward
to
it now I need to
deliver he also have some like
holiday spirit
going but I I do kind of want a little
bit address um
something
uh I will say that I agree there have
been too many watch alongs in my members
streams this
year um we I committed we committed to
something that just takes a lot of time
more than originally
perhaps
anticipated um but I still want to
remind I mean I I feel like most of you
guys don't really mind but you may still
prefer more
variety but at least most of you guys
are not really like angry or so um but I
would like to still remind that I do
lbus streams weekly for almost a whole
year now except for some weeks where I
was like traveling and a little bit too
busy but the simple fact that I do them
weekly
already gives you guys a lot more member
streams and other people are
getting
so even if a big amount of those are
watchong I feel like even though this is
a specific special situation where a
watch
along is just like there's extra amounts
of watch alongs because of the
commitment we made to that one
anime um but
generally like even in my watchong
streams that's the thing like if you are
skipping the watchalong streams just
because you feel like you're not
interested you're actually missing out
too because as the people can confirm
who are are going to my watchong
streams even there I do like I stall a
lot before I begin or after or in
between and do other silly stuff like
the other day you guys had a lot of fun
because I was like messing around in
3D doing those impr prompto impr improv
dance
moves pick it up pick it up pick it up
yeah stuff like that also happens during
the watch Longs
mhm
impromptu you stay for the yapping Parts
see that's that's also I guess a way you
could do
it yeah if you really don't want to
watch the anime that's fine and I I do
feel bad about like spamming so many
watchs but still like I feel like
considering how many member streams I
do it it should
be
forgiven but generally I didn't want to
do that many either that many watch
alongs this wasn't originally my
intention but I'm sure there's still
people who are enjoying it because they
love monogatari and also because they
like to just hang and chill with me so
thanks thanks a lot to you
guys for tolerating this big phase of
endless
Wongs we're almost done like literally
we only need one more
stream we're already in the most recent
season all it takes is one more stream
cuz we're halfway through it it's a fun
series fun fun memb
yeah it's very nostalgic for
me this lot were left down here to die
getting
hungry have a little bit of a snap
here IM the way she says this is so
funny to
me I like how comy member streams are
yeah me
too me too me
too and also
um anyway this was all brought to my
attention because of one reply so it's
obviously I I'm very aware that it's not
like everybody's unhappy with it no not
at all but uh the reply was about you
know was because I I wrote on Twitter
like oh let's watch um El
Camino together in a watch along but
[Music]
actually I was a bit misunderstood there
I did mean to actually watch
that um publicly for once not as a
members watch along no it wasn't really
a joke but I was thinking if I'm going
to do a watch along this one I would
want to do
publicly for
one it wasn't going to be a m only watch
long I don't think I really besides the
Shrek one that I think was on Callie's
Channel could be wrong and the cat's One
turns out I forgot about that that one
the other
day uh I haven't done any besides those
I
think
yeah and but then like people told me El
Camino is kind of mid it's still fun and
like if you love breaking bed it's
probably very worth it to still watch it
especially if you like Jesse and I do
like Jesse and I do want to see more of
the story and when people say
something's mid you know I still tend to
enjoy
it so I definitely want to watch
it but now I don't know if it's worth
watching it as a watch along if people
say it's mid I have not seen the movie
yet at least it's not bad but that
brings me to another thing I wanted to
say that I thought about today while I
was starting to watch uh B call
SA remembering how much people were
recommending break uh Bal Sal to me and
giving it really high
praises I was
thinking this whole Breaking Bad
universe and the shows and the seasons
that come with it belongs to me is
really impressive in
like the quality
quality that they
provide because Breaking Bad had not a
single Bad episode or
season you know with many other shows
it's like you you watch a season the
first season it's great second season
and so on like it just goes downhill
from there
often like it's almost feels like every
great show out there has like shitty
seasons that ruined the
experience but Breaking Bad didn't have
that you can argue about the fly one I I
even I who was very critical about
stalling episodes and stuff also
mon even I thought that was
great it had a right to be there not to
fly course not the
episode yeah it it also it has deeper
meaning yeah
yeah I would like to pick this
up I would like to pick this up I would
like to
okay I would like to pick this
up I would like to pick this
up I would like to pick this up thank
you I I'd like to pick this
up
okay yeah and then like even let's put
it aside that Breaking Bad with five
seasons had no Bad season and no Bad
episode an amazing
run of good quality content and
production let's put that aside even
their spinoff show better call all is so
good that people say it's even better
than the main show which was not to play
Down how great the main show is people
just liked it that much that is an
impressive
achievement those show Runners whoever
is behind all of these shows and
episodes they need a they need a big Pat
on their
uh
shoulder big respect and big
appreciation for not ruining a show at
any
point like
wow is the same team behind medical all
as breaking
B is it the same like producers
ourselves Vince you guys bring up this
guy called
Vince pick it up pick it pick this up
thank
you large of the same oh see that might
be the key
to continuous
quality
perhaps but even even in other cases
where the same person has taken care of
a show throughout the whole show I think
even then there's cases here and there
where there can be some
disappointment so I don't know I was
really impressed with that when I
thought about it like wow cuz even
battle Call Saul has like what six
Seasons or seven
even I thought like I looked at I
started watching I was wondering oh I
wonder how many seasons this has it's
just a spin-off so probably not that
many turns out it has an insane amount
of Seasons as well six yeah
how can you not [\h__\h] it up or well I
mean I just started so I can't judge it
completely yet but you guys are probably
going to tell me that the whole show is
great there's no no shitty season right
otherwise people wouldn't say it's
better than Breaking
Bad where is the checkpoint
here did I check out this whole place
why was the checkpoint there there was
no boss
right also I I literally just began so
don't worry there's no spoilers really
to be heard but I'm so happy to see
reoccurring characters
already like uh Tuco and Mike Mike was a
pleasant
surprise and I'm sure there's going to
be more
reoccurring
characters oh one thing I noticed when I
watched the finale of freaking bad and
and and hold on don't mute me yet I
think I will not spoiler anything um the
thing that I thought Netflix spoilered
me about did not end up showing up in
the ending so I wonder now that I
watched everything where did this scene
happen that I saw in the trailer with
Walter having hair and being on the
phone somewhere out in like a desert or
something was that in the first episode
I can't recall him being in the
situation like that where
he said such
things but
yeah sorry Netflix I was really angry at
you for supposedly spoilering
me f uh turns out I wasn't
spoilered is this from the first episode
I
suppose what what I do
here imprison by do I need to give it an
essence of
[Music]
ice do I have cck ice oh there we go
wa wa
die you've got nothing on
me there we go my power to oh he gives
me Ence we almost
di was this an after effect I didn't
look I was looking at the essence of ey
uh what was I talking about oh yeah I
don't know if I was 100% satisfied
with the ending of
Walter to not be
specific I'm not going to be specific
for [\h__\h]
[Music]
sake I mean it's not bad it's not
completely thank you it it's it's fine
the way it is but I feel like I
envisioned it differently a little
bit but it's okay speak up it's all
right 20% recovery applied instantly oh
that's pretty
sick should I exchange it add another
one onto it and exchange it what do you
think oh
yeah I'll keep my current one but lucky
that this one has also minion skills
yeah do a spool warning and talk about
it Aug get that
one sure
okay sire's goic quar stuff of
dueling o investigator Silver Charm of
the foliage
your speed is unaffected by
slows used when you are affected by a
slow oh but I don't know that first
sounds amazing if it was like
permanent because I imagine like a fight
that we just
had where there's a lot of slowing stuff
all the time it's just being canceled
out once or twice in that battle
M doesn't really help that
much it does recharge per second it's
good to have it's good to
have okay wait I will tell your Tale
that was cute and I
need I need uh this I
think or maybe
not increased spirit and maximum
Mana I still
feel this might be better oh you that's
big at least it does have the level six
skeletal
Warrior Feast on
flesh
[Music]
mhm and
then I think I wanted to look at this
one reduced charges per
use I wonder what's better having it on
the minions or having it applied
instantly on
me more spirit means more
minions oh uh
yeah oh wait in increased Spirit oh
somehow I was thinking about um The
increased energy
thing oh that's great
then oh it's a smaller one okay I'll
just sell both then orello oopsy
disenchant stay inside
wonderful and oh and we got a skill
point I didn't even
notice more
damage oh what about the other things
here I don't know if I want
[Music]
to where this right
now we are not really dealing with ice
right
now ooh oh this gives it particularly a
cold
modifier also interesting but perhaps
another
[Music]
time do we want to look at this one
still
oh oh oh yeah press this increase
maximum energy shield and cold
resistance all
right so much cold resistance now
I don't really use lock uh gr cage
anymore
but
maybe I could use something like
this yeah
ready to go to the Arctic oh I'm sure
one of these days in Poe maybe not until
the second part though we will come upon
a icy snow
land you can take upgrade and move it to
another
skill
what save it for your raging Spirits Why
is my my throat hurts so much today it's
actually good that smoothie is here
keeping me from being loud because my
throat hurts I need another FR candy
she's looking at
me another a FR
candy your cat also arrived
hello our cats are mentally connected
through the
monitors meow to you good
sir is your cat lady or a
boy I need to address your cat correctly
please let me
know please tell me your cat's pronouns
hello your super groupy merch came in
just now
w I hope you like it I hope you'll make
good use of
it I have
both
mhm cute you lucky lucky
bastard I only have
ladies this whole house is only filled
with ladies lady
energy did you guys know cats also have
periods
but somehow I never took notice of it
like they must be doing some good
cleaning down
there
constantly I I never took notice of
it I'm I'm sorry but you learned the
hard way really what did you like
accidentally get some of your cat's
blood on your hands or so when you
picked her up or
so like you know I I I'm constantly
cuddling with my I
cat I never had person
experience your cats are un fixed oh
they are oh wait don't they get their
period anymore then okay then that
should explain the
mystery Oh I
thought they might still get it oh okay
never mind them explains a
lot oh my explains a lot I wonder how
much like worse so to say it
is when your cats are not
Spade
[Music]
huh I guess I got to go all the way up
here where am
I
here I'm
coming
here going
to wait you didn't know what B
was yeah makes them not have
babies checkpoint so what's up
here more
trouble good night
go yeah I've experienced my cats in heat
one
time and that was basically the the
signal to go to the vet
and have
them yeah lose their oh
wow reer
deductive uh
function
man there we go all he dropped was some
gloves but they have 20 no and and they
don't have 20 intelligence but they have
a
slot might be
interesting M they look pretty cool
too n that's pretty lame I think 32 five
physical damage your attacks
is well being able to add a slot is cool
though oh another checkpoint so now I
have
two which point does
what Munitions bunker uh-oh oh what are
you doing crazy Lord true oah The Dread
engineer how fun this seems to be the
main
quest burn burn burn you're stealing my
words out of my mouth that's what I
usually do but I guess I'll give it to
you because I'm not a fire Mage in this
game ow that
hurts explosion W whoo
who death and Decay oh I sent that totem
out a little bit BL I don't have any
minions right
now
[\h__\h] stinky I he has all kinds of weird
[\h__\h] out
here out I guess it's rather safe when
you were that far
away oh God he's raging
I think actually isn't this a
woman judging from the voice and the
name
uhoh I told them gone again oh and it's
gone
again Yahoo I think if I'm that far away
he can really not get me oh
she welcome back welcome back welcome
[Applause]
back
oh blow I was going to say
bro
please down Brea it in
oh
he my totem appeared and disappeared
please stop hitting
it it's such a waste of
[Music]
wood
M very good very good
first try of
course
Oak yeah I've been
there I know how that
feels but I revive at the
end oh I'll take this I was about to not
pick that up because it's uh gray get me
out of here turns
out I cannot differentiate between white
and this
color you're were getting one shot by
the fire damage oh which one the long
one where she goes in the full circle
when you're hugging the wall it doesn't
seem to touch you
though wait this looks so
pretty I want to wear
that but please get me out of here oh
wait there's somebody here
oh oh
oh sorry I was uh
distracted winds praise
you 1,000 Praises my friend you look
cool I thought I would die
here please take me back to your Caravan
and I will tell you anything you want to
know goodbye a defective wait I'm not
taking you then Am I who resist I'm just
leaving you
behind wait what about the other
checkpoint what's
there my quest already tells me to go
back to the halani gates but
wait this checkpoints optional boss
maybe we'll see we'll see
come on you fit in my inventory I know
it oh stretch good stretch you're going
to
leave don't leave
[Music]
a byebye you're welcome
anytime my baby
uh wait what the heck was that
checkpoint for there's nothing
here you replace contagion with a fire
what do you mean now why
now why particularly
now so I got a skill
gem what if I don't want though
I like contagion people did say it was a
good
skill cuz of raging Spirits is that the
way to
go but then I'm just a lame ass boring
basic [\h__\h] fire Mage
again it only works as a way to spread
the other chaos spell essence strain
wait so I won't be making Fire magic I'm
fine with it as long as I'm not doing
Fire
magic
actively oh you look
good
lady level 55
bro you probably outleveled the whole
content of this first part of the game
The Early Access
part you will r a wall but you're using
it to cast
minions so what what what what am I to
do
quickly thank you
o
what what
she what a
shield big big Shield
[Music]
uh swap Grim Feast for raing
Spirits
uh
here Grim
Beast raging spirit
and
then and then what
uh uh where did it go here use the gem
and turn it into flame
wall oh
wait
n this
one create a wall of fire in front of
the character which ignites everything
within its area lame any projectiles
fired through the wall by you and allies
deal added fire damage and inflict the
ignite on
H lame fire lame
lame lame
[Music]
try it no of course it's not lame but
like lame I want to do something
[Music]
else is a different fire spell no no I
don't mean the skill on its own is lame
fire on its like the concept of
fire she's lame
[Music]
um still minions yeah what about my
spikes though I'll keep my spikes too
right we're still focusing on
spikes use Essence strain with conion
I'm just trying to help you cuz conion
by itself sucks now
[Music]
uh phix goes for Rebellion phase
Rebellion fire fire like the
[Music]
fire okay so what you you say use flame
wall flame wall ignites enemies when C
in it any projectile
[Music]
and then instead of
contagion can I still put this in there
yeah
okay it has been done
uh wrong
one I want to make that fancier but
maybe it's not worth it but it looks so
cute maybe it's not worth it
anyway but this one
though this
[Music]
one
intelligence perhaps still not worth
fit uh but right so something like this
I would
Salvage
what oh artificial Shard a stack of 10
shards becomes an artificial orb which I
guess gives an item a
slot nice our first
one cool
and okay then the
rest can
go put the runes
here oh this one makes blue into gold I
want to do this through this one
but probably you guys would tell me to
stop because it's not worth
it okay let's look at
this
uh what I can't use it on anything
why cuz they're all already
maxed nah no way need more stats need
more in are you calling me stupid
what rude into the fryer you
go do not
W
okay use the desert map to travel to the
halani gate okay okay okay then that's
our second desert
goal the helani gates over
here yeah
oh wait I forgot to talk to Lisa oh I
can still talk to
her I know what Jam R intends at top the
burial spirs of desar lie the maret's
most honored de the King has become
driven by Madness to seek any trace of
ancient flesh from those of renown or
power in
life he intends to feed their bodies to
the horrific creature he keeps in a cage
behind his throne they call it the
Beast I have seen it they call it the
Beast and we call it the
tacle his his bug is doing
spein look at it look at him go
oh it's break
dancing whoa look at the girl it's legit
brick dancing why is it doing
that choose or do not oh you gamble
lady wow I
[Music]
see I got some cool stuff but I have yet
to gamble I have yet to fall into the
gamble Rabbit
Hole today is still not a
day here we go maybe uh today this is oh
oh my God
this is very terrifying seeing them all
stand
there I feel bad why have we
stopped oh I'm pissed that we stopped oh
why have we stopped the helani gates are
closed and the fadan hold them in
defense of the
Beast to find another day way okay no
problem I think this is going to be the
last region we're going to do
today wait oh really there's no PO down
there
either so I go back onto the boat or
what yeah looks like
it sounds good yeah it's already 11:00
p.m. oh my
God I'm going to read some super
chats so one more region maybe takes I
don't know an hour how long have these
been taking feel like 1 hour is
pretty oh
yeah
good good uh guess return talk to Ru
okay risu do something about this the
halani gates are closed then jamra must
have succeeded in capturing them he plan
to close the gates to prevent the
Marette from interrupting his Harvest a
Siege from the front would be impossible
now but there is another way an ancient
passage lost to time it was used by the
traitor balbala I can show you where it
is H if you will use it to stop jaman ra
before it is too
late
mhm so you heard that the outcasts have
raised their new king from the grave and
he seeks to violate desar to feed our
honored Deads to the Beast such a
transgression those vile dogs how dare
they our city of the Dead lies beyond
the halani so disrespectful crush the
feran
immediately let us see if this Defector
information is truthful infiltrate this
supposed passage find your way to the
top of the gates
without you have your orders I shall do
exactly as you say me
lady I like her accent I can do the same
accent if I wanted
to I feel like it's a fake accent I
don't think she really talks like that
but I might be wrong it sounds uh forced
creepers and crawlers in dark spaces how
Wonder would never raise the unknown
dead to do her
bidding hey hey hey hey careful you
careful with what you say wait a second
I need my fire skill uh where is
it
play here we go again looking all too
familiar this is exactly what I was
trying to
avoid but okay we're doing it
now it will be hard to differentiate
what game we're playing now
honestly what are these
bats at least it lights up the area it's
going to be easier for your eyes to
behold SP okay spiders it's good to have
fire for spiders we all know
that F you
guys
oh another oh two masks one gold one not
gold he wore two hats I feel bad about
killing him now he was one of the
enlightened ones one of the two hat
wearers that people nowadays think don't
exist
anymore I'm
ashamed one of my
own I took their
life for now I will only be ridiculed
even more for my hat
wearing I need
allies a dark world out there
for two hat wearing
people so dark dark world
will you be my allies
kfp for
justice I like that you're back to
laging I I I am
not but if I may
be honest because it's just between us
and you guys are my
allies I might be able to admit
that I have been hiding my hats in the
recent times because I feared a
discrimination that I often
experience the lack of presentation
representation in the two hat wearing
people community
is so little therefore we are not very
accepted by the society that we live in
and so I must I must take at least one
hat off at a time to protect
myself from the judgmental evil people
out
there who think that I am
evil for wearing two hats
it's been really hard for
me to work through
this and and be
so ashamed of
myself they make me feel ashamed of
myself I thought I knew who I was and I
thought I could be proud of it I will
but people pointed at me and raised
their
Forks the big
forks and and and we're and we're saying
to put me on a spike and and set me on
fire cuz of my two
hats they're
Forks Fork Fork not forklift you know
what I mean pitchforks
yes so after while I took them off from
my own safety please
understand thank
you how you make things up no I opened
up my heart to you right now and you you
claim that I am just lying to
you you break my
heart
e fire definitely very important here
[Music]
how dare he even suggest something like
that what is this hole oh I cannot enter
it I thought I could enter it okay
return oh we two hats from now on and
Sol solidarity thank you that might lead
us in the right direction into a better
future where we all are more accepting
of each other and more
tolerating where people could perhaps
even and now stay with me I know this is
like Unthinkable and perhaps very
intimidating thoughts but perhaps one
day it might even be okay to wear free
hats it's too good to be true I know but
perhaps we can dream perhaps we
can have dreams and goals
and think of a better future and and
when we think of it we can take it we
can grasp it and we can create it but we
got to be the first ones to do the first
step fore hats no
no guys guys calm down that is perhaps
not in our lifetime possible maybe in
hundreds and hundreds of of
years but we have to start now for us
forehead that
is that is too much to dream of I want
to warn you guys to not be too dreamy
You Beautiful dreamy
chickens I don't want to get your hopes
up too
much one day you'll be lying in your
death
bed and be asking yourself
why were you never able to wear four
hats after all that talk motivational
talk and all of these actions you took
all of these times you marched for
hats with no positive
outcome and then you'll blame me for
[Music]
it
foreheads are you saying the four hats
shall go onto your forehead H we will
have to do something about gravity then
I'm not sure how that would
work perhaps if uh
something maybe if science could invent
something like
a an
elastic string of some sort
to uh wrap
around your head and hold it in
place would that be possible I'm not
sure
H how do I get here ah there okay back
we
go even our hats
yeah even our hats could wear hats in
the future
but that is
something that we would be looking at
after perhaps
like a marvelous amount of six or seven
hats that's when the hats start wearing
the
hats
hello very sophisticated hats the
traitor balala has been sentenced to
1,000 years of suffering as a Jin Bound
in this place of her dishonor let no
woman or man of Marth blood enter her
prison before her time is
s okay
I I just couldn't really listen to what
you were saying because I was looking at
this Tower and was just thinking this
Tower would be better if it was made out
of
hats and that really dest distracted me
I'm
sorry true true
true the internet is for hacked the
internet is for
hats buy a hat and put it on for hat
hats
hat there's a checkpoint up
there are you happy guys now with all
this fire on your
screen I hope it doesn't give you
anxiety
BL Maul I didn't even notice you there
because of all the
[Music]
fire I need
more
know oh who that was close oh he's
dead it
appears that my inventory is a little
bit full but that's that that's is no
reason for me to not pick up this item
take it take
it oh okay yeah if I have the inventory
open it does this funny
thing well look at this pretty wait it's
a [\h__\h] yellow
ring are you ready are you ready for
this maximum life maximum Mana increased
amount of regeneration rate fire
resistance lightning increased light
lightning resistance
nice um replace
with maybe this
one
[Music]
y upgrade upgrade upgrade upgrade oh
lightning damage
cool but we don't do lightning but
that's
fine I might want to go to the p uh
poundo a bit
full a bit too
full oh that takes two spaces this one
too a good night gold jum Bo me
bye-bye take
[Music]
care oh this lady has a quest what the
heck quickly I hope I didn't miss out on
anything that I could have done on the
side if you are traveling through
traitor's passage there is something the
traitor Bala according to the
tales I will tell you her story
but did you give me a quest or what she
didn't give me a
quest thought she would
what h
uh I think I can
go or
no I guess it can
go yeah one level is still better
[Music]
speak
up I will tell your
tale speak
up this lady is so funny
always telling me to louder she's like
we need a lady like this for the not for
me but for people who just are in the
class quiet as
[\h__\h] I cannot hear you but I'm certainly
not one of those people my voice is very
loud but I can control it but I can
control it sorry
what
oh checkpoint
someone wanted these doors to remain
shut I should open
them
friend
oo well if it isn't the traitor herself
oh hello let's get this over with do you
have a lower
body doesn't look like it I'm sure you
do though am I am I
what
now [\h__\h] prove oh indeed no lower body I
think emerge
emerge let's go
ohaa very fast spe waa Speedy
gonzale Speedy Gonzalez what the [\h__\h] is
wrong with yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo
yo what the [\h__\h] is wrong with you uh uh
oh she flies over my fire does it does
she even get hit by
it surely the hit box is still on the
ground right yeah it's going to
be o oh fancy attacks
but this kind ah this ah it kind of
reminds me of the um oh
[\h__\h] this fight is so damn hard had to
try many
times I I'll figure it out but it
reminds me a little bit
of the way how we are like in this
little Arena and this enemy fights
really fast and kind of like has some
Ninja elements reminds me of in Zelda um
the Speedy Ninja enemies whatever what
what area again and and the one
boss the one boss fight in Zelda R of
the wild I think
specifically where he then falls down
into this hole I think yeah the yiga the
yiga
yeah not yoga not yoga yiga not yoga
yiga someone wanted these doors to
remain shut I should open them second
try I still have to unseal
you that but then I can't uh I can't
return you anymore if I break the seal
can
I will I get my money
back I just whatever I'll do it then
okay I'll keep you improve
myself I'll just randomly place my
firewalls and hope that sometimes they
will
hit got to be fast really with my
attacks it's kind of stinky
here diarrhea much
Bala time throw those arrows out
right
good but definitely seems difficult
maybe more difficult even than the the
other fight that uh was with the
hyenas spint a
b got to remember to put out my my
motivation toll where is
she oh
hi sometimes she's just chilling there
even though she's so
Speedy not
so face spee
yeah yeah
yeah poison no
oh ah ah stay calm stay
calm oh she left
again where she where
she don't make me nervous like that
where are
youa what is this oh it's like cuz she's
wait she's literally like spreading
poison during this wait where am I
supposed to what what what wa wa what
hey hey hey what what am I supposed to
do hey hello hello hello what do I do at
this time hello I'm dying what do you
do I I have to find her is she invisible
I have to fight the nothingness bro I
was so far with the fight I didn't know
what to do during this
time I was waiting for her to come back
out I thought she went down and the
reason it was getting stinkier is
because she's like [\h__\h] down there
someone wanted these and just just
really having a rough stomach moment
open
them okay I mean that might very well be
what she's doing and this is just all an
excuse it's okay it's okay like you
don't have to be ashamed about it
where is she doing it again oh God so
early on I I guess she did it before too
and I just was lucky wa bro bro are you
kidding okay I wasn't healing at
all n that sucks in the ring is it in
that ring
always someone wanted these doors that
ring doesn't necessarily need that she's
there though right open them that's just
some some seal that she placed there I
think run around the arena till you see
okay I don't have to like attack to find
her me I thought I have
to just hope that my attack hits
her oh
and I wasn't really paying
attention uh so are you about to do that
still noint
is what do you mean like she's literally
she was nowhere to be seen
she's doing it again but she's like here
what what stop it then stop it
then stop
it
y doie doie doie do
no please [\h__\h] wait so I here y y I see
you I see you I see you
please oh man please can we end it now
I'm rolling so much in this game this is
really like kind of a Elden ring game
Dark
Souls Dark Souls Vibes
are there sure
oh didn't isn't this second or third
try not bad spirit in coin how fun not
bad keep on rolling keep on rolling
Diablo
ring oh pretty good I'm I'm I might be
uh decent at this
[Laughter]
game I want to jump into the this whole
intrusive
FS first
try no very very very good because like
the only reason I failed at the second
dry is because I
didn't really understand what to do
during that one
phase it do be like that sometimes I
will you
down I am proud of myself
all right
return wait as s the traitor test reach
the top of yeah okay okay oh I forgot
the mids oh
well yay level up also when did we level
up uh chaos
resistance and gain 8% physical damage
as chos chaos damage do I still do chaos
damage I don't right cuz I gave away my
uh con my my pest attack thingy that was
chaos
right or is this also
chaos oh the minions do okay
cool is my toad
purring no maybe not I heard some purs
like how can I be a
identify what do we have oh not
much nothing that we need to keep
ah I will
Salvage those
booies ah You released Bala the traitor
yeah and it isy to redeem her soul by
allowing her to serve as a mentor Jin
during your dance with a scorpion Jin in
modern times we give aspiring decoras a
straightforward test for this task
however the old ways are required you
will have to face a much deadlier trial
was Jin I know what it is speak to AA
the original trial is not far from here
and the Caravan is Duty bound to carry
you there still is
[Music]
oh I
see
uh what is
thisas why are you standing there
gawking at me we must go to the trial of
the
seas oh need more intelligence
okay so you released balara from her
prison and she fought well not well
enough she may now earn her Redemption
if the ancient places still hold power
her barrier contains her soul she will
tell you what to do next now her body
makes sense with not having legs cuz gin
usually don't have
legs like the the typical Disney Jin
doesn't have a leg a leg
legs
goodbye I guess sometimes in some Medias
uh Gins also get legs like human shaped
legs but generally I guess they don't
have
legs wait so it says use a desert map to
travel to the trial of sea so I'm
already done with that Rion that I said
if I was done with it I would end the
stream today
right too
bad that was faster than
expected no I'm not okay you're not done
you're done when I say so ra
okay
okay I go what
where what where am I where am I I'm
here what do I
here uh
what GP is forcing me to
[Music]
stream is this where I was supposed to
go wait no isn't this where I just came
from wait where am I supposed to
go that zone still has an exit this
one am I right
here not done
here [\h__\h] I should have just taken my
frog huh but I think frog gone now I
will you down or is RO to there was that
a Diablo thing that if you walk out your
portal is gone I think that was a Diablo
thing frog so if I go back to the ship I
I go to
frog oopsy
excuse me I'll pay for the
damages
frog sorry for abandoning you and
thinking that I could make my way
somewhere without you you're still the
only one that I love and the only one I
trust my beautiful frog so spacious and
slimy and
warm
um where am I what another
[Music]
exit
where ah
here ah ah
ah what
the what the
what the
heck we got it we got
it may I pick any of these items up
thank
[Music]
you I may be good at this game
I think but it it might look funny to
people like coming into the stream and
seeing me struggle so hard with picking
up items which seems like such a trivial
Simple
Thing such a basic
thing it's like it's like my fingers
just don't work I bent down and I tried
to pick it up but my fingers are so
slippery and never one of my struggles
besides my hat struggle but let's not
talk about it now I'm already so
emotional and vulnerable from opening up
about my hat
struggle the finger struggle will be a
story for another
day I feel like I'm spamming this fire
wall more now than my spikes which is
unfortunate because that means I'm
generally getting less minions
it's just easier to spam than what I had
previously on my red
click so I need to find a good balance I
need to go back and forth and back and
forth but I'm already like
pretty content with the skills that I
have right now
I don't really think I don't know what's
the normal way of playing this game but
I don't really think that I want to have
like this full bar filled with skills
cuz I feel like I won't be able to
always use them to its full
potential you know what I mean I want to
focus on just like four skills at
most there's no normal way think it's
too new to have a meta yet okay but
maybe it was different in Poe one or so
for some
reason I don't have to use all of them
yeah but the game the more I level up
the game will offer me new skills and
all that and I just want to stay with
what I'm
familiar stick with what I
know it was literally one button you had
only had one button
skills one or two skills oh really did
it not have a big choice of skills
to uh choose from in the first
place I like how they come up from the
CE come down from the ceiling and you
can see them crawling
there nice
detail he only one you put one build
around it
a one skill was enough to blow up the
whole map
okay interesting sounds
fun that's not a chest that's a barrel
have you never seen a t in your life
before
T back in my days we used to call these
things t with a happy smile in your face
perhaps sometimes you would change your
intonation to T or t
or whatever you want
[Music]
man those were some Happy Days man back
in my days should I finish this whole
not not
not this whole part should I fill it all
up t
t pick up entropy might as well don't
don't have
[Music]
to we'll do
it we'll commit to
it guess I really wasn't done here huh
[Music]
there six sisters one day they'll make a
statue like this of me oh I didn't even
see that there were like bodies on there
oo cool a statue like this of me I don't
know if they will do that I'm not really
from here so I kind of doubt it but I
guess I'm finding my way into to this
place and
culture what do you want what do you
want
eh you had 2 seconds to live and you did
nothing worthwhile with it nothing of
big
meaning and this one has a little bit
more to offer
out of Mana out of
[Music]
Mana none can oppose
me none can oppose
me that hits close to home I already
forgot what I said oh living for 2
seconds and not achieving accomplishing
anything your life is certainly longer
than yeah and you still have time to
achieve things don't you worry about
that and you know even if you don't see
your own achievements living life
continuously is an achievement on its
own and doing simple things like going
to
work also achievement waking up
achievement making food for yourself
achievement taking a bath or taking a
shower achievement all of that
achievement life is depressing as [\h__\h]
doing anything anything
that negates the depression
achievement you did
it recent corpses an easy
distraction am I done
now is this being considered I'm done
with that region that I was in
yeah yeah yeah I thought so I hope
so no no no I mean I you know I I'm
enjoying the game but it's like
late yeah yeah yeah
yeah then we shall
return I'm off the hook for
now thank you for your mercy and your
kindness
how can I advise
you I am not
worthy
what I will tell your
tale she's so nice she'll on my
tail
okay that's it ladies and gentlemen
[Music]
K
Yi damn boss is grinding got off work
and she's still playing I got pretty far
today I
think oh
yeah tomorrow my stream is at like 12
right
I need to pin my schedule to the Twitter
top also I didn't post it yet
on wait no it's not
12 oh it's at uh 2 p.m. oh nice nice
nice
nice good gives me a bit more prep
time I
[Music]
sure actually I want to write a message
to
[Music]
uh
Mina for
okay
so uh you also have a m stream I know I
know we already talked about it
oh it's going to be hand cam Stream So I
need some time to set up
but think it should be
fun pictures from the trip yeah I
mean pictures to show to talk about uh
what what we've been up
[Music]
to it will be fun yes I hope so I hope
you guys won't be bored it will be a
little bit silly I
will I will
um I will be
silly I'm looking forward to it I'm kind
of excited for it now members only
stream tomorrow should be good be there
or be square or watch the archive if you
can't watch it
live wa on demand
baby whose Channel my channel yeah both
streams are on my channel yeah
I offered the girls like hey do you want
to do it like on your channel but
they're like no let's do it on your
channel because you hosted us I'm like
[Music]
okay I guess it makes
sense uh let's go
to my RPG office
[Music]
yes my
frone I love this office so
cool I I almost could Envision this kind
of room even on a ship ship on a big big
ship and I am the
captain work so I'll have to be bod gang
oh for the first stream you mean or for
the second one either way you are
excused thank you for letting me
know little bit unusual streaming time
for the collab obviously but I'm glad to
have a a good re reason to go back to
those streaming times every now and then
for my dear dear
sea or wherever
viewers so that it can be more easily
watchable for those viewers as well I'm
sorry yeah okay uh super chats from the
this stream and last stream or even
further back what where are we what are
we
what are we dealing
with sea gang
yeah what's
up got to treat them sometimes
[Music]
too last was ah the K and the one
before we read right did did we did we
The Path of Exile stream uh chats super
[Music]
chats no I don't think I read
that I don't think I
did so let's do
it unknown D Jacob 47 D wait do you want
music
I
suppose I'll play some music for
[Music]
you
actually I'm in the mood for this one
medieval instrument that I can't think
of the name right
now a loot yes okay
now all right let's try to find loot
music
Loop looping loot music here you go
[Music]
cool I like it
W
Co oh
[Music]
oh whoa give me give me wait I need to
log in didn't log in
No Loot practice
stream a loot in my hands would be a
waste of
talent
and
time what it this one
[Music]
yeah I once tried to learn guitar for
like a
day I think my sister had a
guitar I
think
but yeah I think she at that time she
wasn't living with us so
no easy access or so something like that
oh the hookele yeah that's a thing I
still have
it I really wanted to learn it but man
learning an
instrument rough rough rough
[Music]
rough Kon Danon Midnight Rider Dan El
Dapper cabalo Dan or is it
cabayo or maybe it's
cabayo think so far I might have always
ready your name is
cabalo have
I is it
cabalo oh it's
Cabo oh I'm sorry if if I read it wrong
all the
time Midnight Rider d Nathan cotton
thanks for the pinky hi atten even
though I hadn't used it before I figured
your fous could hold my tea to help deal
with my cold when I went to work oh you
were already sick two days ago sorry it
was very effective not at cut not at
cutting me but it did keep my tea nice
and toasty
right fous bottles are awesome great
merch because always always can have an
extra fos or your first
[Music]
one especially if you're stupid like me
and you let one get moldy and even
though you wash it 5 million times the
smell just doesn't go away anymore but
it's okay I have a new one
now so it's always good to have more
than one
fers you might accidentally
forget that you left tea inside one of
them and remember weeks later and
[Music]
yeah Clorox will usually take care of
that
Clorox I think I even uh tried with like
baking powder or so or baking soda I'm
not sure baking powder I think or baking
soda I don't know but I tried the
magical American
way and it didn't work ding
worked it's okay I'm fine now I won't do
it again but yeah thank you Nathan for
that lowkey advertisement even though we
there's no way of buying the fmus
anymore but I heard that there they
started sending out notifications that
they're starting to send out uh my
birthday
merch I already kind of forgot about
that merch it's been half a year already
since my
birthday wait that's that's just n
that's just n too crazy to think about
but yeah rubber de rubber
duck rubber dick see I wasn't going to
say Rober I was going to say rer deck by
accident yeah surprisingly rer duck and
uh uh uh the the jacket the jacket the
happppy and other stuff what else was in
[Music]
there my glass was in the anniversary
stuff right ah the fan the super cool
fan yeah
was that it was it free
[Music]
items and the Polaroid yeah well the
Polaroid is just the extra wasn't it
[Music]
yeah my God I already signed them ages
ago I tried so hard to like find all of
them which is so many um over the course
of several days during my last stay in
Japan because I didn't want to take them
home to Austria and then go through the
trouble of packing them up and sending
them back to Japan and having to pay
extra shipping for
it so I tried to do it during my stay
mhm did they put your the signing room
no I just did it like in my off time
whenever
like yeah while working in my off
time like I only had I didn't have much
time which made it more difficult but I
did it in the the few off
[Music]
times I brought them like
everywhere I was determined
hell yeah uh scallum
D already answered that one GD D Amilia
La D dhood thanks for the pinky W Divine
voice causes and feable which causes dou
Hood to drop a pink Super Chat oh are
you writing this in like Pokemon style
thanks for streaming today W thank you
why well you don't have to thank me
though it's my job to stream isn't it
thank
you but you're sweet you're not taking
it for granted that's also very nice of
you your knees are your knees okay do
you need a knee
transplant you poor
knes I noticed in Breaking
Bad especially around the end I guess
Walter would like always go out of his
way and put some pillow a blanket on the
ground when he had to kneel
down nice detail I
[Music]
guess he must have had really weak knees
too oh oh like Gus wait I'm not thinking
of Gus am I I guess they both did
it even though he never saw him do that
okay they both did it
huh yeah yeah I remember now the reason
it stood out to me is because I think
yeah uh uh Walter was going to throw up
at the toilet but he took the time to
put down a towel to kneel on it that
stood out to me because I'm like yo if
I'm if I know I have to throw up I would
not have the time to do that it would
just come out in
no
damn that was also that scene that made
all the [\h__\h] go
down after he
vomited but metaphorically it made the
[\h__\h] go down as you recall if you
watched the
[Music]
show m
that
toilet that that room that
[Music]
bathroom
somehow was a very important room for a
couple of
[Music]
scenes he knew he might be at the toilet
for a
while I suppose
[Music]
so but then he wasn't
he had something else to
do yeah thank you D Hood appreciate it
Juan Carlos Rodriguez thank you so much
for the support thank you for listening
to me Raj and spanking hi thank you for
the red chat I went to my local
Christmas Market this week o nice how
was it got rocklet and some hand car
food and Catos oh I walked by the candy
almond Booth but didn't I didn't get any
regret spaghetti well then you got to go
again but that almost sounds like you
got everything that we have too send me
some pictures on Twitter I want to
see how big is it is it like rather
small do you have hot wine mold wine I
think I always called it hot wine
recently but I realized it's mold wine
in proper English
huh but in Japanese I think they call it
hot to
wine so that's
[Music]
confusing mine is
small plan taking kfp to my local one
ah wait in
[Music]
Atlanta are you having like a Christmas
Market off collab with kfp that's so
cute hopefully you guys have those
almonds do you guys actually have a same
kind of almonds over there at Christmas
markets spankenheimer
[Music]
popular Street for the newest oh really
well yeah I mean you can even get them
here in the supermarkets even in
summertime but they're just better when
you get them from the Christmas Market
and sometimes you actually get them
fresh and warm I had that pleasure
once and that was quite lifechanging I
must
say
[Music]
mhm I also have blue Vine all right I
hope you guys have fun there
wow Clear Eye thank you d
I've made the tower and Druid named
Lobster
poobs let's
go wait I forgot SP kiss Thank you time
to go back to undo your regrets death
Rex
than Dan I still didn't midnight rer
Dan uh everything's okay with me I
definitely have many many frustrations
but but I'm
okay
it's it's all right thanks for
asking uh now can get super
[Music]
chats what your eating he check for7 dun
Sky
dun oh you're watching g girl let's
go do Hood thanks for two pinkies
there's a word for lava in every letter
of the English alphabet Oh my God you're
actually all right here we go amazing
beautiful creative demure energetic
funny gorgeous
hardworking ingenious
joyful
kissable lovely
magnificent nice
obliging positive quick witted ravishing
sweet terrific
Unstoppable voloptuous
wonderful XXL
heart
okay yapping and desty
yes M you are so [\h__\h] desty but like
a like a instead of a lemon zest I'm an
orange zest like you can rub off my zest
and then put it in your I don't know ice
cream nah I know I know desty also has
other
[Music]
meanings careful too much say wait it's
like
[Music]
gay spicy or
gay it's slang for gay why are you
gay Carey loves and appreciates you
always thank you for the K thank you too
for that perfect ABC now everybody will
have to learn the ABC at
kfp with the
words our small new chicks will be
raised and taught the English language
with this as a reference it'll make
history D Psy D and D thanks for the
orange carpet
wo orange carpet for the Divine Diva
with the captivating Coro my favorite
K-pop singer the one and the
only t
woohoo damn you are
like absolutely treating
me the way I deserve
it thank
you I think that's another
kiss
D and happy
birthday
what you you
your fifth birthday I celebrated in kfb
I'm turning 30 this year oh [\h__\h] I've
been quite busy this year when I'm
always watching you thank you for being
a sunshine in my
days yeah I
noticed due to the lack of takuma
chickens I've noticed you must have been
busy but I'm glad you're still keeping
up somehow hopefully we'll see some more
chickens in the future otherwise I would
cry happy birthday to Daka The Legend
who is kind
of apparent to you
guys
yes happy
birthday seola ice feret Dan zapu Dan JT
Dan mud arade Dan ran froggy
[Music]
for the
pinky SL a little D for the pinky also
comes on you speak Korean better than me
so cute and say so don't lie it's not
true thank you Lord H Dan froggy wa
Dan wait what's froggy wa doing here HH
you look familiar the the last part of
your name looks very familiar
I can't recall the name right now but I
know that's not your
name Flappy Boy Thanks for the red super
chat spending most of the day finishing
the BB finale and I was really in need
of a pallet cleans pallet cleanser some
non-homicidal slaying by the Holo Queen
of kiata Pop with cuteness as the only
addictive being pedal if you ignore the
lyrics of certain songs on the set list
thank you I also kind of needed a pallet
cleanser
yeah yeah that was a lot like I was
really enjoying it and I was
uh binge watching through it
but v no I think it felt really
satisfying for it to end it it it
definitely was a good time to end it
after five
seasons I'm good I'm good I'm actually
for once I'm not like oh man I wish I
had more probably because I have more in
the form of
balol very nice very
[Music]
nice thank you Flappy boy now you can
also move over to better call all with
me let's go I'm just like at episode
three or
[Music]
something asra
D oh thank you I'm sorry for no red
[Music]
velvet Jim Tracy thanks for the pinky
thanks for the awesome K today you sang
so well and it was really cool to see
you rock out in Korean you were nailing
it really thank you and of course Mirage
is always a banger hell yeah
Mirage you know feels like family of
course cuz it's my
song thank
you thanks for listening and having a
good time even while I was a nervous
frck and even when I was messing up
songs
[Music]
hly D flaming pants than sphe D for the
pinky of wa ofhe to you
too gold boom Dan and Al D and py
D I think I'll leave it there I'm pretty
tired and my throat hurts kind of no
energy left hungry hungry
[Music]
alarm oh in 50
minutes in 15 Minutes Advent calendar
update which you will see for the first
time
[Music]
shut
up I plan on binging the Advent calendar
oh okay that's not how you're supposed
to do it
allll the only way to really correctly
binge an advent calendar is not waiting
until the end it's waiting and not at
all opening all the doors in the very
beginning which you can't
but
IRL if you have like a chocolate Advent
calendar or
so there may have been cases also in my
life where I've done that where I've
opened every door
early within the first week or
[Music]
so but one does not s simply wait until
the end of an advent calendar to open
all the doors at once that is just not
how you do
it that is unnecessary unneeded uncalled
for patience that does not need to be
demonstrated for any
reason the Advent calendar is to give
you daily bits of happiness and
joy over the course of 24 to 25 days
by the way I finally I had an idea for
the finale it's not going to be sock
puppets but it's still going
to involve well basically anybody who
wants to be part of
it and um I have I had a nice idea I had
like a uh a genius
stroke in the middle of the night and I
wrote it down and now I'm planning it it
will be a little bit giddy giddy last
[Music]
minute squeezing it in there hopefully
it will uh work out I think should be
good finger puppets
no no it's a I think it's a good idea I
think it's a cute
idea and it's also another idea that
involves everybody without having to uh
have them all be there at the same time
for like recording a
video like everybody is there but they
can record on their own
time for you know whatever is going to
be done but yeah cuz that's the problem
like when you want to do a finale or so
for something like that you obviously
want like everybody involved but then
it's like well [\h__\h] we have so many time
zones and days where people are busy how
are we going to how are we going
to how
how we going to do this it's impossible
it's so impossible it's like really
impossible any chance for one last
Clementine family collab I I tried but
honestly like it's yeah
rough I don't think so I'm
[Music]
sorry it was it was like looking like it
was going to happen and then and things
just got a little bit too busy behind
the
scenes if you hop on Minecraft right now
you can make it happen I'm not going to
I need to
[Music]
go but I am planning a Hol talk with FAA
FAA who's FAA
FAA FAA
[Music]
yeah which is unfortunate that the next
whole talk is again a graduation all
talk and then probably the next one will
also be
that
oops then it will probably feel
like that's a thing now yeah I know I
know I I I I I wanted to schedule a
normal one too I wanted to but this is
happening so
[Music]
fast
yeah oh well so I'm going to go now in
German we say
in I do the exit interviews now yeah
yeah yeah yeah exit interviews are a
thing now I suppose in whole
life
[Music]
bye-bye tomorrow two streams
bye-bye oh I got to make a thumbnail no
damn it
[Music]
you
that one's funny I don't think I heard
that one before
[Music]
redirect
you he you
[Music]