a
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
a
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
Kiki
hello K KY key
welcome did you hear the water is some
more water I love water
[Music]
yeah uh welcome to the stream we are
going to play a game surprise we're
going to play a game what oh my god um
yeah big
surprise where the [\h__\h] is my hell fresh
[Laughter]
order I feel like maybe I'll be hungry
tonight did you just wake up no no no
what do I sound tired I'm not tired you
starving yet to that is MERS only
content
don't I felt a little bit hungry after
my breakfast but it's okay and ah [\h__\h] I
closed the app by
accident
um uh I I I would say I only start
started uh
my diet uh
like 8 80 80% today because I will admit
I have
eaten too
many too many chocolate
pinkies there we
go there we go uh but uh it's okay it's
okay but I also I did more um Garden
workout yeah I had
uh ooh my arms are feeling it really
really
strongly so I burned the calories I
think before I built them but that's
okay right if I burn the calories before
I took them in it's fine right it works
right go away
don't be so strict it's
okay the problem is the sugar what what
what can I burn the sugar
then okay the game today I don't know
what to expect uh I I know it's the
current fotm Flame of the month
game uh I think it's a bit scary could
that
be do I need to be
concerned
[Music]
uh H do I do you want it in full screen
guys for the
atmosphere I can do full screen for
you if you want
and I'm going to going
to color myself surprised no I'm going
to color myself in the color of my
screen yes please yeah yeah yeah I think
I think yeah for the atmosphere it would
be
nice then I don't know is there do you
guys know where this the chat could go
where there's a good spot for you we'll
find out
wait I'm starting the game right
[Music]
now just erase us we deserve it what did
you do to deserve
it game why did you start on the right
screen ah go over
here wait I'm scared I'm scared I'm
scared it's loud this
nah uh
options [\h__\h] why is it what the
[\h__\h] is this
window no it's
like
huh let me try the window it really
quickly
[Music]
uh and show it to
you okay now I like the music now it's
not scary right now
now it's got to chill how do
I huh what is
[Music]
this how do I how do I get to
the Ah Ah that's okay that's the
difference between full screen and
ah funny okay okay I got it all right
oopsie
that's what that means they're so
creative oh I
didn't how do
ah well I'm figuring it out you were
also confused when you saw the menu it's
interesting okay uh what's color blind
mode okay I see no change in
this uh here but that's
okay
okay uh bu shot roulette not to be
confused with back shot
roulette uh how do I start
oh uh I'm scared kind
of let's go wait should I make myself
smaller maybe a littleit smaller
okay oh wait is the game going to crash
oh
no I'm
[Music]
afraid I'm scar no wait I I pressed by
accident scar scared why am I scared why
am I scared this is not scary it's not
scary but can I oh I can't move with W
SD I
click oh I
click
okay oh we're already here oh hello what
a friendly face of okay I guess I
shouldn't is there GNA be a lot of text
sign the waiver General release
of la la la laot labot labot labot
laot
oh I I didn't really oh wait I can't
read it
[Music]
liability yeah from afar it didn't look
like there were so many letters I I know
the Y was kind of like gone H uh uh uh
key so if you have
more letters in your name than 1 2 3 4
five six then you're
[\h__\h] okay what am I getting into
though one two and death dealer uh two
two lives one life round two blank
I insert the shelves in an unknown order
Aha aha okay I see I see what's going on
oh isn't this like a real game that like
real gangsters do maybe maybe not
gangsters but like Mafia I don't know it
is Russian Roulette kind of right I
don't know but do you play it like this
I I usually imagine
someone someone stuck to a big roulette
board on the wall like a
person but that maybe I just have that
from Rihanna I
[Laughter]
think that's the twist usually with have
a
revolver the real one use revolver oh
this is a shotgun
ahuh shooting yourself with a blank
skips the Dealer's
turn skips aha well how do I
know do I have any way of knowing or is
it really like
you think I need a heart rate monitor
for this that's a little bit late to
notice now did just know I will
learn One Life two blanks R his luck
that's the fun part
yay I'm am I am I
shaking what oh I did
it okay all I just I just pressed me
because I didn't know what else to press
but I guess he was also an option Al so
it skips his turn wait was that good or
bad
then if I would have shot myself that
would have been bad but skipping his
turn is good I guess but uh I I I would
have liked him to shoot
himself you think it's good it's 50/50
now uh-huh oh oh oh oh yeah now it's
50/50 uh [\h__\h] e but eh that it that's
the whole
game this is the flavor of the month
game yeah I'm going to
die well thank you oh [\h__\h] there's more
than that
okay don't why would be like what the
[\h__\h] okay oh well this is the same gun
then obviously it's a blank yeah you
don't have to show me that thank
you free life round two
blanks yeah same as before right oh no
no so oh five there's five in there and
there's threee oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] that's
what you
mean
uh again me y I'm going to die
[Music]
Y what I'm
unlucky oh no apparently I am lucky that
it left me with a charge get up K the
night is
young
okay
okay can I look around here do I can I
click anything is there like a Easter
egg no
okay oh you get shot point blank with a
shotgun that all it takes to revive is a
the
fibrillator
Apparently I mean
maybe it was a water pistol after all
but it only turned black because I
closed my eyes because I was so
scared oh okay so it's just a complete
restart as if it didn't happen before
huh One Life round two blanks okay you
you start no I start
right okay okay okay okay I know I can
shoot him too I guess right
but okay I'll do last time I mean it has
nothing to do with Dad but I know I
shoot
you no
[\h__\h] H but it's your turn right don't
shoot
oh of course you would shoot me because
you know that the last one
is man
[Music]
wow wow wow that is uh I don't know if
that's fair
Mister okay okay
okay doing great so far I sense some
sarcasm could it
be hi dealer
die yeah oh I feel like he just ducked
did he just
dodge it's kind of cute his face is kind
of cute oh oh
[Music]
oh I did it
though
okay I mean I died really fast but he
also died really fast I
win let's
go let's make this a little more
interesting uh okay two items each more
items before every load what kind of
items what how does that what does that
do for
me same
same
kinky why do I get the same is it lucky
is it
lucky four lives one life round one
blank ah so we continue with what was
left over oh oh oh oh oh oh [\h__\h] uh ah
okay dealer skips the next turn but I
have to like use the item before I do my
turn cough him I win
really oh because I can just choose to
shoot him even if it's a blank I can
just use up those oh brainiacs
oh it was it I shot him while he was
handcuffed cruel cruel
me okay uh now it's a blank or is it I
don't know but we'll just shoot
him yeah it's a
blank I still aimed at you okay more
more more what is this classica filter
it's a uh
cigarettes okay
and
uh go go
God why was that there oh am you forgot
something when you played this last
night you forgot something it
seems what why was that why was why was
okay what how much what did he say what
did he say how many what did he say it
happened so
fast takes the edge off regain one
charge Ah One Life ooh two two half half
check the current round and
[Music]
oh
w Wait I have this is good stuff he also
has the same things though I feel like
he's cheating anyway so why would he
have to look should I look I'll take a
look oh I break it wait what what what
does that mean what does that mean I
think it's if it's red it's uh it was a
round that does
shoot red is life which means he will
not live right the irony
ha should I put this on him anyway
I I'll cff him
yeah he kind of put it on himself so
okay I shoot
you and you skip the next turn so I go
again now I don't know what it is but I
guess I'll just go for
it he so cute he's so
cute okay yeah I'll go
ahead M I have a feeling it's a blank
though but maybe we're lucky
yeah
okay oh now has only blanks left what's
you going to do about that huh what you
going to do you handcuffing me but it's
blanks and you know that you why you
looking at it it's only blanks right
very interesting you know it though
what's that cigarettes ah he's getting a
life back right [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] should
have shot his
cigarettes but my turn is next right
ha but then he he gets another turn
which is another blank
great yeah he wasted his
items he actually could have totally
known without looking even I would have
known so kind of kind of silly kind of
silly
Dilly oh I don't know what this one is
yet we'll find
out oh that's also new okay
three rounds this okay two
blanks Handa it's what Handa it's just a
like a cutter thingy shotgun deals two
damage ooh that would be great in
combination with the magnifying glass if
I know that it's a uh a live bullet in
it and he only has two lives
left I should risk it maybe rxs the
shotgun ejects current
[Music]
oh well I'm still full HP
so I'm I I
will well the chances of it being a life
bullet are pretty high
so I'll go for
it it' racket is that what I just
did here we go come on come on come on
come on come on come on come on come on
come on come on come on come on Yoo
yay I'm the Russian Roulette
Master yay k
wi nice this game is not scary I'm happy
woohoo long last we arrive at the final
showdown no more defibrillators no more
blood transfusions now me and you we're
dancing on the edge of life and death
oh what's
[Music]
this
oh
what no you reset my items but it's
still gay I'll get some good ones
again this game is pretty short right so
if I win this now then game is over but
we can play a few times again
oh God
item oh oh okay if we lose a life we can
heal back nice oh wait another item
oh oh another one oh oh
okay
[Music]
okay uh one one life no okay I start
right
M oh it's blank
but if it's blank it doesn't even matter
who I shoot though
right oh damn it it being blank sucks
but we'll just have to wait for the next
turn it
does
self oh self skips his turn and I get
another one I forgot about
that
okay uh I'll check again although wait
now it has to be wasn't there oh no okay
ah [\h__\h] wait okay that's fine that's
fine I shoot myself again then I get
another turn and I shoot
him okay go go go
okay and then I I use
this double damage
yeah I play Russian rette the hard way
[\h__\h] you die
[Music]
now minus two
lives why are some of the lives looking
like
funky he extended it I don't know what
that
does oh no he just uh put the thing back
on that I cut off or what oh
oh
oh oh what does that do
again oh 1 2 3 four four four four but
is he putting them in that order
obviously no right why why are they
aligned like that what kind of luck you
think I'm lucky oh we started off kind
of weird racks the shotgun ejects the
CERN shell ah okay
a let's see oh it's Al live one I don't
have anything to double
it so I'm just going to
handcuff
him shoot him and look at it
again he's getting so [\h__\h] man he's
he's he must feeling like what the [\h__\h]
I normally don't lose like
this this
[\h__\h] okay I can't cuff him but it's
okay so what does this mean what do the
last two lives
mean are you ready no ready for
what
what what is that oh he just continues
playing what's this mean he can't heal
ah awesome I was hoping for that I was
thinking maybe that's what that means oh
the drinking does one again ah he ejects
it he ejected two blanks though right oh
and
now are you
dumb is he
dumb what is she so dumb
he already felt like he can't win this
anymore I think I mean that is true even
if he gave me a shot I would have won
next
round that so
funny oh my God that was really fast K
wins by doing absolutely nothing I mean
yeah pretty much oh I have to open it
like this that's cute oh [\h__\h] let's
go that was fun
that was
[Music]
easy that's
it she 70k beat the game I got an
achievement get shots fir at 13 shots
fir Shel rejected 21 doors kicked for
cigarettes smoked zero beer drank zero
hahaa oh I am so straight edge I won in
the most straight edge way possible
[Music]
straight edge I didn't even try say so
rette straight edge Russian Roulette
this is how you do
it press any button again let's go I
guess I mean that was too fast so we're
going to do it again double or nothing
unlocked oh
oh okay double nothing does that mean
that they're always hitting twice or
what
can I choose the
mode oh is this like endless
mode oh what happened to the computer on
the left side ah I can choose the mode
here
[Music]
crony take take a take meds take
pills oh it's my
stats I don't know how this works
oh the leader
board oh oh what are these
numbers H what people what is what is
that number
people
[\h__\h] oh I don't know how this
what
okay oh okay
pills consum pills May impair your
ability to
drive why would I do
this why would I do
this people
sweaty that's the double or nothing game
mode
okay chasing losses consume the double
or
nothing the guy is
gone why
is he the next dealer no it's you again
why is it you again you should be
dead okay I'll sign
it do I have to type it
again
[Music]
where's I think the guy
was
what didn't exist the guy was God didn't
look much like
God wait what does double or nothing
actually
mean in this
case free rounds free free
50/50 I'm having fun this is fun I I
wouldn't mind playing this like with
real Mafia IRL in the real parlor like
this I'm so ready this is preparing me
for real
life after three rounds if you win you
can play against score ah until I die so
there's just
uh okay no particular end unless I die
but I can't kill him either
or okay wait
um so I can't look inside uh but I'll
shoot him hoping for the
best okay
damn it maybe this time I it won't be so
easy dealer Never Dies you can cash out
after the free ones oh so the money is
uh the the numbers is the
money come on come on come on come on
come on come on
yay
okay all right what you going to do what
is that what is that what is that what
oh he Ste heals my item with that ah oh
he ejected
wait oh ah that was a blank yeah good
job dude oh that's that might be
yum that's okay that's okay careful now
for once you did something
interesting for once but the last one is
a blank
right cuz we already had free
what are the why are two I think the
last one is a blank I don't there were
threee originally in there I don't know
why there's only two here maybe because
one hit his face right and two were
ejected I don't know I don't
remember no wait two one hit him one hit
me why is there
what
[Music]
whatever don't regard the shells on the
table okay okay oh yeah one is gone now
ah it's just like the most recent one or
so cuz now it got like
replaced okay ah is this the stealing
item thingy prescription only medicine
Keep Out Of Reach of
children okay what kind of what are we
talking oh more a phone a joker or what
phone Joker H half half only
two swaps to pull clity of the current
shell in the
chamber which just means yeah if it's a
blank it becomes an A Life
One a mysterious voice gives you Insight
from the future oh which also just
probably tells me what the next one is
or the next next I don't
know 50% chance to regain two charges if
not lose one
charge oh [\h__\h] oh we don't want to do
that
uh I want one of either either one of
this will teach will tell me what it is
no wait no wait I should call I should
use the phone if it's a blank one then
I'll switch
it right second shell blank ah second
shell I wanted to know the first
[Music]
shell a
yeah so but that means the first
one the chances of the first one being a
blank one are relatively High wait no he
said no low because the second one is a
blank did he say the second one is a
blank right so
[Music]
yeah yeah the the first
one yeah we
shall we shall try
come on come on no [\h__\h] do something
stupid as you always do please ah no he
checks it out no I'm dead I'm
dead oh I'm
dead oh is he inverting
it oh yeah the next one is blank okay
he's inverting it he's checking out the
next one
which is useless okay I'm dead
huh that's okay that was
fun one more one
more one more one more one more one more
I wouldn't say that was necessarily
anything we did wrong we just
uh it just is what it
is oh you think he's a lot smarter in
this round oh okay he didn't really have
much chances to be smart by the time he
was smart it was already over for me
anyway but I believe
[Music]
you yeah I ran
unlucky also the item the the magnifying
glass would have been better because I
didn't want to know the second round I
wanted to know the current one there we
go magnifying glass and this is uh what
was that again the cut off thingy oh
four items sheesh sheesh this is good
this is good
he
knows okay two live ones free
blank steal an item and use it
immediately oh N I see he has cigarettes
a phone the beer and the magnifying
glass but I don't feel like we need to
do that
now steal the glass oh just to take it
oh yeah I mean actually
yeah just so he doesn't have it
anymore he doesn't get to
see and I wanted to use one anyway
oh
a
k
nice good start very good
start uh the cigarette oh he's getting
his life back
okay oh he's checking out
but do I get to know as well no
right oh that's ejecting right okay the
oh I duck duck oh oh he chooses himself
ah he maybe knew the second
one yeah uh he yeah he knew the second
one he probably knew careful now what a
coincidence huh that he can inject the
first one cuz he has the item and the
one that he is being told is the second
one what a coincidence game
wait so there's no only blanks inside I
think right only blanks so hey I didn't
get to use all my items at
all
jeez ah
okay
phone more mag
the amount of magnifying glasses man all
right all the handcuffs are good uh four
four
four four
four uh I I was I able to use two items
I think yeah right yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah oh we can also
o this might be
good oh
[Music]
well
yeah
bye-bye no I don't think there was a
need to cut him
right let's go let's go let's go let's
go let's go k wins K wins K wins again
again
oo but we continue
okay fresh
table let's set the table with
cigarettes uh that thing whatever that
was handcuffs nice okay handcuffs are
always
good three four
M oh he has a magnifying glass what's
this sealing item using
okay I'll handcuff him and shoot
him oh
wait I I should steal the magnifying
glass just in case maybe I can use it
right away
actually might use it actually right
away
right yeah cuz that's what it does all
right oh
here we go although the
handcuffing oh yeah now handing was good
all right I don't know what it is but
let's see I think we have a high chance
no [\h__\h] damn it okay okay okay okay okay
my
smokes wait even if I only have two
lives
ah H but he okay even if I couldn't heal
High I I thought like I can't heal
higher than to
anyway
oh oh oh uh
risky
oh what why why does he do
that
what what what's with it you guys said
he's smart
enough oh
uh I win
again uh yeah okay yeah I see I couldn't
heal higher but also would have liked to
prevent him from healing himself n hold
hold on hold I'll remember
that nice I win
again okay phone
medicine uh cigarettes and that f
[Music]
oh oh wow so oh so
much to free lives oh only three bullets
and one is
live that's so short give me
more MOSI MOSI tell me the first round
third round blank
no Ah that's
okay we're not going that far
oh
wait he has he has nothing to
steal again one
charge no okay I I'll
shoot I get two shots one of them yeah
the next one is the next one is
real is
real Kow
nice hey and he gets the next turn but
he's blank buddy he's
blank oh he's recharging a damn
it yeah
okay yeah just use the blank one at
least he understands does or does he he
might not understand really but okay a
beer a phone uh that thing I keep on
forgetting is that the oh wait what's
that free free fre fre
free steal item ooh magnifying
glass I would
say usually cuz I don't have it
so probably should go for
it let's go
hey it's it's a blankie then I swap
it right what so wait that's what it
means right swap the polarity of the
current shell just means the blank will
turn into the other one
okay does he have a Steely thingy these
are are these that's the Steely thingies
right do I want to do I want to use more
let's first of all
invert and then
should I should I
ah who says he'll Ste that ah man I
don't know use the use the phone yeah
just in case so this one's this one we
have three free this one turned one of
the threee blank ones into a live one so
it's for
free we'll find out another one mhi mhi
the sixth one is a live round and this
is the first one I don't know if you get
to the sixth one
ah maybe I should have ejected it
first then stole his magnifying glass
and checked the second one and then
possibly change the polarity because at
least then we're like further I don't
know would that have been
smarter okay I'll use
it he has no cigarettes right so okay I
think ready need to
go all
right the sixth one is alive he said
right sixth one is
alive
oh so
there's
dude that
one regains his life okay he calls the
future
uh oh [\h__\h] wait oh my God there's so
much happening he stole my beer
rude oh he ejected the blank one wait he
changes the polarity of the I should
have
counted uh I don't know not a
h but then now is this the six one now
then it's ah yeah cuz he changed the
polarity of the blank one so now the
there probably only one yeah
okay okay
okay
ha
[Music]
interesting oh then it wasn't bad that
the the one that the phone told us is
the last one actually that was
good cuz all of the other ones I didn't
get a chance to use at all ooh
magnifying glass O Okay that was the
two free two
free that was the stealing
okay does he have it he has it
too what if I steal the stealing item
and then it uses it immediately and then
I steal the magnifying glass can I do
that wait I can steal his stealy thingy
right and then it uses to so I can steal
right oh no you can't steal the steel
uh should I steal his medicine
instead the medison or the
glass see this class they yeah maybe
[Music]
maybe that would be
funny is
quank so I shoot
myself and then that skips his turn
that's why I get another turn
right was it free
to now it's free 1 was it free
2 change polarity I guess I could have
changed polarity but yeah now glass I
know I know was it I was was it to now
it's 2 two okay ah it's blank again I
Chang okay okay
okay
and uh wait did I start with 2 Hp I
don't remember what game we are in
anymore I can heal
right we started with free I think yeah
okay all right the
Mets whatever Mets the Mets are whatever
let's
go oh you're down to one life what you
going to do if you try to heal yourself
with the meds
oh oh
yeah then that's not going to go so well
for you uh there's one more in there
only one right I guess it's a a life
one oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] buddy you're not
very lucky are you
for a
god
y oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah double or
nothing
M yes
yes
yes yes yes
yes we can't lose guys we have to win
this
okay this is relatively oh this is good
I mean yeah we get
everything
huh I think I should check first free
free or steel wait maybe do I have a
steel no I don't have a
steel okay then we
check oh nice can I double it with
anything
no but I might want to
call and handcuff
him
handcuff I'll call
mush Mushi F life round
oo that's that will be my turn
right I think that's my turn the third
one is my turn
then cuz this is the first round
second round he skips oh no no I get the
second
round yeah I get the second round never
mind and now I don't
know but the it was free
free there's no way that it's first
round second and third round live right
I
mean it's yeah should we invert and
shoot
it we might be inverting aive to a blank
one
but yeah it could I don't believe it ah
[\h__\h] we
did we did it was free life ones in a
row
[Music]
what oh but then there's now there's
only black ones left he ejected the live
one he ejected the live one there's only
planks left I
win well that's fine
then that's fine he doesn't
know oh he
inverted all right oh [\h__\h] uh ah please
please have
mercy ah oh no oh no oh no oh oh oh
blankie Oh blank oh okay okay
okay last is this last I
think oh but maybe I can invert it
no ah why is it show oh is is this a
new one one
one
[Music]
one you want me to Rack
it ah just in case so you mean that
because even if the current one is a
live one it's better than the current
one
being I think I I seen I think I
understand it's like the safe
is
okay it's the
safest okay new round please go go go go
Please Don't Steal please don't steal my
weapon though please
don't wait does he get the turn now no
right I get it right oh w wow wow wow
wow wow wow
okay free free can I steal can I steal I
can steal right the this thing is a
stealing thingy
yeah I can steal two things I can steal
his handcuffs and his magnifying glass
or maybe both magnifying glasses I don't
know and then I can rack it oh it's
double we're going to double
it
[Applause]
Yoo yay
he's dead he's dead he's so
dead again again again again a gambling
is addicting isn't
it here we go again second
round bring it on cigarettes
uh the inverter
inverter uh meds
[\h__\h] four
four ooh me not likey me not
likey
perhaps I'll just shoot
it's a long round
[Music]
yeah got to waste the smoke cuz he
steals it m sad really what if he steals
something else I guess that maybe
they're programed to automatically go
for the heal items if there's a heal
item oh wait maybe I should have done
the meds and then
the ah it's okay I don't think he'll
steal a meds the meds are not so good
I think I think it'll be a live
one I
believe is just my my feeling you know
my gut feeling I have feeling in my gut
and then he heals
a of course he does oh he drinks the
beer which uh oh o he ejected the life
one so it's now four and two oh oh now
it's four and one there's four blanks
and one life one left right ooh
buddy four blanks and one live one I
guess I'll invert it I hope we're not
getting the most uh
unlikely outcome
again please
[Music]
yeah that's how it's supposed to be free
one three blanks one
life what's he going to do
ooh okay chances for that we're High two
blanks one
life is he going for me no he's going oh
why is he so
dumb why is he so risky he really loves
Russian Roulette doesn't he I mean if
you can't die then I guess that's fun
maybe he has some Phoenix
jeans let's
go let's go let's
go last
round okay m m a little bit of
everything
ah free free does he have a magnifying
glass no good then I want to steal his
double damage thingy
[Music]
yeah let's go let's
go at least that's what I would
[Music]
steal see the
phone he has no heal item either though
so he can't heal that back up he can
steal my cigarettes though so I'll use
my
cigarettes woo
I think that's all I'll
do so
nice what need to be quick when stealing
what do you
mean what what what what what what do
you mean what do you mean what was I did
I what was I not quick enough or are you
just telling
me I stole it though right
[Music]
5 Seconds
really did I was I
fine I almost ran out of time
okay oh I didn't know that was a timer
uh how many are
left one life two black
thanks
well a two life one blank oh
[Music]
sheesh wait I got that switch to some
shades
oh I got the dble Do Double Do
[Music]
should I cash
out I I'll I'll go one more
time we'll be
fine one more time just because that'll
be a lot of good money oh we get to keep
the didn't realize we got to keep oh ooh
ooh okay
ooh free
free free free free free free free free
with
f okay uh we have the double damage we
have no magnifying glass but we can
call maybe it tells me the first one if
I'm
lucky n the fifth one is a life round
the fifth out of six is
live ah well I'll just make him skip the
round at least I'll
shoot
beer
oh well I mean what if it's a life one
though does the phone ever tell first
one it does never it doesn't
oh okay yeah I know it Downs the odds
but also H so it was free free right and
the fifth is a life one I feel like this
is a life one too
though oh good
[Music]
good now it's free two free lives to
blank
drink
again yeah I can drink again and then if
it's if it ejects a live one I might
invert ooh okay so now it's 2
two I know the fifth one is we we're at
the third one now I know the fifth one
is live
[Music]
I can try
inverting because what there's there's
threee left I know that the chances of
this one is
5 is it wait no is it wait
what is it 50/50 right now it's 50/50
yeah let's
invert he skips the round
anyway okay uh this is the third round
right oh my God I have to fake so
hard you want me to saw a [\h__\h] it's too
late I
think I can saw the next one [\h__\h] okay
that it's good I didn't saw it's good he
skips it is this the fourth one but then
this is the live one right then the
fourth and the fifth one is alive and
the last one is a blank or so or are we
at the fifth now I don't I lost track is
is this the fourth okay then I think
this one is
live you think this is a blank oh why
you think so only oh only the fifth one
is live now ah [\h__\h] then I shoot
myself the next is the
fifth I saw it
off and then we good
[Music]
shees I'm trying my best to keep track
and I think mostly it's I'm I'm I'm I'm
doing it but a little bit of help from
the chat is is fine
right oh
nice it's fun what you going to do what
you going to do going to handcuff me
right oh he has so many items he can
smoke the
cigarettes oh don't be so aggressive
[Music]
buddy yeah yeah yeah smoke all you want
it will kill you in the
[Music]
end he's uh what was that again healing
oh you want to use that please take his
life please please
please ah it's a 50% chance of it takes
a life right or two
even good morning doie doie doie doie
doie he didn't even use the
handcuffs he didn't use the
handcuffs oh he inverted the blank not
good for him wait where what where are
we right now okay new one yeah I was
wondering two
two uh is that an
Inver or I could also just steal the or
I can just shoot
myself is that is that an
Aver still
still his
cuffs what if it's a blank one I can
just shoot myself wait wait it's 2 two
22 oh now brain is
so you don't
know
but maybe I should get the
phone steal cuffs or he kills
you okay so how about I I I steal the
Cuffs but I shoot myself cuz I know it's
a
blank so next round I cuff him then I
shoot him might be a blank might be a
not
blank right that's the right thing to
do ah wait ah [\h__\h]
I
forgot because I us it right away I
forgot damn
it ah damn
it
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] doesn't matter yeah well now
it matters wait does he hit still have
the cuffs
on ah this skip doesn't use the Cuffs
okay good good
good oh good good good good good yeah he
still has it I was a blanky
no hey that's good because now I know
this is not a
blankie but the other one is also not a
blankie so he can definitely shot shoot
me but he doesn't have double
damage
yeah he doesn't have double damage so
it's good it's okay we live he gets the
last
one yeah of course you shoot me that's
the only logical thing to
do yeah careful now okay careful careful
be careful be careful be careful no k no
more shoot yourself
[Music]
okay okay we need a
saw wait did he already show me the
bullets
[\h__\h] ah there we go uh four four sheesh
it's a long round
[Music]
ah okay I can see the current one I can
Ste
uh he does he has cigarettes I can I can
use the cigarettes
right he has a double too but I can
steal cigarettes and the double well
maybe just the double then I can wait
okay what do we what do we do first we
look maybe we look first or I should I
steal his looky lookie no I just use
mine should I use mine I'll just use
mine okay okay I steal double and we
win I steal the double
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
y
nice okay that's that's
it that's it
gg gg to me not to him
though was not a GG for him
[Music]
yay this game is so fun I like
it I like it it was fun I love gambu
gambu
D last round right o oh only two items
but they're they're
fine the cups are good to
to the cops are good he doesn't have
cups he doesn't have healing he only has
a steel and a phone let me call too mhi
MOSI it's wait was it 2 two two two for
Shell life
H but well I don't have much choice
so so the fourth is the last
one come
on
ah
oo now if this one's also
blank then I'm going to die though
possib no not necessarily because he
doesn't have uh
handcuffs he could only do one
damage so okay let's
see a oh [\h__\h]
okay oh he gets one shot then it's my
turn and I get a
shot yummy yummy
yummy kful
no more self shooting please
careful one shot
uh yeah then it's a new new
new is life of course it is thank you
for the rest of the
chat
[Music]
okay new items
please thank
you
phone Ms handcuff
beer oh God this is a long one beer
beer o two
two o so many items and only two two
okay
uh I can't
steal uh I can okay I will handcuff
him and I'll call of course maybe it
tells me the second one that be
nice
[Music]
second so we better hope that this one's
live or ah we shoot and then we second
turn if it's if the first one was blank
then we eject the next one right oh you
want to double be oh I guess that works
too
yeah cuz then we can eject the blank one
but there must even if the first one is
not a blank one there must still be at
least one oh but what if it's yeah okay
that works
beer oh it was a life
one
uh what's is the order important beer
self beer what's self a I shoot
myself oh yeah cuz it's blank skips his
turn turn
PE no I just handcuff him I don't drink
the beer again who said beer again who
said that somebody said beer self beer
what if this one is the life
one
okay come on life
yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh wait that was the last round right I
get I get was it it was it the first one
the first was it the first no it was the
first one maybe I don't oh oh now we're
in the last one okay I lose track
because it all feels just like one giant
game okay we have to win we have to win
we have to win
guys okay I can heal uh that's good two
two m
[Music]
I don't
know second
blank well he doesn't know
that should
I I would
shoot do I have to
smoke cuz he's going to steal
it but I will
shoot and then hopefully he tries to
shoot me with the blank
one please please be live please please
please now it's uh 21 and we know where
one of the twos is
oh maybe he'll find out where the life
one is
oh maybe oh he's handcuffing me is he
going to ah [\h__\h] wait yeah it's okay
it's okay as long as he doesn't have
double damage it's okay that was yeah he
knew ah I told him the the yeah the
third one oh the yeah the third [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
wait so the last one is a blank
H he gets a turn ah yeah that's okay
wait does he get the next turn cuz now
it gets reset
right okay okay but then if his last
turn was a self shoot does he get the
next turn he doesn't okay it's a reset
okay oo I don't need the double damage
one one one one wait I call it will tell
me not the current but the second one I
win I win I win I win I win I win I win
I win alive I skipped
oh what it would be so funny if by
accident I did the wrong
thing oh my God okay I
wi
I'm we get Triple
baby oh
[Music]
oh let's
go
no no this one I'm I'm taking
home bab me a
triple yeah catching out it's like
Co nice
money love opening
that nice cash out
[Music]
ni go next go next go
next 140k I earned
140k what I got an achievement or is my
total my is my to no I earned uh almost
69k uh but in total I have 140k now
what cuz I got an achievement for it
oh almost so
close
man
uh what so wa what's my total score
now is it over
140k can I see my score
[Music]
here got show me that every time uh ah
total
cash
34k people has over a
million
[\h__\h] over a
million oh wait no mistake can I go
back can I go
back I need to do
[Music]
endless why why did it make it so
complicated just let me go backwards
back to the door where I came out of
Double Stack Up Qui yeah maybe maybe now
that we have a good chunk of money that
is safe maybe this time I won't stop at
triple maybe I'll just go to maybe five
times should I try to go five
[Music]
times let's go for five
times addict it's fine but I feel like
eventually my brain would like be
overloaded with having to keep track of
everything oh it's okay it's it's not
too
[Music]
bad why do you let me why do you make me
put my name there every time you should
remember by now I've taken so much money
from
[Music]
you
okayo two fre
green I'll steal the
beer I had a
[Music]
feeling uh what is this
I'll invert this one should be this one
I believe is
blank I
believe it's blank right tell me tell me
it
is
[Music]
okay all righty what what you going to
do I'm not hold
up what are you going to do
now me are you
sure why would you do that why would you
do that that's not so much
fun wait
so there's no more life rounds left
right just one
blank oh it better be well thank god
it's the first round even if we messed
up it's uh
whatever
okay
oh ooh ooh
ooh and for the first time almost free
four is it free four my cigarettes
finally make sense
[Music]
I don't even have to use the
double ooh I now okay wait we Skip and
then we look
again
easy look again should be
hopefully then I skip again now I can't
look anymore but chances are good for
me so it it better be it why am I even
doing that I don't need to do that but
nah
go
no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
oh he
ejected alive one he's wait is there is
there only oh I'm probably
[Music]
dead it could be blank though right or
maybe he knows because he called so it's
probably not
blank wow okay first
death that's okay I I really prefer that
happening right in the beginning where
we have accumulated no money that's
okay we had to experience that at least
one
time we did our
best if only I'd have known what the
third one
was do I really need to do this each
time can I type in normally no
[\h__\h] this this important what if I write
Wawa is this for the leaderboard or will
it just always be my steam
name oh steam
name four
four
44 or is it was that
44 or is it free free 44
I
mean I'll handcuff
him I don't know if I want the beer
because I feel like the first one will
be
live
what come on then the second one is Live
come on come on
now come on what happened with my
women's
intuition
uh well [\h__\h] you
sir I have cigarettes
so I'm
fine there's still plenty plenty of live
ones in
there go
oh what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] it's okay
we have plenty of lives
so oh this is such a stupid round right
now there we
[Music]
go not even counting anymore it's just
whatever oh
H now it's empty right is it empty yeah
okay okay well let uh just like the
beginning of another game we have same
amount of lives three lives is quite
comfortable I can heal back up actually
oh two and one ooh
spicy I like
that is it the first one or no it's the
first one
oh oh he knows what's coming if I saw
off the the tip he knows what's going to
happen he knows his
Destiny oh [\h__\h] he's like oh [\h__\h] his
face says it all and my actions say it
all what's she going to do with the
blankies huh not much you can
do there twoo lanks in there oh oh right
he can invert them oh oh oh oh yeah well
oops hey hey hey hey hey hey sir excuse
me that's a bit aggressive isn't
it oh nice nice uh Revival though of
your uh of your
chances you're making the odds Fair
again
okay we're we're back to two lives now
for both of us
wait is it it's blank
right Mama
Mia Mama Mia
M it's even again oh okay
[Music]
okay uh two free I
this is so much fun for me right now but
now I'm wondering if this is fun for you
guys is it just fun for the one who
plays uh let's see I have the changy
thingy okay then we'll check it
out very fun okay
blank so I invert and I
call was it free too or two free
he's fing he's
fun second Channel live so the one after
mine oh then I should actually have not
inverted maybe I don't know cuz he gets
the next one but we don't know what he
do what he will do with it free life to
blank now you mean after I inverted
it okay uh oh well he doesn't have a
double he doesn't have a heal really not
a proper one he doesn't have a
magnifying glass so he can't know the
current
one this one's live now now the next
one's live but he doesn't
know if he use his phone no he can't
know because that he only knows the ones
from the
future not the current one which is now
which is live oh he ejected the life
one oh but maybe oh he knows this one's
a blank and he changes it okay that's
fine that's
okay I'll take
that he wanted to make
sure uh oh but okay
now there is one left one life one left
and one yeah one one right
o I have no way of knowing but I have
more lives than
him
[Music]
so my luck is getting worse now after
our first
wins it's just my luck though not my
skill damn it dude damn it we're all
again we're he just wants to make it
even all this time he wants to go down
with me step by step but let me tell you
buddy life ain't that romantic we're not
going down together free free
okay okay I don't know I don't I can
steal and I don't know so I should
handcuff him and
shoot right cuff and
pray and then we get two chances come on
one of those has got to be Live come
on yeah finally end his
misery took you long
enough what a round what a
game what about
time are we in the second round now set
right
uhhuh okay oh just two
bullets I'll steal the magnifying
glass a little Pokey
[Music]
thingy
ah no problem
wait does he have a double no he doesn't
I can this is okay right there's nothing
better I can do
right doesn't have handcuffs either to
steal nothing good to steal I mean yeah
cuz then every resets wait are we
keeping the items should I steal
something yeah just steal the smokes
because I think he keeps the items right
so does he get confus arino
[Music]
you keep him oh then it's good that I
steal
him
okay next gun please next ammo
please next items also oh
oh
okay free
to damn
[Music]
I may be
a should I eject there's threee blanks
and two live
ones yeah I don't
know
okay all right well we have so much
healing uh
so we got to do it we got to go for it
oh
man
Ohi
uh
ah ah he's on a roll ah he's on a
[Music]
roll 2 1 now it's not
over I'm alive
okay it's
okay
oh it's okay I'm still
alive careful careful kful
now kful
now so is there only a blank left in
there I can double smoke oh my God I'm
becoming a chain smoker no
[Music]
but at least then I'll finally be on the
public
radio get
[Music]
it the mainstream radio because the
chain smokers is a very popular band
maybe not anymore I don't know maybe
that's 5 years
ago so is a
blank I never used the meds before I
think there are odds I don't like the
odds although it always was in his favor
so
far wow
aggressive
aggressive okay no that's good that's oh
that's fine that's fine um I
will handcuff him and I can like double
it twice
it may be doubling a blank but then I
can just double it
again or does it stay short no okay yeah
yeah he would just beer
[Music]
it you mean just throw out both both of
them or
what all right
this is
fine although he also has two two of the
knives [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] but we
reset the round so my turn
again uh free
free okay
manable am am I currently on full
HP it's free free
Right double
beer it's probably a life one I'm
telling
you yeah it was a life one what if the
next one's also live
guys not
good to fre
oh then that means I won't die either I
guess so trans me dying is better
too okay and now it's 2
two he doesn't have a steel right those
are
inverters
okay please
[Applause]
okay one more
shot come
on don't [\h__\h] with me now
Okay
Yahoo wins we love to see
it last round
already
YooHoo ah
uh we have a phone we have an inverter
that's
it four lives
[Music]
toal
tutu Moy
Moy
ooh so maybe we'll invert shoot and then
no should I invert and shoot or should
I well it could be
[Music]
either
self you want
to self and
shot but then worst case
no oh okay this is
good
okay okay now give us some more bullets
please oh wait it's not time yet now
there's uh one live one blank in there
right oh he heals back
no y oh it's my turn
[Music]
Dan w
wowowow wow wow wow sugy amazing
subarashi Divine
incredible divine
fine wait I said that already what was
the other word Majestic
21 magnificent that's the one not
Majestic uh 2
one o I'll just um hope for the best
shoot him
twice hopefully it's not the plank place
chance to are that this is a blank then
his turn is the live one and he can
double it but then I'm still
[Music]
alive
man here we go here we go we're so in
we're so in
oh please please show me the no why oh
wait wait took the month I think I
missed understood the
meds it Oh I thought I think I
misunderstood them uh I
thought I must have misread them I
thought it was a 50% chance that it
takes two
lives and or a 50% chance that it heals
you one or something like that I thought
it can also take oh it's the other way
around so oh it does take lives
sometimes oh but only
one he so far he's always
healed man
two
two and I can take the
handcuffs two two should I
eject
one I'm going to steal the
[Music]
Cuffs mhm
I wonder if I should
eject two two D two
two
okay one
more he has saw and invert
but now it's 5050 for
me oh but he's handcuffed oh never mind
then should I ah should I saw ah it's
too late
[\h__\h] damn it I
forgot you
silky a I can
inverted ooh this could have been a
kill damn it could have been a Kill if I
would have done it
smartly but it's
okay we're getting
there at least I saw my I realized my
mistake on my own I'm getting smarter
baby smarter smarter baby
smarter smart babyart
I love J One J
one here we go again here we go here we
go again uh uh here we go here we go
here we go again here we go
again two one here we go here we go here
we go again
21 m
H invert and
YOLO he has so many
items it just takes one
shot smoke first ooh does he have a
steel oh he does have a steel but he has
his own cigarettes too ah he could heal
up really high
I
don't you think it's a
blank oh yeah he might try for
these yeah I mean you with your
percentages but I don't believe in
percentages oh well it better be good it
better be the good outcome why am I even
doubling it just so that I don't
know no we inverted the life on you
[\h__\h] you sysy
buckers you sysy
[Music]
buckers a no oh no no no now
wait
did didn't he just possibly also invert
a blank
one she doesn't
know oh damn it what the [\h__\h]
man uh okay it was not a blank one but
he didn't
know he did the same
thing
dude do you ever not heal with the meds
you don't I haven't seen you a single
time taking
damage nah that sucks you suck
he it was it one one she that's
okay yeah at least free game and I get
to heal back
up okay
this is
good this is
good look how courageous I am look how
cool I
am I I do the cool
thing two items he has a million items
one one again oh okay wait did I get
handcuffs again all right then
all right
then okay is the game is helping me the
game is thinking that what just
transpired that was [\h__\h] let's bring it
back to how it was
before more or
less should not have used the Cuffs
yet he's
okay why not this is fine this is an
okay way to go about it chip Dam it
yeah yeah he has 100% success on the
meds what the hell absolutely
rigged
M oh again one
one did I get handcuffs again no okay
but first of all I'll
heal wait ah I
can I can steal a magnifying glass or I
can hope that it's a life one and go for
the double you want me to drink the beer
first but what if then I might be kind
of wasting the turn though
h a lot of you guys want a
beer yeah the round is over then
anyway no I'll do it I'll do it my way
I'll do it the straight edge way
[Music]
I'll do it the other way because using
the magnifying glass is the other
way straight edge but stealing that's
not part of straight edge right that
doesn't have anything to do with that
right that's a different
thing H more beer I don't drink
beer again
what's going on is this
normal well now I feel like I might want
to eject
both beer and
wind how is it a how is it a certain win
okay now it's a certain win but it could
have been I could have been ejecting the
live one though how is it certain that I
win oh well oh
well he nonalcoholic beer but even that
I wouldn't drink I would not even drink
non-alcoholic beer this just doesn't
taste
good I don't think I ever drank beer
before but the smell already tells me I
know I know it's going to taste how it
smells
disgusting and why did I only get 10
bucks
[Music]
though no why
why what is that is that
random is the money
random cuz the round was so long oh man
that wasn't on
me
huh too many items used oh man two
one oh come on what
what you're telling me to hurry up huh
wait did are are we starting with two
lives right
now hold
on 2 one wait maybe I should have kept
the phone second shell
[Music]
blank I
could do a lot of
things is
5050 be ah yeah beer and then invert
yeah skip this one oh it was a blank one
oh so wait then I
have oh
perfect now it's a life one the next one
is live
too I win oh this is okay then this one
should bring me more
money
PE this one's going to bring me more
oh it's oh it's only doubling 10
a what well this is not even worth
playing continuously doubling I want to
restart like I want to start from
zero building on the 10 bucks is such a
waste of
[Music]
time yeah restart is better I I mean
I'll end this round though but even that
is not worth my
time even that's not worth my
time
restarting we restarting
guys yeah we got to finish the first
round faster if the first round was like
what we just had now that would be
[Music]
fine damn
I tried to I tried to be fast but then
he heals up with two HP again
and ah it's just not it just didn't go
well and then we kept on getting only
like one one like one life one blank one
life one
blank like absolutely dragging it
out $10 for your FS thank you
question
[Music]
mark and if more items used also drags
down the
money then maybe I I don't know I
shouldn't
[Music]
always I don't
know oh so many
uh four free free do I have a steel I
don't think I have a
steel ah I don't like this free
[Music]
free F sh blank
[\h__\h] come
on
yeah
okay okay okay so there's
uh I don't know I don't want to think
about it I just know the one is
blank eh what you looking at what you
what you looking
at he's taking meds please
please ah yeah
finally getting some
Karma finally punished yeah but like
still it's not even when it really
matters I want to I want to see him lose
that HP when it really matters wait so
he just got did he invert though uh wh
which which round are we in the rest are
blank so I can
invert it's all blank that's a good
thing for
me all
right okay here we
go
okay is blank bu it I thought it was
black you guys lied to me you did not do
the math did he use the invert I don't
think he used the invert I didn't see
him using it maybe he did
though free
free free
free free free he has one life
left he has no magnifying
glasses he has nothing useful really
except the knife but no even that's not
useful right
now oh just in case I guess but he can
steal it back though oh no because I'll
use it okay that's fine that's fun I
guess I'll use it just so he can't use
it
himself and and then I just got to pray
and
pray free
free
Hallelujah
yeah that's what I'm talking
about okay
beautiful nice
[Music]
I love this this is SC I love taking
things out of my little
purse four uh three and two threee four
lives
uh I wish I had a
steal F shell live
uh what was it two three the two the two
were the live ones right threee
blanks three blanks
right the last one is
Alive high chances of a blank
this I'll CU I'll cuff and I'll
invert I think
the the last one was left right
no should I invert
again
s
[Music]
nah it's 2 two now
but the last one is live so the chances
of this one being live are ra relatively
low
right I'll I'll invert
it no
brain brain did not
work what are you seeing you're going to
and uh oh he saw a
blank he's
inverting couldn't he have shot himself
with the blank and then invert the next
[Music]
one is this a last
one it's the last one he didn't know ah
right he doesn't know but wouldn't he
know by now how many are left if he
would take uh
notes
[Music]
[\h__\h] I thought this was the last one
ah
[\h__\h] we'll be more careful once we're
doubling don't
worry don't worry
miscalculation tutu speaking of taking
notes tutu
uh Canal the phone or the
[Music]
meds tutu
tutu I think I steal the
[Music]
phoney for Shell blank so the last one
okay I think the first one is a live one
I have a
feeling but I always think the first one
is a live
one go
yeah I mean the odds were high
so yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah you always
think the first one has it
oh well this one could also be
live that was 50/50
yeah
woohoo Get Wrecked Get Wrecked it's fine
it's okay don't worry this was the right
thing to
do
uh-oh
oh I don't understand what just happened
but it's okay
that's was that was the last one right
okay uh two
two
two two two oh two
phones Second
Life what about the third or the fourth
[Music]
so it's
5050 oh
oh right the beer is all I need it after
knowing the second is okay the first one
was live to see the first one is always
life the first one is always
life yeah yeah I just don't think about
drinking beer you know because that's
just not how I live that's not my
lifestyle I live a straight edge
lifestyle
[Music]
okay all right all right all right all
right all right let's try to end this
fast possibly ooh two items only three
lives two two
to it's always
tutu maybe I drink
this one's not
live it's was life
[\h__\h] he has
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] please oh no ah my
God this one could also be blank
right
50/50 oh you think I should have done
self
[Music]
again I don't know
no oh
no oh no two
damage you don't want to shoot yourself
if you have free charge left because he
can kill you in one shot if he has a
saw but there was only one shot left so
he couldn't have used both four four
four
four okay
okay no what is
this ooh so
bad oh it's so
over oh it's so
over but oh
no oh
no no oh
no oh no oh no Yoko oh
no where are you Yoko oh
no too
bad you so okay next next
next
M please sign the
waer H okay
feels like a
deju this kind of
like keyboard
thingy how old is this does anybody
still use
that from what century is
that looks so old like maybe from a 100
years
ago uh
44 from the 80s
21d 21d Century
What 80s Tech definitely not a Nokia
almost looks like
it four four and these [\h__\h]
items for
rers
yeah y
[Music]
a YOLO never works when you want it to
work you only know you don't know the
current one and you're doing
that
oh he risked it for the biscuit
now the chances of this one being live
are very
high Battle of YOLO oh come on
now I feel like there's only lives left
now I'm just going to ah there was just
one blank left and I get the blank
[Music]
[Laughter]
one I know I know there was at least one
blank left but what the [\h__\h] why am I
getting them
why so
unlucky uh I think I'm
dead he's going to shoot right yeah no
no no
[\h__\h] it's not going so well now
[Music]
huh wait is this a a
prison it kind of looks like a
[Music]
prison red
M like an abandoned prison that's now
being used for these kind of shady Shady
dealings
[Music]
free
lives it's it's um completely random
right like how many lives and how many
uh bullets and how many items it doesn't
seem to be like connected with with one
another I thought in the beginning that
for example if you get like Six Bullets
then you'll have more items but if you
only get like three bullets and you have
less items or so but it seems like
everything is completely random because
yeah the constellation is just sometimes
really weird it makes no sense m
wait so what uh two1 two
one oh thanks for the raid welcome it
was a blank let's
[Music]
go you know what I could do instead of
drinking another beer I
could eat a cuff and invert this one
hoping that I get two live ones
but that might invert the life one
too what do you
think ah certain combinations don't
spawn seven life one
blank maybe yeah it's a risk it's too
risky save cffs for next round invert
after the
beer yeah okay in case it's now leaving
letting out the the life one ah okay
then I invert yeah okay
yeah it would be
fun but as you can see if I would have
done it that way then I would have
inverted the life one and then I would
have gotten no damage through at
all does he have a steal no good
good after the beer e what did I do
something
wrong this is
okay yay finally I haven't had a
magnifying glass in a long time I feel
like okay
uh free
free now then let's take a look shall
we ah it's
black and I just shoot myself
then oh wait ah I would have lik to use
the phone now before I shoot I can't go
back now can I
no because then if I use the phone now
then it could tell me the second
round but now it's too
late now it will only tell me the next
round not the not the current one but
this could have possibly told me the one
that is now the current one you know
what I
mean is it free free now six chall of
blank okay you were not going to tell me
the second one ah anyway okay
the last one is a
blank he has a
steel so I will use my cigarettes
perhaps or should we
just let's just cup for now and shoot
and see what
happens yeah
okay I'll take the cigarettes they're
just candy cigarettes anyway have you
had those before when you were younger I
had them I had candy cigarettes I had
candy paper money I had all the cool
things when I was a child and it was all
fake oh paper P edible paper such a
cheap snack
I didn't like it when I was younger but
now that I think about it maybe I want
to try eating it
again
please
yeah it take the time that I'm taking
also lows my money not just each turn I
thought it was just the more
turns so I should not think so much
either is it counting the time
the powder yeah I didn't really like
them either because they're so powdery
so dry I don't know was that what was
that was that gum does it turn into gum
I forgot what is he doing he's doing so
many
things
[Music]
ah did we already
double where is this a new beginning I
don't remember where we are g i so it
was
come wait I'm handsome hey
yo wait did he just take meds
and go down to one life or did I do that
I think I did that hey hey hey hey hey
hey does he know if
it's
oh okay it was the beginning we didn't
double okay okay wow it's really not
going so well anymore
yeah he probably knew the last from from
the phone does he have magnifying
glasses
too you look good in handcuffs excuse
me are you saying that you're going to
report me for the police to the police
for my
crimes you want to get rid of me one
once and for
all so not kinky at all you just want to
get rid of
me two three four
okay freee
free he has the better
items right now for my place though
should I eject one
[Music]
more no right oh man ah this is kind of
bad 2
Hp it's not so
nice
ah this is not a good start
either Oh
blank hand
CED uh is there free what what's left in
there oh never mind I'll die guess I'll
die where did my luck go they're not
letting me play anymore maybe I was on a
roll and I should not have stopped at
tripling I should have continued because
I was really on a roll and now I'm never
rolling
again someone man this is why exactly
this is actually exactly how gambling
Works they give you a little bit of this
good feeling in the beginning and then
you want more and more and then you
realize oh it's never ever happening
again yeah they saw me rolling so they
started hating [\h__\h] haters
man [\h__\h]
haters what is this I want to restart
two okay little amount of bullets at
least two
one no what is
this it's still a
phone
H okay at least that's one thing
oh successfully shoot yourself with
blank facing 50/50 odds I got an
achievement oh yeah shooting yourself
with 50/50 odds but they the achievement
doesn't know that I knew that the last
one it wasn't 50/50 odds but they don't
know don't tell them give me those
achievements give me
more give me give me more give me more
give me give me
more hey can I ever get more items when
I already have full
items sorry what was that four free or
four what what was
that that was a lot of
Reds
no oh it no new items of no s oh okay
okay four
four okay
check okay I think I'll invert cuz I
have so many inverters and then I'll
double did we start with 2 Hp then he
does have a steal
[Music]
so he wait he's dying anyway what am I
doing I was just
Overkill I love Overkill isn't that also
a game I should play that game
too I uh I think that's kind of in my
head in the list of one shot games I
want to play at some point anyway but
kind of I kind of want to play it in
3D uh in um VR cuz it's a VR game too
right and know that's Ultra kill Ah
that's what I'm thinking of yeah so so
so so Ultra kill cuz I I think crony was
playing it a long time
ago any blue game looks so good on her
PO tutu what does that even mean any
blue game that for some reason the the
is the logo blue somehow the people are
blue right something about Ultra kill is
blue in my mind oh that's super hot oh I
think of super hot wait what wait oh
what no it's all mixing up in my head uh
what Tut
two was it Tut two I'm getting really
confused Ultra kill super hot what super
hot is the VR one huh I need to look up
what Ultra kill
was uh two
okay I should have
called should have called I should have
called first [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I
know it
so it's 2
one proell blank
oh that means this one
is this one's uh
alive
H that but then now he also gets a live
one but he has no way of knowing unless
oh he's ejecting it
let's go oh he's inverting it oh never
mind okay you get one just one oh he's
taking a meds please take a life please
take a life please take a
life
no what are the
odds certainly not
[Music]
50 yeah I could have Drank in like one
beer perhaps I don't know oh
well yay look at my
haul Russian Roulette haul too
free on YouTube Russian Roulette
haul so I got this really cute
magnifying glass which is like so
adorable I got it in this Russian
Roulette parlor I almost died there like
several times but they kept on Def Brew
braiding me I don't know how to say that
word honestly but yeah I'm just going to
go ahead and uh eject the current one uh
oh maybe that was unnecessary but I'm
talking right now doing my haul so I'm a
little bit confused you know but I'll
just look at it again and see with my
beautiful magnifying glass oh my God
it's so cute um so the thing is that
this one is blank again you know so I'm
just going to use these cute cups that I
S adorbs so cute and I'm going to use
this cute little inverter thingy which
totally looks like um
I don't know something really
playful going to invert
it going shoot him with this one cuz I'm
so sitick of the
blanks and then we might just shoot them
again was this okay or was this really
bad I think it was okay my choices were
okay uh now I lost track however uh how
what's in there lost
track uh I feel like it could be a live
one
I think I should go for it
right I should go for it to life one
black all right I love bimbo
K me
too me too my
friend he's
healing at wait he ejected the blank on
so this one
is
what
huh
[Music]
I strongly dislike you
sir we need some good stuff now man
should I take the meds once free to
should can I take some meds
[Music]
ones yeah probably lose a
life uh yeah I'll be low on money again
I think wouldn't risk it
yet I want to do it but I'll get
probably
a what a stupid
stupid
no this is so dumb I should restart
right
now I'll
just I'll play but
[Music]
which which shell are we at right
now the first oh
[Laughter]
H I don't know
anything I can't keep track
oh no my game
crashed oh
know I don't know how this
happened so unfortunate how how how come
my game crash this game is so
unstable I'm going to give it a really
bad rating on
[Music]
Steam oh I started the double or nothing
mode 10 times and only like got
something out of it
once come on 10th time is the
charm I feel
it how are you liking so far I really
liked it and I was on a high in the
beginning but it's just really not going
so well for several rounds now like for
nine
rounds I'm just so unlucky
now so [\h__\h] up
but I
[Music]
believe what four four with two
items and three
lives what what I
know I justt yeah
man
what of course of course of
course
ye
okay
okay oh he's a masochist he feels like
I've been like he's been too much and he
feels not comfortable with
that
so two more lives left four
blanks better
[Music]
inverted
okay now we're
[Music]
talking he finally showed me like his
Pawn charm again
[Music]
oh whoow he's trying to reel me back
into the game by doing lots of Pawn
moments okay my
friend okay he wants me to feel better
about all of
this okay I'll play for a little while
longer you were losing me there but now
you're winning me back two two two
[Music]
two two oh the magnifying glass thank
you all right I wish I had a double D
this would be the fastest shooter in the
wild
west that would be so good he has a heal
though so sad
moyy there's two lives uh two blanks one
life left there there he
[Music]
heals he takes my beer ejects the live
one now there's only blank
SL oh he probably found out about a
blank one not about a live one on the
phone
huh
huh no wait yeah he could have only
found out about a blank one because the
last two were blanks and the one in the
current round was a life one and on the
phone you don't you only get the ones
after the current round so but he could
have assumed that the current one was
blank because on the phone he heard
there was a blank one you know what I
mean yeah you know what I mean uh three
no four
four two lives oh God but we started
with two so I can't heal up right four
four I can steal he has a
phone steal the
phone
[Music]
44 the knife would be good too I know I
was thinking about it
six is a life
one he can still to I have
[Music]
to I
believe yes free
four go for
it uh two four two
m not
good that is probably a live one no it
wasn't one
four one
four
one4 oh
but still not perfect because I didn't
get any new items to improve this
situation but this is okay
free one threee lives one
blank he gets the turn but he can't
really do much either it's
okay I get the next shot it better be
the life one and not the blank
[Music]
one two one it's got to be oh the six
okay yes yes was this the sixth one
which is live the sixth out of eight
then we I could have known
yeah y that wasn't such a long round we
good we good we good we
good big brain
moments big brain okay come on
magnifying glass no magnifying glass
magnifying glass
what oh he has a heal and the steel and
something else oh two and one one
ooh
[Music]
okay what if I shoot
myself
no and then steal the the heel I was
going to say oh
okay h
all
right should I still sto have stolen the
heal yeah damn it I wasn't
sure but I can still do it I can do it
now I can do it now wow
wow to
to I have so many tools
two wait what's two two two
two two he has one life left uh he has
no magnifying
glass why is there no not a single
magnifying glass on this
table but he has cuffs
too be
[Music]
well then I can invert no wait wait no
okay we'll still another beer because
it's 22 so now it's 21
um even if we kick out the live one
now then we can
invert ah it was really two lives in a
row so I'll invert and then we good what
the cops it's okay doesn't fun too isn't
it the same
[Music]
outcome isn't it the same outcome don't
don't
panic Don't Panic same
thing oh this is so different from
before was that one game really so
long oh that's good money
oh and I get to keep some of these items
let's go oh he
y
y oh four ooh three four three lives
four
blanks ooh this might be an easy win
let's
see I can invert it and double it oh my
God
but wait before I do that the
phone
ooh I don't get that
turno he gets that turn he can steal my
magnifying glass too
oh self
[\h__\h] yeah I should have
self he can steal both my magnifying
glass and my heel
[Music]
I have to I don't want him to steal it
and be sure about what's to
come I don't want to give it to
him ah could have been better but
[Music]
okay so what's in there now he heals
one maybe he'll even take his stupid
meds
oh he's doing
it but now it's okay if the rounds are
long because we're just
doubling he's handcuffing me he's
doubling a
no
no if he doubles it again and it's a
life one then I'm [\h__\h] but he doesn't
know he can't know I don't know either
just got to pray that it's a
oh oh my
God why did you risk
that how much just left in there denying
was right move thank you what's left in
there do you guys
know should I take my
meds okay free three blanks and two live
ones or one oh thank
God one
free free
[Music]
blanks I think I have to pray but the
odds are really low
[Music]
[Applause]
but then there's only blanks left so
that's good ah but he doesn't have he
does have an
inverter and a
double oh okay yeah yeah yeah it's fine
is he ever going to
invert is he going to
invert it was to free no wait what no no
I just doubled the that was the last the
last life one left it was one free but
that was the last life now there's only
a blank one
right nice what is he doing Pawn
moment last on blank right but I'm just
going to just in case I'm scared
um doesn't matter which it doesn't
matter right Pond deight back in the
game it should be a
blank but okay let's let's yeah
okay good good good good
goodoo we have salvaged the situation
magnifying glasses nice this is nice
this is okay this is
nice free four oh same as before or free
four free four and I have four
lives ooh I can steal his inverter
yeah and then kill
[Music]
him of course I'm going to S I
know I
know is this realistic by the way in
real life if you saw off your
shotgun how will it hurt more how how
so how does
no no it's
[Music]
notak it changes the
spread it's it's
illegal it's illegal to cut off your
shotgun
really four four uh free four
again it's been illegal since the 1920s
not hurts more close range not well then
that makes sense kind of uh free
four it's a higher chance it's a blank
right
now but maybe that's not invert I don't
know let's just shoot twice
what you
think you you want invert oh
well
y my guts my
[Music]
guts are so good that his guts I'm
shooting them out of his
brain makes no sense but you know now
it's probably a
blank so I'll invert now yeah yeah yeah
yeah cuz now there's a four blanks in
two lives but now I probably inverted a
blank it it's got to
be only one life left and four
blacks
yeah damn it these odds one for
oh
okay oh he's do it again I knew it I
knew it I knew it he's so dumb he's so
dumb
sometimes why would you risk so
much but now it's only
[Music]
blanks now it's only blanks
his face is so
funny oh
[Music]
okay m
M four free again free four again
again again and again and
[Music]
again
no wait he mag he's he's got a
magnifying glass
I didn't
see oh no oh wait I can
s we
good now it's two free I
think
two live free
blank I don't think I want of s again I
don't think
so a damn it now it's to two
what's she going to steal in my
meds come on come on come on come
on yeah finally he's had the good effect
for too
often
oh
nice we like to see
it nice
this game is so
fun this game is so
fun me why why why why what did I
[Music]
do oh it's empty now
right okay smokes phone whoa
oh good good haul free four again oh
we've had fre four for ages
now but he only has one HP
[Music]
left oh how must it feel when you know
it's
over it's over Piana win # y
# last round and then we can double
again we're so back free uh two free
threee lives two
lives huh
not much I can do self yeah then I can
heal it I
guess so one life bullet
left wait oh [\h__\h] oh he also goes for
the self oh of
[Music]
course dump oh oh [\h__\h] oh okay
this time what
what stupid
[\h__\h] why did he do a third time why did
he do a third time last one's a blank
right he F that one would also be BL I
thought it was already the last
ammo I thought it was the last ammo
already
okay he's really really Brave I got to
give him I don't know is it Brave is it
a
brave cocky I think is what it
is free to free lives
to three two two lives three
lives oh I want this magnifying glass I
can't heal up right three was the
maximum I think
um uh free two lives threee blanks and
free free here HP it's confusing that
you called that live I I didn't know
that until
today freeze the max okay ah
[\h__\h] so only one life bullet and free n
that's probably going to be
but first let me take a
selfie what go [\h__\h]
yourself guys [\h__\h] yourself
now oh you're stuck am I going to
die not necessarily right I mean he can
he didn't even look are you going to
look before you cut it
uhoh but what why is he not even looking
at the
current oh he inverted no did I
no I got
cocky
no
no okay last one uh unless I lose
but last attempt
shouldn't go too long tomorrow uh is H
talk relatively early in the day I hope
you guys will be awake for
it hope you'll be there also I still
have to
cook if I if I if I hope I hope my hello
fresh package is in on front of my door
and I just don't
know cuz they did not ring any bells
[Music]
she's
44 she
is
[Music]
uh good for
free I'll hope that this is a live one
it
was yay y yay yay
yay can you track it normally they send
a message like oh it has been delivered
or
so oh he ejected the red
one
[Music]
H free to
free good math two
life [\h__\h] God damn
dude you poor poor
pan so probably blank now one free
[Music]
H damn
son now it's 2
one I'm getting more risky
yeah I don't know what I want to
do I could H I do have heels
true oh now it's
5050 kind don't want to risk
it what can happen HH what's going to
happen let's make this round short I got
to I have some Stu to do tomorrow yeah
hold a talk with what Mr
pie yeah K wins let's go let's
go I actually fought off some questions
on my own because when I you guys had
really good questions and when I was
going through them I some of them I
obviously used but then I was reminded
of a lot of things anyway like all the
things she did
and I was so inspired one one
[Music]
four so getting the questions together
was really easy but I realized I still
have to put it into the graphics the
psds one
one oh let's handcuff
him but besides that everything's ready
I think I know the clips are still being
clipped right now clipped and translated
hopefully it won't make it in
time
uh should
I nah only if the next only if this
one's blank then I'll double
it a damn it
okay all
right yeah it's um like inh house is it
is the usual team but it's in- house m
uh but this time I kind of let them kind
of choose what to clip normally I tell
them what to
clip but this time I I was kind of busy
because I needed to so to say commission
the
clips uh like I need to do it early
because it takes a few days to do these
like two clips us usually it's two clips
per H
talk free free
and I was like in Thailand so I was busy
and I couldn't really think about it so
I was like please can I just leave it to
you guys this time what the by surely
has a lot of fun stuff anyway free
free oh oh I wish I had this magnifying
glass but I watched what they made so
far F shell
blank Nar
should i s
[Music]
off I mean why not so only for kill no
okay sometimes you got a YOLO but okay
you know what I'll do now I'll cut it
off
cuz I think it's a life one trust
me
yeah now it's his turn and this one is a
blank one right
um he will know that with his magnifying
glass he'll turn it around and he'll
double
it so he'll use all his items that's
okay we have so much HP and he only has
one and no
[Music]
heal but since this one was originally
blank I have a feeling the next one is
live
again 2 one live again
reference so the problem is we have no
items but I have the advantage
[Music]
yay pickle pickle pickle pickle pickle
pickle all right
p t
no that doesn't sound so much like her
[Music]
anymore no no no
no con con I need to practice more I
haven't done it in a
while okay wait wait wait uh what how
many was it three four three life ones
[Music]
take these my friend they'll keep you
safe trust
me
Sal not OB no she has a raspy voice you
know he has a
steel might want to heal
two
[Music]
four come on come on come on come on
come on come on come on yeah wow wow wow
we're zooming through it
now we're totally zooming through it
[Music]
[Applause]
now that was
good wait how much money did it say was
it a good
amount I didn't
look 38k okay that's all right we
weren't zooming through it so I expected
a good
amount oh 2 one Short Round I like it I
like it I like it oh oh [\h__\h] actually I
got a good start oh no inverts though
uh I wait look look at all his
items he can steal too live round F
shell this actually wait I can I can
skip
Boni wait so I just skip until the third
round Oh I thought sometimes I don't
think about
selfing I just don't think about the
option
nice [\h__\h] nice next round please next
bullets next items he has so many items
man I got to stuck up ooh nice we can
steal magnifying glass we can steal both
magnifying
glasses well actually no we the Cuffs in
the glasses maybe Tut two
awesome we're
winning what's finish for me a red one
if only he had a
double just when you really want
it uh should I call maybe it tells me
the next
one but well cuff of course
[Music]
and then we call hopefully tells me the
next
one please tell me the second one please
pleas the second number two number two
number two number two number two ah for
CH okay it's the first chance blank
maybe the second one is
also
live it could be could be
should I heal
though so he can't steal it he can still
heal a big heel he has his own big
heel I think I'll
smoke
yeah I could even use the pills
too but I probably should have used the
pills first
don't
[Music]
could oh she's rolling again maybe like
every 10th round you roll although no
this is the 11th isn't
it the 11th try of me doubling or going
on the double mode
gaming I'm glad I gave this game a try I
wasn't so sure about it but I wanted to
play one off game
44 wanted to play one off game and I
don't know it looks kind of funky
so the odds are 5050 and there's so much
in there
I don't know if
I please please be a black
please I'll cough and I'll
shoot o
although ah he probably wouldn't even
have stolen that because he didn't take
damage
oh after
thought oh well at least we got a
hit good point right although I yeah I I
would think
the the way he's coated he's smart
enough to
not steal a heal when he doesn't need
it or he just would steal it because he
doesn't want me to have it next
round oh oh see like now but now he does
need a
heal he does need a heal
actually he does need a
heal cuz I did hurt
him
a never mind then I don't know where I'm
going with
this 2
one oh
one
one or two what's
left only only
lives can't take him out because there's
you know nothing on the table and
yeah you get the
shot ooh
I need a heal please give me a heal item
but like the the cigarettes I'm starting
smoking today I prefer ecigarettes I
guess but
oh uh
oh that's fine oh wait that should that
can work that can
work all right he's down oh he's down
okay didn't need so magnifying glasses
but I got all I
need right in front of
me
hi easy wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow
it's all about luck it's about the items
you
pull pretty much and the items he pulls
that's all it is my
friends why do I have to always choose
where it goes just put it wherever it
doesn't
[Music]
matter two
one uh did I get a magnifying glass
yep I have an inverter
I'll call
First mhy mhy tell me the second one for
live okay I know what to
do actually uh yeah yeah yeah I know
what to do uh I cuff him I shoot then I
because he still
cuffed and then I'll shoot and we good
[Music]
this much I can
comprehend
oh no what why no cuffs the Cuffs do
nothing I I think it would
have because when I shoot him he uh he
he gets the next turn
yeah I was
right the Cuffs only do nothing if I
didn't shoot myself but the first thing
I did is shoot him cuz I
inverted
yeah
yeah sometimes free free
sometimes I I'm getting are you guys are
trying to bamboozle me some of you guys
but it's okay we you know we sometimes
get confused I also sometimes you
probably just lost track of what I was
doing he's so
gay he has two lives
left I don't have a steel I don't have a
magnifying glass I can call what was it
how many was
it thir sh blank was it two two or what
threee threee oh [\h__\h] thir shell blank
free
free so this is basically
yeah I think I'll shoot
him ah damn
it he has two steals
yeah [\h__\h]
[Music]
please chances are high but you never
know oh thank
God thank God
yay
woohoo
oo very nice very beautiful
actually I think I might not go to the
fifth
round I think this is my third round
round right so I think I might just end
it after the third round cuz I'm
scared I'm
scared oh yeah I want to end on a high I
don't want to
lose maybe we can play it again next
week and go longer longer longer fre uh
four four okay
M 44 right 44 uh he has cuffs I can
steal cuffs I can steal phone I can
steal all kinds of things
[Music]
oo I will invert and cuff him
oh
go wait never mind don't worry I figured
it
out
huh
h no you can't steal
steals holy macaroni that was
[Music]
fast I
think K wins oh
[\h__\h] con next they know that I'm in a
hurry they know
it
mhm what
okay
oh uh for free
[Music]
at least nobody has a
double I would like to have had a
double but it is what it
is now it's free
free uh he heals up of course he
[Music]
does he ejects aive one to free he looks
at the current
one what is it what is it buddy oh it
was a life one one
free one free I have lots of inverters
buddy
I
heal I I hope I'm not inverting the life
one but chances are
good thank
God I did but he has no
inverters he ejects a life blank there's
two blanks left or
one is he going to try it it's over
anyway the round is
over damn it it was going kind of nicely
oh wow
okay okay what do we have oh okay one
life two blanks I have inverters uh I
don't have a magnifying glass oh that's
okay should I
[Music]
ah do I
invert or shoot
first let's shoot
first heal I can't heal higher I think
cuz my Max is
to I think I'll shoot if it's a blank
then I'll in uh oh then I then I'll
invert now easy easy easy yeah I think
that was fine that was I think a good
good
decision cuz now it's only blanks it
could have been it could the thing is
even if that was a blank in that moment
I could have just doubled the next one
cuz then I yeah yeah I mean I I wouldn't
have known for sure but this is actually
possibly the best outcome
yay we're really ring for
it R I feel it every every
shot last
[Music]
one I think I'm quite decent at this but
it's just luck so I don't want to feel
too proud of
myself it's a fun game though oh [\h__\h] 44
M this is a long one
y four Lives four eight bullets
actually ah I still this magnifying
glass
nice sorry that belongs to me now
y are the cups would have been good oh
oh he doesn't have a steel so I think
I'll keep my my
heal and free
four I like the little chair squeaky
sounds adds nice detail
atmosphere he has a double too kind of
scary H he's cuffing
me what do you know that I don't know
you think that's a blank damn free
free oh he knows he knows this
one or does
he oh he
knows doie doie doie
doie I have a heal though two
free let let me let me go let me go
oh
oh it's time to stop thinking you have
fought too much is this last one alive
or two lives
oh well I only get one of them
y it's a live
[Music]
stream a stream of Life
bullets
invert
oh just so
that I use one on myself and then shoot
and he doesn't get the last
one
oh it's okay he's probably dead
now oh I have a heal again
only two bullets only two bullets
[Music]
Doo
sth but if I if it's not a
blank then he gets the next turn
[Music]
invert is
safest why it's just
50/50 that doesn't doesn't matter it's
just why why
invert cuz uh we do why why do we want
to waste an
item we don't
right even he dies or he can't shoot
back
M if it's blank you
kill I don't know guys you're kind of
confusing me I'll just do simple
thing why you got to be so
complicated I see the way you're fing
just so much in your little tiny chicken
brainage life's like this y
just go the W way go the W way when
there's too much to when you you were
over complicating the situation guys you
really were over comp over
complicating the
situation yeah
yeah yeah that was a really good run for
real those maybe even better than my
first uh triple
[Music]
win even if he shot you you had extra
Health yet but then wouldn't we move on
to another
round like another whole thing it's okay
anyway we
win should have kept on doubling no I
think I got to go I got to uh cook and
all that but I read some super chats I
think I have enough time for some super
chats yeah
y that was so much fun maybe I'll play
again next
week I wonder does this game have an
English
version
and does this game have a Japanese
version question mark question mark
question mark what did she was she
saying what was Aura
there I don't see her ah there ah your
favorite game real what of all
time you're teaching all your other
favorite games for this one it's great
but wait did the Japanese version is
called back shot rette nah no way no
that's just probably because Bak it's
like in Japanese it's
B and you call it and you write it with
ba in katak maybe that's one yeah the
Bak oh that's one
oh yeah right then she play it that's so
that's probably what there's a Japanese
version I was I was about to say like I
feel like Japanese girls would have fun
with this
too that's just
[Laughter]
n you should play excuse
me Fuki loves it too mik played last
week
Ohi has been playing as well ah okay
okay okay
who who played it first I
wonder cuz I wonder where where did the
fotm where does the fotm start from for
usually like often it starts from
picota but picota didn't play it right
who played
it I want to check the archives I'm just
curious who found this or is this a game
that everybody was looking forward to I
did not have this on my radar I didn't
know about this at all
it stands for flavor of the month it's
like the popular game of the
month you think Ana was the
first the sisifus you mean the the ball
rolling game I don't know
I I think that one can get
boring I've been watching other people
play it and you know I love Kon sire so
just because it was cold in a sfire it
was okay but she played it for hours and
hours and hours and hours I just feel
like nothing really happens in the game
like after a while even if you push it
really high I think it will just get
boring I will get bored
possibly I don't think I want to play
[Music]
it
yeah not interested like I also really
didn't enjoy the climbing game that much
I think maybe those kind of games are
not my thing
maybe who
knows all right we're going to go maybe
to my
office chat thank you for watching guys
by the way hope you enjoyed it
tomorrow's Hol talk I hope everybody
will be there even if it's early in the
morning uh for na I hope you can be
there uh it's been a while I think it's
actually the 20 uh the 30th
episode that's quite special and I hope
I remember to drink to prepare my holot
talk mug my real
mug so that will be the first episode of
H talk where I'll be actually drinking
out of the whole talk
[Music]
mug
yeah the immersion it's going to feel so
real to me
I need to make my whole office look like
the whole talk
office or even just like this office
actually that would be such a cute idea
but that's so much work like holy [\h__\h] I
would have to spend so much money on and
maybe hire someone to rebuild the office
so that it's my office would be fun
though can you wear a pacifier for the
Luna hole talk the thing is like like
I've seen someone else got a pacifier
too right a while ago who was it I don't
know but uh their
pacifier uh moves when they talk I think
people is it hers that
moves I don't think she's the only one
though doesn't Luna also have a
pacifier but the thing is mine doesn't
move like mine was I think the first
pacifier in whole life and it was just
so Random I didn't even ask for it um
but they didn't like animate The
Pacifier so I just feel like it looks
kind of awkward when it doesn't move at
all when I'm talking so I don't like
using it that much if only it had some
animation L has one too what the [\h__\h]
why
why people didn't ask you about what the
[\h__\h] why what's with these un un
solicited
pacifiers I feel like fubuki asked for
it though if she has one you guys say
she has one or
mik
really bubble bubble I ask why about Lia
a lot why L is there so many things to
question maybe yeah maybe her
food maybe her food
but her food looks like it's low calorie
maybe she's on a diet
do you mind waiting approximately 5
Seconds
okay my box is
there my box is there
okay so I can cook after
this Panic Don't
Panic
yeah okay so let's play some
music
damn I I was I was chilling outside in
my garden today quite a lot because it
was really warm and nice
and uh I actually I didn't finish mowing
my lawn yesterday mowing my lawn yes yes
yes because it was so much and I just
wanted to not overdo it uh so I finished
it today after I woke up and um then
then I chilled with my
cats and mowing the cusa yeah and I
chill with my cats and you know toners
really really likes uh the garden likes
being outside and but still they didn't
like the grass so much right both of
them um but chunky wonky I was lying on
my M what do you call it like a lying
thingy an outdoor
bed uh what do you call it
[Music]
again uh not a hammock no
a recliner I guess a
lawn chair a recline yeah it's like a a
length it's not a chair more like a
lengthy little bed where you can change
the height of the head
thingy yeah I guess it's a lawn chair
but just sounds like it's just a chair
but you know what I mean like a lounge
thingy yeah deck chair yeah something
like that that was chilling on it and
and then and then chunky wonky I guess
she wanted to be close to me normally
she likes sitting on the chairs the
normal chairs when they're tucked under
the table in the garden but this time
she ran over the grass over to meet and
she was
like I'm like what do you want come over
here then she came closer step by step
carefully while like paying attention to
the air flow and the bugs and everything
so step by step slowly she comes closer
and then she found her new favorite spot
in the garden which is directly under
the yeah lawn reclining half bed chair
the lounge
whatever in the grass but like under the
whole thing so she gets the shade from
it and she gets to be close to me but
now I have to like I was like kind of
like having my head upside down looking
under the chair while being on it
for a long time so that I could reach
over to her and cuddle her while she's
down there she just prefers to be down
there yeah I was I was petting her she
was going and then I took some cute
photos because the light was kind of
nice surprisingly and she her eyes were
like her eyes were like
this and it took I took some pictures
upside down I was upside down she wasn't
and then I sent it to my friends and
then RBF oh by the way RBF had no no
particular business was just like like
in the area that's why he was
calling but RBF uh and BFF were taking
care of my cats recently right so uh
apparently RBF was taking some cute
pictures of chunky wonky and he followed
up the picture that I took and and sent
to our group he followed it up with a
picture he took of chunky wonky and it's
actually so
beautiful it's so well lit and so sharp
and she's in such an amazing
pose I wish I could show you it's so
good
damn it's so
good damn she's so she's that's the
amazing what a shot I think I want to
print this one out it looks like it
could be in a like picture book of like
wild animals in the
Safari she looks like a lion walking
through her
savan looking around for her pack that's
exactly what it looks like and she even
has her mouth open like
meowing while
looking like really photogenically to
the
side yeah but still you see a good
amount of her eyes and her whiskers and
her paw is like perfectly placed in
front of the other so there's like one
paw she's doing a cat walk you know damn
she's she's
gorgeous
she what a good picture damn sorry you
can't you guys can't even see it but
it's like so good I wish I could show
you yeah
she's playing the camera I don't I don't
think she knows like usually it's hard
because like the moment I put the camera
uh in front of her face she will like
not look straight anymore even if she
was looking straight the whole time the
moment I put the camera even even if
it's not really right in front of her
but like a meter or two or three meters
away she'll suddenly start looking all
all over the place so I can't get a good
picture same
I don't want you to take a picture
they're camera
shy but this one's good sheesh okay wait
I said I was going to put on some music
a the
[Music]
music there's a audio stock track that I
named animals in a square relax
[Music]
what was I thinking but it's
cute I like I think I was thinking of a
Town Square
maybe but they're relaxing it's not that
relaxing
[Music]
H I like it though let's play it
kind of
circusy okay super chats we caught up
with the members only super chats in the
members only stream but what where am I
with my normal super
chats Ena is playing pikuniku
alone is she playing pikuniku alone that
feels so
random just saw it in whole lier
alone is that it's not a solo game I
played it with someone I think but is it
um local co-op
[Music]
only I played with gooa was it
local it's cute it's fun
oh it ends so abruptly oh that sucks oh
well it's also single player yeah so I
guess she'll probably play single player
I did Remote Play Oh huh interesting but
hers is not a collab okay did you guys
say where I have to continue reading I
think maybe girls
talk cuz my girls talk Super Chat button
thingy is not gr out so I didn't click
on it yet
it is it is multiplayer it's actually
really fun I think it's more fun as
multiplayer like this kind of game it's
screaming to be played as
[Music]
multiplayer yeah we're F we're finished
with the like a dragon super
chats okay then it's Girl Talk
[Music]
cute okay here we go Jacob 47
n
monkey the
gamer HD spank thanks for the red chat
oh my God best girl St ever really you
think so do you like why am I still
sparkling do you like these members in
particular I think you'll like it even
more though when call is in it right
that will be the best one for you cuz
you're K ooshi too
so don't don't talk this one maybe for
now it's your best
one but it might change
eventually every single girls talk is
the best girl talk I'm so happy you guys
like it but I I I I said this before and
I'll say it again it's not going to be
as long running as holot talk cuz
um I feel like like the
topics you
know girls
talk real girls talk I think has more
topics but that topics that maybe aren't
really the kind of topics you want to
hear us talking about uh and so it's
kind of limited and I feel like I don't
know there's still some things I want to
do like I want to do the Love Letter
thingy
got to find the right people though for
it who are who want to do it but yeah I
don't I I think it will not be that long
running
maybe maybe three three more times or
so just because I feel it will be too
repetitive maybe if the girls talk is
finished maybe that's when I can start
the book club
yeah maybe I can like replace it with
something like that
[Music]
just make it a normal podcast yeah but
then I kind of have to ditch the girls
talk theme and just make it a normal Dam
but then there's you know I need I need
some kind of gimmick I think to make it
like
appealing um
yeah I know you guys enjoy us just
talking about anything but then there's
no meaning to calling it girl so H I
don't know cuz like I feel like even if
you guys are fine with continuing it
more as a normal Jaan
eventually I feel weird about it still
being called girls
talk cuz then what if people come in
expecting girls talk because I didn't
see the other episodes or they only saw
an early one or so and they're like e
they're not really doing girls this is
just normal do
done I just I know it's girls talking
but it's originally it's supposed to be
a very girly talk like a
[Music]
sleepover I just feel like then it needs
to be rebranded I don't know
man I don't
know it's just not going to be a forever
[Music]
thing it's fine like that
M current events is relevant to
girls what would that be for
[Music]
example tat collabs are so rare in Ian
yeah but I think if it's just a taton
collab I'll be honest I don't I I think
I think it needs a gimmick for people to
really be like oh okay let's go let's
let's watch
[Music]
this no it's it's nice to have zatu
collapse I am with you on that but I
think it needs a
[Music]
gimmick chat cast well chat cast the
thing with chat cast is you know it's
like
a a set group of people
and I don't know I feel like
[Music]
it's a bit different for them
but
[Music]
yeah been a while since the chat cast it
they're not ending it though
right but
maybe H yeah I don't know maybe maybe I
can Rebrand it to Bird's talk then have
it be me and M as the whole
poost and then bring in a new person and
it's just a normal podcast with no theme
but it's just called birds talk because
it's us or it could be I could make my
own chat cast but it's Birds English
Birds only aka narissa me and M another
triple triple
group and then no other people just us
always I don't
know I don't know we think about it once
I feel like G Talk needs to be put to an
end Dana is an English Bird yeah but I
think free uh is good
number I think free is good also you
know time zones if I
add uh
waya I love talking with her but if I
add Raina then we
have too many time zones again and
that'll make it rough
again anyway those are just some
possibilities and faults but yes spank
time thank you D tag thanks for right to
the chat congratulations on the new
living situation boss I am glad you and
the kitties can enjoy something nice and
I'm glad that perhaps we kfp have had a
small part to playing that making that a
reality you deserve all the best things
Ki uh small part uh you had all the
parts in
it without you
guys without the support of you I would
not have been able to afford this
ever ever I mean
maybe you can think about it in the way
that
[Music]
I
uh I am I I don't know but you know you
know we're both necessary and whole life
me joining whole life is also uh you
know the
first part in all of
this but yeah yeah you know not just a
small part in it
kfp I owe it to you thank
you D with those red super chats I'm
paying off my
loan thank you d space waterall NE
goddess NE goddess V
faction oh wait n says M may not rotate
her piercing earrings a yeah yeah I
think you kind of like move him around a
little bit I don't know and you have
to uh like
alcoholized
alcoholized them every day I
think I did that I did that and still
and they were like healed properly like
when I took mine out the ones that you
keep in for a long time yeah disinfect
when I took them out it was way longer
than what was recommended ended so it's
not like it wasn't like the skin wasn't
healed when I took him out it wasn't
like an open wound or
anything but then so soon after after a
week or so they grew back
together what the [\h__\h] it's supposed to
stay open at that
point
regeneration
but I have been gifted
earrings
again
recently I'm like
oh
earrings
uh
h i don't have
holes I guess I got to get holes
[Applause]
again honestly Clips really
hurt really really hurt the other day I
had Clips on for a whole
day and at some point you just like
forget about it especially cuz I was
feeling a pain everywhere anyway so the
ear pain was like whatever but when I
put them when I took them off I realized
how much pain that was inflicting on
me oh she yeah clip ones are so
painful Buckshot R let to get new ear
ear
holes I don't know if they can be so
accurate about
it just shrunk down really no no no no I
swear they were gone they were gone I
tried to put something in there but no
nothing was going
through magnetic earrings I think they
hurt too I think I tried
[Music]
them they're either too weak or they
also hurt not sure anymore also they
just they're just not many of those I
don't ever see them being
sold so there wouldn't be much variation
either why do I have 4
DMS
[Music]
ohon oh
damn yeah yeah I asked crony like why
are you going to to
Poland because like it's kind of close
to me and I was like I
wonder depending on what she's doing cuz
I didn't know I asked her depending on
what she's doing like if I can join her
and meet
up or if it's like a
b un asked for or
so oh
but she's really only there for such a
short time
[Music]
I could totally go but she told me the
reason why she's there and it's
[Music]
probably uh unasked for for me to
go and I mean I could I could go just
for like you know dinner but yeah man
nah uh
[Music]
sheesh if you miss your
flight feel free to come over
oh your flight back I
[Music]
mean nah I mean it would be I would be
like more eager to do it if I never have
met crony before but I met her before
obviously so at this point it's
like a is not that close it is close
with a flight I can be there in like an
hour and it usually it's pretty cheap
[Music]
yeah it's um neighboring Germany
so actually super easy I would go if she
had like free time or more like of
a different reason why she's
[Music]
there ah damn it damn it damn it Dam
She's So
Close you can't just go to Europe and
not but it's okay I met her before we're
going to meet again this is not a big
loss but it just feels like she's like
right there she's right
there wait I got to send her she she
wants to see my
cats I'm going to send her the really
good picture that I told you about that
I can't show anybody
[Music]
at least somebody gets to see
it maybe maybe she'll be like ah damn it
okay I'm coming over I'm ditching what I
have to do I'm coming
[Music]
over reer in with the cat cat Riz that's
all the Riz I have man ah how do I say
that in Korean again wait wait wait wait
wait how do I say the thing again ah is
there any Korean Bros here right
now any Korean Bros please tell me past
the the
Korean cat RZ in the chat right now
please anybody
anybody
anybody Korean bro please please I think
the it was kangi cat was kangi I
think K
Bros KRA is this that is that it oh I oh
that looks like it I I wait wait ch ch
no what the [\h__\h] is it this pole pole I
need to rise her before she suddenly
disappears
yes that's
[Music]
it oh oh it's a little bit different
Boro
G she's
laughing I made her laugh the rist is
working come
s come s she's coing
nice I'm so in guys I'm so
[Music]
in
oh oh is she saying she says meowing
[Music]
Korean what did I say back what did I
say
back what I what did I
say a PO I say po
CH oh no I say give me milk give me
milk you
[Music]
CH okay I got to go back to
my Super Chat raing Kaa
take it out of the fridge oh no isn't
that what she said to me like what she
actually said to me
indeed
oh where am I where am I where was I
here
[Music]
the great
move Jackson
[Music]
FB V faction dun Shred the holic Danon
there's a type called Blue scense that
smells like shower yeah I think I know I
know I feel like it's also for drinks
there's like this blue flavor GAA says
it tastes
blue but maybe that's just because she
can't think of anything else but I think
they actually call
something just like blue flavor cuz you
don't know what else it's supposed to
be simple ton Dan I used to work with a
guy that you could identify where he had
been 5 minutes earlier from the
cologne made me feel like I understood
dog seeing odor oh I could legit track
this man through the
wood
yeah I don't like it like it's it's the
worst thing thankfully it doesn't happen
often really rarely
actually when I'm in a long long long
distance flight to Japan or so and the
person next to me is a guy with a [\h__\h]
ton of cologne
on oh but I feel like you guys might
feel the same way the other way around
some women also put on way too much
perfume I don't like that
either especially depending on the
perfume but yeah it's just both ways
really
uncomfortable like if you go somewhere
where you know like an airplane a long
airplane ride if you know you're going
to be on there and you might be
bothering people if your smile please
realize that not everybody likes like
really strong perfume or
cologne not everybody likes that but I
feel like when you get used to it you
don't understand anymore that you're
smelling really strong with
that and that not everybody likes it you
just don't realize it it's just natural
to
[Music]
you I you read for a plane red maybe to
cover up this uh sweat that you just so
happen to produce on airports it just
happens it's honestly happens to me a
lot
too but the good thing is I love love
for long distance flight they usually
give you a like a hot towel a wet towel
in the beginning and then even like
several
times but it depends actually in I
noticed in economy class they might not
give it to you depending on the
airline but yeah I've been getting it
recently always and then I I wipe first
I wipe my face it helps especially when
I'm tired they give it to you after the
sleepy time before breakfast and that
really wakes me up really good but when
I get the towel in the beginning of the
flight when I just arrive I like wipe my
face and then I quickly wipe like under
my arms armpits and yeah just quickly R
WIP WIP WIP WIP if I'm
[Music]
sweaty honestly I don't know sometimes
sometimes I I don't know like in
restaurants in Japan it's obviously for
the hands but if I get it in a in a
airplane I'm not sure what the real
intended purpose
[Music]
is I'm not sure if they give it to you
for your hands or for your face I feel
like it could be all of it whatever you
want to do with it I feel like it's
really helpful for like in a in an
airplane if you're in there for 12 hours
or so you might want to wash your face
but might be kind of difficult so having
a a face towel that smells nice often it
smells nice to wipe your face cuz like
your know face might get greasy or I
don't
know disgusting throughout the flight
too so I feel like it has a lot of
purposes just to refresh your face after
a
disgustingly long
and dry or humid or hot
flight an Ana flights ah depends not
sure I haven't FL flown flown with Ana
uh from Europe to Japan in a long time
but I think in some cases it's also just
like uh like the really thin paper towel
the wet paper towel that they give you
that's in like in a sealed package but
then in other cases they give you an
actual fluffy
towel that's what I've been getting
recently and they're really nice you
just likeo whoo refresh a little
bit an know is great
yeah but I said this yesterday in my
members only stream I have to say
Turkish Airlines food really was
good it was surprisingly [\h__\h]
good one of the best airline Foods I've
ever had besides surprisingly Austrian
airin but this is only talking about
business class now although I do think
Austrian Airline uh Turkish Island I
think their economy food is probably
also pretty
good I think I think their economy food
might be pretty good
too Island food usually
me yeah
recently this is really just because
business class but yeah business class
food is decent really good actually but
it's probably not an economy I don't
know anymore what's going on in the
economy I I think in summer I might have
a
few premium economy flights again just
recently I had a luck streak of business
flights which I didn't pay for any of
them it's the only reason why I flew
with business cuz I didn't have to pay
for
them yeah all all all of the recent
flights are business thank
God I've been pampered and spoiled
feeling really nice now I got so used to
[Music]
it but in
summer when I fly to Japan I don't think
I'll get a business flight but maybe I
can upgrade I actually accumulated a lot
of miles now because thank God business
class flights I got the miles from them
and they give a lot of
miles I might have enough miles to
[Music]
upgrade I might have to
yeah what's worse Japan summer Tha
summer Tha
summer but Japan summer also bad Japan
summer can also get to 40 C with humid
heat very humid Japan is just as
[Music]
humid but still Tai is worse
yeah spring but it was like no you say
spring but no that was definitely
crazy an exception not really Spring
weather I think what I experienced there
zley Dan Jackson d m Dan I a che beep
Dan and Jim Tracy
[Music]
D
okay next St you
[Music]
Valley maybe I'll continue start your
Valley as a member
stream oh by the way speaking of member
streams oh yesterday I looked at
mon collection Blu-rays and all that
holy [\h__\h] there's like nothing that
arrives
immediately
uh I ordered one big box of like 10
seasons I
think I think it's not including the
bakon season
but anyway I'll get that separately but
I bought it all over 100
bucks um but the the arrival window
first of all is really rough no there's
not any services that stream it legally
nothing legal there's it's un crunchable
it's not on
no not for Europe at
least not for Austria I can't I don't
think I've Been Told by you guys too oh
and I checked as well doesn't seem like
there's any
Austrian way of Legally streaming it so
yeah I bought it but uh it arrives
probably
end very very very end of May to the
first we and first two weeks of June
[Music]
maybe it will oh yeah it will take a
while I don't think it would be so hard
to get
it but it's okay we'll get through
it that's
[Music]
okay want to share Plex accounts what
there's any Plex
accounts they have a streaming service
[Music]
I think we can finish in one month I'll
be busy in June no I don't think so I'll
be busy in
June I be busy in July not in June I
think even July not so bad no first week
of July or so H I think it'll be
[Music]
fun birthday month yeah but I'm not
like okay well I'll still be busy in
July probably yeah but birthday month
for me you know I'm not doing the
birthday life on the birthday day
so will I be stressed in June am I
forgetting
something no I think
July like starting maybe end
of I think I'll be fine we'll have time
yeah I'll do weekends of
course two M streams a week
[Music]
yeah and then I might take a break from
Member streams for a while though I
don't
know we'll see it'll be
[Music]
fine I mean we also don't have to watch
every season maybe that's a season we
can skip because it wasn't so important
I don't know was there such a
season I'd like to watch it all but was
there anything we could possibly skip I
don't remember it's been too long if
there was anything
skippable the movies no we don't have
time for the
movies maybe ni black you mean
the N mon
one they're all important I know the
movies are
good is probably the only one we can
skip in my
opinion
a I wonder if that's even included in my
bundle my
[Music]
bundle has
seasons oh okay it's NE monar white NE
monar black
and so it's obviously
missing
and yeah n where's n what the [\h__\h] how
about I just have you guys uh do this as
homework I also rewatch it but we will
rewatch it on our own
uh
bakak
and we'll all watch on our own and then
the others will watch
together I know those are like some of
the best ones
[Music]
though but then we can get a head
start because the other ones like I
couldn't really
find anything to buy like okay wait this
arriv
really late but
yeah okay there's this Blu-ray
collection it says collection but I
think it's
just yeah it's just the one
season I guess H I could order it it
arrives end of the month
too not quite end of the month actually
the LA second to last week or so
no okay I'll add it and then I
[Music]
need this a France
import is it going to be
English I think all of these are
generally Japanese and I think they have
English subtitles the
[Music]
Blu-rays has Amazon Prime
I could get that one really fast but why
not the others wait who's selling
this this one
[Music]
is one and two is prime but I think
that's the only Prime
ones when I would have to buy it on its
own n it's okay we got to wait we go to
wait there's nothing
Prim so
it's like 40
bucks
[Music]
sheesh uh
languages no subtitles are fra French
only
uh I have really good Japanese but
like anime it's really
rough oh uh is it really only French the
[\h__\h] the other one
is the other one should be fine yeah
Japanese and English subtitles okay the
Bak is fine I need to find a different n
monar man can you guys send me one do
you have one left
[Music]
over [\h__\h] ah wait this one
one oh but no it's not
available it's out of
stock I don't know if I can
get I also don't think I have any
friends who own the
[Music]
DVD well I'll figure it
out I'll figure it
out I also still have to get proper
permission to do this by the way because
apparently when it's like a
series like a long watch along of like
like this apparently I have to ask for
permission is like a weird
rule just because uh something about it
being being interpreted as like I'm like
maybe it looks like it's like I'm
claiming it's my own property or so I
don't [\h__\h] know I don't get
it we'll see I don't understand yeah I'm
not showing it obviously no but I think
I think it's because like it
apparently people might
think I don't know it makes no sense
whatever
[Music]
okay here we go stard
Valley take 47 D cakes k py d you ex
thank you twice no wait more oh [\h__\h]
played this in 2017 it's amazing how
much a developer has added that it feels
like a different game really multiplayer
is new to me so I've been playing it
again with my Bes te yes who lives on
the opposite side of the world from me
nice we both get really into it and
sometimes lose track of time it's funny
I told her you'll be playing so she
might be watching the stream too was she
hope you have fun wa and maybe try to
play it with Mama Someday I'm sure she'd
like that also I got a bonus from work
so here's a little house warming present
for you thank you you bought another
frogy plus let's
[Music]
go thank you very much
yix thank you that's very sweet of you I
give you a kiss M I can't do math right
now but I think it may at least all
almost be a red
one yeah H I don't know I was even
thinking a little bit about playing with
mamaon on stream for one stream maybe
but then I'd have to make a new world
right we both have to make a new
world and I feel like it's it's not as
easy as with
Minecraft because h
yeah yes I don't
know I think it's more difficult don't
no don't get excited about it I don't
think I'll do
it
[Music]
n you just need to have a cabin built to
turn your map multiplayer ahuh oh an
existing one oh
really yeah I still don't know how I
feel about
it because that's more like you know
with narissa and so on like they play
multiplayer with other members because
you know they can make it like a
long-term project and all that
um but I don't really want to do a
long-term project like that with uh you
know if it's a oneoff stream that would
be fine but for a oneoff stream is maybe
not even I don't know if there's a point
because
like I don't know how how to explain
this just doesn't feel
right no just play with your own Mama
guys don't be so greedy play with your
own
mommy M ate things the pinky if you
girls still have any interested in the
grand blue collab the final update is
out at the end of May oh so that would
be a good time for it and there's new
characters to use have fun and start
your T you would watch out for losing
track of time I did several times oh it
was more like like also losing track of
my
stamina I did message uh I think Zeda
and asked her if she still plans on
continuing it and she said yeah oh she's
playing it again she did like recently
okay great yeah she she told me also
that she's plan planning on continuing
it
so
anybody can keep track if she's
finishing it let me
know then we can do the collab although
it feels weird like it feels like ages
ago that I
played it will be weird to go back into
it just one stream away oh nice nice try
NOA D John EG D thank you for watching
while you're
[Music]
working oh someone just going
to oh yeah it's r come on let's read
together St thank you tapall Kon thank
you for the r chat it's been a year
since I've been part of kfb and want to
thank you for being my Kam iie I also
saw you at Hol Fest 5 five was it
already fifth
one fifth and teared up on stage which
was the perfect way to celebrate my one
year anniversary was it fifth one really
I thought it was the fourth one or
[Music]
so it was a one year anniversary it C be
during F sheesh thank you for making my
days just that much more
brighter wait you you don't mean you
were there in person right you went you
watched it online right or were you one
of the people who went in
person no I think I guess it was fifth
Fest yeah now that you guys are saying
it makes sense you were there in person
too oh nice did you hang out with the
other
[Music]
kfp I hope you did there's not so much
chances to do
[Music]
that I was there too oh my god let's go
that sounds like so much
fun the Norr lights are all pink in
Europe I don't think I can ever see Norr
lights
here we don't have Norr lights in
Austria that would be
crazy I'd love to see that though it was
[Music]
solar FL flares made them more visible
sof really I'll check after the stream
is over which is soon oh my God it's so
late already
[\h__\h] okay let me hurry for this thank
you tap G cap I'm so happy we thank you
for supporting me for a long time yay I
hope you had
fun maybe you'll go again next
year Brian hitchner hak T MP5 fre
Ben naon for the pinky heyo hope you
enjoyed this nice relaxing game about
chicken care yeah it's all about the
chickens who cares about those girls
that reject me even the boys who cares
about them I only care about my chickens
I don't have quite the hours that your
mother has put in but i' heartly
recommended at over 1 hour 100 hours
locked
myself amateur beginner
[Music]
Noob weak I'm not taking advice from
you I have Mama
Tony I'm only listening to her because
otherwise she's probably going to Bunk
me
anyway uh I don't know 100 hours doesn't
sound like much in comparison to my
mommy but I guess 100 hours yeah when I
think about how long I've played like
Yakuza games and so on I guess it is a
lot but compared to my mommy weak weak
game weak
Nathan
[Music]
weak Sky Dan Cruz Danish Dy Danish shaie
boy d rainard
d probably not at least not for a single
maybe for an
album Dusty d d Ryan H thanks thanks for
the pinky I got married last week I
snuck in P ah right this super chat I
snuck in pineapple during the reception
holy [\h__\h] congratulations again
wow
wow good job with the pineapple I don't
know if pineapple was the best choice
but um any W song is a good choice I
guess thanks for the rain
P cute cute cute cute cute cute
so
cute isn't doesn't she have like super
cute
eyebrows yeah I love her
eyebrows I want those
eyebrows where was
I last last track Dusty D D
[Music]
D ah yeah she's a Italian I
forgot let's
[Music]
go I am fluent in Italian of course
no like actually like I mean that was
not bad I have some
vocabulary yeah it's just very Hotel
focused
Italian thank you
f [\h__\h] what wait uh
[Music]
what uh how do I say thank you again I'm
thinking of other languages in my head
right now
[Music]
there's of course yeah I know it but
right now I bled blanked out
[Music]
okay I have to hurry guys oh my God I
have to cook I have to cook it's so late
[\h__\h] anite I didn't try that no I saw it
too
late what the [\h__\h] is
that oh man some kind of what is this
what is this it looks
decent
damn [\h__\h] thank you for the membership
gift next time yeah I think there will
be next time
eventually probably not until next year
but
yeah iron
soon wdp
soon
oh you got Mike thanks for the pinky I'm
going to haid for a week this thur day
oh oh allow me to welcome you to
Thailand in advance it's 40 C every day
even at night I'm sweating but I hope
you'll enjoy the trip got get some nice
massage and food like stick your eyes of
mongle I did get two
massages one on the day of my arrival
and one on the day of my
departure and in between there was only
one day so my massage ratio was pretty
high
and it was yeah
actually I feel like in the evening the
heat was uh actually
bearable there was one day where I felt
like it was even kind of un
comfortable but yeah generally the
nights are hot
[Music]
too were you happy after the massages
well not in whatever way you're implying
but uh they were really good yeah they
were really good like the I noticed
there were no like unnecessary moves you
know like
often in the massages I get there's like
some good moves and some that are like
me I'm like okay move on when is she
moving
on but in these ones yeah it's it felt
really
efficient every move was like a good one
somewhere
even
magnificent yeah so good and so [\h__\h]
cheap oil are traditional I had one that
was oil and one that was traditional tie
on the floor with
cloes the oil one was a bit more like
fancy style in in the hotel and the
other one was just in a random although
very
popular seemingly very popular CU very
busy cuz probably in the middle of like
a city
center uh massage place they were so
popular
damn so many people in there never was a
massage store whatever before that was
so
crowded and the lady that massaged me
spoke zero
English
uh and she was kind of cute though and I
feel like we were communicating through
you know just
[Music]
noises she would really hurt me
sometimes and I'd be
like and she's like and then she just
laughed she just laughed at me so many
[Music]
times but it was good anyway and she was
kind of sweet she's like a mommy like a
mothering type of
person I don't know I felt like I she
was really sweet though even though I
couldn't
communicate really good really
good uh J Monkey D CH d d Jim Tracy Dan
space water Dan smelly Mayo Dan np15 fre
G thanks to Red pay my bill I can't I
just spent it on Super Chat fellow C
peace please follow my good
example no no KP
don't don't don't please don't do
anything stupid be careful but thank you
garlics I appreciate it very generous of
you
m always spoiling the WWA Nathan thanks
for the red super chat also YouTube was
telling to send a red to but I can't
imagine why though wait what was going
on what what was happening did I ask you
guys to do that thank
you SW dun Dan dun looking for the top
dun zly Dan Chase wber T and Elie Lain
T oh I was becoming invisible that's
what you mean with empty
[Music]
chair sometimes the Super Chat button
flashes
[Music]
red
randomly just like to remind you that it
exists or what that's
random for fit all Earthly possessions
to the
vtu yes yes
yes okay I got to go my FR hurts and I
got to go but this was a lot of fun
let's do it again next week maybe if I
can't think of anything else to
play and tomorrow H talk at the usual H
talk time more or less 10 p.m. jst 300
p.m. wa
time yeah see you there thank you for
watching I'm going to make dinner now
with
asparagus so excited for asparagus let's
go
asparagus bye-bye
[Music]
as H talk with water Miss Senai