[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
I know you're ready
come on
[Music]
nevermind
thank you
[Music]
easy studies
foreign
[Music]
thank you
TV
[Music]
sit down
there
[Music]
I am
right here we're here
[Applause]
[Music]
hi everybody
[Applause]
welcome everybody to the hollow man
pretty collapse okay
hello
yes yes
with some greetings
[Music]
let's go Kelly
[Applause]
um
Amazon
[Applause]
hi so everybody this is our special
showcase we just performed the classic
shiny slime
how was that I like it it was fun
nervous but we made it it was difficult
though practicing that one because we
had to practice so many things
we can see the chat
foreign
[Music]
is better
hi speaking of our individual showcases
up until this day everybody have them
the first one was how was that to go
first I was so nervous I learned
everything to go you know perfectly so
because that's like a really good mood
for everyone
[Music]
yeah yes stage
foreign
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
everybody
what are we doing
I don't know this is a special occasion
isn't it we're in here together properly
for the first time right look at these
bodies these beautiful bodies
[Music]
like this so we're gonna make the most
out of this occasion yes with we have
two games that we'll be playing games
you want more like that Chinese friend
story right you want more yes yes yes
until the very end of the stream you
might see one
it's worth it
okay well cool then I think we should
start with the first game shall we
what we're going somewhere no huh
okay
yeah why not okay yes not the game okay
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
all right well I need to investigate all
of you closely because now we're in 3D
and now we can't did you do something
[Music]
oh God
it's not real it's possible
turn around turn around
wow
[Music]
you are the one that's gonna get this
channel
so we'll take a picture of the front
face
a photo for all the questions
[Music]
the back yeah
[Applause]
this one
down here that's too short get in there
[Music]
me yeah don't be too short that's what
it is what are you talking about short
stack yeah you want to go
but
uh pretty good all right let's have a
closer look at that thing
back there what this thing it's kind of
smelly
take a picture of this but let's take a
picture of the front first okay in front
oh my mug shot okay yeah mug shot time
stay right here all right Calliope more
come into the frame please
why am I involved with it I did nothing
is she a Lost Child I need to compare
Heights sorry about that sorry I should
have walked into you for a minute there
look at the High stuff first
[Music]
all right all right Chuck get out of
here all right see you later guys
what did I do
um
well I guess I did kill everyone on the
planet admit to it okay but that's my
job okay all right okay let me use sex
around here oh I love these shoes
[Applause]
[Music]
you did something you're being booked
and uh we're gonna take your picture
first so face the front please I'm the
most innocent one here I think she has a
weapons
no weapons I didn't bring it today
look at that all right the side profile
get out of here you're going downtown
okay last the most offensive crimes
against humanity
she's definitely the most yes
I'm innocent really yeah really yeah
because too many buns your crime
[Music]
is there something there
that's dangerous
because she's so cute
she put them away
okay
I'll free you after this I swear I'm
sorry I didn't mean that that's cool
all right side profile please how could
she commit any terrible questions
all right I need to test something for
science okay give me a moment
okay oh boy
what is that
um I need to do a scientific dunk
no Ina stay I need you to stay still I
promise you
dunk yeah
[Music]
okay all right one more one more do the
dunk clean dunk
[Applause]
in okay okay all right that could be the
investigation I'll free you for now no
it doesn't no we have one more left
so
you're not getting away from us
get
down
things
[Music]
what do we arrest you what do you guys
look interesting
because
there's nothing there they can't see it
I can't see it
but they wish they could well we should
take some yeah
okay
no no look at that face sideways
all right what are we looking for I've
never commit a crime investigating us
with us
this footage investigated later yeah
we have to actually go by the script
okay enough of this
um
I need those
so everybody are you ready for some fun
I'm up for anything the first game that
we're playing today is
telephone charade
since we're here in the highest quality
of 3D you want to show it off to you
guys with this special game I will
explain the rules to you guys okay rules
rules rules I love rules
right the first person uh we're gonna
stand in the in a line okay and the
first person on the ever the most right
hand or the most left-hand side will get
a clue that everybody else doesn't get
to see we have to close our eyes yes and
then the person Taps on the next
person's shoulder and they may open
their eyes and they act well for example
with Kelly's first call is first she
will act out
and then we only have 30 seconds for
that and there's no talking allowed so
how will that go I wonder you gotta do
your best to show everything with your
body okay okay okay so we'll go by the
order of Cali please other rides oh yeah
over there you're perfectly in the spot
okay and then Amy please
[Music]
I'm looking
oh boy
this is gonna be interesting
got it no talking 30 seconds can I turn
around
can I turn I think so all right oh okay
check this out I'm not lucky
[Laughter]
oh
oh okay okay that makes it okay oh it
makes sense I think I'm ready I think
I'm ready okay all right yeah look okay
do your best yeah
very nice yeah keep it up oh I think I
get it it's like it you ready to go on I
don't know
okay okay okay
thank you
put your back into it
you got a really nice okay okay I got it
you got it nice legs
foreign
[Applause]
I would say that is a mating dance
are you serious yes
what part of that looked anything like
amazing chance amazing dance
was mine was I
oh
what did you think it was grew up what
do you think yeah what did you think it
was yeah
um uh interpretive dance
well I I thought it was swimming that's
what I thought so that's more like
drowning
okay okay yeah well Sean
the answer is octopus
well okay okay that was okay I guess but
we'll do a second round all right okay
we'll switch up the order so who wants
to go first
oh I'll fix what you couldn't tell I do
not want to be like today
okay Family Mart the next one however
will be more like a situation rather
than an animal or whatever and you guys
will not see the answer either until the
end so have fun guessing with us all
right everybody get it right chat close
your eyes
I think I got it I think I got it oh
okay okay you can turn around Cali okay
what do we got no talking
[Music]
oh got it that's kind of cute okay
yeah open your eyes hi okay
[Music]
oh I mean you're making noises though
I'll forgive that one's not talking
[Music]
I mean okay yeah all I have to do is
what are you doing to me
is that it
is
cute okay
all right
[Music]
okay yeah it seems easy what is it
genius
memory sleepy sleeping
okay
a little more to it
situation
[Music]
okay well okay so the correct one is
falling asleep
okay so we got both wrong
[Music]
I got two pillows right here
comfortable
[Music]
good try everybody
yeah
but it was pretty close the second one
we did yes
um we'll say half correct we have 0.5
points
did you guys enjoy doing the chat
episode
yeah well that's what I was saying no
way
don't you dare you and I'm kidding okay
well with that I think we're gonna play
the next game right away
[Music]
all right
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
the game of course it also is Japanese
inspired but before we get started with
that I want to hear some episodes
because we all are now together in Japan
some of us for the first time some of us
maybe for the second time some of us
flying for the Hunger of time oh but I
think we're all kind of well some kind
of culture shock right now that's true
yeah surely we all have something like
that Japan is very different so anybody
got something oh I do oh I do sometimes
I gotta take a taxi
um for various reasons whenever I do
though um the taxi dude is always like
okay so what's our route like huh what
do you mean what's our route I'm gonna
leave it up to you he's like we'll take
this street and then we'll take this
highway is that okay yeah that's fine
and then when you get off we'll pick
this street but this street is a little
far so we're gonna take this street is
that okay
I'm speaking of taxis you know how you
know when you try to open the door from
the taxi because normally you do that in
my country they say like no no please
don't touch it we're opening it
automatically so please stop don't touch
them when you want to get out same thing
it always opens automatically I'm like
oh okay I got used to it now but it's
nice when you have a lot of stuff in
your hands though because the door
that's true that's germ free any other
episodes
here are insane they're crazy
but it's fun it's like an adventure
yeah I'm worried about you you get lost
a lot indeed hello
you guys all follow me in like a single
file
yeah
because one time you walk too far ahead
and we were like oh yeah
speaking of trains another thing I
noticed with the trains is that uh in my
country everybody's like loud and they
all wake and they're they scream and
listen to music but in Japan they're all
quiet and they look they're sleeping yes
yeah it's really sick very very great
right I'm not scared to talk and how do
people not hold on to the things they
just stand there yeah
hold on to well I can't really I hope I
I was like
any other episodes
oh oh there's lots of there's lots of
text everywhere like I said yeah science
and it's crazy and it's fun to test to
see what I can and cannot read which is
good I wish I could read all of it
because I'm very overwhelming though
right it is but it's also fun because
it's something I've never experienced
I'm sorry I took her on one of her first
days I I took her to the most
overwhelming source
[Applause]
on my door and like open the door for
them they're like the little bow I'm
just like oh they're so polite even like
even I'm not in front of them and like
you know what they usually have like a
little little message they can send when
they say like thanks for the tip yeah
everyone says thanks for the tip and I'm
just like I've never seen this before
they are so full
[Music]
wow those are some nice uh stories
you've got for me thank you very much
yeah we're gonna play the game to
hopefully learn even more about Japanese
cultures
is
it called what is it called it's not
written there anymore yeah the queen of
um
[Music]
[Applause]
the rules are we get one theme one
situation or something like that and
then uh with the theme it comes four
different choices that could be even
wrong or correct there's one wrong one
and we'll have them be acted out by
[Music]
we'll decide together we put our head
together and we'll think which one is
wrong all right okay YouTube chat let's
go let's
[Music]
and before that you always have to take
off your shoes and like a lot of like
buildings too they usually have like
spare slippers yeah
yeah
I've actually tripped on one of those
where it's got like
this
next up
[Music]
um
someone's talking with short phrases
such as yes
[Laughter]
to me because I want to say after living
in Japan
more and more I noticed that I was you
know getting that into my body and when
I came back home to Austria my all my
family my friends they noticed
you keep on reacting to what I'm saying
oh yes yes so but actually I can't get
rid of it anymore
especially like when you're talking on
the phone and stuff like I don't know if
you're still listening right yeah
[Laughter]
so did you girls also start doing that
on your own but yeah
okay
[Music]
separating tissues depending on your
usage all right Kiara this one's for you
you're the one that's been blowing your
nose
this is true exposed I'm not too sure
about I don't think this is separate is
this like separating the trash like the
garbage and recycling they separate the
trash a lot yeah but they like the
tissues I'm like
playing this game are we doing something
wrong no we are all old things
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
yeah
I'm digging in and go to so means thank
you for the meal okay
[Music]
yeah so the wrong one is numbers
we don't even need a second round
[Applause]
[Music]
there's something important that
everybody needs to pay attention to but
oh and listening we want to show off our
merchandise one more time
that's right everybody in their
individual showcases already showed up
their individual merch we'll take a look
at it and now we're time we'll start
with yeah okay
my merch was
I think there's a few people who don't
know how to use it basically when you
you know cook cup noodles and the lid
kind of like always like lifts up you
put that little taco around and stuff on
top of it so that the lift the you know
the lid lid doesn't lift
and then you you look like the most
perfectly cooked Ramen you know cup
noodles or you know you can just keep it
at the figure
yeah so my merchandise was
a bottle and bottle okay
I'm so happy for this one because it's
famous everybody can use it you can keep
your hot wings hot and you call things
cold it's perfect it even has a little
blue button is it thermal this is
you can basically use the cap as a cup
too big
brains yeah
a lovely gift for your significant other
perhaps you just want to look cool
wherever you go anyone can wear this
cool piece of ice what is it is a baby
you can also just display it in your
house because why not why not why not
I'm genuinely asking you why not buy it
or I'll hurt you baby
thank you everyone appreciate you okay
[Music]
yeah
bug there it is tell us about it
what kind of bag is it got a bag
[Music]
with strap it's so cute
what is it inspired after my
is my casual that's right
does that thing you're wearing now
yeah it's like someone stole your
sweater and made a bag out of it yeah
let me
let me come on over hey
sit down there we go oh my God
I'm wearing right now
on sale today
weird stuff with it like smell it I want
it yes
[Applause]
[Music]
there's more
what do we got
oh
wow we have acrylic dance Too these will
be out on sale March 5th right after
this stream please check the shop page
for details let's take a look at them
we can all do our poses yeah oh yeah I'm
holding an invisible book
okay opposed pose wait pose baby pose
wait give it your best lady you can do
it nice yay so if you want these at home
you can buy them together or you can buy
them separately however you want wow
yeah they look really cute yeah
what do you guys think about this yeah
okay how was it so far guys everybody
yeah
[Applause]
can we
go
um
[Music]
[Applause]
this just cool out maybe pick up some
comments how's it going guys did you
post some screenshots
[Music]
[Applause]
because I promise you pinky promise that
there will be more that's right
now a performance one or two who knows
it's coming up all right but we gotta go
to the stage for that okay we're going
already which way is it I don't know
thank you
[Music]
which way are we going yeah
foreign
[Music]
from time and time again take my hand
and enter our
[Music]
please
it is
[Music]
[Applause]
it's our story
[Music]
[Applause]
the Stars
[Music]
we breathe
ter
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
across the skies
memories
[Music]
the strawberries
for me and my friends
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you