foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
hello ID cop 2023.
[Music]
all right
um I'm gonna I'm gonna do a little
speech for you guys
um
all right all right thank you thank you
okay
um as you guys know oh wow this is the
second year of Holo ID card 2023 and I
would like to say thank you to all of
you guys who've been accepting to play
with us
and trying all the games that's been
setting for this year
um and also
um I would like to say thank you to
ollie and rainy for being the emcee
today
foreign
[Applause]
for do a lot of practice so yeah it's
really helpful for me too and well
that's all I just want you guys to have
fun for today let's go
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah nervous and after this what do we
have after this rainy
well we're gonna be having a captain
speech from each of the team
so if we can get the leaders to come up
here please
[Music]
okay what if I shift shift all right are
you kidding me
[Music]
it will be it will probably be chaos
chaos
[Applause]
[Music]
and
next we have risu
please
okay
I'm ready
[Music]
so yeah let's let's have fun today
[Applause]
yeah I love our team leader who is risu
our team thank you I love you too
[Music]
pictures
we saw the leaders and then it's now
time for the full introduction of each
team we can start with
Monday morning
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
Bay Bay
up to you hey do you want to go first oh
okay what's up
[Music]
[Applause]
okay hello everyone I'm Anya let's have
fun today
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
all right
next would be a gray senpai
[Music]
first teams three times
who is hitting me
with your service let me be yours
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
today
bye yes nice nice
nice nice
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you thank you thank you thank you
and next
to introduce himself
[Music]
clean Spirit okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
I'm nervous thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
oh sorry
next we have Kyla oh hello hi everyone
my name is
[Music]
next
Kelly Mommy
let's do our best
number one let's party I'm energetic
Yankee let's go
real cool yeah thanks I know
um it's currently 6 a.m
oh my God
and I am gonna be at badminton and
soccer
[Music]
we have Mona
co-founder series funnel from hollow
life English Council thank you for not
putting me on the soccer team
[Music]
I will be in capture the fort and also
the potato sack race okay
[Music]
we have soda Senpai dosa
hello uh
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
Laura
yay
[Music]
um
[Applause]
wow
that's four that's all for team for TV
right yes
but you know other than like introducing
the members I kind of want to hear
something more don't you think yeah good
idea yeah
everybody come up with their own team
cheers
[Music]
are you ready let's go
so after me I'm gonna start okay okay
okay okay
three two one
five five
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
that was so good yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
let's go
let's go let's go okay okay okay okay
two one second
[Music]
hi
um
[Music]
[Applause]
everybody
[Music]
oh my God
thank you
for the fiery yeah yeah
[Music]
what do we do after this
okay then
[Applause]
wow
[Music]
so the even today
um we're gonna play a lot of games
starting from capture the fort or we
call it bentengan and after that we move
to the potato Cypress and after that we
go tug of war and then after that we
have badminton uh from the a side and
then badminton from a b side and also
after that we have soccer
cool
[Music]
cheese so that's all I hope you guys
having fun for today yeah
now it's it's time for you guys to uh I
think it's back to the interview
actually
yes
[Music]
thank you
hello hello hello hello
[Music]
please
we'll be watching closely no pressure
let's go let's go no pressure no
pressure yes we're watching and you have
to win for us but no pressure okay
um
[Music]
you can watch from here oh yeah we can
watch from right here wait where are
they where do you watch it from
[Music]
there's some seats over there but this
is a nice view actually okay
we can just walk around I guess
whoa Archer
okay okay
cool
sorry sorry sorry sorry
got a little too playful
foreign
[Music]
hello
yeah let's go
it's interviewing time okay
what are you most afraid of of the other
team not
there any special tactics that you're
you know yes secretly cooking yes yes
yes okay so it's like they're so ready
for this game
[Music]
oh
what is your tactic kailashing we have
we have see we have we have secret
tactics that we cannot tell here
yeah because there's gonna be a lot of
sneakers out there yourselves right yeah
audience
yeah you guys will see yeah
seems like you guys have secret Secrets
yeah yeah
I wish you guys the best of luck
okay okay goodbye
let's go
home
um
so yeah I will tell fauna in advance oh
I I've already I've already told fauna
before him
[Music]
is this like three two one
um division uh-huh so basically one
person go to left and three person go to
the right yeah oh okay it's just like
all attacking instead of one defending
no lead
yeah new track for this game but we
believe that we have remembered the
route
[Music]
okay
let's go ready ready I wanna watch
oh
[Music]
how do you zoom again in here I forgot Z
I want to see
okay okay
let's go let's go
[Music]
okay
oh we start already
[Music]
go go
later
we will meet someone okay we will meet
someone but it's okay
they are gamers
[Music]
thank you
that was quick
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
like we thought they wouldn't really use
the middle yeah because we because we
passed that already last night but yeah
okay
so
um
[Music]
but we were like there's a lot of um
success
Hold On music changed me
tactics
[Music]
okay okay
oh it's getting crazy
[Music]
all right
don't hold back don't hold back to hit
him all right
[Music]
give me in the actions
that's good that is vital right
oh
[Music]
interview interview
I think the interview is taking longer
than the game itself
[Applause]
oh whoopsies that's not what I wanted to
do so many chickens oh my God okay
potato race
[Music]
foreign
oh
let's get the other side
[Music]
oh I went to the wrong place
I'm a bit of a dummy okay sorry okay
[Music]
thank God for that that would have been
tough
let's go
be crazy this way I accidentally fell I
think you can you can go
away
okay A little Direction okay
ready good Callie I'm ready I'm perfect
amazing amazing okay again with the
freaking music change oh it's still okay
for now okay okay okay let's go let's go
let's go
okay let's go
don't give up 30 win you guys are great
never give up ready whoa
oh what's in here rope is big oh what
it's bigger
[Music]
the door is opening if you like press on
that
cool oh
man
[Music]
I believe in you
foreign
[Music]
okay thank you
thank you let's just run for now I think
okay just practice practice
warm up warm up warming up
rolling up yes yeah
stuck
[Music]
far strong in the pot right
the pot
he's in her element
[Applause]
I don't know
oh
[Music]
okay okay it's fine it's fine let's go
let's go guys yeah this is the berries
okay
[Music]
not anymore
yeah but you guys were doing really
great yeah
yeah we were watching and we were in uh
we'll be back to you guys soon okay okay
one more and more
yeah
no problem you can do it it's doing
really great okay I'll try to keep it up
no pressure
I mean at least as they're like first
and second our teams
what did you do
ready ready
watching from above
oh yeah I'm gonna go for I'm gonna go
above to win
check it out the Beats look let's go
around while watching
yeah we're watching for everything
foreign
you must look at it
the guys
[Music]
thank you I'm sorry guys uh we had to
restart the race because of connection
issues it's also are bad because we
didn't really make it clear beforehand
but after this after this race in the
other competitions if there are
connection issues uh I think to also to
make it fair for everybody uh we will
not be restarting oh okay in the
competition so um
just wanted to keep everybody on the
same page thank you okay no problem
thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
thank you
go let's go
Thomas
let's go let's go let's go let's go nice
come on
[Music]
oh my God
foreign
[Music]
let's go
oh
come on the game yeah
[Music]
nice nice
let's go
[Music]
it's okay okay
don't worry about it
okay it's okay
you did your best that's all that
matters you guys were fast plus I mean
okay we had the two fastest people
though let's be real so it is I feel
good
it's okay
[Music]
you're amazing
I believe
that said three candies oh my God
it was oh my God I shouldn't have read
that
I don't know how to explain it in
Japanese man
hey
that was good okay okay okay okay okay
okay
don't forget to hydrate guys
what what is after this
oh my God
[Music]
oh boy
me too
I mean I won't be here but you're gonna
be out there
just thinking about it as like making
making ramen Ramen
um
[Music]
yeah the other other person
thank you yeah yeah let's go oh
no problem
for anyone who wants to watch can go up
so I think everybody's already I think
we can fly later on when we watch yeah
yeah we can fly oh
[Music]
um not now not now when it's now yeah
when it starts when it starts
hi
okay okay okay
[Music]
I'm gonna do my best
I hope my mouse
yeah you can do it you can do it
oh I I
had this okay
let's go
this is the time where I think I hope my
mouse can get like double clicked what
it's all day
[Music]
no problem no problem okay
wow wow
[Music]
warm him up
moving up warming up
[Music]
[Applause]
are you ready yes
yes
everybody's
let's go let's go
a little bit
oh
here we go
let's go where am I okay
we can fly we can't fly
again
[Music]
come on
let's go
[Music]
[Applause]
crazy
[Music]
[Applause]
so much
[Music]
[Applause]
yo good job I'm not gonna I'm not gonna
lie um I actually thought we were losing
because when I was practicing we were
fighting I was red team
winner go to this I'll explain later I
thought we were losing
[Music]
that kitty cat I hear a mouse
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
it was so awesome so awesome so awesome
so awesome
[Music]
temperatures
okay okay
[Music]
oh yeah
oh God
look at this okay okay
let's go let's go
okay
thank you we can do it we can win this
[Music]
oh yeah
Kiara and Kyla the badminton yeah
[Music]
it's kind of like went somewhere again
you're a a
oh let's go let's go we can do this we
can do this okay okay you got this no
problem
yeah yeah
no pressure I already win the game for
you yeah
yes you were so good I was watching you
while I was cooking you should have won
honestly
I'm proud yes
you're a legendary yeah let's go oh yeah
you go he also win one the finger uh
competitions
good job good job
but I still wanna play
I'll stay in the front yes yes
finger competition oh you can watch
who's that Strat
ton
at the back I'll protect the frogs
[Music]
yeah ready ready
I'll try to stay calm you'll be fine
I'm not actually in the club already in
the ball already fell to the ground you
can actually yeah just Spam just like
that we have practice so much about this
okay
I will see you
are crazy at this game who knows I don't
know you guys practiced a lot so just
don't worry it will be okay
so if you if you feel frustrated just
shout like a real sport
ready yeah
[Music]
okay I believe
first
okay okay ready ready guys get ready
okay
let's go
[Music]
they could shoot any moment now okay
there we go
oh nice nice
[Music]
best backup oh
good job good job good defense
no problem it's out it's out it's out
yep
[Music]
it's on your side it's on your side
don't worry you're doing great
nice save
[Music]
don't worry don't worry don't worry
though don't worry it's out it's out
it's out
yeah
the
wrong side yeah okay
you have to hit the yeah
[Applause]
for the first hits after the first hit
you can hit wherever you want yes
I'll take it
okay
[Music]
I'll take it
so far it's so fun
don't worry oh
okay totally winnable
[Music]
okay
my name
last one
let's go
[Applause]
[Music]
we'll take it again
you guys definitely got no problem
will there be an interview in wado not
yet I think after this
let's go let's go let's win this
come please
[Music]
oh
I believe
okay
[Music]
okay okay
wait
yeah yeah
[Music]
okay okay okay
nice nice nice nice nice nice
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
in real life
okay don't mind don't mind
do your pets in badminton in real life
do you pass to your teammate no no no no
no no it's gonna be out we only we only
can possibly do like one one hit okay we
cannot pass no
oh
my wife
okay okay nice nice nice nice nice nice
nice
why
[Applause]
okay okay okay okay okay
I'm enjoying this too much
winning feels good
[Applause]
yeah
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
all right
okay
we sweep
let's go
interview too oh should I oh no yeah
yeah okay
oh no it's caught up the
cut up the knee
thank you thank you so basically after
this soccer will be like the what is it
called
the it would be the deal breaker yeah
yes yes okay so if you want to win win
the soccer if they want to win they have
to win the soccer okay sure you guys got
what it is we will win we will win
match
of course we have to know because
winning it just felt so good right now I
want more of that yeah let's go
but like seriously you guys are like
really good at like uh hitting the we
are practicing morning early morning
afternoon evening yeah
wow yeah like Kyla was a great backup to
have behind me like she was managing the
backside and I was managing the front
but they normally shot a lot of like
shots to the very far back so you know
Kyla was always there to support me
thank you guys yeah thank you so much
for waking me up too you're great I want
to play more badminton let's go it seems
fun but yeah
[Music]
support and
and that
I'm team Wing yeah
can you keep the server online so I can
play more badminton for the coming
months
actually everyone
really to play yeah
yeah
let's go
[Music]
okay we're back let's go
okay
so they said that there's 10 point
difference and soccer is gonna make the
big difference yeah we are leading but
we still need to win the soccer ball
should I maybe try to stay in a certain
area like close to the goal or so any
any I think uh uh uh Kiara and Kyla uh
are both great at uh
uh striking right yeah I mean
too much forward while uh the others can
I at least one tries to stay back and
guard uh without being gold somebody has
to stay around to go like yeah
I'll be the first defense
okay yeah before EOP okay
second goalkeeper
how can I translate in Japanese
like this is just a little little
information that you can actually
dribble the ball when you're actually
clicking
the ball ah hello
[Music]
um
okay
[Music]
let's go let's go
after 10 minutes
oh yeah you better not bring the ball to
me okay
do we automatically run
are we automatically running by the way
are we automatically running no we need
to press I think you always have to
press it okay yes
middle finger gets tired from it after a
while but because I'm pressing it
nothing's changing so it is
it you can jump as well but but it's
like wow
[Music]
pass it yeah yeah yeah
to your friends go
[Music]
don't worry
don't worry don't worry
it's okay it's okay all right it was
close it's okay it's okay it's okay
um
[Music]
it disappears it is
[Laughter]
he's just so close
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
's a really good goalkeeper
died
nice
tickets
go go go go go go go oh shoot that was
before oh sorry
okay okay okay what does that mean okay
don't worry okay don't worry right side
okay go oh
okay you need to stay back a little bit
now you no you don't take the boat
that was awesome
is up
okay I gotta redo
okay okay
go go go go go go go go no
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no okay
okay
I'm gonna take it to the left okay oh
[Music]
Watson
I'll be just staying close to you okay
please yeah I think I'll just be going
to the hospital
[Music]
directions
let's go
I'm rejoice
[Music]
okay oh
okay okay okay
I'm gonna take it to the left too again
all right all right
okay okay okay okay we're gonna take it
to the left again go go go go go take it
nice one
[Applause]
okay
she's gonna get distracted yeah
wait okay
we still have times it's fine you can
definitely do it I'm gonna take it a
little bit longer okay okay
oh
my God
[Music]
nice okay
um I need to stay close I need to stay
closer to here yeah I'm gonna go into
the right side
[Music]
come here
I feel like it always goes okay
[Music]
okay
wait hold on oh
need a second to turn around
[Music]
you feel like you're running I didn't
feel like I am but I'm not holding
control
it is
[Music]
I'm sorry it's fine it's fine it's okay
okay okay
[Music]
okay
yeah we're already in the second half
not yet not yet I think it's 10 minutes
yeah it's 10 minutes
[Music]
okay here we go you ready all right
foreign
[Music]
what the
okay okay okay
let's go come on
[Applause]
[Music]
it's okay yeah I did I didn't know
soccer will be this oh sure
[Music]
this is how real soccer works
ah
[Music]
[Applause]
um
yeah no definitely do that oh that was
that was nice that was a good night
[Music]
it's okay it's okay it's okay no problem
s okay
[Applause]
dance
yeah maybe just scrub yeah
[Music]
more aggressive
I wonder if maybe I should not defend it
I should strike instead no I think it's
good
okay okay you're good okay I feel like
I'm doing a bad job
[Music]
I think we need more defense though
we can because we can just kick the ball
to the front we don't need like that
much of like you know we don't need much
of the attackers
yeah so if we got the ball just kick it
foreign
[Music]
oh
um
they're going to be more defensive 100
because they're winning so we we really
need to be aggressive I think okay
[Music]
you see
okay
[Music]
all right
okay
yeah I think I need to be more in the
central area please
oh you'll be
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
I don't know
[Music]
that's true
very classically
um
[Music]
bad weather by the way I really hope I
don't DC
okay
to chill out
chill chill
keeper she is really good options
foreign
another guess
okay yes that is
if we have any strategy yeah okay okay
just just leave it to Lady Luck I guess
maybe there's a miracle comeback yeah
[Music]
stronger aggressive everything stronger
okay
[Music]
let's go let's go
okay nice nice check it off
[Music]
all right
I don't okay
okay okay
all right get ready ladies here we go
all right
bring it back okay okay okay
I'm Watson day
yeah she's really good I'm Watson
okay where is she gonna go okay okay
right over my head I wish I could jump
better
today it's a good fighter
I don't know
we cannot shoot from there I don't know
if we can shift from there it's gonna be
like good looking realistic
it's better to cry no no no
yeah
okay okay okay
so aggressive I think we need somebody
doing what is doing over by the goal can
we just follow her yeah
away
[Music]
okay
I also still have to turn around every
time they're already looking in the
right direction yeah
[Music]
come on there's no way I'm sorry but I'm
sorry
oh
try good try good time
[Music]
aggressive the aggressively
where is it oh okay oh no oh no Kelly
Kelly protect me I'm ready I'm ready
yeah but nah
nah she wants to go okay okay
I'm gonna be tactical about it okay okay
don't we love each other
[Music]
it's fun
oh yeah
all right nope
got me asked up over here
now Watson's too good
yeah
oh God okay
[Applause]
[Music]
I
foreign
[Music]
let's go
keep going gotta keep going
[Music]
you can do this
how about the comeback with the comeback
[Music]
protect me Cali all right I'm trying
okay okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
she wants to confuse us
okay
[Music]
ready ladies we're here we're here let's
go let's go
[Music]
my size
if we can tie with them we just need to
tie with them yeah
no no no no no no no no no okay it's
fine it's fine it's fine it's fine even
defense defense defense defense
I'm here
[Music]
get ready
okay okay defense defense defense
okay okay
nice nice nice nice
[Music]
defense defense
what are you gonna do Cobble
what are you going to do
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
no problem three minutes we can do it
one goal per minute
watch let's do it now you never know you
never know exactly take it I'm gonna
take it okay okay okay
[Music]
oh
come on
the Wall come on
steal it
you gotta steal it
nope Cali
that was close that was close that was
close
[Music]
extension no like 10 minutes
was it good momentum
[Music]
pick it take it take it nice nice
Foster does fly
it is
all right there you go
nice nice
nope nope nope nope nope nope
whatever happens
yeah this is a lot of fun
[Music]
okay shoot
okay
[Music]
they needed her to be there
my team is the best
[Music]
we didn't even know
but it was good that was that was great
that was it that was great we did our
best
yeah yup me
at least it was close it wasn't like
they completely destroyed us right yeah
yeah not like Pokemon unite or anything
like that
we did decently but
there was literally do not get gas lit
into thinking that we didn't do well in
that tournament because we did okay we
did we did it
was great
even though I was watching it was it was
it was really awesome
um
the whole time
good thank you
dang I'ma too strong I mean it's a good
amazing
we are in the hub yoga and Cali also
like
um what is it
[Music]
yeah
I I might can reach the ball who knows
[Music]
look at our bodies we're all the same
not even wrong
I know
um
[Music]
so so much fun I really enjoy all the
games
[Music]
Edmonton easy
I think the map is open until
um
20 something something yes everybody
wants to try it yeah if you want to ask
someone to play with you
hear me Kyla not asking anybody to I I'm
still trying to get a friend to play the
top of War because I really love that
one my hand is crying
I'll play against you Kyla anytime yeah
thank you thank you Kiara we have to
play uh like two two versus one like
both of us versus Kyla what wait what no
I don't stamina no no no
don't worry I can maybe do it alone
against Tyler oh yeah let's go let's go
I will just die but you need your hot
chicken
good games
[Music]
okay this
is
[Music]
when did I look cool yes
I should have been cheerleading where
are your pom-poms
in my heart
you mean in front of your heart
oh wow
honestly strong
that was wild yeah the movable wall
how strong are you now though getting
punched like this yeah
he likes it she likes it you sure about
that
just like back in the day
thanks thanks I'm not abusive to my gym
it's pink
pink
everybody gets thanks
oh
give me a five stars
Emma did you play soccer in real life
before or what I have I have oh
my reflexes are there
that explains everything
never had a prayer
[Music]
oh yeah okay
announcement
s
are you announcing your wedding with
someone
[Laughter]
good job guys
[Applause]
it was intense and well after all of
those intense game will be announcing
winners
yeah so first of all from the bending on
the capture the fort
the winner well three coming with 40
points
[Music]
yeah and then we also have the sack race
but 30 points yet again three can you
win so that brings us to a total of 70
points
[Music]
and then Renee what's the next one
the next one was
tug of war
in which it was a blue versus pink team
OMG oh my God
[Music]
and then badminton again two matches
both won by partially so 20 plus 20 so
another 40 points for per TV
so after three candy was leading pretty
we managed to catch up by 10 points and
then that's where soccer came in and
became the deal breaker yeah
Watson too strong and we are happy to
announce that the winner of the whole ID
cup is the
supper
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
it's just that one team gets like a
better medal that's all
it's okay I'm a loser it's okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
all right
foreign
oh yes hi Mada I sent it please
distribute everybody
I put it on now
um
death metal yes
let me see hey what if I just put on the
gold medal anyway
[Laughter]
the gold maybe I'm gonna put on
them
[Music]
oh and I love it
yeah
the pink one is cuter anyway you you
like the pink one
better
[Music]
does everybody have their medals yes
yeah
[Music]
that's so good
yeah
this thing is heavy there's our Shot
Show just like the opening we will be
asking for a few words by each team
captain starting from the teams
[Music]
that was it that was really fun really
really fun and
um
can we do oh can we do the
um the the yellow together again let's
do it again
let's do it let's do it again yeah yeah
yeah yeah okay let's go okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
everyone did their everyone did
um everyone did their best during the
games
thank you so much for being such a good
leader thank you
[Music]
thank you for playing with us as well
thank you so much
thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
we love you all thank you thank you
thank you
we can we have a little bit of some
words from the captain of Timber TV
please
everybody
[Music]
oh yeah yeah first I would like to say
thank you for all birthday team too uh
to actually make time for this and also
I love birthday
because they are all
um hardworking so they practice too and
they like oh my God I just I just love
the team so much I love you too
[Music]
thank you so much everybody thank you so
much for inviting us
this year was really fun thank you
thank you thank you
[Music]
please yeah next year again please
guys yeah
let's go okay do you want to do the
cheer for one last time yes
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
a picture
everyone go into the podium please let's
go let's go
oh I know
okay okay
[Music]
okay
three
two one
[Music]
yes okay okay thank you
this is the better one look look at me
look at me okay okay uh
foreign
[Music]
good time good fun time
okay
[Music]
thank you
oh the cute metal yeah okay
where should we go for the picture
should we just go fly up so we can get
like all of the games
the balloons to ships yeah
let's go here let's go here follow me
follow me
follow me follow me
okay so teach us how to fly in Minecraft
please
see creative mode yeah and what I can't
get the
London how do I fly you need online
game has been updated to creative mode
Here There It Is
need to wait until the button go up
again wait wait be patient
my hands are a little strong
I didn't manage to get into the uh
double jump Oh I thought it was just one
jump oh sorry it's okay it's okay it's
okay right click
all right
[Applause]
let's go here to the dragon dragon ships
let's go this one this one
it's so pretty so we can get all of the
hair and maybe copy what we're doing no
wait are you are you taking
hold on
I'm flying all right let's go let's get
in the dragon in the dragon dragon's
mouth and uh yeah there we go cool
dragon's eyebrows
yeah a dragon's head cool yeah
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah
you can
so please make sure that I'm in the
middle so I can get like a better
picture
mm-hmm okay
maybe
Luna Senpai can go in front
yeah
okay okay
[Music]
I cannot see who's at the back
oh okay okay right
yeah I think it's too far we can go a
little bit
or is it good enough like this I cannot
even I can't even see Kylie's name
oh hi all right
okay oh one two three four five six
seven eight nine okay all right yeah
this one's nice this one is nice
bye
oh hi yeah okay okay
all right
okay got one
we got two
um
okay we look up yes everybody yeah
everybody look up how um
perfect
okay perfect perfect side please
okay okay okay I think it's done
okay I'll send it
okay
thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
I want to see what's in this ship this
ship is cool yeah you can look around
[Music]
before
yeah yeah
Indonesia oh
and the other one I don't remember ready
wow I'm an explorer
I'm gonna send the pictures
[Music]
sports festival is
I thought there should be an
announcement about that Japanese Japan
and I believe was that
yeah I got it okay I need I need to
close my stream first okay
my stream we can stop the stream now
yeah okay okay
then goodbye thanks for everything today
thank you thank you thank you
okay
he
yeah I freeze the l2d guys because if I
keep moving the metal will not be there
so I so I just freeze the l2d right yeah
it was fun it was fun
it was fun and why that face though why
it's a full of excitement face
yeah
let's go
nice
um
there is no other announcement I thought
there's gonna be announcement but maybe
maybe later I don't know there should be
announcement right hold on let me let me
ask Anton first
uh
okay
oh it's already in the oh
Danny
Curry
M10 is typing
or
oh
okay
no spoilers then adios you just need to
wait then
she
she she
oh okay okay
yeah so there's gonna be something on
17th
there is gonna be something on 17th
that's that's the spoiler but yeah
that's that's the spoiler
yeah nice right okay thank you so much
Dan
um
I'll be reading the donations later on
and I really hope that
um probably someone or maybe anyone that
have that was that didn't joined the
event probably we can use this Arena to
play before it's gone I don't know if
the server gonna stay or it's gonna be
gone
this is
yeah
mm-hmm
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
nice nice nice
21st okay then maybe I need to like I
don't know maybe I need to
um
I hope that we can play with
other other Members First if they really
want to play
back of War versus Bijou Bijou
you know
still in the collab band
so yeah
uh
yeah you know last night I was last
night I Luna Senpai and risu Senpai was
trying to memorize this and we we have a
lot of strats actually but probably it's
just like we choose the wrong straps
because
yeah we we definitely we definitely
choose the the wrong stretch
um because we expected that they will
not use the middle one we we actually
prepared the middle Strat already but
um we didn't think that they will choose
that shred we think that we're gonna
fight under uh the basement
ah
yeah
yeah yeah opposite team choose to not
fight right yeah that's why that's why
that's the reason why we
um I wanna explain this threat because I
haven't um explained this threat before
but um what we have in mind uh we go
so we um I even I even um stopwatch you
know the the right side and the left
side last night I stopped watch it and
then
um we know that the the fastest way is
actually the right one so we asked like
three people to go uh to the right
because that's the reason
um I don't know if you guys know about
the rules
if you know about the rules right uh so
if the enemy is staying in our side we
just need to like one punch and they
will go to the jail right so if you look
at this
the I even tested the area so I asked
Luna Senpai and risu Senpai to fight
over in this area down down here right
and then um one punch we can send the
the red team straight to the jail if we
fight under this base so we only have
one person there and then why we sent
like three people here is because all of
the stairs all of this basement is their
area
so
um we send like three people to fight
down there that's our Strat actually
um but
but yeah why we are not taking the
middle straight just because we think
that they will not take that path so
yeah if you think that we are not
defending we do defending the reason why
um there are three people need to go to
the right because uh after we reach the
basement here it's gonna be fighting and
the enemy just gonna punch us once and
we go straight to the jail that's why we
need to like have three people there but
yeah
and then I already I I already said to
resus Senpai we even prepared like if uh
risu Senpai found anyone in the basement
I asked risu Senpai to just lure them to
our area just go back first and then
just punch them in our area so that they
can go into the jail directly we we
prepared a lot guys
we prepare a lot but yeah
yeah they they just go straight into
this one they they take the fresher
plate right I exactly know the the
thread but yeah
it's okay
yeah
nice nice nice getting defensive
guys
it's a wrong Strat anyway so yeah it's
fun it's fun it's fun I'm learning a lot
of things
and yeah
um
no defense for Middle yeah because we
didn't expect that that's that's the
that's the what that's the exact mistake
mistake yeah it's a our team mistake
anyway so yeah
[Music]
we're super fast right it's super fast
yeah
but I mean that's literally there are a
lot of uh stats right resistant I
already said that too so yeah I think
that's all
10 seconds no it's not it's it's less
than 10 seconds
yeah it's less than 10 seconds
but yeah you didn't expect they will do
that yeah um because at first what we
had practice is I I keep going to the
right and then rizu Senpai and Luna
Senpai go to the middle at first but we
think that or maybe they will like just
go to the right or to the left and then
we just go fight uh under the basement
but well it happens
yeah it's okay
hey thank you so much
thank you so much and yeah
hmm
okay okay thank you so much for now I'll
be seeing you there will be no stream
tonight because I wanna go to yeah I
have a meeting with amtran uh tonight so
I cannot uh I cannot stream I'll there
will be a junction in stream tomorrow
for sure and
[Music]
then maybe I will go back at night
because the whole afternoon I'll be
focusing on the refill stream
um and then the Tuesday one gonna be
refill right yeah if I'm not mistaken
for the day yeah yeah
I think so
okay thank you so much
adios
I'll be reading the donation later on
after the refill stream bye bye I think
it was fun
[Music]
everything
foreign
[Music]
thank you