[Music]
so
hello
[Music]
welcome to
portal 2
let's go
[Music]
hopefully there's cake
is that even like
i know
and it comes from portal one do they
even like uh like talk about cake in
portal 2 i wonder if that even is a
topic
but it would be nice if there was cake
mm-hmm
[Music]
i have a little bit more iced tea left
over
yummy yummy yummy iced tea i tea is like
my favorite
soft drink what about you guys
um i like fizzy soft drinks too but iced
tea is like always
always the way to go for me um
i love iced tea
oh my oh my oh my you know what when i
am i live in austria as you know
and we love ice tea in austria but when
i went to
germany several many many many times
uh
whenever i would ask for iced tea in a
restaurant
i
so often they would not have it on the
menu
which i've noticed that in germany they
just don't really like to put ic on the
menu why
please put iced tea on the menu eh
i go to germany quite often and then
every time in the restaurant i'm like eh
i don't drink alcohol so if you don't
have iced tea
like
sparkly sparkly
carbonated drinks don't always
go well with what you're eating like you
know coca-cola and fanta and all that
yeah
what no no no not fizzy iced tea i'm
talking about normal iced tea
yeah
no
i'm not not gonna order beer or anything
like that no
yeah and usually what i go for then is
coca-cola because
the rest of the drinks on the menu are
just carbonated drinks usually for soft
drinks and i only drink soft drinks mmm
disappointing yeah
yeah it is
me and my friends really wondered about
why there is a lack of iced tea in
restaurants in germany
i don't mean fast with restaurants by
the way i mean proper restaurants yeah i
mean sure there are definitely
restaurants that have iced tea but there
are also a lot of restaurants that don't
have iced tea
[Music]
i see supremacy mm-hmm
uh so welcome to portal 2
uh last week we played portal one so if
you missed that you should watch it uh
people said my portal one player was
funny i don't know how but
i'm glad you guys think so um but we're
going to play paul 2 today paul 2 is
longer i'm aware of that so i'm not
planning on finishing it today um we're
going to continue tomorrow so probably i
i i calculated five hours today five
hours tomorrow approximately
um
what a night
i was pretty good i would say it's
pretty big brain today don't expect that
from me
my brain capacity
capacity capacity
uh today feels very low
[Laughter]
and also
somewhere in the middle of the stream
i think my hellofresh delivery is gonna
come so i'll have to quickly put the
stuff into the fridge just so you know
okay
uh
yosh then
yeah i expect this speed run i wish i
could speed speedrun it by just being
smart and and impress you guys but
that's not happening you put you know
what i love already
the way
the way this menu works
i love it
and let me turn down the volume a little
bit on windows sign
okay
uh let's go play single player because i
was told to play single player first
before playing co-op with kobo because
the story and all that is kind of
different and the content
so
i'm uh curious about it oh it might
still be loud you have been in
suspension for
eight days in compliance with state and
federal regulations all testing
candidates in the aperture site
uh
is closed captioning subtitles
yes subtitles only full captions just
subtitles only maybe
i think it's good enough
i still make assumptions
michelle let's go
extended relaxation center must be
revived periodically for a mandatory
physical and mental wellness exercise
you will hear a buzz when you hear the
buzzer look up at the ceiling
[Music]
oh you will hear it there's nothing
there when you hear the buzzer look down
at the floor
[Music]
wow carpet it looks nice
coffee please call that mental wellness
although with dark green
there is a framed painting our green
carpet
a walk you know this is hard
oh my god i i walk like i move like i
have uh
inline skaters oh sorry
you should now feel mentally
reinvigorated
suspect staring at art has not not
really but i want to live there
sustenance reflect briefly on classical
music
[Music]
modern one would be nice too but but
living so closely hell yeah please
return to your bed
all eh
i mean i i don't mind i don't mind i
love staying in bed it's that's that's
not a tv though that it almost looks
like a tv but if you guys could ah
there's one here all right let's watch
some netflix guys
why do i move like a jelly oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
i moved too fast what is this
good night
[Music]
you have been in suspension for
oh
[Music]
i heard about you are you okay are you
don't answer that i'm actually sure
you're fine there's plenty of time for
you to recover just take it please
prepare for emergency evacuation stay
calm stay calm prepared
prepare it's all fine all right don't
move i'm gonna get us out of here are
you one of them you might want to hang
on to something word of advice up to you
hang on to something
hang on to what wait what what's going
on why is it suddenly so [\h__\h] up
how long did i sleep
we are
at technical difficulties
wait what the [\h__\h] it
you wait
subjects do experience some cognitive
deterioration oh yeah a few months in
suspension now you've been under
for quite a lot longer and it's not out
of the question that doesn't look like i
might have a very minor case of one day
or so
but don't be alarmed all right uh
although if you do if you do feel
alarmed try to hold on to that feeling
because that is the proper reaction to
being told that you've got brain damage
do you understand what i'm saying wait i
told you you're your voice sounds
familiar to me who voices this person
again
i have a very specific actor in my mind
right now when i hear this voice
who is this steven merchant stephen
merchant
yes yes that's exactly who i had in mind
oh my god i know this person's voice
that's exactly who i was thinking of
now every time i look at dad's face
which is not even a face i have to have
steven merchant's face in my in my brain
wonderful i don't know if i like that or
if i should be freaked out by that does
any of this make any sense just tell me
just say yes
yes okay what you're doing there is
jumping uh you just you just jump but
never mind it's like i didn't really
jump
apple
okay you know what that's close enough
just hold tight apple
apple is this sponsored by apple
non-functional
i prefer windows
speaking of windows oh
i wasn't going to mention this to you
but i'm going to switch hot water here
what
how are you doing down there what's
still holding on
holding on to what what mr
so of course the whole relaxation center
stops waking up the bloody test subject
um
um hold on
can i go back to bed nobody tells me
anything no why did you tell me anything
oh my god why should i be kept informed
you know about the like
of the ten thousand people
yeah
i'm in one of those cinemas in
disneyland
space
yeah yeah this is exactly like
disneyland i'll get through here
okay i just gotta concentrate
and whose fault do you think it's gonna
be when the management comes down here
and finds ten thousand flipping
vegetables and they think that we're
gonna we're we're healthy we're eating
our good good diet yeah yeah
why are we okay listen we should get our
story straight all right if anyone asks
and no one's gonna ask don't worry but
if anyone asks tell them as far as you
know the last time you checked everyone
looked pretty much alive you're
stressing me out buddy
okay almost there
on the other side of that plan it's one
of the old testing tracks
there's a piece of equipment in there
that we're going to need to get out of
here where i think this is a docking
station get ready oh yeah it says
docking station i mean already
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah
oh
break the dark existence
[Music]
oh my god
are we done now are we docked
there we go my poor room uh-huh you are
probably in no fit state to run this
particular type of cognitive gauntlet
but um
at least you're a good jumper
cognitive gauntlet um just do your best
and i'll meet you up ahead
what are we doing though like
all right off you go i don't understand
like what what's happening anyway
what's happening look just marching
through that hole
but what's that what's happening can you
not explain it to me it's all right go
ahead okay
okay
i know i know i have painted quite a
grim picture of your chances but if you
simply stand here we will both surely
die you can't even die or a machine like
really are you even alive as a machine
once again just
move along one small step and everything
[Laughter]
and again welcome to the aperture
science enrichment sound
we are currently experiencing technical
difficulties due to circumstances that's
the same room apocalyptic significance
beyond our control however thanks to
emergency testing protocols
these pre-recorded messages will provide
instructional and motivational support
so that science can still be done even
in the event of environmental social
media
collapse
the portal will open and emergency
testing will begin in three
two
one
[Music]
let's go look at me over there it's me
quick
that's a deja vu especially because we
just played it so recently
okay we're in the same place
[Music]
wow how many years later is this
in order for plants to grow like that
holy [\h__\h] it must be like maybe like
60 70 years or so
it's crazy based testing remains an
important tool for you i remember
emergency
i don't remember this maybe this will
help me that i haven't played it
are very recently
please note the incandescent particle
field across the exit this aperture
science material emancipation grill will
vaporize any unauthorized equipment that
passes through it
wasn't the voice originally a woman have
they
fired the woman what happened why did
they re-record it with a male voice why
what was wrong with the female voice
i'm i'm having a hard time listening to
the male voice to be honest
well elevator you look different
i like oh i killed uh well but if it
wasn't recorded like can't they play the
same thing if you feel liquid running
down your neck relax lie on your back
and apply immediate pressure to your
tempest
you are simply experiencing a rare
reaction in which the material
emancipation drill may have emancipated
the ear tubes emancipate the ear tubes
what does that mean like
what does that mean
i mean i know emancipate in the context
of um
um
wait was that where you don't want to
like have your parents be your parents
anymore
or what's that when i don't know the
other things
oh
yeah man to pay this to
become free yeah yeah okay so yeah okay
good to know that that will happen my
ears will be free good for them
how long is that
is it going to turn itself off
immediately
there's three buttons
i don't have a gun yet
what is there a
a right order
wait
can i like open this
open
nope
okay first riddle
there should be like an order
no
what
on the wall
oh
what
but this is where i can't i thought this
is where it came from
[Laughter]
oh can i open with this no
but wait
i have this
but where do i put it
on
what is this not where i came from
i need my portal gun otherwise i can't
think of portals
bro
how do i fro
where am i throwing it at oh can i like
shoo
oh okay okay
oh it really is that how we're gonna do
it
huh
okay wait
what no i don't think that's how it
works
no i have no gun yet what are you saying
press more buttons
more buttons how about this one first
and then
this one
ah
that blue one opened up but eh
eh
what
oh
that's the same room
that makes sense because there's a
portal but i want to get into this room
ah can i open ah
wait oh i always looked away so fast i
didn't realize the portal is opening
okay okay sorry
i'm sorry
[Music]
okay
didn't see anything happening
so that opened up that thing
uh
is this did we have this room
when we first played portal 1 what is we
are currently experiencing your test
environment is unsupervised before
re-entering a relaxation vault that room
doesn't look familiar to me please take
a moment to write down the results of
your test and aperture science associate
will revive you for an interview when
society has been rebuilt
what
when society is there no more society
is everyone dead
like everyone was there an apocalypse
if the earth is currently governed by
apocalypse animal king sent me a cloud
or other governing body that either
refuses to or is incapable of listening
to
animal pattern sucks you look ugly in
that
doesn't look good for you at all i don't
know you need something more
something more calm for your look
honestly something that brings out the
color of your eye because with that kind
of pattern you honestly look like one of
those car
one of those cars that they try to hide
because it's a new model yeah
yeah you look like you're camouflaging
yourself of a disgusting animal pattern
go for something more neutral it's not
your look no no
no no no no
oh this this feels familiar this room
this pattern you made it ah
hi a portal device on that podium over
there
i can't see it though maybe it fell off
do you wanna have a quick look
[\h__\h] you whitley
can you see the portal gun
also are you alive
that's important should have asked that
first
do you know what i'm gonna do i'm gonna
work on the assumption that you're still
alive and i'm just gonna wait for you up
ahead
oh wait i'll wait one hour then i'll
come back one hour assuming i can locate
your dead body
i'll bury you that's so sweet of you
oh there's a portal
my character probably wishes she was
dead at this point
uh okay
not a hotel
oh companion cube
this is a
scientist or
like the ones that are strangling
themselves what the hell
this is me
with my weird shoes that make me go
beyond and some
oh
that looks so good some yummy looking
cake
and more companion cube
and i suppose that is uh the
the boss that we fought glados
is that me
wait i look gorgeous wait let me look at
that from afar
oh
that looks so pretty that could be a
t-shirt
or unlike a bag you know one of those uh
light brown shopping baggish things
orange is my color look at me rocking it
it is on the t-shirt really
except too soon
oh my god ah here it is
blue oh yeah i got the blue portal
let's make it on my crotch
let's go for my crotch
hell yeah
[Laughter]
all right
who else did that from you guys who
played portal 2
don't remember this place i think i mean
we've been for rooms like that probably
but i don't remember it
we're going like for different paths i
think this is not the originally
intended path some emergency testing may
require prolonged interaction with
lethal military androids rest assured
that all lethal military androids have
been taught to read and provided with
one copy of the laws of robotics
you should provide them with more to
read
yeah
if they can read then why not make them
super or maybe that's bad to make them
too intelligent is also a bad thing huh
should we go over there
there is um
onyo is this momentum again oh no no no
no no no it's not
just walk through here
i know
yeah okay i finally already had two
portals two guns to work with that's not
the case
but there we go android has not
respected your rights as detailed in the
laws of robotics please note it on your
self-reporting form well i didn't read
it how can i know lots of robotics
appropriate grievance paperwork i
wouldn't know if i've been mistreated by
a robot but if they shoot at me i feel
like i've been mistreated
i don't want to meet those rabbis please
no
please no
so far so good
all right this next test is very
dangerous to help you remain tranquil in
the face of almost certain death smooth
jazz will be deployed
three
two
one
oh
i don't like dez do you like jazz chat
[Music]
hey
don't stop the music oh [\h__\h] you
by the way [\h__\h] you
eh am i not getting any anything for
that
in this game let's see we'll do it a few
more times before if we find one
oh oh companion cube
pick it up
there we go
oh that's trippy again leave it here
wonderful door is open yeah i remember
this room
yeah yeah oh it was not company it was
yeah it was just a normal one
well but i i think of companion cube a
lot okay
why is it not working
what do we need batteries or what's
happening
oh
sorry for some reason i suddenly thought
that
portals are made with the button e i was
confused never mind
okay we'll go here
maybe and then we'll go here
oh i'm so smart
uh
one more please uh
cube
this is where i came from right um
[Music]
there's an oh there's another one that's
good that's perfect
oh i'll take that
through
here and then just drop it off because
this message is pre-recorded any
observations related to your performance
are speculation on our part please
disregard any undeserved compliments
i deserve every compliment oh
wait a second wait a second i'm gonna
fall through there uh let's go no
oh okay that was supposed to happen
okay
interesting
is that open
oh
what about here
oh i don't like it when there's two
paths i don't like that oh maybe this is
uh optional to look at on reason oh math
oh was only here a cat cat jumps over
the moon
i don't know if my cat can do that
cat over the moon
[Music]
is that is that in this world at this
time because so many years have passed
is that our overlord is the cat the
overlord because they're so powerful
that they've grown so big and so
powerful so jumpy that they can jump
over the moon
you know what i'm fine with that i feel
like a cat overlord might want to um
kill us humans but i mean they deserve
their time to shine right it's not like
you know we humans have the power but
i feel like at some point we have to
give someone else some some like time or
opportunity to shine you know
it was so selfish of us to always take
control
yeah we need to let go
we need to let go guys give someone else
the opportunity started with fireballs
and meteorites or other objects from
space please avoid unsheltered testing
areas wherever relax you guys are
chickens so i guess it doesn't matter
what i'm saying
where's that water coming from
has it rained and it just
accumulated somewhere but look freedom
is so close why can't we not just climb
up those leaves
and say sayonara
thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
for the red super chat
i caught up with super chats yesterday
so i think i can read them today
depending on how long we play but what
the [\h__\h]
portal
i don't have the orange one yet
[Music]
ah there's an orange one okay
yeah
oh it wasn't so bad
it looked like i was falling pretty far
but never mind it wasn't so bad oh
oh okay
oh
wait this room do i know this room
i'm not sure
okay so we have to
use the orange portal
in some ways but let's see what the
buttons do first
ah cube ah okay let's use the can i get
the cube
uh
no
no not really yeah
unless i
no
mozakashi can i jump up here no
what about
am i thinking before those shut up
i'm trying i'm yeah i'm thinking of
portals i'm thinking that if i if if i
do a portal here well how am i gonna
reach that orange one up there huh
but if i do one here then i'm just gonna
fall out there again but i can try
momentum i don't know but i feel like
i'm gonna fall through here okay wow
please shut up everybody who says kiwawa
please after
me being
yeah i want the cube though after me
being one minute into a a riddle can
shut up give me a moment to try to
understand it okay
did i miss a cube somewhere
is there a cube here no
well let me fly through again
[Music]
that doesn't even give me like oh
and but i wanna
[Music]
you guys are putting me under pressure
you know
[Music]
yeah i know i made some cute but
this goes away
[Music]
i was thinking i was trying to think
with portals
but that
i need my second gun you know
i need my second gun
oh
cute oh
okay so probably wanna
have one fall through there
yeah yeah
so we get it on that side
ah i see okay and then we want to stay
in the in that region okay
on the right time
is this the right time maybe no yes
you're done i didn't even really look
okay
i was overthinking maybe maybe maybe all
right
beautiful
the enrichment center reminds you that
although circumstances may appear bleak
you are not alone all aperture science
personality constructs will remain
functional in apocalyptic low power
environments of as few as 1.1 volts
wow that's actually impressive
so you can um continue to abuse humans
even in an apocalypse where there's only
like one human left
wow priorities guys
priorities because that's there that's
the priority when there's an apocalypse
to continue this [\h__\h] huh aperture
laboratories correction i call you
this next test applies the principles of
momentum to movement
no longer apply in the future god help
you
on your momentum
we have to test no they've done enough
testing why is there a need to test when
at that point
there's no more need for testing
wait what are you testing for if there's
no more humans
what are you gonna use that testing for
at that point
i wanted to speed from that okay but
okay
so we're here now
um
but
okay so that floor i can't make a portal
on
i want ah
that
therefore i can make a portal on but
maybe but not
can i but not for if anything even if i
can not through that glass so
i have to go there but no dear
oh dear chat is gonna be like
ah
aha
momentum
okay and now can i like
do that yeah okay
fatso
do i
is my portal still there no
do i froyo for the same portal but are
you not because you're like i is that
cube lighter than me or
or
same weight you know you have to think
about that too physics or we just jump
together while i hold you is that gonna
work
oh it works wow i thought we would be
too big
if you are a non-employee who has
discovered this facility that was
massive civilization
i figured that without balance is the
future and the future starts with you
i am the future
testing
testing is the future and the future
starts with me so i'm i
this testing starts with me have you
guys even ever tested anybody else
besides me why is only me
why is it only me
orange portal down there wants to fall
through it
fall out of blue one get cube that's my
goal
whoa
where am i
hello cuba
take cube
bring to uh there's a button there but
um
[Music]
nothing too portal
what are we gonna do with you just fall
for fall for the orange one but this
time this time we're not gonna land
we're not we don't want to fall out of
there we want to fall
[Music]
ah
there's nothing there i can work with i
can just land here maybe
oh but ah
no no no no no momentum so if we shoot
ourselves out of there we might land
there
yeah yeah yeah cause we gotta consider
that we'll have momentum guys think of
momentum not with portals
no no no need for hire i did it i did it
and big brain okay
no more of that what was that
uh-huh
um momentum this time we might want to
go higher yeah
do we want this one um
it's hard to tell let me stand here
i don't know this one
chihuahua exclamation mark isn't much
better
okay
let's see if this works
so close just a tiny bit
just a tiny bit could have even made it
if i would have
controlled my body
future
one question look yeah what the [\h__\h] you
think
the future what should i do
and send back someone better qualified
for
testing working can you just praise me
and then end the sentence there
no need for making the sentence worse
like that
okay well question mark is like uh as if
i did something wrong and then i need to
really question what i just what i just
did
testing protocols all safety devices
have been disabled the enrichment center
respects your right to have questions or
concerns about this policy but you're
not gonna answer them are you
we may have questions but we may not
have answers
can i
you did find a portal gun yeah
do you know what it just goes to show
people with brain damage are the real
heroes in the end aren't they they are
they have brain damage i don't have
brain damage that's so rude
and i'll meet you on the other side of
the room what oh
okay
hi
okay listen let me
lay something on your head it's pretty
heavy oh
if i can hold it never never ever to
disengage myself from my management rail
or i would die oh but we're out of
options
no you can't only you're ready to catch
me all right on the off chance
not dead free yourself i pop off this
thing emancipate yourself ready yes one
you'll be fine i'll catch you
three that's high it's it's too high
really that
just gives you too much time to think
about it let's uh go on one this time
okay ready yes
i'm not dead i'm not dead
i can't move then that's the problem
are you still are you still there could
you pick me up do you think oh wait a
second
can i like push you over
hello i don't want to touch you pick me
up please only with my feet
yeah yeah yeah yeah
wait about this floor are you still
there could you pick could you pick me
up i'm gonna push you through this
portal
oh this won't work okay thank you great
plug me into that stick on the wall over
there yeah and i'll show you something
is something here what stick of the wall
what did you say jeremy in over there
where
yeah what
gem you in where right on that stick ah
i didn't see that what is that yeah i
can't do it if you're watching
okay
can you just turn around for a second
are you gonna pee
and you start no
i'm gonna look very closely
i can't do it if you're watching
[Laughter]
i sometimes see that in like netflix
shows or whatever when there's a scene
with with several guys in one toilet i
can't do it standing there in a row just
turn around and then one is like okay
i'm done are you not done and he's like
no no i need i need to be alone
you guys
we always have private toilets we lean
it's not that i use them it's only a
robot a bloody stick a different one
i'm looking away
all right you can turn around now okay
secret panel
while your back was turned
well let's get out of here
would you pick me up no
where are you anyway huh what
ah did you pick me up yeah yes
no rail to tell us where to go
we go wherever we walk
hold on
[Music]
just follow the rail actually
okay
follow this okay okay why why am why do
i have to help you are you gonna help me
do you know the way
oh no
yes hello we're not stopping don't make
eye contact whatever you do no
we're good appreciate it keep moving
keep moving
that's so cute
wait
hi
i'm here do you want to come with us
you're different
we're the same
it's okay we're the same
you can come with us if you want to
let's escape together make a family
maybe not you and me but maybe turret
with wheatley that could work you guys
are robust right
wouldn't that work
for him over the rails oh why did i not
do that
i should have done that
karen is the girl something right now in
order to escape we're going to have to
go through her
and she will probably kill us
if she's um awake if you want to just
call it quits we could just sit here
forever that's an option
sit here do nothing option b go through
there and if she's alive she'll almost
certainly kill us
[Laughter]
well if we just sit here and then we'll
probably also die because we don't have
food or anything at least i'll just so
if you've got any reservations
whatsoever about this plan now would be
a tremendous time to voice him
well i think we'll be fine if you talk
to
uh the moment we walk in there she'll
fall asleep just because
you talk like a waterfall and that might
bore her to death
yeah i think we're gonna be fine the
card's on the table i don't want to do
it i don't want to go in there don't
don't go in there
let me pick you up back over she's off
oh fine here we go
huh
she's off
oh that's her there she is
what a nasty piece of work she was
honestly like a proper maniac oh the
whole thing is
not taking her down in the end you're
not going to believe this a human i know
i would have believed either
[Music]
um absolutely nothing happened and then
there's us escaping now so um that's
pretty much the whole story up to speed
don't touch me what what and there was a
lot when
she's dead for real right right right i
mean
how long has she been sleeping
she's dead right she's not gonna
suddenly wake up and we have a big boss
fight
can i walk in that water
yes okay i was scared of walking in that
water
oh
yeah yeah yeah this is where we dropped
little ball things that looked exactly
like you lately that's kind of
oh isn't it it's not sus why did it look
like you lately
should i
open this up and drop you in
you'll you'll be free in a different way
oh
wait
i have an idea i have a theory
oh no why did i just
then just figure out the story
is this one of her eyes and she's trying
to deceive me trying to get
um
to get me to help her
oh
no
oh no wheatley i cannot trust you
oh stainless steel oh [\h__\h]
i said jump
actually look at it that is quite that's
quite a distance isn't it
well we can roll the credits now because
i know that thinking
you're awesome although no braces on
your arms though so you're gonna have to
relax can you go first can i drop you to
keep a grip on the device and bike i
think for it
you guys like experiments and testing i
think for experiments sake you should go
through your spine either so so don't
land on that um all your head no braces
shut up already
still held still being held
i wish i could drop it tremendous
i wish i could drop you a little [\h__\h] i
know you're deceiving me i know it i'm
smart like that you didn't think i was
gonna be that smart al ah i'm just sorry
i just looked down i didn't think so
someone only someone as smart as
look down only someone as smart as me
can stay alive for so long oh oh this
one is the main breaker room oh let's go
in
what the [\h__\h]
look for a switch that says escape pod
yes don't try something else
anything else don't touch anything else
don't you don't even look at anything
else yourself just gonna look everything
else to find the escape pod but as soon
as you look to something it doesn't say
escape pod look at something else look
at the next thing all right but don't
touch anything else or look into they're
so funny maybe you should be looking
with your big eye i can't see anywhere
uh tell you what plug me in and i'll
turn the lights on
that does not help that's
god
ominous but probably fine long as it
doesn't start you know moving off
now
escape by escape pod
this is moving up okay okay no don't
worry don't worry i've got it i've got
it i've got it this should slow it down
hey didn't we want to turn something off
power up initiated okay don't panic all
right stop panicking
still stop this hey um
hey
there's a password i'm not here i'm not
i i i i i
[Music]
it's been a long time
how have you been
really um
being dead you know after you murdered
me you did what
i didn't do that no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no and you don't act
like you don't know whether you know
everything
we both said a lot of things that you're
going to write
but i think we can put our differences
behind us
for science
you monster
i will say though that since you went to
all the trouble i will say nothing until
i have my lawyer by my side
oh i love it too there's just one small
thing we need to take care of
mommy i'm dead game over bad ending it's
not like i have much choice yo
this is what you get for helping others
could have perfectly fine escaped on my
own
oh you know nom nom
my dynamic super hot body escaped all of
that and look at me i'm still alive
the incinerator room
not to trip over any parts of me that
didn't get completely burned when you
throw them down here
the dual portal device should be over
now remember that uh once you find it
it several times gladys do it
wait i still don't have my orange gun
wait i don't have my
i can't even use any of my guns now
oh you're okay
guess we gotta go without oh oh cubes
now
come here no no no come here come here
baby come here i'll catch you coming
through did you hear that that was so
cute
i
hold
on that
is that my gun
okay you're gonna give it good you have
to do a portable device you should have
all the way back to the testing area up
ahead why are you helping me
why
why are you helping me
why are you helping once testing starts
i'm required by protocol to keep
interaction with you to a minimum
luckily we haven't stopped testing
this will be our only chance to talk is
that like
is like testing like her fetish
is this for her having fun right now
pinky
[Laughter]
it's her way of getting satisfaction i
understand
here let me get that for you what
do you know the biggest lesson i learned
from what you did i discovered i have a
sort of black box quick save feature
in the event of a catastrophic failure
the last two minutes of my life are
preserved for analysis
i was able well forced really to relive
you killing me again and again forever
oh you're welcome you know it's not
beautiful to somebody else they might
devote their existence to exactly
revenge
than that i'm happy to put this all
behind us and get back to work after all
we've got a lot to do and only 60 more
years to 60 more more or less
i know what's going to happen in 60
years what's in front of me
what's gonna happen
what's gonna happen in 60 years is that
the end of the world
oh my life's all
60 years that's pretty hopeful because
by now my character is probably already
like 50
considering the amount of time i've
slept mean i still i don't look like 50.
i look i look like i haven't aged at all
but
like not even my hair has grown
[Laughter]
oh
i was kind of frozen
well can't we not just do that again
all right anyway oh sorry i was
distracted with talking are we going
over there
i suppose so
maybe i'll go like this
that's better
oh
oh oh
what just turned on and why did it turn
on that's scary
oh 19 though
so far already speed run it really is a
wreck for the one speed run important
thing is you're back
with me
and now i'm on to all your little oh so
nice you're opening the path to stop us
from testing
for the rest of your life
after that who knows
i might take up a hobby
maybe
really i'm meeting the dead
we're animating me you mean
yeah so i'll never die
yay
[Music]
don't really need you to do that she
doesn't know i'm a phoenix she's lacking
critical inflammation
[Laughter]
[Music]
the cold boot
boots are supposed to be warming worry
about the mess i've really let the place
go since you killed me by the way thanks
for that
oh good that's back online i'll start
getting everything else working while
you perform this first simple test which
involves deadly lasers and how test
subjects react when locked in a room
with deadly lasers
yay
deadly lasers
one i don't remember there being deadly
lasers in one
um
there's water
did i fall into the water
come on
no no no no no stay there you're not
gonna move right
okay ah
oh i'm so smart
i need to go there first can i
yes yes yes
myself
i forgot how good you are
you should pace yourself though
we have a lot of tests to do i'm pasting
myself nowhere we're doing two streams
today and tomorrow
i got an achievement i'm discouraged why
what what did i do did i do something
special
i'm just playing the game
normally okay i was smart
and that was that was fast time
surprised that was easy too
this next test involves discouragement
redirection cubes i just finished
building them before you had your well
episode every summer so now we'll both
get to see how they work oh something
new in the corner
in the corner
which corner
jump
oh this is fun it's like
don't look at me
huh there we go it's like one of those
you know uh secret agent thingies
which corner
where is that
cute oh
oh pretty oh hello wheatley
sweetly
that was not replay was it was it we win
it look like wheatley
whaley little [\h__\h]
where
that wasn't why did he not speak why did
he not speak to me huh
oh redirection
um
oh wait i don't want to hurt myself
what is love glados don't hurt me
don't hurt me
no more
what is love lottos don't hurt me
don't hurt me this will be our song
gladys our songs i need another cube
can i get another one
there's another one in there
i'm gonna get another one
oh wait what did
it closes
oh wait i didn't i don't even need this
anymore
no mine oh no i don't need this still i
got them it
ah
i still need it
[Music]
keep that portal
i'll pick you up i'll pick you oh oh
it's happening to me too
where are we which side there we go oh
what happened with my other heel
it destroys the other one what
how would i know that
until i experiment with it
but
wait ah
hmm
i think i have an idea i don't know if
it's gonna work but i assume i might
have to use this too maybe resistors up
yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
hi
okay well done
i just needed to find out that
i can't get more than one cube okay and
then i knew immediately what to do a
horrible person
we weren't even testing for that
you're so [\h__\h] rude
wow
you're a horrible robot
and that's actually impressive you know
because a robot
i'm in this game i'm a human okay and we
we just you know we are
don't let that all kinds of things but a
rabbit being horrible means that you
were
programmed to be this way or or you
somehow managed to be so horrible that
your system was overpowered with your
horribility ah
anyway i spoke all over you i don't know
what you said to me it's not like i care
[\h__\h] you gladys
what are we doing playing games again
yeah yeah
i want that
i'm coming to get it
and i'll bring it
over there
can i fall from there uh-huh
i almost thought i heard meows
beautiful
should i go there too
because it didn't land it almost landed
perfectly
okay now we stand it here easy
uh
what else
is that it
nope
[Music]
first of all take care of that
oh yeah yeah
wait i need to look at this from a
higher perspective
so we have
one cube glowing from here to here
and we want another one
oh
ah
can i
open this up with a laser
it's on the same
height but how would i even
how would i even redirect this one oh
wait i took a look at it oh i just saw
this now
on that
case
how do i
um
i remember we did something like this
before
congratulations oh my oh my
most people emerge from suspension
terribly undernourished i want to
congratulate you once
[Music]
i don't not particularly just i just
feel normal i feel like my brain is a
normal capacity
[Laughter]
did she call me fat
oh i filtered that one out because
i don't feel like she's talking to me if
she says i'm fat that that can't be true
so she must not be talking to me
ah why not
the thing is if you if someone insults
you and you feel you feel like that was
directed at you then there might be a
little bit of truth to that insult
do whatever it is you do when you're not
destroying this facility
you're building it right now huh
wow i like that floor that's like a
marble effect that's not on purpose i
know but it's pretty nice
i would like to have this as a table
all right a portal
portal this knit
portal 2
there's one thing here
oh wonderful wait i don't want to get
hit by that
there we go nice
kind of dangerous dell we want to go
over there
wait should i make this portal after
going over there
maybe
because that one i can still make even
when i'm here
now what does this do
give me a cube
ah
okay
now we go on the platform
i don't know where we go oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
okay continue
i guess you are listening to me no i'm
actually not most of the time
oh my god
that was fast
where's the oh there we go oh you're
still building okay okay
i'm too fast yo i'm speed running i'm
too fast
i had to get over there but i need to
first get rid of the laser no you know
you know you know
you have a big brain thinking time i
didn't expect that huh
hey thanks for cleaning up again just
involves the aperture science aerial
faith plate it was part of an initiative
to investigate how well test subjects
could solve problems when they were
catapulted into space results were
highly informative oh goodness knows a
lot about being catapulted into space
when i did a test is good at gladys
sir
holy [\h__\h] i i need um i need to um can i
join council i don't want to be too
close to gouda right now
hey
i got a point
oh my god i'm in danger guys help me
can you guys help me i feel like i'm in
in very bad
oh [\h__\h] i didn't expect that okay
very grave danger
what did that do
oh
wait
was that happening because i activated
that
i guess it dropped one
and now it's just bouncing there
but we need it here
oh
it's just gonna kind of hold me back
do i need to catch it while i'm flying
no [\h__\h] way
how high am i gonna be
uh flying anyway
let's test it
oh wait i don't need to i was thinking
you know while i'm flying maybe i'll
fall through here and then fall through
there and then land it on the other side
again but
yeah don't need to do it in one go i
guess we can go back
nice
oh that's too easy i was thinking too
complicated
you are not breathing really
it's too expensive to pump the spot down
you just take carbon dioxide out of a
room freshen it up a little and pump it
back in
so you'll be breathing the same room
full of air for the rest of your life i
thought that was interesting i don't
know this is interesting
wow i expect i respect the
science behind that interesting stuff oh
so let me pour some water this water is
not reused hopefully
the next test is oh advanced aerial
faith plates
currently i don't mind doing tests of
you this is actually fun so far entirely
of glass and pick up 15 acres of broken
glass
by myself
guys is this even fun to you when it's
fun to me or do you only enjoy testing
when the test subject is in pain and not
enjoying it
should i enjoy it less
you gotta make it more difficult for me
um
wow
big room
big room both she just she likes both
testing is very versatile i suppose
what
where are we gonna go oh oh oh oh dear
oh
oh there
hi but where are we going
didn't i didn't think ah
maybe for here
but now
you need to go back
yeah yeah okay okay
okay okay okay i think i think i know
that one i can keep there um but the
other one i'll make while i'm flying
hi nina
yeah
look how smart i am
wow
oh god i almost first tried it okay
almost yeah i mean
how can you first try that anyway
how do you know so sometimes there's
still trash in them
try to avoid the garbage hurtling
towards you is one of them wheatley
that piece of [\h__\h] better come here oh
no turrican
oh okay bye bye can i get some some one
of those
it's the garbage it's gone now i want
one of them the button again
i want to further over there on the
button
you stay here it might be useful what
that's going to say
scroll scroll scroll scroll oh there we
go
let's go
wait what did you say before let's go
she said to press it again
oh
there we go that's what we actually want
come here
reina did you ever play
a portal
i hear a radio
oh [\h__\h] i should have caught it uh
can i
wait wait wait wait wait
um
and wait can we just
fall together
yes we can
did she say did she say i played both ah
why did you play it on stream
did you play it on stream
oh [\h__\h] how did we get back
yeah i'm [\h__\h] no i i'm i'm really
[\h__\h] now
i think i have to yeah kill myself oh
wait no maybe not um
oh yes
ah no maybe not
you guys give up too fast
oh yeah portal one also gave me a little
bit of motion sickness too yeah about
smelly garbage standing around being
useless
that was a metaphor i was actually
talking about you
and i'm sorry you didn't react at the
time so i was worried it sailed right
over your head which would have made
this apology seem insane
that's why i had to call you garbage a
second time just now
she's roasting me so hard
you know those what do you call those um
events where you have like a round of
people roasting you what do you call
that we should definitely get glados for
that she could handle all the roasting
that normally you need 10 people to do
she could handle all of that alone or
you just call it roasts
just a rose
roast the phoenix not the chicken not
the chicken not the chicken roasted
phoenix
only gladys is able to do it
but honestly i'll just be laughing i
don't mind
i don't mind it's okay
did you know that people with guilty
consciences are more easily startled by
loud noises
[Music]
i started one coming i saw it coming
also it wasn't even that loud anyway
just an interesting science fact
i was started by some other loud noises
i'll admit dad but that has nothing to
do with my consciousness
i assume that i can't jump over that so
i'm just gonna portal over there
before i risk it
did i accidentally fizzle that before
you could complete the test i'm sorry
go ahead and grab another one
well that's just mean
you're gonna take that away too aren't
you
no
okay
it was not funny
it made me sad you can't just take
companion cube away like that when i
finally retrieved my cube okay
finally after all these years
oh how do i get up there
no
i fizzled that one too oh it wasn't you
that was the laser i was trying to see a
warehouse full of the thing
absolutely worthless
i'm happy to get rid of them oh no
no no need to get rid of them
um do i see something how do i get up
there
a portal brain empty brain
made white cube oh yeah i have a cube
i have a cube i need to do something
with it apparently i
can't use it
to do something with the laser i don't
see anything there
oh maybe i need a new perspective by
being on the cube no
no
these ones won't work stop the laser
but if once the cube die one night
oh she took it away the moment i um
i put the cube into the laser so i
thought that it can't handle the laser
oh
okay well that was a legit um
thought process of me i would say oh but
wait now i need to take it away because
otherwise the platform yeah okay
what wait do i need a pump do i need you
with me
oh i might need to
uh place
our orange portal here eventually if i
need it if i end up needing it um but
for now it looks like we need a momentum
so we're gonna do
a blue one there
and
oof
oh maybe uh oh i can i can take cube
challenge with me
here it is hi well now we have you up
here pretty easily
um
now i don't know if i still need you
ah yes i do need you okay
you fly with me
[Music]
buckle your seatbelt companion
let's go
wasn't that fun
we can do more we can do it several
times as often as you want
[\h__\h] off
now we probably need to fly over there
with maybe even more momentum
can we do that
oh that feels good um
i'll leave you here okay you're safe
here
evil lady will not hurt you there every
test chamber is equipped with an
emancipation grill at its exit so that
test subjects cannot smuggle test
objects
this one is broken don't take anything
with you this one's broken
don't take anything with you
sounds like a challenge
does that go away though
it does
he ah on the platform
[Music]
ah
okay okay but we still got to go back
then right
we'll still have to go back
there is a
what if you don't take it with you maybe
maybe just taking it with you um
wait is that the correct color that i'm
using
do i just
yeah yeah it's okay it's okay it's okay
it's okay
okay so i just got an achievement but
it's probably not like i need the cube
right
i think that one was about to say i love
you
they are sentient of course you lied to
me
you said it was broken or was not
working
i didn't misunderstand right
my baby
no i should have kept it there who would
have been saved
no
[\h__\h] glasses [\h__\h] you
[Music]
oh man
oh man i killed i killed it emancipation
grills remember i told you about them in
the last test area that did not have one
[Music]
oh i have to go
wait this next test does require some
explanation let me give you the fast
version oh that's going to be really
fast
if you have any questions just remember
what i said in slow motion
i don't
uh is there a hole there
oh there's a hole but no way outfit for
that but a laser can fit for that
probably
oh no maybe i can just make a portal but
ah yo you
all right all right
here we go
that probably activates the other laser
or
ah no it just gives me a cube
uh-huh probably we want the cube uh we
want the cube on this side so i'll bring
it over here and then the laser can go
through the um
well we'll see i think i have an idea
uh the cube i will bring there by
bringing it through this yeah and then
we redirect it uh to go through oh it
goes further
it does go through the window okay
perfect it's not a real window i suppose
what
what's that
was that always like this
oh
i i
used portals to get to the other side
was that unnecessary
out of camera
it was more interesting the way i did it
come on
beautiful
oh it is it was more interesting the way
i did it
it deletes portals enough oh
oh okay well i may have been able to
walk through but the cube would not have
been able to go for another huddle
okay but no me going to the other side
to inspect alone was unnecessary though
with the portal i suppose i thought it
was a window
i thought it was a window
oh well i did everything correctly
anyway
are you okay
stop hurting yourself
stop it
glados what's up you were you left where
did you go what are we gonna do
the aerial faith played in here is
sending a distress signal
you broke it didn't you
there try it now what
interesting where are we going oh so
wheatley are you good i was just lying
there
[Music]
shut up right now at least i can afford
eating all that fast food without
getting fat unlike you gladys if you eat
all that fast food you'll explode
because you can't even handle
you seem to have food its load-bearing
capacity well done i'll just lower the
ceiling no wait but wait look
what do you mean you lower the ceiling
wait wait
[Music]
wait
what happened with whaling did we like
it crushed
cube generator this net
a cube generator
cube generator oh momentum
this name momentum destiny momentum
that's more momentum destiny my mom
would be so proud is there anything even
to use for momentum oh
yes there is there is that's a little
bit ink
a weird way of doing it but it works it
works
uh ah but wait it doesn't spit out cubes
yet
i need to go
there to activate it
what's up oh okay we'll just go here
first we'll just do this one first
and then we'll do the other one
momentum yeah
look at you look at i'm looking at me
oh look at me look at me being smart and
figuring things out without the help of
the chat
russia
oh
cube generated
noise
all right i'll be rb
into blue portal four times
okay we could have maybe done it
differently but it's okay it's okay it's
okay we're doing it like this
so redirect to
uh
over there probably and i'll send it
somewhere with a portal
she's not sure where
ah here here here here
there we go
that did open the door now i just need
to make my way up there which is not
that difficult
uh
um
except for
i need a portal for it but the portals
are currently being used
right if i
get rid of them it will close again
which means from up there oh i have an
idea because from up there i can still
make a portal one of these portals here
so i'll just i'll keep the blue one
intact
and i'll get rid of the orange one so i
can use the orange one to get up there
oh honestly i can do both
i can do both from above i will need
both anyway i do need both
so let's do the blue one here
and then
the orange one
here
look at you sailing through the air
majestically like an eagle like a
phoenix yo i'm not an eagle
but at least you didn't call me a
chicken gladys
could have really
pained me there but you choose to call
me an eagle
thank you i guess that was an honest
mistake probably
called me
where where was the insult i was i was
distracted by the fact that she
actually called me an eagle not a
chicken that's for me already an
improvement
an eagle piling a blimp what's a blimp
it's a blink 199 enjoy this next test
i'm going to go for seven what's the
number it's a beautiful day out
yesterday i saw it oh if you saw the
ears outside maybe not you ride an
elevator all the way up to the break
room
and i'll tell you about the time i saw a
deer again this sounds good okay okay
let's do that let's do that
ah wait i wasn't ready i wasn't ready
but okay
uh
oh there's a cube dancing over there
being played with we need to rescue the
cube
but how
momentum
so for example probably we'll have one
here
but the other one
let me i
will
see can i get
wait
i don't know how about here
this might lead to death
no
wow
oh i think
here
no that won't bring me here either ah
wait here
okay
gently there's a dangerous laser there
we don't oh
oh [\h__\h] we don't want my beautiful twin
tails to be cut off am i supposed to use
that momentum again
well i mean i need to get out of here
first
maybe
yes
maybe i'm confused
please
just maybe that was maybe the original
idea was okay
oh [\h__\h]
i'm confused
uh here
maybe just higher
just a little bit more
a little a little bit more
wait where did i put it originally ah
here
at the very maximum
come on
uh wait i'm i'm confused
what if
what are we doing right now
i forgot what i was doing
is that what i was doing
[Laughter]
it works
i have the cube
where was a button i don't remember
seeing a button
hmm
deal with me we're just going to go for
a little walk right now
we just end up here again
[Music]
okay
this is better um
i don't see a button
[Music]
am i still supposed to like
throw myself over there
huh
do i have a queue
what is the what
i wait
let's take the
cube with us
what's happening
ah
oh wait i can just
i was like
how how do i let go
i didn't say there was a platform there
oh maha mahama
now now we can try to catapult even
higher right we want to we want to end
up up there
um
our best bet
is
[Music]
we're gonna be in the middle
it will have to be here
and that's not enough
but maybe making a portal while flying
again you know after going one through
once
i don't know oh [\h__\h] what
what what what what what what what what
what what what what what what what um
hmm
huh
where'd you go
must be somewhere up
hello
good for you good that you're here now
um i'll need a laser
to go through
um
let's not mess it up okay
was there even a wall there
maybe maybe it's maybe i have to replace
it
maybe i have to replace the normal cube
down there with a reflection cube is
that too am i thinking too far
and then use that cube that i have down
there right now over there
because i just need a normal cube over
there is that am i thinking too deep
okay well we'll we'll try it out uh by
uh just jumping down yeah
thank god there's no fall damage
um i i just wanna
no no no no no i don't
[Music]
okay no it's okay ah this is connected
this one's connected okay i'm good i
forgot i didn't realize okay so
we'll take this one we put
we put uh this one redirected to
uh
a wall yes this one where we can what
color was that blue
redirected there
that's just ost or
is it working
yeah
that looks like it's working so far
now i just need to
go back up there
without hurting myself
now that's thinking with lasers yeah
[Music]
i didn't see the dare today i did see
some humans oh they're still humans i've
got more test subjects than i'll ever
need
[Music]
can you not switch me out i'm losing my
brain compact
capacity capacity
you're making me lose brain cells glados
you you'll have a better time testing
with someone else at this point probably
maybe switch me out for a newer model of
humans
what do you think doesn't that sound
nice a fresh new test subject
fresh out of the
overworld
these bridges are made from natural
light that i pump in from the surface
if you rubbed your cheek on one it would
be like standing outside with the sun
shining on your face ah it would also
set your hair on fire so don't actually
do it
okay but it's just standing on it is
fine this is new
oh can i send the portal through a
portal at the bridgepro portal is that a
thing that we can do
it is
oh but i want it higher
i want it up there
[Laughter]
now hold
don't worry i understand
these bridges are made from natural
light that i pump in from the surface
if you rub your cheek on one it would be
like standing outside with the sun
shining on your face it's even crossing
paths now
of an intersection guys all right what
happens if do i get a did i get a
cube
yes
no it dies down there
wait idea um we need we need a bridge to
stop it from falling we need to pick it
up
so
oh it doesn't go that far
it doesn't go or it doesn't go through
the uh window i guess there is a window
on that side too
and
i guess lower lower is an option too
maybe is there
ah
[Music]
no it's not an option it's not an option
how did i do it before
didn't it go for it before
it doesn't go through it doesn't stop
the oh but what is that
is that a reflection
that thing there is that a reflection
or is that actually there
ah
uh brain hurts brain hurts
oh my god
maybe if i
have a bridge going from there we can
stop it but like what
what
give me a moment i need water
wanna go back
uh
i i wanna
i wanna go back
[Music]
oh yeah
okay
uh
[Music]
uh maybe i can walk around ah
um
if if i were to make a orange portal
orange right
orange here now
the bridge would probably need a bit of
time
to build itself right it wasn't that
immediate so i would fall
before it can catch me
or am i going to be fine maybe just do
it kind of lower
it's pretty fast
up jump
oh we're fine we're fine
but now it's pretty low
now we put it uh
here
oh no no no no
and then we can catch the cube
okay
but now we want to go back oh oh no
problem no problem
cause we have a portal
wow okay
now we just need to get over there to
put the cube on the button
um
maybe maybe was there like
a wall there that i could portal for
that would be too easy right maybe the
floor
ah
or
the ceiling no the ceiling no no we're
gonna just have to take a look at it uh
let's walk over there
now you're thinking of bridges first
portals then lasers then bridges huh
oh
no i don't see
i don't see anything to work with over
there but
we must
redirect more
i don't know how but oh no i don't know
how we couldn't build it
never mind
you guys just need to give me a moment
yeah yeah yeah i want it to be uh here
here remember the clean ones
okay
ah
no no no it's okay it's okay it's okay
it's okay it's okay it's okay it's okay
yeah
i don't worry about the chat backseating
i try not to look at it too much
whenever i need help whenever
to only look at it when i already
figured out something
okay
who's that big brain
wow excellent
you're a predator and your tests are
your prey
speaking of which i was researching
sharks for an upcoming test
isn't this never proof that gladys is
good at don't you think it's says as she
was researching sharks
do you know who else murders people who
are only trying to help them
did you ask sharks because that's wrong
the correct answer is nobody nobody but
you is that pointlessly cruel
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
what a [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
i'll wear this on you oh good news
i figured out what to do with all the
money i save recycling your one room
full of air
when you die i'm going to laminate your
skeleton and pose you in the lobby that
way future generations can learn you're
gonna laminate me unfortunate bone
structure
you're [\h__\h] insane
um
i think my delivery is already here can
i check
because apparently they just put it in
front of my door i think one second um
i gotta put my hello fresh delivery in
my in my fridge really quickly okay
and even
i'll be back
we're not reading super chats yet don't
worry we'll continue
[Music]
me
oh
[Music]
is
oh i'm back
it was already there
it was already there you shall
see this is exactly why i don't i feel
really um
i really don't want to leave like even
just for going to an idol meeting
in the middle of my of a gaming portion
because like what chad says 400 people
left this even though i said i'll be
right back
that's why i hate leaving even for a
moment it's so stupid
like you would have stayed if i would
have not left for two minutes what
no i said i'm not reading super chat i
said i'll be back in two minutes
yeah it's like the attention span is
like that little
oh my god
it's kind of disappointing sad why why
why you leave that easily come on we're
we're far from being done today i'm
playing for at least like two more hours
no we're not running super jets
um
what was i gonna say what was i gonna
say oh yeah that's why i always went to
go to the idol meeting um um until right
before i read super chats
okay okay now
obvious obvious don't troll me right now
i'm
even more people are gonna leave obs if
you throw me like that obs disconnected
for a moment but we're okay we're okay
return to game should i save the game by
the way i haven't saved it at all
oh
is it saving on its own
is this auto safe
oh there is autosave oh
okay
oh there's these bridges
oh
hard line bridges
scary
what the door is malfunctioning ah i
know somebody's gone don't smash me
repair that too
no don't get up
i'll be right back no
she says she'll be right back
everybody's gonna leave don't don't
don't go glados
oh sorry
sorry about ah dammit those
birds that's probably the bird in it
that laid the eggs
livid
the point is we're gonna break out of
here all right very soon i promise i
promise i just have to figure out how to
break us out of here here she comes
just keep testing remember you never
sold me
where is she
how did you know she's coming when she
doesn't have a body right now not living
anymore
anyway
back to testing yeah important things
we're testing that's all we all we need
okay uh cube uh-huh do we need a bridge
again yeah i see one there
okay
um oh you know what we could try to land
on the bridge
let's see if it's close enough yeah okay
well we are on the bridge
we want it to
save the cube again
uh let's see
it's probably on that height
so
wait i don't want to fall down
i'm scared they'll fall down
we just need
the blue portal here
and then the orange one there
but am i gonna am i gonna fall down no i
don't know how about we um how about we
how about we
do this
okay
this is this is okay
how
how do i get up there again
no i need to be i need to beyond
i wonder no
yeah yeah come on
okay start from before
start from before
okay
thinking of bridges
yeah we could lower it maybe like
this
yeah
or actually
considering that the height of this
platform
is where that line is
and the portal might go through like
around the middle or like more like the
bottom of the portal at the bridge might
go for the bottom of the portal
okay
now
uh
wait wait
brain
oh it's okay it's okay ain't going
nowhere we're fine we're fine
we're fine
it's just a very
dangerous feeling you know living on
living on edge when you're on that
bridge that could disappear but not in
this case okay
and now we wanted to go over there
which
probably just we need a bridge again is
on this side of the platform
[\h__\h] wrong color
i just wanted to look though
oh well we will go with the cube
take a look
and yes
we see here
we could place it there that or even
lower that should be okay
and uh orange
there we
go that's pretty simple
okay cool calm down
in fact you did so well i'm going to
note this on your file in the
commentation section
oh there's lots of room here did well
enough
well that's enough i'm fine if in my
life i just did well enough then
i'm fine with that
that's okay we don't need to over what's
the word
over perform
this next test life is tough man so many
things to deal with can't always
overpower things that are full of
bullets oh my god it's dropping its
bullets
good luck
you see me in five seconds
okay one
two
three four five
hey
[Music]
sorry
are you dead now no it's not actually
that is it
was it
it's not functioning anymore okay no
we're fine now um
no no no don't deploy don't deploy
i'm really bad dealing with you
okay
okay i put you down i put you down okay
uh
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no no no no
okay okay so far no
self-inflicted damage
actually surprising
okay
i see you do you see me
do i need to use the cube
no no no no no no no
search continue searching
oh
there's many cubes why is there so many
cubes
wait that doesn't do anything
[Laughter]
ah
that's when there's so many cubes
okay okay
okay okay now let's take another one
although now we can ah just use the same
one
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
is that gonna land on it
yeah okay that one worked now
one of them we can just
push over but that one that one i don't
like that one
not there i'm not
is that gonna
is that gonna land on him
i know
hello i'm not sure
oh we can look we can look for the
portal
and see if we're right oh that's pretty
good i can also go myself i guess but
drop
yeah yeah
wonderful
beautiful placement
and now we're just dropping around
what's he gonna
oh
i destroyed them all
almost missed you
at least you
had first row tickets to look at this
beautiful scenery
of me killing oh
the turret so i can't take you i'm sorry
i'll take this
zombie turret
you want let's clean up i'm gonna do
gladys a favor she's gonna be so
thankful
[Music]
she's gonna be like oh my god i'm gonna
hire you as a maid you're not the
testing subject anymore
you're gonna work as my maid from now on
cleaning up one by one
say i am i am the highest rated maid on
yelp oh [\h__\h] i can't do this
the cube too i guess
we couldn't take it with me so where's
my where's my yelp review gladys where's
my
where's my praise
huh
no nothing
what about talking to me in five seconds
what happened to that
yeah
what why is no one talking to me
[Music]
and add adrenal vapor to your oxygen
supply
so you may be confused about the passage
of time
the point is yesterday was your birthday
i thought you'd want to know happy
birthday to me
happy birthday to me
happy birthday
dear quinoa
to oh
[Music]
uh i thought i could be smart but no no
not smart enough oh
i know i'm no no no no no no no no no we
can do this yeah yeah we can use the
laser to go for all of
[Applause]
them it's the hint to not use it in the
first one
but instead use a portal to go oh
go for the first one
and then
[Music]
usually
this one
there's one missing
maybe yeah the angle i was thinking so
too this angle
could work
or or that angle
thinking so maybe
um
we'll we'll do this one instead
now it's
working oh
what no it's not working
eh
now it's working
uh
[Music]
i know what we need to do
but i'm not quite sure yet how we're
gonna do it
maybe i don't need the fruit i'm
thinking too complicated
right i don't need the cube ah
if that works there then
then wait we can just ah we can't get
two from here
okay
okay okay okay it was fine using the
cube here and not a portal first okay
then
we go from here and we activate
this last one how i'm going to live
forever but you're going to be dead in
60 years
well i've been working on a belated
birthday present for you
oh
more of a belated birthday medical
procedure
[Music]
medical procedures can be pretty
expensive so
not a bad birthday present
experiment sounds a little bit
less exciting that sounds like it can go
wrong
but considering how expensive some
medical procedures are
you know
what what would i need to get done
though i'm perfect the way i am
very complicated and creative solution
creative what do you mean
what do you mean creative her gift or or
my solution of the riddle wasn't mine
the most obvious one [\h__\h] it's right
here in your file on other people it
looks fine but right here a scientist
has noted that on you that is impossible
my image color is orange should old
engineer know about fashion he probably
oh my solution was different still what
does she know oh wait it wasn't easy
away
in fashion
from france
what i
normally one would make a portal to hit
two at once
oh
and
don't mind that i wouldn't call my idea
creative i know
[Music]
protect me
hello
[Music]
well that's cool i'm protected but
what's next though can i go through here
okay i'll put you down
oh i can fit through too
i'll leave those for where they all go i
think um i prefer not moving them
i was just trying to make some do some
groundwork you know okay maybe maybe
maybe maybe maybe maybe
do i need to protect myself again
this is it
[Music]
before that was it what about you
goodbye goodbye
harry lost okay okay that works okay so
the idea
the idea is uh fine the idea works
um
oh there's a lot to look at here
and they're projecting a cube over there
so i will have to
somehow
get by them or kill them all
oh um
is it too early to test this out
at least i can get to the side
guys i need i i will need a moment to
think about this
oh no
i don't know
this is this is too complicated for me
i'll go wait
[Laughter]
that is dangerous
um
okay so we don't want that interesting
that opens up the door so how about we
just stay in this safe zone that we have
created until now
never leave
or or i just run in there
quickly bump them all over can i even
run there oh up there
probably not
well let's let's let's jump again and
see what we see
ah
we would like to ah
momentum is there momentum
somewhere
i want to land over there
ah well how about
we can try to
oh no
don't look at me
um
i'm thinking
does this work no
no it wasn't about it no it's not about
the color
i want to
i want to get out there
how how
i can't just
i can't make that jump
i lost my bridge oh yeah oh wait i
should use my bridge
ah
uh bridge
[\h__\h]
i need to go back
[Music]
you saw nothing
nothing at all
bye bye
okay uh
yeah i couldn't thought of that
the bridge
it's the bridge
on the bridge
[Music]
no but that is i need it to be a
oh wait it can stop me from
from
flying oh
wow
that's why it's that way around
hold on
[Music]
um
do they really want me to jump in the
middle is anyone there would you come
over here
would you come over here i guess i i
guess i will
um
[Music]
that was scary
that is something only a crazy person
would do oh
stop me okay thanks
nice dominoes yeah we had a domino
effect um now
oh
sure um we have the cube but i don't
really want to open it ah
i could can i
uh create
no i have to
wait no no
no
no no no no no no stop can you stop can
you stop
i'm not here
no no no can you can you stop hello
we need to make it go for one of the
side doors
perhaps wait do i even need mine
no i what if i land behind them do i
even need my my bridge still i don't
think so
um um um
[Music]
[Laughter]
you guys also said run i tried how far
are we now okay okay okay okay
that was maybe not the most ideal way of
doing it huh
we'll figure it out
well this is the kiana way okay
um
how about we we already prepared this
okay
oh
ah
leave it there beautiful
[Music]
okay okay okay
wow
i managed to find two with your last
name
a man and a woman
so that's interesting
it's a small world oh you mean my
are you threatening my parents
is she threatening my parents
but they weren't even put to sleep at
this point wouldn't my parents be dead
anyway
that's probably
dead
she found it because you probably found
her dead bodies waiting for you after
this next test
look at those colors oh well i told you
that one was [\h__\h] get rid of that one
the zebra one too no not looking good on
you
the pastel colors look good on you
and make you look more gentle
don't know the turret fell
oh they're looking more military-ish now
oh this one just wants to be a wall
no no
well interesting color choices yeah yeah
you want to look fashionable maybe we
can have a fashion runway with turrets
yeah
are we going
i haven't been looking at the numbers
much are we going backwards by the way
also it was like 19 before but now we're
at 22
oh
what are you doing there oh you're stuck
in there
good night good night that's a mean
place oh
to be set in
oh god there's so many
what's this
ah
can i shoot them
oh my god
they're going up in flames
poor babies
poor babies all right um
i guess we can put
the i need to sneeze
i guess we can put the cube on it
um
perhaps we needed for something
uh
bushel
oh
this goes further oh [\h__\h] he said i'm on
fire yes you are oh oh no oh [\h__\h] well
okay i feel kind of
terrible now
glados might be right i might be a
terrible
being
she's not so wrong
[Music]
why are you singing this glados
why are you trying to tell me something
at what times do you sing that song
at birthdays
i'm not a psychopath it says this next
test was designed by one of aperture's
nobel prize it's usually what
psychopaths doesn't say what the prize
was for
well i know it wasn't for being immune
to neurotoxin
what does that mean is she roasting me
again because i don't understand it is
she saying
what what what's she saying
well
i i want to understand
what's she saying is she calling me
stupid
no she killed all the scientists oh
well i mean she doesn't seem to need
them so yeah good for her
um
doing her business alone
sometimes you just work better when
you're alone you know some people
don't need teamwork in their life
i'm trying to get her on my side okay so
i'm trying to
we are
trying to make her like me
but maybe it's too late for that
gosh
am i too fast am i too fast for you guys
to keep up can you guys keep up
oh no wait
oh
oh no we need to get up there oh so
portals
oh portals
it's not coming down anymore didn't it
go up because i put the cube there or is
it because of this laser
is it because of the laser
let's leave this one here
and
uh
can we
oh no never mind
we'll get up there maybe no movie
i'll just i'll just put this here for
now
is it gonna
wait what am i doing
hey
i am maximum confused
this one is tricky i will figure it out
i will figure it out so i think um am i
correct with uh the assumption that this
one went up because
i freed the laser
in that case
um
yeah okay
i will
go back up oh that's a little bit
wrongly placed
i'll go here again
now
we put it back down
um i have an idea i'm just not quite
ready to comprehend my own idea
leave it to me guys
i know what i'm doing so next thing i'm
gonna do
is put this here
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah um
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah okay okay now
we have it going down again
and now
i think it's in a position that if it
falls it drops on here
so i will already stand here oh my god
am i too smart i will already stand here
and i will let go the cube and we go up
i bet you well wow
in fact we're headed to your surprise
right now
after all
you gotta give me credit for that one
just thinking about it you've got to
give me credit for that one
i'm getting better at this guys
wow
wow chat you're just too nice you're
buttering me up are you making butter
chicken
phoenix butter phoenix
[Laughter]
true gamer opinion thank you oh the
surprise wow birthday surprise i've
never had a birthday surprise i think
getting surprised in three
two cake one
oh i made it all up
that's i like that thank you
that was worth it for me
if it makes you feel any better they
abandoned daddy both so i very seriously
daddy didn't even want to see you
no
no i don't think they did that no don't
lie to me you can't manipulate me like
that oh hello turret john
big room i don't like big rooms the
smaller ones are so
compact oh man
okay well uh i already have a light and
i i had an idea
what if i
oh that doesn't stop the laser another
hotel not sure if i if that's really
what i want to do anyway but
it is going through the laser right
maybe i should go down but i like having
an overview here right now
um
light doesn't stop like well who knows
it's a game it might have its own rules
you know
let's see where can we build things
it's pretty cool we can make a wall
anywhere we want
oh we need to get the laser to go
through these things
all three all four of them
and through here that one laser
i will need some cubes i will need a lot
of cubes
i won't need many cubes yes yes these
ones
okay
where do i start
[Music]
no
no no no no no dangerous
um
turret we want to kill the turret where
are you oh you're in a cage oh i don't
even know if we can take care of the
turret then
it's in the cage
oh brain
let there be brain
um
sorry sorry i'm using my brain so much
in the other room now it's taking some
time to
load up again
oh
well that's something for later that's
something for later uh
i don't know where to start
i don't want to start
uh
maybe um
where even is a button to turn on the
turn on the
thing machine ah wait there's two
is that two different ones no it's the
same cubes
start replacing a wall
oh we can walk like this
uh but where are we going uh maybe is
there something there
this is stupid this is stupid this is
stupid
no there's nothing there
ah
hold up
do we want to go over there maybe
so how about
here
uh
i may be hot no we can't go higher
i'm thinking like go over there and
invest wait why why am i
can i not just what why am i why am i
not thinking with portals
i wasn't thinking with boils
ah i was picking with bridges i can't
think of so many things
hello oh ah you're not completely in a
cage not a whole doll
um oh
did they uh fall into the water oh
there's a catapult there
uh-huh bridge this net
bridge
either below or or
in between
but
uh
where oh yeah bridge bridge here
wow
um
[Music]
now
now bridge
no bridge
[Music]
what scroll zoom in why would i zoom
well good to know oh
[Music]
ah
help me chad
now don't help me
don't help me dad
i don't know why i just walked in there
maybe it was the
maybe it was um
desperation
eh
why do you want me to do this
no bridges what do you mean no bridges
oh are you telling me to not think of
bridges
oh
yeah
are you telling me to knock single
bridges write a button again
um
now think of bridges
yeah yeah i know i want to block the
kills on the bridge but i don't see uh i
currently
don't see an option to make it go
through like on this height or
maybe let me let me go back uh where are
we okay let me go back here
only let me look at it
this can't be that difficult
so we definitely need a bridge
um
sorry guys
in german we like to say ich haben and
henga
ah
i do this it's like this if i do this or
something
oh
what
does that does that help me does what
just happened does that help me
no maybe not
look at it from a different perspective
oh
don't propose with me like that ah maybe
maybe that's not even the first step
maybe the oh maybe the first step is
working with this laser but no i need
one of those cubes the first step is
this
okay okay okay
okay
okay come on kiwawa
you performed so well until now what
happened
i feel under pressure
go back to the button
okay
go back to button um
um
[\h__\h]
protect me
okay go back to button
go back to button go back to the button
i'm back at the button
now this wall is sus too isn't i
this wall is us too
does this help us somehow no
[Laughter]
[Music]
i want the wall to go through there
somehow i mean i know the concept i just
don't know from where
wait don't don't give up yet don't give
up don't give up don't give up um
[Music]
no
that doesn't get me any closer
i know i need to stop the crash you're
like
but there's nothing there
oh my god
oh it took me so long to see that
took me so long
ah
yeah okay now now i have the cube now we
can uh
can i teleport this back up you know
okay well i would like to start by uh
killing this turret because it's [\h__\h]
annoying me
wow
well okay no first we can do this
then we have two of them running
um we still haven't we can get more
cubes can we
previously when we produced more they
got eliminated but there's still one
over there is the maximum of cubes that
you can have in the room too
or can i get unlimited ones
only two okay i thought so
so if i just uh push the button again
because i don't know how to reach that
one
but just push the button again this one
will disappear and i'll end up with
getting one more of those probably
so
i will um
go over there
oh wait first we place
this one
they will both disappear oh [\h__\h] yeah
right
ah the one that i already placed is also
gonna disappear
so maybe i don't need to work with one
just grab it
i think i can reach
oh
i didn't think i could grab so high i
need to
you know
i need to
uh
i need to i need to think um that my
character has more abilities than that i
think i i think she has
[Laughter]
okay uh
can you [\h__\h] stop shooting me
oh i see i see how it is
i see how it is
yeah finally
hallelujah finally we have some silence
here and can move around freely okay
but
um
what's about the last one
what about the last ones
[Music]
hey
oh wait
no
no we need them all we can't just use
this one directly
ah
can i
a different angle
maybe with a different angle um
[Music]
tell you what let's give your parents a
call right now i don't think my parents
want to see me like this right now
they'll just be face bombing
[Music]
maybe they worked at the phone company
no no no gladys i'm not that stupid okay
you may think i'm stupid by looking at
how long it took me to solve this but
i'm not that stupid no you're wrong
finally sorry that took so long oh man
oh man oh it's been almost three hours
so maybe you know
maybe my brain
is used up hi wheatley all the way onto
the old nanobot work crew rebuilding
this show they are reasonable
i know jerry no i'm on a break mate have
a break
are you
just hanging there but only australians
say mate jerry you can't fire me for
that
yes jerry or jerry your prejudiced work
site should have accommodated a nanobot
of my size thanks for the hate crime jer
i know a jerry took anyway look just
hang on
for five more chambers guys have some
problems what
what five more chambers is that what he
said
until i can meet
british people do do again you know the
old formula
comedy equals tragedy plus time and you
have been singing for a while so i guess
it's actually pretty funny when you do
the math
i'm interested in that formula because
i'm thinking maybe i can use it for my
streams
ah no not another big room are there
turrets yes there's turrets um
oh look at that little obvious cube
there
and oh an obvious one down there
but the lasers are
the laser is up very high
there's another one up there oh dear
free cubes
i already see
an opportunity for building a bridge
here
later
or or we're not building a bridge
there's no bridges here maybe
uh bill again letting the laser go for a
ride here
okay but um
i would like to
um
let's just start
with one
oh
are you are you done
okay
how about we start by going up there
because that seems very accessible
oh
never mind
oh no wait we can get that one
okay number one activated
when the floor doesn't know how to be
fly yeah
it's kind of cute though everything is
kind of
a robot everything everything we're
looking at is a robot oh [\h__\h] ah
can i not make any portals up there
should i have looked at the floor
was the floor
portal
portal portalesque can i make a portal
out of the floor
never mind we might not need that
there's catapults
[Music]
don't know
ah
we can get that one
i suppose
okay
i got the second one
we want that to go over there
um do we have to
play with momentum by any chance to get
over there because i only see the
these ones over there
trampolines
that one is actually pretty easily
reachable too
isn't it
or or maybe that's the perspective
playing games with me
but i want to go over there now so
that doesn't work that doesn't work
hmm
that must be a different way to get
there bye
what else let's go down i guess uh-huh
we can maybe
ah nice to see you ah we can use these
ones
but we'll need the momentum i think
right
now i already jumped down
uh
can i make portals while i'm holding
[\h__\h]
no
let's test it out
yay
okay
um
[Music]
what
didn't realize i could make a portal
there
what well that is a game changer
that
might just be well let's test this
why what oh
what
huh
that's not helping me right now
oh
i can't make a portal while i'm holding
this
but i want to go with it
or maybe
uh oh yeah uh i'll pick you up i'll pick
you up uh
which which color
i didn't oh
i don't understand
blue
maybe blue yeah i think blue
is this how you're supposed to do it
like picking it up while you're falling
there and making a portal in that very
same movement
was that necessary
oh my god
no that's a way
it works but no okay
but it's a cool stylish way to do it
don't you think
all right
now
uh
ah i have an idea
i have
an idea
once again we'll do the same thing
and then
i will make a portal um
or
which color
a orange one i think
over there and then while i'm flying i
don't care
i will while i'm flying i will pick up
that cube i will try
let's go
wow maybe too high where ah
i pushed it
[Music]
[\h__\h] so close
no problem
okay
oh that was it that's so that that was
an easy one i could have oh oh thank god
let's burn them first
oh no they cry i i'm not i can't hear it
oh my god
wow
okay once you have an overview of
you know everything then that's
manageable
now we need to fly again maybe and then
have me go through this one
about
i can only make the portal while i'm
flying
blue blue blue blue wait where are we
there we are
blue
right oh [\h__\h] oh sh
dangerous
something faster than me really
[Music]
with the solution that i honestly think
works out best for one of them it's a
difficult one too but i hated the room
before that even more this one was still
manageable that that one room with the
fridges oh man
oh man
you're doing so well nah
i got stuck in that stupid ass room the
rest was okay i guess
i feel embarrassed for getting stuck
like that you know
streaming this process makes me
makes one feel a little bit stupid you
know being exposed having their
stupidity exposed to so many people like
them you know
but there is less accidental
solves
than we had imported one right
last time i did a lot of accidental
jumps and all that but now pretty much
everything was on purpose yo
i knew that this next test chamber is
looking pretty good oh that's right the
facility is completely operational again
oh you caught up with me because i was
so [\h__\h] slow understandable yeah
yeah
right y'all
all right well we have lasers cubes that
are ready for me to use it it's almost
looking too easy
oh
but i mean
they're all
uh no i mean
[Music]
how about oh
where would that go
i
it hurts
if
is that uh if i put a portal there would
that get one of them
it would
wait what
no wait uh that's not how it works
i don't even need to
have it go there
huh
i
could for example do this
okay and then we have one activated but
i'm guessing we need the portals for
other things too
oh although
we could probably make one more i know
but
um
it's not a distributor
well that will be a little bit difficult
but i am confident
uh just like what's her name julie
andrews
i have confidence
something like that in me
out well we can send another one through
the same portal oh
where does that go
out
i'm gonna kill myself here
okay
if we send it in a little bit of a
different angle or maybe they all have
to come out of there but just in a
different angle right
mm-hmm mm-hmm i i understand
because i mean this one is
already angled which
is interesting um oh my god
help can i
maybe
i want to experiment a little bit
oh oh
can i send them through the same portal
what happens if i do that
oh wait what color what color what color
am i sending
let's send orange oh
i turned on two oh my god oh my god oh
my god oh my god
[Music]
that's playing music oh that's why she
likes alexa's room yeah it's a pretty
cool room
okay okay okay okay
uh which one are we now sending
this one
ah
[Music]
oh i'm sure we can make it well this one
should send it also for the same portal
well that was not so difficult wow
oh
yes right that was fast yo that was fun
i like this one i like this puzzle you
know just chambers look maybe just okay
i i think you know
all of us we have brains with
you know
you know some things are easier for
certain people than others and this one
maybe the other one was difficult but
this one the stuff like this is maybe a
bit more easier for me to comprehend
yeah okay maybe some of you had a hard
time with this one but had an easy time
with the other one okay no need to make
fun of me for having a hard time with
the other one okay
even better than they did before
yeah easy really it has music look at
things objectively see what you don't
need anymore
and trim out the fat
that's like also like um
you know how some people in school are
better at
math and and phys
physics and and chemistry and all that
so those kind of subjects and then
there's others that have a more creative
brain and they can like me
and
they're better at for example language
subjects or or
i don't know
other kind of subjects yeah yeah
yeah so
that's that's also maybe a connection to
how i see certain puzzles in this game
no feeling bad about being
uh
a little bit stuck here and there
not a fake tragic surprise like laughs a
real surprise a real surprise with
tragic consequences am i going to kill
companion cube confetti this time real
confetti the good stuff
our last bag is going to miss it but at
the end of the day it was just taking up
space are you saying like that but
that's the thunder and you talking you
using your last bag of confetti for me
i feel a little bit of love there gladys
where is it
oh this room looks familiar i remember
this room i think
class where's the confetti
where's the confetti
gladys
where's my surprise where is the
surprise what is the surprise gonna be
maybe at the end maybe maybe the
confetti is gonna fall out of there
instead of a cube and she's gonna be
like ha ha no cube for you
oh after the room ah okay
all right
well we start
with using the bridge i suppose
this way i can stop whatever falls out
of there
oh and push the button
cool
[Applause]
run your necklace more like this oh [\h__\h]
i'm running yeah okay let's go
which way okay quick recap we are
escaping all right that's what's
happening now we're escaping uh so
you're doing great just keep running
i can't i can talk
[Music]
making decisions okay oh it's both the
same way okay thank god yeah it's like
an airplane the last test
here it is
why don't you just do it trust me it's
an easier way out than whatever asinine
plan your friend came up with no
although i like solving your puzzles
i will use the other way
i'm sorry decisive though
the illusion of choice was it an
illusion
what would have happened if i went that
way oh would she have dropped the bridge
let's go lately let's go i will talk in
your language now
uh
can i go through the two perhaps oh [\h__\h]
what's happening oh no oh oh [\h__\h] no man
no oh kill me now oh oh
oh oh [\h__\h] these babies oh drop them
they don't fall down they have a
superior sense of uh a balance oh [\h__\h] i
can't do it what am i oh my there we go
this is what i wanted where am i going
[Music]
i can't fit through here i'm too fat
after all glad this was right
oh do i just need to kill them all
right
there we go
what now oh portal wait where are we
where are we puddling through
where are we going where am i going
there's no time
[Music]
maybe is there something there or
wait lee where the [\h__\h] are you tell me
where to go
is that where i want to go
you're okay great come on
otherwise which way which way this way
this way
it feels so dramatic almost like we're
at the end of the game but no [\h__\h]
way this is a longer game
i'm like only maybe halfway through
at the best at the best halfway through
in the left in the left is this a lift
not even halfway okay great good to know
all right whoo
whoo
not even halfway and it's so dramatic
oh my god
how are they gonna how dramatic is the
last uh like the last few areas
the escape oh we're far from escaping
according to my chat you can't fool me
game
bono
i i prefer the puzzles can we go back to
puzzles follow me we've still got work
to do because it makes me feel smart
please
um
okay
okay uh don't move [\h__\h] [\h__\h] it's too
dark
i'm scared and dark okay all right so
i've got an idea but it is bloody
dangerous
here we go oh
ah
you're a flashlight
they told me that if i ever turn this
flashlight on i would die they told me
that about everything but i don't even
know why they bother giving me this
stuff if they didn't want me to use it
they're manipulating you
don't believe them
like you're not allowed to get off the
rail and stuff like that they're just
trying to hold your powers back
they say that the old caretaker of this
place was absolutely crazy
chopped up his entire staff where are we
going robots it's too dark robots they
say at night you can still hear the
screams
of their replicas
all of them are functionally
indistinguishable from the originals no
memory of the incident nobody knows what
they're screaming about walking on dead
robot bodies
though obviously not paranormal in any
meaningful way let's keep moving the
factory entrance must be around here
somewhere okay
all right careful
you're too slow careful let me like this
jump for you
thank you you're funny uh
here i go
okay we're good thanks dude thanks
wheatley
stay close to me i'm scared about you
uh apparently you need me
i'll hold the leg steady oh down there
oh nicely done oh no nothing i just
dropped oh wait let me explain this to
me
weightly
lately
explain this [\h__\h] to me
hey
you've seen this
[\h__\h] carefree are you seeing this [\h__\h]
um
oh no wait we're good
unless
quick this way
okay we're good never mind kfb we're
good
i almost got a job down here in
manufacturing but uh
with only an exact duplicate of himself
ended up giving me the worst possible
job that's terrible they didn't deserve
it at all
the the um
sorry that's uh
you would have done such a great job at
it obviously sorry about that that just
that's just slipped i'm sorry for that
and then you might have been still you
know
happy working here if you got that job
you know yeah
yeah yeah that's not nice it feels
unfair life is just unfair for a moment
portal up to that passage and i'll see
you on the other side okay
watch where are you going
whitley
whitley wait lee huh
it wasn't you
can you reach that wall back there
well probably
that's an easy task kind of lately
apparently i'm here okay there's another
wall over here ah
it's like a tutorial again
uh what
i made oh i'll tell you humans oh i love
them
what now
i'm just that way okay
you can go ahead of me i prefer it that
way because if i go ahead i'm probably
going to fall into a big big hole and
then it's going to be like whoopsie
sorry kiwawa
didn't see that one coming
uh what the [\h__\h] lately
really wait
what do you expect me to do
yeah
right
well i'm gonna take this rail down the
back way
good luck
[\h__\h]
you should stay with me
and we're just going to walk
all the way to the bottom of this okay
all right i could probably jump but
no i like to have control over my body
authorized personal only factory is this
where you want me to go
or even further
there's uh something to land on here
[Music]
now
wait wait
i'm cool right there okay okay
leave a portal oh they don't work like
that they don't work through these
levels
these chapters
but it seems we were correct
is this like the ones that are broken or
are they currently being assembled
turret retention lines active
please do not engage with turrets
heading towards redemption redemption
redemption is that death
redemption arc being like
not very much redemption oh poor babies
oh
oh do i want to go there
you guys want to see what redemption
looks like turret redemption lines are
not rides please exit the turret
redemption line uh
well if i don't
where else could i go
what
can i go there no
uh
am i going in
nah
no way no
you went down
oh
you said jump
okay i could probably make that jump but
[Laughter]
[Music]
um jump up near the end
near the end
turret retention lines active
please do not engage with turrets
heading towards redemption turret
redemption lines yeah
i accidentally before you were even done
talking
oh oh oh oh oh my god workout oh by the
way i was uh oh hello i was on physical
therapy again today i talked a little
bit with the girl again
no hard feelings oh
well you know you weren't completely
dead yet so probably better to drop you
right
um
also
yeah a cute girl cute girl yeah just
asked her like why what what issues she
has what what
well why she's there and all that but
i'm not gonna share it with you because
that's a privacy private data you know
only a little bit though
oh there you are the one from before
thank you oh it's thanking me
how else can i help you
women got mad don't make lemonade
why not
prometheus was punished by the gods for
giving the gift of knowledge to man he
was cast into the bowels of the air and
pecked by birds
it's the birds again
oh is that all
i'll put you down here are you going to
shoot me if i were in front of you
no
oh you're so sweet
what a cute baby i'll take you with me
i'll take you with me
let's go dirt dan
yeah you're trying you shouldn't go in
there
i'll i'll i'll go instead okay
um i is is good gladys name carolyn is
that what you're saying
caroline
they're learning how to shoot me
by the way this time i ate breakfast so
the the
wobble machine
i had a way better time at that
time
open huh
[Music]
it was so exhausting though it's like
just for two minutes you stand on it and
it goes like
[Music]
and that's uh depending on how strong
you make it it's supposed to either like
um make your muscles uh oh
yeah
even
like not relaxed like um
lokem uh
what's the word for looking
[Music]
yeah loosen your muscles or if you make
it stronger it kind of works like a
workout because yeah it's pretty tough
to keep your
uh
when it wobbles that strongly to to
stand still
okay
is it gonna shoot me
no okay ah i mean
that's fine
oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] look good look good
oh you had one of those
i guess there's like cheap versions for
that you can use at home yeah cause like
um i know i heard of like
more
um
definitely definitely less intense
versions of that that you can use at
home and like you know what was it they
advertised so that you lose weight
without even doing anything
oh [\h__\h] template
response
template why are they doing that
oh if they don't answer correctly
response
hey you still have
the ability to respond though what's
what's wrong
it's not effective for template this one
is right huh
[Music]
template
response can you not repair them
[Music]
that's brutal
response hello hello hello oh so cute
can we have siri but like in that voice
and then that like
attitude and all that but just don't
shoot me you made it through well done
respawn follow me you're going to love
this
where's my coach glass had another big
surprise for me
my last battle's confetti she said
thank you very much yeah come on look at
the window good
see that scanner right there right it's
deciding which turrets to keep and which
to toss and it's using that master
turret there as a template if we pull
out the template
it will shut down the whole production
line which monster or that one um
i'm gonna have to hack the door so that
we can get her you can do it nicole um
you'll need to turn around while i do
this
all right i'll only be a second if you
wouldn't mind hey are you embarrassed
again
why no
he won't he doesn't want me to look
because
i'm still with my theory that this is
part of gladys and if i were to know i
would know how to hack things
and then i can use it against them
yeah yeah yeah yeah all right i look at
what
that's not hacking
never mind okay
you just want to look cool in front of
me huh
saying that's hacking but that wasn't
really anything
what what oh you want me to go inside
huh
that should do it
continuing from memory oh it hasn't done
it all right let's figure out how to
stop this turret line
have you got any ideas
wait uh any ideas any ideas no no me
neither no
no i never have ideas wait are you
actually expecting an idea from me
uh
i don't know
are you are you still thinking or what
if i put myself there
here
oh my god they scanned me i got an
achievement for that
is that not it
wait but
how did that one make it fruit if i had
to sample it
from the temple how did that one make it
through
yeah but why won't he use me
let's just both continue
contemplating
ian absolutely oh i like that
silence i like that that's beautiful um
um
can i push some buttons here
oh wait ah no no i got it i've got it i
got it really
no okay of course not where are you
going well i'm going back maybe i see
something here
okay
just do your idea and then come straight
back oh i think i might be right then
considering that reaction
am i supposed to go back
wait what
no is that that
response
template response
response sorry what's going on over
there i don't know
i have one what did i do with it
oh i put it i'll put the defect one over
there where the template is a broken one
then it will only accept broken ones
right response
response send another one
number one
template
response
catch i got it
when there's no way to go forward you
need to go back guys
remember that response trace your steps
guys
and think backwards
what what are you oh brilliant
if we're lucky she won't find out all
her turrets are crap until it's too late
classic okay keep your eye on the turret
line i'm gonna go and hack the door open
oh okay all right beautiful beautiful on
the back
it's a little can you say funeral pal
from your side it should take about ten
minutes
[Music]
this is funny i want to listen to what
they're saying
the broken ones are funny too i gotta
give you that the non-broken ones are
cute but the broken ones are funny
i want i want them at home to keep me
company maybe if i put some fur on them
they could be on my cats
and then at least they will be able to
talk to me
i'm sorry
i mean was there any sort of
announcement before open like a like a
buzzer or an alarm of some kind or like
a hacker alert
fair enough the important thing is it's
open but just let's just mention in the
future cough or something what what what
what's this problem
did i come too early
what's this problem no look what's my
dad
all right now she can't use her turrets
so let's go and take care of that
neurotoxin generator as well
okay that's smart
good good plan good plan i guess
what can we go in here okay
uh
bring your daughter to work day that did
not end well
what happened with them
14 potato batteries embarrassing i mean
i realized they're children but still
you know low-hanging fruit all that
barely science really
who brought their daughters to work here
electricity from a potato as well
totally
i need to
need to learn
i need to learn how that works that is
like next level [\h__\h] man
we never had a pro
experiment like that in
an hour school they're even using lemons
oh [\h__\h] those are some old [\h__\h]
lemons
lemon battery which one was better
conclusion
was the potato better
did you guys do something like this in
school well you know at least it's not a
potato battery i'll give it that oh
volcano we never did something like that
either
not exactly primary research i was
seeing in tv shows you did guessing this
wasn't one of the sciences so many is
that like an american thing but let's be
honest it's got it's got manual labor
written all over it hasn't it now saying
they're not as good as the professionals
you know they're just they're just a lot
dumber
is that an american thing we never did
anything and i went to several schools
and dubai too did it in europe what
and i want to make a volcano like that
wait and what subject did you do in this
this one
this one something like that in
chemistry or in physics or where did you
do that
no way too oh mexico what
it's science oh
science for you is what what we call
kimmy or physique
maybe we should make a volcano on stream
can we make something like this on
stream
[Laughter]
i wonder does anyone have the recipe for
a volcano
it seems to be baking soda and vinegar
is that it
wait let's see
baking soda
i don't know i can't read all that uh
aluminum foil a pen and some green
liquid
[Music]
ask scientists
i wonder if she ever made one what is
that ceiling
dolplex
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] and my potatoes are currently
growing stuff like that too but i'm not
not quite that far
oh my god
copy machine that's that's uh i just
scan my my butt
i can't damn it there's no electricity
well then the potatoes failed [\h__\h]
if only the potatoes wouldn't have
failed i could have scanned my body
[Music]
i really like that song
it's about walking one path
this is the path i will be working on
basically translated
no matter what happens
this is the neurotoxin generator a bit
bigger than i expected wow you'll be
able to just you know push it over have
to apply some cleverness
am i the one who will think of the club
let's go investigate
investigate
all right
thinking speaking of investigators i
watched a little bit of ammo's 3d vr
stream
i should um really they do feel pain of
a sore it's all simulated you know but
uh really enough for them did you guys
watch it
it's really cute
i really like she used like both her
real 3d model and the low poly one and i
thought it was really cute like
a real model
it's like so fluffy because of the coats
it's like always like floating i really
like that like i don't have anything
like that with my outfit we talked about
it before that like the
the the the tight fitting outfit makes
it easier to see my body movement and
all that that's true but i i love the
floatiness of you know ammo's outfit and
and and kelly has like you know her veil
and all that
there's a little part of me that feels
like oh
i want some some fluffy outfit too that
um
works like that mm-hmm i have some
physics with it
um
but did you notice did no way to hack it
did you notice your boobies were really
jiggly like weird jiggly
mine actually have the same issue when i
tested it um it out or like when i'mma
test it out actually with my model um
did you notice
yeah we're trying to get that fixed
though
yeah no
mechanism must oh now look at that
that's a big laser
doing this to ignore it though just
leave it be we don't wait i'm going here
it's cutting or going could be somewhere
important although it does give me an
idea what
if we stand here yeah and let the gentle
hub of the laser transport us to a state
of absolutely
it might help us thinking wait isn't
that the one i'm supposed to use for
portals
if i'm honest but i'm afraid it's all we
got at this point
silent contemplation are you just
waiting for me to solve it
sorry sorry
he is isn't he is that going through
that's not going through science
discipline here it comes
100 silence
well i mean
where where where do i stand in frugal
it was
here we go the hardest part of any hack
is the figuring out how to start a phase
that's always tricky
but let the games be are you really
gonna do something all right what have
we got
a computer
he's not doing anything what the [\h__\h] i
gotta do all the work again
look directly at implosion in case of
implosion wait what is the implosion
explosion is going outside this
implosion inside
why would i look
why do i need to look at the implosion
if it implodes
okay i'm having a a feeling that we
might need the laser after all
uh
cause uh otherwise uh he's just not
doing nothing what's the floor doing
can i just use the laser to blow up this
thing
yes i can probably
turn around
toxic levels up to 50
sorry my mistake can we do that here oh
yeah
let's send it over there is that one
gonna come out there again no i need to
use one of those
oh
you're so useless lately i'm thinking of
all the solutions by myself
yes
let's look at it let's look at it we're
supposed to look at it
[Music]
i thought it would be more like
dramatic than that
where are we going
i'm here
get in okay
[Music]
after all where did that come from
i can't believe i'm finally doing this
oh [\h__\h] is this good are you saying this
is good that we're going straight to her
it wasn't fun at all so they said it's
not fun at all i i believe that
years ago of course we should be getting
close oh i can't wait to see i would be
sick man no turret she'll never know
what hit her i would probably throw up
in this part though because i'm fine
there is oh
oh my god
yeah i'm going the wrong way kind of we
are laughs i'll find you
oh
it's like different a little bit i can't
play this exact game in vr
and i don't do
that but there is a vr pro program okay
okay
yeah oh my god imagine like vr portal
you make one here and then you make one
like somewhere else no not there but
like for example down and then you know
how you how i said it was so trippy when
you switch like
the you know
oh i can totally see that being very
very very trippy
crazy
oh yeah let's look at
that wow
why am i able to make a portal there
is there a reason behind that there's
always a reason
oh
this doesn't open does it ah there's
always a reason
oh i'm safe oh there's something here to
land okay
when you got through this easy one
why don't you let yourself get captured
this easily i would have just dangled a
turkey leg on a rope from the ceiling
toilet oh no is that the starting room
ah
well
it was nice catching up let's get to
business
i hope you brought something stronger
than a portal gun this time
otherwise i'm afraid you're about to
become the immediate person oh [\h__\h] is
it half time is this the halftime show
oh my god where's beyonce goodbye
[Music]
are you saying about that gladys i
outsmarted you
okay the idea was from wheatley let's
give him credit for that
well
i suppose we could just sit in this room
and glare at each other until somebody
drops dead
but i have a better idea it's your old
friend deadly neurotoxin
if i were you i broke that door
[Music]
in fact i feel pretty good alternate
core detective oh that's me they're
talking about to initiate a core
transfer please deposit substitute core
in receptacle
what
we can use him
as a part for him you are kidding me
i've got an idea
do not plug that little idiot
mainframe let's go you become gladys
maybe you were never glad to begin with
like i said
but maybe you're becoming gladys
substitute court are you ready to start
the procedure yes corrupted core are you
ready to start the procedure no oh yes
no no no no no
[Music]
yes do do it what do i do
which button you don't know what you're
doing oh there's a button there
think about this
no
trained stalemate
i'm not that stupid gladys i've learned
so much
it is true that you don't have the
qualifications you've got something far
more important no no glad it's so stupid
uh you're so stupid gladys
[Music]
uh
into the fortress
oh no not quite oh
no stop
you no i love it oh
oh
gladys
we're experimenting with you doesn't
that make you feel really really hot
we did it
that's pretty hot
don't mess it up dude you're going to
mess it up aren't you
massive it's not just me
is the power gonna eat you up
there we go let it cool oh
thank you is it a limousine please i can
barely see you
very tiny and insignificant yeah
i'm the protagonist i can't be in
significance
wait i know you gained the lift okay
then i'll eject myself out of my new
body into the lid how about how about
you don't leave it's perfect and just
keep this uh factory safe the way it is
now
let me tell you wouldn't that be better
to be in charge of everything but
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
uh
actually
why do we have to leave right now
do you have any idea how good this is
i did this
are you turning into glasses
is this one yeah i kind of said this
would happen
oh really that's what the two of you
think is it whoa yeah i did do it all
the
give me way back i guess we can do
puzzles peacefully
oh i see this is the halftime show so
i'll fight you now and then later i'll
fight the real glados again
but sacrifice to get us here
sarah all you've done is boss me around
you're bossing me around
that's right it's you
oh
i never had one of those i never had a
potato battery
sorry uh
where's the glass
generating an endless stream of terrible
leave steven merchant alone
oh no you made a match
can you leave me out of this
[Music]
okay not quite exactly what i said in
the very beginning
um but similar
somewhere up there mm-hmm the fall oh
yeah
that's gonna be a short chapter
slow
um i don't want that to drop on me
wherever we land
together with the express purpose of
building the dumbest [\h__\h] who ever
lived
and you just put him in charge of the
entire facility you both are morons both
of you good that's still working
why not both
what you want me to hold you what strap
you ow
potato
what are you cute is she gonna stay on
potato we can play with her we can put
air
we can hold her
above the fryer
and and and make her
panic
she's going to be like no oh no don't
fry me and all the already fried kf
chickens are just going to be laughing
like
now it's your turn to be fried oh
what the [\h__\h] birds are glad is away
oh can't be
hey
what the potato
we could have with this fire we could
have made some nice fries
on it
we're
kind of outside kind of
no one is with us are we escaping from
wheatley now
what happened with gladys
portals
what portals
what am i not seeing
ah
over there i was thinking too
high there you go
portals
okay
yeah well you know in portal one
the whole section with the the whole
escaping was also
i didn't like it as much as the whole
puzzle section i don't know because this
is kind of like
um
if this is gonna be continuing for the
next five hours which we're not gonna
all of it play today but yeah then i
must say that is very very very
stretched i should have had more puzzles
then
i mean yes all of this is a puzzle too
but you know what i mean i mean those
testing like rooms
i wanted to be contained in the rooms
and then be like happy after each puzzle
like oh my god i did it you know what i
mean
you know what i mean
this is nice too but not for another
five hours
keep out do not enter
but am i at 50 now
or still not
this feels like i'm in the middle of the
game right now
why are you telling me to zoom
ah i'm supposed to look for the portal
and find something that's far away
oh wait but i can't shoot for the portal
huh
wait what
where are we going here
no that's not the
white surface
forty percent
two thirds
and we can go for like i was planning on
five hours so
um we might not
i mean depends i might read some super
chat say yeah where the [\h__\h] are we
going
oh there
wow
holy nah
i suppose here and
[Music]
did i
come from there no
that is i hope i'm progressing
there's only one way right there's no
like
accidentally going back hopefully
can i make a portal for here huh with
zooming
no
where am i going
there's only one way i suppose i have to
go up here but um
[Music]
no maybe the other way
eh no
this is this way
it might have been this way
hopefully and it looks new to me
do i go down
it's so so quiet where the hell are we
this place is huge
[Music]
mysterious where are all the caspers hmm
it would be
kind of stupid to pull a lever when i
don't know what it does but okay let's
do it
oh it just opens the gate that's it
i thought it was more important than
that maybe it was more important than i
turned on the big light
two
one
yeah
uh-huh
and let's go to one first shall we
what's up
reclusion override what does that mean
too bad i can't speak english
26 10.
zero ew
that's uh
that's very fast what what what does
that even do
was that two
how fast do i have to be
oh
i guess we'll just make a portal first
oh gotta be very very very fast um
[Music]
we gotta make a portal
over there
uh
probably
and let's say
one here
where are we okay and that's enough time
i think so we push the other one first
does it matter
yeah it probably means like normally
needs two people one on one each side
and they have to press the button at
like the same time to open this thing up
probably
okay okay okay
oh [\h__\h] i
made some alarm go off
is that good or bad
eh
it's like the wind wake of fortress the
lights
they may not see me
shh sticks sneaky
sneak show come back
they probably already saw me
oh thanks for opening the door so nice
where does this place even lead to
where does this even lead to
oh and every chapter done that was the
fall
um
[Music]
really curious to see how
the rest of the game is gonna be
oh dear
okay don't enter the water i get that
i was shaking earthquake
did you sing
the factory is falling apart
nice music by the way
i want to go this way no i need to go
this way
no
portals by the way
portal
i'm here put one over there
no
over there no
yeah this is that's not the actual year
right now maybe that's just the year
where it was built
maybe this door
no
what about what about here
that's where it came from
missing something i feel like
ah not only white surfaces but sometimes
i try anyway to see if i
maybe get lucky uh or if i missed
something because of the lightning
sometimes they you know don't look
exactly white if you look at this
surprise wow
yeah some people might be thinking oh my
god she still doesn't get it but i get
it i understand
just i try some things you know because
it's better than not trying anything at
oh all
because that could be just as white as
that is like honestly that looks like it
could be the same that could in that
lightning that could be that could just
as well be one of those walls to be
honest
um
yeah
not sure now no
i understood
don't worry guys i'm not that [\h__\h]
stupid i understood in the very first
moment of playing portal 1
that the portals don't work on every
wall okay
you don't need to be like oh my god
is as stupid as a [\h__\h] egg
okay
yeah
just because i try out things
doesn't mean anything
did i go up there
would be too good to be true
egg brain
yeah cause i don't even deserve to be
called birth brain anymore i'm just an
egg brain at this point
where the [\h__\h] do i go i don't see
anything
oh
i thought that was sus
i thought that was sus but you know
being shown something like this you
think that you got to go all the way up
there
yeah i don't know
uh that open no
what leather
i just love it
coming through
where am i yeah
who is cape johnson
[Music]
did they use these people as test
subjects or to help them work at
aperture science
all the people who got fired
yes sir mr johnson caroline who's
talking about you
sorry married to science
ha ha
married to science
yeah
territon would have loved to marry her
if she wasn't already married to sci
science oh no
uh okay i see we're probably gonna play
with momentum here
um
i don't know
i don't know i don't know
where where do we even when i end up at
on this platform yeah probably maybe the
door can open
uh
okay
whoa too far
kind of kind of too far
cape johnson
og owner of aperture
was this always his goal though that he
wow poor deception
[Laughter]
[Music]
this is probably not the right way to go
uh
what
what's up there
oh my god
that is maximum momentum i don't think i
can get any more momentum than that
oh wait a second
uh
is that useful for me
because there's a there's an angled
platform
uh
so
[Music]
but
where would the orange need to be
i don't even know where i really want to
go at this point
or do they want me to go through the
logo
oh [\h__\h] well thank god there's no fall
damage
no
can i make that jump
[Music]
maybe if i run really fast
what
i'm overthinking
[Music]
wow bunk
okay well i mean
that was okay wow
[Music]
they are used as test subjects
those of you who volunteered to be
injected with praying mantis dna
i've got some good news
bad news is we're posting
definitely good news is we've got a much
better test for you fighting an army of
mantis men pick up a rifle and follow
the yellow line you'll know when the
test starts
oh man i thought you know because those
people what were they like scientists
and then spaceman and all that
it seems like
the kind of people you would want to
keep alive in order and insane in order
to help you build this kind of stuff but
they use those kind of people for test
subjects
all right we're going up
up we go
all the way to the top
yeah astronauts spacemen i like to call
them spacemen no need for fancy names
here we say it loud and clear
spaceman
is cave what's his name cave johnson is
that an actual person that exists or is
that person completely fictionary
what are we zooming it there
okay
um
which door is the chosen one or no door
at all
no door
if you need to go to the bathroom after
this next series of tests please let a
test associate know because in all
likelihood whatever comes out of you is
going to be cold
only temporary so do not worry if it
persists for a week though start
worrying he's real kidneys
i'm sure he is i'm sure he is darling
uh
what
are we gonna fly again
where are we going
momentum
momentum doko that's water
with that
huh
if you've cut yourself at all in the
course of don't talk to me right now i'm
trying to focus
pure gasoline that's normal we've been
shooting you with an invisible laser
that's supposed to turn blood into
gasoline so all that means is it's
working
don't talk stop talking
[Music]
is that
this is too big you guys know the bigger
the room gets the less i can comprehend
it
helpful
who's the most confusing part of the
game really
what
look at the elevator again
and there was a going down button but
do not do not fall down the elevator
shaft
[Music]
so is the elevator for momentum
hmm
but wait should i place a portal
somewhere before i do that like maybe
here
i'm going down that doesn't give me
momentum
walking down
i missed it i missed what
what what what
at this point
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] that was close oh my lord
jesus
know your hazardous materials don't
touch anything unfamiliar
that might not work with today's game
know your chemical hazards do not inhale
fumes no matter how good they smell i
don't think they smell good at all so i
think i'm good with that one
pump station alpha what are we pumping
oh we're pumping
water
blue stuff
oh
what
nah
that is a portal wall if i've ever seen
one
or we can try to close this one too
and don't lie to me
that's the portal one
all right fine i don't need that one i
can use any wall i want
baby
i don't need you
maybe maybe i can use
this
a little bit lower
eat low hmm
science is built on the shoulders of
giants
not here at aperture we do all our
science from scratch no hand-holding
why does everyone ban hand-holding
that's not that lewd let us hold hands
i want to hold hands you can't tell me
not to hold hands with my beloved ones
we need to ban the ban of hand-holding
justice for hand-holding
you know what i had today before the
stream
a bubble waffle
with ice cream and strawberries
yeah
it was yummy
and i even have dinner prepared
because i thought it's gonna get late
again i have some japanese food for
dinner i took it uh to go i got it to go
i'll warm it up afterwards i'm excited
for it it's called repulsion gel you're
not part of the control group by the way
i'm already hungry so son of a gun got
blue can't wait
all joking aside that did happen broke
every bone in his legs tragic but
informative or so i'm told
what
repulsion gel
was aperture's first attempt to create a
dietetic pudding substitute
ooh
it's true the gel is a sweeter slightly
less non-toxic form of fiberglass
insulation that causes subsequently
ingested food items to bounce off the
lining of a dieter's distended stomach
stomach and out his or her mouth for
various reasons this product was pulled
from shelves
do i sound smart now saying stuff like
that oh
wait can i touch it
is it
is it like pudding
can't make a portal on it i had to test
it what if i touch it
[Music]
oh
how fun
what is this why is that
oh you want to go up here
oh
big red button
where are your signs what are your signs
telling me
exit
yeah i thought so wait can i take some
of the pudding and they put it up here
i guess it's not where is it we need an
object
can we open this one up there's looks
like something is going to fall out of
there
[Music]
can i like
open it up by bouncing at it no
oh
okay we're back to puzzles yay
uh what if where was um
where's that thing uh up there
there we go
it's on now
[Music]
wait
boys you informed me that i should not
have mentioned the control group they're
telling me i ought to stop making these
pre-recorded messages that gave me an
idea make more pre-recorded messages
here i can talk about the control group
all damn day feel free to do so uh it's
nice to hear from someone else for once
next test chamber this way
[Music]
this whole part seems kind of unfinished
uh
where are the the robots that finish up
the the test chambers huh or am i too
fast again i can't i can't believe that
how do we go this way
this up here
[Music]
can i
drop down and fall into oh ah there we
go
no need for dropping down
from that oh oh this bite is from really
from 1952 then from when is the other
part
me a little bit there a little bit
did they just like start building it and
we're like [\h__\h] it ditch it and then
build the other one but why
for this next test we put nano particles
in the gel
in layman's terms that's a billion
little gizmos that are going to travel
into your bloodstream and pump
experimental genes and rna molecules and
so forth into your tumors
i didn't know i could even do something
like that
i learned a new skill
uh but we probably want to bounce
let's bounce kfb
who would have thought that
halfway through the game they teach you
a completely new function here um
okay we're back oh someone now we're
doing the puzzles of the old factory
okay okay okay i was hoping for some
some more puzzles i'm fine with this
we want to
get on there
can i reach that if i jump over there
oh [\h__\h] wait
wait for me of course not
um
[Music]
no
can the jump give me momentum too but i
wanna go that one
wait a second
but
yeah no that's why i need a cube
no [\h__\h] sherlock
ah would you look at that
would you look at that how did i missed
it
i got
why
because i bonked it against the wall
or is it that
sensitive
oh
or was it just
the timing it really
is is it okay too
do i need to hold you that gentle oh no
on you wait wait
okay see it can handle
some
some bouncing some bunking oh [\h__\h] why
am i going there why am i going down run
run run run i'm gonna go over here
okay it was just uh
a bad
uh coincidence um
uh and now we go here
no no no we bounce there
can we
bounce right into that or the
upper one
[Music]
bounce
ah almost
prevent
bones
no need to be closer to the edge
what
what oh
okay yeah
[Music]
sideways bounce
wall jumps let's go who's this
that's very dangerous
you can't put that there you need to
cover that up
[Music]
you okay no problem no problem
hey
oh wait am i is this one i'm dropping no
no no no okay let's bounce
let's
forward
oh [\h__\h]
never mind this is again thinking too
much because i can just go here
okay
wait what happened
what's happening
something down there
stop it stop it stop it
what stop it stop it stop it stop
prevent
what happened
what happened follow the line of the
button oh oh it was something outside ah
okay okay i thought so like i heard
something happening there
but i was like on it
why why would it be there
okay
are we
no it disappears when i leave
can we
holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
too much too much
no
no i want to
never mind maybe i can just
do this oh
so close okay okay
but i know how to do it now don't worry
guys
i'm thinking with jelly now
okay
oh in case you got covered in that
repulsion gel here's some advice the lab
boys gave me
do not get covered in the repulsion gel
that is so helpful i don't know i can't
even look at my body but i'll tell you
this it's a lively one and it does not
like the human skeleton
can does someone have a mirror i need to
i need to look at myself
i need to see
if i need to take a bath quickly
very smart um
oh man
game feels more slow paced right now
we'd like to get some more
fast-paced sections all these science
spheres are made of asbestos by the way
keeps out the rats let us know if you
feel a shortness of breath a persistent
dry cough or your heart stopping because
that's not part of the test that's
asbestos good news is the lab boys say
the symptoms of asbestos poisoning show
a median latency of 44.6 years
so if you're 30 or older you're laughing
worst case scenario you miss out on a
few rounds of canasta plus you forwarded
the cause of science by three centuries
i punch those numbers into my calculator
it makes a happy face
um
you mean those little portals that i'm
walking for are made from that
you
you you you you
where
where are we going this time oh
that is not it
there's something there but i can reach
out anyway
exit
i found the exit guys but
it doesn't look much like an exit up
there
oh wait there's something here
[Music]
don't know how to work with that
walk around
[Music]
i think
pink
oh no
i want wheatley back
wait talk to me
yo
pink pink
keep looking up
i don't see anything
oh
never mind
but
now
thank you but that's pre-recorded so it
doesn't really feel very genuine
what you fired someone for being in the
wheelchair because ramps are expensive
oh
that is
not very nice of you here at kfp we have
ramps everywhere not only for the
wheelchairs but also because they're
just fun to
run
downwards too
makes you speed up and you can do a
naruto run
this guy he doesn't understand fun
oh wait i didn't even test out the
button what does the button button do
oh make does it make this platform move
oh jelly
oh
forever
oh it's creating endless jelly let's go
[Music]
what are we gonna do with that jelly can
i
i was thinking oh yeah yeah yeah i was
thinking maybe we can portal it through
to go somewhere else
can we oh
make it go for a while
i think now i am pretty certain that i
am covered in jelly at this point
go here and then go here
can you cover
that somehow no what do you what uh
where is it going
oh my god
it's not going anywhere wow
[Music]
hmm
what's over here
nothing okay good to know
can i come with the jelly
oh
oh oh oh oh oh
what what the [\h__\h] was that
yeah yeah yeah okay
where's that platform before that i saw
what
hey didn't i see a pla another platform
there now i'm confused
oh
okay now we go this way again i gotta go
back up
overthinking again
and this one i meant this one
well i can't reach that one anyway
oh we're thinking well the errors say
that one but am i okay to ignore those
arrows
okay oh maybe it does want me to go all
the way over there oh
i must go out here first
wait i'm overthinking
i'm probably overthinking
where am i overthinking
maybe i really should take a break from
portal
move the poor lad it's falling yeah
sure
where to
will you
i want to go back up there
yes okay
oh my god oh my god
can i um
oh
oh you oh we just wanted it to land
there once
okay
and then and then and then and then
i wanna uh go for here
but with some momentum please
oh that makes my portals disappear
oh
[Music]
i i get okay okay
uh i want to go
into that the moment i'm flying i need
to make the portal
is that enough
no no no no
no no no no no no
ah
i need to be more
exploring
[Music]
yeah i want to go up here
i guess but yeah that means first i have
to go there no
do i want more of this stuff
i don't know
ah
let me go through here
and then
while i'm jumping oh but that deletes it
that's a that gets rid of it
i don't know
what
[\h__\h] i had so much momentum just now but
i wouldn't have known what to do with
any with it anyway
[Music]
okay
here we are again
look to the left
wait you mean when i'm up there again
okay i'm
okay
i didn't look over here but
um
[Music]
that's not it
and then it disappears
so
almost
i knew i knew it wouldn't work i was
thinking i don't know either portal for
the jelly but what does that help me oh
my god
yo
okay so one portal here
and um
[Laughter]
okay
i'm coming i'm coming wait no no no no
no no no we don't need everything to be
covered in blue
oh
and oh
i got a vertically unchallenged
achievement i'm not so sure about that
slight chance the calcium could feel
very challenged
anyway don't stress yourself thinking
about it i'm serious visualizing the
scenario while under stress actually
triggers the reaction i need to eat some
chocolate right now i still have some of
the that bar left over from yesterday
with the waivers mmm
yummy yummy waivers
you're thinking of goo
i i see there's really a lot of new
elements i really have to um
carry cobra jump probably
get that sugar rash let's go
this is a good place to stop is it am i
really 50 through now
if i am then yeah i would agree to stop
and then play tomorrow again
but you guys got to tell me because i
don't know
i am a bit over 15. now if you're part
of control group kepler 7 we implanted a
tiny microchip
most likely you've forgotten it's even
there but if it starts vibrating and
beeping during this wait i'm hoping for
under five hours
oh
next test let us know because that means
it's about to hit 500 degrees so we're
gonna need to go ahead and get that out
of you pretty fast
um
i miss gliders
why not
the puzzles get harder and harder
[Music]
really
but eventually you know the more harder
they get they will also you know i will
also get better at them so
um
it will balance it out itself out
probably right
right hopefully
okay
yay
portal too sorry the end got a little
bit wet because brain also blur
my brain was basically that blue jelly
bouncing information from one side to
another in my brain but not going
anywhere
um
but hopefully tomorrow we can go back
into it with some more energy again
yeah
told you two is harder yeah i've heard
people told me i uh
that's okay that's okay i just i just
hope that for you guys it
doesn't get too
boring at the end there
i like it i do oh i'm it
i really liked your pretty vr stream
idea again i love how you use everything
yeah
and make it your finger i wanna if i
when i finally um have the ability to
use my um suit that doesn't exist yet
then i wanna play that game too
it looks like fun
you're not wearing a bra
because i saw your boobies jiggle
but it's okay i'm also a no-bra person i
prefer
i prefer you know going without a bra to
give those boobies some freedom
sorry i'mma for confronting you with
such a weird topic um my brain is jelly
thanks to portal
oh my oh my bad brush
yeah
i'm on team ben brass oh also amen did
you know the gladys is guna
that's something we figured out today
something new new knowledge don't tell
her we know though she might try to
eliminate us
if she knows that we know
no no no
yes yes what was the moment where we
realized before before the shark
experiments no not shark experiments
what was it
what did you say what did you say that
made me think this is
gooda
there was this one moment
gaogudados
she did talk about sharks later yeah
yeah yeah but there was something else
going spiral launched into space and
then the name glados i mean
come on
oh yeah oh yeah the small experiments
yeah launching people into space she's
done that been there done that
and then the shark research
oh
thanks for streaming played well thank
you for the pinky
yeah i'm going to read super chats now
uh from today's stream because i uh
caught up yesterday with everything
and now i will actually
uh do i still have water yeah i still
have some water you know what i'm not
gonna take a break i'm just gonna
pour some more water i have one glass of
water let's see if we can get through
the super chats with one glass of water
i
actually i think
i think streaming actually makes me
hydrate more because i talk so much and
i need to drink more water
if i don't stream i really don't drink
enough um
water that's
something i should fix
a fruit candy too yeah fruit candy
always helps for the moment so
hmm yeah that's actually good streaming
really
makes me drink a lot of water a lot of
water very healthy
thanks for the stream tango thank you
thank you everybody who came you're you
can leave if you want to but why would
you want to because now
i'm gonna read some um
cozy stupid chats with you guys let's go
to my office
oh and uh oh [\h__\h] oh my god all the
hands
uh did you see the community post
about you know kfp lord that we might
want to explain in form of a video
because you may remember i wanted to
make a video series
where
um
kind of like with a voice over from me
uh i explained the kfp lore while also
showing some clips
with help from none other than kyle
carrot because if anyone can do that job
where you have to dig up really old
information and compile it compile
information from all kinds of streams
uh then there's cow carrot if anyone
didn't call carrot
yeah but i wasn't sure of what to start
because i kind of want to i don't want
to like
mix it all too randomly i want to start
with something
like
doesn't need to be completely
chronological but like somewhat
chronological you know what i mean
so
uh i don't want to start right away with
casper because casper is not the first
kfp lord that was created yeah something
early casper will definitely be made in
one of those
um videos but not the first one
yeah now i know one of the first things
would be bottom left and i don't mind
making a video about it but i do mind it
being the first one because yeah
i don't know i feel i don't feel like
it's a good idea to make that the first
one
no i think it's it's okay to
to explain it we can still say
put a disclaimer that we don't really
use this anymore
just like the australia thing i'm gonna
make a video about that too even though
it's not really a thing anymore
kfb itself
the usual room
how early
was the usual room a thing
was that always a thing
i don't remember anymore
also i need to put on some music
november
it was not there from the very beginning
was it
yeah i was also thinking about kiana fan
club explaining how can a fan club just
turned into kfp
i'm not sure if there's enough video
content for that to
uh
create an actual explanation but i mean
there is voiceovers
the user room was a few months in
was it
i don't i don't
it's hard to
think of oh all that by myself so
especially because kfb lore is all all
very logical to me i understand what it
means but
um
you guys already got gave me some good
ideas on the community board if you can
still think of anything let me know
um
was it around establishment of jfp hmm
it was a thing when i joined in november
yeah it's definitely very old it has
been around for a long time
she's going to struggle explaining
kotonii
why
should i make a video about codoni too
is that necessary
it's just uh that's so easily explained
it's just a mascot
oh yeah btm what which one do we want
this one
i've given four different explanations
for kotori nah that's not true
[Music]
yeah that's too
too late though i want to start with
something early but i am aware of all
these things woken yolk of course we're
gonna do one about that too
oh you know what what one good idea
would be i don't know if anyone
suggested this one but we could um
make a video that also explains the
origin of the m videos because the
origin was sakuna
where i made a frog um
impression of a frog that's where the m
videos came from
[Music]
but that would be a really short video
like there's not much else to
explain
oh and belle and ryza was that one too
a reason to which one was first sakuna
or
raiza
i have to go to bed thanks for watching
[Music]
i watched the videos when i left ah i
was i was thinking of a small video
ideas right
oh mama mama
are you okay with the full idea during
your ride stream
how do you remember
fire emblem
how would i put fire blood in any of
these lore videos
what lore was created during fire emblem
[Music]
employee numbers that's so
what that has nothing to do with that
employee numbers feel more recent
being european
ah oh pantomime i love a pet oh you're
right we can make a video about that
[Laughter]
[Music]
who is gloria wait who is gloria uh
ah was that like a typo thing in a super
chat
and i was like who's gloria
is that something like that
i think that was a super chat from lft
oh and cove oh yeah
oh yeah yeah yeah it was a typo
from what what was the actual word
[Music]
gloria
what how do
what's the original word
glory
all right that's something that i would
like to
uh
repeat again like i would like to i
would like call carrot to make a video
about that and remind me how that
started
but maybe that's too minor
[Music]
sounds like from a katamari game
makes you want to roll up academy wow so
many of you guys are thinking of
kakamari
fire hair i think that's also something
for later i just want to focus on which
couple videos i want to do in the
beginning now so one is definitely going
to be australia
um
and then hashtag hill i think that was
that was that was implemented already in
fire emblem
and then
i don't know if the whole re-debut thing
should be one of the early videos maybe
yeah
no
gravy
[Music]
ah alternative lives
oh you guys you guys use those ideas and
and put them as a reply in the community
board because there i can go back and
look at them
here in the comments i'm probably just
going to read them and forget about them
but thank you
ah my cats are instagram famous and
that's why they don't show up on camera
exactly
on the other hand bonkers is not
instagram famous and that's why the
bonkers was able to show up on camera
okay well thank you guys for your help
already
we're gonna make some cool videos that
also serve as fillers maybe when i'm on
the vacation as well
very useful
multi-use
[Music]
okay i'm going to close portal
um
openly super chat
we had a jfp thing
that's literally lore that was created
by fans though right
you really make a video about that i
don't know
[Music]
do you like the thumbnail for today i
already have a thumbnail for tomorrow by
the way they're matching
it's not cute isn't that cute isn't that
cute isn't that cute i was thinking to
continue the theme of the portal one
um thumbnail with the hands so i looked
up some more stuff
and
i found this one it was cute you want to
see that one for tomorrow
[Music]
here it is
i'm i'm i don't know what kind of
expression that is
gloves are rough no yeah but i look kind
of like
like unsure and not confident which is
fitting because um yeah i'm worried
about part two of this game
the part one there were many riddles
that i absolutely aged today
thankfully i didn't completely make an
idiot of myself a fool of myself
you like them
[Music]
will be quite a headache yeah
yeah i thought so i thought so that's
why i thought when i was creating this
that um
and
a scared look
or
uncertain look might be the way to go
yeah
okay
don't worry i have a png of that too but
really just that part of you know with
the cut off head and cut off body that's
all i have
i will upload it for the people who want
it anyway
portal tuesday i wanted to use them in
my title that was so so
smart i almost put that in my title it's
portal tuesday but then i was like
people gonna laugh at me for that stupid
joke
[Music]
yeah the smile from this
um
thumbnail
i could do a smile like that i can't
no matter how hard i try
but this actually
helps me imagine
how i would look like if i had visible
teeth like that like ame
and you know what i i always was worried
that maybe that would look weird so i
never requested a fix or something like
that
i don't even know if it would be
possible probably not um it's too late
now but
but
it does work it doesn't look weird it
actually looks pretty cute
[Laughter]
[Music]
you guys you guys want
me to be able to have
you know a mouth like that
like use my teeth more
say cheese
would you guys like that or should i
keep my mouth the ladies i don't even
know if it's an option but
um
yeah
it would probably change
the way my mouth moves completely
forever and ever
and you're so used to this mouth now
it would be very different
yeah my feet might be
pretty cute to be able because i always
look at amit with her mouth movements
and i'm always like holy [\h__\h] it's so
cute when she smiles
it kills me it's so charming
[Music]
it's partially a rigging thing too but
also a thing of the base art i would say
i'll ask if it's a possibility first of
all we don't have to have it that
extreme but you know a little bit of
teeth
would be nice
i'll ask
but maybe that's something i can't get
until 3.0
which is so far in the future and i can
only get it for my default outfit for
now so
that's so far in the future and i won't
even use it much hmm
[Music]
i'll check though oh i might check yeah
okay let's read super chat though thank
you everybody for supporting me again
today i hope you had fun in portal let's
go through the super chat
harbor line down cushion
a root canal oh my god
that sounds so painful
hope you're doing okay myth and duncan
mr caspian cushion
that's cool thank you for the rest of
the chat
oh [\h__\h] that case was supposed to go to
harvard line
a case for you
yeah for that are you is is the harbor
line in the chat
are they done with the road canal it's
been it's been like quite some time
could be done by now oh you're here
are you like
under
some kind of
doctor drugs
when you do something like that don't
you get like drugged up by them
or is that when only when we're getting
rid of wisdom to you
i'm in so much pain oh
[\h__\h]
did you not get like something
or is it not enough
blah
blah wait when when
i hope i don't i never have to i hope i
never have to do something like that
what
what times do you do a root canal
[\h__\h] and what times when i
want to know that i never have to do it
oh
i was thinking of it hurts
yeah i still need my wisdom teeth
removed like a previous dentist told me
that like i should start thinking about
it before i went to japan but now i have
a new um dentist
and he never mentioned it so i i also
just ignore it for now
yeah we were focused on something else i
guess
but
it will hopefully be gone soon the plane
just
try to distract yourself
and take those painkillers let's go
wait some teeth don't always have to be
removed
um well my dentist said i would have to
remove it eventually but it's still
definitely at the point where i don't
need to worry too much about it
[Music]
tangent
i have a tangent for you
i um i did some research and um
uh about aquarium
and uh there's like
there's like one thing that i decided to
put in besides fish
what are they called in english ah
a blue crayfish
[Music]
in in german we call it uh florida
grapes because i think they come from
florida
yeah
yeah they are so blue look them up
flower florida crips florida blue clay
blue crayfish
they work
okayish in
i was told that they work okayish in in
aquariums it's just like sometimes it
depends on their character
uh if you're lucky then they don't
attack the other fish too much
and the other plants and all that if
you're unlucky then it might constantly
be on the hunt
um but i kind of wanted something else
in my aquarium besides fish and the idea
like i asked
is it possible to put
like some kind of
um
creeps
cancer not cancer
honey honey
honey crap crap thank you some kind of
crab uh in there uh and i got i was
recommended a blue crayfish
[Music]
that's not a color of crayford's change
no as far as i know i looked up some
youtube videos too um
these blue crayfish are blue because
they were kind of like um breeded within
aquariums to
turn blue so now they're blue
um
i think i think the ones that you find
in aquariums are always blue
they stay blue yeah doesn't matter what
you feed them they stay blue
[Music]
do they glow in the dark i don't think
so but but they have a very vibrant
color and i thought that would look so
cool and and really be like a highlight
of my aquarium
oh if if amit if alma visits me
i'm sure she will love my aquarium i
want to have an impressive aquarium so
that emma will be like
your aquarium is so cool i love that i
love that uh crayfish that you got there
tell me about it cuba
yeah they're very eye-catching
yeah you can keep those i i i heard that
um one thing that you just absolutely
should not do is um like if you want to
get rid of them never set them out in
the free because they can carry some
really dangerous uh
crab illness and kill literally every
other
crab in the country
by spreading some kind of crab pest
i know about that now i wasn't planning
on setting them free
as long as you don't set them free
everything's cool
it's just there's a there's a chance
that they carry some disease and spread
it and kill all the other crabs
yeah
yeah it's not gonna happen
can they mix with your facial right yeah
i mean
um
i'll get some
help with choosing
the rat fish to go with
the
crab
and uh the other way around
[Music]
nine months
free to live what
[Music]
months ah you're nine months in now
three more two okay
let's go
so close why are you looking sad you
should be excited
[Music]
and even if they attack um or try to
catch the fish the fish are usually fast
enough to
um escape not get caught normally
normally
if they're
if they manage to actually catch a lot
of fish and kill a lot of fish i'm gonna
have to
find a solution switch out the crab i
suppose or
um
get stronger fish
no
now the cats are fine because i'm gonna
get an aquarium that's closed at the top
so no worries about that
crap again
it should be fine
it should be fine it's a it's a crab
that many people like to keep
in their aquarium apparently
so
yeah i asked about a frog but
um
frog is very difficult and it would have
to be
less water i can't put a frog in there
unfortunately but i'm gonna get a crap
so
oh wait i forgot or maybe a turtle but
the turtle probably doesn't work with
the crab probably
i might i might check because there are
some turtles that are mostly like
swimmer turtles right my mom told me
um
they do need some land
but not too much
[Music]
not sure
wait a crab another cream fish it's a
crab it's just called a crayfish
it's a crab dough
if you look it up blue crayfish then you
see a crab
it's not a fish yeah i know it's
confusing um
sounds like a crazy ecosystem nah
it will be just one crab and then many
fish
i want to get some some fancy fish
um
it's a
oh a lobster yeah that's what i was
thinking of when i was looking at it and
i was like this doesn't really look like
what i was thinking of
no
crips
the german word crips is crab
but it's a lobster it looks like a
lobster i was i was thinking more of i
want a small little crab in my aquarium
you know and then i was recommended this
thing and i was like
that doesn't look like the crab i
envisioned
uh
oh well i mean it looks cool though so
i guess i'll go with the lobster
i guess i'll go with the lobster then
[Music]
yeah
that's what it was ah
i forgot the word for it
i was so confused by the german name
though
like it that's a that's a clips
but that looks like a
hummer
how is that a wait is the clips and the
humor the same thing
the crab is there is a is a lobster
under category of a crab or the other
way around
[Music]
oh yeah good out good i would love to
see my
uh
crayfish someday too probably
i want to show her my aquarium too
the shark i wonder what the shark is
ever going to say about my aquarium i
think i'll i'll get it
um done pretty soon
sooner rather than later
crush the crust quest questions crush
craft crush
and from the same family not the same
species
then i'm really confused by the name
but both the english and the german name
are confusing
it's
blue florida crab in german in english
it's crayfish
which implies it's a fish
crustacean
[Music]
why are these names so confusing
crayfish wait which one was it
crayfish
oh well whatever
i will just expose the fact that i know
nothing about fish when i talk about
this stuff
but i'm gonna uh
i'm gonna make a great aquarium
yes i'm gonna put it in my living room
where i barely spend any time but my
cats will love it my cats have been
spending a lot of time in the living
room these days because um i built
something nice for them there and they
will have even more fun once the
aquarium is there yay
and and i decided to get a big dinner
table after all so whenever
i have dinner with some friends at my
place maybe then we can look at the
aquarium because in the same room i kind
of want one somewhere where i can look
at it more often
but i feel like
if i had one anywhere it would have to
be in the living room and i don't i
don't think it makes sense to have it in
the office it should be like somewhere
in the biggest room of my apartment yeah
somewhere
it would be nice and relaxing to have it
in the
in the bedroom too but then it also
makes noises and it just i don't know
takes up a lot of space too and i still
have i still have this one
empty wall in my living room where i
felt like it would fit perfectly there
while in my other room so i i don't
quite have that wall that says put an
aquarium right here that's why i'm going
with the living room yeah
yeah i think it's perfect there
[Music]
yeah i think i think the noise will be
mostly relaxing i don't think it will be
that um disturbing
like a hamster wheel would be for
example
or a bunny i i hear that bunnies and
rabbits
are very noisy pets to keep for example
but as long as it's just a water sound
like
that's okay oh yeah the bubble wing yeah
hmm
this is gonna be fun i'm um
i that's that's more like white noise
almost if it's coming from the next door
room
i don't think i'll be bothered by that
especially like if it's sound that i
know where it's coming from
and that that's supposed to how it's
that's how it's supposed to be sounding
then i'm fine with it if it's something
that is unfamiliar to me then i'm like
what the [\h__\h] is this sound turn it off
i'm so excited ah
[Music]
i don't know much about aquarium and
it's not like i'm the biggest fan of
fish at all
um i like i prefer fluffy pets
but
but i think i think um it will be nice
decoration and it will be relaxing it'll
be pretty to look at and and i can show
it off to guests
yeah
i'm looking forward to having that
maybe i'll learn to love fish and and
have a really deep relationship in
connection with my fish and my crab my
my lobster
[Music]
yeah i was thinking i'mma
i could maybe talk with emma about it
because she's into that kind of stuff
more she's more on the terrarium side of
things but
i'm sure she'll like my car
emergency food supply no no hell no hell
no
[Music]
oh oh the good thing is that if a fish
dies naturally
the crab can eat it the crab will eat it
the lobster will eat the dead fish
that's like a natural way of getting rid
of the dead fish
yeah
yeah it's big rain i don't have to like
take it out of there and flush it down
the toilet
i can just leave it in there it's
efficient yeah
it's
don't don't look at me like that guys
that's what happens out there in the
ocean the whole time they don't even
wait for the fish to die naturally they
just eat them while they're alive they
kill them animals eat animals that's
nature guys do you understand you guys
are too spoiled for me honestly you
chickens are too spoiled
if you guys were not working for a
campaign you were out there in the
nature foxes and wolves would hunt and
eat you guys you should be thankful for
giving this opportunity to work at kfp
in a protected environment where you're
never able to get outside but also
there's never a a fox or a wolf walking
in right into carefree trying to attack
you no if anything attacks you it's the
hot oil of the fryer but that's all
planned and you know that's happening at
least you can at least you know when you
die
huh unlike having the uncertainty of oh
my god i'm just chilling out here in a
huge field suddenly
suddenly i'm getting attacked by by i
don't know an elk who knows if elk eats
uh chickens they might you don't know
because you're just a naive little
chicken out there in the wild
see i'm protecting you i'm protecting
you from all of that
you're welcome kfb
i love you too
hmm okay let's write some attempts
[Music]
elaborate
an m
video that's a good idea
for my next m video
yeah i hope i don't forget that
msego mc go
remind me if i ask you guys
i should do mc girl next but wait there
was another one that i wanted to do
sometimes
uh
one that i learned recently
uh um
i'm still no
was it i'm seeing you i told you guys i
learned a new um
i knew
a penguin it was penguin yeah i can do m
penguin or m sequel
or yes i'm turkey
ah
well there's so many i can do right now
and i was worried about running out of
uh the ones i can do
see go let me write it down see go
penguin
[Music]
and turkey turkey might be my best bet i
think my turkey is the best because i
even do it when i'm just not trying to
be a turkey
[Music]
no not running out of animals but
running out of animal
noises that i can recreate
yeah
hmm anyway thank you liberty
for reminding me looking for the top
down
[Music]
what
can you confirm with jen live there's
going to be an official kiana cut out at
dopamine you want to appear in a group
photo but i don't want there to be two
life-sized kiaras out there
this this feels like a portal riddle to
me
what why would there be
what
oh
you mean because
oh oh you're making a cut out you guys
are making one
i mean we're making a cutout are you
coming to goku me
[Music]
are you coming to dookumi too
another one
[Music]
you guys are making up
ah you're not coming but you know that
people are making a cutout
you're planning to make one
hmm
yeah i'll ask if uh if it's being
planned to have some standees let me do
that right now so that don't forget
[Music]
oh my god caps look
is there going to be um
[Music]
standing he's
all
sides cut out of
us
at the community
one unknown because you can't be
thinking
of making one themselves if not if not
right that's the thing if we make one
you guys are not gonna make one
[Music]
who is who is thinking of making one
even
who is that not everyone knows about it
apparently
yeah we only need one i mean
not necessarily we can have more than
one create a kiana army assert dominance
guys think smart think
but okay i asked the question
[Music]
all right all right and to satisfy thank
you soon
thank you
autumn camp
what's autumn camp where are you going
hope you're coming back soon
you mean extinction
this game still makes me real nauseous
i'm actually fine today i can tell you
that last time yeah i think there were
other factors that
added to
me feeling
um
dizzy and sick afterwards but today i'm
i'm totally fine you know
[Music]
hmm
uh also also also speaking of final i'm
not going to finish out of a rise this
month after all because the month is
literally ending and i don't i don't
have time
i'm like going to physical therapy every
day and streaming for five hours and uh
in between i'm doing other things too
so
don't say el mao i knew it shut up i
tried okay i actually am trying to
stall even like even while i'm playing
now because um i don't want it to end
okay don't stress me out let me enjoy
this experience a little bit longer okay
but i at least got back into it within
this month okay you're gonna give me
credit for that
i got back into it and i could have
finished it if i wanted to but i wanted
to do more side quests
which is just me appreciating the game
more what's wrong with that hmm
[Music]
i think i might finish it next week
though
um
[Music]
what do you call that again
the one where you like kill a million
mobs
uh
i don't know i wouldn't have been
open to playing it if it was a normal
fire emblem
um
yeah
let me tell you this if they put out a
new fire emblem game like a proper one
this year next year
[Music]
i'm pretty sure i'll make a stream out
of it
even
even if it is a very long game that
people don't like to watch mostly
i i
really um
found an interest and a liking and fire
emblem thanks to that playthrough that
we had i would like to
dive into it some more
it was really fun
i i have very fond memories of it
even though it was a tough time and
maybe not the best choice of game to
play in the beginning of my activities
but i really had a great time with it
and
yeah we spent so much time
together or playing that game
so many
nice characters
[Music]
fire emblem
need to go back and watch the vlog
aren't you all ready aren't your hands
already full with the current bonds
[Music]
foreign fireblam is one what really sold
me on becoming kfb yeah i know i know a
lot of you guys who actually you know
watched those streams
we we bonded it was a bonding experience
of you guys no
that's why it's so special to me yeah
no regrets
no i want to play a new one not an old
one
i mean i will play an old one in my free
time but on stream i would want to play
a new one if anything
[Music]
all right and jose hero darkest in for
the pinky i got this game as a gift from
my sister back when i graduated high
school oh
it's been one of my absolute favorite
games ever since
but your your sister has a great taste
in giving games i wonder if she did that
like really randomly or
like knowingly
hope you have fun and believe in your
big brain attention thank you
that reminds me uh
my my sister
once gifted me randomly
did i ever tell you
she randomly gifted me
um a volume of a manga series but not
the first one but like it was like the
third or the fourth one
so
uh
um it was sugar sugar roon
cute shoujo manga about like two witches
um competing in like a contest or
something like that
it was really cute um i read that one
and then uh there was an anime too so
i think i tried to get some more volumes
but i also wants the whole anime and i
really i really liked it and it was one
of my favorite animes back then
she was shiva ruins
[Music]
so that was a weird gift though i don't
know why she gave me a random volume why
not the first one
that's confusing
she probably just picked one cute licky
look cute looking thing from the shelf
and was like i'm gonna give this to my
sister
[Music]
that's probably when i started getting
more and more into
manga probably when i was uh going to
the library and
[Music]
it's a classic yeah
your library had that yeah they had like
a really really tiny corner
of some manga like naruto probably was
there
uh
was probably there but i didn't look at
those
i looked at the more cute looking ones
like um one of them
was um
that was my first manga because i found
it there ah my goodness goddess and then
then uh slowly but surely they started
selling some manga in the bookstores too
and i found vampire night and i would i
got so i think it's a vampire night i
didn't know at what pace they were
releasing them but i
so i kept on coming back to the
bookstore again and again and checked
that they finally had a new one coming
out i
had to get the um german translated ones
which probably made it take even more
time
to be released um
yeah and i kept on waiting and waiting
for them to have the right volume yeah
vampirina and i started watching the
anime and
vampire night nowadays i would not enjoy
it
too
cringy shoujo for me
but back then
oh i was falling over it oh
i wanted to be the protagonist um
and the other one was kaiju amidosama
that i also was reading at the time
and got really into and then also
watched the anime back then i actually
read manga but nowadays i don't read
them anymore because it's like i don't
know a bother a bother to get
[Music]
zero
oh i don't remember anymore which one i
liked more the one was white-haired red
and the other one was like black-haired
i think
i don't know i don't remember which one
i liked but
maybe i liked i just like both and i
thought it was so cool the whole vampire
concept and they're going to a vampire
school
and
this one girl for the protagonist i
don't know what the thing was with her
but she was kind of special i don't know
why but she was special
maybe because she was not a vampire and
everyone else was a vampire i'm not sure
no wasn't everyone with the white
uniform a vampire and everyone with the
black uniform was a human
was that it
[Music]
does someone know
i'm the protagonist yuki i think was her
name she had a black uniform and she was
uh she was normal therefore
[Music]
but yeah i think she got turned into a
vampire
yeah
by the heart by the hot uh male vampire
oh oh yeah so stuff like that nowadays
[\h__\h] no hell no i'm not getting into
that
it's too too
girly too cringy but now
now i don't like it back then i was like
this is so
[Music]
nice it's so romantic
oh my god
i wanna be here i want to be bitten by a
hot vampire
oh my god
[Laughter]
a
[Music]
you too hi tanja in korea we just
started to vote
oh that's what you mean
that's what's going on who you want to
invite at seoul popcorn so since you
have a new shining user room i think
it's time to put all 50 million
50 million koreans to vote for you i of
course voted for you
but where is that poll
where is that
is it on their website
[Music]
that's what they meant with
like whole life is coming to are we
winning the pool
[Music]
where is it
where is the pool
participation inquiry no
[Music]
show us a link or what do i need to
google
it's a survey ah
it's not a public poll it's a survey
[Music]
i added you a bit oh
what if i fill it up
what if i
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh think it is
oh
[Music]
which do you want to meet at seoul
popcorn voice actor edition song edition
virtual character edition overall
edition so i suppose um
virtual character edition is the
uh the virtual youtuber
with origami
[Music]
but that's already not specific people
know
interesting
thank you for showing me
very curious
korean clipper ah that's what the name
sounds familiar and they follow me too
on twitter
um that's why it sounds familiar all
right i was like i've heard this name
before
can we vote too who knows you can try
thank you little punk thank you thank
you that would be so cool
let's hope for the best
[Music]
korean bro zero school the gamer created
my twin brother's birthday
if you could say something nice and
maybe even seeing it would surely make
this day a little more special for me
him oh i meant him what are we talking
about but do you really have a turn by
the bill are you really a twin
that's so sweet that's a round round
about round round round round about way
of asking me to sing happy birthday to
you cute
don't be so shy
you need to be so shy you have oh cool
julio that's that's cool
all right then happy birthday to your
twin brother what's his name
just kidding
[Music]
have an instrumental
from audio stuff
there it is
let's make use of it
happy birthday
uh it doesn't start
yet happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you
happy birthday ultimo mk zero happy
birthday to
[Applause]
i didn't prepare the lyrics
but yeah you know it
i wish you
a happy birthday
happy birthday to you
happy birthday optimal m k zero happy
birthday to you
so you have a twin brother
i hope he's not telling you stealing
your thunder
happy birthday to him too i guess but
you're
[Music]
happy birthday to you to you happy
birthday
and while we're at it
let me give you a number
not my phone number
[Music]
oh that was it
yay
[Laughter]
[Music]
i came up with some lyrics at the spot
i forgot about that part
i hope no one else has 203 already i'm
trying to give unique numbers
i hope it's working
tell me if there's ever something
overlapping um
and jake is monkey
oh by the way i'm not gonna sing this
song for everybody okay
i usually
if i turn this song on for every [\h__\h]
birthday i'm gonna be singing all day i
usually do it for i like to sing happy
birthday for red super jets okay
oh too loud
[Music]
angel thank you for the red super chat i
must say this is really entertaining to
watch another 10 10 show thank you
oh bing you actually i was already very
worried about if it really was that
entertaining when i played portal 1 at
least around the end
my portal streams tend to get
kind of um
stretched out at the end is what i feel
i hope it wasn't too bad
this is really these thinking games very
exhausting for the thinking muscle aka
brain um
it was fun it was funny really
i found the whole way from really
[Music]
it was fun thank you
thank you
[Music]
thank you thank you
you guys are too sweet
angel thank you you're like an angel man
[Music]
martenshi
thank you
thank you very much
hope you'll enjoy tomorrow too we're
continuing tomorrow
reaction to the story
we're gonna learn more starring tomorrow
i'm sure of it but today the banter with
glados was fun yeah yeah and wheatley
really that little [\h__\h]
say against monkey danger
dot dot dot how dare you how dare you
dot dot dot me
thank you
at least that face makes it better dead
are we not going to learn that anyway
from the game no
logan boyfriend
malek the navy
bh
kelly you're beautiful being and i love
you oh
quick question should i join your
membership what do you think
yes
yes yes yes yes yes yes
are you still here
[Music]
if you haven't joined yet then join now
obvious yes
yes yes yes
do it do it do it don't let your dreams
be dreams
do it
[Music]
you were like waiting for it you were
ready
welcome egg
i'm i'm i'm
i'm really sorry but i actually might
not be able to
have a memory stream this week
um
but instead what i think we'll do is
we'll have a
member stream two weeks in a row so next
week one and the week after that too i i
feel like i can't fit it in this week at
least not in a good time if i were to
fit it in it would be in a shitty time
for most of you guys and the next one
will be a movie much longer um
that the one after that either gaming or
singing
but i think for movie watching lungs i
should make it so that many people can
watch it live yeah
yeah yeah
thank you guys for being so sweet
i wanted to do one this week because i
tried to have one once every two weeks
at least but
when are we watching uh
what what were we watching again
[Music]
yeah he checkers the galaxy right
i think
[Music]
doesn't that have two movies or was it
only one
hitchhiker's guide to the galaxy
[Music]
a series
um
[Music]
i love this so much this
track i love it i need some more i need
more tracks that go like pop up
i need more like that
how do i find more like that is that
like a genre
look at what they like i elevated it's
elevator music but i want more of a
pop-up
so good
oh
the genre is katamati
ah
you need to go for audio stock though
i've been really good at finding good
songs in audio stuff but
looking for something like this might be
difficult
i arrived really late but you arrived
and that's what matters welcome
[Music]
would make for good stream
i know katamari but
what platform is that
switch right it was on the switch
was that uh
is there a co-op in this game like couch
color or is it only solo looks so cute
[Music]
switch our pc
multiple
playstation 2.
here's couch co-op
oh
[Music]
why is everything couch cool
hot dog has multiplier
we need we need we need oh you know what
i was thinking
um
when when i have uh guests coming over
all the hello live english members
you know i told you guys i want to play
some couch co-op only games but i have
one more idea
we could make
the
monthly stack box
of that month
we could make it not a solo review but a
together review
let the other
girls were there at that time
snack with me
yes yes wow yes wow
ah chickens are so easy to impress
they always go like whoa
whoa
[Music]
ah sorry my mom
oh i guess yeah i could also make a
special episode where i let them taste
all kinds of austrian slash german
chocolate that's true too
because we probably really
even if they're here they probably won't
really get to taste
many of them because like we'll eat
proper food and
i don't think we'll be spending much
time in supermarkets
[Music]
yeah
good ideas good ideas
[Music]
oh a holo talk
while they are here
that's that sounds uh funny and all but
i think i'll probably be doing a better
job if i don't have
them with me here i can focus better if
i'm alone in my office
dealing with all the documents and
windows that i have open and and that's
something we can do anyway when they're
not here i prefer doing things that i
can only do when they're here
like eating stuff together or playing
couch co-op games but i am planning a
reverse whole talk or
uh uh interviewing whole live english
members
eventually
[Music]
that is
uh okay
well although reversal talk is more like
i want to interview myself
rather than having someone else
interview me oh that could be ame amer
could interview me but no i'm i'm i was
thinking more like i'm one version of
kiwawa is interviewing a different
version of kiwama
um will this be all on your channel i
don't know
um there'll definitely be at least one
stream on my channel but i don't know if
i'll do like everything on my channel
probably not probably want to do it on
someone else's channel too
[Music]
okay um
super chat super chats
[Music]
yeah my lawyer
you're late
kiana thank you and gary carson
moonlight and kitchen thank you guys
thank you
very cool 86 tankition
everyone notice how the logo for
aperture laboratories makes it look like
capture all
because of the circle
no never noticed that no
motion
companion
[Music]
why is there one that's
just angry at me and the other one is
nice to me i think one is fake the one
that's angry at me is fake
ah
ah that means that ah i didn't know the
meaning of aperture i'm not gonna know
yeah yeah i see i think
i have noticed only duncan
i only got around to starting the
multiplayer with my friend it's been
really fun so far so i hope you'll have
fun with cobo 2 and keep destroying the
cameras
ah
thank you
yeah i'll try my best to continue but i
don't i think i definitely missed some
cameras especially in portal 2.
um
uh
i hope i hope but i hope the collab is
going to be fun for coba ah do we need
two point of views what do you think yes
right i think i asked before two point
of views right
for portal 2 co-op
i would say
[Music]
okay
jackson effie thank you for the pinky
remember karen if it helped you solve
the problem then it was necessary keep
thinking of portals
uh you know you mean that part where um
people said my my solution was
not the one that they would have done
that does not mean that your solution is
the right one and one is the minus the
wrong one right yeah there's many ways
to
get to the goal and i think it's
actually interesting
to see that for you guys who already
played it you see that there are
different ways to solve it as well
if it works it works yeah
yeah yeah i agree thanks jackson
[Music]
thanks for the pink
was this when i was gone for like a
moment yeah
ellie r rt dankesh and jackson evie
duncan and yes i agree
even when you make it very clear
they still
act like it wasn't clear
but oh maybe they were just you know
waiting they were they were gonna leave
anyway eventually but they were just
waiting for a good moment to leave
because they had to do some things and
and they were like oh she goes afk for
two minutes this is the moment i need to
leave right now
i can see that that they just were busy
with other things too
yeah but i guess yeah i wouldn't really
use it much but a different afk stream
that's actually like me being afk
would be useful instead of the super
chat rating screen
um
yeah yeah would be would be um useful
sometimes
when i just have afk
i don't know
i guess i could do that
use a city gift no that one deserves
like something that gets used more often
now it's behind me on the tv
[Music]
what is a dollars is that australian
dollars
[Music]
eleven wasn't it aus no a-u-d is
australian dolls what's 8. what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
i thought that i see in my youtube
studio it's written as aud is this just
a different in the chat window i never
noticed that difference what the hell
[Music]
eight ten dollars
wow
it sounds so flat she can be used as
money oh
i'm sorry
don't tell her
go man
i didn't say anything
[Music]
oh
is justice too it's okay
in her next monthly stream a good good
thing that she did one today she might
forget until
next time
[Music]
happy birthday
no that was for me
you're saying happy birthday to me
thank you for the red super chat happy
birthday boss glad this didn't get you
anything so here's some love from her
feet oh thank you guys
i can always count on you guys for the
happy birthday surprises and stuff like
that
you guys are always gifting me with your
presents every day though
presents your presence is the present
[Music]
it is
true though it is true very true
thank you jesus wow that was very cheesy
enough
with mary poppins
[Music]
i recently caught up on tons of whole
life clips you guys are all super
entertaining oh i don't really watch the
stream so i'm only here briefly to send
this compensation no stay
did you guys not put him in in chains
keep up the good work is he still here
did you guys put him in chains or did he
really leave oh my god
attention span of a
fly
stay
stink he broke free
ah man
come back
come back yo cliff watchers come back
come back to me
[Music]
come back
come back yo
come here
i'm waiting for you
hey
you
hey you
come here
hey
oh [\h__\h] you guys look it look very very
threatening
[Music]
that doesn't look like we're a warm and
welcoming
company
can you guys be a little bit more warm
and welcoming
you look very threatening right now
no no no i yeah the fire i guess helps
it's not not quite
the hearts yeah it's the hearts isn't
that difficult to put out a chicken with
a heart
isn't that the obvious choice of making
us look
warm and welcoming
not the fire the one with the heart
ah what happened did i not train you
well enough guys what's happening are
you guys malfunctioning
what's going on do i need to kick you in
that
lava pool because you're malfunctioning
if you're malfunctioning i might have to
do that
you know like those turrets
you don't want that do you
[Music]
i believe in you come on you can do it
yes more hearts
more hearts
[Music]
more
more you can do it
just for one moment come on
make us look warm and welcoming there we
go there we go there you go so proud i'm
so proud of you yay
[Applause]
we did it kfb now the clip watchers will
join us hopefully
[Laughter]
thank you wow you you union
yeah
not that kind of union though
[Laughter]
ah legacy heart duncan kiara dot duncan
drakonic 174
black mage 666 pakistan navidad
dead
[Music]
what do you mean the big potato was mine
i'm like the names on the bring your
daughter to work day brothers are high
school friends of the person that did
the textures oh let's use their own name
on the volcano before you know the dumb
kid
why why would i be the dumb kid
because everyone made a potato and she
made a volcano but honestly the volcano
is more um impressive
is it like she missed the
the assignment completely
a volcano is easy really
[Music]
it's the easy science fair oh really it
looks so cool though
yeah
we never had a science fair
i'm so jelly i thought that was only
something in tv shows but then everyone
in the chat was like i did it i did it i
made a potato i made a volcano
[Music]
wow
fan special it was like 50 volcanoes oh
my god that's funny it's so
disappointing as a teacher maybe
i don't know making a volcano on stream
i like the idea but it sounds like it
was gonna be really messy
it sounds like it's gonna be really
messy
what if all that [\h__\h] lands on my p on
my pc
or on my floor
[Music]
i can imagine
it will be messy yeah
maybe we can make a baby volcano tiny
baby volcano
embrace regular mountain
what does the mountain do nothing
hmm
[Music]
i could do it in the bathtub but i don't
know how to stream the bathtub to my pc
here
i don't know i don't know if i'm ever
desperate for content i might do this a
volcano but for now i already have like
many ideas
for other things
like i still need to iron my clothes on
stream
[Laughter]
so many things you know
we need to do a proper cooking stream
again sometime soon
yeah save volcano for later i need some
ideas for for like half a year later or
one year later you know i can't use up
all the
ideas that's what i'm thinking too when
i play games like this
these
these legendary games
i play them once and i won't play them
again so
ah it feels like
ah
i don't know
i i need i need to leave some for like
one year later or so
[Music]
first time experience is also always the
most special one too
[Music]
yeah i need to space them out
mm-hmm
i need to space them out
raising them yeah yeah that's what i'm
always thinking
goddamn streamer brain
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat wow
kfc r d department what's r d again
please work on our kiara ai we can strap
to potato battery i believe a portable
ai will improve productivity and morale
by 42.69
stupid meme numbers
oh
i don't know how that would work i don't
[Music]
potato battery i'll leave that to you
guys you're welcome to create something
that you can strap the potato battery
i don't know how to do that what are you
the research and development department
for if not for stuff like this
you're at school i'm leaving it to you
looking forward to the
yeah do it i'm looking forward to the
result do it
then i will get a potato too and strap
it to my potato as well and see if it
works
[Music]
yeah that was like my very first idea in
the very beginning
of like even before debut i was like
can you teach me memes but it never
happened
uh taco five six eight duncan
and i might have forgotten to give a
kiss maybe leave
there you go
uh cruz duncan
thank you for the pinky thanks for the
stream you played well
you're so kind you guys are so sweet
thank you hi
i appreciate that even if it's maybe
partially not true
sorry thank you
uh
was i supposed to read that in
chinese
[Music]
thank you
i know nothing of a testing facility in
kfp
mrs duncan how you owe hundreds of
thousands of
[Music]
i remember that
roughly
barely vaguely
[Music]
can we get another video explaining how
you owe hundreds of thousands of euros
to the austrian government for setting
up fire alarms
right
where did you dig that one out
i remember mentioning something like
that but don't bring it up they're gonna
remember they forgot about it
how are they gonna ask me again send me
letters telling me to pay up
oh my god
that is
some tiny vague knowledge man
no you have a list
wow sasuka
shouldn't have doubted you guys
avenged me face of the pinky netflix
original documentary narrated by morgan
freeman or christopher walken
what is this telling me
[Music]
what is this what is this what is this
super chat telling me
[Music]
wait what the [\h__\h] is super fanx
is that the
is that the thing where you can thank
afterwards in the archive
i i just now noticed i have a button for
super fans
should i turn it on
but just like not read them
because like i think they will it will
be hard to have an overview of those
[Music]
now why not i guess
i wonder
if i have them on
if that's so like if that intervenes
with like you know when i have super
chats off but super fang's on
if that's like
intervening with the role of no super
chats for certain games and so on
i might ask
amy uses them
oh really
i'll turn them on
but
i wonder also
how they are look how they will look
like in my
list
or if they will not show up at all i
turned them on right now is anyone who
wants to test it
because i legit want to know if if i can
see
the difference here
[Music]
you can comment on a different one that
would stand out more too if it's in my
list
maybe the previous one from yesterday
but none
yeah some one one person is enough
yeah i mean
i don't think anyone really expects me
to
rate them
if they're in abroad
but how do they show up as a comment
[Music]
i did you did
refreshing
um
[Music]
no
i don't think it's in my super chat list
unless it takes more time but let me go
to the vod from yesterday
[Music]
no i wouldn't mind like at least going
through them privately and liking every
single one of them but like
i will totally lose sight of them
at some point because how do i know that
oh somebody just sent one to that stream
somebody sent one to that stream from
like two weeks ago or so
um
maybe i can at least look for the recent
ones
um like let's say okay i did a stream
yesterday
it's been 24 hours so i look into the
into the comment section
and i go through them
but the thing is i can't sort it by
i can't i can only still sort it by
newest or most relevant but i can't sort
it by superfangs
so if it's like all mixed in between
normal comments
it's like gonna be buried in between
that kind of sucks too
[Music]
yeah
i don't know i mean i'll leave it on i
guess for people who want to use it
maybe some people who have bought
vouchers and never get to watch the live
streams
maybe some sea people
want to use it i don't know
but yeah i i don't i mean if anything i
read it in my private time if i go for
the comments sometimes
yeah i don't think people expect them to
be read on the stream if it's like
donated to a board yeah
and it doesn't logically it doesn't make
quite much sense yeah
especially if they keep on coming for
all of us like how would i know
how would i know
[Music]
but yeah if you guys feel like it you do
you
[Music]
thank you
in any case thank you to whoever wishes
to use it thank you
uh now where was i i refreshed there we
are thank you avenged me for the pinky i
don't quite understand it
uh what that was related to
but thank you
okay
oh my god it's almost midnight let's
finish this up make well cfaa thank you
for the pinky hola don't mind me here
showing some support from my beloved
boss also my mom finds your love
interesting
uh her name is angelica she likes you by
the way well i'm glad she does
i won't say liking because of work but
i'll support you whenever i can't grasp
you thank you too
oh i remember something someone else
what was that anyway thank you i'm glad
your mom likes me
it's a bit embarrassing thinking that
your mom's army
um hope she didn't cringe too much
but thank you very much
ah
apparently
you just comment filled in the comment
section of the youtube studio ah okay
okay okay i'll take a look at that
thank you make well
final at work okay
might be tough sometimes but fight oh do
your best okay
and you'll always be welcome here
on stream
[Music]
i'm getting really tired man mrs duncan
oh no you had to do it too holy [\h__\h]
grim dancing
[Music]
oh make some mexican dwarf crayfish
instead of regular blue creamers
remember that they're pretty small and
they do come in blue and orange
i like the big one though
[Music]
i look a little bit more into it but i
like the blue big one
it's cool
john mesa duncan
oh i will also put in some shrimps yeah
probably because i heard the crayfish
goes well with shrimp
[Music]
optimus prime thank
which one it's gonna be
i'm gonna test it that was a straight
chicken almost eaten by an elf before
saved by can't be true attention's
kindness is only matched by puzzle
solving and cuteness
that sounds like a perfectly sweet super
chat or am i not picking up some sarcasm
or so in here
it sounds super nice
and he's he's playing along with what i
was saying
oh
[Music]
i'm glad i saved all these straight
chickens out there
[Music]
almost eaten by an elk that must have
been a very traumatizing experience
that's maybe why mother-son sometimes is
a little bit tsunsen
we have to understand you know
you never know
what these chickens have gone through
you're welcome guys
[Music]
uh
papa
[Music]
oh
happy birthday to you
we have birthday today so happy birthday
emma naden
attorney at music duncan
remember about playing cafe member
custom levels
a great workshop feature where people
can design their own levels what
really
like super mario mario maker
that's implemented in the game
[Music]
i have no more water i'm gonna die
but i'm almost done
oh i might look into that
thank you for telling me ultimo mk zero
three ah the zero turn into two zero
three thank you
wow
huh this is about thank you soon coconut
duncan for the red super chat oh see
here it says aud okay it just looked
weird to me and
in the chat window
dear only phoenix from the immortal
realm i am here to confess my sin
i wasn't able to stay up to catch your
stream today oh but since you're still
streaming i'm offering to you this
prayer i'm going to take an important
career designing exam in two hours so
please bless me what university
thanks a lot tanjo
well that means you probably have to
study so it's all good that's important
you will
be just fine you will pass it i know it
i can look into the future and i see you
passing
yeah if you're nervous then just breathe
in breathe out breathe in breathe out
slowly
i believe in you
and then after that exam
you'll have a lot of time to watch my
streams right
so you better pass
thank you for the double red super chat
mwah
i wish you the best of luck
[Music]
no pressure though
if i could i would even pack you some
lunch
so just take that imaginary lunch okay
they might already be i don't see them
in the chat anymore they may not
already be on the way to the exam
in two hours so yeah maybe they're on
the way already or or still like
learning right now
two hours before the exam i feel like
two hours before the exam
you might feel desperate to study some
more but
before so close to an exam i think in
most cases it's not really going to help
much more
but i understand
i probably did the same in school
[Music]
but generally because i didn't start
learn studying early enough for most
things like math
yeah last minute cramming yeah
conduction means
[Music]
oh
yeah i've heard of it so it must be
one of the legends hell
it was kfp lore avenged me
next looks original
but i remember that when the [\h__\h] was
that
what was that about
about about camp p
a
a documentary about cave pete narrated
by morgan freeman and christopher vulcan
[Music]
is something i mentioned before or what
wait i don't remember that at all does
anybody remember that
and nobody knows
[Music]
it's apparently some kind of care of
people well i don't remember
it's too deep
no i remember david attenborough
i oh i love i love those super chats
okay i'm i i don't have the patience for
it right now because i also need to go
to the idle meeting
and i have no water and i'm gonna die
i'm gonna just dry out right here i'm
done reading so get that hallelujah see
you tomorrow guys for portal 2 tomorrow
more portal yeah
[Music]
did i say that thank you i love you guys
do
[Music]
you