[Music]
talking to my cat don't mind me
hello everyone
oh
hello
ew today is
one
week anniversary of sparks therefore i
shall sing sparks and only sparks and
nothing but sparks
i hope you guys don't mind
[Music]
let me pull up the jacket yo
it's too big
push bars like the lights all the way
starting to find you today don't stop
don't stop just go your own way how are
you guys
one week one week it's been a week
yo
spock spike sparks have you been
listening to sparks
have you been listening to it a lot um
i wanna i wanna just note because
even though i already talked about it on
stream uh
people keep on pointing it out to me on
twitter which i'm thankful for but i
already know about it um the fact that
my song is currently uh at least like on
amazon uh you can only find it if you
type in either sparks or my name in
japanese but it doesn't come up if you
look up my name in in our english
letters uh i i am aware of that we are
trying to get that fixed i don't know
what happened there
uh
seems to be a mistake uh but people keep
on pointing that out to me as if like uh
the song is not there at all it is there
but you have to
even look for just sparks then it will
come up or you look for the name in
japanese however if you look on like
spotify and so on it does come up like
in english right
right it does right
but then there people are pointing out
to me that someone has been you know
writing on my back um please don't give
it any any lessons because that is um
yeah that is not cool uh that is that is
uh yeah i've already talked about it but
uh the fact that there is a song there
that is by supposedly takanashikiya but
obviously not by takanashikira and that
is uh
well an imposter but like it's not even
funny because they're like like trying
to make um money from like
uh putting their songs on to like
registering it to people's artists names
that oh yeah they have nothing to do
with and they also have nothing to do
with the the that song and that artist
who yeah you're just using a random song
blah blah so i just want to say number
one we're getting the name thing fixed
supposedly at some point and number two
uh don't listen to that imposter and
number three strange box
it is definitely up on all the music
services
uh
that you can imagine spotify amazon
music apple music itunes everywhere or
just in some cases it's maybe a little
bit more difficult to find them than in
others ah unfortunately yeah it happens
but i hope you guys will still are still
supporting spikes and in order to get
your spirit up to support it more i am
now gonna sing for two hours
just this one song
sparks
[Music]
actually uh this idea kind of comes from
poruka senpai because she did that when
blue clapper came out and she sang it
for two hours and i was watching that
for a while and i got i got brainwashed
myself
so i thought we should probably do that
with sparks in order to brainwash all of
you
in case you haven't been brainwashed yet
it's a super hype song it's a super fun
song uh
yeah
so i think this will be fun
all right are you are you ready for the
first time
uh let's go let's see how many times we
can sing it in two hours
let's go
all right we need to test the audio too
by the way
[Music]
yeah there we go maybe around this
oh you think
oh yeah oh wait that's something else
i i wanted to try like putting up my
music video in the back and all that but
there was like a tiny tiny tiny tiny
tiny delay with the audio so
[Music]
[Laughter]
wait we didn't even really test it just
tell me in the chat we'll be singing it
a million times there's so much time to
improve it
lying down on the floor late night and
you don't know don't know don't know
what to do
hard to tell what's wrong what's right
if yes or no don't know don't know what
to do or the storm hits hard and you're
losing the way
just take a chance and dance in the rain
[Music]
you're gonna be
okay so go ahead and do it to it if you
want it let's get to it everybody's
gonna know your name which is
[Music]
[Applause]
get out of your head life is only once
you make
is
[Music]
[Applause]
is
[Music]
[Applause]
don't be afraid
[Music]
[Applause]
don't stop don't stop just going away
[Music]
[Applause]
ah
was that so loud was the pgm too loud
wasn't too loud let me know
[Laughter]
was fine perfect perfect really
okay we're going to keep it like that
then
when i was looking at the the volume on
obs it looked quite loud but if you guys
say it's fine i shall trust you so uh i
guess the name of the first song was
sparks
number two
by the end of the stream you will know
the lyrics by heart and hopefully me too
lying down on the floor late night and
you don't know don't know don't know
what to do
hard to tell what's wrong what's right
if yes or no don't know don't know what
to do oh the storm hits hard and
[Music]
don't forget what i
of your said
life is only once you make it you're
gonna be okay
so go ahead and do it do it if you want
it let's get to it everybody's gonna
know your name
cause sparks
[Music]
[Applause]
don't stop don't stop
[Music]
that's how we like
so take a step and move it move it
unless you try you won't get through it
[Music]
[Applause]
don't be afraid
[Music]
[Applause]
bright you're alive from the ashes
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
i am
[Applause]
wow
what a perfect rendition of sparks that
moisture i wonder wonder why i can sing
it so well
let's go
drink some water in between of course
gotta drink some water
i wonder what the next song is
[Laughter]
i wonder
it could be could it be could it be love
conqueror my name is
could you be high challenger could it be
no
it's sparks
lying down on the floor late night and
you don't know don't know don't know
what to do
i could tell what's wrong what's right
if yes or no don't know don't know what
to do when a
[Music]
don't forget what i said
so go ahead and do it do it if you want
it let's get to it everybody's gonna
know you're cute
[Music]
so don't be afraid
[Applause]
[Music]
is
everybody
[Music]
don't be afraid
when the flame is
[Music]
[Applause]
is
[Music]
i am
[Applause]
wouldn't you say the song gets better
each time you listen to it
and that was only the third time
well the banger with a banger stream
spikes listen to it get it on spotify
get it on itunes get it on amazon get it
on apple music get it everywhere i don't
even know any other music service but
i'm sure it's on more than just that if
you want to find out there's a link in
the description which leads to the
streaming services
yeah or you can just look it up by
yourself and you could also watch the
music after this stream is over at the
music video yeah
yeah
sparks
stream blue sparks
blizzard sparks level
sparks challenger
okay
okay i think
we're ready for
another one
wow now this one is really brainwashing
background material
pita
let's go
party all night
don't know what to do
hard to tell what's wrong
[Music]
never
so go ahead
[Music]
don't
[Applause]
[Music]
get out of your head life is only once
you make it you're gonna be okay
so take a step and move it move it
unless you try you won't get thrown
everybody's gonna know
yeah
[Music]
keep up and never be afraid
your eyes
[Music]
wow
don't be afraid
[Music]
[Applause]
spikes
did you guys feel like listening to more
well
even if not it's not like you have a
choice
stream sparks james box street fox
sprays supreme supreme
hey
don't know what to do
i
[Music]
take a chance and dance in the rain
cause
[Music]
so go ahead and do it do it if you want
it let's get to it everybody's gonna
know kiana cause sparks like the flames
[Music]
[Applause]
you're gonna be okay yeah yeah so take a
step and move it move it unless you try
you won't get through it everybody's
gonna know your name
[Music]
[Applause]
so don't be afraid
[Music]
[Applause]
from the ashes
[Music]
i don't even know what this part says
do you know what it says
[Music]
[Applause]
stop just go your own way
[Music]
[Applause]
hmm
yo
that was good
yo i love that part that was like gonna
make it hard i got volcanoes right come
at somebody
[Music]
i love that part
i might be one of my favorite oh the
favorite part was that though yes that
was the fifth time
uh that's already been 30 minutes
easy
one one more
one and a half more hours easy guys you
gonna stand till the end aren't you
you have to
but let me turn these crazy swirls off
for you because they're they're making
me crazy too
and
nightcore version
sure
sure okay
but it's difficult because the key is
not going to be correct i think
i just have to ignore
it what i'm hearing because i hear it
too i hear the fake voice
[Music]
[Applause]
kick your feet
[Music]
once you make it you gotta be okay yeah
yeah so take a step and move it move it
unless you try you won't get through it
everybody's gonna know your name
cause spots like the flame turn the back
of the
[Music]
so don't be afraid trust your heart keep
your head in the game
[Applause]
[Music]
from the ashes here
what does it sound
[Music]
[Applause]
don't be afraid
[Music]
[Applause]
satisfy
[Music]
[Applause]
what is this how to what kind of effect
does this give me
we can see if we have any other effects
we want to try out here
effects
we'll see
hello moshi oh wait
hello i'm on the phone
do we want to do phone phone version
spikes oh god this is pretty noisy oh
can we
post game turn it down down down nice
when it's over oh my god
this is like
really
really bad quality spikes
help me
what's buzz club this is
this is tweet i'm not sure exactly what
this is supposed to recreate but it is a
thing and also when you have some robots
and they're always too noisy let me try
out
wait oh my god it's so funny
[Music]
different robot another robot this one
is a little bit more okay-ish i guess
sorry it's so loud
turn it off turn it off it's too crazy
do we wanna do we wanna do uh
uh on the phone on the phone
on the phone uh spikes
mushy mushy it's gonna be a nice one i'm
gonna
just imagine that i am almost so loud
just imagine i am
your girlfriend and uh
i'm singing
sparks for you on the phone because you
want to really listen to the song so bad
but you have no means of listening to it
in that moment
so you ask your girlfriend to sing it
for you on the phone before you go to
sleep because that's what you need
oh we could ask
oh let's do a romantic phone a cappella
version
wait did i forget to did we already sing
it the sixth time or or and i forgot to
write it down or
[Applause]
did i forget
or is this the sixth time
this is dizzy okay
okay well done
wait
let me add that to it
phone
gf version okay
stunts
lying down on the floor late night and
you don't know
don't know
don't know what to do oh
hard to tell what's wrong what's right
if yes or no
don't know
[Music]
[Applause]
don't forget don't forget
what i said
[Applause]
get out of your head life is only what
you
so go ahead and do it do it if you want
it let's get to it
everybody's gonna know your name
[Applause]
so don't be afraid just your heart keep
your
[Music]
gotta make it hot like a volcano strike
a match and burn it up kick your feet
against the table
don't stop don't stop just go your own
way
you want to listen to more
we're going
[Applause]
is
[Music]
[Applause]
so don't be afraid just your heart keep
your head and
keep up keep up and never be afraid
[Music]
you're alive from the ashes your eyes
[Laughter]
going your own way so don't be afraid
just your heart keep your hand okay keep
up keep up and never be afraid gotta
make it hot like a volcano strike a
match and
[Applause]
[Music]
did you fall asleep now
wake up
it's time for another one
hey
am i louder than before
number seven
[Music]
lying down on the floor late night and
you don't know don't know don't know
what to do
hard to tell what's wrong what's right
if yes or no don't know don't know what
to do oh the storm is hard and you're
losing the way
just take a chance and dance
[Music]
so go ahead and do it do it if you want
it let's get to it everybody's gonna
know
cause sparks like the flames
[Music]
so don't be
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
no
doubt
so don't be afraid
[Music]
is
good
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
wow
need more of that
let's go number eight
[Music]
don't know what to do
hard to tell what's wrong what's right
if yes or no don't know don't know what
to do or storm his heart and you're
losing the way
just take a chance and dance
[Music]
so go ahead and do it do it if you want
let's get to it don't let your dreams be
dreams
cause spikes light the flames turn the
dark of the night and today don't stop
don't stop just go your own way
[Music]
[Applause]
kick your feet
[Music]
so take a step and move it move it
unless you try you won't get through it
everybody's gonna know what's your
name don't stop don't stop just go your
own way so don't be afraid
[Music]
is
good
[Music]
[Applause]
today
[Music]
brb phone
i had to put on pants for that one
okay
okay one second i wanna
change clothes uh okay guys you must
[Music]
hey you know some of you guys are
recommending um
german or japanese spikes and i wish i
would have followed that earlier than i
would have prepared lyrics in english or
german japanese and german but
unfortunately i haven't
maybe next time
sorry i didn't think of that that was
that would have been fun uh
coming up with that would take a little
bit of a while uh so yeah however
uh there's a song i want to sing
and it's called
drum roll please
spikes
separates yes
wealthy version
that's it
[Music]
don't
[Laughter]
[Music]
just take a chance and
you get out of your head life is only
once you make it you're gonna be okay
so go ahead and do it do it you won't
get through it oops
[Music]
that's what i wanted to do
[Applause]
[Music]
let this only once you make it you're
gonna be okay yeah yeah so take a step
and move it move it unless you try you
won't get through everybody's gonna know
your name
cause sparks like the flames
[Music]
so don't be afraid
from
[Music]
[Applause]
start a fire
[Music]
i am
[Applause]
thank you that was fun
okay
apparently it takes us uh in one hour we
can sing ten times
so the next one will be number ten
let's go sparkle
stranger
i want to put on my glasses
it's so sparkly i can barely see
you need to put on glasses
yes
oh yeah
shaking
oh yeah feel the beat
lying down on the floor late night and
you don't know don't know don't know
what to do oh i could tell what's wrong
what's right if yes or no don't know
don't know what to do the storm is
[Music]
don't forget what i said
life is only once you make it you're
gonna be okay
so go ahead and do it do it if you want
it let's get to it everybody's gonna
know what's my name
[Music]
so don't be afraid
[Applause]
[Music]
don't stop don't stop just go your own
you heard what i said
[Music]
so take a step and move it move it
unless you're trying to get through it
everybody
[Music]
[Applause]
so don't be afraid
[Music]
[Applause]
can't speak english
poured over
[Music]
[Applause]
it's like a match
[Music]
i am
[Applause]
[Music]
yum
go to spotify go to amazon music go to
amazon there's a difference between
those two and go to apple music go to
itunes what are the other ones what are
the other ones huh
i don't even know let me see oops
streamlink
dot t o sparks uh line music
youtube music maura
yeah that's that's pretty much about it
as well that's already good it's good
enough
and if you can't find it in the amazon
go right in spikes and it should come up
it
doesn't come up with my english name
currently weird stuff
yup
thank you for supporting up until hours
to one more hour
it's not over
can you take it till the end easy right
this was such a fun song it's just easy
how about
i kind of like being
small
[Applause]
i'll be small
divine
exquisite
lying down on the floor late night and
you don't know don't know don't know
what to do oh hard to tell what's wrong
what's right if yes or no
[Music]
take a chance and dance
so take a step and do it do it if you
want it
[Music]
so don't be afraid
[Applause]
[Music]
that
so take a
[Music]
don't be afraid
[Applause]
[Music]
tonight
your eyes
[Music]
hands every one
don't be
afraid keep your head in the game
[Music]
don't stop don't stop just going away
[Applause]
[Music]
if yes or no don't know don't know what
to do oh the storm is hard and you're
losing the way
just take a chance and dance in the rain
cause you got the key never throw
[Music]
so take this
so don't be afraid
[Music]
[Applause]
we're going
[Music]
okay
yeah don't be afraid
[Music]
just your eyes
[Applause]
wow
[Music]
so don't be afraid
[Applause]
[Music]
wow
that was
original potential version
that was number 11.
the wealthy ones are fun too
thank you thank you
little little water very uh water uh
break
70 bang oh my god
you remember
i remember my shammy bang
jeopardy bed
you can also do a birth version
oh my god
we can try
i mean i can i can instead of using
those pre-recorded ones i guess i can
do it myself
version
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
ah
i mean you know what let's do it this is
this is like a like millie millie millie
million millisecond off uh but i think
it should work anyway
[Music]
crack
me
god
[Applause]
[Music]
tv
[Applause]
[Music]
wow
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
beep beep beep beep beep
beep beep beep
[Music]
[Applause]
my
[Music]
ah
me
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah i hope that was fun
okay but this
is the vine
exquisite
oh
baby okay we can do baby version and we
can do a cat version
good ideas
wait
now we're just around
all right we're looking right we're just
around
beer but
gotta get into my baby attire
how cute
oh how adorable i mean
come on how can you resist
hey i got some bars
not i'm not actually good with being a
baby
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
kick your
[Applause]
[Music]
that's how we like
come on
[Applause]
[Music]
stupid
[Applause]
[Music]
wow
[Applause]
[Music]
wow
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
okay okay i'm sorry
i'm sorry
i'll make it i'll make it up i'll make
it up okay
wait
uh
i'm gonna get up
trust me
everybody likes cats can't tell me you
don't like cats
how much cats do we want to be
50 or 100
lying down on the floor or 100
[Music]
yum
yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
yum yum yum yum yum
yum yum yum
[Music]
yum yum yum yum yum yum
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
meow
[Applause]
[Music]
now
[Applause]
[Music]
meow water
let's go back to normal
if that's okay
cat version
which one was your favorite up until now
[Laughter]
that one was
quite something
phone call um
there was no government girlfriend
version oh
oh
cat
very version
wolfie
oh thank you thank you oh i'm glad you
guys like those so much those versions
we're going back to normal though
chris it's uh quite exhausting after a
while
by the way by the way just put
information
and after this stream i'll take a one
hour break
and then i'll read super chats for like
three hours or four hours
yeah gorilla super chat reading because
i really need to catch up i didn't read
as many as i thought i would be able to
read yesterday so i want to
catch up a bit more
okay
next version
back to normal
sparks
but i'll stay a cat if that's okay
[Music]
don't know don't know what to do
take a chance and dance
[Music]
so go ahead and do it do it if you want
it let's get to it everybody's gonna
know your name
cause spikes like the flame turn the
dark of the night into they don't have
those
[Music]
[Applause]
is
[Music]
[Applause]
there's one more
from
[Music]
[Applause]
keep up
[Music]
[Applause]
16 times already oh we actually kind of
uh
did those few like arrangement versions
so fast that we kind of like did more
than in the first half
i feel like
we can chill a little bit
how about um
um
how about
another not not phone version but like
acapella version
normal acapella
especially when i was singing because
sparks like the flame turned dark of the
night and today
so don't be afraid trust your heart keep
your head you guys gonna get so sick of
it especially i'm also gonna get sick of
it if i sing the whole song like that
ah
gonna make it hot like a volcano striker
match i'm burning up kick your face
against the tell you about take the bat
over your underwear
now i can't do it
i chose that and that
i can't jeremy yeah unfortunately i
didn't prepare a german version yet or
japanese version unfortunately sorry
about that next time next time
i don't know who the out the kiara
is
sounds good they sound good they sound
legit
yo if there were any like proper remixes
yet i would use the remixes
but unfortunately there isn't so
uh
welp
ah that's the one more normal one
why not
[Music]
don't know what to do
hard to tell what's wrong what's right
if yes or no don't know don't know what
to do oh the storm is hard and you're
losing away
just take a chance
[Music]
life is only once you make it you're
gonna be okay
so go ahead and do it do it if you want
it let's get to it
everybody's like
[Music]
[Applause]
kick
[Music]
life is only once you make it you're
gonna be okay yeah yeah so take a step
and move it move it unless you try you
won't get through it everybody
yeah
the spots like the flame turn the
[Music]
[Applause]
so don't be afraid
[Music]
[Applause]
from
[Music]
wow
bye
[Music]
[Applause]
so don't be afraid
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
repeat after me
stream specs
repeat that to me
strips back
stretch box
straight spanx
not sparkles not sparkle
not kidakina sparks
stream sparks
spike swing
strings box challenger
this doesn't necessarily count with
streaming sparks but uh stream specs
extreme specs afterwards
after this stream is over all right
okay water drinking everyone go
we are getting closer to the end half an
hour left
[Music]
i can't sing this song in a deep voice
because the key is so high the only part
where i could sing in a deep voice is
where i'm actually singing in a deep
voice anyway where he goes
get out of your head life is only what
you'll show me to think acapella
i'm sorry to disappoint you but the song
is very high
oh you i mean i can i can i can i can do
i can do this
but who wants to hear that
one no one yourself okay
no you don't wanna hear it
sparks acapella
i mean i tried already before but it
sounded really
one of those versions i did high key and
loki
but well it just doesn't fit the key of
the song because i can't manipulate the
key of the song while i'm manipulating
the key of my voice
manually on the mixer
no one wants to hear that what the hell
okay a white version
all right okay okay okay
shanina
[Music]
don't know what to do
i could tell what's wrong what's right i
guess or no don't know don't know what
to do through the storm it's hard and
you're losing the way
just take a chance and dance
don't forget what i said
[Music]
today
[Applause]
[Music]
let's
is
[Music]
[Applause]
i hope
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
do you regret your choices
do you regret it i regret everything
i regret everything so much
i feel like i lost so much weight
i don't understand
i don't get it can we get a straw hat
version going
your shot
straw hat version straw hat version
straw head straw hat straw
nice
like a country girl unfortunately i
don't really know how to sing
like a country girl
sorry so don't ask me to do that
imagine it
imagine imagine you it could be more
like a girl next door okay
that's more like it
and
how about we do acapella for real this
time
but like without any effects
maybe maybe even live way less
way less
yes
okay
yeah
i'm listening to the music anywhere in
the background
lying down on the floor late night and
you don't know don't know don't know
what to do
hard to tell what's wrong what's right
if yes or no don't know don't know what
to do or the storm it's hard and you're
losing the way
just take a chance and dance in the rain
cause you got the key never throw it
away don't forget don't forget what i
said
get out of your head life is only what
you make it you're gonna be okay
so go ahead and do it do it if you want
it let's get to it everybody's gonna
know your name
cause sparks like the flame turn the
dark of the night into the day don't
stop don't stop just go your own way so
don't be afraid just your heart keep
your head and look and keep up keep up
gotta make it hot like a volcano strike
a match and burn it up kick your feet
against the table to the feet of your
lung drum sparks light the flame so
don't wait start a fire today
we ain't looking back take the fast lane
now and the driver stayed strapped they
just gasped out loud we're going so fast
that it shouldn't be allowed that's how
we like it you heard what i said
get out of your head life is only what
you make it you gotta be okay
so take a step and move it move it
you won't get through it everybody's
gonna know your name
cause sparks light the flame turn the
dark of the night until they don't stop
don't stop just go your own way so don't
be afraid just your heart keep your head
and looking
and never be afraid
let go of the past tonight just the
future only you'll be fine even when the
flames burn too bright you're alive from
the ashes
[Music]
could have done that better
what was a hidden mess
[Music]
don't stop don't stop just go your away
so don't be afraid just your heart keep
your head and again keep up keep up and
never be afraid gotta make it hot like a
volcano strike a match and burn it up
[Music]
start a fire today don't stop don't stop
just go you're away
[Music]
could you have guessed
what the next song is i already wrote it
down but i know it's very surprising i
know i know i know i know i know
hey some asmr oh god
i'm not i'm not quite the asmr type of
person so i wouldn't really know how to
do that
that would just be whispery right
that's so boring who wants that that's
so boring
i will do that if someone makes
like a
like a lo-fi or like piano or some some
kind of calm version of the song
then i will do that okay
but there's still like no real uh like
remixes everyone's welcome to make
remixes of the song uh i know it might
be hard i don't know if so
is it hard if the instrumental is not
public yeah maybe i'll upload the
instrumental on my on my channel
sometime soon
the instrumental if you listen closely
you hear all the
harmonies
you want to listen
[Music]
[Applause]
harmony
[Music]
[Applause]
so don't be afraid just your heart keep
your head
[Applause]
i can't hear it
[Music]
that's like the low slow harmony
yeah yeah
get it if you listen closely you'll
probably hear it
if you listen to the harm uh
instrumental
gosh
pickle version what the hell
okay i'm just gonna add pickle after
everything
pickle
it's like the
[Music]
don't know what to do
hard and you're because
the way they go just take a chance and
dance in the rain back off got the key
never throw it away
[Music]
[Applause]
is
[Music]
[Applause]
don't be afraid just your heart keep
your head
[Applause]
[Music]
ah
[Applause]
[Music]
no one needed that
except baby for
bacon
[Laughter]
spikes pickle
okay okay can we go back to normal
spikes
it's the best spice the best spikes
is the normal
okay i brought we can fit in two more
two more spikes i think
thank you thank you thank you i'm glad
i'm glad it helped you guys
okay
we're going into the last spurt
i don't know
i don't like any of these
are you vibing sing with me guys you
should know the lyrics by now it's not
so hard
lying down on the floor late
[Music]
don't know what to do or the storm is
[Applause]
gonna make it
[Music]
[Applause]
you heard what i said
[Music]
[Applause]
be afraid
[Music]
so don't
[Applause]
feet against the table
[Music]
[Applause]
you know why for people who don't know
uh sparks was written and produced by
kira who is
one of the two people behind getcha
and he's a really really great really
talented producer from germany
who also
not also but interestingly enough has
a chicken like baby chick icon
as his like thing you know and uh i mean
his name is so similar to mine too so
just wanted to remind you again of the
funny lord that
is there
and germany says we both speak german
it's just so funny
yeah i love it i love it it's just
perfect and i love his songs
because uh you know i was you guys you
guys were asking for
a japanese and not non-japanese song for
a while
and i was thinking well
who
i did i didn't even have to think to be
honest by that time i already knew kira
like his songs and i already knew like
if i wanted someone to write an english
song for me
i don't
i don't i couldn't think of anyone
besides kira he's so talented
and he wrote such a banger and i'm so
grateful for that i don't know kira if
you're watching this
by producing this song you probably
heard this song even
about a
million more times than i even did
so you probably don't want to listen to
it anymore but
i'll sing it one last time
one last time
and it could
it could only be
last time
[Music]
yes or no
don't forget
so go ahead and do it do it if you want
it let's get
[Music]
[Applause]
so don't be afraid
[Music]
[Applause]
that it shouldn't
[Music]
so take a step and move
[Applause]
so don't be
[Music]
[Applause]
that's right
reach
[Music]
future tonight you'll be fine even when
the flames grow too bright you're alive
[Music]
clap claps
[Applause]
[Music]
don't stop just going
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
that was 22 times of sparks
thank you thank you thank you for
supporting me thank you for supporting
sparks please listen to it on on
whichever music device you're using new
music service whatever it's in the
description open the description go on
the stream link and then please support
my music so that i can make more music
for you
please also continue watching the music
video it's already reached 500k thank
you so much for all the support you guys
are amazing you guys are really really
really dope and i hope i genuinely hope
you like this song because for me i
think it's a nice summer banger and i
just personally am as i've mentioned
before a bbp which stands for uh based
basic
i love my edm i love kira's songs and
i'm hoping for
maybe more stuff like this in the future
and
and after this i'll take one hour break
as i said and then say uh
then uh sing super chats no no no no
i'll be reading some super chats not the
ones for this one i don't know if you
saw the message i think i hope it was
pretty obvious but uh i'll not be
reading them out loud i think i'll read
them privately so thank you to everyone
who uh sent super chats anyway sorry i
won't be reading them but uh i need to i
need to catch up you know i thought i
always i usually always read them all of
them
yeah but
you know i'm still very far behind on my
birthday super chats
you know if you don't have money that is
totally fine you can support me
nonetheless by just watching the music
video that is free
so
i would really appreciate it if you
would do that yeah that would mean a lot
to me and just genuinely generally thank
you also for coming to the stream to
just hype up hype hype hype that it was
really really lovely from all of you
thank you for being here
[Music]
music
by the way we took a free week break
break break because i i broke my neck
and
and had birthday and was busy
but we're going back to yakuza like a
dragon tomorrow and that might be a long
stream
but i hope you support me with that one
too because it might be the last episode
i'm trying to make it the last episode
we seem to be very close to the end and
and i want to end it so that i can start
something new because i have permission
to play
uh zelda
sky uh
skyward
sky
i almost want to say skywalker
zelda skywalker who the is that uh
yeah so we we might want to start that
as our next rpg uh
yeah cause i got i got permission and
i'm really excited for it because i
never really um
like fully on my own hundred percent uh
played a zelda game from beginning to
the end on my own i think i always got
like help or or didn't finish it only
played it like until a certain point
didn't kill the last boss or whatever
because i was always
not good at games back then uh and yeah
most of the times i just played it with
my brother
but this time yeah i i want to play it
on my own from beginning to the end and
uh
i think i think i think this is perfect
timing because uh yeah that will
probably make up the time until we play
tennis of a rise
yeah so i hope you're looking forward to
that
um
[Music]
see you later super chat reading bye-bye
love you all thank you for the support
love you
[Music]
you