[Music]
Please give
me a new one. I'm asking
for a new one.
Chiara-chan, tell me, please.
What's real? My
senior is real.
That's what I'm talking about right now. All 1.
Who's the cutest one?
Peko-chan is cute in real life, but she's still a
cat, right? Tiara-chan also says hello. Yaro Peko. Oh, that's right. After
all, all I have
is the key, so could you please make me something cute?
Pikola-senpai is a genius, so Tenten is a genius
Tensai Kiyana-chan's
greetings
Kiriki-no- Please
put it on, it's a bit
too unreasonable You're suddenly so unreasonable
You're such a celebrity entertainer, so you
can do it Since you're
in the same group as Hololive, now  I'm
not going to rush in. I
'm a senior with no experience, so I just tried it and it's 321.
It's super cute, super strong, and the strongest phoenix. It's
not a copy. It's a
copy of that one. Thank you very much. Well, today, before we start, it's important to make one more pico. An important tweet.
Last time.  We
collaborated nine months ago, but it seems like the two of us
have been together for a long time.
Seriously, it's been a long time since we've been together. It's a
song that we've been apart for a long time. Time passes quickly, but at times like that...
Pecora Senta
was writing that poem with me, so let's write it together today.It
starts the same way as it did 9 months ago.Once upon a time, I
didn't understand the words that started with these words.OK,
mix.
Phoenix
[Music] It's
unnecessary to say that Japan was
built. I went to the Japan Tower. OK
[Music]
Art
Yes
OK OK
[Laughs] I do
n't really understand what that means.
What does this mean? Yeah,
um,
new
, um, I
feel like it's going to be a lot better than before.
Good words are kids. Good words, good words. That's
right, okok,
ah,
pekona.
GO
or higher is fine.Finally,
let's enjoin.  I
was still really bad at Minecraft, but
since then,
I've gotten really good at it, and out of all the mackerel,
Ina-chan and I are probably the best at it.Top We're the
top two, me and Torina-chan.That
's right, Chiara today.  It
means you can see her growth, right?
[Music] I wonder if
Tiara-chan made this in the place where Pecole is right now. It would be
even more amazing if a character made it. That kind of
thing makes sense, right?  It's
nighttime.
Well, I don't have a bed right now,
but for now, please
take the mine cart out of here. I'm
fine. There are already zombies, but I'm
fine. I wo
n't die. Please
help
me. This title is
already dead. I look
surprised.  Ara-chan also
has an Elytra equipped with diamond equipment.I
thought, ``Seriously, my senpai.''I was the first person to
get an Elytra at a Minecraft Sour around here.
[Music]
Wow, that's Pico! It
's so amazing. I'm
getting chilly. I want that Elytra. It's
getting cold. It's a little
bit now. Hey, hey, hey. The
first thing you see is that.  Amelia-chan's
body is normal. She
has big breasts. She's on
this roller coaster. It might be
dangerous, but she's not at all.
Please don't look at her panties. Next up
is Una-chan. Um, Mona-chan.
It's a memory of when my mother came to this mackerel.
Yeah, yeah, what's this?
It's a ritual like passing under everyone's trees or something, but it's
dangerous, there's an enemy, this is dangerous, it's going to break, it's going to
break, isn't it Pico?  This is a
normal place with enemies, but
it's okay, it's okay, this mackerel is very
springy and easy to crush.Here
we are,
heroes.
Oni-chan visited this mackerel and said something like, Wow,
this
was a dangerous place before, so he cleaned it up and
gave me a rainbow, and he
also prepared a lot of beds,
so I
took one.  Please,
what do you like?
[Music]
[Music] It
's Peko's first time here, but she did
n't expect to suddenly feel a warm welcome passing under her feet.
Pekora-senpai's one will also be made on the 5th.
Please let me take the other side.
Okay, that's
amazing.
Let's go through the Rainbow Bridge. It's
Rainbow Road. It
's beautiful here.
Tiara-chan and Gura-chan are so
cute.
Do your best.  I made it for hours and
hours and hours and hours and hours and hours.
It's a piece of wood that's in a high place. This is what it
took to make it.
We're beginners, so
even beginners can do it. It's not fast. You can do this.  This
is Peko, this is the event, and
it's the only pixel art.
That
's you. It's not terrible.
That's not 3D.
[Laughs]
[Music]
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's amazing.
Peko looks so cute in the forest.
So, when you go here, first of all, on the left, well, it's
a little broken in half, but here it is.
Also, it's Ited Sex. It's true
that Mike's number one in the house is no lie.
This is
it.
[Music] A
long time ago,
when I invited that polka-senpai to this mackerel, I
made a battle owarina for that purpose, but because of the
scary
Cure, that computer and
Minecraft crashed over and over again, so we couldn't collaborate at all in the end.  It seems
like it became the center of attention because it
wasn't there, and here the revelation became a child, but
that's right, but it's nothing. Well,
this is also the management P that I
made a long time ago, quite early on.
[Music]
There's a hell of a lot of staff, right? That's right, the store
staff and the customers. Both of them are chickens. Also, they're the
ones who cannibalize the customers. They're the ones who
cannibalize the customers. Yeah, yeah,
yeah, it's not that person, it's me.  I was still a beginner at the time,
so it
wasn't really that amazing, but that house was
one of the buildings that really stood out.
Crispy Chicken, please, OkOk,
please wait a minute.
Eh, chocochi,
chocochi, pochapocha, if you don't do it,
how are you going to kill them?
Why don't you just kill them one by one? Yes, it's crude
oil.
I made it.
It's a map of tomorrow's Pika-chan. Iina-
chan.
Well, it's not all written here,
but I don't
understand, wait a minute, it's a
little bit okay.  I
think Peko House
doesn't make any Pecolas.
[Music] It
doesn't matter, it doesn't matter.
It gathers a lot of rabbits,
but I
want to go to a Peko scam cafe later. It's
okay, it's okay, it's OK. That's the
top of the line.
Spongin is a
world-famous and interesting first full chain,
and I'm the store manager.
Yeah, yeah, that's nice. It's a rich man, isn't it? Tiara-
chan, then everything around here is mine.  That
's right.
The first thing you need to eat
is
Ciara, you're really a bird.
This is how
good you are. And down here, you'll find something like that for the first time,
along with Amelia, who made something amazing. But already, there's
eggs.  There were too many, so I stopped. I see. The
birds saw the eggs and collected them. It
makes sense automatically. I wish there was a store nearby that
could produce eggs.
Oh yeah, yeah.
It's amazing, isn't it? It's amazing. This isn't particularly amazing,
but it's
amazing. This
has a lot of history.
When we first started, we had curry with Kari-chan
and Opera-chan, and then we thought, ``
Well, let's build a house together,'' and we
said, ``Let's do our best with
Tiara.''  This is the house I built for Kari-chan, and the
rented girl slept with me for one night, but after that she
went somewhere else.
Eh, a lot of things have happened since then, and that
room mate came in and left,
but it's the
dance spot, and that's Chiara's dandruff, and it looks like her father
slept only in the human version,
made by the synthetic leather meat room.
Yes, it's something that doesn't happen in Minecraft Saba, but I
only said it for one night, but
in the end, I end up living alone over and over again.I
see, it seems like no one will give everything to me.
But I've been living in this humid house for a long time, and
as a result, I felt like I needed to make a more beautiful house, so I
built this one.  It's a
bird's house, and it's
really stylish. I
tried my best to make it look like a kitchen, and
here it is in the living room. That's the
TV. Which
TV is
that? The refrigerator, oh yeah, that's nice. What is this?
Well, I'm
sorry, that's right, it's stylish with the lighting.It's
true that I'm always fighting with this door.It's
difficult.Thank you,
thank you.Are you okay?
Eh, I
won't let it fly, but I'll probably
die.It ca
n't be helped.I
worked hard to make it, but in the
end I ended up
using it.  No, I
can't even buy this bed. I thought it was just for looks. I
just accepted this house.
No, Chiara-chan's home base isn't here
right now. That means it's Pyoko. No, it's
true. It's said in the documents, but she doesn't actually use it. But it's okay. I didn't look at anything and just
made this. I thought about it myself.  Tan: Wow, good
night. It's
like Christmas right now. It
's Pico. Yeah, there's already a lot of cats. This
area is tucked away here. It
's the main place where everyone gathers.
There's Merry Story, etc.
Nina-chan is also very good, it's amazing. She's evolving more and more. On top of that, she made her own handmade key. She's a bonsai tree. Ina-chan
loves animals and collects a lot of
them. She's a
friend of mine, Fubuki-senpai.  That's
amazing.
[Music] It's
so authentic. Ina-chan's authentic style. It's so nice to have a tree inside the house.  I
think it's okay to go upstairs.
Okay,
senior. He's
eating something. It's Pico. He's eating something big.
He's adding it to his mouth. It's the first time I've ever heard of him being able to do that. Hey, that's
cute. It's
not food, is it?
Everyone has cheese here.
It's cut, there's an axolotl, it's
flattened, oh yeah, this is also recent,
recently,
yes, it's
beautiful, beautiful,
Ina-chan has this kind of sense.  I'm so
jealous, it's so amazing
Hey, I've
done almost everything here It's a
terrible thing to say, but I know what I'm going to show you from here.
And this is the first part of that house, Rain's,
uh,
Nether Portal. I
see, I
might show you a little bit.  What's inside? It's
Pyoko that's
doing it. Yes, it's doing a little bit
. You can see all kinds of things about Ina-chan here.
For example, it's wool. It's
amazing. There's
also
a little bit on the back.
There's a lot of things going on here. I didn't
know about this. I didn't know about this. It might be the
first time for people like Infinity Stone to make stone.
That's right, Ume-chan, Ina-
chan. Ina-chan, I
don't understand this. It's
Peko. It's a new Cairo.
That's how it works.  The mackerel at home is
evolving more and more. It's
so nice.
[Music]
Chan,
Muna-chan, and
Reina-chan's
grave. They
died. It
hurts. I wonder
what it is.
[Music]  It's
a little scary that there's a grave, Pyoko, but yeah, it's a little scary,
but
here, Neina-chan is making
something.  I
can
do it Hey, I can't do
it. Box donot open. Please teach me how to make it.
Yes, this is terrible.
How did you make it? Pekura-senpai,
bazaar or something.
You know, there's a lot of skill to it,
and it's not easy to make it because I'm a low-ranking person.
[Music] I wonder
if Gura-chan can teach me how to do it if she joins me in building the plate.
If this cunning of Pecola gets inside, things will
get tough around the house.It
's okay, it's already late, it's already late, it's too late.  I
had an image that Pico
wouldn't fit in, but I guess he did somehow.
[Music]
This is the cake to commemorate that
six-
month anniversary.
There's an ender dragon egg on top,
but we
recently defeated it together.
Yes, it's
like we're all going to do it together. Lately, we've finally defeated it, but it's amazing. Everyone was so bad at
it. [Music] When I look to the left, there's always that Gura-chan house. Gura-chan is here.  I'm
trying to make a glass with a glass pattern that's trying to fill it with axolotls.
But it's still a long way off.
This is what Goya's house looks like.
Yay, that's
amazing.
It's the ocean in my mouth. I wonder
what it's like. It
says ``Kids.''  That's right, a kiss
That's right, that's why it says kiss. I did
n't chew it. There's
nothing written here.
Hey, it's a riddle, Senpai. What,
no, no, no, no, no, no,
Noah's.  It
's a DJ boost. I
don't know how to use something like DJ ugly, but I
have an item called a record in my house, so I wonder if it will
make a sound if I put it in. But
no, it's broken here.
[Music] It's
fine elsewhere too.  I'm currently making something amazing in a faraway place,
so I'm looking forward to the next one.Everyone's so
cute.Thank you
for making things like houses.There
's also a collection for beginners.Everyone
has been working on this savant for the past year.  It was
created by just the five of us, so there
's still a long way to go, but here
are the memories of the Christmas Minecraft collaboration.It's
nice to have fond memories of collaborations like those we made together.I want to
make as many as we did with Japan Seven.
If you want me to make one for you,
then I want you to see a lot of things. Let's
get down from here carefully. It's
Chan's house. It
's in a good place, right?
Wow, it's covered in water, Pyoko.
All around me. There
's a lot of stuff in here. It
's Amelia. There's a garden here too.
Tiara-chan, where did she go?
[Music] I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.  Oops, I
can go upstairs. I've never been to the top. What an
amazing dog. Today, Meiya-chan, uh,
there's a dog, and we also have two dogs and a cat.
Go back to that different job you brought me here. Ah, you
're dead. It's the one who
killed
Miya-chan.
During the broadcast, the dog always
says wan-wan-wan, wan-wan, so that's amazing. That Ban-chan is
famous. She's
cute today. This is cute.  I
don't think it's cute if there's a mascot on top of the house.Okay,
let's go back here once.Eh
, here's the Holo family where Kari-chan's
house is.
Holomis I
haven't played that Minecraft the most in my training,
so I'm just wondering
why you moved to this remote place
from the house you worked so hard to build. You've
moved to some amazing place,
right? It looks like it's
inside a rock.
Hmm, there's nothing around this big cat
Really
[Music]
Daruka Kokoro Tai-chan's house
That A on the left
looks a lot like Kari-chan,
right? Dokuro-
nee, Chan likes red wine, so I like this.
I guess you like colors, too. I see. I
see. This is my
first time at home. I think it was my
first Minecraft collaboration. It's
amazing. It's my first book, and it was
distributed only on Gura-chan's channel. It
was about building a tunnel to Atlantis.  We did a collaboration,
but I wonder how many hours it took to dig?
Well, the five of us dug, dug, dug, dug,
dug,
dug, dug, and dug for
4 hours and 3 hours.  It's
not really that big, it's amazing,
but in the end we decided to dig all the way to Atlantis,
but that's where Gura-
chan was running the place.Also, the
store clerk is in the back there.Ah,
that place is a bit dangerous.  But
there were a lot of zombies, and they all
had eggs.When I screened them, I found out that
Zombies
were chickens everywhere, right
?
Well, in Atlantis, they
didn't create Gura-chan after all.
But there are
other important things at the end, so
let's go. I
have a cart, right? I have it. I
don't have it. Oh, what should I do? It's not here. It's not here. I do
n't have anything like iron.
Please wait a minute. Give it there and wait. It's
okay. I'll
go back outside.
[Music]
Iron. Was it just
iron? Iron. That's right. 5 irons. Oh ok. I
'll go back. It's
so spacious.  The
five of us were making something, and all five of us were
so
sleepy, and
Gura-chan was wondering how long we'd have to dig for this. It
's a memory that keeps coming back to me.
There are so many different kinds of things.This
is a subway, created by someone who stops after digging.It's
just like that.  I was
playing it in the morning on Japan time, and I thought I was playing some kind of minecraft
game, but when I saw the railroad tracks, it was
just pulling out, and I saw something like
1-2-3-45678. I
got the impression that it was a cute Peko doing something while counting.This is
the result I made.  That's when Mamilia-chan
became a subway person. This
subway person is
very long, but
Opera Club-senpai, please understand. It's not quite
big,
it's
marching.
Yeah, I think I was surprised when I dug it up a
few times. I'm digging a lot of things here. It's
long,
after all, it's Atlan. There's
a lot of different songs on there, right?
On the way, uh, I just passed by, but
on the way.  There's my town called Phoenix Sen, which I'm sure
was written about in the small print, and I
'll introduce you to it later.I now
have a way to
get there.It's faster than the subway.
Tiara made the way to go with that ice cream
Pierre car on the boat
Shortcut Short
It's so cute, it's so
hard on the subway
It's
okay because there's a reason There's a reason It's okay There's a ghost It's
my own.
This is the last thing I asked for.
Um, there's coffee made by Amelia here as well.
PP
Pico La Peco La Peco La.
What's that? It
's on the left.
Wow, that's amazing.
Please climb up with all your might.I just
joked that the name was Pecola Pecola Pecola,
but apparently that PP is
Preview Three Pecolas.It
used to belong to Pecola a while ago,
but now it's Pecola's.  It's not like it's a thing.
Pico probably copied something made by a senior.
That's right, it's probably just that and that.tkt
Yeah, that's right, I use it often.  I'm
pushing here and pushing. It
's coming down so I can go higher up, but if I go up higher,
more seats will
grow.
[Music] There's a
bed above me.  The
feeling of going to sleep is getting better and better.
Wow, I'm already feeling like Iriyata.
[Music] It
's a big building that's really important.
[Music] It's
different from here. I
see.
Which one is more interesting? I wonder
if it's more effective.
No, I don't know, Pyoko, but
this is amazing. It's interesting. This is a pekko that accumulates. Is it
different from the senior's one
? It's a completely different pekola that just flows and falls like a normal pekko, so it's not like I'm involved in it.  It
's funny, the best Senpai. I'm glad it wasn't a complete copy. It's amazing.
This Senpai
is the inspiration for Emuya. I
like this, but this button keeps coming up.  I do
n't want to press it or just press it once and it'll be forever.I press it every time.It stops coming.When I
think there aren't enough of them, I go up one more time, go
to sleep once, and go back down one more time.  It's amazing.Eh, it
's about one person to make a pico.It must
have been very difficult.It's
amazing.This is the music from Zelda.But
if you do it like this, it's a bit
Wait, how do you make that
sound?
Hado
[Music]
Also, it might
be a little different.
[Music]
Hmm, I have to fix it. Apparently
Iris-chan
broke it. Also, there's a very popular fishing spot over
there on the left.
[Music]  Don't
go there
[Music]
Your ears aren't right here.
Fishing.
Fishing both up and down here.
That fishing is popular. It's
not like there's no one out there who's dangerous.
If so, there are a lot of them. For some reason, I'm
waiting for enemies to spawn from above. If I do
n't have equipment, I'm in danger of using a diamond sword.
So let's do something about it.
[Music] I do
n't have to cut people anymore.
Please give Pecoara the diamond sword.Give
Pecola the tire sword.I'm in the mood.There's
nothing but a diamond commotion.Aside
from that, I've got some presents ready for you.
So, are you going there? I
want that really happy Peko as a gift.
Giveme present
[Music] It's a
subway
car. I have
enough for each day. I've
brought my own exchanges many times. It
means I'm not connected to JP yet, so I
have it.  I just
came to the subway. You got on the subway first.
This and that.
Senior, I'm going now. I'm going now. Yes, I'm going to go now.
Okay, I'm going to use something amazing. 2 Well then, it's a
useful Pyoko. Yeah, well, recently.  The number of
people who use it has decreased a bit, but that
's right.I do
n't ride it that much anymore.I guess it's
something like a train.I don't know what
it is.I still have a lot of beginner-like ones
left in my family.  It
's all about Elytra now. It's
not like it's grown too much.
How are you doing with 350,000 people in 9 months? I
wonder what kind of gifts they'll give you. What, what,
what? Is there a
god of MyCraft's en server?
Guess I'll get some kind of present. Stop it. Are you looking forward to it? Don't get your hopes up.
[Music]
[Music] It
does exist, but after all, it's
only within the house that we've collaborated with. What do you mean, uh, the
person who collaborated with the house?  Chiara is the only one who is peckish.
See,
your English is so bad. You must
speak a lot of Japanese like Tiara-chan. If you're
not that good, you'll probably cause trouble to the other person.
Tiara-chan
doesn't think about it, but Inu-chan and Kari-chan
can speak some Japanese. I
wonder if they're going to cause trouble from here on out.
That's something I'm worried about. Japan's
face always says things like that.  You're
holding back, aren't you? You shouldn't be
holding back.
No, it's difficult. Minecraft
ran away. Minecraft ran away.
[Music]
Let's go
OK OK
[Music] I
wonder if the server will give you all the equipment for Netherrise only if you have it.So far, all I
have is that ice ax.I'm still
collecting them.Well, when I
finish collecting them...
Of course you are. That's what I
meant from the beginning. I'm glad.
[Music]
I can't stand it. I
look like a girl, so I'm going to show you my present now.
[Music]
Kahlo is this. Ah, this is it. I
want you to look at it from the other side. Is
it the other way around?
Pecola calmed me down. It's
in the Bunny House Diamond Sword. Seriously? I
had to wait for a while.
[Music]
Eh, thank you
Pico.
[Music] Yeah, I'll
give you the Eternal Car Box too. Hey,
but I haven't enchanted the window.  So
maybe it's better not to use that book yet, because it will break easily, but I left that book behind.
Um, and things like
totems, things like don't die,
diamonds, fireworks, things like that.
In order to fly, I need that carrot. I do
n't have 64 diamonds, but I do
n't have enough here.
Please give me a break there. Are you serious?
Please live here. I tried to make it a little more stylish. It
looks like a fighting game. Here
's a photo.
[Music] Hey,
wait a minute. First of all, why are
Muna and Tiara fighting here? I
thought that Sakura-senpai must have really liked it.
Yes, the video. I was
watching this thinking, "I'm loved."
Please,
stop cleaning up your nightmares, we
won't fight. I'll
protect you. It's a song that will protect you. It
may not be there left, but it
won't work either way. I'm scared, but
thank you.
[Music] It
's close to everyone, so come see me anytime.  I can
go.
Thank you, Human Pico. I have a home. I have a little more space
on my home server that isn't finished yet.
Well,
there's a new member's home recently. It's a bit damp, but
I'll show you just in case.  Eh, I'm
wearing it a little bit, but I
guess I'm an idiot who started playing it recently.It's
okay, but I think TV Koala is
great in any house.Also,
as a senior, I'm sorry for being too harsh.
Piss fans are just acknowledging the reality. Those people on the
left and right
are scary seniors. I have to give them a little praise.
Where are the juniors? Yeah, it
's a bit of a detour. I'm disappointed.
What's with Pico's disappointment? Do you
want me to explain a little bit? Well, this place actually
looks like there's nothing here,
but it's a historical place.
Many
Hollow Live viewers are watching Hollow Live
English.  Someone is trying to solve the mystery about this.
[Music] You
can't fall in. I
want you to fall in.
[Laughter]
Well, what's in this hole? There's
something really mysterious about this
hole.  I
didn't think anything was suspicious about that,
but it was in a strange place, and Chiara fell into it
twice and died, so I got
really angry and wondered who made this Anna,
and the
winner was there too.  I
did my best to look into it, but I've
asked all the members of Hololive Image and found that no
one has made this version, so I'm
seriously wondering who made this.
Stop it, it's
hard.
Since Tiara-chan didn't go forward, I
thought I couldn't let this go. It's because I
know my seniors very well.
[Music]
This is the
new member's house.
Pekona, where we all live together, used to
be like that, but lately I've been feeling a little...  It looks like they're building a house or something. It's
amazing. The helmet on their head
is all messed up, but I'm wondering if they'll sleep at least once. Did you
see the new members? Did you
see the house? I'm curious.
I thought everyone was cute, but
Pecola-san said a little while ago that
Hacos-chan, that rat-mouse, that squirrel-chan
from ID, and Pecola and Hakushon,
and that something like that was a pean or
something, and I
thought it was interesting.  I'm a little
worried about it. It seems like you're saying, "Hey, hey, hey."
Hey, Eclat-senpai. Yes, I
want to join that group, okay. Yes, I want
to join, okay. No, I don't know what's going to happen.
But everything is fine.
Pekoira is getting a little better at English,
so I think I'd like to try communicating with him.Well then,
Holtori is really fun too.Follow
Lauren, that Pekoa-senpai,
I'd
love to get to know him and study English with him.  However, I have
n't been able to do it very well, so I
'd like to try my best at this, but here's the Minecraft Anand that Chiara and
Chiara's real mother made together.  Has your
mom been appearing lately? Or is it about the
way you fly? Oh yeah, my
mom was also on the broadcast for the one-year anniversary,
but my real mom
Mike is an addict, so my
mom has been helping out a lot lately.
Well, this
is Iris's house. There are
so many amazing flowers blooming here. It's so
cute, Esprecure.
PreCure Saul Spy's
friends are normal too.Everyone is
watching
me.Why do you
keep this thing here?
What the heck, it just appeared recently and I
don't know who remembered it.It's nickname is
Fukipuu.It's a prank by Furi-chan.  That
ice cream girl who has Santa Claus everywhere
is famous for hating Santa Claus.She's a
killer peko, so she plays
Wide Sheets and
Wide Ceiling Games.
It's scary because it's something you don't like. Oh, I see. And I didn't have that in my whole life, so I guess it's a
memory from when I was little.
Someday, I talked to Iris. If you
have a chance, please try playing around with Santa Claus.  It's
like speaking.This is the
new member of the 2nd generation recently.It looks
like they made it in Japanese.So,
how many people are there?
Well, let me tell you something interesting. It may not be particularly interesting, but the two names are Sana-chan and Sona-chan, but if you combine the names of Sara-chan and Former in the announcement, it becomes a sauna. Ah, it's really boring. I don't like it.
That's why I like this.  These two are making the rods.
Who is this? Who
is Pico? Did you make this? What's next to it?
Is this a cat you don't want? It looks like this furnace.
The two of us made it. That's right
. That's right. It's a
nice sauna. It's just the
two
of us. I'm sorry. The difference is really small, but it's just a little bit more. Just a little more. This is my
forward pride. My
pride.  I'm going to show you what I'm most proud of. Please
get up from here.
Let's GO.
Senpai, you haven't won yet, so run away.
Maybe you two can run away.  It's
okay to ride with two people.
It's the worst thing to do with two people.
[Laughs]
This cat has been tested. This is the
boat. There's
nothing there. There
was a Pico where the door didn't work, but
wait a minute, it's okay here.  I
worked hard to make it, and I
rode along with it.It's
amazing, it's a little short, but it has a bit of
history, but when I
first
went out to play, I
passed by this waste, so I rode
in a tortoise.
All the people in the village died.I
felt sorry for them, so I made a plan to rebuild it.That's what
Ina-chan, Chiara-chan,
Gari-chan, and I first walked
through this village in the early days.  When I
passed by, some kind of enemy came and all of them
died. That villager was
really dead, Ekari-chan,
so I guess that's it
. I'm so
sorry,
Chiara.  I
want to get back on my feet and get back on my feet,
so I'm a phoenix, so
I'll do my best to assist you quietly Shift
Shift Shift If no
one explains this too much, I'll die That's where I often
die
From various things
How many from 0 Without villagers
From 0  I've
gotten back on my feet, but lately, since I've
become a mother, there
are a lot of people in the village, and I'm having a hard time getting into them,
but now I'm in the
process of redoing all of those random photos.  When I
looked at the houses and things like that, I saw that my
mom and I have been building them recently.We're building them
for the villagers who can really use them,
so we're going to
get rid of everything else.The
plan is to
make everyone's houses look like this.
So if you go over to that side, you'll see those
big pores made by pores.I
made them recently, so I'm sorry, Tial-chan.You
can ask me once.Here you go.I'm a
villager, so why are these growing like this?  It's a
mess. The people who are trying to enslave you are probably not trying to make you into slaves. That's not what you meant here, and there should only be alpacas. However, it turns out that they aren't trying to make something dangerous.
I want it, right here, here, here,
here,
Kirara is
doing her best to build that amazing village, just like Pecola-senpai, and
Pepper-senpai, that amazing person.  It
can only be used without blocks.It
's not like that.It's not that kind of thing.It's not that kind of thing.It's not that kind of thing.It's not that kind of thing.It's not that kind of thing.It's not that kind of thing.It's not that kind of thing.It's not that kind of thing.It's not that kind of thing.It's not that kind of thing.It's not that kind of thing.  I
thought that was too cruel.It
means it's not a reset.It's about the president.
Well, I tried to make it fun,
but I'm still making this so far, I'm
still making it, and this is still
in the middle of this, but I've been trying to make it look even more beautiful lately,
so there's
a lot of things going on here.  Megumi, the
one person that Tiara has worked so hard to raise,
for example this person, whose
name I can see, Eric
Jer
Click
[music],
and many other people who are very important to me.
There are a lot of them, and
I'm proud of them.
All the diamond equipment and stuff are taken from here.
Only the talented people are named. Pekko. What
's that? That's right,
where are you? Are there any seniors there?
Are you pyoko pyoko dakocchi?
[Music]
Hey.  If you go a little further, you'll
see this place too.The most famous person here is the one called Tetsu-no.I want to show you the enemy who came in somewhere with boss Face.
Well, for now, this is
Dust from the character. He
wants to keep a pet, or something.
This means that all the villagers probably haven't been
able to sleep. Well, there
have been too many of them recently, so it's just a bit too much. I
'll clean up the
humans next time.  Clean up.
Don't you have to say that in a shocking voice
? No, you can't clean up people. You're
doing such a scary thing.
[Applause] You're
acting like that angel.  Are
you saying that you wouldn't do such a terrible thing
?
Yes, Peco Rise Angel,
please come out.The
last thing I'll show you is the
carnival that Kani-chan recently started making, to welcome the second season of this house.  It's
been about 12 hours, but I haven't finished making it yet.For
example, here, you can
have a
fortune teller.How do you use a
fortune teller?Don't just push the handle here and there.Here, go ahead.  It
says, ``Oh, I'm here.'' So what did you write? The Sharif Bless You And Sharif
Sheriff Cherie Sheriff How do you say this in Japanese? A
person named Lee. A person called Hallory from Texas. What does that
mean?
Texas
[Music]  ]
said to you, ``It's a
good thing that you won't get arrested.'' The
main building bless you, and
it doesn't mean that the police will take care of you.  That's
right, the handwriting is different. Ah, that's
okay. I think it can't be helped if it was Pecola-senpai,
but
yeah, it
's still a good thing. It's
not care. I
received something that was made for people who absolutely hate it.
English
English puns.  The
words ``atte'' and ``e'' are wonderful in Japanese, and the
English language is excellent.
It's like this, it's excellent, that's right, that's right, you know what an egg is?The pores of the egg are like those of a chicken.They're immortal, but eggs are nothing.They make puns like that, and they eat fire a lot.That's it.It's supposed to have a lot in it, but this.  That's interesting. This place isn't finished yet. It
's a Ferris wheel, but it's still
being built. This place is
cute
. It's nice. It's still a work in progress. We're here to collect horses and pigs.
It's P. I'm on a business trip. I'm
having dinner here. I wonder if there's something here that shoots arrows. It's
like someone could easily come in and fall without seeing the video.
Maybe it
hasn't moved yet.  I do
n't think it's running I think it's probably Mr. S. It's something you
often see on game shows. I was here
and typed it and it went bang.
Try it. It's scary
. Wow, that's so cool.
Please don't die, Bekula-senpai. You can
sleep. This
is an interesting place, but it
seems like something here wants to explode.
But it's okay.
Please put your own things here. Maybe
they haven't yet.
[Music]
There's a place to hit one more thing.
Nothing happens anymore. That's
not it. Maybe it's in the
middle. It's okay, it's not in the middle. It's good. It's
really good. This kind of stuff gives it a bit of a festival
feel.  I
guess Kari-chan
saw the festival at the Japanese Saba and said, ``We want to make one too.'' Well, that's great, because it's
really amazing. I'm going to
say it here. I guess we'll
close it soon.
Our Saba will be connected soon.  Right now,
Pecola-senpai, I
want you to lend me your strength. Please
make EM mackerel even more beautiful. I
want you to call Pecola Pekola Dish Construction. I
like it, and I want to make something with the sabali.  I feel like
that's true. I don't know if it's pretty
or
not. [Music] At the end, everyone is asking me to show Kuro-chan's house. Where's the glass camp irondad? Coordination ah, ah, but I'm
sorry, I forgot something a little bit.
Yes, I see. I can't fly. Senpai.
I see. Sorry, I'd like about 15 more minutes.
[Music] I
started using it 9 months ago.  Even though we
were just walking, things
have changed, right?
Well, well, well, well, this
place is Gura-chan's winner, and Kuwa-chan's other one. Well, it hasn't finished yet, but at the finish line, it feels like a sacred place.  It's terupeko It's
like a temple Yeah, it
's a temple
Awesome
&conder
What's that? When are you going
to say it in Japanese
? It's the one that can breathe. That's right. That's
right. 1
Please come in with me.
Um, he
came to our side a few times a while ago, but for
some reason he didn't come anymore, so the last one
was this Togo, so I made a heart tower and
jumped off.  That
's when it ended, and I was thinking in my head that this thing might be destroyed.I
see, even if I said that and jumped off, I still wonder if it will come back.It's definitely true, it's definitely
going to come back, right?
Well, it's
amazing. It's a shrine built by my favorite girl. It's
nice. Aira-chan set off Happy's fireworks here. It's really, really beautiful. If you look at it at night, it'll be crazy. It's
beautiful, so it's
here.  If I could just show you
Kura-chan's
Trident, I'm sure it's the place where you collect the Trident. It's something that
's also that wide. It's
amazing. It's okay to tell me the amazing things. I do
n't need it. It's
a lie.
chan has a trident as a weapon,
so it's only natural that he would get a trident in Minecraft, right?
However, even though he chased that trident over and over again, he
couldn't get it, so he got the
trident.  You built a farm, and
then you realized that it was really El Pico.
Even though it seemed like you could get it, it still took hours and hours and
hours, and it
was really hard.
[Music]  When I
went out to play somewhere, I was attacked by an enemy, and when I
defeated just one enemy, I
posted something that made them hate me.I was lucky, but when I tried, I
ended up broadcasting the video for a different purpose.  I
thought Triant RTA was fine, so I gave it the
title and gave it the same
name. That's terrible. When I tried Trident for the first time, it
took me 13 hours.  It
was really fun. I've spent hours on it. I
've turned him into an enemy, so now I ca
n't do that. That never happened. I can't use it there
.
By the way, that ending on that staircase of ours.  It
's the
road to the Endo portal.
Eh, yeah, follow that on Twitter for a
while.
Eh, if you follow that path, you'll reach the end. Eh, that's
right. End portal. End portal.
Rain Sky Temple This is the Sky Temple made by Ame-chan. It's
amazing. If you do the subway, you can also do the sky. Is it a
pico?
Well, there are some
smaller ones here and there, but I
think this area is probably good. By the way, here's
something.  I wonder if you could change it
for me Pecola-senpai It's
nothing, huh?
Impressions
Wait a minute, make it, make it, add it
Press But it's
amazing
[Music] You
can write it What if that
mackerel connects from here?
Eh, can you make something for me?
What do you want to make first
?I don't know what to make, but it's too peaceful.Shadow
server.It
's so beautiful and has so many cute buildings.I'm
flat, but isn't it a little too peaceful?Isn't it a
classic?I don't like peace.  It's a rabbit. Yes,
Simon.
There might be natural things like screaming or splashing or falling into a hole or something like that,
but it's a bit too peaceful, so I wonder if it'll
cause fear. I
'm scared.
As expected, I made a good idea for that Pecola-senpai,
but Pecola-senpai
is not allowed on this server
[Music] I'm looking
forward to seeing your senior do well. That means you should be
active, Kirara-chan.
Still, I
received it, so
please
mix up the characters.  I'd like that.
Ok, so what if something Peccola created
turns someone into a boner,
and it's all Chiara-chan's fault?
No, I don't think they'll have a separate ownership.
Thank you in advance. Where should I play? I wonder
if it's
above.
Where should I play?
For now, I'll leave
my impressions
here.
[Laughs]
Just here, not over there. Eh, that's
fine. Eh, Poi.  Monobashi
[Music]
[Music] I don't know
what to do about my
waist or
something.
What do you say in English?
Today
[Music]
[Music] Shall we
do this?
Even if you say that in such a cute voice, I
'm not scared at all. I'll
make your screams echo through the cat's en server.  That's why I've
been waiting for you.
[Music]
Here's the pun I told you earlier. You
should've run. Xent's egg. Do you want to learn English? And that's a Pyoko that can be used. It's
not just here. It's a Pyoko. If you can
use it.  It's
funny,
no, it's
scary, right
?
[Music] I don't know what to do.
But I can't say I'm looking forward to it, jp.
But it's connected. Pig-chan's shooting fireworks in vain. It's
not Peko.
Well,
Peko-ya-senpai, I'm looking forward to getting out of here.
Please feel free to visit Potara anytime.Prince Kamueni
Time 2
Create
By the way, if you come here, I think you can probably bring some materials from that Japanese mackerel,
but if something happens.  There are
n't many if there are, but everything here is
free to use.
Thank you,
nice 19. It's okay for Ina-chan's rules, too. It's
okay to take all the iron things of the test. I don't
need any help here, right? That's
right.  People are being killed.
No, I don't like them. It's a sad sacrifice,
but it can't be helped.
[Music]
-
Chan:
Yes, it's because we have Peko at home. That's right.
Thank you so much for allowing me to use it without losing it. It was
fun. The
next collaboration will be in 9 months. The
last photo like this will be in a double spot.
The two of us will take a picture at Pecola-senpai's house late at night.
What a miracle!  House
[Music]
Night I'll be
living in Nami, so I hope we can get along well. I wonder
if I'll do something all of a sudden.
[Music]
OK, it's okay, thank you
[Music] Bye [Music
]
Bye
[Music]