[Music]
[Applause]
oh yeah ready oh it started it started i
started i started
hmm
hello
hey
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh no um yeah when we entered the vr
universe our bodies uh
they warped into these special forms
yeah something happened and we were just
warmed into these forms
look at this cronie staring right
straight in my eyes oh no
what i'm perfect
oh yeah you were too perfect for this
world introductions are in order yeah
okay
[Music]
who starts
you me
oh okay um
hi
it's
iris i don't think you guys can see how
i look in my perspective so
yeah check out the other perspectives to
see what i'm uh what i have turned into
uh in the vr world um
yes
everyone's just so cute and just sad i'm
being aware of and crawling and cronies
just like i want to disappear from this
world sort of pose except never mind no
she's looking at us now
excuse me
you're staring at the wall
so i'm just sorry when she pulls up
i know it's like domination she's not
even t posing and it feels like she's
t-posing
very nice
anyways yep next
yep go around
[Music]
the council's keeper of nature
i came to this costume party i got all
dressed up you can't see if you're
watching my stream but
um the elevator broke and we're stuck
here so
all you can do is stare into the vortex
of time endlessly i suppose
also has a long neck
long neck
your eyes are still shining brightly
wait wait why are you guys looking at me
it's your turn it's my turn
oh my god oh wait oh oh okay hi
oh i feel put on spotlight hi i'm oral
cronie i'm the warden of time and right
now i don't have my body because
this world couldn't contain me and
only part of it arrived but you know
what that's okay
because
that means i i'm ahead of this game
yeah yeah yeah
i don't know
i don't think wayne why are you standing
on top of some broken cogs what's
happening
wait oh so
is this
the reason the elevator is broken
yeah yeah
is that something you'd like to tell us
explain yourself it wasn't really
it wasn't really my fault that the
elevator attendant was rushing us all in
and
i did get a little annoyed
so you annoy the back
[Music]
don't worry about it just don't worry
about it just don't worry you don't know
his name yeah i really don't know wait
wait what was that someone's name like
what
oh paulina karen is
like you know those i would like to
speak to a manager
oh
would you like a kiss
come here
[Laughter]
who's next
[Music]
the guardian of civilization but i died
and everybody screwed now
everybody screwed no no what about the
elevator this is part of civilization
too
there are a lot of screws in here but um
yeah
that's true yeah that's great yeah yeah
good luck everybody i'm in my retirement
oh retirement faces
how's it going i'm glad you're not
part of a
oh
oh the ghost died
there's nothing in here
[Applause]
becoming a predator i see it remember
the beat okay
you want to give cpr hello
it's me
i'm a solo worm cute cute cute worm
cute
like a delicious gummy worm
oh is it gonna eat her up oh oh oh come
here
[Applause]
how does that taste how
[Laughter]
yeah that means you're sweet you're
sudden i hope you're she's not the sweet
and sour gummy worm i know those exist
it's just a complicated i like the sour
ones yeah i do like the sour cream
what are you talking about i do like
them too they just make me look
like i'm dying
it was a little time consuming all right
tickles
[Laughter]
did you
[Music]
have you got the you've got the lump
lump
not lumps
oh what's going on over here oh yes oh
okay
we're seeing a nice present
oh
no
i'm just thinking
hey
oh no hey guys it's a mistletoe uh
needs to introduce herself yes
introduce yourself yes babe that's what
i wanted to stand reginald what's up
what's up representing
chaos from council um i don't know what
happened to my model um i was reduced to
primitive form
well i'm inside your head this is crazy
this actually looks oh my gosh
that was that was a wild ride i'll never
forget
are you able to look into our minds when
you go inside of us
oh let me see
what what sort of mind do i have
why are your hands inside of your body i
have no idea there's a rats in here oh i
see your tongue that's kind of i see
this
no that's probably my nose
you see what i only see cronies
[Music]
okay i don't know what's happening
anymore we're we are
we are combining into
one
one extreme existence powerful being
powerful being yes
yeah
my nose is in the way yeah
really
i literally
[Music]
your modesty your modesty my body what
am i lying down
oh we all died
what is santa crawling for oh
yes you die we're all dead
[Music]
oh
what's going on
the flashing
[Laughter]
why are you in that position stand
properly it's kind of like i am standing
right
this is
[Music]
oh
destroy these monsters
[Music]
that makes sense
yeah it should be i think it's just a
problem at my end i think it's just
my
[Applause]
[Music]
now
is
[Music]
no
oh
[Music]
your claws
can you pet me too
can you tell me
oh i'm sorry i'm sorry
i wanted to get a good shot hold on i
gotta watch something really quick i
just gotta check something you guys do
whatever
we're gonna go check
i really
oh
you're just as small right almost
professionally oh
[Music]
very nice just like you in the real
world give me that little button though
button
i only give my second button
oh wait actually no you can have my
second button all right well that's fine
i can just tear it out of here
though why is there so much blood on it
senpai
oh just because i'm uh i've been busy
recently you know just um getting to
work do you want to date hiatus
no no what i'm doing is is work for good
i'm saving lives oh you know oh savings
i'm
[Music]
i'm not very good at it though which
might be why the survival rate is a
little low but that'll change something
survival oh no
no you can imagine if she's gonna lose
her job soon yeah okay
well who is this
professor are you professor professor or
iris in the in the microwave i don't
know if i'll survive that fridge fridge
hope rachel
i mean i'm not fridge hopefully my
microwave oh yeah
jelly hole jelly
i don't know
i'm made of jelly hole fluff
oh yeah hello hello oh you're almost
you're good
all right oh hello hello
dinosaur
hi oh you're so cute
look who's talking oh
you're coming oh
oh my god
yeah who would think i would see a mad
scientist
and the cutest dinosaurs both the cutest
things in the world in one screen
oh my god yes oh no it's head is is
twisting off
oh no don't worry about it don't worry
about it as expected in the mindset you
can't
control the weight
you can't support the body it's also
messing up
[Music]
[Applause]
ah
um
[Music]
just looking at herself oh look at those
eyes and those eyelashes
okay
i'm ready
oh gosh that's perfect perfect it is
perfect
it's perfect your head with my body is
flawless yeah there's nothing else you
can change about it we're unstoppable
i'm ready
[Music]
all right so this is uh pretty much like
our terminal here at the time
headquarters as you guys know cronie
over there is the head of the branch as
you can tell
um so these are our time terminals which
uh um is the whole bunch of amis run
them and uh recently we did have a
zombie outbreak a zombie army outbreak
so we had to close off this section here
but um nothing we can uh unclog that
soon yeah so zom zombie on it
and uh we also have a few different uh
reception desks here we do have a small
one like usually i would be here and uh
i would help you guys uh you know if you
had
issues you know if you guys wanted to
know what timeline to go to i could help
you with that uh today we will be
traveling to another timeline and as you
guys know council came from another
timeline which was in another dimension
and you guys got all messed up in the
elevator somehow
it has been having some issues so
the elevator door did not open up here
we have concierge as well which is
currently closed as it is a holiday
do not press the second button we'll be
using that later and over here okay
okay you're welcome to help
oh no don't press it the world's gonna
end if
[Music]
give me that lollipop
okay
[Music]
this lobby uh has a lot of timelines
attached but we do have portals
specifically for all of the small
members here
uh
[Laughter]
why don't you try it oh what try what
okay what there's no candy you ate all
the flavors
yeah let's run
[Applause]
[Music]
oh no she on the site
we're very close to you right now yeah
we're very very close
[Music]
so large and
beautiful like the moon yeah your eyes
shine like the stars
i see your right eye
i see
heaven when i look into your eyes
is that a good experience i fell
you fell
i fell i fell from this world oh
if you guys go too far from here you
fall out from this world who wants to
join me i want to try it i want to try
when you fail okay follow me
come on camera yeah let's go further
i'll give you there you go
[Music]
oh we're here
we have oh we have we died
[Applause]
this is my third actually oh yeah you
died one tourney
over to the next area now let's go over
to the next portal to the next house
where's my syringe again
[Music]
i'm
this umbrella is huge huh um
[Music]
i can't get
take a picture
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you
oh
[Music]
we have some pumpkins for decoration and
this is like the main town plaza is
really nice kind of reminds me of like
animal crossing do something it's really
cute it's my first time in australia
as
much as you want you can take them
trick or treat
you guys take whatever you like we're
not gonna be moving over to the next
portal
[Music]
oh
oh we're under the sea
we're under the sand up there there's
the sun is that candy oh yeah there's
candy
[Music]
oh no i have bad memories of that
trident wait uh
oh you guys have bad memories
can we get something
strawberry jelly filled straws
[Music]
is gonna hurt my
my
really pointy object from a different
dimension
i think
[Music]
uh
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh no oh no she's being stabbed oh no
the strawberry jelly is gonna
[Music]
ruins of atlantis which we could go back
in time and bring atlantis back and it's
full glory if you guys would like to see
that at another time but today this is
the timeline that we are in
it's quite beautiful here under the
water yeah under the sea how deep would
you say we are good at how how many uh
like meters are we down below the
surface
i don't know how many eiffel towers that
is oh the worm has all the candy uh four
i don't know
[Music]
[Laughter]
she's
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
feeling a little intimidated right now
uh
[Music]
oh there's a cookie i'm gonna sit
oh my
it's perfect oh it's so cute
oh wait there's works of art
there's a paintbrush
iris yes
[Music]
you're
i'm a multi-tasker
[Music]
okay
she's stuck
i'm not sure what that one doesn't know
oh
is
[Music]
it's for you
grape juice
[Music]
just to tell you guys about this area i
believe this is inna's retreat uh a
cabin in the woods with inna's
lab also here nice relaxing tea area as
well as some nice open windows with a
bookshelf and of course some painting
equipment as you guys can see up here
these are canvases
painted are actually from her first uh
how do you say the game pass apart out i
don't know how to say it properly
oh
[Music]
oh there's even a pumpkin dodgy
[Applause]
[Music]
all right everybody we're now gonna go
over to
[Music]
oh
she
[Music]
eating candy this camera is
oh there's a blue there's a blue oh this
is a what's in concoction
where's kiara i think
oh she's over there she's trying to fix
them oh yeah so uh this is uh
some small i want a taste of this yeah
yeah here yeah can you open your mouth
i've already been stabbed a bit too much
why i'm not maybe no no no
you can we can you know
[Music]
[Laughter]
i didn't know that this was a deadly
concoction it was an accident
she looks so happy though look at that
smile
she looks satisfied
she looks very central that
[Laughter]
concoction of life
oh i'm sorry
she likes her position right now she
really likes to be dead we're gonna take
a break and sit down in a little bit
when we go to the next area
oh yeah
okay
just tell you guys a little bit about
this area this is where some small
almonds come to rest whether it's uh due
to
time or crimes uh it's a bit of a prison
it's a bit of a resting place it's a bit
of a good thing for each of them
[Music]
all right
just go straight yeah i want to be i
feel like i'm faster when i jump
everybody's here and stop stop stop
stop
okay this time
attention everybody we will now begin
the second portion of the field trip as
today is halloween so we have some
spooky activities planned and we're now
going to go into the spooky halloween
timeline
all right so if you guys would please
press the second button here the instant
teleport button let's go instantly oh my
god
[Music]
welcome to explore this area
i couldn't make it i couldn't make it
yagu's dream was too much
do you like too much
iris is in here
you're giving up too quickly
i'm dead
yes
[Music]
while we're in jaguar's dream you wanna
give me a kiss
dream yeah
that's true right
i'm gonna kiss your eye your eyes
[Applause]
oh
horrible
[Music]
of this area let's start over here
you're first
um i actually believe this might be what
caused
your guys's
um
of sorts
uh there's been some
messing around going on here oh but this
looks like an evil ritual for each
council remember there's the time oh
maybe
that sounds tasty yeah the little sample
excuse me
a dinosaur's doing something
the trees are dead though it's true the
trees are dead over here
let's see
[Music]
oh is it is it hibernation time is this
a mouse
i'm sleeping peacefully
rest in peace
oh no wait there's no there's no humans
on the floor
[Music]
maybe cutting
half or something i don't know
that's a great idea i like that get over
here
[Music]
i'm
this is like the settings
[Music]
an ice cream sand noise
sure you betcha
here we go all right ice cream bag
here we go um
[Music]
what do you think hello
um
hold on hold on hang on a second you're
dancing um
what tune is really popular for
uh ice cream trucks
[Music]
people that have ice cream or sweets in
their hands
[Laughter]
what's going on over here each other
[Music]
dead beats oh no but dead beats has a
huge grave and we also have
the great yellow pumpkin
oh no ouija board i've never played this
before and i know i want to keep it that
way the ouija board
you're welcome to take a seat we do have
chairs scattered all around this area
i'll take a look though
does anybody have the planche and we
also have this music
now
[Music]
[Applause]
has nothing to do with
this spirits if you're here
give us the sky
nothing
who do you like and what from the mario
franchise huh who's your favorite let's
go this way
oh you don't even have a favorite i see
i see how it is
can you say that oh shut up
shy
shy guys
are way too shy for my taste
i like the ghost whisperer and you're
just
you're into the underdogs
what's wrong with them all take a seat
he lives in mario's shadow no luigi has
his own reputation he has his own
franchises
he lives
in luigi
stands for losers
i'm gonna cover my ears no no no no no
no no no no no no oh
[Laughter]
please take a seat in the couch or one
of the cheers
[Music]
yes the best
in between
you know
[Music]
yeah we'll survive right i mean look at
our forms right now
we're not human yeah i mean i'm dead
oh babe what's up oh are you bowing down
to me finally have you finally learned
your position in our relationship
oh thank you i appreciate the respect i
feel utterly respect right now right now
mm-hmm yes how do you slap in this game
[Music]
branch is a part of you it looks real
strange
yes it grew right out of my skull
and i like you oh
water
confession time magnifying glass we are
watching news but it's in the other map
cronies watching owenie's watching
she has big eyes is there a problem
cronies
funny
[Music]
okay why are you suddenly complimenting
me
because i like you too
could you guys see it i mean we're going
to have a go sorry who wouldn't like me
oh
who did it who did it
what are you what are you huh
what what do you what are you doing
yeah
okay
[Music]
you can stand if you like especially
since chairs don't really work
there's a chair here a chair oh i'll sit
here then
yeah you can sit down
all right i'm in the middle of your
relationship too
yeah i could say um
is so wide that it's just like cutting
in between everyone
why not lied fauna
do you fight with your neck like other
giraffes
[Music]
a neck grab
she oh you grab by the stand because you
have no neck yeah she has no knife
everybody's her head is everything about
it well at least i don't have
whatever you have right now
oh no what cronies crony's clock is is
like grinding into me oh no a buck tooth
by the way
i'm being sliced into pieces right now
i'm not gonna say korean
yeah
oh
all right um okay everybody welcome to
the spooky spooky timeline as you can
see we have a big yago here and we could
uh actually this report is used to talk
to the great spirit of yago but
unfortunately it seems like we've
misplaced the little planchette i
believe it's called uh so it's not here
but
i thought instead of talking to the
spirits we could tell some ghost stories
do you guys know any ghost stories
anybody
i know
oh you do move me yeah she's a ghost she
wouldn't know some stories
that's true
have you ever seen a ghost before
yeah do you want to hear the story
yeah i want to hear yes
okay once i was driving down a winding
dark road and i saw a lady and she had
no face
so i hit her and she turned into a ghost
she had no what's the what's the point
that she had her
she had no face
no i'm curious about why she had no face
did you kill me
sometimes in the dark like faces
disappear yeah
oh
no i i i
i was also in the car i wasn't driving
enough because i can't reach the pedals
uh and uh i think it was with my mom we
were coming home from somewhere it was
really really dark and then all of a
sudden across the road there was this
like mist
of some sort that had no beginning and
end it was just in the center of the
road and we drove right through it and
we try really hard
to will you ever see something and it it
takes you by such surprise that it
leaves you speechless for a little while
oh yes yeah like that's what happened it
was it was it was kind of genuine fear
for a second uh but we're trying to
think of what it could have been and
there's no way it could have been
smoke right because smoke
doesn't you would have seen it fizzle or
how would it have traveled out into the
road like that without any
well how would it have lived that long
you know but it was really scary and i
don't know how to explain it funny
explain what it could have been
[Music]
yeah at least you guys were in the car
so you guys are in the safety of your
car
i look
like us like a kind of spooky story but
it's like from a thing it's like a book
i'm not going to read it but like i can
recount it to you
yeah yeah tell us about it
you get in trouble
i think it's okay just behind change the
details yeah okay gotcha
so basically here's how it goes
all right
here's how are you okay kiara
i looked at the chat for one second i
just had some luck
oh it was a mistake
all right
so
there's this girl right
and she's at a gas station
she's filling up the gas in her car it's
just a normal day getting off of work
you know
the usual
and then she decides it's time to go
home as any other sane human would you
go to work you go to home just a typical
day
right
so she finishes getting the guests
settles down in her little seat
gets ready to drive away yeah i hear it
too gets ready to drive away boys that
uh
i don't know
i hear it coming from your area that's
fixed she gets left she takes a little
station story
[Laughter]
[Music]
down the down a dark and musty and
spooky road and she's on like a
countryside roads there's no one around
until she realizes that she's being
followed stop oh my god no way
someone is following no way someone is
following
yeah that's right there's a car that's
hot on her tail and it's been following
her in fact for a while she realizes
that it's been following her
ever since the gas station
oh
not from the gas station this
car yeah that's right if you remember
the gas station there was a dude and you
followed
you caught a vision in your head now
there's another car there's one car here
there's a car here and they're going
down the road and it's dark outside and
then the car behind her this innocent
victim starts flashing his lights flash
flash flash over and over again over and
over again the body motions her flash
what what could it mean
what could it mean
she doesn't know but she's starting to
get real scared
she's got
another 30 minutes left to drive all the
way home so she keeps driving oh that's
realistic the dude just keeps flashing
the lights flash flash flash
she gets very scared and decides i need
to call the police i need to call them
so they'll be ready when i get to my
house this dude's going to kill me he's
going to jump out of his car and then
and then hold on i got i got my effect
my special effect he's going to come out
of the car
and and stabby stabs
she had a stabby step
no i'm too scared of that happening all
right she's scared of them with a
chainsaw yeah
so did you just beep at him with the car
like you know beep
and so she keeps going and he keeps
flashing eventually she gets home she
runs out of her car the police are there
they all pull up and she runs out of her
car and the guy pulls up in his car
and he comes out and he's just a normal
dude
and he says ma'am are you okay she says
what are you talking about
my man says
there's a dude in the backseat of your
car getting ready to stab you and every
time he was about to stab you i flashed
the light
and then they caught the guy in the back
of the car oh
so it was just a warning
why didn't he just unroll the windows
and scream at her that there was someone
behind her trying to stab her
did they kill him and turn him into a
ghost
thank you callie that was wonderful
[Music]
i guess it's a true story it's about
living in space australia or australia
bank yeah if you have any sort of scary
bug stories
oh okay i mean that counts you're scared
yeah okay
[Music]
about bugs
counters
[Music]
i don't know i have something
i was thinking you would have swimming
as well anyway oh i did but they're not
like scary i mean they're scary but it
looks like this is
um you accidentally you accidentally
step on the floor and you accidentally
step on a center feed or a slug or like
like a furry spider like a furry spider
was once in my bed
[Music]
and then i was just staring at the
ground and then suddenly out of nowhere
a huge like black light up just crawl
under my bed and then
i didn't do anything you didn't do
anything you just left it there behind
it
this is scary you never found it oh
it disappeared
you know what it went inside your ears
sometimes when bugs funny they disappear
inside of you now it's inside of you
watch your mouth when you sleep but does
everybody gonna throw up the spider
because it's inside you there's no other
way to get it out you're gonna have to
isn't that statistics that like um you
swallowed like 20 sliders in your
lifetime when you oh yeah they do say
that yes
i don't i do know that we probably
definitely swallow
[Music]
yeah i'm only showing five percent does
anybody else notice that coney has fans
i do
oh
sorry
some
juicy meat
um
[Music]
oh
what was i'm oh where are you where are
you taking it
were you taking it the wrong way oh okay
work i was um
i was living in japan until a while ago
and um
i i moved after after joining whole life
uh uh i moved in to a big big house
but the house was
very very
uh old it was that when you walked on
the wood it would make sounds like
wait wait
wait
right
oh yeah
so it was really really old and it had a
lot of
it had a lot of uh issues to it but well
it was a big two-story house all to
myself so it was like i'm just gonna try
my best to ignore that it's the looking
really old so
the first night
arrives and i'm i'm like yeah i got this
whole house to myself and i was trying
to chill but i was hearing noises
from the ceiling
[Laughter]
[Music]
i immediately contacted
my my landlord and he was like yeah
there
there might be some history of ghosts in
this house but please don't worry about
it we'll send you some ghost
exterminators
now
a few days later
and the ghostbusters came by and all
those days i i heard the ghosts like
continuously not only in the night but
also during the day and was kind of
freaking me out because i was also
trying to stream but it was i was
hearing it on the first floor and on the
second floor and on the in the side of
the walls and in the bottom and at the
top everywhere so
uh the ghost extremely is they came and
they looked into the ceiling and they
they saw the ghosts they saw the ghosts
and they said that it's like so it
wasn't like about
animals three ghosts three ghosts
no no no
and they actually have ghost poison with
them
and they put the cast that's right girl
they got the ghost poison and they put
that the they put the ghost poison in
the ceiling and then they closed it and
they they were like okay kiara you call
us and tell us call the ghostbusters and
tell us how the poison worked
and then a few days later i did start
hearing less
but it was still
a little bit a little bit
so i called again and i was like yo
ghostbusters i'm calling you because who
who else would i call
right girls so they say oh
they said they were gonna come back and
they opened the ceiling again and they
looked inside and they found the ghost
of two ghosts
those two ghosts of the ghosts where um
the parent ghosts of the ghosts that
survived
and it was weird because they added they
kept on trying to add poison for the
last surviving ghost but it seems like
that ghost has started to form some kind
of immunity
oh
we tried many times but it didn't didn't
work and then one time for example i was
sick
with the door open because i had it was
like such a tiny idol meeting room that
it's like almost impossible to close the
door and i saw the ghost myself with my
own eyes
and it made itself known to you
like ate your food once yes
that's horrific
i don't know if you've heard of it but
ghosts are apparently um uh
not they don't like eating chocolate
because they will kill them
they're allergic to chocolate
but let me guess the ghost ate the
chocolate of course the ghost
won't be able to eat chocolate survived
so the whole survived chocolate and and
poison and all that
so in the end i started to accept the
fact that i'm living with a ghost and
actually we're best friends now and the
ghost name is casper
[Music]
remember too but it wasn't a ghost story
hold on uh
sorry
[Music]
she's collapsing in on herself
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
it might help um purge the ghost if you
want to play on desktop that's okay too
because i know you're feeling a little
sick so if you want i will reinvent you
okay if you're feeling too sick
okay okay all right
good for you it should be really easy
just get comfy yeah
you need to purchase this
from her
sit down relax
hey you can hug follow
will come back right she'll come back
she'll be
[Music]
why are you pretending
oh
[Music]
yeah she can totally hear us
she's all alone
[Music]
my
i'm assuming she's talking about me
obviously i'm just wanting to make sure
that crony's floating head is just
possessed by existence
why is everyone getting possessed
[Music]
yes
i can tell you guys it's not a spooky
story but it's uh it's terrifying in its
own way
all right cool thank yous yeah um all
right so here's the story have you guys
heard the story yeah the crunch bird
what my grandfather told me the story of
the crunch bird long ago yeah i remember
it was an old story my grandfather told
me i know it sounds like that right like
kfc right exactly like you can imagine a
big scary phoenix
yeah so basically
the crunch bird my grandfather told me
this story it's been passed down in
reaper legends for generations so
basically there's this couple and they
decide that they want to have a pet
right they decide it's finally time to
get themselves um a pet of their own
because you know they've been living
alone can't have kids that kind of thing
so uh so they've decided okay we're
gonna go you know off to the pet shop so
the husband's really busy he's working
and so he tells his wife go ahead and
get us a pet he doesn't care what it is
he says whatever is fine right so the
wife goes to the pet store and uh is
kind of talking with the pet clerk and
she's like i wonder what would be good
you know a dog a cat hamster all very
cute but
hear me out how about a bird and so the
shop clerk says all right i got some
birds i'll show you some birds takes her
to the back starts showing her the birds
and she's like oh these are all very
fine birds but what's that one in the
back there's this big cage in the back
it's got this huge foul beast of a
creature inside of it he says that's the
crunch bird that thing's way too
dangerous yeah crunch bird is what it's
called you can call it whatever you want
but i call it the crunch bird and she
says well why do you call it the crunch
bird he's like do you really want to
know she says yeah i really want to know
he's like do you really want to know
she's like yeah i really want to know
show me the bird really really no
exactly
and so
he takes he takes the bird from the cage
all right and and he says crunch bird
table and the crunch bird goes and it
destroys the table goes that table just
messes and destroys it it crunches the
table i said
exactly that's why it's called a
crunchberg iris i can see your pantsuit
all right now just be careful um
so next he says excuse me next he says
crunch bird crush bird chair the crunch
bird goes
and it destroys the chair all right so
now the chair is destroyed and so the
wife says you know what this is a
dangerous animal but i think it's got i
think it's got potential you know it's
got like
it's different you know it's not just
like your run-of-the-mill usual uh pet
and i think my husband might like this
exactly it's got that potential real
special pep tension
try saying that ten times fast real
special pet potential special pep it's
probably not that hard so so she says
you know fine i'll take the crunch
and um and he he they do the exchange
she gives him the money he gives the
bird right she takes the bird back home
sets up the cage gets it all nice for
her husband to come back home
now husband walks through the door and
he sees this foul beast in the corner
and he says what the f word is that
can't say the f word we have children
watching possibly so she said let me
show you she opens the door lets the
crunch bird out
and she and he says what can you tell me
what on earth is this thing she says oh
it's a crunch bird he says crunch bird
my ass
[Applause]
i think you know what happens after that
just in time
who's telling him about the crunch
she censored the s word but not the
yeah
it's gonna crunch
story do you have one for me i want to
hear from you guys
your wisdom
sit in the rocky chair yeah yeah yeah
sit in the rocking chair
but not dead okay i am athletic oh
[Applause]
this is something that i experienced
oh no
so a family member and i were just you
know chilling out in our room and at
exactly 12 a.m
the phone started ringing so i said
oh wow
why would friends call you at this hour
that's really disrespectful
and then
and then she looked at me and said that
that's not my ringtone
and
the the song that was playing uh was
pretty much all about
uh like i've been everywhere searching
for you where have you been because i
see you
like
are you hiding somewhere in the crowd
and
and then we got kind of creeped out we
uh picked up the phone
and it stopped playing
and then suddenly at every night
exactly at 12
that same ringtone was happening
and that was that was not the ringtone
that she set and
later on she decided to delete the song
from her phone
and it still kept playing
and
and then we had some
interesting events taking place such as
how when i was all alone in the house i
would hear
a piano key
a single
piano key just going ding ding and
i would go and check it out nobody's
there or
i'd be all alone in my room and my dog
uh who's in the same room would
look at whatever's at the end of the
hallway and i keep trying to call their
call time lut's name and
they won't
they won't turn their head it's fixated
at whatever is at the end of the hallway
everything was pitch black
uh yeah
um
that that phone kept ringing
and maybe something about that house was
weird um she should just turn around are
you sure he wasn't a prank
[Laughter]
uh maybe it was a whole can door
or can door hand door
and that same family member had
some other experience where
they would have nightmares
about how they can't move but they would
be in a fire or they would get shot some
a lot of nightmares every single day
and that can't be a prank
sometimes
a woman like crawling over the ceiling
really fast just to look at friend's
face
that's why everything that's on the
ceiling is haunted
like a ceiling fan yeah everything is no
and then later on that was when she was
living alone and when she decided to
live
with her family again
this time she couldn't move again in the
dream
but
uh at her bedside she saw
a woman with all her face covered
and
and you know with the hair and
everything and she said oh you know what
i see that you're with your family now
and
because of that
i won't bother you again
it's nice of her to talk to you
after that she never had those dreams
where she's paralyzed in her sleep
[Music]
you should get a little you guys listen
i'll get more height on you to touch
this guy
you guys listen up
hey
yes ma'am
yes ma'am she is amazed
so
we're gonna have group a and group b so
if group a is gonna be council you guys
just step on over here for a moment all
the way over here to the left or to your
right
thank you and we have miss and iris over
here
i'm on i'm on i'm a
midsize senpai yes i'm senpai you guys
keep forgetting that button
some pirates oh yeah
i get to be some pirates okay
the way this is going to work is i'm
going to send you guys counsel don't go
into the maze yet but i want you guys to
go all the way over there to the other
side um where the summoning circle is
and if you guys could wait over there uh
that'd be great thank you guys
[Music]
later towards the end so they can't hear
us
showing her moves
yeah i'm a different beast in this model
to be honest
from beast
all right sorry what's your game plan
ladies oh sorry i didn't mean to do that
are we also going to go through the maze
too be spooky
yeah so we're gonna switch um but uh so
uh you guys if you go to your avatars
that you can select you have a few
different options you have two different
options um and what you can be you guys
are gonna be monsters and you're gonna
hide in the maze uh as they enter in and
try to spook them just don't go too far
into the maze we don't want you to
complete it just pick a corner once you
get in there and then uh you can
surprise them there are some little
hidden alcoves in the maze as well
you guys can i mean like this
yes
i like that oh my god
oh really yeah
all right
wait we can use anything can we use
anything in public
not anything in public just the two that
you have we have to pick between uh
[Music]
just stay here um
[Laughter]
[Music]
all right you guys stay here okay don't
don't follow me just uh stay here
momentarily
and knock some [\h__\h] down
yeah i can show the full extent of my
wrath
and i'm looking
[Music]
like i said in the maze don't go too far
just kick the door pick a corridor and
uh try not to go too far into the maze
and we can get you out easily when it's
your guys it's time to switch okay you
guys are there to scare them so oh you
don't use your scary voices so should we
not move scary voices
you can explore the maze but not too
deep okay
okay don't go past the uh i guess we'll
say the black
[Music]
oh do we go through the mirror
don't go past the dark part don't go
past the uh black section okay
okay okay
all right i'm gonna give you guys if you
guys can hear me i'm gonna give you 30
seconds and then i'm going to release
them into the maze
okay okay
where is
oh we can't go through here right the
dark part are we oh my god it's scary i
don't know if this is the dark part
not sure if this is the dark part that
mommy mentioned
i'm gonna sit in here is this the third
part i don't know i don't know i'm gonna
sit around the corner i think this is
the dark part oh my god what the what is
that so scary wait this is the dark part
girl
i'm gonna sit here okay okay i can sit
around
here
oh
[Music]
i'm actually pretty nervous
maybe i should have it off right now
should i have off right now
are they going through wait i'm not sure
if they're going through yet
are they are they are they going through
chat can you tell
oh yeah i don't think so oh oh hyena
actually no wait i'm not so sure
it's enough right
all right council uh you guys can go
ahead and enter the maze
[Music]
okay
is
oh
[Music]
get out
oh my god
oh that's so scary
[Music]
wait a minute
no i'm a scary monster all right
[Music]
whoa
[Laughter]
[Music]
what is happening
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
wait
shadow
trick or treat oh yeah
[Music]
hold on
you okay
[Music]
i have names off already so i don't know
who's who yeah
peace
peace i move my fingers
are you guys doing really good
check on us yes it's sharp
yeah we have a selfie
okay
tick tock
i don't know where the exit is i think
so
i'm assuming it's this way i think it's
this way oh wait never mind nevermind
it's not this way
oh we go through here
hello
this this way
was it this way oh it was this way
oh cam family is cute
oh my god
oh
my god is that
oh my goodness your belly button myth
please go back the way you came and exit
yeah see i was i was chilling in the
corner for the longest time
world alone
i was hearing all of you in the distance
like chatting and then
i was just chilling on the ground
because i thought no one's coming and
mummy comes around and i get the biggest
shock of my life like
i was supposed to scare her but she
scared
looking for you
[Music]
oh yeah who's back hey guys
there's still more of them you guys can
uh
keep going
oh there's still more of them
we get to go oh there is oh i thought we
were sex with the maids right
we get to explore more of the maze
they're flying
don't leave me
this way i'm going so fast
[Music]
this is a surprise oh my god
this is something that this looks like
something that moon made true
yeah it is right it is
a creation it is her baby
we haven't been here hello
oh
it
okay never mind i thought i was i
thought she said irish too okay i guess
not ah this way this way
where did everyone go though i don't see
anyone
uh-oh
i don't see anyone
where is it where is he good at it
though where where's where's where's
mister oh there we go there's it oh i
see i see someone here hi
whoa oh
it's the real shark it's the shark it is
the real shark i'm just following the
planet oh okay
ghost all right uh who is
this gonna follow
[Music]
i think this is a shortcut so you guys
go back to the beginning
another u-turn
oh my god
oh i don't know where i'm going i'm not
either
okay there we go
i'm lost i i know i'm not lost anymore
we're back in yago's dreams uh casket
yogurt
yes yeah let's all take a selfie here
let's take a selfie here
shelby
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
oh
she's actually hopping yeah they're very
good yeah she's straight up just the ass
yeah
the frog the frontal part of the frog is
really kitty kitty like yeah
oh
[Music]
spare me
okay
he's gonna
[Music]
oh
opposites if council could go to the
mirror area it seems like she tried to
die she almost died doing what she was
doing
it was worth it
it was pretty good
[Laughter]
i'm gonna kick you if you don't wake up
oh she woke up okay see perfect way to
wake her up all right uh
council if you uh the rest of council
can go over here in this area
[Music]
over here guys oh my god we're turning
red over here
the red lights oh my god you guys look
even
[Music]
oh she's dancing
is
[Music]
you could go into your ui settings and
turn off name plates if you guys don't
if oh it's already iris because you're
streaming it's already off right now
yeah your name plates are off yeah it's
already off yeah okay okay i don't know
ask me to tell you guys okay now you
guys switch back to your normal avatars
please
[Music]
oh wait they left us behind we gotta go
oh actually
actually never mind never mind
sorry yeah charlie just went somewhere
okay
yeah from america
all right uh you guys stay here and face
uh the crony grave and i will come back
and get you when we're ready okay this
is the crony grain
rip around oh my god my favorite topping
hey guys
[Music]
hi guys selfie time hi
hey
join me
[Music]
sunglasses
yeah i don't know about you guys i
really liked those um i really like
those shark and like frog costumes
because they felt like they gave me the
expression to be myself mm-hmm oh yeah
like
full dance moves with the small enough i
wonder where those models came from
[Music]
there's nothing random about that it's
destiny it's destiny the whole world was
once created by a frog and a shark
that's adam and eve they were a frog in
the shark did you know really
it all started
with sea creatures with a frog in the
shark which i don't know
i don't know if i can believe that
out of the frog and the shark came a
dinosaur now that the dinosaur came to
manchester united
hold on it's simple history why do
[Music]
i don't know where that even is
oh really wasn't it
yeah but is she original i feel like
that's a meme like a japanese meme maybe
i don't know i i don't i've never
remembered like what i sent by uh saying
it yeah yeah she said that yeah but i
don't know where she has it from
maybe it's original
i am like so dead is this the senpai
curry that we're just i don't know too
old for this
it might be i feel like i've descended
and ascended
ah that feels great
sit down
have you guys been standing on the
hunchback
yeah
[Music]
and get all the way to the end okay
all right
all
right let's go guys
too
yes yes i'll go all the way to the end
area
okay
we're going in
we're going in oh yeah and do i remember
the way come on guys
[Music]
you should be easy yeah no problem
oh there's a mushroom
what are you doing this makes sense
oh my god it's scary
oh my god
what is this what is this it's a
mushroom it's a mushroom it's a mushroom
oh please don't eat it i think it's good
bae is a real rat
i don't see anything
i don't see anything i guess oh yeah
there's nothing here yeah i really don't
see anything i hear something here i
hear things i don't see anything
yeah i guess she's just not here oh oh
i hear asmr though asmr i'm assuming
it's bae
you can see them but they can't see you
they can't see you that's not that scary
okay
whatever
my
heart
who's this
oh it's probably
so dark
[Music]
i don't
that's a lot of vocal like it
that is so disturbing didn't you try
this
wow yeah it's very disturbing fantastic
do you want to know why i made it yeah
why
came to my stream and said cute and i
got really flustered and was trying to
draw her but i got really frustrated and
i made that instead
oh you drew that oh it's sweet
[Music]
that is disturbing
why are the other ones
[Music]
thank you thank you for the guide
yes
i don't like how the ambiance stops here
we go inside here
go in there you guys have to go in we go
inside
the prices
[Music]
it's actually awesome it's great i
promise
okay
here we go one at a time or do we go
together
[Music]
looks like she's really not up for it
it's okay
oh
come here it says come here
come here i can't take it i can't jump
anymore when did i forget how to jump so
scared oh no my battery
[Music]
what's that
oh my god it's the final boss
oh there was a heart somewhere
oh my god
that's a wow she has what is she
carrying is she carrying like fruits
a huge pomegranate is that one
pomegranate it looks more like two
pomegranates
[Music]
your big red heart biggest red heart
pineapple
pineapple can i do that i want to do
that one i want to do that too pina
colada
hey
i'll give her my bigger heart here you
go oh i can also splash some sweat
i can splash sweat all over my big red
heart
that's it
[Music]
[Applause]
i'll give you
who's this who is this who's this
mushroom you should try releasing some
bats who is this mushroom
oh my god
not the mushroom no
we shouldn't eat the mushroom it's
poisonous
oh my god cronie is becoming a predator
stop stop
wait this is
christmas she has become oh no oh look
at look behind you guys
[Music]
very
oh he actually is succeeding and scaring
him that's a good time
to exit over here
i
[Music]
oh there we go there we go oh my gosh oh
my god who's that waiting at the end
is it is it chew again oh it's it's
probably true again oh
hi oh never mind
it's the harmless come here the harmony
oh wait what are you guys planning on
doing oh
yeah yeah i like your buttons oh thank
you thank you please don't take my
buttons my buttons are important to me
oh no not another chew monster
not a mushroom no no no no
mush
mushroom mushroom mucho room
[Music]
that sounds cute if you just don't look
at their experiences
i think we made it i'll be here you guys
look like your names are gary
gary
jerry gary
oh there's only one rat here
huh no i'm uh i'm kind of getting did i
hear stuff i thought i heard something
[Music]
oh
yes we have a special premiere that we
are going to be watching in the
auditorium and we're going to go back
there now
[Applause]
[Music]
oh we're
back that was an adventure oh one of us
is still a mushroom
oh christmas mustard
now there we go
there's the cronie
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
okay i think we're all here if you guys
can follow me into the auditorium do not
press any buttons in the auditorium
[Music]
no idea how this looks like this
this hits me cute
it's floating yeah all right
now i think originally i'll wait until
everybody's here no bread sticks that's
sad to make a quick announcement
hey all right oh [\h__\h] i fell off the
stage
no
you guys are welcome to take a seat you
can stand if you like um okay so
originally we're gonna have some
performances but uh it looks like it
didn't work out in time if anybody does
want to perform now's your chance you
could do show-and-tell maybe you want to
choose you can juggle or maybe you want
to see
anybody want to come up anybody any
volunteers no i have stage fright i'm
okay volunteers
okay well we do have uh for chat and for
you guys here in the crowd we have a
special music video premiere oh yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
so if you guys want to get a good view a
good seat now's a good time i got front
row seats from rosie
[Music]
it's a
irish hasn't seen it either i don't
think no i haven't seen it
you guys is this i'm so
excited i see a black screen i only see
a black screen ready you guys are all
ready yeah we're getting we might watch
yeah
you guys are ready
here we go
sorry my light stick is a sideways don't
mind me there we go i don't know how to
fix it oh
[Music]
oh my god this is so cute
with the very
[Music]
oh my gosh
oh my god this song is so good though
[Applause]
[Music]
i hungry to change the screen
[Applause]
everything was amazing
um it will premiere on my channel so you
guys after the stream if you want to
rewatch it you can go there and rewatch
it as many times as you'd like and uh
yes definitely who wrote the lyrics
kelly wrote the lyrics
with the music and also kanaru the music
video animator made such good use of
everybody's models made by seafoam
hasksoff and also twilight 3d it's so
awesome so many people worked on it so
thank you everybody that worked on it
thank you so much thank you guys for
watching that's an experience
oh my god that was amazing
it was
[Music]
as many times as i can
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
i just noticed the graffiti
ah this scene
[Music]
it is a phoenix
[Applause]
i just saw mikko senpai for a second
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
oh no
oh it was the berries
the red stains
[Music]
i just noticed a luigi board has yaga on
it
[Music]
amazing lyrics
um if you guys want to follow me to the
reception area
[Music]
we're gonna jam out a little bit and
then we'll say goodbye to everybody you
guys have always done some cool
screenshots so dance together waltz
together hold each other's hands hug
each other whatever you want to do dance
on the tables dance on the chairs all
right let's get this box
how do i can i sit and have a drink i'm
thirsty
[Music]
[Applause]
like bad yeah
bad girls
whatever
get up there whenever i backflip it's a
pumpkin
[Music]
[Applause]
oh yeah
[Music]
yes
thank you
[Music]
i get kicked off the table
i'm trying to fix it
okay can i get on this chair
somewhere actually i don't think i can
go from the bottom
go from the back go from the back i know
how to take a screenshot i don't know
how to take a screenshot either i'm just
like
that's the best shots
yes yeah i'm gonna grab take the
screenshots
i can't
i can't multitask like that
[Music]
how'd
oh my god the inside of the cronies
heads are scary oh my god i can see the
eye holes
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh my god is horrified
all right
thank you guys for watching the
halloween stuff
[Music]
[Applause]
give me a second give me a second i want
to play the credits yeah i'm going to
play your credits too
[Music]
thank you
just a short one just a very short one
gonna go screenshot time after this
that was so much fun
happy halloween
you lots of candy sorry for lying i
didn't mean to lie paris
oh my god
what
did i just hear something
nothing
you