thank you
[Music]
oh it should be fine
it's fine with your chicken spot we are
not the same anyways
[Music]
over here
hey you you're finally away kick it
again
you might be wondering what's going on
we'll see it has come to my attention
that way too many chickens have not been
following
so I'm investigating with the help of my
trustworthy employees
or that's what I thought but these
idiots keep bringing me the rhyme
tickets
I mean you're obviously in the Newbie so
you probably don't even know what
hashtag won't cluster girl because in
the first place oh man uh you know what
you're supposed to learn this in the
usual room but since we're here I'll
give you a quick lesson
you don't know what the YouTuber is Eva
talk to anybody make friends socialize
touch
grass man well I'm sure you'll learn
about it at some point but for now let's
focus on hashtag look hashtag young
all right
okay KSP 101 how to become one with the
Buckhead on today's episode hashtag book
hashtag yo
so before the concept of hashtag woke
haschak yolk came to life the idea had
already been established I bet all of
you have a girlfriend or a boyfriend no
this is okay
you have me
don't date anyone just
watch my streams every day what only me
just Kiara just Kiara just Kiara it
wasn't until a fire emblem stream that
hashtag will cash up yolk took shape
thanks the minds of a few chickens and
of course the most genius among them all
me hey
YOLO
YOLO swag
y'all
that is funny because of egg yolk You
Only Live Kiana she's funny funny I feel
like that would be a slogan for my
employees though but not you only live
piano but it would be you only love Yeah
woke watch only every day
so we at kfp we hashtag yolk and we
hashtag woke
after that I've been watching over the
cave people closely to make sure that
they are taking Ashton killed very
seriously
some of you might have some archives to
catch up on hashtag woke hashtag yolk
maybe you're better off without a
girlfriend just hashtag Vogue hashtag
yolk hashtag woke hashtag
what that's a little a little hashtag
that we use oh that's very sweet yeah I
think nice job you guys are not behaving
well these days what happened to hashtag
will classic yolk huh just watch My
Stream and I'll be the life that guides
you hashtag woke hashtag yolk
instructions unclear hashtag well
Patrick milk
up and now it would have expected and be
religiously following this weird chicken
Idol what the [\h__\h] who are you talking
about
#will catch the kill that other Chicken
[\h__\h] can you know fly to the [\h__\h]
Moon it hasn't breaking up back that was
it right I almost forgot it there's
another one by the way here let me throw
it out yeah hashtag VOC hashtag yolk the
art and the design is by me hashtag look
hashtag yolk
hello tension I survived the usual room
and now I don't know what I'm going to
do with all the free time I have watch
my streams how is that confusing the
goal is to watch takanasi Kiana
that should have been talk to you in the
usual room over and over and over Nova
is this what I have to accept because I
work with chickens yeah Chicken brain
forgets everything in one second
he's in the usual woman's like yeah
get out of the YouTube room one second
later
[Music]
so in any case just remember hashtag
look hashtag yolk what only me I wonder
where you guys were doing all this time
when I was gone
I said look
I said yolk
correct
what kind of rituals hashtag woke
hashtag yolk
kind of stuff oh and um by the way we
are not a cult nope totally not no get
that out of your head right now I Cove
you guys what does that mean again a
pre-chat meme
are you guys spreading the mindset of
hashtag woke hashtag yolk by the way we
are not a cult I am
I am God of kfb hashtag look hashtag
yolk by the way we're not a Coke by the
way share the hashtag fantastic yolk
ritual
hashtag roll clashed a joke became awoke
woke woke and yolk but we're not a cult
there you go now you know that you
should always abide by our slogan
hashtag woke has a joke which doesn't
really mean that you can't watch other
whole life members
it's totally okay to support them but
only as long as I remain as you wanted
only the true the biggest Aussie
or Chihuahua now go my dear Chicken Go
fantastic book
milk
me proud
[Music]
wait stop there what is that in your
pocket
is that Amelia Watson acrylic keychain
TM
so you have on emerge but not mine
even though I just released you birthday
merch recently link to the shop in the
description wink
well just let me tell you one thing
I
love to do the famous announcer from
Battle dates oh my God simple so come
close I want to see I want to see show
me show me show me give me give me how
shiny is it have you been polishing it
properly
oh so cute it's actually the most
adorable oh she's your sister she's just
the best oh my God nobody can top
forever all right anyway let me take
this uh this keychain has now been
confiscated and you are going to the
usual use your room I'll finishing you
little [\h__\h]
what's only me
[Music]