foreign
[Music]
thank you
At Your Service yeah
hmm
[Music]
today
me Princess Kubo kaneru
not arrangement I mean uh uh still
Arrangement but princess Rachel man
please call me princess
[Music]
you guys remember what day is today
right huh it's
[Music]
you guys you guys won't forget my
birthday right okay in this room uh come
on
I will do my best to speak uh with
English Okay mostly with English
so
[Music]
oh I'm so I feel like I'm not ready but
but yeah I must I must be ready ready or
not must be ready okay
by the way uh why I choose to speak uh
with
uh speaks more with English in this room
because uh this thought so much history
right right now is uh for my JP and Ian
senpai's only
[Music]
and for other people
uh we'll be in separate
waiting room yeah that I haven't
made
[Music]
it
um
foreign
[Music]
this is my first time celebrating my my
birthday with a lot of people
yes yes secondary thank you thank you
yeah yeah I can do it I can do it
oh by the way uh uh for you for you who
does uh heaven
uh no this this little thing
above me
they call chillers chillers for Timon
mulus
[Music]
because look at look at the uh the the
fluffy fluffy what what
what does our means clouds yeah yeah
the clouds fluffy clouds and the water
Warrior thingy
it's around me
you guys can finally see my power
with your own eyes okay I think uh this
is the time uh to bring you guys to my
dinner room dinner room yeah or whatever
it is okay
okay
guys
[Music]
wow we finally arrived
welcome welcome
to do characters
wait let me let me shoot my water first
because it's very watery watery
uh
okay so uh let me invite the first guest
who's the first gas gonna be
I'm waiting for the first guest hmm
hello
wait no no not yet
I cannot
oh
ah
wow
happy birthday
yay Daddy
happy birthday to my favorite son how
are you you're so cute for your birthday
wow
hey you have a little friend on your
head yeah yeah yeah
it's uh they're called chilos
chilos yeah so cute I love it oh thank
you I love your dress Diddy oh thank you
my son I have a gift for you whoa what
give what give here I got you your very
own golfing clubs it's in the pictures
the pictures Channel
dolphin gloves
what though whoa
I got you golfing clubs oh my God it's
yeah cute they are yeah for you
thank you
a golf sticker yeah golfing golfing
clubs
golfing gloves yeah your own golfing
clothes
thank you you're welcome
in your golf yeah yeah thank you this
makes me wanna a golf more especially
with you yes let's Golf together Cobo
we'll go together again
ah my son you have a nice party I'm a
little thirsty I'm thirsty
what do you want champagne champagne you
like drinks yeah yeah I like Mojitos can
I have the raspberry mojito
[Music]
okay
yeah yeah
thank you oh thank you so much move away
man move away okay
thank you sir yeah thank you yeah you're
welcome uh drink this
yum yum yum yum yum yum yum why awesome
that was refreshing ah nice and nice
thank you for coming Daddy okay of
course no
choose truth or dare
dare I'm not a coward ah wow
wow I'm not a coward yeah okay okay okay
okay
let's see what you got okay
oh my gosh the wheel
[Music]
your daddy voice let's go okay all right
all right only for you Kobo okay
[Music]
foreign
happy birthday I'm I'm embarrassed but
happy birthday my son
um
[Music]
maybe maybe take away food
yeah I want I want the pasta you want
the pasta all right give me that pasta
cheers yeah pasta the noodles yeah this
is a truffle pasta okay it's very
expensive Daddy okay so make sure you
finish it yeah yeah it's a fancy okay
okay you got it Coco here I go
okay it's empty
okay I don't want to I'm full ah I can't
eat anymore nice
thank you
thank you son for the food and drink and
for the Dare enjoy your golf clubs and I
you know I your party's so fancy thank
you I feel a little sick this is fun
though why you just say it too much
please don't shake okay I'll try to get
better for you I'm gonna go sit I'm
gonna go sit in a chair over there and
maybe dance a little bit afterward by
myself wait for me I want to dance with
you okay oh can we have a dance together
yeah yeah yeah but please don't shake
okay all right no sick I promise okay
okay I love you Kobo I love you Dad
okay this year this year do your best
okay yeah I'm in all right and and golf
please lots of golf let's go yeah yeah
thank you Happy Birthday
you're welcome love you too Coco bye bye
oh my up bye
the hell
oh
okay
foreign
please
please come I am lonely
ah
anyways I love my dad
yeah that's very awesome look at what he
got for me damn this golf clubs it's
blue it's freaking blue like me it's
blue and have a you know that yellow
pattern I love it and the and the
raindrops oh anyway so so someone is
coming
[Music]
back
yeah thank you what should I call you
can I call you my auntie
yeah yeah sure yeah oh auntie I I'm I'm
sorry about like
what we were watching way back when do
you remember when we may and I were um I
don't know something something meant
with one cup or what
foreign
Ty
it was like yeah yeah oh yeah I remember
what I mean why why don't you guys you
and mummies and fight on don't show me
like why
oh no you were there you were there like
we watched it and that you were just
very confused so
yeah it was it was a very funny time
oh sorry sorry if the word of you no
it's okay I mean I can I can look it for
look it up myself
[Music]
I'll like if you really want to look at
it like a a link that the proper one the
the funny one the funny one okay you're
funny yeah okay I love funny things all
right Auntie crony tea so choose truth
or dare
now
okay now
okay
all right truth truth oh no why truth
you know Auntie okay fine there okay
let's do there
spin
why not again yes
oh really okay that's easy
um
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
it's a it's a it's a big compliment
hearing from you
it's a what
it's a it's a it's a compliment hearing
it from you thank you yeah yeah it's a
compliment it's it's a good thing yeah
yeah yeah nice nice
so
yes
lovely weather we're having yeah
but uh do you like oyster
me
um oyster
uh hmm oyster
it's it's okay I would are there other
food
yeah
why why not oyster
um
I do like seafood just like maybe not
oyster how about
oh how about um
that's like vegetables right no it's
okay
[Laughter]
no no no no no no no no no no no yeah
maybe hey it's a very oishy yeah you
know yeah I'll eat vegetables just for
you
wait you you don't eat vegetables
I
yeah vegetables are kind of not that
great but you know that's that's not the
point but the point is that you did you
prepare all this food that's that's
amazing yeah it's uh it's uh my my five
stars you have cooked all of this
oh dang I will send my regards to your
Chef because uh
why what why what why regards
a good it's like good it's it's like it
means
like I I give my compliments to the chef
I thought I thought you want to complain
oh no no no man it's like a Michelin
star shot oh yeah I am Michelle in the
Stars Chariot what is Michelin
I didn't you just it's like
it's like a officially rated chef
I
I thought
[Music]
so you can look it up you can you can
look it up it's like an officially rated
Chef which can Michelle
[Music]
Michelin Michelin sorry like five star
micheliness
oh
[Music]
okay wait don't you just say Michelin
yeah so yeah it's like it's like
uh a worm
a worm it's like it looks like a worm
yeah
oh my God are you nervous Andy
no I'm just I can't keep up with this
conversation
I'm a little confused but you know
how long has it been already wow it's uh
I'm already dizzy um
you need champagne you need champagne
I need you yeah I probably need
champagne you need to like more a little
you know
yeah I mean it's already pretty late but
I guess I'll just crack open a cold one
because I may need a
um
here's gonna hear a bottle of champagne
look look now oh really look look
okay okay
I my alcohol tolerance is actually not
that good so like I think
I think I'm gonna throw up no it's okay
um
[Music]
uh you know like your throw up
clock
yeah so you you won't throw up you you
you no please don't dirty this place
I
I'm gonna hurl
what I don't huh I don't feel so good oh
no why why I oh my God I can't you just
made you just forced the entire bottle
down
how am I supposed to live bro
this is okay it's actually it's actually
just like uh one person alcohol
it's it's actually a soda
it's it's soda yeah
are you sure like it says like 20
percent
on the on the list
a scam you know it's a scam yeah
dude is the soda expired that why is so
bitter I don't understand like this is
juice this is soda
wait let me read uh
no it's a coffee
carbonated coffee yeah yeah yeah
in a bottle yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
coffee's clear
coffee is
clear yeah why
you you just ring this huh oh my God you
need to explore more auntie
this is a very uh uh
really uh uh you don't even if I don't
even know
famous product from friends yeah
I I see
this is coffee I thought you said soda
no no no no
you misheard it yeah okay well
I feel I feel Gaslight I'm sorry but you
know yeah yeah thank you for um I'm I'm
still pretty sick so I think I'm gonna
go and uh throw up yeah that's okay
why'd you just put that on top of my
head I don't know it just look good on
you I don't know I mean that is a pretty
good hat I didn't even finish the food
yet you know what I'll just like wrap it
up for it to go thank you man I hope you
have a good day good birthday though
cause
you know yeah hope you enjoy it thank
you thank you
please be good don't throw up too much
okay
yeah I'm gonna throw up so much bye
bye thank you oh my God
[Music]
what the hell first daddy Mori second
it's my auntie why
just
I don't understand why
okay let's see who's the next
who's the next person coming
oh
awesome fine
hello hello
[Music]
thank you for coming to my birthday
thank you for for saving me in Minecraft
ah yeah
um
hero
[Music]
I have a spin wheel
oh
please
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
it's a wheel spin um
oh
say happy birthday to Kobo with your
coolest voice
[Music]
okay okay okay
okay
can you be
um
happy birthday
[Laughter]
[Music]
quarter boys
it sounds very very good uh cool ship
foreign
[Laughter]
I love I love your songs too because
your voice is very
well done
it's very soft
call nobody
oh yes
yes the song is one of my favorite
I I uh I I can sing it with my uh
ukulele you know
[Music]
senpai
hey
I Know It uh let's let's have a song
covered together
oh
cover song okay okay okay okay okay okay
um
I don't know
[Music]
it's demo
okay okay
uh
thank you for coming to my birthday
party
thank you once again uh sorry uh I I I
still I still don't know what to talk
with you senpai
me too I said me too
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
summer
[Music]
time
foreign
[Music]
oh my God
man I don't know I don't know uh what to
talk with my JP's advice but
um
I try my best because uh I I want to
talk with them but it's it's just so
hard
[Music]
uh
uh okay uh okay I'll do my best next
time okay
okay let's see
let's see
um
oh what we got here now
so no Senpai cannot come
so she sent me a letter just a letter
um thank you Miss Empire but it's okay
if you cannot come
happy birthday
wait what what is this
if you can see
that means let's play together again
thank you thank you Madison bye love it
especially for me tokun
a
is uh
a male version
it's like uh it's just like table with
melto Kobo and Mel
cheboyto
thank you bye for the letter thank you
[Music]
okay
next we have Tata from atang atan cannot
also cannot come so she she gave me she
sent me this this beautiful artistic
drawing nice I love your what is the
hell
what is that I love your personality and
music Talent thank you
thank you I love your uh your glasses
and your purple hair too
thank you thank you thank you for the
illustration thank you for the happy
birthday
thank you I mean thank you for the happy
birthday words mama mama thank you
okay next next let's see
we have uh what do we have here
pretty big one it's from
it's a it's uh uh
cannot come in so they both sent me this
illustration and letter thank you
happy birthday
I love your voice your stream I want to
talk with you more from nanoka harasaki
ah thank you for the beautiful and
artistic Art thank you
[Music]
thank you for the happy birthday words
okay
next next
we have oh
oh
okay let's see
oh okay okay uh let me restart it
[Music]
happy birthday
happy birthday come on I'm so sorry I
couldn't make it to your birthday party
today it's okay I wish you all the
happiness and all the joy and all the
fun on your very special day today hope
you're having a great time and I wish
you a very happy birthday
foreign
[Music]
okay
I don't know what I don't know what did
she do but it's pretty cute
yeah but thank you thank you awesome bye
thank you I don't forget the Senpai
title okay
thank you let some fly yeah
I will call her rotten pie but with
French action you know
what
what sorry sorry sorry sorry oh my God
Friends Action is very hard thank you
thank you bye
okay
what do we have here
[Music]
boom
oh
it's pretty big oh my God
what is that oh my God
what is that
whoa pretty long letter from Mama
cannot come to this not so much so they
they sent me this letter too and the
kids TV illustration there
um
look at that
TV cover
let's read it together guys
happy birthday Kobo hello my little girl
[Music]
mama
so sweet I I I I I I haven't read the
rest of the letter but
is very sweet
[Music]
thank you
sorry I couldn't say happy birthday to
you on your life
thanks for always bringing so much joy
into my life
[Music]
when I see you enjoying life it makes me
happy too oh
eat a lot of delicious food play a lot
of games and sing a lot
mama
I hope this year will be a great and
dreamy for you wishing you a day as
special as you are happy birthday
as special as me oh
thank you Mama
[Music]
it's okay if you cannot come
mama
will try her best okay don't worry
oh my God
ah
I don't know why I'm I'm tearing up
it's it's cute
maybe it's because it's it's my first
time got something like that from my
mama I mean not my real Mama but still
my mama
yeah
I love my mama I love my mama
and my Mommy too
um
thank you
okay
Okay so
I wanna I wanna uh inform something
that I will have a cover song
and it will be premiered at around 10.
45 P.M
um do you guys already know no no no not
yet okay just wait just wait for the
waiting room okay
it's uh it's a
Indonesian song
but
the lyrics is in English but isn't it's
it's from it's an Indonesian song
yeah
maybe maybe it's not like uh something
like uh
but I I prepare it specially for today
for you guys okay I hope you guys enjoy
it
um
ah
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
so we still have uh some time
and
and I don't know what to do
but let's talk about
uh let's talk about my
my merch
my merch will come soon like very very
soon and you guys need to buy it have to
buy it because it's very useful wow what
is that you guys will see it soon okay
finally finally my own words wow wow wow
yeah it's very useful it's a useful
thing well for me
at least yeah but it's very useful
um
I hope you guys use it okay
I hope you guys just no it's it's
not an umbrella Please don't don't
expect
so much okay it's not an umbrella
uh the merch will come we will out at
8pm so just be ready okay just be ready
all right by the way uh for
um for
umati which is after this after this Rim
uh
I will I will I will do thoughts mucho
with uh Indonesian YouTuber and
Indonesian people but not only
Indonesian there's like other YouTubers
but like uh this room is
um
especially just for uh my whole loss and
buys yeah my JP and Ian holas and buys
um
thank you
[Music]
okay uh
foreign
because princess usually dance like like
a princess have a dance after party you
know like in the in the ballroom
don't know how to dance but
I like to have a royal dance you know
like in Sofia the First I love Sofia the
First
[Music]
training some Italian no I don't wanna
training with you guys
nah I doubt that you guys can dance
though
um actually there's uh actually oh yeah
yeah oh guys guys actually there are two
cover songs that I wanna I wanna
I wanna boom like
in this birthday stream but uh uh I
think it's too much fun service so I
delete the other one
I delete the other one just just wait
for it and it will be released uh
uh this month but just wait for it okay
um
yeah and uh let's talk about yesterday
the other stream
the my my my my my my
my countdown stream do you guys remember
that I have I have a pinata or how to
say peanut butter pinata
pinata
so I made the peanut to myself
I made I made the peanut to myself
so and it took a lot a long time like
maybe three days
three days land I I cut my fingers too
but
but tomorrow we have a Karo kishorium an
honor Kaif one an archive karaoke stream
acoustic
yeah acoustic honor cause
shrimp ah acoustic undercut karaoke
shrimp
so even though I cut my fingers but uh
it's it's you it's it's healing so I
think it's fine I still can play My
Guitar
hmm
yeah I think it's fine
yeah
yeah so that's all that I want to inform
to you guys
um
be careful thank you you cut what I cut
my fingers
three three fingers but it's okay
um
[Music]
I I have so many stories that I haven't
tell you guys that I really really
wanted to tell but
I I just forgot all of it suddenly I
think it's because I'm nervous I'm so
nervous right now
I'm still nervous ah and and I got I got
I got I got many kicks today
I got many cakes yeah yeah I got mini
cakes from Ollie from Kaila and from my
other friends
yeah yeah yeah thank you but I will
pause it later on Twitter
um
I will pause it later okay
just wait for it it's a very cute cake
from only it's cute from Kyla it's cute
and from my friends also cute
[Music]
Spiel no no no no I don't wanna give you
guys uh a spoiler okay
I Don't Wanna Give You guys spoiler
that's
[Music]
foreign
wait a minute
who am I waiting for Hmm this just wait
okay just wait and uh we're ready for
for the merch
[Music]
for the much for the months okay just to
speak patient or just be patient
seven minutes left seven minutes two to
the merch sale
and it's a flash sale okay it's freaking
flash shell yeah for this who asks me
like is there any flash sale because
it's 12 12 right
yeah it's freaking flesh cell okay
bro
good morning yeah
[Music]
okay there's flesh now
uh you guys want one the one the spoiler
now
nah just one minute left okay
one minute left and I will show you guys
the merch what's the merch line
okay
so
one minute let's go so the merch
what will it be what would it be what
will it be oh my God so oh my God here
we go let's go the merch is
oh
yeah
yeah you are so cute right
so okay right yeah
by the way it's uh uh the illustration
is from uh useless and say um
the illustration it's from usual sensei
[Music]
oh look at it wearing uh what is the
nickel nickel
nickelodeman headband yeah yeah so cute
right
but uh the merch will will out in 8pm
okay 8pm remember 8 P.M so it's five
minutes left but I just want to show you
guys
oh I want some made and Bowl oh my God
lunch man
and a bowl called
so you guys can use it
you know to wash your hand as a as a
wash bowl a bowl wash what what would
this yeah whatever you want to call it
so uh it's a man called manko book from
Bangkok and Cuba and kobok
[Music]
in English
is bull
and Kobo is Kobo
and kobok
and kobach is you know how to say it in
English
[Music]
yeah and it's very useful you can eat it
with your iron fish
meatballs spaghetti oyster
Ratatouille you can use it okay please
use this bowl this is a very useful okay
let's go
use the monkey block okay use the mango
book
wisely yeah for it not for drink okay
oh by the way
by the way here's the that's in the
description
I will I will uh
uh
the the the the the how to purchase it
you can purchase it in the link that I
drop in description okay
wow and the bonus look at the bunnies oh
postcard oh postcard with my own
handwritten autograph yeah I signed it
myself like so many many many so just
buy it uh complete okay complete set
okay because if you buy it
uh buy it completely to set completely
you will got the bonus and that's the
bonus of postcard yeah
and don't forget the lunch mat the lunch
mat also can be uh accessories
[Music]
can be accessories to Discount wait a
minute
uh it is already discount okay uh the
first price is at like 10
10 million dollars and it's because it's
a flash sale so it's a cheaper now okay
so please please bye bye bye bye bye bye
bye bye
please buy okay let's see oh and also
there's my birthday for I said it's a
situation wise and in the Japanese
version
titled being your cat
the English one titled don't make me
fall asleep because of you
hump
and in the in Indonesia Indonesia one
it's called I'm I'm afraid of thunder
I'm afraid of thunder
hump
yeah let's go and if you buy it complete
set you will get the bonus and what's
what's the bonus you will get the script
data of the voice recordings that means
if you buy the uh if you uh if you buy
the set and you don't understand the
Japanese one you will get you also will
get the translation
[Music]
my my merch my birthday March here is
approx
h35 x w 4 4 cm let's go and the link is
open now let's go check out tickle
tickle check out let's go tick tack oh
take it out take it out don't copy Sun
guys
sort out the hell
bruh
[Music]
bruh we are sold out
huh for you bright bruh
not nights it's impossible no it's
impossible
no no no no no it's impossible
okay
the link is on the description guys Link
in the description
I got the description
yeah but it's very cute right the launch
man
we cannot launch
matsato said wow
illustration is uh from usual Sensei and
the balls into illustration to be cool
boy illustration
and the the patterns the side design is
from
Sensei arigato
hmm material pad ABS residual uh
[Music]
um
the bonus
postcard with a handwritten autograph
yeah
[Music]
foreign
look at my merchless birthday merchat
birthday voice
yeah the Delta voice back their voice
box and the the lunch mat and Bowl let's
go
[Music]
dinosaurs
please buy it let's go buy it let's go I
think this is very worth it because I'm
cured and if you have the merch you will
be uh like very very cool in your
friend's eyes okay
[Music]
you guys lying it's not sold out yet
okay
it's not sold out yeah guys please
[Music]
foreign
here
it smells all out yet guys okay
[Music]
um
it's very cozy I chose this Vim because
because I like rainy I like rainy in the
night at night
because it's very cozy and comforting
makes me want to sleep forever
thank you
[Music]
good right cute right please buy it
please buy it please buy it because I'm
cured and because it's
it's cool yeah
because it's cool it's a very good
reason to buy yeah please ask your your
parents your mom your father's
your dad like uh oh my God my mom my my
oh she have uh already launched uh Her
First Merch I wanna I really want to buy
it please give me some money and I
guarantee your parents will will give
you guys so many money let's go because
because it's a tough child flash sale
yeah check it out check it out check out
check out check out the karanja morning
let's go
check out month
guaranteed got slap somebody in the chat
said says
guaranteed to guaranteed got slapped
yeah
I mean
fifty percent fifty percent just to try
this is a gambling you know yeah
yeah
that is foreign
[Music]
yeah
um
[Music]
what's up
lunch yeah
[Music]
Marcy
yeah
guys yeah
yeah okay
[Music]
foreign
guys
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign foreign
[Music]
okay guys
okay bye
[Music]
um
ini
[Music]
Akinator
because because the next person is
is
my my
you know my
um
[Music]
my mama
no no no no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no not my mommy
not my mommy
guys
please take a a nice I guess oh
[Music]
uh
hello hello hello
[Music]
Papa
oh my God I'm sure oh I'm very shocked
thank you for coming bye-bye
[Music]
pop up
because this is a princess Kubo party
hmm
yes yes
[Music]
raspberry
foreign
[Music]
please drink drink after it
yummy yummy yummy
foreign
[Music]
okay let's dance and spin it's awesome
ah okay if Kobo were a worm would you
still want to be friends with me
[Music]
foreign
what
insect okay is present to surrender
[Music]
yes insect or cash oh my God
present
oh my God
demo I
kimokunai
because it's uh
yeah yeah Mike okay
arigato
[Music]
let's see
what's going on
[Music]
okay yes
[Laughter]
thank you for coming Papa come on let's
see
[Music]
birthday presents the presents hi what
is
oh
birthday cake
[Music]
what
cover birthday cakey
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
please come in
please please hello oh hello hello
oh happy birthday
[Music]
thank you for coming so fine
so because it's a uh
summer party so yeah
sauce yes yes yes yes yes
wait uh
hmm
[Music]
job
protein protein what what
you're so awesome
I don't I don't know
[Laughter]
yeah
[Applause]
thank you
oyster
[Music]
okay
where's the where's the meaning hello
hello do you have oyster
no the oyster is already sold out
oh my God
okay okay
[Music]
oh okay yeah uh your favorite food
please
your favorite food yeah
okay okay yes yes yes Korea
duh put it
possible soup
[Laughter]
um
I like bread yes yes
oh thank you Arigato yes please eat this
drink the protein again
thank you foreign
okay
[Music]
um please
Discord yeah
oh yeah yeah yeah okay okay okay too
easy
okay okay
three two one
hey
[Laughter]
valoran
[Music]
thank you
bye bye see yeah happy birthday
wow
I don't know what what is going on but
okay all right
I'm in okay all right
it's
cool yeah he just drink protein and yeah
it's it's a it's a real protein okay
it's yeah
it's not the scam I'm not I'm not scam
him okay it's it's a protein it's
one person protein
wait he went wrong right he won't drunk
right
well
I hope so
yeah
okay
[Music]
oh I wonder who's the next person please
oh my God
okay
yeah
he could be a good boy yes big big boy a
big
big boys also oh my God thank you for
coming yeah
[Music]
um
oh my God I love your voice Olga senpai
yeah
can I call you um
can I call you
um
[Laughter]
oh okay
so princess yeah
oh princess
okay
oh nice okay okay
[Music]
okay
so Sam
yeah oh
oh
say cool was opening with your version
opening
at your services
okay okay yes
foreign
[Music]
thank you thank you for coming to my
birthday party
um
present for you
happy birthday
[Music]
um
happy birthday
foreign
nice nice voice
thank you oh thank you for coming it it
was really my first time uh at uh
talking with August Senpai actually but
yeah okay
[Music]
I wonder who's the next person is
happy birthday
where's my present
oh
okay where's my present do you have a
favorite person
oh present gift
ah okay what okay what do you mean okay
um
[Laughter]
go present present what uh come on hi
okay
Discord oh
Nani got it
haha come on
come on
what
okay
oh nice combo uh hi arigato
um
yeah yeah happy birthday
for you okay
foreign
[Laughter]
okay okay what the
what oh there's an audition please
come on nice to meet you thank you for
coming audition
yes
[Music]
um
oh no it's not dishes
[Laughter]
[Music]
no no
random grandfathers
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
yeah
nice
go away go away
again
happy birthday
um
yes
welcome to Japan
bye
[Music]
[Applause]
my Japanese
foreign
please come in next person please coming
hello hello
[Music]
how old are you
wow this is
no
no no yeah yeah
okay who kiss
um
oh hold it
duh
challenge don't don't angry don't angry
yeah not angry yeah no okay okay okay
because uh yeah yeah yeah uh challenge
for you
challenge for you okay challenge
challenge
[Music]
ah not not this no no no not this I
don't want this no
oh my God
okay anything any animal please
[Music]
oh
no no
no no no no sorry
this animal is cats oh my God yeah I I
am so tired help me
help me no no no no no no please don't
be tired please okay please uh one more
one more okay one more yeah yeah
[Music]
happy birthday
come on
oh
no no I want other animals please
[Music]
help me
help me other animal please
please again
what's giraffe
okay okay
happy birthday
help me
hey
oh my God oh my God oh my God
foreign
[Music]
very beautiful language so
um
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
uh foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
too soon
okay okay
foreign
[Music]
whatever
foreign
[Music]
amazing amazing foreign
foreign
[Music]
bye wait did I call you senpai
did I just call
will you send what no it's not
it's not senpai
I just realized oh my God why why did I
oh my God why did I call him simply
oh my God
I'm so I'm so stupid I just realized it
right now oh my God what the hell
maybe maybe because I'm nervous no
shabiru shabiru
I don't know what's the Japanese but
that's my first time
that that was my first time really first
time
uh calling talking with
oh my God
okay
[Music]
but okay
very uh experience but yeah
okay
[Music]
um
please come in please comment
s
oh
[Music]
Mommy
me
um
but I have a present president
why am I trying to speak in Japanese to
you I'm so confused yeah me too I don't
know
I'm so surprised if Japanese is getting
so good no no no no no not as good as
you Mom
[Music]
you will get there I posted the uh
present on the uh what is this
yes yes yes
a ticket
[Music]
it's a golden ticket oh my God one free
horse riding session oh yeah you know
buying you a whole horse is a bit
difficult because you have to take good
care of it and you're still very young
couple so I don't trust you with a whole
horse but we can go horse riding
somewhere for one session for one day
only one day only one day and then if
you treat the horse well we can see
about a horse
I'm I'm a animal lover so yeah but you
know you need a place to put the horse
and then you need someone to take care
of the horse every day and you need
someone to ride the horse it's not so
easy cobal but I I have my dad
don't be don't be you know we have to
first try it out okay we go normal horse
riding session one time
one time so if if if it sucks it so will
you buy me real horse oh maybe maybe
maybe maybe
don't crack over first you were so happy
I'm I'm still happy it's just okay I'm
unhappy I have I I got this golden
ticket yes and we can go together yeah
together
yeah thank you thank you
I want to play roulette roulette
roulette what roulette truth or dare
um
both
yeah let's go there's a spirit Mommy
that's the spirit okay okay
what will it be what is what is that
wait oh oh my God
one more one more yeah what are you
going to do if I Cry
well that just happened
if Kobo cries we have to make a
compromise oh my God it rhymed the
compromise is we first go normal horse
riding one time to try and then we can
see what happens after if you if kobojan
is a good good child then we can think
about the future
okay I have couple cries I give Cobble
hug hug hug yeah
you like chocolate I love
[Music]
lots of really good chocolate in Austria
I will bring it to you in Austria
oh yeah
I want to go next year to Indonesia
I don't know sometime but maybe in April
or so
[Music]
let's go
let's let me announce something because
we are here right now uh to all the cool
Pokemon
on Christmas Christmas
we're going to release a song cover on
my channel
[Music]
maybe 24 or 25 or so but yeah it will be
on my channel and we will hear couple
John sing with me
[Music]
oh I want to hear voice with me yeah
yeah it will be perfectly blend yeah but
I'm still waiting for your recording
[Music]
tomorrow you can record okay
yeah yeah okay
one one quick challenge go go go go one
quick challenge okay challenge I love
challenge what is it yeah no no no no
voice talking with me
starting now
I think Discord will cut it out
it's okay because it makes makes it
funny
did you hear it
wait did you just no
okay but this court says it's too high
oh no it doesn't work it's okay
[Music]
I wish you all the best I hope you will
become very very old Josh why like your
grandmother was well yeah I became a
thousand sixty 62 years old once so
maybe little Cowboys like five years old
now but surely you will reach that long
long life sometime just make sure to eat
your vegetables every day and stay
healthy okay so then you can live long
and you can survive even the dinosaurs
all right kobuchan
foreign
bye bye have a happy birthday little
princess oh
thank you I mean a grandma mommy mommy
everything yes yes anything you watch my
dear okay thank you bye bye my grandma
[Music]
and dad is are coming to my birthday
party tonight I also let me thank you
thank you
and and I got golden ticket from Mommy
riding horses let's go
let's go
laughs
Tennessee
thank you Mommy bye bye Mommy
okay okay okay
[Music]
wait a minute wait a minute what what
wait wait wait wait a minute
um
[Music]
okay please next person please join next
person oh hello
hello hello
[Music]
princess
yay
princess party
[Music]
okay
I need what yes
[Music]
you drink alcohol
yes this is okay oh
wow yeah
that's a good time
uh
I want cake you want cake okay
okay okay
put it
[Music]
um
I'm so nervous no no not this way
[Music]
okay okay
say happy birthday with Opera
[Music]
come on
[Laughter]
beautiful beautiful okay
that's the song
okay okay
[Music]
hmm
first Olympics
all right
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you
happy birthday
happy birthday to you
yeah
beautiful voice
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
singing voice
let's go
[Laughter]
thank you
[Applause]
bye-bye
[Music]
oh my God bye-bye
I love Rio because he is
a ghost
night
[Music]
foreign
next person
next person is coming
[Music]
up there
foreign
by the way don't forget buy the merch
guys don't forget to buy the merch okay
okay
[Music]
and happy birthday
[Applause]
Hoshi
thank you
nice nice nice toys
[Music]
Google
thank you
yeah
because I'm Samurai yes Samurai likes
tomato
[Music]
Samurai yes
okay
senpai
[Music]
okay okay
say happy birthday with animal language
[Music]
foreign
cold what yeah what's your name for your
own head friend's name is
cheers
[Music]
no problem so I'm very happy
easily so let's play so together yes
game so yeah would you like to play a
game with again and I was glad to work
so concerned and talking English we have
that crap thank you okay okay
thank you
yeah let's play game together yeah
hey
baby
[Music]
I need my voice
oh
[Music]
come on
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
guys always message me for like
can I uh can I stream this
uh like a news you know news news
often often to message me for for her
asakoyo stream and it's it's very funny
so very funny
okay
[Music]
say happy birthday to Kobo with your
coolest voice
foreign
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
happy birthday
um
foreign
[Applause]
huh
[Music]
um
oh okay okay so
[Music]
um
I like to because you seem to like
insect Steve borrow suprance oh my God
obviously it's eating me
what eating you
yes are you happy
no I I know
no no no no no no no no
I'm leaving
I am strong okay
[Music]
and let's pray again together
let's play chess again
[Music]
the president
the more
[Music]
wait
Salama
um
what what
what
I'm shocked I'm shocked oh my God
I try I practice
okay
[Music]
Dominica
oh manika oh yeah oh my God
no please please no please please no
please uh I mean I mean uh sure sure but
uh sure sure okay okay Monica
I don't know
I'm in the Mary
yeah I know I know I know but okay okay
um
I want to marry uh you too
help me
[Music]
you know meetings try the porter means
no butter is a Potter
I I don't know
[Music]
huh
is
means I can say yes
[Music]
is it bad word
yes b i t
yeah you can say it
oh my God
[Music]
oh you already know the meaning yes we
are so much
yeah Tama is not a
foreign
[Music]
what do you want
oh the like the mama
Margarita
Margarita oh nice toys nice toys and bye
what is it what is it
foreign
[Music]
yeah it tastes like oh and I mini coated
oh it's like wagywaggy Cobble
what
it's my Senpai such a word like that
oh many times
yeah it's uh yeah it's okay I mean yeah
it's okay
okay okay
oh my God okay uh just just let's do the
challenge already do are you ready yeah
yeah of course challenge for you senpai
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
happy birthday
yeah
okay
uh
that's okay
[Music]
I'm a bit traumatized I think but um my
sanity is still okay
um
what the hell did I just Witness
wow
[Music]
foreign
but is Cheer yeah
[Music]
thank you
because you ride riding bike yeah
[Laughter]
thank you for coming yeah
[Music]
party
oh
um
princess okay
okay
sorry
today today's princess combo
today only princess Kobo okay
ah every day every day every day is
Princess you know oh everything oh I
don't know
I'm bringing
it
so you you are so dirty boys I I very
like huh
huh dirty voice huh dirty boy is buried
I like oh that's on my voice yeah what
what voice yeah
thank you thank you
okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
there we go yeah
bye bye bye bye bye-bye
[Music]
oh okay
okay okay okay okay okay
I like so I'm alive
[Music]
ouch
foreign
[Music]
oh my God oh my God ah yes
thank you
thank you pasta
they're yummy
um
yeah yeah
okay soccer ball hi present for you
go go present for you this
what what
[Music]
this this present for you
nice
okay
you couldn't you couldn't
so sorry
this
um
you like money I love money okay
arigato
[Music]
thank you thank you for coming to fun
bye bye bye good luck good luck too
[Music]
foreign
like this
premium nickel oh my God please please
thank you very expensive is
[Music]
thank you thank you
into
uh products okay okay
oh
let's go let's go through it oh let's go
oh okay
okay oh
since it's okay
oh my God
ah okay
put it foreign
[Music]
what does it mean oh my God I'll I'll
make make the house uh sorry make a
house
um
[Music]
surviving
for survive
yes yes oh
[Music]
this is
translated
foreign
[Music]
no no no no no
One More Sad
yeah
oh my God
foreign
[Music]
eh
now who don't
I look for you when you are gone
[Music]
yes yes
foreign
[Music]
by the way there's a
so there's a
birthday gift from from
her senpai
and tadas
[Music]
love you happy Birthday wow uh very
artistic nice art anyways
that's cool
happy birthday
I mean uh good evening
hello thanks for inviting me to your
party it's beautiful in here yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah thank you for for coming
it's our first time talking right
right we talked you showed me your
Minecraft house
your animals
yeah remember yeah I remember but wait
wait did we talk
yeah we did
oh
sorry I forgot because it's just like a
really little a little interaction from
that moment so I need to talk more right
no we need to talk more thank you for
coming soon
mm-hmm I love your voice I love your
ASMR content you know
oh thank you yeah so sweet someday I
will be like you to I want I want to be
I want to make ASMR content like you
yes you should you'll be good at it yeah
yeah thank you thank you the cover is
tomorrow to bless our ears
thank you I will learn more from your
ASMR
why is why is everyone saying no why is
everyone saying no ASMR I don't know I
mean they just stopped up
thing I don't know why
do you need me to to slap them for you
princess
[Music]
no it's okay you don't need to dirty
your hands
okay okay we'll we'll let them slide for
now yeah it's okay it's I'm I'm used to
this no no nothing
to treat you that way they shouldn't
treat you that way you deserve better
princess
hearing you calling me a princess is
it's really something
it's only natural
you are a princess
sorry
um
let's do Truth or Dare shall we okay
what do you want truth or dare
um
there there oh there oh
I'm scared
oh no no no no
oh
this is what you want
it's random you know it's ruled right
right random it's it's random yeah
okay Adam princess
[Applause]
um
thank you so much for coming oh
and and
you know I I heard that you're really
good at DotA
really good I don't know
um I played a long time ago
[Music]
but you know what
I told my chat I would never play again
but for you for you I might
let's let's for you let's play Let's I
mean I can play it but maybe you can you
can teach me
oh I don't know if I'm very good but we
can we can lean together I play support
so I'll support you
no but I also support oh let's support
each other then yeah yeah cute nice
thank you for coming so fine thank you
happy birthday Como thank you
bye-bye bye bye see you later bye
[Music]
laughs
foreign
[Music]
who is the next person I don't know
uh
[Music]
oh
yeah yeah
I you know
and yeah
are you sleepy
no
what full of energy happy birthday
oh yeah thank you thank you for coming
with you're really for real you're even
not sleepy
I'm no I'm fighting through it
sleep
no don't worry about it
it's okay
so because your eyes is already yeah I
can see through your eyes yes you sleep
you can see it in my eyes no that's just
me being really
relaxed by your presence I'm really
relaxed by your voice oh really
yeah wow yo oh so you're like my
innocent mushroom
[Music]
I love your ASMR stream I listen to it
when I go to sleep and when I'm working
and I listen to it when I'm streaming
oh my God
yeah oh my God like it's very relaxing
huh
yes it gets me through my day today
thank you I'm so happy to hear glad to
hear that and like I think I need two
more Duets in my stream
yes please
ah thank you you're so sweet
you are so good at ASMR yeah yeah thank
you for the compliment
you're welcome okay okay all right
I have I I picked some berries for you
berries what berries
where do I put them pictures
oh okay no berries is not the pictures
berries is a fruit though
it uh it can be both
yeah wait I sorry I have to drop them
into your hands here you go oh my God
oh my this wow it's a
it's a blueberries
yeah
they're special they're blue cocoa
berries
blue it's like me it's yeah it's cover
yeah thank you
they explode in your mouth oh it can
explode nice yeah I love explode things
explosive yes it's good nice nice yummy
yeah
[Music]
yeah nice I think I think my poop will
be explode oh no oh wait no not like
that oh my God no no
just in your mouth
oh be careful yeah I mean it's okay it's
it's a it's a good thing uh I think oh
oh okay I see okay it helps you okay
okay yeah thank you it's like medicine
for me it's it's yeah it's good it
tastes really good thank you same five
for the berries
you're welcome
so uh let's do a challenge quickly shall
we oh God challenge or uh truth
truth or dare
oh
anything I can do anything okay truth
okay
uh
no please don't imitate me
ah this this is bye
yes if you were a couple mate what kind
of service would you like to give to me
[Music]
um can I be the dog
is that a service
yeah
and then you have yeah I'm the dog and I
will be a dog for you and then you will
feed me and give me a bath and take me
on a walk
but
but but what's yours that's
[Music]
you're the mate
no oh I'm a dog maid oh
do I still get an outfit
uh yeah yeah obviously oh made out okay
oh okay Ali I eat the food off of the
floor that you dropped that's the
service
but are you still a dog or not
yes so your service is being a dog that
[Music]
the
I made you happy
I mean yeah I'm I'm happy thank you for
the service
[Music]
thank you for barking
yeah I think you should go to sleep now
[Music]
okay it's dog nap time okay yeah
thank you for coming Dogo
thank you
[Music]
happy birthday yeah thank you how do I
leave I'm a dog or if that I figured it
out okay bye bye bye bye yeah
[Music]
well
at this I got my stock there yeah
[Music]
yeah nice okay
thank you for coming saying bye
yeah
hi happy birthday
thank you
all right
party yeah
[Music]
I'm princess yes thank you okay
is a princess too
oh my god
let's go
foreign
[Music]
come on combine
yeah
delicious yes
thank you
got something yeah
okay okay
[Music]
um
okay
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
happy happy birthday
[Music]
yes okay okay yeah yeah
um
[Music]
what is the presence
and you love and ideas are you a baby
[Music]
um
bye bye
bye bye-bye
[Music]
hello baby now I'm not a little baby I'm
not a baby I'm an adult I can't drink
alcohol
I can drink alcohol I'm I'm a dog duh
but but thank you for the gift make me
call senpai
not the baby though
but now I'm very happy thank you thank
you because I'm fine
[Music]
oh senpai
happy birthday
I have a uh I have a gift for you
whatever
okay all right
now I thought a lot about it uh I went
through a lot of gift selections but I
decided that this would be the perfect
gift for you so here you go happy
birthday what the hell is wait wait a
minute
[Music]
coal beard
sphere your face
[Music]
um
cold beard it's yeah it's a cold beard
yeah yeah yeah
okay thank you
[Music]
it's very
uh comfy I guess yeah you know it's uh
Christmas is around the corner so you
can it's a Jolly Jolly Cobalt beard cold
beard
happy birthday uh yeah thank you for the
gift
yeah
so happy birthday again and uh yes you
know I still think fondly of that time
we played Ballarat and uh
I actually think I said I would play
with you
and then when you called into my
birthday actually I think I think I owe
you I still owe you a game
[Music]
together please I I want to test your
skill in Valu
played since the last time we played
with um
I believe it was Cali sempinal Terror
uh so I'm garbage but yes yes we'll play
again oh yeah I forgot
oh we did play once I bought that 60
skin and uh I haven't touched it since
uh especially with me okay
okay sure yeah yeah okay now Truth or
Dare choose
no no never mind no never mind no no
don't choose truth truth for you and
there for you
let's go let's go
okay if you were incarnated as a pet
what would you want to be
truth
[Music]
you know what what I would prob uh
you know there's a lot of uh there's a
lot of animals that um that you could be
yeah and uh you know I think
I think I would be a horse
because um
you know I would I would be able to give
you value
um because you know you could pet me and
I could be all cute but you could also
write me yeah
yeah yeah yeah
I love horse so you just ask a horse
because you know that I love horse right
right oh I like horses too you want to
hear my horse sounds yeah yeah please
okay
nice horse let's go
riding horse
let's go I love horse thank you for
being a horse so if you if you're a
horse
um
so I can write you right
yeah yeah
going going anywhere
uh as far as I can go yeah how about we
go to Japan
okay
um yeah yeah I'll have to learn
how how to to swim horse horse swimming
yeah yeah yeah but we'll figure it out
why don't we why don't we take a plan
okay okay all right I'm gonna have to
buy a few extra seats
but yeah we could take a plane and then
we could ride through the the wheat
fields of Hokkaido or something yeah
yeah yeah please
yeah of course of course anything
anything for you okay okay
understandable
[Music]
oh I'm doing both I see let's go please
role play as someone who has an opposite
characters from yours
hi there my name is
cobal senpai
we should uh play some Valor sometime oh
my
God
okay what what do you want uh sir
protein shake protein shake okay I'm
very strong
and uh I'm strong because I'm the guild
leader we're just out there I like a
protein shake and I get uh
they're all and strong
oh I just oh I just realized your role
play as that that guy oh okay here's
your protein sir
look look
look look look look nice
nice
yeah
okay birthday Kobo thank you
okay or you nailed it no no did I yeah
you nailed it but I just stupid that I
don't realize at the first time but okay
all right well I'll I'll get I'll get
out of your hair so have a good one
Happy Birthday yeah thank you thank you
for coming
[Music]
so she was
role play as ragus
huh okay I just realized that the at the
end of the moment
who's the next person
is ah
nah this one
[Music]
yeah
wow
after all I did after after all that
time that we've been through playing
Valor together I'm just that guy
wow I I I'm Gonna Keep your present I'm
Gonna Keep your present you'll get for
Christmas instead I mean no it's it's no
no it's um that guy no no no
no no no it's a joke it's a joke it's a
joke it's a it's a just it's just a
gimmick for uh for you know as an
Entertainer we do a gimmick you know
gotcha and where's my person
present reason
I was
[Music]
ah don't worry happy birthday princess
gobble happy birthday
uh thank you for treating me and the
boys very very well let me give you a
present before we get started
so here is part one of your presents
like what what what
you can use those I'm gonna give you
five valorant tickets and you can use
one of those tickets anytime you want to
play Valerian with me okay with this
five
they're only five and you gotta wait
until next year
no no
no I just five listen patience is a
virtue patience is a virtue you got to
learn it from uh that guy
I'm sorry
but as a second part to your gift
um this one you probably shouldn't show
on the screen but uh but have some have
fun with these
enjoy some skins buy some skins for
yourself
some pretty skins
[Music]
yeah Cutters courtesy of uh that guy
happy birthday
it's 10 o'clock in the morning
no wait don't cry Wait Wait Don't Cry
wait wait wait don't cry oh
[Music]
thing that you've gotten everything that
you've achieved
that's that's you you did it you did it
so happy birthday be proud of yourself
be happy
foreign
enjoy life enjoy your life okay also get
to um get the Platinum so I can play
ranked with you
[Music]
yeah yeah
thanks
happy birthday
let's play soon um but I think there's a
wheel I should be spinning right where's
my blue crap
[Music]
you said you wanted it you wanted me to
deliver it in person so I I gotta wait a
little bit I'm all right you're right
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah okay okay
big blue crab for you okay blue crab
okay yeah
okay okay
because I choose
I'll you know I'm feeling a bit nice
today
what is your first impression of me
brat annoying loud
[Music]
what a sweetheart really really nice
really really kind always there too you
know have fun with you always there to
you know enjoy enjoy the time that we
have together but also still a brat
still annoying really short
um stole my color
uh
oh yeah cumulonimbus cloud yeah very
stormy very uh rainy
yeah but adorable and a princess
[Music]
okay next
if you have the chance to meet me what
would you do with me
punch you kick you as far as I can
across the room try to set up the field
goal that get three points shoot you
straight through the goal upper 90.
[Music]
let's do the Dare probably give you a
hug or something
[Music]
probably what
punch you kick you punch you I said that
after that yeah yeah after after you
punch
I'll hug you I'll find out
on one condition I get to hold the blue
crab while we while I hug you okay so it
might snap at you it might pinch you but
[Music]
what the heck it's my blue crab it's not
yours yeah it deserves to be hugged too
bruh yo noon
whatever I I can I can still more blue
crap
okay they're they're there for you one
there one there okay okay sing me the
birthday song with any lyrics with
clapping let's go let's go let's go
foreign
[Music]
happy birthday enjoy the rest of your
special day have some fun with your fans
enjoy your callings and let's play some
Valor later okay yeah
yeah all right bye-bye happy birthday
[Music]
finally it's gone bro I'm so tired I'm
so I'm so tired gimmick like being like
a sweet little sister to him it's just
because I don't know I'm just tired bruh
bra I know all of this time he he didn't
mean it but it's okay but anyway next
person who's the next person
I wonder hello hello hello
[Music]
happy birthday Kobo senpai
I miss you
I missed you too it's good to be back
and thank you for inviting me
yeah
it was kind of last minute so I don't
have a birthday present prepared but I
promise you I'll get it if I'll get I'll
get you a present this week your
presence here is already a gift
thank you but I will get you one I
promise you it's hard to follow up with
what what uh Altair got you sounds like
you got you a really great gift but I
will I will get you something I'm gonna
think about it really hard and I'll get
you something nice is it the three cycle
hahaha
you want me to do you want me to okay
you know what
I'll try to get you one
came to get you a speed
who even want a spear oh
[Music]
my God nothing don't don't worry about
it it's just
they're being weird don't worry about it
just ignore it just ignore the check
okay so that's right you will buy me a
tree cycle
yes or something actually yeah yeah
nice nice thank you
[Laughter]
okay let's do truth or dare
okay uh truth about truth
yeah yeah
[Music]
if we both got separated in the forest
what would you do
this like Taylor Made for me because I
love I love hiking and stuff like that
okay but I concentrate that like uh
imagine we go hiking in the forest
together
I would try to find water right because
if I find water I find Kobo Senpai no
matter where it is right oh my genius
guy uh so a trick to finding water if
you're in the woods and you're lost is
to always go downhill which makes sense
right Global Center like water always
flows downhill so if you go down hill
you'll always find water eventually
yeah yeah so that's what I would do I
would try to find water go downhill and
then uh reunite with Kobo Senpai but
what if like I'm not in the water what
if I'm on the top of the tree what would
you do oh
okay then I would panic and just start
yelling come
[Music]
come
[Laughter]
[Applause]
I would try
oh yeah I forgot I mean yeah if you jump
of course I would try to catch
okay I'm I'm afraid that you will break
your
backbones
I'm sure I could catch you I'm sure you
ain't like no I would it would be easy
don't worry about it despite how I look
I do workouts you can turn into bed
right
ah I could neither confirm nor deny that
I could turn into a bat I don't know why
you would think that could why would you
think that
oh wait you can transfer
right
right don't don't don't tell anyone but
yes yeah don't tell anyone yes nice nice
yeah yeah yeah
okay yeah I want uh can can you like I
mean sometimes just uh I don't know when
but turned into a bat and I like I wanna
I wanna play with a bat
you know what look I don't think we
could do that on stream yeah but I all
right the next time we play Valerian
I'll play the entire
valorant game this is a bat with your
whoa with your bat form yeah yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
nice nice nice okay no another another
one okay uh do you want me to do a dare
this time or another truth okay it's a
third again but no no not this
the answer is yes to that though
nah not this
and not this
nothing you could just pick the one and
I would I would answer not this
not this
yeah okay whatever
where your sister for a day
what would you do with me
hmm
a younger sister right younger sister
I would
instead of a tricycle I would try to
teach you how to ride a bicycle because
I think bicycles are
better
[Laughter]
because it's better
yeah I would try to teach you how to
ride a bicycle instead of a tricycle
uh
yeah okay
[Music]
mm-hmm
okay
you want to try a dare or uh just keep
fitting until you get the one that you
want
if if you were if you were uh my uh
Cobra mate a butler what kind of service
would you like to give to me
okay ah you have a lot of really good
food here so I don't know if the food
that I cook could compare to the food
that you normally eat as a princess but
I would like to cook for you
I think that would be what I would like
to try
so you wait you can cook
I can cook but not
high-end food but I can cook I think of
the four boys in Tempest I think I'm the
best cook
let's cook them fire
nice nicer okay
oh thank you thank you for inviting me
and happy birthday I hope you have a
great day and a great year yeah and then
I promise you I will get you that gift
the tree cycle
as a tricycle yes yes
okay yes
thank you
yes I will get it for you
take care bye goodbye
nice
grandpa I love my grandpa next one next
one please coming coming why why why why
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait
hello
where's my present
ah God damn it already yeah
okay okay okay but here here oh okay
okay calm down here's the thing it's
kind of similar to your your big
brothers present shall I say it's kind
of similar you know I guess uh it's a
great minds speak alive what about my
brother
I I don't recall being your brother but
uh my brother you're my real brother
yeah whatever you say man whatever you
say you know huh let me just whip that
out yeah
yeah whatever you say uh here you go
this is your little gift
very very uh
very happy oh hell yeah I mean yeah I
mean so yeah this is more it's better
it's better this this one this one is
better than that that blue guy
oh but do you know why it's better then
because
no I mean it's it's not better uh never
mind I mean like it says I can invite
anyone for you right and
you know you want you want me to invite
certain people right so
you know
[Music]
yeah you know
yeah yeah yeah well
yeah
[Music]
happy birthday yo yeah yo
thank you
no Pro like uh no promises though
because uh that person might just
decline the invite so you know that
yeah you know uh
yeah yeah happy books yeah it's okay
it's it's a Volvo anyway okay
thank you yeah yeah no problem
[Music]
okay now there for you
huh
there there I am there for you no no no
no no no
why say happy birthday to me with your
coolest voice what the one two
three
wait do you want it in Japanese or
English
Vietnamese too okay
happy birthday Kobo
you done
uh what do you want me to say in
Vietnamese I don't know how to say it in
Vietnamese I don't speak Vietnamese
Japanese Japanese now
please always
calling me princess
I'm calling my name too please
how should I say this uh
yeah how do I say this it's weird it's
kind of difficult hey
okay okay okay
no Truth for you
[Laughter]
question of me
first impression I mean a very energetic
little kid wow little kid huh okay
yeah I mean what you want me to call you
an old person then would you rather be a
kid or an old person right I'm a kid
okay
yeah exactly
only that
um
very easy to hang out with and talk to
very extroverted it helps actually
um sometimes you know it's better well I
think I think it's easier to talk when
the other person is as crazy as you yeah
you know yes yeah very crazy bratty
small loud yeah
yeah okay
yeah
like a like a preschool kid uh
understandable okay yeah thank you for
the uh I uh compliment
yeah yeah no problem no problem yeah
yeah and thank you for the ticket too oh
yeah no problem yeah
okay
okay well happy birthday Kobo thank you
for coming Ryan yeah no problem I hope
you have a really you know great
birthday of course of course I have
because
yeah because of this uh your present too
yeah thank you yeah I hope you get to
play valet with uh the person you want
to play with one day yeah I really want
to play with you
[Laughter]
totally well uh enjoy your enjoy your
birthday yeah thank you Ryan
hey no problem see you ladies bye bye
see you later bye-bye
[Music]
oh my God
okay next person oh that is called
[Music]
Daddy
hi hi
serious
oh
yeah
um
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry
thank you
thank you for coming
thank you thank you
[Applause]
princess visit Japan
I will conduct okay
clear
here
princess
Disney princess okay
also disco
um
okay I will remember okay
okay
I will go to Japan soon
oh yeah next year so go to Disney next
year okay
okay okay okay
[Music]
um
challenge hi challenge
okay
foreign
language
animal language
okay okay
that's cool
it's okay
uh nothing sorry
chicken
huh penguin penguin you know
penguin
it's okay
okay
uh I come back I come back eating with
niceness
[Music]
thank you for coming up
foreign
hahaha
he really drinks yeah
let's go let's go
okay
a nice pink pink with nice
[Music]
foreign
guys
and they talk about this car
it's okay okay okay
very strong nice so arigators
thank you for watching us there thank
you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
I will die
oh my God please don't
die
no
no no no no no no
no bye bye all the time
I got the heaven bye bye auditoris in
peace
bye
no
[Music]
wait
he really gone no bye-bye
he really got no rest in peace
asteroid because of this
this last champagne
this last one for him
bye bye Grand pastel
bye bye Grandpa still
rest in peace
I will remember you forever
[Music]
I mean
anyways anyways we still have another
stream and after this don't forget
there's uh my new cover song will be
premiered like and like it just just
like a few minutes there's like I think
there's uh waiting room already I don't
know and then after that in 11 P.M
just wait for it so I gotta go now don't
forget by the merch too guys manko book
and kobona okay don't forget the merch
don't forget to buy the merch before it
uh it it's gone okay thank you guys
thank you for coming to princess
cookbook birthday stream bye bye
bye see ya see you on the next stream
[Music]
thank you