[Music]
[Applause]
uh-huh
hello
can you hear me let me know how the mic
volume is um
yeah how does the volume sound
no more smoke this time i can't get
betrayed again
i don't know if you can hear but uh
i have some wine with me
two dollars fifty cents from the
convenience store
i believe that's
why
so um in order to uh
flow a bit more smoothly for all of you
um i have had to
set my computer to turbo mode and uh
it's real loud so apologies if you hear
some static in the background when i
speak
it's a very there is no salt situation
um but i'm trying my best for you guys
please please please forgive me please
i'm begging you
but maybe grab a drink or something um
if you feel comfortable
smoke is bad it's it's true and honestly
i couldn't quite figure out the source
of it
where it was coming from apologies kind
of wanted to look like a cool guy there
but
in the end ended up becoming a huge mimi
oh well that's life
huh so did you guys listen oh first of
all uh
i wanted to mention some people were
asking about uh the standby screen
i actually did make that um yeah i don't
really consider myself much of like um
a really good like artist or anything um
but i do like to animate a lot uh just
for fun really
um yeah it was it was fun to draw the
whole gang together
um yeah especially because it's me
chasing them it felt so natural
i mean i wish that i wish that they were
more interested in lethal tag
i've brought it up to them before but
they don't really seem to um
vibe with it i guess no one wants to
play lethal tag with me and i think it's
a shame
um it's a really fun game i used to play
it all the time back when i was in
reaping school
smoke caused the lag yes yes indeed it
was um
her real shame i know when i look back
on my debut it's not going to feel very
great but
such is life i suppose we all make
mistakes
just i make a whole lot of them
today um we're gonna be talking about my
song
um the one that i released uh yesterday
yeah i had to upload it pretty quickly
actually because um
well i'm very honored many people seem
to enjoy it
um but many people also wanted to share
it
on their own channels um which um
did it made me feel great
i'm honored but um it's a little damai
please don't
please don't anyway
no dwelling on the past we're going to
talk about the song today and what you
guys thought of it so what did you think
tell me in the chat i've been getting a
lot of really nice comments
i was worried what people would think
about me but um
potato pc yeah you could say that you
could certainly call it that but
i think that that might change maybe
donate to cali to get 60 fps
that's okay guys i'll figure it out for
you somehow i want it to be better
no i'll do it i can i'm going to take a
big sip of this aqua one real quick
i'm not drinking it out of the bottle if
that's what you think i'm doing
you'd be incorrect it's not
i'm classy yeah i know that rap isn't
really um
everyone's thing and that's fine uh
that's cool
um if it's not your thing uh no problem
um but i've gotten a lot of really nice
comments some people
even say like i'm not a big fan of rap
but i can tell you worked hard and that
in itself is very wonderful i think
and that makes me feel nice
bird
i forgot i forgot that honestly i forgot
that that bird was here
um yeah i suppose that i did
i did invite her to chat about this song
huh
i am now remembering uh
i have to i have to talk to her for a
while
i thought it would be a good idea to
invite my friends um
to talk about my songs but i'm now
realizing that i have to spend some time
chatting with
she's not all that bad she she means
well hey hey
i didn't tell you you could unmute
yourself i didn't tell you you could
okay mama don't call me that's so
strange that is strange i feel strange
when you call me that
i don't mean i don't mean to bully her
it's just she she needs a firm hand
sometimes
swear he needs to learn when to die
you've met too many times
what did you do for the accompaniment
for the song do you mean the the backing
track
oh that was made by um by a great music
producer named kays aka kokorobits
um yeah i highly recommend you check out
his stuff
well let's go ahead and switch the bgm
real quick
to the bgm for the song i made a
loopable version okay um
so kiara you can you can pull yourself
up if you want
come on
[Music]
don't make it weird dude don't make it
weird
[Music]
is her volume okay can i get closer to
you
yeah it's fine you're just not too close
oh i'm just getting closer because the
microphone is there i need to reach it
what are you what are you trying to do
it's not like i want to get close to you
just the microphone ah
oh geez let me know how how the
chicken's volume is everyone please
in the chat section chicken you like
nico wrapper yes
i love nico nicole and uh
yeah big inspiration for me
i prefer not to do that in front of the
people or actually even in private i
wouldn't do it in private with you
either
you don't want to pulling with me
you do it on purpose and i do not that
is the difference between you and me
come on boy come on bye
bye bye bye i cannot do it on command
well you brought your bullying in anyway
even if you don't want it
don't make it weird i already asked you
don't make it weird
hmm starting to have a couple of regrets
what are you looking can you go ahead
and like raise your head up a little bit
my eyes are up here as they do say
i need another sip of this freaking one
while you're sipping can i take a sip
two
nope get your own i actually bought you
a chicken wing
oh what yeah it's in my room yeah one
chicken wing
uh i forgot to actually put it into my
room so i'll kind of just one chicken
yeah just one i mean do you need two
chicken wings you already have two that
you can bring out whenever you want
why do you need why do you need four
four chicken wings or five chicken wings
wait uh well
since you know i eat a 50 free chicken
nuggets per day
so the more the marriott you really need
to be careful about that
why actually just kidding do it
do it the worst that it is for your
health the better it is for me
so please continue it's healthy fast
food is very healthy chicken
meat is very healthy i googled it
you know google yes i am aware of google
i've been using it this entire time to
understand the slang of this generation
and i've become quite good at using it a
lot of the humans
sounds it sounds natural weren't you
making fun of me
in the collab stream and i said nearly
but then then you keep on saying
mimi hey now i now hey listen
the word the word the word melee
is um a very old word that has been used
for a long time
oh mimi is a new word
so give me a little bit of credit okay
and can probably
be pronounced in different ways i'm sure
you are
a boomer is that what you're saying i
that word has lost all meaning to be
honest
in this generation that word doesn't
mean anything anymore
i have a list actually of words that
don't that have completely lost their
meaning
by the way have they lost any meaning
words because you've been
alive for too long and you don't
understand those meanings
no it's not like that it's because
they've been used to death simply
that's about it all that there is to it
i love you
people saying okay boomer in the chat
get out of here
just kidding but mentally i'm like get
out of here please
stay but get out of here would you make
would you mind making yourself a bit
smaller or maybe not looking at me in
that fashion
and maybe like raise yourself up a
little bit
off the ground please and i'm begging
you i'm
i'm seriously begging you okay that's
fine
no i'm not it's not
[Music]
really don't like i don't dislike when
the humans call me that but you it's a
little weird
um what did you think of the song you
are here to tell me
your impressions right
i have a lot of impression but first of
all let me say
um my papa look at papa uh he's been
listening to your song
non-stop i saw that yeah
that is so that is absolutely
crazy to me because um i actually
i've been a very big fan of your your
papa since
before uh i began youtuber activities
back when i was simply killing folks
and the slashing throats and that kind
of stuff um
i used to be a big fan of this artwork
so well
who is not a big fan of my papa true
yeah okay
but honestly i think everyone loves this
song so much i also really do
it's like i don't know you're you're
like super cool
rapping like that but you're also sexy
yeah
what i don't know why
it's so that's that that strong vibe you
give off
is so sexy but i don't know i
mean i feel like maybe it should be more
feminine or something
but i can't really control it i just
kind of don't really like if
we were a couple which we secretly are
uh
we're not i'm clarifying we're not we're
not we're not a couple just so you guys
know
um that's not a true fact slander
slander
whatever yeah i mentioned that too by
the way
in um you know in the song one of the
most uh favorite parts i think not only
for me
it's the moment when you cough and
you're like [\h__\h] it
well i mean in in fairness i
i did go through a bit of a dilemma
right deciding well how i should present
myself
as an entertainer uh it is natural that
right you should in the beginning
perhaps think that you need to play
some kind of character right and so
that is kind of how i approached it
in the beginning when i started writing
lyrics i thought i'll be very cute
i'll be a cute idol rapper that will do
like
very very high high pitched and cute
sounding
rhymes but as i wrote i realized that um
it was the same feeling i get the same
feeling wrapping as i do when reaping
uh the the intense longing
to uh f wording kill everyone
just f wording slay everyone in my path
in my vicinity
and uh when i get that feeling it's
impossible for me to be overly cute
you can't hide it it's okay you weren't
able to hide it for long
but uh i wanted to i've i'm
still even now and i want to be clear
i feel as though i'm not i don't really
feel like i'm
i'm pretend pretending per se any longer
but i am attempting to reel myself in a
bit
because i feel like if i'm 100
um hardcore all the time
um not only is that
uncomfortable for others but it's also
uncomfortable for me because i don't
want to be that way
everyone has to wheel themselves in
sometimes you don't want to be that way
then why are you always shitty to me
well because i can be myself around you
duh
okay you can't and i don't mean that in
a super
complimentary way or anything i thought
that was very romantic what you just
said it's not romantic it's a fact
don't take what i said out of context
well the fact is romantic
okay let's move on
what i wanted to say um
you are one you wrote those lyrics
yourself right
i did i did i have to write them myself
i it was so hard for me to follow along
because it's so
quick and there's so many words i get
that a lot actually but the the thing
that i got out of it was a lot of [\h__\h]
and
i don't know the rest i forgot but it's
nice that you can simply say that word
in speech and
not feel terrible well you also don't
feel terrible about it do you
i have to say it under my breath a bit
because i i worry about making others
uncomfortable
i genuinely do that this isn't this
isn't a show or an act i genuinely worry
about it
a long time ago i saw i saw um
a fellow shall i say co-worker of ours
and i won't say anything
to discern anyone i used such such an f
word
um and people were quite angry and that
made me quite a feared of what might
happen to me in the future music is one
thing and i think that
everyone is well aware of that right
that music is
is a special case yes
but how did you how do you
write so many lyrics how do you come up
with so many lyrics
ah it's strange if i'm in the right mood
i can write an entire song in maybe 30
minutes
but if i'm not i guess in uh the
murdering mindset shall we call it it
might take me about a week to write um
one verse didn't you write this
one pretty quickly yes i had to actually
the production time was
very very very
it was it was tight yeah well i think it
turned out amazing you can't really
notice that you didn't have much time
thank you i did like some lines and some
i didn't like so much but
however you do you realize that
your japanese is having some
mistakes in there you should tell me
about them
but the thing is i only noticed like of
course like after you already wrote them
you need to like let them go for a check
through
for me first oh really if you're saying
when you said
uh
why do you not use why do you not use no
do you know the reason behind it is it
just like
uh it's just like that it's just feels
simply grammatically incorrect
it is yeah it'd just be like that at
least
what other what other mistakes did i
make i'm curious
uh i already forgot i don't know i said
not the only one that really uh
came to my kind of stood out to you i
have a really small
short attention span yeah well what's
interesting to me actually is as a big
fan of japanese rap myself
um i also enjoy a fair few
uh japanese rap crews and japanese
rappers that love to use english in
their music
and i don't want to be rude because it's
not it's not an insult to them
but a hundred percent of the time their
songs are fraught with english mistakes
and that's fine
because i find myself myself still
vibing to them in my room yeah right
i'll start singing out the lyrics even
though they're in completely botched
english
i will shout out the lyrics uh in said
terrible grammatical fashion because
it sounds fun so i'm hoping that
japanese don't mind so much
[Music]
actually
oh we have to talk about something
though
hmm when you when you first gave me a
listen to that song
uh-huh uh i listened to it i was like
this song is [\h__\h] fire and i was like
can you give me the lyrics because i
it's too fast i just wanted like read
along
and then he sent me the lyrics and then
i read them
and then i noticed in the lyrics
you are hiding a certain sentence
ah you didn't pick it up actually
i i did very much pick it up it did say
uh what was it die [\h__\h] bird
come on come a little closer then laugh
at me
ah that was it that was it
well you are no
you are a [\h__\h] bird oh no you are an
s word s word bird hey
sounds like some bars no but actually
listen um
you thought i wouldn't notice listen it
makes perfect sense
because i don't know what a masochist is
but i have a bad feeling about it and i
think that you would laugh at me about
it
so in that case i'd like you to come a
little bit closer
so you can so we can be real close
and um i can put my scythe directly up
to your throat
and we can do the same thing that we've
done thousands of times
throughout history if you would please
kindly
okay now you've pushed it a little bit
too far
swerved you said come closer swerve
swerve i'm on hiatus i can't actually
kill you right now swerve yeah get away
from me get away get away get away get
away i'm calling the police i'm calling
the police get away from me
move move get a move on it's doing me a
big scare dead serious
dead serious but um i have to say like
even though
you're trying to diss me like even
though this is basically a diss
track against me uh i do
feel like you were putting me in there
because you secretly deeply love me
look we've been over this before
correct about the fact that you and i
will always have different morals
i will never understand why it is that
you think it's okay to keep coming back
to life instead of simply
accepting that life is over and coming
down to the underworld
right i don't understand how you don't
understand that death is the highest
honor
i feel like a lot of people why do you
not understand
you also don't die we're the same we're
just saying we should let's because i
don't
i i don't have life in me i don't i
don't have the same existence as
beings that are alive i'm a concept i
don't function the same as you
it's like that we are made for each
other
i don't think so i would have to hard uh
hard disagree with you on that one
as they say hard disagree you've been
disagreeing with me
for millions of years but i feel
you're actually disagreeing with me you
love me you want to see me every time
and that's actually
why you joined whole life because you
were sick of only seeing me every couple
of hundred thousand years
so and that's why you went on hiatus
because you wanted to see me more you
wanted to stop
raping people you wanted to join whole
life just like me so we can have
conversations like this i know
you cannot deny it 100 not even not even
within the range of being close to being
correct on that one hate to break it to
you
what does the chat say i think that
sounds pretty legit what do you think
chat that's i don't like it
i don't like the proven theory
whatever you say men keep deluding
yourself
well chad is agreeing i would say
okay fine freaking rolls my eyes into
the back of my head
aren't you like lonely sometimes i mean
i wouldn't say
lonely i i mean i mean yeah i don't
really have any
i'm not crying i'm not sad about it i'm
used to i have
lived for an eternity without friends
until i met all of you
and it's been fine but it has certainly
been nice
to get to know other other beings i
suppose
as it is guys there we go that's the
data that's the delay
i don't understand what that means i
literally don't know what that word
means it's you
it's sunday that's you okay
just take it just accept it it's you
it's really it's just dude i don't know
if i should trust you though
just introduce yourself hello record
to say hello i am i think i won't do
that because i don't understand the word
completely
i don't want to embarrass myself you
must understand
i guess you gotta go to japanese lesson
with me
i really do need to get better at
japanese i know that a lot
of you are probably laughing at me but
you're doing a japanese lesson stream
though right tomorrow yes tomorrow i do
have one
a japanese
i don't know if it will be japanese or
english band though just because
i don't i don't want to alienate the
english viewers as well i want everyone
to have fun together
yeah yeah it's like that wait but
you're teaching japanese to english
viewers right oh no
no this is for all of us to learn
japanese together i don't think i'm in a
position to teach japanese
yeah you're also going to learn japanese
at the same time
yes
you could teach japanese but i i think
i'll just stick to learning streams
oh yeah i'm teaching you the first
important word it's tsundere
and then there's one more word that
describes my feelings
towards you it's scotch coin i
i actually don't know what the f word
that means
god i hate saying my god
hey no no no hold on swerve you can't do
that
swerve we've done it before didn't we
nope we haven't i don't know
i don't don't stop trying to fool them
you're giving them false information i
don't know what she's talking about
forget what she said
oh yeah i'll stop time
i shall follow your orders i like when
you ordered me
fine whatever we still have one last
thing to do oh yeah
so a lot of people have been posting
some lovely content involving both you
and i
that i find to be rather humorous and i
wanted to take a look at it together
unfortunately i could not grab the
credits in time but i will be reading
them
um off of off of twitter i believe
is where i found the credit it might be
a little
uh a little difficult to manage um
i need to go back into my likes but it's
it's hard to do because if i do so then
i will stop moving here
so give me just a moment everyone we're
going to go to standby for just a moment
yay okie dokie
here we go
fashion
fish
i hate everything man
we've already ruined the surprise ladies
and gentlemen take a look behind the
curtain won't you
i'm bad at preparing for these things
sasukami kalaipimori who ruins
everything i touch
that's freaking sasuka all right well
it looks like that was shocking already
that's right let me try and at least
cover my tracks
idiot no wait i'm revealing more
gosh you can tell who it really isn't
used to streaming
anyway this is my favorite oh my gosh
yeah i've been on for the sake of that
look okay for the sake of not getting
like being allowed to be monetized
this isn't blood it it's ketchup right
people love or actually no it's barbecue
sauce
people love barbecue sauce with chicken
correct especially on
chicken yes so in this case
uh in this case i would have to say um
the what is coming out of your mouth is
barbecue sauce
it makes sense it makes sense because
like you hit me from behind and then i
i spewed out because i just ate too much
chicken with barbecue it makes sense
amazing
it does it do make sense let me see if i
can find the source so that people can
can enjoy this on their own as well um
i'll try and
maybe oh i just don't understand what
what that even means because like
i didn't get like why do i show up again
in danny's is that because i revived
again
i suppose so that's the only explanation
that i can come up with
and you're like is she gone now is she
is she finally gone
like behind you oh my god
kiki ricky man bleeding
geez anyway this is by at
yo ain't on on twitter it's at
y o h underscore e
i e n let me see if i can type into the
chat my glasses are going to float for
just a moment but please excuse me
okay you like the look i'm giving
this is so
right but it's funny
uh it's very uh yeah
[Music]
yeah i mean i think it's quite accurate
as
how things usually go with you and i
yeah but usually i die by myself
it's true but occasionally i have a hand
even you can't deny that at least back
in the day when i was allowed to reap
that's why we fit so many times i
suppose
you were not very effective okay well
that's not exactly my fault is it now
throw shade when you actually are able
to throw shade into
the great great amazing
invincible strong depth and you can't
even
yes well i am all of those things
don't get me wrong i am all of those
things but
listen man you are a special case okay
there are some forces of nature that i
simply cannot go against
that is the truth as such as love
between us
that's absolutely incorrect we're going
to move on to the next uh image
this isn't an artwork this made me laugh
so hard
what is going on here yeah what is
happening i don't know but but
amelia is there so i was like this is
good i'm sure someone in chat will know
where this is from
but it gave me i mean i think maybe
amelia knows
why is amelia i just love the look on
your
certainly though if you go and look
through my likes everyone which i'm fine
with
i have nothing to hide you may have
trouble though because i try to like
every single comment
or every single reply in some of my
tweets sometimes
so you'll really just end up scrolling
through endless text
endless endless texts if you want to
find the uh the good stuff
but
i've spent too much time on reddit
it's really bad but that the stuff that
they post there is really great
uh refresh to stream refresh i yeah i
know
i think your internet connection is a
blog because i also
know your voice was kind of getting
robot
hold on a minute it says excellent
connection on youtube
oh that's gone yeah it says excellent
excellent as your shitty piece
hey now pc and internet are good for us
hold on why you need to get both to
understand
read back some say yeah i think yeah
speedtest.net good weekly good you're
good
excuse me for that everyone
refresh underworld internet i tell you
what and you know what's the most
annoying part is i'm actually paying a
lot of money
i'm paying so much money for this
internet that's supposed to be
good there are some things that you said
i gave it to you for
free f you'll just kill them if i don't
give a good internet
oh jeez goodness gracious
um yeah it's gone again but honestly i
see it stream
it's smooth for me but everyone else
says it's gone
gosh speed test let me do a speed test
god why let's see
ping is good ping is at 12. download
speed is
fine 28.
[Music]
you even hear me it's okay now you're
fine now excuse me everyone
i don't know what's going i i'm supposed
to have good internet i'm spending i
hear you yes
spending so much money upload speed is
35. huh
bizarre it has to be youtube [\h__\h] i
i i'm is it i feel like
if it wasn't youtube [\h__\h] then i
wouldn't even be able to hear you
because i hear you loud and clear
very strange very very strange
oh okay but you sound robotic to me oh
jeez
sorry about that everyone well we're
almost done anyway we're just going to
look at a couple more um
this is from reddit and i can't find
this
wait hold on i bet i can because i saved
i saw this one it's really funny this is
perfect
perfectly describes our relationship we
said
that uh yeah oh yeah of course because
we're working together as you
see how how we work together here yes
how we typically go for our pistons
ridiculous but also very accurate to us
i would have to say i'm going to find
the source for this
i will not allow this to go unsourced
because this is magnificent and that's
super cool wrapper pose on you
it's it's so good yes very accurate to
me
here i have to go to my saved post
ah let's see
see i actually don't know how to use
reddit i've never actually really
used it before now to be completely
honest
uh yes posted by you
surami oh i'm not gonna read this hold
on it's just too
confusing i'll post it in chat here i'm
gonna my glasses will float for but a
moment
oh oh you're right then okey dokey
yeah big kusa big
kusa i love these i love these sounds
on stream i thought so too yeah i feel
like kiara's voice is coming through
loud and clear i don't know what's going
on i don't i don't know it
can't be my internet but it must be
maybe i'll check out my encoder settings
later but thank goodness this didn't
happen during the debut
uh uh let's see
all right let's just do a couple more
this we got from senpai nico senpai
i was so happy about this when i saw
that it's so tall but since she's
writing this daily and she's writing her
diaries and they're so adorable and i
was so surprised when she wrote about us
it's so adorable we can we can talk in
elite english very soon
yes surely
yeah i think you can really teach her
some good english
probably
my songs
i know enough that's always what what
japanese acquaintances will tell me is
i'll say my my nihongo is very hetero
and they will say you know enough
and that's like the biggest backhanded
compliment you can ever receive from
someone right
it's enough um
that's good enough well it's elite
nihongo elite indeed
let's see another meme i love this this
is because
someone was drawing pictures of all the
other girls right
and i guess they i i don't this man
didn't draw us
he's f-worded um i wonder if it's
if it's because the picture seems to be
less serious than the others
kana i'm not sure but this made me
big koosa big time thank you
big waddle it's the first time i see
this w w w
w w w w
you all better draw the d how do you
call it oftp
otp otp i know that from
my days my back in the day fun times
that i have also had on the internet
oh you know this one huh i do i do i
know so i
do know some slang because there was a
time in my existence where i was
i was a bit more hip with the time yes
all right excuse my glasses one moment
otp what does it stand for again
original wait uh original troop a one
true pairing one true pairing
ah we see i indeed the one true pairing
uh i don't know about that i'd have to
argue it with you on that one this one's
by harutemu
haru tim my man's haru tim
on twitter check him out
okay last last because if if people
start having trouble again
um with the lag i'm gonna get mad
hopefully it doesn't happen again
especially if i'm not in call with
someone but i don't know i don't know
what's going on youtube
is more cinderella than i am apparently
not like i know what that means because
i don't know what it means
i'm gonna continue on anyway um
this is super cute i will say i will say
it's indicative of our relationship
not like i like it too much
sight is like backstabbing me exactly
yeah that's the part that i like the
most believe it or not thank you so much
that i enjoy the most about that's how
you that's
how you pay back all the love i give you
you backstabbed me
yes as it were yes this is by cc
silverheart or i'll type uh the
the name into the chat excuse my glasses
here we go oysha
this is so adorable i love it awesome
thank you i want it as a sticker or
something
can you sell that as stickers i would do
that
you can't but you can certainly give
them away
i'll make my own sticker out of it i
print it out and i put it on my forehead
okay well that's
fine geez
i mean the the back setting part is not
ready today but but
the hugging part is very pity
whatever man oh it looks like we've
actually just hit the
45 minute mark good because i'm getting
tired
and i'd like to continue drinking this
one not in your company no offense or
anything
but you know i can only take so much of
you right
why i can never get enough of it
that's the reason why you answered your
own question
um but but kelly
oh god i i
i say anything weird on stream we we're
no strangers to love
you know the rules and so do i all right
we're going to end the stream right here
so thank you for coming
by livestream we wouldn't get this from
any other guy oh my god i just want to
tell you how i'm feeling
i gotta make you understand yep i'm
never gonna give you up
got it i'm not gonna let you down
understood
they're looking around around and they
search you
okay okay okay got it
we're done no more
god can you leave my house i mean thanks
for coming and all that
like i appreciate it but can you get out
of my house now
okay all right peace
all right let me let me kick her
yeah mute yourself mute yourself as you
exit my house
thanks all right well she's gone
i still have a couple i have some small
announcements to make
well not really announcements more like
things that you already know
so let's see ah yes
i'm in the way of the information of
course i'm releasing my debut ep this
week
um but the times for like our chatting
streams
about each song uh they vary by day
um or not by day rather
the time is varying right um but they'll
probably be around the same time
um which is i suppose this time actually
every day except for thursday i'll post
this on my twitter
so that you can get a better look at it
as well as my schedule for the week
because i'll also be doing some other
streams unrelated to music as well and
you can check those out
so yeah um i hope that you'll enjoy the
ep
uh i'm not i'm really not best track
maker i consider myself more of an
arranger because
i use so many samples um which i will
also link the sources to of course
in every video um but
it was really fun to kind of experiment
on my own um
in fact tonight i'm such a
procrastinator i actually have to finish
mixing some of them
i'm quite busy i did all of the
recordings a long time ago
but then when we had to start get
getting ready for debut everything got
so crazy
yeah it was a lot but i want to make
sure it's great for you guys
so yeah spotify uh that's a little
difficult right now unfortunately
uh just because there are certain things
that i need to check
um with my agency hold alive um
so i need once i can figure that out
we'll be good but the ep will be free
for streaming on youtube
for sure and we're looking through
different options but i want to make
sure that everyone can listen to it
completely freely
um i don't want to charge you guys for
it or anything because you don't even
really know if you'll you'll like my
stuff yet or not so
but yeah
anyway um i really hope that you'll have
fun
listening and um tomorrow's song uh i'm
actually going to have another guest
my dear friend gooda good at a shark
ah so they say god i hate it i hate it
i i mean it's it's it's fine for her but
i can't
i can't say it with the same level of
charm that she does you see
it's like that i suppose oh
gouda is great he's very cute i will say
and so small i kind of wish i was that
small sometimes
he's tiny i want to put her on my
shoulders someday
we ran around huh i wonder if that's
kind of weird
it's probably kind of weird huh anyway
moving along gude will be joining me and
we'll be listening to my chico shokai
wrap
i have a recorded version for everyone
to enjoy uh that's a lot more high
quality than me just doing it by myself
so yeah um
the beats i made actually just with
everything in my house
i looked around my house and i thought
to myself
uh perhaps i will beatbox and find
different
things in my house to use as the
instrumentation
so i think that you might find it to be
a bit interesting
if anything interesting even if you
aren't a big fan of the music which is
fine
but yes it's like that
so yeah i think that'll be fun and then
the
the third track i'm going to just review
with you guys by myself is
rather chaotic it's a chaotic one
um and the fourth song will be my ending
theme
for all of my live streams afterward um
and the guest for
that is a secret right now i'll reveal
it later after that i have the
instrumental and acapella of my main
song that i will be releasing because
we're doing something really really cool
um
and you won't know about it until friday
but just get ready because
it's going to be really fun um so yeah
it's like that
for now um i'm going to go drink another
bottle of red wine and navy chill
because this weekend has been chaos i
would say
i think it's fair to say that myself and
the girls have been going through quite
a bit
um but thank you everyone for being very
kind and understanding to us
as we're really just kind of getting
used to this stuff
so yeah cantaloupe summer all right it's
time for me to end the stream
um at that that is where we will leave
off the street
why with the cantaloupes man come on
like of all
of all the fruits it doesn't even taste
good
just a bad fruit well enjoy your sunday
maury thank you
that's very kind i'll try i'll try to
i shouldn't be drinking it this time but
i feel like it is necessary
so rest well okay guys will you all take
care of yourselves and make sure that
you're drinking
and drinking lots of fluids especially
alcohol
just kidding or maybe maybe i'm not
kidding
drink lots of alcohol for me and if it
feels like it's too much keep going
maybe we'll meet pretty soon just
kidding don't do that please don't take
my advice
i'm not allowed to be reaping at this
time and i don't want to get in big
trouble with death sensei so actually
please take care of yourself
and with that i suppose i'll sign off
alrighty guys well this has been fun
and um so yeah with that uh i'm your
mori and i hope you'll remember me see
you around everyone bye-bye
see ya bye
peace
[Music]
you