[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
a
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
the a
[Music]
[Applause]
n
a
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
oh oh oh
oops surprised I was
muted K Kitty once
again
yay
Kitty hello we are so back to play more
Minecraft
hey and we are going straight to bed as
we we are so
motivated yay oh three people joined the
game at once they're all starting the
stream
probably uh let me make this window size
[Music]
good today I am once again night but
today I put on my weapon in the back
doesn't it look nice just having that in
the back already makes me look so cool
like OMG
[Music]
yeah okay so today we'll fight the end
of dragon today is the day the finale is
finally
here I can't hear my effects either wait
what I I I I changed some
things H what
what did you hear it
[Laughter]
oh there it is okay got it got
it uh honestly I don't think we really
need to prepare
anything uh but uh we W we're not going
for a little bit so we can try to
prepare something I just don't really
know
what wait a
second f Last
Words feather fall potions ah I have the
feather falling
boots um let's see if there's still some
slow falling potions that would help
right end up9 or they keep ah okay okay
uh should I should have like
two I should have two by the way P had a
good laugh out of my
uh uh reference that nobody noticed the
[Laughter]
chickens that was one of the things she
laughed the hardest about let me just
say it that way
[Music]
okay okay donating some ender pearls cuz
she's saying she needs
[Laughter]
[Music]
more y
she can't go out there with iron armor
she's got to go get some uh Diamond at
least please okay we have
strength slow falling there's a lot of
slow falling I'm sure they prepared this
with the fight in
mind so should I take a couple of these
then we're
good although even then like I don't
remember even using slow falling potions
really did I in our end of dragon fight
I'll just take five I
guess or or or just four
okay I won't be needing the golden
helmet anymore either right wait I wait
I think my important things are in the
Ender Chest right because I I hid them
there in case my house was going to be
attacked
[Music]
yeah more golden apples would be also
cool but no no no we don't need it we we
don't we didn't really even need it
yesterday and
yeah
yeah some water buckets and never
scaffold would be great to climb Towers
oh yeah neck will probably be good
enough scaffolding not that necessary
maybe but water buckets yeah to like
fall down
or to protect myself from the Ender
right cuz there's a lot of Enderman
right right right right right right
right soda
soda let's get some milk uh water blue
milk as they like to call it in the wild
west I finished watching The Fallout
yesterday
man I'm sad it's already over but it was
really really interesting at the end
he's like I see he I won't say who but
he's walking towards New Vegas I had to
Google though I had to Google where did
he
go uh at the end and because I didn't
recognize it but players would recognize
it interesting N I don't want to play
with pumpkin head it like I don't like
how much it obstructs my view really I
guess I I probably don't need so many
water buckets but I could give it to
others if they need it
um yeah what was the other thing we're
not going to get get
elytras because the game ends after we
kill Ender
Dragon they're closing the server today
like right after around 11:00 p.m.
probably yeah I want to have never my
never right armor
on but yeah New Vegas I the show man I I
I can already
sense um due to where Maximus is
now
that even though he still wants to help
her there will probably be
misunderstandings because of certain
things he will have to do in order to
help her that will seem evil to her from
her POV and she'll be thinking like oh
that bastard he's he's not loyal to me
anymore he's [\h__\h] me over and then
she'll get really angry and there will
be like a lot
of difficult
situations uh that will arise due to
that I can literally sense it and smell
it she's a bit morally flexible at the
end I think
why
why but oh my God the the whole reveal
with the ghouls you know
the
ghouls
uh uh is
wow okay so the
brain
is the one that was sitting in one of
those chairs
right and oh my God that that oh the ah
the brother ah the
brother oh oh no like he was so brave
though to like check everything out I
also had to Google like cuz I didn't
really understand in the end what
happened to Vault
32 so now I understand um I feel like
they kind of left it vague in the show
as
well like what actually happened cuz
they weren't sure either like oh this is
weird they strangled each other what
happened so I guess there was like Civil
War says Google but doesn't mean there
was Civil War within the Vault they just
like were like unhappy with how things
were
going
so ooh and the Sandy
[Music]
Shore there's so much stuff man oh that
was like shocking and exciting and
yeah it was a good show I hope they
bring out a new uh season soon hope they
don't wait too long the video that all
no I found one thing really interesting
when they were involved four was it and
they were like yo what's your experiment
and and and Lucy is like M what do you
mean we don't have an
experiment and for the longest time I
thought yeah they don't have an
experiment until the very end until they
revealed
ah it doesn't seem like an experiment to
them but not at
all but the [\h__\h] ideas they came up
with in that table round where they were
like oh we could have this kind of
experiment oh we could have this kind of
experiment what the what the [\h__\h] that
doesn't even make sense like some of
those didn't even make sense like are
you
serious I want to find out more about
more vaults do you learn about more
vaults in New Vegas or do you not like
learn anything about them so say some
totem she's selling totems for 100
diamonds I don't have them oh wait how
many diamonds did I get uh probably not
that many she's selling totems from 100
diamonds I was wondering why so many
people had
diamonds h
I'd like one but n whatever doesn't
matter no need it's last day if I die I
die I got 20
[Music]
more so I can't afford it but I could
ask her if she will give me one for 50
diamonds there's nothing else I have use
for it for right
[Music]
wait what did you guys
say summon Lord summon
Quest there are more Vault LS but New
Vegas is more about above ground
politics there were two vaults where one
was 99 women and one man and the other
hand had 99 men men and one woman oh my
God what kind of experiments are
those I feel
like they would end up killing the one
other gender
person there's a ton of wacky ones it's
so [\h__\h]
weird so [\h__\h] weird man why why like
it doesn't even make sense what are you
going to do with that experiment what
what do you like the one from the the
free connected vaults makes sense
because they have the
that motive
but
uh for science that's but that's just
dumb that's not the kind of science that
we really
need right
like and did suicide sampai revive the
farm I wonder if she's like still
working on it today she was put in
charge of the farm after she died I
guess and this just a ghost
farmer but let's see if there's some
more food there
now the chickens were revived oh no they
were not revived they grew from the
flowers that I planted for
sure a so many
too oh that's nice to see the cows are
back to it's all like it never ever
happened what we saw
yesterday uh oh my God there's even more
chests than before
[Music]
I'll
take a couple
more
maybe a few
potatoes
yeah the power of the community
yay what's
this that was wasn't that supposed to be
a uh grave but oh no it's here then what
is this qu a
NY no this is n grave wait what what's
with EA's
grave I thought this was supposed to be
it when is the fight uh I think we're
going to look for the the thingy in 40
minutes remnant of old home yeah she
revived but still like even for for the
revived people
they get to keep uh the the graves
usually stay who is there what are they
[Music]
doing
e
for okay
okay was that snow
before ah
[Music]
for okay she wants to make uh a pun by
making a tofu house because there is
some pun she can make but I destroyed
the floor
apparently it was like on the last
[Music]
day hi
hie
fore
fore okay
[Music]
oh I didn't know that would happen she
was like oh you can you can uh tease her
all you want now because she's AFK and I
was like M I don't want to punch her
but because I'm too strong but how do I
that's the grave how do I tease her and
I thought a the
buckets it's okay they'll fix it
um she said there that she's going to
buy one of the totems and also she said
there's golden ah
there oh she said there will be many but
there's not that many left I guess some
people
took took a bunch M just one
then just one is okay then I have
sixs hi babies how you doing let me feed
you a little bit this is what you eat
right I forgot oh yeah you do oh you
totally eat
this are you eating are you eating I
feel like I only am using my shield is
this working yeah okay ah there for the
babies for the babies
oh you know yesterday I cooked the like
a curry green curry with a paste oh that
I had from Thailand and I used a green
curry paste and I used so much more
coconut milk
than one would usually use because even
after like 500
uh Mill of a gram of coconut milk it it
was still so spicy so I added like
another like 250 or
so she it was still spicy even after
that and I also added some brown sugar
because in the recipe that I had which
was just a simple one you know I don't
have like Thai Basil and all that stuff
where the [\h__\h] do I get that from just
used a more like simple recipe the brown
sugar I added to uh it helped a little
bit I feel like to make it more sweet
kind of Curry Greek yogurt I didn't have
any yeah normally I think back in the
day when I was leaving with Mommy in
order to make it less spicy I think she
was adding like cream fresh and stuff
like that some kind of
cream I don't know how many calories it
was in total but I didn't have such a
big potion and I made it with like some
Bean
thingies uh and uh bell pepper and
turkey turkey meat not chicken because
turkey has less fat fat
right bell
pepper yeah that's pretty much I added
some more spring onions and stuff too it
super good though but like the spiciness
uh it it gets even worse because of the
temperature of the food I feel like so
my nose was r running really badly and I
was
going the whole
time but it was yummy though no no
potato hi
anaa what are what are you doing
generally right now how are you
preparing yourself just taking out my
diamonds are you buying a totem I'm
pretty much done I'm pretty much done oh
no I only have 24 diamonds only 24 okay
I also don't have enough
yeah so no token FR I mean it's last day
if we die we die yeah I don't think
we'll die though she going to she's
going to revive us anyways today Ana
today will be the last day that we talk
to each other for a long
time yeah I was thinking about that wait
when's your birthday when's your
birthday again ah in
July oh I guess I'll talk to you in two
months then yeah I'll talk to you in if
you if do talk you then I'll probably
talk to you I think so okay next time
I'll talk to you it's probably around
then
okay okay so but still today we shall
treat it as our last day together ever
yeah
true
true goodbye see you see you in my next
life yeah probably hate you in my next
life I'll hate you in every
life yeah me too
good luck you
too good luck byebye wonder what what
Ena is
doing it's probably trying to enchant
things did she get did she get uh any
neite in the
[Music]
end love hate all the same if you want
play the game I'm locked up up I can
fight the feeling and I will
try I'm going to miss Ana
yeah I haven't talked to
Ana like so much over the course of
several days in a
while oh one more thing yesterday for
the first time uh I really used my not
just tested but used my running machine
my
treadmill for the first time yesterday
after dinner after everything I'm glad I
did it after everything because that was
so tiring and I have like zero stamina I
couldn't do it for too long um according
to the running machine I burned like 70
calories which is probably
nothing no I mean it's something but
like in terms of time I was like
sometimes I was walking then I was
running then I was walking then I was
running and then I was like [\h__\h] dead
and the moment I stepped off of the
treadmill I noticed my my legs were
absolute jelly and I was like wobbly I
was like what the [\h__\h] is is
happening I got pretty sweaty though so
it's
good I
think it was it it it felt satisfying
and kind of fun not the best idea to
exercise after eating e
why why because you feel so
full make it hard as you get used to
well I was mostly walking and then I was
just running for as long as I really
felt comfortable
[Music]
[Laughter]
she offered for me to get into her boat
but it's already
there hello what's up I I was wondering
uh where did your hair go
and did you do the my hand did you do
the Bold thing I
did well actually I wanted to ask you
what what you have been up
to oh I'm trying to get do you have some
red stone no nothing okay well I'm
trying to get some Redstone and then
trade for some ender
pearls is a Trader for end Pearl end
Pearls do we still not have
enough oh no no no it's just for my use
[Music]
oh
okay a ah yeah I don't know if many
people will be using the potion machine
still but yeah she could get it from the
potion
machine oh she she was speaking
English thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
gave her my last Emeralds cuz I don't
think I need them got to give it to
someone who needs them
[Music]
the carrot of Happiness yes should give
me a carrot well I'll eat it right
away just takes up a spot in my
inventory so yeah I think I'll try my
best on the running machine to gather
more stamina and go further and further
Beyond yum Galu G
un
return I don't know I wouldn't get my
hopes
up so what do you think am I ready I
have a few slow falling potions I have
the water buckets I have some I can get
some more building
blocks and I have some food I have my
weapons I am fully Enchanted and never
right I don't think I could be any more
prepared
really
okay okay let's get this the blocks
easy easy easy
easy I was watching pea senpai's uh News
stream
again and she was mentioning how easy
the wiow was and that maybe the Ender
Dragon would also be super
easy like she was already hinting that
that might
happen
so for
[Music]
oh oh yeah I apologized to her she was
like ah no
problem H I love her voice I love her
energy I really like her design too like
oh my God I love everything about
her I need to collab do we need a boat
in the oh we could sit Enderman in to it
what if we
all what is there a strat where you put
boats all over the whole like area of
you know where the fight is like
everything everything is
there cuz then I guess they would all be
forced to sit if you if you absolutely
plaster and cover everything in
boats I I just realized how genius that
is wow
so
um yeah never is is L should be fine
right it's pretty fast to like get rid
of it
[Music]
again a the pickaxe we can no wait I
need it I need it I need it
[Music]
one
chicken welcome to the
world you are now my pet chicken for a
really short amount of time yes yes yes
yes do you want to come with me to the
to the Ender Dragon can
you Jimbo Jimbo
oh I have some more I could make you
some sisters and brothers but
nah
nah yeah I'm ready I'm so ready
wait I'll try to bring him along but I'd
have to carry the thing in my hand the
whole
[Music]
time take him with you I want to he will
totally not be baited it will totally
not be emergency food either what are
you doing running around get back in
there get back in there
no do the pumpkin seeds work as
well look at this you want that don't
you well let's test it with you you're
going to follow me from so far no that's
where it stops yeah well that might not
work
huh that might not work if if I I have
to be so
careful
yeah that might not work sorry chicken
bur a
leash a
leash how do you make a
leash probably Lea or strings lead
Le oh those are the things you can't uh
make yourself right
[Music]
slime ball and a string that's so much
effort now we're going to leave in 20
minutes minutes I don't think I have a
slime
[Music]
bowl no Slimes like not even the magma
slimes right get them fishing
too
fishing
fishing true maybe there's some actually
like some leftover
lead at the fishing house
[Music]
no
nah maybe Kyla has
one Kyla seems like she might have
one his insect should be to follow his
lead Val Le exactly like you guys but
Jimbo is still young he was just born he
doesn't get it he was born with like
half the brain cell that you guys have
unfortunately not my house I knew that I
just wanted to look
[Music]
inside for
you begging you don't need a
totem I
mean but you know the fomo no you I
don't have one even you're in freaking
neide and you're Enchanted too you don't
need
it you know what you might
need yeah what water buckets diamonds
water buckets oh oh yeah oh yeah do you
know should I explain it to
you oh yeah yeah okay it's not even for
falling down it's for keeping the the
Endermen away from you when you
accidentally looked at them they will
all chase you so you just pour a water
bucket around yourself and then they
can't reach you cuz they're afraid of
water yeah okay but also so do I just do
I just like click on the water bucket at
like random places like this but you can
pick it up again if you pick it up then
nothing will happen but otherwise you
know
oh yeah and then you can let it spread
out and you stand in it and then they
can't touch
[Music]
you see you can pick it up again at the
source right right right nice okay okay
okay I see I see protect yourself thank
you thank you m don't look at them in
the eye you want give your diamonds to
me uh I mean you don't need to to
[Music]
them oh she wants to trade
she needs 34
[Music]
diamonds I think I have that
amount I'm not going to give it to Anna
because she needs way
more I can give her the rest n
[Music]
that's so that's so messed
up up that's so messed
up when it's me you give what bucket but
when it's her you give Diamonds oh thank
you
[Music]
for
okay I'm giving away all my valuables to
people who think they need it
more power on your power yet power on my
bow or on my ah on my
sword no that's
okay I don't need anything else power on
my bow no it's okay don't need
it already
strong W already strong
strong why do I have this
button
[Music]
um there she goes I want to buy the
totem I can't believe P like Ana was
like kind of like appealing uh to P by
because she was saying like oh I did so
many translations you should give me
more diamonds please
uh and she was like well you know yeah
I'm really grateful for that but I can't
give you that many like cuz she said she
needed like over 70 or so she said if
you get 90 diamonds together by begging
to people uh then I might be able to
give you the remaining
10 that means she would not have given
me a 50% discount either on the already
discounted
price I would have not been able to buy
it with my 50 diamonds anyway
so much bargaining they'll see it's
going to be easy unless she spawns I'll
be [\h__\h] if she spawns free Ender
Dragons let's just say it that
way I'll be [\h__\h]
[Music]
mhm okay let's put this here see I'm
going to I'm going to stack it like
this going to stack it just like that
maybe I can give some more buckets
[Music]
away free to Kyla is selling totems too
probably for a cheaper
price
o o then I could have maybe bought it
too why
creating Revival
Market did P S I even get those totems
properly or was it for Creative Mode
that would be no I don't think she would
do
that I don't think she would do
that I don't need the bed right I no for
traveling up until that point probably
yeah oh
um I'm ready can we go let's go let's go
[Music]
go bring competition but she still
doesn't say how
much
uh what do you guys think will will we
have an easy time what if she spawns
free do you think we'll still have an
easy time
free would be fun free might be
[Music]
hard she only has 44 and 20 of those are
from me
[Music]
think she needs
Stones she's selling way
cheaper well Kyla won't really need the
totem either let's be real let's be
honest yes
don't
tell she's reading it she was just
reading
[Music]
it are there any admissions
today no but she's advertising her
sale how many pearls do we have now oh
ah is that enough
hey K hey
k i I watched by the way I watched the
clip uh and confirmed that when I was
standing in front of P Senai when she
was AFK it was indeed uh being captured
what I was saying to her
stream it was indeed being captured
and that wasn't even my best impression
what I was doing but they were still
like oh yeah her impression I haven't
heard that in a while she's so
good Ana you're using those 44 diamonds
where half of them are from me to get a
totem
huh no you only gave me 20 I had 24 so
it's not half pretty much half
well well thank you for if I die you
know I'm dying because I sacrificed my
diamonds for you to not die Oh no you're
not going to die it's almost as if I
loved
you yeah it's almost as if love hate all
the same if you know play the game I lo
up I can fight theing and I won't try
yeah don't tell anyone but I Loop that
song oh thank you you should sing it
yeah I was joking or maybe seriously
saying that we should one one time
perform it together cuz of the lyrics
being so perfect you know for
us I mean I would be down for that ooh
one day one day yeah do you do you say
do you feel the
same okay yeah we feel the same about
our hatred we do you going to Kyla now
yeah I am okay I'll follow
you
okay hold on let me let me
take is still an iron outfit she's I
think she's the only one in Iron the
most yeah actually she
does she really does I think they're
selling they're selling diamonds armor
in Ida
here selling well if she's only wearing
Iron I feel like she doesn't have the
money to afford diamond armor you're
going to go with the
boat yeah I do okay let's go okay you
come in yeah
okay this is s if this is as if we like
each other yeah but just as
if yeah just don't get your hopes up
guys don't get the wrong impression oh
okay
[Music]
yeah yes she tried to stop me for
selling the totems for
you power harass power
harassment power harass
[Music]
I have three totems I have four actually
four
totems four totems are going to sell it
cheaper price
nice
Che price
[Music]
[Laughter]
H okay
okay once you not not to sell too cheap
cuz it's illegal but don't listen to her
don't listen to her it's like a black
market it's Black Market I told I told
her that this is this is because we're
both IDs hand hand to this really but I
want bring up one thing even though
you're e you know she's buying off of
you for 44 diamonds
right yeah but out of those 44 diamonds
20 are from me
Kyla did you hear me there 20 half of
Ana's diamonds are from me so maybe oh
really maybe you can give Ana and me a
totem
cuz I I donated my uh diamonds to
Ana because she wanted to get 100
diamonds but now half of them are from
me and now she's giving them to you so
actually actually 50% out from
me hi hello hello hello hello
hello how how how many how much how
much
[Applause]
100 anyone wants to go higher than
that auction
okay ID business here come here
okay she wants two for 100
diamonds thank you okay thank
you okay this one is auction this one is
auction 100 100 higher I gave my
diamonds to an
oh well two totem it's business two
totems wants two
totems oh two totems she wants two for
100 in total oh two for 100
[Music]
oh how much do you want
100 we have
[Music]
another auction totem totem totem in
my totem how much how
much mhm 10 Diamond 10 Diamond no no no
no no no no no di she starts from 10
maybe 10 diamond oh start from 10 okay
okay
okay Aqua is not she's not Bing she's
just here to watch okay
so you don't you so Kiwa you don't want
this totem well I want but I gave all my
di to to Ana I gave them all to an you
you you don't have like any No I gave
them all to Anya and donated also to
okay so no one is actually joining the
the the the auction you you should type
in chat you should type in chat I I'll
type for you going to come to me again a
it's so
over it's over 75 how about
75 what
[Music]
no oh guys we got to go you have you
have 0 no you you want one or
two two two for eight
cannot cannot cannot what if I just bet
these diamond blocks auction use these
for the auction and replace them with uh
I don't know
Iron no no no I I only sell one how much
you want for
one one one one
only
yeah just
one come
again
coming really
[Laughter]
okay you have to sell it fast because
we're about to leave yeah I know
[Music]
right how how much how
much how much do you for one how much do
you
want uh how uh 69 for one ah Lo
okay
[Music]
okay what a what a weird
number oh
yeah I wonder
why thank you thank
[Music]
you let's go let's go let's go we need
toet secret secret secret secret
secret I didn't give get any I thought
Kyla would understand that those
diamonds are mostly from me
[Music]
[Laughter]
anyway what
dooming oh come on come on it's night
time
it's
it I'm going to be
late it's like a
raid not quite yet but you mean the
trades before really are people trading
in raids
like
[Music]
this she is she works for p so if you
don't want her to tell she's going to R
her out if she doesn't want to be red
out she she has to give her something
she just
[Music]
said oh my God
okay okay okay she's saying please get
your get everything ready we're going to
go
soon she's blackmailing her I wonder if
it will
work it's not like P I can do anything
about it she should just you know keep
her things move on
[Music]
sometimes I have this feeling
everybody's muting me because I'm asking
questions in Japanese and they don't
seem to hear
it
oh oh is it
over she's talking about buckets and I
was offering
her but nobody hears me
where are we
[Music]
Gathering Maybe
Anya did Kyla get
blackmailed no um no she she threatened
her back good she threatened her back
with
what well she was about to I think I
think a violence violence was about to
happen and aqu Senpai gave up was like
okay okay we friends no
hieee
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah [\h__\h] there's a lot of
people h two ghosts are watching
[Music]
too everyone keeps giving de Flex yeah
said she thinks she will die on the way
to the whatever what what do you call it
not stronghold what do you call that
thing or maybe it is called
stronghold she has a
totem she'll be
fine oh this
[Music]
called thank you thank
you for
[Music]
he normally sells it for
69 she has a SH
[Music]
now SC SC SC SC SC
she was screaming like oh my God what do
I do what do I do I have the I have the
arrow out on my bow and I don't know
what to do I don't want to shoot anybody
but I don't know how to get rid of this
and then I was like scroll scroll
scroll I don't even do
that I don't even do
that I heard her panicking
[Music]
today I'm just here to relieve
everybody's
[Music]
problems problem
yes okay
everybody's just talking to their
chat while waiting to
[Music]
sleep yeah I was doing side quest pretty
much
pretty much I think you're ready to
go
thank ready to
hello I think they're ready to go coming
yeah I'm ready let's go are you hiding
because it's so
loud it's lot of people yeah it's a lot
of yapping from all sides
[Music]
spe
[Applause]
[Music]
she's leading the path
there does that mean it's close just
because it didn't uh go that far no
right was under us the entire that would
be crazy
if it goes back there
[Music]
then I wanted to change
[Laughter]
[Music]
not Boss music quite
yet over the
mountain do you hear
[Music]
it school trip again
small army for this fight what small big
[Music]
army I don't have a
KY left again oh no her
DC's she de sees a lot
huh maybe we'll find her Trident here
what about the Ice
[Music]
Bears as long as there's no babies he
won't attack
right is baby
[Music]
because baby no no baby
[Laughter]
there's so many in never r
[Music]
why is she not
here I don't see is she preparing
something Secret
is she preparing something
secret maybe she's going straight in
creative mode and spawning or
maybe oh she's the true final
boss it's
broken oh no
it's so pretty
here
it please do not oh baby baby ah this
one's I think
dangerous yep
[Music]
y has the Arro and we're fine
no don't kill
it no no don't hurt
[Music]
it you're so evil
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh Anya you made it an
orphan you have to adopt
it sure that came froma
better kill it too to end it suffering
no it's not suffering yet maybe it will
be adopted by other is that a thing like
two Ice polar bears uh adopt others
other little babies if they see them
alone is that a mess bi
[Music]
absolutely not probably not not usually
a cats do that though
[Music]
this would be a weird place for a
stronghold but I guess it could be
anywhere oh that looks funny
nice
catch place your bets now how many
seconds will it take to die for the
Ender
Dragon cuz you don't have to shoot the
towers do you or I guess if you don't
shoot the towers he will not come down
it's been a while I don't remember
[Music]
okay sleeping on the
edge 35
[Music]
[Applause]
seconds I 2 minutes or free May
[Music]
free be will still eat you no
baby what are we going to do we have no
boats
thank
you didn't even bring any wood to build
[Music]
them for
freaking
[Music]
chest can I go with you
look
up your neck is so
kind of freeing me out oh my
[Music]
God yeah I don't have to do anything's
go
[Music]
[Laughter]
taking
screenshots this looks
good
[Music]
cute all that way
so
far the fleet
[Music]
yeah go go go go
an ocean Monument yeah and we can just
defeat it too if we find
one that would be fun extra
mission
bat
ship
oh
p and another boat ship shipwreck and
portal what's that shipwreck m in front
of uh behind us now yeah
oo is the
land a little
bit but maybe still better if we go by a
[Music]
boat is there m here
maybe we'll find a
[Music]
witch was there a sign from the outside
no right you have to dig down if you
think you have it
[Music]
right left her boat got a
dick let's go
oh then it has to be
[Music]
here Bo maybe it's where the
cow still further back
[Music]
I want to
take oh I didn't bring my
shovel well I can't get rid of those
[Music]
jft someone got lost
oh Unbreaking wow wow
[Music]
I put it there it looks so
nice bring it back home there is no home
after
this I put the nice pressure plate here
[Music]
why did she get
lost what
[Music]
happened it's got to be there in the
water
[Music]
can you follow in the
wall didn't bring a
door oh one
[Music]
no
Trident damn
it but nice of him to show up and say hi
oh I feel I hear another
one she's thring
[Music]
okay sleepy
time L was found how did you get
lost the trees mixed up n leave it to
the other
[Music]
[Laughter]
so much chat chaotic chat
[Music]
walk
okay make sure to pick up your bags
[Music]
now we're looking
for this new generation keeps on getting
lost
[Music]
for why is not here she's just laughing
in a
chat making fun of our misery maybe when
we're back we'll see the whole village
destroyed by by Withers
[Music]
oh she's doing spectator mode
ah why did I make so many
doors
what well under water yeah but why are
they showing them off
[Applause]
[Music]
I think I guess Al was looking for ladin
and ladin was found but Alon was still
out
[Music]
there all the doors in theall
water well I'll use my hand for now no
wait should be from a
door Ena do you have a shovel with you
no I don't me
NE
oh the door is not working on me
is that stone oh it's
Stone this is kind of scary this is kind
of
scary this is a little bit scary
this is scary this is too scary
[Music]
look everybody's
doing everybody's sing everywhere
scattered hoping to find it
oh 5 hours
[Music]
later make a small box house remove
water from it
oh feel like it's not even necessary and
then I'll have troubles getting
out not this
big oh well I'm too scared anyway [\h__\h]
[Music]
did we get
it no I should just bring the door with
me take the
[Music]
okay if it's like
uh if I find
bricks what's this what's
this an air pocket
Kyla got it
oh KY found it
[Music]
it's
bable what
claustrophobic for
real oh but this is
impressive dig
down oh they're down there somewhere
down
[Music]
there I'll make
stairs no water
oh I don't really know what I'm
doing water came from
above wow
ask for Fort I'd like to know the
entrance there's so many
doors you don't know which
one which one is
it she's oh she's all the way like over
there can you see it
[Music]
here here hello
hello please us the
[Applause]
[Music]
way
here wow
[Music]
I don't know
how want to go
[Music]
[Applause]
I forgot which one it was here
[Music]
I'll
go cuz nobody's
going oh is this water what is this oh
yeah it's fine it's fine that one is
fine I got stacked
[Music]
before is there something interesting
maybe it was
taken didn't somebody just go in
here it's a
prison is it down here
[Music]
ah there like spiders and stuff here
like feel like I remember oh if there's
a torch that means somebody was here
before
right hey yo this is kind of like a
horror
movie yeah spider spawners and stuff
so nice that they put buttons
though don't get lost n don't worry we
just got to follow where all the names
are where did I come from
though
zombie oh that's pretty good
that's pretty good but I don't need it
anymore sh this freeing for protection
free oh they are they let's follow
[Music]
them oh they're still waiting for the
others
[Music]
you think they found
it what's this place wow wow
[Music]
oh it was just right
there
oh
nice wow
[Music]
beautiful welcome to the underworld
now my inventory is so full now from the
[Music]
digging that's yeah normally there might
be some in there already
[Music]
right do we have enough
she's making a trash box
[Music]
or
the the other thing
[Music]
girl can be clutch
you L them
[Music]
again oh we have enough
she wants some people to make a path
first
[Music]
is good at that stuff I
think didn't I have something here out
of
[Music]
bed
fore speech
[Music]
onion getting onion achievement
before she removes
it I'm there why it moves so
[Music]
weirdly the ghosts are going in too
no they started uh they they first had a
group that decided on but they wanted
ky's Help mik Wanted ky's
help solo
it yeah for the briding
[Music]
I want to go I want to
go good oh good
[Music]
job okay do we remember how this works
let's go Ana
[Music]
just four minutes
though okay let's
[Music]
go that came right at me
hard to
reach no way she spot those
[\h__\h] no no no no no no I didn't
bring milk
no no I swear to God take
it okay okay okay we got to we got to do
something about
that but I don't
know hey can you even the ones ah the
ones that are in cages you don't shoot
them or you shoot the other ones
first oh nice I got one I'm not looking
at you
dude I guess we can shoot over
it calm super calm I am oh it's so
hi which one's left where are the
withers are
they do you need help with the withers
oh NAD is dead where the
withers where is
everybody I don't see anybody
uhoh did I did I look at one I looked at
one no leave me no leave me
alone it's okay I can kill
him okay do they all hate me okay no I'm
going to die I'm going to die I'm going
to die wait wait wait wait
[Music]
wait no no no no no no no please no
no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no y I'm going to die
what if I kill him like further away
from
everybody okay do they do they do they
all go for me are they are we good now I
think we're good now wait but where is
everybody I don't see
anybody there's one person
there well
where ah here
here ah they're taking care of the Widow
first
[Music]
huh all right
okay no the buff the debuff goes away
after a while
right I think
so okay yeah it's
gone see that's not natural
right sorry I got so lost but we we did
some preparation with the shooting of
the towers
he doesn't have any more Towers right oh
this one
maybe I
think looks like there's something still
there oh it's so hard to
reach whatever can probably just
wait let me drink that potion right
now did I land on
[Music]
water that's what happens sometimes
but when he comes down I want to hit him
yeah come
down I feel like I'm not doing
much oh
I got the
last
[Music]
y
beautiful
oh no no no CH go no no no no no no no
no
no no please leave me
alone I was just taking pictures
what she doing a
picture what's she preparing
[Music]
for but only one person
died only
one wait why does she have a sh
[Music]
box she she's want she wants to do
something
[Music]
Lun she
what is she last B where is
[Music]
she I think she wants to be the last
boss
[Music]
[Applause]
I can't
see there might be some accidental
deaths like
this hun the bunny hun the bunny
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
I will be the
one how much how much does it take oh
she has a toilet
[Music]
[Applause]
too he's too strong anywhere so
that if anyone get this no
[Music]
is she trying to protect
her
uh oh there she
is prach the gold post ah she used the
totem she used the totem
[Music]
are they hitting me you want will you
want some you want
some okay okay okay
okay so much collateral
damage why is
[Applause]
[Music]
she tried to
kill
again what's happening
[Music]
[Applause]
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
by her
gmate world is at peace yeah in the end
all of this there is a big evil brain
behind all of this and that big evil
brain is called peka Senai does she had
to die in the very
[Applause]
[Music]
end peace oh oh no picture wait I guess
we got to go back to take the
picture no not this super long ass
Minecraft
ending oh you skipped it too yeah I
guess cuz they wanted to take a picture
maybe we'll go back to the end after
everybody gathers here is this where
everybody will gather where everybody
will respawn got pushed in Oh Me Oh wait
oh yeah right I guess I was standing
right there I no bed
anymore yeah
[Music]
H I don't have a bed except at my home
so
far let me go back to my home at least
you're not alone
yeah they're leaving through the portal
now and then they watch the ending but
don't they all end up here then
wait as I'm riding that she teleports
[Music]
everybody made
everybody's revived
[Music]
[Applause]
spe will be on the list of people who
didn't die a single time let's
go where are they taking the
[Music]
picture jazz is back guys after a war
the only music that really fits is this
kind of jazz right
[Music]
[Applause]
why why are so many people naked
[Music]
oh they want people to get naked but I
look so cool like
this
okay oh KY looks
cool wow beautiful
[Music]
your outfit looks like armor already I
know right it's my well it's my night
outfit ah yeah do you not want to get
your hair back
you might not be the only one with a
bald bald head left what about
Ena is she still
bald a know you got your hair back I did
how did you grow it back so fast good
for the
picture is there a trick to Growing it
back you eat a lot of seaweed seaweed oh
really yeah is that actually something
people
say I don't know
my
journal oh do we write journals today as
well as well got to record
true a lot of people are riding
it
[Music]
oh bring home the
bacon oh wait mine's the I think in the
Box
[Music]
I have too much stuff I picked up so
much that I will never need
again so sad I wish I could keep this
[Music]
all
okay well I think this was my fourth
day cuz I started a little bit late
but it's also the last
day the
[Music]
19th I wonder if she's going to do one
more news show to read these I feel like
I want to take my time after we take the
picture but uh let's keep it short
uh fore
[Music]
okay I wrote something
poetic I wrote Today is a sad day you
know why because today we are separating
with
everybody this Ki who didn't die a
single time was she able to protect
anybody was she able to rescue
anybody what I can say is that me
personally I was rescued by this
event
done isn't that poetic and
beautiful I think so
I think there's nothing else to say
[Laughter]
really we need to sign
[Music]
it like at the end
here
I I I added the book title in the
beginning I think it was a phoenix
Journey
okay there we go a phoenix
taale what's the
story I love the poetic approach I try
it's a bit more difficult to do it in a
different language but I think I I
nailed
it so wait how long did well I guess you
can't really count how long it took
because we had other fights to do too
the withers and I I got kind of lost cuz
everybody was somewhere
[Music]
else
oh and then even after the dragon there
was pic Empire to
kill I missed the old fight yeah but I
wasn't the only one who was focusing on
the dragon first and then the
DN animation font
hi hello hi hi hello you look so
beautiful without your armor
oh really yeah let me put it back then
no don't you look beautiful without it
don't hide your beautiful self behind
the armor but but I mean I really I
really love your this this this you know
this one yeah my outfit this one it
really looked like that you're using
armor when yeah yeah I use it for like
RPG streams because it's a warrior
outfit you should get a warrior outfit
too I hope someday right
yeah you finished your your diary
already yeah I just wrote one page I I
wrote something like a
poem oh I see that's so
cool what are you going to write you got
to write about being uh being power
harassed by us p
no she did until the very end she was
trying to harass
you power
harassment oh oh they're
putting they're putting their heads
there I guess we don't have to be part
of the picture or is this the other the
people who aren't here
today
yeah yeah that's what it is
[Music]
cute cute cute
cute the
Heavenly
Powers
Rive The Souls of all the heroes
[Music]
we already took
it what we were we are going to okay I
follow like I missed it
now cuz she wrote in past
[Music]
tense
hello I did you write your
diary yeah but um I'm trying to figure
out how to translate this to Japanese do
you want to do you want to hear my diary
yeah
okay the day has finally come the vanal
the one and only and the dragon fight
like shown in anime we combined our
nakama power into one and defeated the
evil dragon oh I was targeted by the
weer that bastard he know that I hold's
ancient power oh he was targeting you
exterminate me yeah yeah he did I was I
was running like my life dependent on it
but I of course
[Music]
you no we hate each other we hate each
other
no let me out let me out let me
out throw up
no no e that was the worst seconds and
moments of my life ever I know I
[Laughter]
know well I don't think you'll have a
problem Translating
that cuz you're a
pro well I I'll try how long how long do
I have not
sure soon you should hurry
maybe thank
you thank
you um
[Music]
[Laughter]
that sounded like crony for a
moment you guys got to listen back to
that the way the it was also distorted
by
noise for a moment it sounded like crony
cuz when she laughs she laughs also
like and like it gets distorted also I
think it's like so
similar I was like crony
[Music]
but they could have built it with
something else than
[Music]
dirt I don't know what I expected I
didn't think I would be
teleported oh
wait she said in 1 minute we should take
a
[Music]
picture stand here
orange hair
[Music]
people maybe without the shield takes up
some
space for
[Music]
[Laughter]
ana ana stand next to me ana
ana ana next to
[Music]
Anda in front of
me oh it's looking
good looking
[Music]
good the best I can
[Applause]
[Music]
do
for I
[Music]
[Applause]
our chees
[Music]
is okay
[Applause]
[Music]
I thought there was an evil brain inside
of P's head there's nothing in
there that's the point
[Music]
[Applause]
doesn't doesn't count though doesn't
count that was it was
over wee
yeah everybody's slaying everybody now
oh Aqua died by P senpai's hands oh I've
never I don't how do you go down oh
there we
go my
face
what what is she
thinking yes
yes I don't think she hears me though so
much everyone for
watching she regrets nothing in two
months if you do to that is yeah I'll
see you in two months
[Applause]
[Music]
Goodbye Oh no I wanted to take a picture
with them and never write armor r a trim
[Music]
I love
you no the T I died too
[Music]
soon they don't know I'm watching
them they no I have my eyee on them wait
wait wait did I get
[Music]
[Applause]
revived not again
no wait Ana wait no no no no no no no
you have a sword never mind sword I have
nothing no no no you
got what me you got
[Music]
some for
okay was by road please stop killing
people yeah they're
leaving that [\h__\h] that [\h__\h] right when
P I wrote normal Revival it's
over that
[\h__\h] I hate
yeah this was truly a anaton
Arc was it
[Laughter]
not
H she yeah I will read super chats but
damn that was uh my adventure on the
Hardcore Minecraft server thank you guys
for taking part in it today was also
pretty short huh it like each stream
became shorter and shorter the first day
was 9 hours then seven then like 4 then
two yeah it became easier and
easier after Gathering all all the
things that I
needed I had my fun I think first the
first day was it the first day the day
no the day when we went into the never
was the most fun
M PE call alive yeah Minecraft is kind
of our game or it used to be but it's
nice to get back to something like this
it feels very nostalgic chaotic mining
happy you joined thank you I'm happy you
joined refreshing seeing Hol playe MC
together again yeah I'm surprised not so
many Ian members joined it was only me
and
Ena but
oh yeah I think a lot of them a lot of
people were busy I feel like if Will M
weren't busy they would have probably
joined uh but it is what it is and
honestly uh me and Ena being the only
ones may may maybe made Le things less
chaotic
[Music]
yeah they're busy I had fun watching you
anina thank
[Music]
you yeah I don't know fora I ended up
not joining but maybe we'll have
something like this again sometime and
then maybe we can have it even like
mostly for Ian people like an Ian
hardcore
challenge but you know we always say
stuff like this after events after
Japanese members have like organized
some events and it's always like M yeah
it would be cool if we had that but like
who's going to take care of it I don't I
don't know maybe with ID
together and then all the yapping can be
English mainly I I spoke way more
Japanese than usual in these streams uh
I I'm I'm happy I was like able to speak
a bit more again for the first time in a
long time and communicate with other
Japanese members and with Japanese
viewers um but yeah we we don't worry
we'll get back to the usual English
ratio yeah also Ollie why was I thought
I would hang out way more with Ollie but
she was not around that much I'm kind of
sad what happened Ollie what happened I
wanted to see you
more where was my other OE
dates sorry cracking my
hip she's sick I all right but still I
thought she was getting better
[Music]
first first never day was
fun I think I want to or um ask mik by
for a oneon-one or maybe a small group
people a small people group what
collaboration I want to talk a bit more
of mtin stand by she's been so nice to
me GTA collab I don't
know I think I do want to do that but uh
don't we need a server and also somebody
is like do we need a server if we're
just a small group I don't know uh but
also like I think we have it we have the
game on different
consoles no not Ian server that was the
discussion the idea that me am and
mikochi I think us three would play GTA
together for a little bit GTA online
specifically
yeah
yeah yeah like if it's just free I think
we don't need a whole server right like
I don't know how it works but the
problem was yeah I think mikoi plays on
PlayStation and me and Amy play on PC I
think at least I
do
but I don't know maybe we can still make
it happen yeah do a heist together oh am
doesn't even have a PS5
oh well that would be an argument to get
mikoi to get the uh PC
version
Oh wait did I play on
PC I think I did I think I have the
games on Steam I think I did now I'm not
sure either but I think I did yeah yeah
yeah yeah but switched because of
hackers oh yeah that that was also a
concern I
guess yeah yeah press F uhhuh uhhuh stop
pressing F just press four
guys well let's go to my office my IP
office I I'm getting good use out of it
once once
again it was so fast if I'd have felt
more confident I would have joined since
the first
day and then we would have had even more
of all of this but I think it's fine
some other members even if they joined
the first day they maybe didn't join
some other days
so but can you imagine I I caught up so
fast with everything like with armor
thanks to Ollie first and foremost in
the beginning but I caught up so fast it
wasn't even necessary for me to play in
the first couple
days yeah I may have not been the first
with never armor but I was the first
with the right amount of never right
[Music]
yeah now I kind of want to maybe one
time one day maybe I can challenge a
Bastion uh on thean server
alone I mean I'm like kind of the only
person playing there but it's something
I have not done yet and I never really
considered it because I just didn't
really know about it also cu the trims
are relatively a new thing right oh the
the the the template as well I guess it
wasn't the thing back when I was
playing yeah this
costume wait let me show
you H oh I guess it's hard to where is
it where is
it this is what it looks like
I guess it should be
even bigger maybe
even
but this is this is this not part of my
costume it's just uh you know from
my uh
dear dear providers of
[Music]
pngs
yeah it's that easy it it it would have
been that easy just I all I needed is a
PNG to put behind myself uh but when I
can't get it from the real Source I get
it from my fans tascal I think it was
made by Sky right
or I saved it a while ago I don't I
don't uh remember wait I think it was
made by
Sky yeah that was sky thank you
ah also I saw Skye also made my me a Pip
Boy for Fallout which let me show you
now I'm so excited to use
it yo I'm going to use this I was so
confused the first time they mentioned
Pip Boy in the show I was like I was I
thought they were talking about a
person I don't think they really maybe I
missed it when they first explained that
a Pip Boy is the name of that machine
machine but the first time they
mentioned it I was so clueless like what
do you mean and then later on I I
figured it out on my
own they yeah they did not explain it
right pip ball was that even mean was
the PIP part
mean they didn't mention it till nor
asked okay okay so it wasn't just
me good good good good
um I so maybe next
week maybe next week we play fall out I
was thinking New Vegas didn't we do
a a poll on it did we do a poll
everybody was mostly recommending New
Vegas yeah it won by a lot
okay without Maps it might might crash
what does that mean without
Maps my mom also wanted New Vegas Oh H
did she want New Vegas or did you just
want Fallout like in general a mods you
mean oh yeah I'll ask Amed what she
did like it worked fine for her
right four has better graphics but Envy
got more Soul
oh m
well New Vegas I guess plays in New
Vegas uh where where's like where can I
meet um the most related things to the
show probably New Vegas
right
for New Vegas New Vegas New Vegas New
Vegas most people say New Vegas and the
cool thing is that it seems like the
next season will play in New Vegas so
then this time is this a bad thing I
don't know I don't think I ever had this
case before where I play a game and then
I watch a show based on the game but
already know everything about it oh go
it might not be it might just be the
location right because they're making
their own story yeah then it's fine I
don't think if I I don't know if I would
like it like knowing everything already
like
but it's got to be
like either even I watch the show first
like let's say for example for
Witcher and then know everything about
the game or it's the other way
around I know the show is like very
different but still not not that
different for has the visual aesthetic
of the
show
really New Vegas is far more of an RPG
uh well you guys voted for New Vegas so
we're probably going to do that one
you will see Shady Sands in New
Vegas Oh when it's broken or when it's
still
there I won't
oh oh Shady sand is in Fallout two one
and
[Music]
two Hardcore Minecraft is over
the OG and it sequel
n okay let's read super chats now
um uh where did I leave off maybe I can
tell by looking at
[Music]
hyzer well I really like the show the
show is like I already decided to play
Fallout before I watched the show but
the show is helping me get very really
motivated I'm I'm excited to dive into
the world hopefully I'll see some
references that feel familiar at least
Hol
talk ah okay yeah he what about Buckshot
roulette what about Buckshot
roulette better than the one show ah it
depends because one piece is like more
fantasy
is in a different way in a cute
[Music]
way
oh you like the bird talk idea well it's
still a while until I have to do that
probably
but you were looking at the game even
before the show
wait what are we talking about
Fallout looking at the game yeah I
already decided that I would play
Fallout quite a while ago yeah I don't
know why I don't know several
influences
[Music]
okay uh
yeah I'm telling you next week we're
going to have a fun collab to
with with some cute
birds I think I can put out the schedule
today
yeah sadly no holot talk though because
I didn't hear back
yet I was going to do it the coming week
but uh I guess I got to move it again
because I didn't hear uh back
the delay is not always my fa fault guys
but it's nobody's fault but um you know
it's not always on
[Music]
me I'm looking for better music
oh elevator
[Music]
music that's quite
upbeat okay let me put up the thumbnail
what are we reading Buckshot roulette
first I
think that was fun too and I said I know
I said I'll I'll play it again but I
feel like this is one of these games
that you really just play once after I
was done with it I realized it might
just get like kind of
repetitive if I play it again even
though it was so much
[Music]
fun yeah I think I'm fine done with it
not that it was bad it was really good I
really liked
it
yeah I think we we got the gist of the
game there's nothing new
to like find except I I zapped no
actually I watched quite a bit of amen's
Buckshot roulette stream I think on that
night when I uh cooked myself dinner I
was like still so excited about the game
so I watched am's archive afterwards and
I think I saw am ending up in some place
that I did not find some crazy
weird
place and I was like what what is this
how did I not find that
[Music]
cuz she died but didn't I die
too and I never saw that place she was
in I don't even remember it anymore
black and white Place probably she was
dead dead how do you go dead dead when
you die before the meds you can go
there before the
meds how do you die before the meds you
mean the ones you take
uh if you die on the round three you're
dead you die at normal mode on stage
three see I never saw that but oh well
I'm not going to go back for
that okay Jacob 47 d py d space
waterfall d d thank you for the red
super chat hi wa can I buy a healing
kiss for yko yko smashed wing while
trying to dust under the 50ft golden
Wawa statue wait wait what is this a
metaphor for also sorry for being away
job sucks our sucks lollipop sucks
lollipop what's that
another another metor all sucks I'll
will keep my beak up and keep listening
to Kima Banger thank
you that was so long ago well excuse me
princess
oh oh because you suck
lollipops
oh is that why you said
that well well well I don't know if your
wing healed already
but I hope this helps I don't think it
can heal fully that fast
right how did you do it though I'm kind
of
curious kind of curious
but that could you get one too of course
M for for working so hard behind the
scenes to earn money for every
day as normal people do working so
hard yeah and for that you may not be
able to watch my streams so much
recently but I'm sure I'm sure you're
still around thank you for listening to
Kima d
you still feel a little bit of pain when
you press your finger
I uh
actually when I you know I I hurt my
foot twice right once with the bowl and
once with the
dumbbell the one incident with the
dumbbell I
noticed uh like the the pain of that was
not
as
strong for as long as the other incident
but I noticed even like weeks
later like if I put pressure on it it
would it still felt kind of
injured feel like I I heard something
there uh a little bit too much without
realizing
but it's not
like big big
[Music]
pain only if I push really hard into it
yeah I think it was a fracture or
something then I know when I push into
it I notice Oh all but now let me try
now cuz I tried a few days
[Music]
ago uh yeah there's like one spot Maybe
very slightly I think it's pretty much
healed pretty much
gone no I wouldn't call it
broken
sadly Sky Dan r on and Dan H oh Dan be
Dan G oh thank you for your red super
chat I feel like this is your first
one H hey K I wanted to let you know
it's my birthday and I'm happy for the
past year of great streams you had as it
helps me get for the day much better
also I haven't stopped listening to Kima
at such a banger really you're not
stopping let's go several people still
listening to Kima makes me happy even
now that I kind of stopped promoting it
thank you and happy belated birthday I
hope you get to hear this I hope you
didn't give up on me because I'm so late
on the super chats thank you though for
supporting me over the year and for
still being here I wish you Happy
Birthday Studio Rob Dan for the pinky
Teno is the swellest of the sweller
family swellest kind of like uh a way to
say someone's cool right I never us use
that
word you're so
swell you're quite swell too Studio Rob
thank you swell
Cho does swell come from
swell it's an old word
a yeah I feel like I hear it yeah like
more an oldfashioned kind of shows or
so B time
[Music]
Tracy jul
kingra ASMR for the of
chat oh thank you from is this from
Singapore I think that that these are
Singapore dollars sing a Bo so
cool thank you so much I'm happy to be
your coming
oie hopefully one day I can like be in a
convention or so in
Singapore and then you guys hopefully
will be
there that would be nice SE St flight of
fancy d py d the steel
D spaghetti s m yummy thank you for the
red the pinky hello la I lurk most of
the time but it's my birthday today
oo I just wanted to say thanks for being
who you are and cultivating a great
Community you and kfp are the reason why
I started to travel more for conventions
it's always a blast to meet kfp oh
that's great to hear I you know I can't
really relate but I can
imagine that sounds OD
amazing I can imagine you guys like
after one experience you feel like you
want
more especially if maybe you're like me
and your only human interactions come
mostly from Anime
conventions then of course feels great
especially if it's such like-minded
people yeah sounds like a lot of
fun I'm glad to hear it and happy
belated birthday spaghetti son I hope
you had a wonderful day and I hope all
the following days will be wonderful
[Music]
too yeah space wonderful thank you soon
Shan from
Brazil and oh I do I do um constantly
also consider ID Girls uh as well for
girl stock don't worry they're in my
consideration they're always in my
[Music]
consideration this account on this
account you have an
egg emo a members emoji
thingy what happened shouldn't do this
your your second account or so unknown D
and pety
thank always love
ID always I feel like uh
from judging from who like I've met them
all so judging from that uh honestly kuo
is getting more and more girly each time
I meet her she's like
doing all the girlly things I constantly
see her like doing stuff like like she
got
lashes she got this she got that I'm
like
girl you the first time I met you you
looked so boyish to
me
and every time I meet you you're looking
more and more like you know a
[Music]
lady it's so confusing
so she probably would have some stuff to
talk about
um and uh other than that I feel like
Zeta she always stood out to me in terms
of you know looking really
cute
and oh my
[Music]
think cute girl sees
a fanny
pack right she had a [\h__\h] fanny
pack what
[Music]
it yeah I think those two are the
girliest
really maybe MAA too because like she
once did my
hair she did my hair
once and we were having some girl early
time
yeah understandable
right okay where was I oh I finished
this box
roulette H talk super
chats
here there we go
let's
[Music]
see
pyck Jacob 47 thank you for the RP
another birthday T today is my birthday
and it seems that I have the very nice
gift of the return of Hol talk on it
yeah been looking forward to this
episode for a long time and it's nice to
have an early stream I can watch and
then spend the day celebrating thank you
thank
you happy belated bir birthday sorry I
couldn't say it on the day but you know
how it is I hope you celebrated yourself
well I want to celebrate you
[Music]
congratulations thank you for supporting
me all the time thank you so much much
much Cho Mah mwah mwah mwah mwah
mwah let's spend the next one together
too
hopefully m
[Music]
monk thanks for the pink
also from
[Music]
Singapore super excited for this whole
talk Myan oi and Japan o she have a
one-on-one collab I'm die thank you
forever you lucky
bastard good for you always glad when
this
happens thank you for enjoying it thank
you for waiting for it it's been a long
time coming to have what by Hol talk
sorry for keeping you
waiting D fre D dead Bob five
D ah the speed round yeah like she was
giving me such unclear answers I was
trying to get something clearer out of
her that's why it was a kind of slow
speed speed
round but I'm glad she was so
enthusiastic about answering the panty
color question
yeah that was definitely the slowest one
I gave her too much time also I didn't I
don't think I explained it properly uh I
was confusing her like how to
answer should have prepared her
beforehand that she had to answer in
English
yeah frankenheim thanks for the red
super chat thanks once again while for
the best whole talk ever thanks
you best H talk as always right spank
and I'm you say that each
time I'm pretty sure you say that each
time well every Hol talk is maybe the
same amount of
bestness they're all the
[Music]
best
yeah yeah every talk is best Hol talk
every talk B is banking hi
[Music]
m i
AEP D fried screw Jim Tracy thanks for
the pinky thanks for the great episode
today I've always been a huge fan of lam
m music and Performing so it was cool to
learn so much about her she's done so
much and stayed herself for it all one
day vame will perform at Budan for sure
yeah maybe she will maybe she
will yeah well
I'm glad Jim Tracy I'm glad seems like
maybe she was also one of your
oshis yeah so once again a collaboration
of ooshies together the best thing you
could ask for let's support her to make
her dream come true but I I also need
some support from you guys
if I want to
eventually perform somewhere you know
have a solo concert my first solo
concert at some point somewhere
maybe thank
[Music]
you if it will ever happen that is but
anyway
[Music]
AP waterful D thank you alasan
D and punk picture thank you
[Music]
D yeah even if it won't happen it's not
because of like the lack of power you
guys have you guys are very
powerful m
[Music]
for after she replied to me on on
Twitter I reached out to her on
DM tried to have some chitchat with her
and offered her to just like if she's
super bored and at some point because
she seemed really bored from watching so
many
shows I offered her to just like hit me
up whenever she wants to talk and she's
like oh thank you and she was very happy
that I reached out to
her tried to yeah have some conversation
a little bit yeah did she already I
wonder if she already finished Fallout
because she asked for some more show
recommendations
oh I guess I think she also has a steam
deag and now she's asking for game
recommendations I hope she'll come back
soon but I think she should take her
time yeah she should take it
easy nothing wrong with taking it easy
she's been working so hard for a long
time
so nothing wrong with
[Music]
that yeah yeah I read the
post all right Dragon's Dogma is next
one of those games that perhaps I would
want to make a series out of
but I need I just want to can I just not
have bgm I'm so
I don't want to hear anything right
now just want to
be peace peace and calm bring your own
bgm to work
day also I feel like I need to go to
idle
meeting but it's
okay I'm using fro candy
Now vaa voice only
I put chimo in the background oh nice
good one wait do I have like a text
layer
no it's so quiet holy [\h__\h]
I feel like I can breathe
again my
bladder the tinitus what you hear a
tinitus but it's not from me
right Jacob 47 D Nathan coton D for the
pinky I hope you enjoy the game tantel
I'm going to be B ganging this one but I
imagine this must be a perfect Mother's
Day game to
play oh
was that Mother's
Day I don't know probably not the
perfect Mother's Day game but I did call
my mom on Mother's
Day I did call her and talked a bit to
her I think actually so I'm obviously
taking tomorrow off because I feel like
I didn't even have a day off in this
week I've been streaming
nonstop almost
nonstop but early early in the day to
so getting up
was against my
will but I'm glad I pulled it off but
the coming week we'll have two days off
and one of them will be Monday and I
think my mom is
coming to stay over either at my place
or at my brother's
place uh yeah from Monday to
Tuesday m so in any case that will not
really affect you
guys but I do think I will stream on
Tuesday yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah pretty sure I will but Monday is
day
off mama told no
no no no no no
no but I do I do want to show her the
updated upgraded Garden
and maybe we'll do some gardening
together
so might need some time to give her I'm
going to tell her to come over to my
place anyway thank you Nathan I hope you
called your mommy too on Mother's Day J
R Dan Sky
Dan canny stamps D Prince of Denmark D
Unity CH D Doug Hood thanks for the
pinky t fun thank
you I have so much tea right now but I
mostly drink it in winter so recently I
haven't been drinking so
much but sometimes I like a nice cup of
tea before going to sleep because it
feels like calming and
soothing ah ah that
H you had multiple accounts when you
pretend to be Lura snooky rowy and Luke
dur during the April food's cooking
stream
ah what you completely reset to egg you
don't have
any any other like higher status
accounts no no but I know I know you've
been around for a long time YouTube will
not Gas Light Me youtube cannot fool
me shouldn't you have like uh the
highest ranked
Emoji I'm pretty
sure don't worry I do not believe
YouTube's
Shenanigans badge yeah I mean
badge yeah
but I love that you were role playing I
want to see more of that where am I role
playing chickens
huh I miss
it it's so fun to read or people's
reviews of the shows I watch I like
seeing that too eggs lay down their
lives on the front lines I'm proud to be
egg
again you're basically just being a
Phoenix right now starting from zero
again that's just what a phoenix
does Kramer and Seinfield accounts I I
haven't been watching actively anymore
just every once in a while to fall
asleep but good show friends as
well
yeah thank you for the member
renewal and anyway thank you for the T
funds as well ter Dan Dan exre dog who
loves bread and Hungry Jacks Dan Sy Dan
spicy BC danan Mr V danan REO danan RS
danan
Cas thanks everybody for wishing me
happy Mother's
Day to me Miss for Pinky happy Mother's
Day thank you for mothering and serving
so much I hope you keep doing and
creating everything you want
to thank
you
uh uh thank you son question mark uh uh
thank you my
child please stay safe don't get
slayed don't get slay like those
chickens in Minecraft by the
weather be careful 3,000 cordium fight
Jets of soup
than
and J 8891 Dan spank Dan space wonderful
Dan J Monkey D
Ty har Haro of the Box than
at lunchbox Dan py Dan spank thank you
for the red chat the kitties and I feel
blessed to get a full weekend of V
thanks for the stream denel thank you
too we always have to like think that
the number of people that are watching
my stream might not be the real number
there might be pets like spankenheimer
might be ghosts
too you okay but are you implying I
think you weren't thinking about it but
what we're saying is I'm pretty sure
they can't just watch for a YouTube
account maybe they're just like behind
me around me watching the stream like
from this very
room that is a bit terrifying I would
like that to not be
true or maybe from your guys's rooms I
don't
know watching from right behind you
but I don't really believe in
ghosts even in made
outfits can't be real right there's no
ghosts I think she's she must be faking
that she's a ghost I need proof she has
to prove it to me otherwise she's an
impostor yeah yeah it's spanking
time after it thank
you I'm glad you're getting excited for
Fallout as well and let's thanks for the
red super chat thanks for the stream K I
haven't been able to catch you for live
for a while but been loving the v as
always thank you well well well New
Zealand you should have been able to
watch the recent streams quite well no
are you here
endless I think they are at a better
time time for you than my usual streams
I I would hope so that uh some of the
people who usually can't watch my
streams maybe were able to watch them if
you're from sea or
so maybe maybe but endless does not seem
to be in the
chat oh you're from NZ oh nice to have
you where is endless is is here te next
to you behind
you I'm here from Australia I also have
trouble with streams but have seen all
the MC ones
nice I'm so happy more of you guys could
catch it don't get used to it
though don't get used to
it but it's it came at a good time
because recently every time I was making
my schedule I was always thinking like
ah haven't done an early in a while I
should do one maybe again to like you
know help you guys out a little bit for
everybody who's like in Asia or in that
area but then there came
Minecraft I actually like early streams
they're refreshing this early though
wasn't it like 300 a.m. or so for you
guys
that's a bit too early that's more like
late rather than
early
Shake yeah free for PSD right at least
on the day where I streamed at
11 oh God endless thank you Mah I hope
this kiss reaches you maybe in the vaud
greetings to the vaud Watchers by the
way py d p Dan be Dan space waterful
danly Dan and G
Dan let's read maybe one
more
mhm days with
ol dance with
o what a
game what a game but yeah I hope she
um get some money back from this
project py D j47 Studio Rob thanks for
Pinky t t is r in kind or so I thought
but apparently I'm not Studio Rob the
game has proven us all
wrong everything I do was just
wrong j monkey
Z happy
birthday yay and congratulations to
getting a raise at work that's awesome
was that also a birthday present to
you
congratulations you worked hard for that
that einander
d d salent
Nerf mp15
G uh na Dan Jackson FB Dan Maxi Dan and
Maxi again
D these
people it says Hey ke guys me and my f
fiance are huge fans and we're getting
married tomorrow here to share happiness
to everybody oh my God
congratulations they're married by
now sheesh
that's so cute when like people are
watching my stream together it's kind of
hard to imagine feels feels embarrassing
a little
bit Nathan CAU and danish for the pinky
it is honestly pretty Bas to pick K as
an a she always got good taste so
true so
true she gets
it I love her too she's great too
yeah makes me feel really happy that she
supports me like
that yeah chy Channel danan Jackson FB
Dan and B and doule Jones thanks for the
pinky you can do it K don't over it just
go for
it
what what was that about was it still
about the
game probably right because the one
right before him talks about not turning
on the cell phone flashlight in the
darkness or was it about the MC
streams was it about
MC that makes a little bit more sense
maybe yeah I did it I did it Bia I did
it as you have seen and we're done with
it now it's
over it's over I am a tee
[Music]
stret and again Jackson FB thanks for
the
pinky if Mama watches members vs from
your account doesn't mean she also get
no no no no no no no no no no I mean
actually I guess partially
maybe in some way or
another possibly yes
uh okay okay I I'll read one more one
more from the first Minecraft
stream beautiful art everywhere
right I brought out some Banger artworks
for these
thumbnails and yet my graphic design
skills are not matching
doesn't look good enough to match with
the art
sadly no I don't think I'll catch up
until the end I really need to go
pee which I could just do now I
know but also I feel like I want to take
a
shower something
smells and I don't know why I think it's
the shirt though cuz I took a shower
last night I think it's the shirt it's
really bothering
me I don't
know I think it's a
shirt it smells
[Laughter]
weird I don't know what's
happening uh py D Jacob 47 D John D d428
N D zly Dan harlo music thank you for
the rainbow
it's your birthday I should give you a
rainbow tomorrow is my birthday but
since I'm going to be super duper busy
tomorrow I'm sending the super chat
today I'm omitting 10,000 words
describing how much I want to thank you
and love you as I have probably already
St it before and well let's say I'll be
working on stuff related to you
soon anyways I hope you are also doing
well recently love you always finishing
up up the rainbow thank
you what are you working on are you
making some music for
me I want to hear I want to hear but
happy
birthday happy birthday to you happy
birthday in your
shoe happy birthday in your pants
too happy birthday to you
yeah yeah yeah
yeah congratulations thank you for the
rainbow let's go M M M I hope I don't
have to wait too long for the reveal of
whatever you're working on I'm going to
go now for idle meeting of beb that way
maybe we can go longer maybe I'll even
change my shirt
me
e
e e
[Music]
Yoo
um here I changed
shirts yeah that smells much better
and I gave smoovie a
hug and then I trapped her with me in
the adle meeting
room stinky Joe has been cured
woohoo unknown wrong
color wrong color you need to study
color theory or something like that
okay SK d g d well SK got my popup
parade figure precisely on your birthday
happy birthday oh thank you for getting
the figure Sky
[Music]
Dan P thanks for the the pinky just had
a good dinner with fellow kfb ah thanks
to you I'm able to make friends all over
the world thank you for nurturing safe
and fun Community while I care you
forever you're
welcome I am quite proud I have raised
you guys so
well thank you for being such a sweet
Community too from from me as
well thank you
Kam thank you I'm glad you had fun with
them won Tonk honk
wonk what's AIM May
racing
uh how do I read
this oh what the
[\h__\h] Yan wait
[Music]
and py D sky for the rest of chat it is
my birthday now
17th my fourth birthday what you're
turning 17 no right it was because it
turned the May 17th oh my God for a
moment I thought you were that young you
were that
young thank God you're not because I
would feel old
may I ask for a blessing for my lovely
wonderful cute talented Kami of course
happy birthday the fourth already holy
[\h__\h] it's so crazy to think that we
already spent so much time
together I can't believe I'm still
here that's so crazy I didn't believe it
in the beginning
sheesh I'm like a veteran
now I really am like I have to think
about how I was thinking about the
highest senis back in the day when they
had like when I joined I think you know
they had like four three four years on
their backs and I was like
damn yeah and now I'm like past that too
um what it's going to be four years this
year
shees that's
crazy and you have been part of it for a
long time too I don't know if it's from
the very first day but certainly for a
long time judging by your badge as well
Skye thank you for being here still even
today thank you and happy
birthday day one
baby they want
baby
baby you baby bubble
bubble yeah yeah myth has been here
longer than soda Senai was when we
debuted yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
I've heard that before that is quite
impressive which means now s Sena is
like
double double has like double the amount
of uh time on her back then when I
joined probably
she shees one thing I really really
really really respect about Japanese
people although in some cases like they
may be doing it even though they don't
want to but they keep jobs for a long
time they stay in the same job not just
occupation but in the same company and
all that for a long time usually and
that's pretty impressive like I don't
think this is
like a lot of it not I don't think this
supplies to whole life at all but a lot
of it uh in normal companies has to do
with just the the society pressure that
if you don't have jobs for a long time
then it looks really bad on your
[Music]
resume but yeah I guess people Japanese
members they're not only you know
disciplined and all that but they was
really happy in whole life so they're
staying for so long
H I'm I'm glad because graduations are
obviously sad and it's nice that you
know all these familiar faces are
staying and we can do so many things
together don't cry
now doesn't Japan also have more workers
protection so people less likely to be
part of a big layoff oh yes I think so
yeah yeah I think
so it's hard to so to say get rid of
people yeah yeah yeah yeah 5 to 10 years
I feel like even five years is way too
little uh in
Japan couldn't be me Whole Life whole
life is the longest job I've had but I
mean you got to say like before that I
didn't do that much in general I didn't
have much time to even stay that long in
a job to give a good example uh you know
you know I did my training and then I
changed places cuz that's usually what
you do after that training of three
years most people 99% of people
change uh their workplace after they're
done with their apprenti
ship the even the companies don't expect
you to to stay but they're happy if you
stay often but yeah obviously I I wanted
to go somewhere else and I feel like
depends on the job maybe but uh for
hotel jobs in at least in in our culture
here in
Austria it's actually kind of a positive
thing when you've been in several
hotels or even restaurants or so because
like you can bring ideas
and and I don't know like Knowledge from
different places and maybe improve the
the new workplace or you
know work with the all the all kinds of
different
experiences yeah it's more
perspective it's not really looked down
upon at all if anything it's even kind
of kind of a little bit of a positive
thing if you've been in SE a lot of
different hotels
yeah
yeah very normal to job
H I'm glad you joined I'm glad that I
found you to call my cute girl my oi to
call a cute girl my
o after my 12 years in the Army I've
been in my current company for six years
wow well as long as you're happy there
and as long as they pay you well I think
that is obvious obiously the ideal uh
way to
go if you feel comfortable
there I'll change position this summer
oh let's go I hope I hope that comes
with more
pay it has to
right anyway thank you
Sky I am a te
D Jones d py d
Jim Tracy D
Nathan for the pinky you know T while I
appreciate you streaming through my
entire shift and then some you don't
need to keep streaming all day no but
that day the 9 hours stream N9 and a
half hours or so it didn't feel long at
all that was really like it felt so
short and it felt really comfy I had a
good time there's other streams where it
may be a little bit more tedious but
that wasn't the case in this case so I'm
good don't worry thank you
though yeah don't worry when do we get
pay
atten when do I get pay H when do I get
pay oh smoy
hi what what did you hear that hi wait
did you go to the
toilet oh when I was using the thread
yesterday before I started it chunky
wonky was like sitting in front of it
comfortably cuz I put it in front of my
work
PC uh and so chunky wonky was like kind
of chilling comfortably in my chair and
smoothie was chilling in the bed in
front of it and then I started and
Chunky wony was like what the
[\h__\h] cuz it was so loud and the faster I
would go the louder it would get and
then she ran away pretty early smoovie
still kind of she was very like what the
[\h__\h] too but like in in like a half
sitting half about to run away manner
she was just like staring at me and
observing the
situation yeah she stayed pretty long
but I think eventually she ran away too
because she was like this [\h__\h] is too
noisy like when I started going from R
from walking to running she she ran away
too too loud too loud it is pretty loud
also I've noticed yesterday when I was
like really running on it or like
walking first of all I lost my balance
so often is this
normal even when I was looking straight
forward I feel like I'm like wobbly
wobbly do you guys get that too
sometimes you're like oh whoa whoa whoa
[Music]
and then I realized also like one of my
shoes was getting loose and I was
thinking oh I should like adjust it but
then I realized oh wait wait wait I
should really not just stop walking on
the treadmill because unlike walking
outside the treadmill will not stop with
my steps like you do IRL outside like
normal ground does normal ground doesn't
just move with you the treadmill does
it's different you have to remember that
and not just like out of out of uh what
you're just used to in everyday life
stop walking does do you guys ever do
that have you guys ever done that
forgetting that you're on a treadmill
and just like doing something
stupid I hope not I was close to doing
it but I didn't and then I also noticed
I feel like I don't know if they're all
this uh small but I feel like I don't
have that much space on my
treadmill but this is what I bought and
I think it was plenty expensive I'm not
going to buy a different one now but
yeah I think in the fitness center
they're way
wider generally and more
bulky mine's relatively
small small smaller tto
please be careful yeah you'll need less
space as your running posture gets
better yeah and as I get less
wobbly the one you got should be good
enough yeah but it's also uh constantly
on an angle I cannot change it which is
fine it's fine but it's a bit more
exhausting than just a flat
one but I just got to adjust myself with
that there's no incline no it's like
always always at an
angle no it's it's supposed to be like
that yeah just a little bit upwards
still not not too
much not too much
though you want to hear how loud loud it
is
guys it's right
here
oh oh smoothie came to check what's
happening with the
beeps oh she's she's looking very like
what the [\h__\h]
again okay I'm I think there's some
noise cancellation but I'm making it go
to like comfortable running
speed like this can you hear
[Music]
it oh oh she's smooy smooy she's
like let's turn it off off
again yeah so I also need louder
speakers or something because I realized
I can barely hear the show I'm
watching on the PC I even I I attached
some speakers which I normally never
do I always have headphones on here but
attached some speakers for once and even
at max volume I can barely hear
anything that's why you get earbuds is
that what you guys do cuz I was legit
also thinking to just use my noise
cancelling uh
headphones although I don't know how to
connect them to the
PC cuz they're Bluetooth I don't know if
I can do that but I can definitely
connect them to my um bedroom TV so I
was thinking maybe I'll move the
treadmill into the bedroom even though I
don't really have much space there
I might still move it over there I need
a Bluetooth
adapter I don't think my PC supports
bluetoth I think the the
broadcaster in theory uh supports
Bluetooth but I tried using it before I
tried connecting headphones Bluetooth
headphones but it didn't seem to be
working I don't know what I'm doing
wrong I went by a tutorial and it just
doesn't find it
but I have to figure it
out soon because I think I'll be wanting
to use uh wireless
headphones uh for
ofai I think actually that was just that
just reminded me I wanted to buy Ina had
these cool Road Wireless tiny ah leveler
I think they're called leveler I wanted
to get them let's see oh they're so
expensive but they they look really nice
and easy to
use Road Wireless
skull
oh lav wait which
one I have to look into this I have to
buy one I think they're a good solution
it's what we used for um streaming at
ena's place to
together because she only has like this
one main microphone but she thought if
it's us two together maybe it's more
comfortable having uh the leveler mics
so that we don't have to like lean
towards the
microphone is that like studio quality
kind of yeah I think so the only problem
is that it probably only lasts for like
an
hour that's what Ena says even though
here it says 15 hours battery
live is it
really ah well there's built-in
recording
for internal speech but when you use it
live maybe it's like it takes up more
batteries well I look into it I think
there's another good other option that I
saw but this one is same brand as my
roadter so I think they actually connect
really
easily even though I hate my
broadcaster I have those those can
connect ah see oh yeah yeah yeah I
thought so I think I like watch a video
on them connecting really easily
you have these you have these why do you
have these do you stream or
what w definitely needs a headphone
sponsorship I already got one are you
joking Lin did you not watch
my YouTube short and a stream where I
was using
them excuse me
hyper
X oh you yanked my chain whatever that
means I'm guessing that means I'm
teasing
you at this point I'd prefer a roadter
sponsorship at least for the microphones
but I have enough headphones at this
point I
think I mostly still use for just for
streaming I still use the fired one
though because it's
easier that wasn't sponsored oh yeah
true it wasn't sponsored it was just
free stuff that I I guess no that's
still kind of sponsored because I had to
make a video or so on it in order to get
it I think that's still still kind of a
sponsorship yeah I do hate the
roadter no I'm not
hated now that I you know have all
these options I like it
more but that's really the only good
thing about
it oh well uh where was
I a
here waterall danion Cru danion fried
screw
Dan that ends day one
of Minecraft
streams now I shall read day two which
has a lot of super chats because that's
the one where I was
mining that felt like it was yesterday
but apparently it was the
day the day before
yesterday no I went to the ID don't me
so that I could read
more for you guys check 47 Dan motion
Dan for the pinky it's my fourth
birthday as a kfp so much of my life has
changed in these past four years between
CID unig grad and starting work uh but
the one thing that stayed the same is
the comfortable home that I've had in
kfb thank you for all the fun every year
a that's beautiful I love to hear
that I'm glad you're still here I'm so
happy to like see people that are here
since like kind of the beginning see
that they're still here
[Music]
great
happy
birthday
[Music]
motion thank you thank you and I wish
you so much luck with all your endeavors
now that you've started work I don't
know how long that is ago but
yeah
F damn many lifechanging things like
graduating from University that's
big I'm glad you were able to do that JK
Monkey D tyon
D
[Music]
oh oh you're using the kfp fers for your
runs outside and you're going to adopt
the doggo let's go
exciting
exciting Studio thanks for the pinky
[Music]
my Nathan cotton thanks for the pinky
hien hoping on Mid break to say hope you
enjoy hooping on Mid break to say hope
you enjoy another day of being hardcore
I'm not going to read it the way you
wrote it also hope your diet is going
well thank you
uh so far I've lost no weight but it's
okay I was like I when I was like
running on my treadmill
I was um dressed very lightly because I
mean that's what you can do if you run
at home and not in
a not in a a fitness center so I had
like these booty shorts on and like a
short crop top okay and I was looking at
myself in my
reflection in the dark dark window and I
was like hey
yo booty is looking good
actually fires are looking good
too actually I look kind of
good but no I want my tummy to be a
little bit smaller
please no I know I know I know but I you
know you know sometimes you you
feel bad about yourself sometimes you
feel worse about yourself and you
know yeah the dresses I need to fit into
the
dresses
yeah my [\h__\h] dresses they cost so
much
money I need to get into
them too much
selfless no that's not self lesbian
that's selfcest excuse me
boohoo 72 fre
[Music]
Dan H life ID so many people joke about
being like Ana Ana's joke is being whole
live Japan other people from Japan they
joke about being whole live
English nobody jokes about being whole
life
Indonesia but I should be saying
that Ryden LS than Des than for the red
super chat y
oh I am oh I am oh oh oh oh thank you
oh now don't say it like that don't say
it like it's a
fact I am honorary yeah yeah
yeah since nobody outside ID speaks ID
well but are those Japanese members like
uh mikoi Senai and others who claim
their whole life Ian every once in a
while do those members speak
again H not
really no no no no okay desel says I
couldn't spend my fourth birthday as a
kfp on Wednesday with you and kfp but
I'm glad I could be here for this fun
stream with Ali and MAA oh yeah that was
the later stream right I'm looking
forward to what the next year looks like
for myself and especially you and the
rest of kfp love you boss love you too
thank
[Music]
you I don't know was it because I was
streaming so early is that why you
couldn't watch I'm sorry if that's the
case but you know I stream at better
times most of the time at least better
times depending on where you in where
you at but yeah uh thank you though
desol happy belated birthday
ah thank you for so much fun times
together as a kfp crusader this whole
Arc must have been kind of exciting for
you though cuz we went to war with the
Wither and then with another couple of
Withers and then with the End Dragon and
another couple of
Withers yeah good good War Arc for us in
Minecraft
thank you desol and happy
birthday Kiana's feathered protector
that's so cute that's so cute I love
that the yeah the worst of all pul him
but I guess if she does another news
show tomorrow and she reads the Diaries
I think she'll also probably report
about the
KY uh under selling totems thing I was
just wondering what else you could
report on cuz not much
happened unless maybe some stuff
happened like from the night of
yesterday to today that I'm not aware
of did those totems ever get used oh
yeah see I didn't need one I wonder did
did yeah did Ana have to use one and did
uh Co have to use one some of them got
used it's also just that you feel maybe
more confident just by having one and
then you're safer maybe I don't know
although that should maybe if you're too
confident should be the other way
around well well she used it differently
she was in a different situation
[Music]
Anya use it because P almost killed her
that's also not really what I was
considering I was thinking like during
the Ender
fight it was like R over again
exactly yeah you're so right
true there were no postmortal
achievements in the main fight I think
so too
huh
huh huh well I didn't need it
either title oh wait did I give Des a
kiss just in
[Music]
case oh yeah I read this
one I hope it won't really be like so
bad
delar d space waterfall Dan Bruce D
Cardinal
[Music]
crar same
same cppy sappy cppy B cppy sappy B
sappy
D swaner Dan Cardinal crowbar D
[Music]
Kim
you joh
[Music]
m
y
one
maybe
you and here comes the Red
Wave here comes the Red Wave uh watering
thank you for the red super chat already
thanked you on stream though but thank
you uh Bob Dylan thank you for the red
chat nice to see you again ien your
rough day today but listening to you
made me smile again also sorry for being
here a lot you mean not being here a lot
I think but yeah I'm still here love you
my
Kami love you too happy to see you
always Mery
B don't worry just having a life sign
every once in a while reliefs me from my
worries ziply thanks for the red super
chat sub Tano as of right now it's my
birthday I don't usually celebrate them
but last time you got kind of mad I told
you late so I promised to better my
ways have this as an apology stay cool
oh well okay I'm not even that late
either this time happy birthday
dipping Mah congratulations F thank you
for you know bettering
yourself not that you ever really had
to yeah so many birthdays today well not
really today but
yeah so many congratulations today
though yeah diply catch the kiss catch
[Music]
it I saw it flying
Sky Hollows me andly or May
17th but I feel like I read you on
different
streams did you catch it did you catch
it simply is 18
yeah random collusion thanks for the red
super chat ancient debris times one no
no no no time over
20 but I know what you mean you are the
ancient
debris thank you you know I was randomly
colliding with ancient debris quite
often
too for real though like this is so
fitting thank you for starting the wave
cuz I think uh you are who started the
wave for real for
real but and dougle Jones thanks for the
red of chat here's some l f thank
you it worked out in the end all was
well I looked super [\h__\h] cool thanks
to you guys thank you
viia see bass also thank you for the red
super chat indeed it is very red thank
you J swag Burg thank you for the red
super chat too you guys are so crazy
thanks for the jumbo siiz Minecraft
streams L they weren't even that long I
thought I would be streaming way longer
each day but maybe I would have had more
longer streams if I started from the
beginning but the in the end like there
wasn't much more to do besides fighting
the Wither and fighting the Ender Dragon
no you know it was probably for the
best so that first of all the VOD
Watchers are not being overloaded with
vods and also that I could take it easy
here and there
so this there wait I didn't put the
thumbnail up what the
[\h__\h]
okay and where was I yeah and thank you
to SW B R thank you for the red super
chat for the luck yay for the win with
the luck I win thank you
Rana for participating in the the red
craziness Tassimo thank you also for the
red super chat skirt I'll have to join
in here's one for good
luck you guys
why you oh maybe okay I think I
understand you guys see
red on white assuming you're in not in
dark mode Let's just say you're not and
you think ah
friend because chicken friend red white
friend must make more friend so you send
red Super Chat to make more friend and
then we have many many
friends yeah I get it now it's like a
chain reaction that is only possible
within
kfp no no no just for the situation you
have to say that you are not using dark
mode because otherwise my explanation
makes no sense
friend yes cute
friend kind of weird looking friend but
still friend pretty sure it's friend
yeah yeah yeah Tassimo also friend M
Mary Pippin also friend don't take this
as me friend zoning you you know it's
just just just just just mer Pippin
thank you for the recipe chat we just
like you isn't that enough yes you like
also all the other friends that's why
you sent that didn't you is that not why
Mary Pippin is that not why thank you
the chicken Zone yeah welcome to the
chicken Zone Mary pins want to watch L
of durings Ah that's right I think we
can start next week with monat first
season uh I'm planning it on Saturday uh
we're going to start like at 400 p.m. or
so w time I don't know how long it's
going to take but we're going to watch
the full
season so you got perms um it's kind of
weird uh
it's
okay it should be fine I was told oh it
should be fine
[Music]
it we'll watch it together um because I
think uh my DVD or Blu-ray for the first
season should
arrive uh in a few days like I think
like very soon in the next couple days
so yeah we can watch the first season B
mon yeah five for six five to six hours
for season one wow
okay col it five to 6 hours
shees no problem no
problem also a short stream yeah but
I'll make sure to not uh tangent too
much before and also in between we need
to get this done okay I cannot
underestimate how much time it will take
you don't have to like you can even just
watch a few episodes with us jump in
somewhere in the beginning or at the end
or the middle if you want um yeah intro
outro I don't know that would be hard if
we skip it it'll be a little bit hard to
uh time everybody I
[Music]
think it's uh members only I was
thinking of doing it members only
yeah oh yeah we can skip the outro cuz I
think usually there's nothing
afterwards yeah so everybody prepare
bakim monoar season one until Saturday
okie dokie okie
dokie okie
doie where was
IU thank you for the red super chat it's
okay because it's payday hope this
brings luck for another ancient de yay
thank you makaku welcome to the chicken
Zone Tim Tracy also thank you for the
redp chat Phoenix like boost thank you
and welcome to the chicken
zone so many chickens s d chy thank you
for the red super chat as well good luck
thank you welcome to the chicken
Zone and fried Screw As Wow might as
well we just love W thank you you guys
are so generous thank you and welcome to
the chicken
Zone
ter not quite there but still thank you
n also welcome to the chicken
Don you entertain us that's all you need
to deserve it thank you thank you so
much you guys went a little bit
overboard though let's be real thank you
so much I appreciate it M
and welcome to the chicken Zone K to you
too thank you for the red super chat and
resine also sending one thank you so
much welcome to the chicken Zone let's
go t let's go thank you for the support
and being so
generous see this is where it calmed
down a little bit my throat hurts w why
does it hurt so much why why I'm
drinking so much
water lunchbox space waterfall
Kon uh thank you oh hey yo your heart is
at risk what what nothing
nothing no my stream was not
so doy doie inducing right
zum bont
than and thank you thank you myin um
pyro thank you for the pinky no you're
actually smelling oh what I'm the color
of pink super chats it Blends so well
with my pfps hair color yeah I would say
it's more red than pink though now that
I see it next to each other background
Blends seamlessly as a green super chat
but that's not as cool Co and Chan has
the scent of fox and toasted
fruit is that the name of the person in
your or should I say the furry in your
profile
picture is that is that
it Coen
joh maybe I take that as a
yes thank you for the
pinky and
uh Cruz D soon zap Min D GD thanks for
the red super chat to my lovely lucky
wonderful amazing
Kami yeah you guys were telling me on
Twitter too that apparently I was really
lucky was I
really thank you TD for the red super
chat and for chilling with me in these
streams I hope just this once you were
able to sleep through
an actual night or or did you guys did
my Australian viewers change their sleep
schedule for these streams or did you
keep the usual sleep schedule the crazy
one that you have to keep in order to
watch me it would be nice if you
actually got to sleep through a night
like a normal human
being I don't have a sleep schedule oh
no it's bad for your health
probably imagine sleeping at
night I sleep whenever you are not
streaming you're actually okay
see maybe the reason why I don't really
do Guerilla streams is because I feel
bad for people like you I don't want to
like have you either feel bad because
you missed a stream or like mess
everything up in your life because I
suddenly stream and you have you thought
I wouldn't and you have to throw plans
around again in order to watch it so
maybe it's good that I don't do gorilla
streams yeah but generally if I feel
like I could possibly be streaming on
that day I'm just going to schedule it
gorilla is not really my
style there was that time you told us to
go to bed and then change your mind and
try to wake us all up until yeah cuz I
felt
bad here in Vietnam it's basically 4:00
a.m. every time you stream a I basically
use your streams as a background voice
to sleep M that's nice I also always
listen to something
on the TV to fall
asleep what or utan streams what what
what
what what you mean what what do you
mean the one collab uh we had for that
one game a long time
ago where I used the
art where we were all monkeys
or I know it's a monkey but yeah the
gorilla something is that what you're
referencing the fasmo
collab that was gorilla
yeah but that's really late oh wait you
know you're just like making a joke
about gorilla streams and orur Udan
streams and monkey streams or whatever
that's what you're saying
man ah didn't get it I didn't understand
your joke Council got delayed that day
wait was it council's debut that got
delayed I completely forgot that their
debut got
delayed
H
H that was a thing
that's why I made that
[Music]
stream yeah I on cuz it was a weekend
and we were keeping like some stream
times open for the debuts but then it
didn't
[Music]
happen yeah that was kind of nice that
was fun everybody was like getting
together just you know
for a normal stream but we were all
having
fun I mean the viewers
[Music]
too good times good
times good times you know it's always
nice I'm I'm generally always excited
for new people to join actually I say
that now but I think it may have been
different at
times um especially in the beginning cuz
um you know I just felt like you know we
we were doing
fine but generally I feel like you know
it's always exciting to have new people
and I'm I'm open for it and all that uh
it adds excitement and it adds new great
friendships like narissa for example but
then at the same time I'm also like
feeling
nostalgic and kind of miss the times
where we were less people cuz it was we
were all like
doing more stuff together just because
we were less people and we were you know
closer uh bonded and you know it was
like yeah when it was only myth it was
just about us and yeah like not saying
that uh I want everything to be about us
but it's just like um it felt more like
a small close-knit family m
and then the more people join the more
it feels like at the same time that
everything has scattered like this
closet family of myth like you know like
may maybe cie will go and be close with
like Iris and Bales and do stuff with
them which is great like there's no
problem with that just like me like I
also get close and do other stuff with
other people but you know what I'm
trying to say it's just like times
change and then the interactions change
and the collab change and everything
kind of changes the focus changes the
vibe changes the atmosphere changes and
both are
great things to have both are great
times both are great great eras in h
live
English but I'm sure that people who
also have been watching since the early
days when it was just myth I'm sure you
guys also kind of can relate a little
bit because those times were really
precious and
special to me and to the others too I
think and probably to you guys
[Music]
too
yeah oh now I feel little emotional
I don't know why I don't know
why
[\h__\h] I got tears in my eyes I got too
emotional
I don't know why I'm
crying I don't even know
[Music]
why how did we get here from a gorilla
joke
okay I'm good I'm
okay I'm
okay yeah getting nostalgic and
sentimental oh
[\h__\h] okay
okay let's just finish these super
[Music]
chats
you unknown things for the red super
[Music]
chat what the [\h__\h]
man I need a tissue I hate it when all
the
fle them goes into my
throat YouTube crashes my browser every
time I try to send a super chat but
nothing can stop me from giving you
money you did so amazing today I'm super
proud of you Wawa thank
you thank
you yeah you made it in time all good
thank you for the big support thank
you don't make me cry again Coral go you
little
[\h__\h] you little
[\h__\h] man
don't don't hit me with the
feels if you read the Super Chat I sent
earlier you will laugh what from
today from
today uh uh uh from
today today
today today today
uh I don't see
one what how much
earlier I don't see it I'm
scrolling okay I calmed down though it's
okay last banging ah it last member
stream what I'm not gonna go there
now let me finish this thank you
unknown thank you soon wait so are you
are you still there or did you you you
flew right you flew back to
Australia I hope I hope you didn't miss
too much of the stream cuz you were so
worried about
it welcome back to Australia
how's the weather is it hotter in
Australia or in Thailand probably in
Thailand
right you didn't miss anything
y
nice weather is cool and nice
really pretty cold in Australia really
damn it's cold now town is probably more
humid yeah I can
imagine it's Autumn now oh yeah right
you're the other way around right it's
not spring I guess it's Autumn and then
it will be winter you're not going
towards Summer right now right I totally
forgot that for a
moment we're going towards Summer but
not
you so
is spider sees
that was also like a an an an argument
to why the [\h__\h] are you guys all
Barefoot I know I talked about this
yesterday now I'm bringing it up
again but to my Australian viewers is
this really a pretty common site to see
so many people run around barefoot in
Australia might I I taste the snot e
it
happens I don't even I don't even want
to judge you because as a child I was
barefoot more
often not even only on the grass even on
the
pavement and it's nice if you feel like
the neighborhood or so that you're
walking in is like clean enough like no
no glass sharts or whatever to do that
you know that's nice
but yeah can't be so sure about it yeah
that was a
childhood I would never touch anything
on the street with my bare skin is it so
dirty
then
maybe [\h__\h] it's not maybe spider poop
is all
over you just don't see it how big is
spider poop huh
how depends on the spider I guess how
big is spider
poop the real
questions not an inches I want to know
in wa I'm going to look at pictures
e e e what did I
expect
e it's like just a [\h__\h] ton of dots ha
[\h__\h] ton but somehow it looks very
disgusting oh that's
disgusting
oh oh that's so disgusting but those
must have been pretty big
spiders I think that's pretty big
spiders oh this is not a picture of poop
this is a picture
of wait maybe it's poop and spiders
cuz I see a [\h__\h] ton of small
spiders on top of something that
maybe I don't even
know average ay
spider okay I need to I need to spit out
the snot to let's finish this I think
there were like two or so yeah
Cannonball Dan Alvar danash and I am a
danash I'm going to spit out all my not
now spit and blow it
out but I'm not going to swallow this
[\h__\h] again I'm going to sprit it out so
in German we say
in schedule a little bit later
today by
oh disgusting disgusting
[Music]
waa bye-bye