[Music]
[Music] I'm
Iris, thank you very much.
[Music]
Thank you.
[Music] There's
a bit of lag.  Yes, I
had a very touching experience with my brother,
so today I
don't want to die, but
let's continue.
[Music]
Hello everyone, good evening. I'm
Kihara Takanashi from Hololive English.
[Music]  I
have some experience with the game, but I've
never been able to import it during distribution, so I
'm nervous.
Thank you for your help.
This
game has a bit of a map and
has ramps, so I'm sure it will work.
If it's not there, it's a voice. Are you
talking even though it's not there?
[Music]
While we're making it, everyone please introduce yourself.
Paradise
[Music] I
'll do my best
[Laughter]
[  music]
Thanks to everyone's kindness, I have been able to participate in the competition today.
Thank you very much.
[Music] As
someone who has worked in Japan, I hope I can
ask everyone about things they don't understand.  I
think so.
[Music]
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Well then, this
is the back button for Hololive Awakening. Today, it looks like I'll be
able to talk a lot with everyone, so I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you in advance
[Music]  This
is Gamers Shirakami. Today, I'm
going to go to this Armon training camp Crew Bait. I'm
definitely going to go there with that Hacos cheese on my head.
Thank you.
[Music]
Yes,
everyone, straight to this live 3rd generation.  This
is Shirokane-no-ma, please. No, I'm
really nervous, but
please do your best. I'll try my best to use both English and Japanese.
By the way, I can't speak English.
Thank you for your
support.Five
Stars Yukihara Rummy Hey
[Music]
Yes, there
may be some trouble, but please stay warm and
take care of me until now.I'm
prone to big troubles, so I'll take care of you
once.  I feel like doing the weather inside the cat's room,
so I'm going to do it at high speed.So
when I call you, I hope you'll say yes.Yes.  If
you couldn't hear it, please tell me you couldn't hear it. Yes, yes.
When you get closer, the voice gets louder, and when you
move away, it gets smaller like this. Right
?
[Music]
The name is Top Shaxx,
but it's
Comet Hoshimatsu. Nice to meet you.
Thank you very much.
[Applause] Can you
hear me? Yes, yes, yes,
yes, I can hear you. I'm white, I can hear you.
Yes, I'm in paradise.
[Music] I
can hear you, yes.
[Applause]
Can you hear me?
[Laughter]
[Music]
There's a bit of a lag, so please wait a moment. Yes,
Aoi
[Music]
Lee, I
hear you. Can you hear me?
[Music] [
Music]
[Music]
Just like before.  It just
sounds very small,
but I'm saying that I want you to continue as usual.I
was thinking that it might be better to have people talk on Discord instead of normal times.
So please, Iris
[Music]
[Music] I
think it's ok to mute it first.
So let's get on with it. Let's go like that. Let's
go ahead.
[Music]
Senpai
[Music]  ]
[Music]
Oh,
I've never done that either. That's
right.
[Music]
Wait a minute.
[Music] Do you want to continue?
Okay, so here we go. Do you want to
continue? Okay, yes.  Is this
a meeting?
Yes, I just saw Ramy Ramy's dead body,
and I
saw that senior Elite Meko senior
really jumping into the lunch box.
[Applause] It
was love
[Music]
[Laughter]
Huh? [Music] I think I saw it for a moment.  I can't help but wonder
who that person I was walking with
earlier was Aki-senpai. Was it Fubuki-senpai from Akisen? We
were around there together.  I was
walking. I wasn't with him. I was the only one who saw the
corpse. I guess I didn't get this far. I was so
moved by being able to talk that I didn't look at anything.
[Laughs] I guess I was
nervous.
Let's do it.
[Laughs]  [Laughter] Let's
play a test.
[Music]
Mito-senpai, my junior is lying. Are you really
saying that?
[Laughter] He
only tells the truth, right? There's nothing he can
say back. I
'm sorry. [Music] [Laughter] Is that so, bro?  Who are you?
[Music]
Please don't kill me,
please don't kill me
[Music]
Definitely, that cheese, that cheese. Well, my new
member Bales-chan
wants to eat it, but
wait, it's dark.
[Music] I
can't hear you, I
can't hear you.
Hey
[Music] It's a
voice next to me. I
can hear it. Is it a
voice?
Hello, hello.
[Music] [Music]
[Laughter]
[Music]
When everyone was stopping at the reactor.
Button Paradise's top saxophone
was left alone
in front of the door, and Paradise was in front of him,
telling everyone to follow, so they all followed. What the heck is
going on around the entrance to the office, that
admin at the entrance to the Green House?  Once upon a time, I was
doing the task at the entrance to the Green House, and there was a power outage, so
I went to fix the retirement, and when I
went to check on it, it was dead. Is this the
Aiai Balbaru
button?  It
's Mr. Bare Bare Button.
[Laughs] It was like that
before too. I
couldn't hear Corone-senpai's voice anymore. Hmm,
where was I? I was in my management office. Oh no,
seriously, seriously, right before that, Suisei-senpai.
And Corone-senpai was with me.
So I went to the office
and I could already see that Swiss-senpai had gone, so I
went to the management room, thinking that the lights would be turned on
anyway.
There's also a possibility that it was a self-talk, so I can hear that voice this time.
I'm already going to kill him. I couldn't hear Corona-senpai's next line after he said it about Corona. He
killed me from below, after all. He was with me.
That's why Tsuichan's line is funny
. Sui-chan and I were together when the power
went out. I was there with Sui-chan. That's why it
must have been that. It was a power outage. Oh no. I was inside.  I'd
understand if she came later, but she came first, so it's probably
not true, but she
hasn't seen it.She hasn't seen it, but she hasn't seen it either, but I wonder what
Sui-chan will say when it becomes about who is the two of them.
Yo
[Music]
That's right, you
can listen to me. I
want you to listen to me, but
there's something I'd like you to hear
from me. I've been hearing the voice of Miko-senpai's ghost all this time.
I'm already feeling so bad that I
can't talk at all.
[Music] I
want to do it with my brother.
[Music]
Do it once, do it once, do it twice, and then
switch back to normal mode.
My brother is coming back,
so it's ok, please.
[Music] I'm
sorry I saw it, but it's okay. It's okay, I did it.
There's no one like that coming in
.
[Music] It's like
everyone's there, or so.  Yo  Let's
find out
[Laughter]
[Music]
What should I do? Air syrup, no.
[Music] Something like that [Music]
Please
[Music]
Thank you, thank you, OkOk
[Music]  I
think something like 60 is fine. The default one is OK. It might work here or there. I'm used to it.
Country name: Yeah, it's
North America, but I want to put it in.
[Laughs] I
put this in there.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Stop it, stop it, stop it so I can eat you Stop it,
stop it, stop it
[Laughter]
Childbirth
turns into a lunch box [Music
]
Or was
there a paradise too?
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] I
'm in the Communications room.
[Music]
[Laughter] I was
working on that task at Electrical right now,
and I met Daffodil-senpai.  I
met one of my seniors who wanted to stand there alone, and we talked for a bit, then left again. That's right, I
found the Electrical.
Actually, I
went counterclockwise from the cafeteria to the Electrical,
but
during that time, I
didn't meet anyone.
Everyone was on the right.  I
think it's because Tiara came in, as Tiara said earlier when she entered Electrical.
From the cafeteria, you went to the admin, and then
from the admin to the electrical. I see. But that's right. From the cafeteria, you went to the admin, and then you
went down to the electrical. You must have met someone who was at the electrical, after all.
We
went to the admin.
What about the timing?
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
Well, something like Electrica is fine. I was
screaming at my place just now. No one said that. Yes, I
found Noel, but due to the timing, there is a
possibility that Mr. Button pressed it to erase the sketch, so it's
correct.  No, it's electric right now, it's
dead because it's electric. Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right. So
in terms of timing, the timing of finding it
and the timing of pressing it
was that. But that's what
happened earlier.
[Music]
On the contrary, on
the other hand, no one has done it yet,
Schiffer Noel-senpai, I
think me and Fubu-chan
stopped it. Yes, I stopped it.
There were people who stopped it, and on the other hand, there were people who
hadn't turned off the oxygen, and people who hadn't come. When I
tried to go across from Lamy,  It was over, yeah, it
was over right in front of my eyes, and I had to do it a little while ago,
so what are you? So I really
had the same timing, so now...
[Music] [Music] [
Music]
[Music]
[Music] I
went to the shield room, but there were
two events going on
there, so I thought this place was definitely going to be attacked, so
while I was heading from the shield room to the storage room, I saw that board and...  I'm
standing in between,
so there's no storage
in front of the communications bean,
no storage, no
, I'm
Japanese.Discussion The
last time I met with my senior was in the shield room,
in the front and in the back.
Fubuki-senpai put it in the wrong lunch box once.
Do you know? It's over there. I wonder if it's
Senpai.
[Music]
What's going on?
Hey,
Button-senpai
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[  [Laughs]
No, no, no. I was
running and asking if anyone was there, and
the first person who
came to me was Iris, so I killed her.
[Laughs] I
should have done that.
[Music]
[laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
Hello Akorone-senpai.
Can I shake your hand? No, no, you
can believe me. It's
far away.
Hello Christmas tree Sears.
[Music] [Music
]
[Music]
That Christmas  What's going on today? This
is a Christmas tree. I
saw the body. I
went into Denki's Rare with Yuki and Senpai, and there were both dead bodies.
[Music] The
last time I saw Elite Mikoto on set.  Tano
Ha, yeah,electric
Eh, there
's another Ranramy here.
[Music] I
feel like there's another person who's come in after that. I
remember what color it is. I remember what color it is.
Wait, in Discord, now, Miko-senpai is
that big brother.  I think he was
translating that deep voice in English with the Japanese army,
but after that, he said, ``I want to do it with the demons,'' and he said
in English, ``I want to do this with the demons.''  It's
like, ``I want to do it.'' It's like, ``I'm going to
scream.''
[Music]
Then someone comes and does a dub
kill. I think it's a dub kill of Iris and Paradise,
but
when I found it, it was me and Paradise.  Also,
Tiara and Kira were there like Tiara, and the
three of them were there, and the three of them were there, so
there were two of them.
[Music]
[Laughter]  I'm
going with just one vote
What, here I am, my Spoo-san [Music] [Laughs] You're exposing me in so many ways, no,
no, so
cute.
[Music] I
just saw
that.
Yes, that's right.
Sui-chan was lying on the side of the road where Button-chan was walking.
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter] Do you
have an explanation?
If I were to say something back to you, I
guess I was just trying to go to the first birth room.
[Laughs] I was
trying to go to the oxygen robe. It
came from the oxygen room.
No, it's not coming. It's not coming. It's
not coming.
But...  The
archive is the proof.
[Laughs]
That's right, I don't understand it now, but
[Music]
This is still that. It
was bad timing, right?
[Laughs]
-
[Music] I hope you
can hear me, Kanami-chan's heaven.  I
can hear voices of all kinds right now.I'm
living my life with all kinds of sounds on my shoulders.I
wonder who the other imposter is.I think there were probably a lot of two-person acts, like a
double kill or
something like that.  I'm a little
suspicious of myself, I
think it's Lamy-chan...
[Music]
Could you please change it a little?
[Applause]
[Music]
Iris is nice.
Can you hear me?
[Music]
[Laughter] It's
so much fun.
[Music]
[Laughter]
OK.
[Music]
Everyone's finally
broken.  It
's a virus, it's a virus It's the
same map
[Music] It
looks like a vtuber It
's true
[Music] -
Please
[Music]
[Applause]
By the way, I said I was an imposter one more time.
[Music]
[Music] I
saw someone doing something in the boiler room near the water
[Music]
I hit the boiler.  Okay,
Fubuki-senpai came from above.I
reported him from the security department saying that he had killed a little girl.
So, this one, I thought that if that happened to Senpai, he would die,
but he wasn't killed, so I have
a little faith in him.
[Music] I
don't know, but I guess I can
see. When I
looked at that, two people were dead, and I
said if I didn't let it go, I might wear a double coat.
When I went to the management room, Tsui-chan was
there.
[Music]
[Music] I
saw it. I
saw it.
Ah, OK.
YES
OhYeah
Ohame.
Oh, OK.
Senpai.
Good, good, good,
Water-senpai
Joint
[Music]
Hey,
uh, where did I find the dungeon?
But right after you
exit the boiler room, there's a
weapon room, and anyway, right after exiting on the right side, that
Olly-chan
was dead, but
like that leader.  What's really weird is that when Fubuki-senpai and
Alice-chan
put it into practice
, they first
had to repair the moon, so they
went to the electrical room electrical room to repair the moon.
Then I saw Fubuki-senpai and Iris-chan, and
Iris-chan was there, too, and
there were a lot of other people there, too.The leader
was working in a blank area above Boilash, so I went over
there.  Hey, Fubuki-senpai and Iris-chan
came. I thought they were there,
but they were out at Boilerush,
so I thought they weren't there, but I was working alone. And then there were those
two.  Maybe
after I did it, I'd come back up after doing it
and it would have been different, and if I
passed by and looked at it, I'd
probably be the leader.The reason I couldn't kill it was probably because
of that cooldown.
That's what I thought, but I guess you weren't there anymore. No,
you were working on your tasks in the boiler room, and the
guys from above came along with you.
When I was there, I was heading directly in the direction of Uemoto.
Yes, that's why it's strange to testify that way. Eh,
who's that
? Enoel
isn't in it. I
went to the left side and saw her breasts.
[Music]
Oh, hello.
[Music] I
think that's it.  But on the other hand, if you're feeling a little scared, I
think you can just watch Iris-chan. I'll just surround her and see a
cat watching somewhere.
[Music]
I still have one emergency left, so yeah, uh,
let me in.  You
can also make a sound, but if you
do that and it causes a power outage, I
feel like a roller would be fine, but I
also think it's fine.  Let's
go on an adventure. Okay. [Music] It's supposed to end. You're supposed to be
done. [Applause] I'm sorry. [Music] I thought you were gone somewhere. I
lost sight of you. [
Laughter]
[Music]
What's going on with this? The kill cooldown
is 27.5. Yes, but is this enough?
Yeah, let's do that. It's
okay.
[Music]
Start
[Music] Hey, there are
three
[Music]
Teacher.  Teacher, I saw
you [music] I saw you there with me, and
I was scanning them, right?
Below that scan, there's a map.  I
went into the D Kancharumination room, and
when I was going out, I saw them go out together.
Where was the body? Well, it was mainly the women's room. Well, I
thought I'd find it and do it myself, so
maybe Olly did it himself.  I pressed the report.
Well, I really
enjoyed the place that was twice as recommended.
[Music]
[Music] I don't think
this is
anything special.
[Laughs] I
have time to vote, so I might want to decide on that one.  He's
not a suspicious person, but
there must be an impostor next to him.Well,
this year, he was with Chiara.Yeah,
right now, those two
have been together for quite some time, so it
's probably safe for both of them.
[Music] I
guess I'll go with Fubuki-senpai. I'll
have someone come with me.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Yes,
Paradise-kun,
where, where, where,
where, where, appeal
OK, Aki-senpai, ah,
nice pen cue  It's
common to have drop tails on the sides, right? Yes, the left
and right people
went to the left.
As I was walking towards the right side like this,
Chiara-chan was vibrating at the bottom, and
Lamy-chan and Button-chan were running on the left side.  I
saw them running around, so I think these two are probably different.
[Applause] I was
running around, and I
didn't know what was in all the different places, so I
ended up running around all over the place.
[Music]
He ran off towards the bottom,
but underneath it was Chiara-chan's
corpse, which
wasn't there when I was running.
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [
Music]
[Music]  ]
[Applause]
You know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you're right now, you
're at the end, you're about to hold your hands
together, and when you meet Aki-senpai and you hold your hands together, you
think, oh, it's teamwork TT, and then you
get killed.
[Music]  ]
Others
After we overlapped, I couldn't go anymore.
Button-senpai has already
been Imposter many times,
but I guess I'll kill him if he becomes Impossa next time.
But today, I do
n't want to do it again. I don't want to do it anymore.
Ok
[Music] I
want to see Impossa.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] [Laughter] [
Applause]
[Music]
[Applause  ]
[music]
[Applause]
[Music] There are Noel-
senpai, me, Rami-chan, and Comet-senpai, but
Noel is dead,
which means that for me, only Rami-chan and
Comet-senpai are left.By the way,
that's what I'm going to do, but who is that
Noel?  They split up soon. Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm like,
wait, wait a minute,
uh,
security-wise, they're doing this, and
privately, I'm thinking the same thing, and I'm going to press this button.  That's
what I thought, and by the way, I
didn't remember Ravi, so there's no way he doesn't remember, because we were together a lot.So I
remember that there was that other person,
but
yeah, no, no, this one is a bit strange, no, he's
not there.  I
think this is a button.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] I
want to hear it, Nami-
chan. I
was there. I was there, right? That's
Sui-chan and
Shishiron.
Ramy and what else is there, Mr. Noel and Parker are here,
so let's go in.
[Music]
Father Anne outside
[Music] Let's do some
karaoke.
Ah, let's
do some karaoke. It
's a tour.
[Music]
[Music]  I
guess you should ask him where he is, so let's tell him where he is.Yes,
I was in the room next to him.  There
was something that turned it, boil rush. I saw Kana Aki-senpai and I was breathing. Yeah, I was in the oxygen room, and the vacant senior was from the government. It hurts, because we were together for a while. Eh, where is the place in the first place? Right in the middle of the upper door in the upper room. The
door closes.  I think they probably turned off the lights and
let everyone go upstairs. I
guess that's what happened.
Where was the body? It was
in the weapon room until about the time the lights went out.  I
think it was someone who was nearby.
[Music]
I was alone with my senior. We were
in the math room. The
amount of oxygen was right in that oxygen room. Yes, it was in that oxygen room.
Yeah, I guess it was in the electrical room. Well then,
that corpse.  Who was nearby?
Who was who?
Chiara, who was far away.
Who? When did he die? I don't have
a photo of his face. Who
was that? I was looking at him, wasn't he?  I saw it  I
didn't see what happened after we were together, so I
think he probably left it there.
Yes, that's why I was chasing him,
or was it someone I just happened to meet?
I left the left side with this senpai.
[Music]
Safety, safety, oh, it's so difficult. What should we do? I
might not understand, but this is a problem.
I think you'll show up every now and then.
[Music]
[Music] [Music]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]  ]
You know, this is the most important thing to do.
This
is what you did. Did you do it? What did you do? What did you
do? No, I
can't do this anymore.
[Laughs]
Is this a confession?
[Music]
I pretended to be Lamy, I think someone else was the culprit.
[Laughs]
That's right, big brother, it's suspicious, suspicious, suspicious.
This was definitely the culprit.
But
I thought Ori was next.  The very first
Because she was laughing so hard, I thought it was suspicious.
Really?
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] [
Music] [
Laughter]
[Laughter]
[Music]
Karaoke Sisters  Probably the guy
Charm Best
[Music]
Who was the last person to see it? I saw it over there.
But my brother wasn't there with me at that time,
but I
think we saw it together.
[Music] He was on the
laboratory side.  hey  I
was there, and I was playing that guy on the other
side. He was doing it, he was doing it, he
was doing it, he was doing it, he was out, and he was 5 minutes older. Who was that? He was
in there with the descendant. He was
in there, but the
red one was there.  There's something like a medical checkup,
right? I
remember getting bored,
but
Sui-chan, on the other hand, why is there an emergency meeting
now? I'm sure Fubu-chan was probably with me right now,
right?
Well, there's something called Vital over there, and I
recently saw someone die, so
if I remember correctly, Miko, Senpai, and Olly
went into the women's room together and said that
after they left.  Also, I'm
pretty sure it wasn't Tiara and someone else who went in as a group.
No, it wasn't. It wasn't
someone, it was AccuRose.
It wasn't someone who went in with Senpai.
Well, I'm a woman, so I was the only one who entered, but
before that, I saw Lamy-chan in the laboratory, she was
rubbing Tiara-chan, and I think I
might see Button-chan in front of her as well.The
two of us are going in together.  That's because
Olly and Miko-senpai were right at the time when I said that.
[Music]
Where were you in the future?
Should I go to the storage room and see what's going on in the office below Tom?
[Music]
Please
Hey, I remember
[Music]
[Music] I
'm not the leader, I'm not the leader. It was really dark and I couldn't
see. I
really
want to, I don't know where I found it. I
know, I know, normally. I'm
sure the leader was on top of the electric.  Ni,
Mizusei-senpai,
from the laboratory: Yeah,
that
electrical room was dark, so I
went there to fix it, and Sui-chan
told me that I knew exactly what it was,
and then I was about to leave.  I
was behind Sui-chan, so if that's the case, there would
be a dead body, and I'd definitely be suspicious.I
think it was either Sui-chan or Noil-senpai,
but the moment I saw that, that nee-nee flopped and was
about to fall.  You really
think he's dead,
so I fixed it and the screen went blank, and
when it changed, Noel was nearby,
and when he went out, he saw a dead body, and
Noel went to the security side.  Nede me
I
went to the right side from Electrical, but at that time, it flopped and
fell down, so it's
not impossible that another person killed it and made a U-turn at the moment Noiru came in. I
think that's the case,
really.  It's
a bit weird if the moment you fall down and Noiro is the security guy.
[Music]
[Laughs]
If you talk a lot, it might be a little like that
[Music]
Please stay behind Sui-chan
IhaveNowyoubling
Fightisto
Oh
your mybends
Fightingsundays
please
Donki-senpai
can't do it
[Music]
Where was it discovered? It's right in
front of Vital. I think I saw it.
Yes, Vital is
something like an electrocardiogram on this map.  That's where it comes out
.
[Music]
Well, I'm
sorry about that, but you
can go get some ramen. Uko-
senpai.
Until now.
What kind of passage did it use to come out like that? What kind of passage did it
use to come out like that?
Okay, everyone, please take a moment to talk about Miho-chan. I've been thinking
about cats.  You were watching it, right? So
who was the last one to go there? Yes,
at the beginning, we
were doing tasks in the room with Miko-chan and Lamy-chan, but after that.  There was a
power outage at the electrical,
so I thought I should go that way,
but I found it near the area where
Minnie came out of the electrical, but I couldn't find Minnie for
some reason.  We
only ran together for about 8 seconds,
so to be
honest, I don't
think I can make that judgmental judgment now.
[Music] Maybe it would be
faster to find the reason why Fubu-chan died.  That's
right, I was wondering if it had moved by venting,
but I
don't know when it died, but
what do you mean when you said you saw Coronet?
Well, I
looked at it on the camera in the security room, and it
was showing. I was
running out of time,
so if I had to let anyone
in, I'm sorry. [Laughs] It's okay, I'm not doing it, so I
don't think so.
That and Niko-senpai
Okinawa Is it a
chance? It
's not Cascus
. Communication
[Music]
Who's going to finish with just one more?
I want someone to come with me. Well then, I'm a comet.
About Senpai.  I guess I should go,
but I'm alone with Corona-senpai right now. I'll
say it. I'll say it. Yes, I
saw it. Yes, I did it. So I guess we're all
together.
Well then, I follow someone.
Recommendation: There
's one thing about my seniors. They do each
task one by one, but it's
my fault. If that
happens, it would be
a waste, so I'd like to talk about it.
Everyone, I
saw you go into the reception room.  But it
's a female director.
[Music]
There's something about this senior that I think is a little suspicious, but for quite some time now, I
was looking for a room for my camera, and I was running towards it.
Even though I didn't finish the task, I
went to the task stand with you for a long time. Why do you
have something to do
? I'm
afraid you'll get suspicious, so it's the same as before. It
won't be hard if you're alone, so I'll come with you.
When I looked around, there were about 5 people in the electrical room,
so when I thought about it, I was the only one left,
so I looked in front of the vital signs.
Since Fuu-chan was dead, I saw a woman acting like this, so I
think Coroney killed Wanchan.
[Laughs]
[Music]
OkOkOkOkOk
Where is this senior sesh saxophone? Hmm,
what happened? Yes, he's not
dead.  I'm wondering if
everyone is doing well.Someone is okay.I'm going to follow you.I
feel like I can talk about this task.I feel like I can do it.Okay,
me too.Okay,
then I'll give my best regards to Corona-senpai.Yes, okay.
[Music]
What do you think?
Well, I
honestly don't know, but it's
difficult. That's
true. That
's right. That's right
. There's definitely one person left.
Yeah, then,
skip. Yes, then
follow me. That tic.
Senpai
Yes, yes, yes, yes
[Music]
[Laughter]
That's right. I
was in my hands, but the
leader
was there. I was
concentrating, so someone must have gone to the other side.
After that, I looked behind me and
Kirara-chan
was dead.
Open Rose-senpai
[Music] It
didn't stop on the right, so I went to Swiss-senpai and I on the right,
so we're not here.I
remember my grandma, who was always using her hands, and her hands
were big, so
even though I could see her shaking, I was Corona
FC2
Senpai remains on the left.
Is
n't there a possibility that Aki-senpai is like that? He doesn't have an enchu, but the
leader
kept using his hands and was
the first to go to the left.
[Music]
Hmm.
Before I reported it myself, I was
thinking, ``There's no point in leaving the paradise on the left side.'' I thought, ``If it's chan, I won't be able to do it.'' When we
both
went to the left side, we saw a lot of kids
chatting, but
everyone
went to the right side.  Mr. Paradise
[Music]
[Applause]
Odara: Just now, Koruru-senpai
said that he was suspicious because he didn't do the task, right?  You
were trying really hard, weren't you?
[Music]
Let's stop. You must feel sorry for the
other person. Be
kind to him. Be
kind to him. There's
no hope.
From now on, he'll be more kind to you.
[Music]
So, today is like this.
That's the end. Well, there were some troubles,
but it
was really good.
[Music]
[Music] It
was also my first time asking the cat about things around the house, so I'd like to hear your thoughts.
I think
this is the
first time for this big collaboration with the seniors at JP, and I was
really nervous, so I didn't really lie, but I
was a bit torn inside, but no, it
was a lot of fun, but I guess that's just how it is
with that ID.  There
was Olly and Chiara Chiara
from En, and they all spoke Japanese well, so I don't think they would ever say that they were better than I
don't even speak Japanese anymore.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Thank you, you know. I didn't end up being a crewmate this time either,
so I
hope you'll call me again and again.
[Music] The
new features are
great too.  It was so fun, so fresh, and so
refreshing.A few months ago, I
think everyone got really hooked on it and played it over and over again, but I also thought they were getting a little tired of it,
but this time I decided to use this feature.  It
was really refreshing, so I
want to do it again, so I
want to do it again. [Music] I want to get really good at it too. I want to do it again.
Aki-chan, that
scene at the beginning where I was so lively, was after I died, and I
talked to Ramy-chan about what color her liver's face was.  Please check it out.
Even though I wasn't able to witness the scene, the incident already
happened in the conference room, so
nexttime I'd
like to be there like that, so I'd
like to do it again.
[Music] [
Music]
Here you go, I
have a good time. It was really fun, and I'm kind of shy about that person, but I feel like I was able to talk properly today. I want to praise myself. Please play again. [Music] I'm sorry, but Captain, I'm in a bit of a hurry.  Can I just
say that? Yes, it was
really fun. Thank you very much. [Music] Bye bye. I'm going to participate in the research. [Music] I'm very happy to have you. It's
okay if someone asks me.
So,
everyone had a lot of fun, so I want to do it again.
Thank you very much.
[Music] We
met up and helped each other out, so now
everyone is
smiling. It's
cute.
Okay, so it was already fun. I want to do it again.
There are a few ways to say things like this, but I
personally really like it when I say "Ora-ora" to my seniors.
[Laughs]
Please let me say "Ora-ora" again.
Thank you very much.  I
met Airi-chan last year,
and we were
able to make a poster together, and we
got a double kill. Thank you. Let's
play together again.
Thank you.
Since I can communicate with Hanesui-chan, I
really want to do a beautiful double kill so that I don't have to hold her back next time,
so let's deepen my understanding.  I'd be
happy if you could call me chan. It's funny. It was really fun.
[Music] I'm going to let
you all know
for a moment, but it's the number one thing you can watch
as much as you like. Even though I can't speak English and I'm a little bad at it,
thank you very much for playing with me.  It
was a lot of fun. Let's meet again.
[Music]
Thank you everyone for coming out tonight.
Bye bye
[Music]