hi
[Music]
I will be speaking for Kiara and Kiara's
behalf kikiriki she says thank you son
she says for showing up all these past
few days
we have a special announcement today
actually oh
we have a Christmas song cover from the
four of us I'm a Kiara Iris and gura
going to release in one hour
[Music]
[Laughter]
so so any thoughts on uh recording this
uh Christmas cover Kiara I'm sure you
recorded it when it was your voice was a
lot better huh
it was fun to sing this song even though
I did never practice it much since I
heard it a million times before it went
smoothly
try to listen to the harmonies too
I think they came out nice
more song cover wolf
yeah I remember hearing like the mix uh
but I only had your voice since you
turned in your lines first and it
sounded really good like I almost want
to hear just the cover of your like just
your version almost uh
maybe one day
thank you um
most song cover will follow soon perhaps
maybe possibly
oh yeah
how did I cut you off okay
did we announce what song it is or
should we just wait until like this
actual thing I'm gonna be able to see it
right
oh oh yeah oh yeah it's snow halation
[Music]
is like a melody in my head it's the
remix version right Kiara
no it's not it's not safe from here
it was fun
sorry
say premiere
oh Premiere yes the premiere will be uh
up in one hour uh about one hour after
this video goes live so look forward to
it it will be on the whole life English
Channel right
yes yes it will be on the whole living
room Channel and Iris and gouda are also
um singing in the song so make sure to
check it out and then uh my thoughts
about recording it I feel the same way
like I've always heard it and I like to
practice that song
um because it's a I don't know it's a
banger it's a banger so I'm glad I'm
happy that I was able to do it with you
and everyone else and yeah I actually
haven't heard the final final version of
it and I haven't seen the video yet so
I'm definitely gonna check out the
premiere too
hmm
thank you for watching guys
bye bye merry Christmas and happy
holidays
[Music]