get it if you ever want to get it um
actually i'm not sure exactly when yeah
actually nice timing huh thank you
yeah you're welcome i had a feeling
what is that oh that's somebody i want
to talk to you guys are you messaging is
there a dm on my bottom is that at the
end
dms show up at the bottom oh yeah so
there's system and party i think it's
nobody's damning you hopefully
uh someone dm'd me
just like just ignore it
oh no
you're so you're still in the party i
think
oh okay i can only open a party chat i
don't know how to get back into it into
the screen that i saw before oh that's
okay i'll just put us into a game
okay
uh oh yeah so this is uh my first uh i'm
allowed really this is my first um
pc fps my first online fps and my first
time doing an fps with the mouse so yeah
it cools down
five pot matches yeah who is your
champion oh god the numbers might be
just wait are these really bad
joining
yeah uh there's bots on the enemy team
so uh if you pick your character that's
the character you get for the whole game
you don't get to choose in between some
games you can do that oh
wow okay oh i see they have some kind of
classes the plus one is probably some
healing yes or so yeah the plus one is
healing so if you want to try healing um
no
i mean whatever you pick whatever looks
interesting to you uh i'll help you
through explaining it
um there's
they're all not looking very cute um
the only one looking cute that's
available is a girl called cassie oh
yeah uh she's um a sniper i think she
has a bow so it'd be pretty interesting
if you want to try
hell yeah i like a bow i like me a bow i
have some experience in my brain's your
channel
maybe i wanted to pick somebody else but
okay this works
on you're you're uh you're a a cute
world of warcraft looking dwarf uh yeah
yeah he's not well he's kind of tall but
why doesn't it why is he saying paladins
above is that because you're an
announcer
oh no i i think i got a really cool
frame i just spent some money and some
school things ah
you look very special there facial
regulators
uh wait can you speak again actually yes
yes
[Music]
i'm getting thrown into the cold water
i'm feeling but what is
okay
eight seconds after using dodge roll
your next weapon shots damage is
increased by thirty percent uh huh
what
okay so
don't don't worry about it for now you
get it just shoot and get a feel for it
uh so yeah you have four different
abilities one of them might be a passive
or so and then you have an ultimate
which charges throughout the game and
your ultimate carries over to the next
round
so you'll see now
you get on a horse and we're gonna ride
to the point and just just try to shoot
the enemy let's try your best they're
they're bots so
uh it's not it's not too scary right now
but on our team they're also bots
because they no no no
on our team they're they're not bots
okay so they're also beginners who still
have to do the bot match yeah
who are oh that's from me okay is is
friendly fire even possible
uh no not in this game no
okay no friendly
[Music]
okay and then i have to stand in the
control point
yeah so you just stand here until that
little timer or the little bar at the
top reaches 100 and then we get the cart
which counts as one point in the game
so once you get four points you win the
whole game uh-huh uh-huh okay uh-huh
uh-huh
uh by the way everybody the game is free
to free to play yeah it's free to
download yeah
you gotta get them
it's kind of hard
[Music]
how many have you got announced uh
amelia watson uh six
i i guess i think they're assists so i
don't think it
counts she's cute
there's like a pink bunny girl actually
that's you that's the character you're
playing is perfect because you have a
bird right above your head
it's like i think it's a phoenix
actually yeah
what yeah
wouldn't that be too perfect
i have some attacks don't i what's
what's a double kill
if you get confused about what your
attacks do you can press k
and uh it brings up
like uh the
descriptions
i'm carrying on it
you are you're uh our kill leader
probably
[Music]
i'm just pressing buttons without really
knowing what they are right now i mean
as long as here you have somebody who
like just shoots stuff and you're just
shooting stuff at the enemy that's
pretty much all you need to do
okay i think your character might have
like movement abilities or things like
that i just i just did a movement oh
nice
is it does it matter where you should oh
um
yeah it does matter so you always want
to aim for the head yeah you'll do more
damage like that
it's okay we got the point
wait what what purchase items no no
right oh so uh it should be on automatic
purchase right now but there is a
mechanic in the game where you can
purchase slope
roll back connector
we're all back in the base oh yeah yeah
so once you capture the payload and push
it all the way to the end on their side
then it starts again because now you
have to capture the point again
and then try to push it
okay
uh disengage blast shot fire and then
find an explosive crossbow to blast away
enemies in an area dealing 450 damage
okay
the famous announcer paladins
that you can only get like one more day
or so so download the game
actually guys this stream was [\h__\h]
yeah i think she used her ultimate
baby and you [\h__\h]
god i gotta cuss like a like a fbs
player yeah yeah
how would you do that
what kind of swearing do they do um help
me out here oh uh
what's the [\h__\h] thing yeah are you
hanging
where is that hacker i'm gonna report
you to the vms or so i don't know
the point and a lot of times if you
can't finish pushing the payload all the
way to the end we have to capture the
point again but we're obviously gonna
get it so it's gonna be game over here
yeah obviously not a match for us
nice apparently the the champion that
you're playing people think is like a
little op or like broken so she's really
good
who's opie
the the champion that you're playing
cassie really really
i don't have much choice so
double kill
i wanna hear that i'm a voice actually
so far i must say
um i'm i i'm what are you doing
oh that's that's uh this big dragon's
ultimate yeah i thought so i must say it
looks pretty good visually i'm liking it
visually this game
yeah yeah it's really nice
it's not bad
it reminds reminds me of a
a pretty uh world of warcraft oh yeah
yeah
[Music]
seven kills is that what you're saying
where do you see your total kills you
press tab
[Music]
we did it was that the first game yes
that was the first game and four more as
a unlocked adorable that's me i'm
adorable
cute so at the top like where it says
everybody if you click on the last icon
at the top you can see the scoreboard
what where where everybody
uh oh did you exit out of the
victory thing where it shows everybody's
poses
no i'm still in there ah so at the top
there's like these little icons that you
can click on
ah
oh
yeah so if you go to the last icon it
shows the scoreboard and you can
see you know how much damage you did or
if you're a healer how much healing you
did
i'm still
looking the weakest
out of all this i need to become
stronger i'ma teach me the fps skills
teach me
uh
okay okay i'll try oh maybe we should go
over this
oh what actually no my damage is higher
than yours what was your class what was
that oh i was playing a tank but i kind
of wasn't actually
okay how do we how do we continue
um
how do we continue oh yes so we'll play
another game but i wanted to talk if you
click on that champions uh tab uh on the
main menu
yeah so here you can look at the
champions and then also like say if
you're playing cassie you can click on
her see she has a bird
she does and she has kind of orange red
hair like me yeah
it's actually like the perfect character
for you um hell yeah so if you
you can see all the abilities on the
left side and if you click on um
uh hold on oh yeah if you see at the top
there's like a little cards thing this
is maybe a little complicated for now
but i'll just explain it briefly so that
you understand because when you do start
the game it asks you like what abilities
and what cards you want to pick
um
so if you click something like create
new loadout and click on an empty slot
there's like different cards that
enhance different abilities
sort of yeah it's just like for the meta
gaming abilities and stuff you don't
have to look into it now but just so you
understand
how it works yeah and so you just put
different points into the cards for the
abilities that you like and then you
like build your own loadout sort of
thing so even though somebody else might
be playing the same champion as you you
might have it built like differently
just built different
oh cool
um
[Music]
cute cute cute cute
can i use that or is that do i need to
unlock it
is that the sign for
needing to unlock it
check you see it right now
look at the skins skins
here skins skins
cassie
oh
cassie why does she change her voice
why is she becoming a different
personality when i give her a different
skin oh yeah sometimes they do that
there's like some robot skins where they
they get they have like robot voices and
stuff well that's cute
that looks like me
timber timber and tinder
what
why is it's the same outfit but it's a
different name and it sounds very
similar what does that mean
oh holy [\h__\h] casey
dragon cross dragon she called the
dragon now
ah
cassie oh my god that's the valley girl
outfit oh my gosh she's sunkissed now
beautiful she got a freaking parrot on
her hand
it's funny how she changes her voice i
like that
oh dark cassie oh
did i say what can i use that one
the coral one
that i'm opening something
i want
i want the
i want the timber i guess
yes
[Music]
she's yelling timber
i need more i don't have enough crystals
i thought i had money that was not the
right money what about this three thirty
thousand i'm close no wait i haven't
okay i can be coral cassie oh
right yeah yeah the other ones are
unblockable in a different way okay
and a coral crossbow let's go
oh that's wasting hold money on it
if it's at least the gold coins you get
those pretty fast uh while playing and
stuff so yeah all right oh i didn't
equip the last one okay
okay i'm ready ami
i'm ready let's go let's kill some
people they're cute there we go
oh two out of five
champion
i shall be the bird lady once again
[Music]
if you could have me be
a
[Music]
narrator which game would it be
which game would it be uh yes why not it
doesn't have to be anything
maybe i don't think they need two whole
live people in this game
[Music]
i don't
know a fortnight they have a they have
announcer packs sort of in like halo and
call of duty
oh by the way uh i mean you are aware of
my
of my deaf loop um
adventure right you know that i was
playing that right which one
def loop
oh yeah yeah um how is it you like it
yeah i saw you freaking out while you
were playing
i liked it a lot it was uh
it was on on the ps5 oh um so it was
with the controller
this is already like a lot easier yeah
play than on the controller on the ps5 i
gotta say
yeah fps games are they're kind of made
to be played with a keyboard and mouse
like to me it just feels so familiar but
yeah you do have to get used to it but
you've been playing minecraft so you're
pretty used to it by now
[Music]
okay
oh
it goes let's kill him let's kill the
bots
yeah i'm already scared of
playing without oh god
playing without the boss and playing
reveal people people don't have mercy on
those sorry it's okay
can you
when you get matched in this game does
it only match you with people who are
like as new as you are
i'm not sure actually maybe chat will
know um yeah i don't know what the
matchmaking
really good people when you're just a
noob
yeah we'll be going against people who
are new to the game too i think
it depends sometimes it looks like a
really high level person partying with
somebody who's new is that their base oh
my god we're camping at their base okay
it's fine they're bad it's not
acceptable
oh god
the [\h__\h] i got too close to that
weird fairy yeah
she does a lot of damage because she has
like these spam projectile things that
explode
oh and they do it it's like a wide area
that they cover
oh
okay i'm coming back wait for me i'm
gonna protect you don't be scared i'm
coming i'm scared
yeah
[Music]
i'm here for you
i
should talk you much harder than this um
be
careful uh um uh
you you little [\h__\h] uh yeah
what am i you can't you suck at this
game you can't shoot you don't know how
to use a
you gun shoot yourself in your leg all
the time every morning
we're doing stealing oh now
um
yeah
and my feelings are hurt
right in his heart
yes oh my god chad i know it's
incredible i'm playing with the
announcement
[Music]
that's our ultimate she does like this
weird bounding thing
oh i thought that was yours the bot is
stuck like in the map
oh [\h__\h] oh
you can kill him kill him
why are you moving so much
it's pretty good not bad
eating carrots over here i'm sorry
oh my god
we got the baby out of it
oh
my game is not moving am i still in the
game
yeah
it happened baby was too
powerful you're about to do it
i'm back really no i guess it's a bot
don't worry you can't connect
oh okay i got kicked out of his destiny
it's out
i'm back in the starting screen
oh you'll be able to rejoin
here
how do i be doing
that please
i don't think i can rejoin i'm not in
the party i think
did you see that that party message
uh
yes i saw it i saw it
honey
i'm in the park we're about to finish
the game um in like the next few minutes
i don't know because if i just leave i
think i might get like a cool down
but does this count as one game probably
not there might i thought you could
reconnect on some games but maybe
because it's a bad game it doesn't let
you
damn it
damn it well that just means more time
with the
paladins
[Laughter]
[Music]
if you want to see like
a healer that you might want to play or
like a tank usually i have somebody in
like every class sort of that i like to
play
what is that what is that one something
new
let me see where chad where is that new
thing
something new
yes yes yes yes
announcer yes chad i know
weapons here ah weapon skin
oh there's a new one
i look at it it's a clip
it's still there i don't know
all right let's see who they are
[Music]
i s i see character nelly hodor where's
squishy
cute she's cute i think
cute cute cute
she's cute she's cute
[Music]
or you can unlock them with the gold i
thought you have to unlock them by
playing the game but i guess
at least then you can
decide who exactly you want cute
30 000 hmm
all right again it's over oh well almost
there
looks like a
night elf
oh
cute
cool
wait which skin stretch you have herald
oh
who is this lady sea queen sati oh the
girl i just looked at
she she has the uh
beautiful beautiful shoulder pads
[Music]
did you know this chat that i was only
looking at girls has absolutely nothing
to do with anything
nice
i i made cassie now
so no one can take her away from me
[Music]
i mean her
melt in my prayer
i got a gift and paladin somebody might
send you a random gift it's just like a
skin or something in the game yeah
what you can just send it to people that
you're not even friends with
yeah i think so what
oh
christmas okay
i will gladly accept all kinds of um
skins
but uh
i'm not i will not be accepting any
friends requests just
okay
i just saw yeah
but with me in it
i was born ready i'm going impulse oh oh
my ball looks nicer now i can't move can
you move
um
oh yeah oh this is weird we're not in
spawn
oh yeah this is
this is a different game mode than the
one
i think you just get kills in this one i
follow you
just get kills is there no no base or so
to like the [\h__\h] thingy
not really it's just um i don't know
where everybody is actually oh [\h__\h] i
think i fell do not follow me did you
follow me
[Music]
oh i see somebody okay
we died together
[Music]
oh my god oh my god i in the tutorial i
learned that i can zoom but maybe it's
um
right click probably usually uh
just right click no no maybe maybe it's
not possible with the bow
oh
yeah it might not be possible with the
bow because i think the bow might only
be hip fire
yeah chad is saying it it's just hip
fire but if you play like a character
that has a sniper there's a few
characters that are snipers uh you can
zoom in
on me
i'm dying so much right now i need to be
more careful
i should have played a healer i forgot
that i put a different game mods in
no problem
do we have any healers at all right now
thank you yeah we do
it's a treat
uh i think
probably cassie is like not so much
close range because if you get close to
that guy his guns are pretty close range
yeah
i felt that
oh
oh the tree
what the [\h__\h] was that tree
that guy's on our team he's a healer
and he is good if you stand near him
you'll get heals
[\h__\h] burrito
not my best game
are these bots no because it looks like
they have real names
yeah exactly no but i think the bots
might
that was close i don't know guys this is
you
is this you guys
i thought that there was five matches
against the box but maybe they changed
it
i'ma protect me be my meat shield okay i
actually have like a legit shield
nice
moving in moving in oh behind us
oh
you get wrecked
now here's the job we just need um like
20 more kills
20 more kills are we winning we're
winning and we're winning i have a
carrot in my mouth
yummy carrots hmm
i like carrots too
i'm gonna kill you gonna kill you gonna
kill you damage dealer oh
[Music]
let me use my old teeth what does it do
um i don't know am i doing something
i think it's like a auto locks onto
people probably oh
oh [\h__\h] no idea what that did what's it
tattoo chat
this verbation fire
[Music]
fire
[Laughter]
oh no it's okay you spawn instantly we
just need uh six more kills to win
six more oh my god yeah i have more
kills going against us
that's so strong
it's my task
i feel wow most of the time i was
shooting air but i tried
i bet you you know you hit some stuff
what's important for fps games is to
make sure your mouse sensitivity isn't
too high or too low
uh-huh okay uh what's also important is
that the healers do their job and adjust
their flow with their healing honestly
it's their fault yeah that's true that's
their fault stupid healers
can't do [\h__\h] oh so if you want to open
any presents that you got if you click
on store
which won't open anything weird and then
if you click on the top icon in the
middle it's a chest and you can there's
a thing that says open gifts
wait uh sorry uh a store
uh
chest
[Music]
opening i got no gifts um
it's okay you'll get them soon
next game let's see let's see next next
game until i can get i'mma we're gonna
we're gonna play this until i get the
i'm a voice pack cool oh before you
check them
somewhere oh yeah there's a check quest
and then page yes uh you click at the
top
there's like a second icon you can see
your progress on the emily watson
announcer oh three out of five noise
we don't even need to do ten apparently
yeah i think they changed it when i
played a few years ago
you used to have to play five games
against bots but i think it counts now
just like any matches that you play
okay i don't even think the last match
we played was against bots i can't tell
cat what do you think about that i don't
think it was bots
but i don't know anything about this
game anyway
uh
but if if it's only two more then i
guess after getting the voice pack we
can play
a few more because i need to listen to
the beautiful voices amelia watson
double i want the double oh experience
okay
i'm gonna be sandwiched in between
amelia watson and amelia watson
is that the tree from
that marvel movie
um no
it's similar you know it's similar his
name starts with the g2 so this is
grover
yeah
oh it's not the same one
i like that dream
match error
what do you mean if someone didn't our
team didn't pick a champion so we we
have to look for another game
it should auto select
yeah but then he's like oh this person's
probably afk so might as well ah how
smart
let me see
i got freckles i like freckles
i mean my character has freckles yeah
yeah they're pretty and when the
freckles would look really uh cute on us
don't you think
freckles yeah
i don't think i've really seen a
vegetable with freckles before there
must be green outfits they have freckles
cute
freckles hella cute hell yeah
hey i'm using the the german announcer
pack yeah i'm learning
you don't need that i can announce for
you
[Music]
guys oh
[Laughter]
are you listening hi rez
record this right now
into the game directly
it doesn't change much to the
to the english words i guess we use it
similar words
um
[Music]
i don't know i don't want to read i'm
just gonna
i'm just gonna go with it oh it looks
icy here
yeah this is
we were here too
this is a king of the hill map so
there's just like a point and you just
have to capture it yeah
i think he would um
are you a vegetable
did you manage to become a potato or
what i've heard you wanted to be a
potato what is what's that about yeah i
became a potato but now i'm sprouting a
little spud
you're a broken now a bland
your skin that needs some skin cream
because you're like oh i'm dry
yeah you look very dry
i'm trying to heal you that guy does a
lot of damage
it did i ran right into the middle
south cap oh i couldn't fly
verb come with me
are there there's other characters that
like you can fly around a sm or you can
jump really high or
holy [\h__\h]
they're in control
they're in control okay we'll get him oh
but you're here with
[Music]
how about not dying
around in front of me how traumatizing
is
oh
[Laughter]
nice uh wooden butt you got there oh man
thank you right this way
okay
there's a guy behind us
oh so this is this is king of the hill
so it's like a control point and so
whoever has control of this area
uh the number goes up what is the matter
with you i just woke up
[Music]
where is the party here is the barney
don't you hurt my baby
oh it's okay you got the kill you got
the kill really i did oh yeah you did
wow there's a lot going on man yeah
sometimes it's kind of scary because
there's so many abilities and characters
that you don't know what they do
yeah yeah yeah yeah what's your favorite
fps game
favorite
uh
maybe cs go i really like csgo
[Music]
but uh it's it's kind of
it's a little punishing like when you
first play it but it's like a good bare
bones fps because there's no abilities
and things like that you just have a gun
and you're just a regular person
i i have heard a lot about that game and
it has been around for like a long time
right yeah it's like the game well
counter-strike in general has been
around for a long time but yeah cs go to
has also been around for quite a while
wow
[Music]
do you see their their blue guy that he
puts totems down on the ground and
that's their healer so that's what that
was yeah can we kill the totem too yeah
you can shoot the totem and you can also
uh it's good it's always good in these
types of games to target the healer
and uh do
damage and kill them and distract them
because then they can't heal they have
no idea that they're dealing with two
gamer girls right now
yeah i don't know if the thoughts are
cuties
if they knew
uh so this guy's ability he has like a
[\h__\h] kid an airstrike
oh
that's why i went like
[Music]
yeah yeah
oh man
i don't know
i think we are playing against pause
i can't tell
no no
i think every time you play like another
game they increase the difficulty
[Music]
be using like uh
what do you call the thing that you're
used to look at people fall away
oh a scope
oh yeah 30 60 no scope or a 360 no scope
what's that what's that mean on there
what does that mean
that means you make a complete circle
with your mouse and then
shoot without scoping in
what is what does scoping mean
keep opening this egg
uh scoping it means like when you zoom
in you know how like
you can zoom in with a gun ah
bam cool i wanna do that that's my goal
your goal is to get a 360 no scope
no it's a freddy 60 no scope oh okay
i can't tell them this guy's on me the
electric guy
he's the healer
nice
okay apparently these are real people i
didn't know
i'll bring it for real
we're playing against real people
damn it's no mercy on noobs like me huh
yeah well they you know they don't know
they're just playing
i hate you so much
[\h__\h] boomer you're going on my block
list after this
it's okay okay now i'll play i'll play
for real for real i was just playing
like i know i'm gonna play i hope
i need my pro gamer girl amelia watson
what did i i called you for this collab
because i thought you know
fps gabe's who could teach me that is
not a question it's only one person that
i can ask to teach me an sps game when
it is amelia watson the announcer of
paladins it can only be you
true yeah yeah you made it you you made
a good choice just
you know i'm warming up i'm warming up
well then i wanna i wanna buy a champion
really quick hold on
hey you got an eight kill streak oh man
maybe
wow well then i'm getting more crystals
wow
where are the presents
where are the presents where are the
presents friends request where the
prisons men what what
where the prison's lame
is that presents
no that's what i bought
i'm too low level for president your
level is too low they were trying to
give me presents but i'm too low level
oh
oh you're too low level what i didn't
know that was the thing
what is my level four oh okay i need to
be level ten apparently
oh
that's okay they'll all come in when you
get to level ten
yay
[Music]
i'm waiting for it
okay ready something right now oh yeah
ready i'm done
i'll just uh
the event pass gives us an uh unbeatable
plus zero percent esp
why
that lady
i'm gonna try to get some
more headshots this time
seems like some people can survive a
headshot though not very realistic gotta
say
yeah i think most people can survive
um because your health is pretty high
we don't have a healer but a new trick
for this is for paladins if you walk
away there's like this little cool down
bar underneath your health
and if you're out of a fight you're not
taking hits you'll automatically
regenerate all your health back
okay
okay kill your enemies hold the
objective to gain points first team two
ah so another 400 points okay
yeah i'll put on
the next game instead
is this the last game for you for like
uh to get the announcer back
probably
opponent yeah a mouse too fast killing
me oh my god
oh my god there's a lot of money here
i'm gonna take some of that home all
that gold oh i was so shiny shiny
oh yeah which one is um that's you oh
hello oh you're also healing as well or
what is that um character is that now
this is a it's called the flank
character so i just i just do have like
machine guns and
this is that applause so that you can
pounce with and then oh you want to
scratch my back with that
i'm feeling safety
oh
that's a cool map
i don't think i've ever been on this map
before it's like haunted or something
it's oh it's like a kazula map
oh
honestly everything looks like world of
warcraft to me
i see you
oh
take cover
i'm scared i don't wanna die
shouldn't press f uh f is really just f
what is your f there's a movement
ability uh it makes me shoot like
forward dash forward while attacking i
suppose oh
yeah if you go closer they kind of
the smartest thing to do when i'm trying
to stay away from them
they do be dead though oh nice we did
that was a nice combo you finished him
off i was doing damage on him
where are they
are you fine you need some some help oh
shoot
is she behind the wall sometimes i'm not
quite sure where they're ah
so they are here
i feel like someone in kfb has that name
oh
somebody's about to get fired
yeah
is it easy to like snap someone in this
game or is oh this is pretty tough i i
feel like it's pretty tough because
there's just so much going on but uh for
like if you're sniping against bigger
characters it's easy because there's
some pretty big characters
oh [\h__\h]
she built the world
oh i can shoot the wall you can break
the walls
uh i don't think you can right well it's
a
it depends i don't think there's
anything like that
oh no we're waiting at the moment though
nice oh beautiful [\h__\h] i fell off the
mountain
i didn't know there was a hole right
there
[Music]
i think i revealed people to the rest of
that's so useless
oh [\h__\h] at the moment
don't die
it's okay i have expert movement
abilities oh they have more kills than
we do now oh no we're falling behind
i killed ghost
[\h__\h] i killed a ghost
nice they were already dead but i killed
them again because you're now a double
ghost
what is that
magician looking lady
oh
um
magician looking lady this the one with
stones or the one
the one with the dress oh yeah i think
she's a tank so she has like a wall and
she's pretty tanky
uh she shouldn't do too much damage i
think
a tank oh that's what she yeah she has a
wall
well
204 oh we're winning this is a nice
match i feel like we're we're more equal
than before in the previous one yeah
yeah especially because like this type
of game mode a lot of the times people
don't pick like a real composition for
the team and usually a real composition
for a team includes like having a tank
for defense you know
and then having support healer
yeah
uh we don't have that here
it's a different game mode you killed
the one who killed me thank you thank
you again revenge
rocket
that was german
oh did you watch the did you watch the
whole talk with juggle yeah i watched a
little bit of it
he was praising you amen without me even
like really
yeah that's crazy
[Music]
talking about vr chat and embarrassing
how he studies it and then i'm like yeah
it's all possible because of her and he
said yo ami she's so impressive
wow wow
yeah
he got his eyes on you
it's sweet i don't know it's kind of
embarrassing but
no
not embarrassing i i feel like very
proud to have you
oh
me too i mean yeah the what the way that
you do holo talk like translating
everything and stuff
is so good
[Music]
[Laughter]
as long as he dies
sooner or later
i'm happy you should try um like another
character because sometimes there's
characters that like they have area
effects which can be especially like for
somebody's new fps can be a little bit
easier
because you're kind of like hip-firing
you're like a hip-firing sniper
hip-firing
yeah i know it sounds weird
well yeah my hips are on fire can't help
it i mean i can't stop that
we're all dead
uh and there's fun
oh god i got stuck on the wall
[Applause]
how do you undo that
are you dead yeah
oh man
i guess i could uh
try out more
characters when i have like a bit more
choices and like time to look at every
character yeah
yeah some of the characters they like
rotate them out for
like who you can play and stuff during
different weeks and things like that
where'd she go
yeah no
it's okay i've been adventure oh thank
you
thank you thank you very much
i have cute and right yeah i've been
using human already looks good just just
uh
maybe not that often oh that's right i
just saw somebody jump off the map
what you jumped off the map no not me oh
damn there was a lot of damage oh you
saw someone yeah
oh thank you
my hero
amelia wants him no i was dead
you could probably pull this
like that i wanna i wanna do that too
yeah that'd be awesome like any any kind
of game
yeah
isn't it that one rhythm game
ribbon game ah yeah i guess
my my song is in the ribbon game yeah i
think there's like a little ciara pixel
like uh
yeah
um
no voice though oh no
has a
like a narrator voice oh
shouldn't have been so close to all of
them we're waiting let's go come on nine
more nine more go go
what
[Music]
that's a pretty challenging game
kiana you're a sniper what do you mean
oh yeah you mean because that was too
close yeah
i got that i unlocked amelia once in
here
you're legendary emma you're legendary
quickly
uh copyright 2016 cover corp they had to
write that on there didn't they yeah
yeah a tiny picture
i got it i want to listen to it
yeah can you play game call okay
[Music]
what does objective time mean
uh objective time it's like uh how much
time you spend on the point so the point
is the objective during the game
i heard you talk louder can i turn you
louder uh
i don't know
maybe
might be in the volume settings yeah
character music
voice voice volumes
notification
and turn them a bit higher maybe that
helps
[Music]
oh yeah this one's pretty good
i mean not you oh
fast
i want i want the the fake no the
legendary i'm in
the
diamond that i have here in on my screen
in obs she's a she's a shiny
oh yeah
rare element and the one in the game is
a legendary almond can i need to be
discovered once became
oh no i want to change it did i already
select it huh
oh
[Music]
do you have your own voice back on too
no i i switched it from the terminal
i want you to know that
listen to yourself i can't
but uh i hope you enjoy it if you get
three kills
[Music]
i'm gonna like really rock this i feel
so strong now
and i immediately died
maybe i was flustered by the
overwhelming amount of ammo
uh yeah
i'm gonna snap
i'm gonna act like a santa oh who's
shooting me
it was the other sniper i don't know
where she was
i'm supposed to be the only one here
it's faker
he's a different character boring
oh my god oh
uh yeah so there's a point over there
that we're supposed to it's like the
other one of the other games we played
where we get the payload and get to push
it
do i have to shoot the payload uh no
just uh try to kill
uh and stay alive
okay
it's again the cassie that killed me oh
what did this guy just do
he fell off the cliff
not the smartest boy
oh i eliminate it thank god oh oh what
the [\h__\h] they're coming
all right we're defending we got a good
choke point here
[Music]
do i have to stay close to it or no you
don't you don't have money to have that
yeah you're probably better off going
somewhere else yeah that spot back here
is pretty good
that's that guy's ultimate it's an
instant kill if he hits you with it
damn
and uh there's like some abilities you
can get to help kind of kill the other
team like there's one of the items that
you can buy
that uh reduces the amount of healing
that they get from their healers so
right now they have two healers so
that's like
you know you ah
oh no
yeah she's
that lady that killed you is actually a
healer too
unbelievable
what is um
i got it i got i just died but i got two
kills with my ultimate
oh
good job
where are they
are we are we winning we're losing right
now um
either
i guess kind of we're losing a little
bit
30 seconds remaining says amelia wants
it
30 seconds remaining
oh
oh no
okay they're in overtime right now but
they're yeah they're dead got it
okay oh actually that was us together
[Music]
this is
pretty fun i could do this more often
you might find this more often with you
yeah
i think you you'll probably like if you
try some of the other champions and
stuff you might find somebody who's like
a bit easier or so for you to play but
yeah
you know it's good practice for you too
especially for aiming and things like
that
true yeah
i i like a quick
[Music]
one where i have to go slower i can take
some time to aim
properly
yeah
it's it's better in the long run because
then when you do switch to like
you have a good aim for it
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
go ahead go i'm in on the horses go go
go
i'm
a bit confused i thought snipers were
the ones who can zoom in and i'm
snatching well there's like a few
different types of snipers in this game
because she is a sniper but
yeah she has like a crossbow so
uh yeah it's just difficult
[Music]
oh we gotta get on the point it's at
seventy percent
ah
oh sheesh
oh damn
bird lady i see you there i see you he
does a lot of damage guys he does a lot
of damage
we're on camera they're about to be
right around the corner
[Music]
yeah they dried out yeah
how long were they alive
uh for like a solid 10 to 12 days i
think
damn that's that's pretty good that's
decent
yeah i think it's pretty good yeah
nice
oh thank you again
do you have a favorite flower
yeah i like i like um sunflowers are
pretty
true
i don't really know too much about like
flowers pianist
but
we need there
the
flowers they came with like a little
tiny bug and i trapped him i captured
him
and
um
chilling there
uh well it was just chilling but i put
it in a terrarium
because i have a few and then i gave him
some seeds and he's he's chilling
damn i messed that up
it's nice that they sent an extra pet
yeah
nice of them
as if they knew that uh
as if they knew that you like
these kinds of
insects
yeah
you should get a frog on it i've been
thinking about it
i've had a frog before it was a fully
aquatic frog yeah it's called a african
dwarf frog and they uh they're really
cute you can keep them in like a five
gallon tank
is it as as toxic as uh you are almond
i don't i don't know if it's toxic it
might be
i wouldn't be surprised
hey can you get
toxic frogs that easily
uh actually probably not i think the
only
i think there's like poison dart frogs
you might be able to keep as a pet
but it might depend on where you live
because sometimes not allowed
one
beautiful announcing i'm a good job
wonderful oh so if they capture the
point of this game then it's game over
yeah we're losing a lot
they don't know who they're dealing with
oh why did i jump in here
um
they just have so much or they don't
really have too much damage just they
have a lot of heels because they have
two healers it's the hooded lady and the
little fox looking guy
they both do heal so it's kind of hard
to do damage against them sometimes
would you say this game is paid to win
or not really no no not not at all i
don't think well i mean you don't have
to unlock champions and things like that
but it's oh wait we have the point
but it's not like a pay-to-win thing
because it's not like you can only
unlock abilities with
oh
nice
good to know yeah
and you can uh if there's like a
champion you want you don't have to use
real money to get it you can
um
my team is bringing it
who's this guy i'm scared
i'm scared mommy
what a kill what a kill as if i got a
hawks eye man
nice job
actually uh before the stream
i took a little nap because that was
getting cozy with my kitty cat yeah
and i had a
a weird dream
oh
what about what
was i in it
i had a weird dream that i
um was lurking
i was lurking in uh
in
the discord where i shouldn't
be and they were talking about me and i
i uh i didn't realize i was using my
real account oh
and i i i answered something oh and then
it was so [\h__\h] embarrassing it was
like holy [\h__\h] they hundred percent
sauna
how can i
get out of this mess it's like it's like
when you have a nightmare like people
that go to work and stuff they're like
oh i had a nightmare i went to my office
naked it's like that sort of thing it's
like a work-related
weird dream i woke up and i was so happy
that it was not real it was not real
do you remember your dreams a lot yeah i
do i usually do but uh i don't i don't
know if i dreamed last night
that turned into a chicken
what that's possible yeah it's the the
fox guy on the other team um his his
ultimate ability turns
people into chickens in like a certain
area
yeah
maybe i should practice that
okay right there yeah he's pretty good
he has like a
he throws like potions on the ground
sort of and they heal or do damage
what's his name you know the name hip
hip okay i'll try to remember do we
still have the nothing objective yeah
we're still pushing it but the person
who's on the point right now is pretty
low on the house push push push
okay over time we're in overtime
uh oh it doesn't look good
[Music]
[\h__\h]
oh damn that's a lot of damage
all right we gotta we can capture the
point we can try again if we get the
point we can still win what what
happened did i just
i did it did oh no oh we got okay we
restarted okay
capture the objective
objective
oh
apparently paladins is in the chat
and they said
they said that you shouldn't be able to
play any champion maybe i don't know if
that's for me or for you not sure
you mean they just unlocked me some
champions
maybe
no way
it might have been for me but i don't
know let me check is that paladins from
the game palaces where emilia watson is
the announcer of pelicans which is only
available for like one more day so get
the game now free of free of charge is
that that
they're a person i thought it was a game
how is that possible thank you paladins
thank you paladins this stream is not
sponsored no it's not a trump
learn an fps game yeah
and if you're really shitty at it
[Music]
if you give um
some characters that i wouldn't mind
getting one or two beauties as well and
just kidding
she's kidding she's kidding this sounds
like um
[Laughter]
[Music]
[\h__\h] sake
it's the ping it's the [\h__\h] thing it
was
oh i got an epic skin
you got an epic skin what did i get an
epic weapon
got another epic skin
oh a champion pack
garlic
looking pretty empty here
yeah yeah i think it's because you have
to be level 10 to get the gifts
maybe they just don't know your account
name that's it i'm just joking i'm gonna
do this on my own i'm i'm an independent
businesswoman okay i'm the owner of the
worldwide's biggest fast food franchise
kfp okay
yeah
nothing
you get them i believe
i want to play another game
okay all right
this is fun
yeah it is it gets pretty addictive
especially when you start getting like
kills i love the sound it's like boom
boom when you get a kill like a really
satisfying sound i like the the red
color in the text when it says i killed
the enemy i like that it's beautiful
yeah yeah it's a little like symbol
that's that appears when you get a kill
oh oh someone in the chat asks how much
does the ammo voice cost it's free of
charge
five games and the game is free of
charge too it's like this is a second
sponsored stream
never done a sponsored palette in
streams
oh oh yeah i guess that was just uh yeah
well yeah normal stream but yeah i guess
kind of on your own i just like paladins
you know it's fun
i've been enjoying it too actually we
chose this game because i'm uh i asked
amma for a collab like what one day ago
two days ago one yeah yeah yeah and she
was doing a members stream and then i
was like oh man which which fbs game
could we play together for a beginner
and then she asked her members so her
members decided that we play this
yeah
and it was it was it was it was fate it
was destiny
that will play in this
yeah because i asked like which out of
three games would be best for somebody
who's new to fps to play and paladins is
pretty easy to pick up because there's
just so many like abilities and
champions like one that'll probably
click with you
oh yeah yeah [\h__\h] your abs
what uh yeah it might have been uh the
official paladins
amelia
oh
wouldn't mind getting covered on to buy
a bubson again
holy [\h__\h]
oh yeah this is a nice life guys
i'm not surprised yeah this is a
rainstead adventure
you're putting so much work in these
days it's showing
thank you yeah i've been trying i've
been working hard
um chad what do you think is the best
one does anyone know
what's good here i don't know which one
i don't want i don't have time to read
who has time to read nowadays huh this
looks cute because there's a big big
boob
it's a big burp one oh it is like a if
you ever like want to or take time yeah
you can if you know your abilities you
just read them and you're like oh this
does that and blah blah blah uh yeah
it's kind of like a meta gaming sort of
thing where you just boost the abilities
that you like to use like say if there's
like a movement ability there's probably
a card that boosts that movement
in some way
everything you said 100
entered my brain while i was looking at
your both arms and abs um
well i'm glad you're enjoying the view
it doesn't feel to have so many muscles
i don't know how it feels left noodle
arms
uh i feel very buff not gonna lie
absolutely first blood i
panic
you panic don't panic it's so good so
good gonna be okay we're gonna win this
i believe yeah
i have yet to hit someone i think
that's okay
okay this is not a good not a good arena
for me
are we are we uh we're winning we're
winning are we pushing something uh
we're capturing the objectives so it's
just like the last game we played where
there's a point in the middle and then
uh yeah you capture the payload and then
push it
okay
paladin's unlocked everything for you
just now are you sure where do you see
that
why would they do that that's so nice of
them i might have uh typed it in the
chat maybe i wasn't looking at the chat
it hasn't hooked me up yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
where did she go
[Music]
oh
our healer is pretty good that she's
good at keeping you guys up
oh yeah thank you
wow nice shot
[Music]
we're winning
yeah we got it
yeah
well i kind of feel bad for the other
team they're getting rolled a little bit
i mean
we got paladins on our side yeah
china's too strong right now
what's successful
what should we call it amen oh
oh yeah push successful um maybe like a
mix of our names yeah because we both
you know helped and
you know did it
like um
[Music]
i thought i see it oh that's cute
congratulations you're gonna grow up
into a strong strong child
yeah
beautiful
baby seconds
uh-huh
your voice could be a bit louder
honestly i would like to hear it louder
maybe there might be a setting to turn
it up maybe
this is like you you gotta imagine these
people are gonna download the game just
for your voice just like me
so we're like
we're we're a whole live
uh uh fans looking for a ushi that's all
we want man
yeah i wanna hear her loud and clear
end it up
okay that was that was uh
i knew that was gonna happen
fantasy style fps game yeah yeah it's
like a you know you have magic abilities
and things that can't really be
explained
yeah
because other other fps games they they
look more i don't know stale
they look more
gray and and sad
okay not all of them but with some of
them that i've seen so i like i like the
look of this one yeah
got her butt
nice yeah it gets addictive when you get
the
kills yes
i'm using the german announcer pack
because uh i thought it'd be good to
learn german you know
oh really i want to learn january
deutsche
your name pronounced in german is amelia
by the way
amelia
oh i picked the wrong ability that's
okay
[Music]
no wait that was you killing someone
yeah yeah but uh if you get an assist
that still announces it for you because
you technically did damage you were
doing damage and you helped
even though you didn't get the finishing
blow it still
counts i think
oh baby
oh
i got the assist ah
um
so while you're watching how about
putting emilia and kiara's skins into
this oh [\h__\h] that'd be crazy
i can totally see like a kiara skin for
cassie because she has a bird
i'm a phoenix battle with paladins if
you didn't know i'm a fan
of phoenix just saying
just kidding just kidding no pressure
man i'm just joking okay come here come
here
okay
we're punching we're pushing oh nice you
finish them nice
that must have hurt
i'm sorry
killing spray she says
oh
what am i getting these kills who am i
what what's happening it must be the
paladin's buff
oh my
god i got look maybe uh yeah 50 damage
buff
[Laughter]
nice the true power that was not true
guys
cara's just getting used to the game i
think
you're used to it
good good yeah get on my level amen
[Music]
oh i didn't know you could climb walls
with the person i was playing useful i
was beautiful
wait oh let me look
maybe i need to restart the game or
something
oh you shouldn't have to if you got it
um
and you should receive it like uh
i don't know maybe because you're not
level 10. you're gonna get something
right
i i don't know if i got it from the from
playing the game or from uh
uh from them but i got a sexy new outfit
oh
you should have all the champions
unlocked maybe
how do i do it just click clear all but
then
and when do you
ah thank you paladins thank you thank
you
that's so sweet it's a collar ninja
son when are these things go do i have
to click
oh my god belly girl cassie i got her
[Music]
the way she says cafe like as if she has
gum in her mouth
[Laughter]
hmm yeah maybe she's chewing bubblegum
but bear wick
barry world champion yeah he's really
fun he uh you can build turrets so you
can put down like two little turrets and
they shoot people within a range and
then you also get like a shield that you
can open up and uh you have a shotgun
and you have like this really fun
movement ability with it
okay
thank you paladins
i need to get used to like the whole
interface i don't know how to do things
at all yeah kiara's cara is new to uh
fps games and things like that
very new this is literally my first
online fps game yeah
literally the first what level are you
right now
uh six
six okay
no no i will i will use this beautiful
one
okay
[Music]
i don't know if you have time but we
could play until i don't know how long
it would take to get to level 10
but uh then you could get presents and
things looking pretty slow yeah maybe
i think there's uh some quests but oh
it's too late
i don't know what the there's sometimes
daily quests that you can do to get more
xp and things
if i write in the lobby chat uh
only our team can read it right yeah i
think so yeah
[Music]
somebody stole cassie from you
did i not walk in i don't want to be
no okay the other cute girl but she's a
hero i don't know no
i'll be dora
amen
[Music]
okay i'm a cute dragon now yeah yeah
um
how do i use the dragon uh i think the
dragon has like projectile missiles so
you shoot from
from pretty far
okay
and then uh you can also fly around yeah
like a phoenix so you can fly
yeah
and your ultimate ability is like as
soon as you hit somebody with it it's
like an instant kill so if there's
anybody you really dislike you can
target them
oh
you're you're
grovikad looks really cute cool
thank you very fancy okay what is this
fusilli mamma mia damaged out when
hitting an enemy directly with robot
laundry is always increased by 25
movement speed
fire spit applies
knocked by these additional 300 damage i
don't know i'll use this oh i can't okay
um
okay whatever
you look cute it's very blossom tree now
i think sort of yeah i think it look
like a christmas theme you're so cute
look at the peace tree you are look at
this i'm spiderman
uh yeah so i think uh because it's a
projectile it might do damage in like a
small area it's not like a sniper where
if you shoot a specific ah okay so i
don't have to be so exact yeah you
should try to be but i think there's
some
it's already showing
we're in
wayne
well that cassie just died in front of
me so i think she needs to give me the
character bag
yeah i think it's that it's a little
difficult because we don't have a tank
oh no
that's all right
[Music]
all ready
oh
okay
yeah yeah just trying to do my part here
oh we have somebody that disconnected on
our team
[Music]
come back to us
because rejoining is not really an
option
i think
we should be able to um
we'll see
it's okay a lot of times when you have a
game that
you're getting rolled in the game goes
pretty fast
like uh if you look at the top it's two
out of four so it's just one more round
of them winning like that and then the
game's over oh man
super short game
yeah
oh [\h__\h] what windows update can you read
the room the air in the room windows
please i'm streaming and playing a game
windows what the hell
playing paladins
i'm not gonna update my windows now do i
look like i got time this is beautiful
yeah it's pretty
like a nice garden
you like oh you can go over here
oh oh swim
oh [\h__\h] go
no time oh okay no time for taking a
bath okay
oh i need one
you're stinky
yeah playing fps games makes me a little
sweaty
oh
i'm not sweating at all maybe uh you
need to try a little bit less hard
no
apparently there's like this thing you
can take it's like some
deodorant pill
yeah if you take it it like makes your
sweat smell nice
what yeah
that sounds
really
weird
is that even healthy i don't know
i i heard about it and i i don't know
too much about it but i think it's real
it must be real because i know somebody
who takes it
now i know what now i know what to
send you as a birthday present next year
yeah deodorant pills
my aim is so bad right now it all
happened
[Music]
i also noticed a strong difference in
the way my projectile
acts
yeah compared to my arrows like my
everyone's like super fast but my
shooting shoot now it's like it arrives
way later yeah yeah yeah
a lot of the times like uh when you're
playing fps games people talk about the
difference between a hit scan uh weapon
and a projectile weapon so projectile
usually has a travel time and hit scan
is usually
you know almost as soon as you click
yes to my understanding
professional
talk amelia watson
i just uh shoot shoots
and out ouch
i keep thinking i keep seeing our cassie
on our team and i keep thinking asu oh
[Music]
okay she's almost dead
okay
i mean you need to send me like a fps
dictionary
i wonder like as a joke item an fps
dictionary uh i think it might be well
yeah there might i could totally see
that being like a joke item
joke
uh
yeah you learn it as you play
nice
like something that some people will say
like when they're communicating in fps
games is like oh that enemy is lit like
the
the uh
you know what what are the name what's
the name of this guy
we're on day
i can't remember the name
oh look i'm lit i'm lit
that means you have a little house
don't die don't die
oh i i just healed you too scared to be
here alone
super little
like a lot of times if you just died to
somebody but you did damage them you can
say like uh they're lit they're lit
they're
live i just opened to try to heal you
i would like to write a formal complaint
i'm gonna pull uh an amelia watson at
the end i'm gonna say the game
disconnected
close the game
i ate that's what amelia was the game
just crashes you know it just crashes on
its own it just happens i know i know
i'm in
[Music]
we tried our best it's just it's it's
kind of difficult when they have
somebody who's really tanky and we don't
um because it just means they have
somebody to absorb all the damage
like a sponge like a spongebob yeah
i could have played tank but when you
have to pick between playing a support
character to heal your team and like
tank you're probably better off
picking a support oh
ah i unlocked a champion pack
sorry i mean that one isn't a sniper why
don't sorry to me hey
hmm
[Music]
[Laughter]
there uh are they apologizing because we
lost probably yeah they tried their best
they tried their best
oh the normies must be thinking like
what are those idiots talking about
lamb baby okay let's see let's look at
this whoa
the paladin's with the heart in chat
thanks powder damage
thank you paladin
oh that pack gave me all the people
yeah so you can uh go through
[Music]
she looks like natalie dorma what the
[\h__\h]
looks like nathan and dormer in um
when she had um
what what what am i thinking somebody
else i'm sorry
in in the in the in the movie uh um
she played in that movie where she had
her hair blonde and and shaved on one
side not in vikings but she does also
look like that vikings
yeah natalie dormer in the hungarian
[Music]
the
lady called tyra
oh
tyra the untamed yeah she's she's pretty
good too
she has a it's not a sniper rifle it's
an assault rifle so i guess it's kind of
like a maybe an ak or so
and uh she has a fire grenade
is that pew
[Music]
and she has a fire grenade i'm sure
you've seen it in um one of the games we
played but it does like a fire spot on
the ground and it does quite a bit of
damage
and then uh her ultimate has like super
rapid fire where i think you have
you don't have to reload so you just go
bop
i was a favorite uh for the paladins
community manager yeah she's really fun
to play i like her voice lines a lot too
she's like don't run and that sort of
thing
who's who who all right tyra the one
here let's start talking about tyra yeah
yeah
well that one looks nice
not
bad tyra
ah
oh cute russian tyra
is that russian tyra i think she has a
russian accent i don't remember
oh
that kind of sounds like it yeah
good
obsidian
whoa oh cool obsidian is cool tyra
cosmic time
[Music]
shows has some good
good looking outfits there hmm
tyra yeah she does
i like the the fish one
i saw the fish one like on the screen
and i thought oh is that a new champion
but it's a tyra it's tyra
oh yeah oh she's cute what the [\h__\h]
what's her name io
the shattered goddess oh she should
debut as a v
oh yeah she's a she's a does support
yeah she is cute i could totally see
this like a being a v tuber
so she also has i guess it's a bow or is
that no yeah it's not a it kind of looks
like a bow
i can't tell
you
have you played here before it is a boat
no i haven't played her um yeah she does
a lot of the supports actually can do
quite a bit of damage like um
she probably does quite a bit and then
yeah
uh ying yeah she does a ton of damage
too
it's also pretty
oh
man i don't know who to go with i want
to play well one more one more man yeah
yeah yeah yeah
try somebody new if you oh my god
um
chad who should i who should i go if it
must be a girl i recommend tyra because
um she's like good for especially for
practicing shooting and things like that
oh okay
okay let's go with tyra okay let's play
thank you thank you
[Laughter]
speed running the game right now
it's pretty funny yeah there's like a
you know you can play with five people
in a party so it can be pretty fun
yay
i feel like i have unlimited
possibilities right now
power
oh yeah
the voicemail again
huh what what did you say
who's your favorite i mean
rover
oh okay oh wait where'd she here there
she is okay tyra
customize your champion
uh
uh i think like oh can't wait 45 i'll
have
not enough money right now that's okay
we're looking at default tyra
grover's my favorite
and now sakiana would be cute
imagine
[Music]
i'm trying a cute
looking forward to
how you're gonna play her
yeah never played her before
so i'm red gaming that's uh that's so
damn right is all these fandom right oh
yeah the
enemy team
has at least one sniper there
i mean you know what to do
yeah i know mob mob the zombraid
enemy team has a mccoy
the smallest being he's a turtle
mercy kill nate launcher has three
charges but reduce the damage of h2650
okay
you can only do this one anyway okay
wondering his
blessing auto rifle fast firing
automatic rifle that is inspired
by a grenade that explodes on impact
okay okay the only 700 fire bomb heroin
incendiary device leaving a pull of fire
on him
mark your prey to gain vision fifty
percent increased weapon damage against
him um enhance it
wait a minute
what
uh she already uh
in game and started counting
oh oh oh okay this is where it is okay
oh did i just did they place that
is that a wall yo that's cool
do i do like uh uh
uh uh continuously push the left mouse
button or do you usually
so usually like with the when you play
with guns like that that continuously
shoot you can hold it and pull down
because a lot of time there's recoil so
you want to pull down to account for
that recoil
um i don't know for tyra you can use
first so that's a good one so just like
click and hold for maybe like a few
seconds now a few seconds okay
a short amount of
thank time for auto reload thank you
game death luke did not have that
no really no that looks pretty difficult
man
especially with the controller yeah i
think if it's your first time playing
it's probably pretty difficult um get
used to like some mechanics if you don't
know
become fried chicken by my hands yes yes
or turtle yeah oh shoot that's nice
snake
oh she's doing the naruto run
pink hair chick what's doing
yeah she does a she does the naruto one
i knew exactly what you were talking
about when you said that yes
[Music]
yeah they killed like three of us i
think
unbelievable
i'm really sure what my fox does i think
it makes it so i can do more damage i
don't
know your fox yeah i have a little fox
pet that i spawn on the side oh i think
it oh
okay it's like emanating heels okay
oh
cute
[Music]
yeah it's like a spirit box
it looks a little bit confused like why
am i here what am i doing here we have
like the ultimate base set up actually
because we have this uh engineer on the
site with his turrets
they got no chance against us
keep it sad yeah
i think the tank is scared of us you
should push
oh my ultimate dust let's see
oh
i tapped out of the game what the [\h__\h] i
killed him
who
the tank i think out he got mad at those
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
i want to hear more of that i want to
hear toxic i mean i really like toxic
amen
but balance has been so nice i don't
want to give them the wrong information
saying pickle pickle pickle while she
was running there
oh
did you kill two people yes
[Music]
double kill
oh
okay
yeah oh [\h__\h] he died i'm sorry
i was healing
i'll forgive you this time only if you
give me back a kill
all right
we'll make a trade
why am i here why am i here
i think they i think the tide might be
turning
what's
[Music]
tide like the tightest turning is in uh
you know the tables are being turned i
think they're no no no no no they're on
the point
no no nothing's turning
everything is stable
okay
i'm sorry
get out of here
i just i can't stop shooting
i just like hold it
[Music]
spray and pray that's another
uh slang tournaments used in fps games
i think you spray and pray a lot
probably
okay i got you wait uh okay
you might have feel oh i see okay right
click oh okay
okay i know how to heal now
some red bunny losing on purpose just to
make us happy oh
damn
[Music]
wow unstoppable oh
nice that's a fast game
gt
enemy team
no not really gt but
no it wasn't
[Music]
get the care package sweet care package
i wanna wear the
the russian skin yeah i got a new skin i
wanna try it too
do you know any russian of me uh
we do be looking ah there they are
sorry
i've been focusing on the game i have
barely seen them
now i see you oh i learned how to say
happy birthday in russian it's like las
vegas
ah i forgot i i know i know babushka
oh
no it's okay it'll kill us again
he looks cute oh
i got a really cute skin too
i like it
i'll be a huckleberry
why is there a
who is that cat that's me is that yours
yes you have a pink cat
oh cute oh my god
it's not the same character as before
but with again yeah it's a different
skin
i like it
what did you see before i'm your
huckleberry
and she she said that i just quoted her
she said something like you need some
candles i have a huckleberry ah that was
like a band-aid skin
oh okay that's your american accent this
world's wrong
it's her american accent no more
american
oh that's here
uh
okay hunter hunting party
has been unlocked
you're so cute
it's not not okay to be so cute you look
like a magical girl
that pose is very elegant too
oh yeah i do i do feel like i look like
a magical girl apparently uh uh
she's a cat oh
[Music]
oh it's this map it's the oh it's
what this episode you should lock on
oh
this is the cat oh the cat's name is
miami oh
it's not a box it's a cat i made it my
my personal space i don't think that's
okay
she's speaking in the russian accent
where is the other team
oh
that's cool
i like the movement ability on this
on this chica
[Music]
okay i see it i like transfer my heels
over what what the hell
what
i just
found
uh
i found a gap in the matrix
oh did you fall through the ground
yeah yeah there's a there's a
there's a little area here where you can
fall off
i did not see that coming yeah it's kind
of hard to see because it's like a
little foggy but
once it once you know it's there you
know you learned your lesson
or did i
oh yeah
i wonder if i can click on people
through the wall
no okay
i think the other team is stuck over
there
[Laughter]
they're scared of our cute outfits we're
too cute yeah i think that might be
that's really close it's definitely a
buff
wow
oh they're behind oh i think
i thought it was a friendly but she shot
me oh
oh
what's going on everybody i hear people
dying everywhere
if they fell into the hole
on
[Music]
they're on the point they're like behind
us hello they found the alternate path
smart
smart very smart
but i keep pressing the remote button
this is
inevitable oh oh
tried to shoot the bird but she was
already dead
he's killing my steelers
i want some kills too man
oh i didn't find any items oops
okay i'm killing you
is that your
ultimate yeah but i don't really have a
target right now so yeah
[Music]
that's okay you get it back pretty fast
um
we are
two
we
our who strongly asserted i mean they're
too scared yeah i think that's it
i like i like uh
characters have a lot of moving
abilities and on this
this lady you get a big jump it's really
fun
yeah maybe it was thick like a milkshake
mixture huh
what's a milkshake
you should try the oreo shake from
a
burger
yes
burger king
oreo milkshake says so good yes they
have oreo ice cream and oreo milkshake
it's like i guess it's not really
milkshake it
feels very ice shaky
oh
it's so good it's so addictive
i said i've had it many times i have to
go to the i have to go shopping later
i'll get some oreos and i'll make a
homemade oreo milkshake
oh i'm sure there's a [\h__\h] ton of
recipes for that online yeah was pretty
easy i think you just put oreos in a
blender with uh
with ice cream
and some milk
hell yeah
i'm dead but we only need uh frame oh
winning winning winning
nice
yeah
you should buy better i mean i don't
hear you hello
hello
do you hear me in game
no
not enough i'm gonna need some more i
mean
so what do you say about that what's
that gg on one
uh that was a good game yeah
i have the seven kill streak nice
wow but you had a 14 kill streak damn oh
yeah i don't i don't know if i die oh it
had one dead didn't do much damage i see
naruhoto that's all right are you
playing more like further away from
enemies they're like pretty close up
i mean right now because of the map i
feel like i was
like on the
normal in between distance yeah
there was not really like
so much space to
go further away and still do damage
that's true yeah yeah
[Music]
oh that was fun
yeah that was fun i could play forever
right
now why you want to play another one
last one last one okay
i'll put it on stage so you can try tyra
on like one of the payload maps
okay
where is she going oh because i already
have it now the advertisement is gone i
love maybe yeah
i guess i'll i'll practice some more
tyra then or should i try someone else i
don't know who is who is evie
if he looks cute what's she doing oh she
has like ice abilities so she flies
around on a broom
and uh she can go into an ice block to
heal
she has a blizzard a blizzard ultimate
which does quite a bit of damage
hard to play evie is really tricky oh
can i switch oh i already locked that's
kill it
she's kind of difficult to play because
the type of abilities that she has and
she's kind of supposed to be like a
flank but
uh you know you can still play and try
i'll try evie is the hardest character
what
[Music]
hard for beginners oh no that's all
right you just have to win anyway get on
your broom a lot you can you have an
ability where you can go in your broom
and you can try to get away from enemies
so just run away when you take damage or
something okay
they're probably like the enemies
probably looked at our lineup and
they're like oh she chose evie she must
be meeting her yeah
you're scared
they're scared no [\h__\h]
generator um
i have to go through the cards and pick
a
like a nice loadout
oh that's teleporting cute
blink magical teleport forward short
distance
ambassador
uh-huh uh-huh oh some of the massive ice
cream that deals 40 damage
[Music]
yeah it is fun
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah
what button was that that's all right
we're getting it we got the point
really nice i guess that was uh
cute
but that was a short thing
it felt like i i went so far
all right
all right we're ninety percent on the
point that's weird
[Music]
yeah i think they're still coming at a
spot
come here oh now
[Music]
you can mess around with the cards to
make the teleport reach father of life
[Music]
is she difficult do you feel like she's
difficult
very difficult
yeah we're successful though and i did
almost nothing that's i mean that's all
right you know you get to try it and fly
around i like playing uh eevee and like
just going on a broom and flying behind
the team and and i'm trying to mess with
them a little bit that's what she's good
at like poking it's probably why she's
difficult to play because that's kind of
how she's outfitted to play in some
cases maybe i think uh-huh been a while
since i've played her remember i like
her voice lines evie
why
different
horses and things you can get like
mounts or whatever
wait
i'm a ice buck
i just can't do anything it's just like
a shield where
oh yeah so
it might be like on default uh cards and
things like that you don't get heals but
there's like a lot of times when people
play eevee when you go into your ice
block you also generate
health in there but you might not have
it equipped maybe
okay okay
now where i have my heels on you
oh
that was not my kill really it feels
kind of like
um
disappointing when you think you killed
it yeah and you look on the right side
and it says someone else i think you got
an assist it still counts sort of but
yeah it is more satisfying to see your
name up there i'll just imagine it was
me
oh
wow
this
[Music]
one yeah is
one kill
probably my only one
ah there's somebody behind
oh i died
oh
you finished me i stole it sorry
now listen it's still okay you got it
okay oh you'll get them this time oh
nice
i'm learning yes baby steps i can't wait
to show this to my star system thank you
for
uh playing with a noob like me you got a
seven kill hill streak
oh well it's gone now
two obvious
uh points i just wanted to ride the
[Music]
please
victory yeah yeah that was too fast that
was a really fast game
you wanna play another one
you gotta end on a satisfying game right
yeah yeah i'm gonna oh seven wow i'm
gonna uh do a different character though
okay um
who did i
play the best with i had i guess a lot
of
experience with cassie so i got used to
her uh i want to play the valley girl
cassie oh yeah yeah do it
okay
kasai you hear that guys coffee
[Music]
holy shish that's a
that's quite delicious
like the chesticles you have there me
lady
oh cassie
i am the bird is so cute holy [\h__\h]
let's try this new tank an outfit never
played them
looks good tank yeah looks like a
paladin
oh
you got wings yeah
and testicles
got a strong tank on our side looking
respectfully yes yes
only respectfully
what did you just say
she just cursed she said something
[\h__\h]
oh maybe she said beach
beach a beach ah
b-e-a's okay
oh oh that skin is really cute
beach episode
a sun on the beach oh
sun on the beach oh okay
i feel like you purposefully said it
probably
as if it sounds like [\h__\h]
okay
cassie it's you and me again
hello hi
you you want me afterwards go for a
drink you want me oh
sure
it's cool nice sunglasses and
thank you eating something you see my
bird
oh yeah oh it's purple it's like oh it's
like a parrot
i'm just looking at my okay
this is a
oh what is that your wall yeah i don't
know hey i'm gonna set up you so now you
turn me away first you say yeah and then
you build some walls
[Music]
i thought we had something going on
there but all right
okay where am i oh
i gotta do is pull oh it's the snap i
like this map whoa i think they updated
this map it looks different when i first
played
i did get a nice kill there
very sniperish
i don't hear you
i use are you i'm just healing oh what
is forward oh okay
okay
[Music]
i need a
cover oh here i got a wall wait oh this
is the wild walk
oh i trapped oh
um
i might have accidentally trapped you
[Music]
thank you
you wanted to put it in front of me nuts
behind me i know it
they have two healers you should get
cauterized
oh
eliminate it
is that thing in the way oh oh that's
pretty fun
okay
nice
oh
are we pushing
oh i think their whole team just got
wiped
but
is it still now it's ours no
uh no well they already captured it so
now we just defend for the next minute
and then we can capture it on the next
round
oh
spurs you little [\h__\h]
if you're sniping if you're one of us
then you must go to the usual room
afterwards tell me
i don't know what my ultimate does okay
does something oh [\h__\h] okay
is it powerful
does it do something nice
yeah i think so i don't know i didn't
kill anybody with it but i think it
maybe it's more like a crowd control
thing
[Music]
um
i guess one one thing to learn as well
is
like how the maps a little color design
yeah
to know
where to shoot from
yeah ready to take cover and all that
nine
eight seven seven
six i just freaking hammer
stop jumping around so much
yeah now so when you defend on like a
payload see how we have one and one at
the top on the score
yeah so when you capture it and then you
get it you get two points and then yeah
when you defend you only get one
it's a little complicated um but you
can't actually win the whole game like
say you have three out of four points
and you do you win in defense even
though you get a point usually you can't
win the game like that you have to
capture the point that makes sense
[Music]
see it's it's kind of hard you'll see
when you when you play it might happen
this game
i may speak very fast like a machine gun
i'm sorry
i guess that's the
pro gamer inside of you oh yeah
sometimes i just are the gun yeah that's
true
[Laughter]
infiltrating the system
oh nice one okay so this does a circle
okay
or maybe like a half circle oh my god
when's he doing that
not cool
do you remember when you recorded these
lines yeah i do oh [\h__\h]
remember remembering
anime killing spree
i wonder if there's any randos who just
got you and just trying to bro then
they're like yo who's this cute girl
she's kind of kind of cute man
what the [\h__\h] is a million emilia watson
maybe yeah oh they got it again
man
[Music]
how do they keep on doing it
i know
oh god
this is scary
what the hell oh
oh i used my old bite oh okay hold on i
can do this
uh okay
oh
killer
um
wow that was just a lofty shot
i'm spectating what ozone
oh yeah what are you doing trying to hit
people with my slow hammer oh then i'm
gonna get on the point
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] oh not smart
i'll try to do better on that point
yes
he can get on the point
oh somebody said something in the valley
girl accent about a sunburn
you need some help applying some
sunscreen maybe
yes
gentlemen
did you bring some of that milky
some lotion uh you know i don't have
some but i know where i might be able to
get some yeah
the store
run
defend our honor we lost too often but
at least this is a good last match where
it's not too easy yeah
you get to you know play the character
that you like
last thing you lost to you i see you
whoa whoa oh
all right i distracted them for quite a
while
but i wonder maybe i guess because they
have a buck on their team and he's kind
of good at getting behind and taking out
our healer maybe that's why we've been
losing
ah
eh cara always forgets to buy items wait
you can no no no it's on auto she has an
auto buy which is fine yeah sometimes
what items am i using uh so it's just
items that
i feel like i've been missing a critical
information here i mean it's kind of
important but the game also takes care
of you
oh i can't get on the point
paladins
[Music]
like this you can y'all bad easy one
yeah the person on our three on our team
was probably throwing it
oh
thanks amen
no not really no yeah i guess it was
cheap
oh let me look at the
scoreboard i didn't get any kills but uh
i have a lot of assists
you know this guy the guy was playing
can't really get kills with him too
easily
oh wait a katie a killing defense assist
or what was that again yeah uh kills
death sentences
ah deaths are my own deaths
yes
ah holy [\h__\h] nine deaths
um
oh yeah the i mean that guy was roasting
us but he can't he can't even properly
name uh put a name uh
in on the keyboard he just rammed the
game and brown pounded it so
honestly
what you think about us we're amazing
gamers we're the gamers yeah
all live ian okay yeah you did really
good for playing your first i mean your
first time like i think you did really
good yeah
it was fun it's a i think it was a good
choice from your members too yeah use
this as the first
fps game for someone they didn't know
who they were choosing it for though
right no no i was just like oh if it's
somebody who's new to fps what do you
guys recommend
yeah it was a perfect choice i really i
really like the um the game it's fun it
has a lot of different characters yeah
oh and and and very colorful i like the
the graphics yeah especially
you because
like jrpgs and things like that uh
because it has some magic elements i
feel like uh you also might have liked
it because of that
yeah yeah yeah indeed
and now thanks to that you know i don't
think we would have gotten so many uh
supportive
items from uh and characters from
paladins uh i i don't think we would
have gotten that from the other games
yeah
that is so sweet especially
uh you know a lot of people like to play
and so it's nice yeah thank you thank
you thank you yeah i'm definitely down
to play anytime
it was an honor i was so nervous to play
with the
announcer the famous announcer from
paladins amelia watson that made me
quite nervous that was probably
why i was not doing
so good i could do better
and
she made me blush and
just listening to her gave me
butterflies that announcer
yeah it made your hands shaky i'm sure
you know so it made it difficult to aim
properly sweaty palms spaghetti
i like that that's kind of like a like a
meme yeah i mean
funny
who knows maybe one day come on kiara
skin hey hey
one day i am so weak i will take you
down amen oh
i will become a professional fps player
that is part of tournaments and i will
take you down oh yeah
we we should do more training yeah
yeah you train me and then i become
that's how it works i become the the
teacher
like the the
pupil overtakes the sensei or whatever
yes yes yes
so you gotta step up your game to um and
practice a bit more i don't think you've
been playing enough fps games yeah yeah
i've been meaning to now that i have my
pc is actually fixed
because it's kind of hard sometimes to
stream some fps games and play them at
the same time because you get low
frames yeah
i see i see
i can see that i've been i was also i
feel like i was uh around the end
focusing and and not
focusing on streaming but focusing on
the game rather than streaming yeah
that's kind of nice
and i guess
uh i've seen you getting sniped a lot
maybe that's the problem too yeah that
happens i mean do you feel like they're
they're targeting you a lot yeah that
does happen that's why you have to
practice so that you know when people
try to do that to you just you know roll
them
um
yes yes
although they kfb supposedly has
i think a lot of respect for their
attention they know what happened i hope
so bully me too
well i think i'll try out some of the
different champions uh if i ever
uh stream this again yeah what's
best
for me
thank you for accepting the spontaneous
request of teaching me ahmed oh thank
you for inviting me
[Music]
maybe there's something that i can teach
you
yeah you said you wanted to learn german
i can teach you german oh that'd be fun
yeah
my memory is great
you'll be fine you got a talent for it
i'm sure
secret hidden talent maybe i'd like to
find out
um
don't do it
all right thank you everybody for
watching today thank you
yeah
next stream on wednesday schedule is out
on twitter check it out
thank you thank you thank you paladins
again it's really fun
so nice if you want to help us how did
they even find out i guess because they
maybe they have their eyes on you yeah
maybe
we're on the
player count because i think a lot of
people also start to play
when uh when we're playing because they
want to play with us
maybe they notice spike yeah and they're
like maybe they're sitting in the
headquarters and suddenly they see like
a huge spider what the [\h__\h] what's going
on
we want a lot of servers going down
almost what is happening we need to find
out the source what is oh oh is it
because do you famous announcer amelia
watson is playing right now um
oh that is super cool to get like so
many cool skins for people that we like
to play so thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you
i love playing paladins awesome i look
so play anytime
all righty uh and in german we sail
finale
thanks for watching everybody have a
nice evening
[Music]
uh
you