[Music]
so
do
[Music]
first question hey guys can you hear
amitan
ah hello
what time what time is it
that's a secret it's a
time a different time everywhere is
asked
oh time to kick kiana's ass
excuse moa
okay question number two can you hear a
little bit of the
of the game bgm it's like really quiet
but um
you guys hear it
no
what she
time traveled uh one second
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
oh oh we are oh
oh we are on the right spot uh hello
hello uh we just uh went a little bit to
time traveling
excuse us hopefully no more um no more
time traveling now
sorry and once again
[Music]
that's right i am
and today's guest is number one
detective
time traveler zoomer and
the girl who ground-pounded your mom
i don't even know what that is
please um please be nice to my mom she
recently started watching my streams
yeah i heard i heard wow that's really
cute
what about your mom um
she uh she knows what i do but she
doesn't um
i don't want them to watch my streams
better not show them the real toxic
gamer that you are truly
yeah it's too embarrassing
i also i also felt a little bit
embarrassing once my
mom told me she watched hours of my
super mario 64 stream
where i said stuff like uh
the vibration of the controller arouses
me
mom i'm just joking oh wait no
sorry don't mind the game the game
screen screen is gone don't don't mind
it
i can't fix it yeah just keep on
laughing everyone keep on laughing
[Laughter]
so people people were like uh uh amma is
trying to steal kiara from cali but the
truth is
i'm gonna kick her ass so hard she's
gonna go back crying to her
i wonder what she thinks about the whole
cali thing
[Laughter]
oh your mom yeah my mom
i know i know kelly's mom thinks well of
it can can you like
tell a good zoomer story amen
zoomer story yes
uh being put on the spot here
oh well oh about my dream okay yeah
yesterday i had a dream because i've
been playing a lot of minecraft
so it kind of like took place in
minecraft but i was like in this
i was like i don't like tall buildings
not because i don't like heights just
because i'm scared like
you know tall buildings will fall or
something and i was in a tall building
and i kept taking the elevator and it
was scary because the elevator
uh was not very stable and then um i
don't really okay this is weird i don't
really like
i don't like justin bieber but for some
reason he was in my dream
and he was like really sad and he's like
how come
my friends don't love me and i said you
need a real homie that'll play minecraft
with you at 3am
and then um there was like this party
that was going
on and i was trying to look for like uh
some
some sort of alcohol i don't drink
alcohol i don't know why this is part of
the
story uh and it was like brandy
and then i like went to this convenience
store to try to find this like special
alcohol and then um
yeah wow
wow wow what uh what a story
i'm i need to take support
what happened
the why is it
the elgato doesn't like me today
[Music]
okay tell tell another story maybe like
five minutes please
five minutes what the heck
myself uh okay i'll just let the chat
i'll just let the chat ask me questions
and i'm really bad at thinking of
stories like on the spot so if i if one
comes up while you guys are asking me
questions i'll uh i'll tell it
no not my brain it doesn't work like
that
i can't just think of something
i'm not a believer i'm not i don't even
know why he was in my dream i only know
that one time like baby
baby and that's the only song that i
know
oh how much sleep i got two hours of
sleep
and then i used all my three alarms i
kept turning them off
and then the last one um i got up
and then um and then i started uh
i started making my tea i'm almost on my
team now
and then i started reading the witcher
book yeah it's kind of weird actually
i talked about it a little bit like uh i
started reading the book but the way
that
the first chapter is written is like
really confusing so like
i'll read you up i'll read you a passage
a jerk some force plucked her up pulled
her onto another saddle hold on
again the bone shaking speed the mad
gallop arms and legs desperately
searching for support the horse rears
hold on there is no support there's no
there's no there's blood
the horse falls it's impossible to jump
aside no way to break free to escape the
tight embrace of these chain male clad
arms
there's no way to avoid the blood
pouring onto her head and over her
shoulders
like the way the way the first chapter
is written is really confusing because
it's all written in like
these short descriptive sentences um
so it's really hard to get i mean you
wouldn't think it would be hard but like
for the flow of it like it's like a
dream they're like describing describing
a dream so it's pretty
it's just kind of confusing um but yeah
i was getting into
it and then uh i warmed up the same
witch and i'm here with kiara
fixing technical stuff again it has been
fixed
oh yeah hopefully it will stay like that
i'm again sorry this was unexpected
because like in the previous streams
everything was fine i'm sorry
um it wasn't expected i mean
yeah why
no nothing oh uh
i just oops oh my god did you see
something what
yeah you started playing this i don't
know what this is yeah
oh wait wait so it's not a
is it
[Music]
the gaming screen on stream labs is
frozen
hide it and then unhide it network but
in the wrong
place i've deactivated it and activated
it
but you have like on my elgato screen
it's
moving you're in the right place yeah it
is talking exactly
[Music]
i believe in you you can do it yep
did i tell another story
can we get out of the game yeah okay
good
and
[Music]
one second i shall
uh delete that
delete
try to open it again amen
how was your sandwich uh
i i i uh ordered it last night because
uh it was like one of those things where
you know how when you order something
and they put on a fee and it's like oh
well if you add
four more dollars worth of stuff the fee
is gone
uh so it's like uh i left it in my
fridge and then i tried to heat it up in
a pan
and then it was cold on the inside so it
wasn't that great yeah
ah i have some i'm having a deja vu
because something happened that happened
before you remember the time where you
tried to help me with the fire emblem
stream
oh yeah uh and then i tried to to delete
in
because every elgato was working again
but then in streamlabs
uh i tried to close the video capture
device and reopen it because it was
frozen
just like last time and then
just like last time now streamlabs froze
ah um yeah well okay
we can uh just close close streamlabs
the stream will still go
i get it'll be fine if you close it okay
yeah you restart restarted yeah
streamlabs yeah
i feel like it stopped last time
[Music]
hello yes yes okay
thank god okay let's knock on the tables
on all the tables
[Music]
sorry bubba knocking on all the tables
so that this doesn't happen anymore
let's get into it i would say uh
what do you want to start off with we're
playing four teams today
uh we can start at the at the start at
the beginning
[Music]
yeah the game is too loud
i know why okay now it should be back to
normal
ah is it okay now i tried mankata before
the stream i did not really understand
it but i
i did win so i think it's a good idea i
mean
yeah i like mancala i used to play it
i used to play a lot like uh you know
like after school
uh in like grade school if you had like
after school program
we used to play games and stuff play a
lot of mancala
it i never honestly until this switch
game i never
saw this game ever before oh the seeds
and dropped them in there it's just like
it turned the game
[Music]
so hard to satisfy yes and
these six pockets what about now chat
yeah
you have to have to collect the most
it's good now perfect everything's good
does the chat know this game does the
chat understand this game
uh i'll explain it briefly so pretty
much like uh
let's say hypothetically i'm on the left
side and kiara's on the right side
it would never be that way of course
what and uh
so the person who has uh whose turn it
is you want to go through all the rows
and you want to end up at your own goal
with as many of the marbles as possible
so like you have to calculate because
you have to pick up your your marbles as
you go along
but you can also pick up some as you go
past
so you have to calculate it uh to make
sure you're you're
gaining instead of losing yeah
calculation is
i'm really good at that and i also just
fixed that i put myself to the bottom
left and you to the bottom right i think
this is more accurate
i don't know why i didn't already
intentionally do that from the beginning
let's play mancala right
wait i mean i think i remember how to
play i i think
i mean it's just like throwing uh these
what what do you call them marbles i
don't know actually
are they marbles it's your journal right
oh no no it's your internet oh chiara's
in control
i don't know what i'm doing i'm just
doing it
so uh i i don't know which side is mine
i think it's
i think it's i think it's on the left
side yeah the left
okay okay top six the top sticks are
yours
and the left like you have to go well
you guys will see
you have to go past and drop one and
hurts too if you go that way
um that's just a demonstration
yeah one two three four five six i don't
know what i'm doing
but the marvels are so pretty
see um i didn't know you could only pick
from one side
but um
ah okay okay okay i think i get it i'm
making you win right now because i'm
putting some in here god damn it
i mean essentially okay okay okay so you
want to build up as many marbles as you
can in a pocket
so that you can go around and put drop
one in your own wait how did you get
that in there
i don't know how did you get so many i
don't know how did you get so many
i only have two you have five hey no no
no you are
you have you have six that's mine yep
i don't think so no it is yours
but on my screen you're on the right
side
yeah yeah i am on the right side but but
the big one on the left side is yours
so you have another six yeah yeah
[Laughter]
just accept it you're winning all right
we'll see if it wins at the end i don't
know who is
i'm so confused as chad we are all
confused
well whoever has that many is is a
winning i don't know
i know who
oh i'm winning apparently
yeah you are
did you also like when you were younger
collect marbles like this
uh not really i used to collect the
rocks i really like
like like fancy rocks or just
gray rocks uh we sometimes you know
depends any type of rock
any type oh you like all the rocks
that's so nice of you
yeah did you
eat snow i had me in snow before
me too i will i will confess that
you're capturing again why are you
capturing so often
i think i think the way it works if you
put one marble in
each row on your side you get to capture
maybe
so like let's say on the first one like
this one that i'm my hand is over
if this one has uh six marbles i go one
two three four five six
okay the next one i think it makes it
lets me capture them yeah
i don't know i i kind of did understand
it when i
when i played it with the npc but now
now my brain is just empty
uh chad says no chad says oh
oh well i think i think the way i played
this game is different than the official
rules
ah okay you skipped mine oh okay okay
okay okay
i just gave you a bunch of marbles no no
no you
you don't put any in mind only i put
stuff in my um
oh but you gave me some ah yeah yeah
it's true
well amen you're in control the whole
time
she keeps winning she keeps winning
[Music]
hell yeah
if it perfectly ends in the capture
thing then
oh okay okay okay
okay trying to be smart again uh ah this
one
yeah hey but that's where it ends
yeah yeah give me give me all those yeah
i have some small marbles
[Music]
wow
oh it looks like you have much more than
me so that's
don't worry about it
the marbles look yummy it's like candy
it looks so pretty
or like a mana in a game i don't know if
it's
loud enough for the people to hear but
the sound when you drop the models is so
nice so satisfying
one feel free yay extra turn
[Music]
my dogs are not they're not fighting but
they're like uh growling at each other
over a chopstick
chopsticks on the floor
cute cute i wanna i wanna
i wanna take your dog for a walk amen
ah okay okay wow
just you just give me your dogs like
that
don't trust you thank you i wouldn't
trust myself
with a dog i'm only good with cats but
thank you okay
man did you why why did you
oh
i didn't even think about what i was
doing
that's not fair that's the way to win
that's exactly the way i won when i
first played this game
but i thought you were winning because
you actually understood the game
okay okay go back next game do we want
to do dots and boxes
uh sure this is like uh you know this
looks ex tic-tac-toe sort of
yeah that's in boxing yeah so you played
it before
no oh
i played something like this yeah you
gotta create a box i played something
have you ever do you know the muppets
i heard of them pen and paper uh they
made it they made like a knockoff mario
party
game on the gamecube called the muppets
party cruise and they had a game like
this in it
you know how to play you draw you you
should you should try to not
let the other person do the last uh
rules because they would fill up the box
so
yep ah i think it's easy
simple yeah apparently this is like a
game that
that children would play in school when
they're bored
oh okay okay okay did they really finish
the box
you get to keep going you know you can't
skip this okay
yes please
let's draw some straight lines
you're blue okay well let me show you
how i win this game
okay i'm quite confident with this one
uh i am not i played connect four with
ina
and i did really bad
the one where you dropped the the the
things from the top
yeah hey why did i i think i even saw
that when you guys were playing that
i see i see you don't really have a
strategy
ah you have you don't have a strategy
either what are you doing i have a
strategy
i learned my strategy from the npc
oh yes i
i see what you're doing
here comes the big brain from the big
bird uh no small birds
my favorites just played this before
it's not fair
once you lost against me once you will
understand
[Music]
are you trying to make like a big box or
something
not necessarily i can start doing this
here
i don't like this
[Laughter]
i love your hicks amen thank you
do they say in uh the english speaking
lens
that when someone hits that someone is
thinking of you do it did i say that
uh no not sneezed
i don't think there's anything like that
that i've heard of before except like an
anime
we're like oh somebody's talking about
you sneeze
maybe that wasn't only sneezing eh huh
i see maybe i make something up
it it's really not hicking is there
nothing like when you hit
then this and that is there nothing like
that
uh oh uh
[Music]
uh no
i see let's create something i always
thought hiccups like
like uh oh no wait no not hiccups no
nevermind i don't know
i don't like those yeah you're trying
you're trying to capture a big area
aren't you
no i'm just um my strategy
is basically just uh first of all
not giving you a chance to do the long
last
uh last line for a box
so i'm trying to not create any boxes
i'm not going to fall for that can you
capture the whole box
oh no no no i cannot
only like the small boxes
by the way i'm in yeah i've never met
a person before that takes so much as
you do i think it's really cute
ah thank you well you know it might be a
sign of a serious illness but i think
it's
probably fine are you okay on it
are you okay i'm okay
they're just um they're just burps like
but they're upside down
burps not hicks yeah that's not very
ladylike ahmed
no no no that's why that's why they i
turned them into
i've turned them into uh
hiccups oh i'mma's doing a thing
oh smart amen
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
you have another turn once you close one
box you get another oh okay
but this is no problem yet sometimes
it's better to let someone else
close the first boxes
indeed
think big thinking
this is so chill i like this game
yeah the music in this level is really
nice
this is like almost like lo-fi hip-hop
beats to
study too yeah yeah i don't think
there's
any that i can do where it doesn't
create a box for you
uh and yeah it does uh
ah wait let me see
no there's still there's still one or
two where you
don't create a box
is there a timer on this
oh actually huh maybe it does uh
maybe
i'll give you one ah
[Music]
i guess won't you fall for my trap
now you have to give me one i probably
give you more than
one i calculated mine so i'd only give
you one instead of giving you two there
you go
take all of them but it it must stop at
some point
hopefully oh hopefully oh
are you sure about that wait oh wait
wait
make it stop
yes yes that's what i thought that's
what i thought and now you cannot stop
me
because you make one line and i fill up
all the others ha
[Music]
see we'll see about that
i'll find some way
it could time travel
there's no there's no escape on there no
no no way accept your fate
hold on running through simulations in
my head
there's no way ahmed it's over it's over
give me all that i know it
there's no way out there's only a way in
okay thank you itadakimasu
run
[Music]
foreign it gets even it gets higher and
higher
yeah cheated because she knew how to
play this game she didn't strap
beforehand
this is my first time doesn't count
[Music]
i mean if you want to challenge me again
we can do it again
or we move on we'll find that one
yes two wins for me already i'm winning
let's okay what
which one do you want to do next uh
something we can do whatever you want
d-r-a-u-g-h-t-s
ah drat oh checkers
yeah and so this is super easy uh you
said you didn't play it before but it's
like
really easy you just gotta listen to the
explanation
if she wants to sleep this night with me
nothing
[Laughter]
so you can only move diagonally
unless there's a there's a catch
it is not if i can reach the other side
and get kingd
so if you reach the other side you win
uh no but then
you can also move backwards now what
happens to be a king
you can move backwards otherwise you can
only oh wow
whoa whoa i haven't played this before
apparently has it has a different name
called checkers too i've never heard of
that one
yeah on your screen it's called drought
drop ah
probably ah i have uh i guess i bought
the european version of the game
ah that's interesting that it's called
different stuff
yeah because apparently it's originally
a french game
yeah here it's called checkers this is a
checker pattern
that's why you asked me to spell it out
ah
yeah okay i understand okay it
might turn first very nice very well i
shall
i shall dominate you amen um
i know you're into that okay
concentration
but you do understand i can't go that
way no you have to jump over me
diagonally
diagon day
diagonally diagonally thank you
diagonally diagonally
yeah thank you ahmed for teaching me
english
welcome i should take english less
lessons
with ame oh so i can't jump over my
own
[Music]
well yeah that's okay i'll i'll take it
um
is there is your dog giving you tips on
how to win
yeah not fair
bubble check up checker master
maybe maybe instead my papa can help me
with my papa was in the chat i think
[Music]
i wonder if he knows this game
ah what do i do what do i do
your turn
if you don't jump over someone you can
only move one square
wait it tells me yeah can i only i can
only move
yeah in this case it does not give me a
choice i must
trade with you there you go
take me take me now
fine
oh nice try okay
this is quite we're quite equal right
now
yeah not bad ah
i feel like you're farther along the
board than me
i'm rising like a phoenix
tactical tactical sacrifice i mean i
mean
there's not much change to the board but
oh wait oh yeah
ah what i can do
if it's possible to take two and in a
row i can do that
i take the heck i didn't know
[Music]
i'll move forward
this is you know i'm probably very good
at this because i was playing fire
emblem which is a
which is a strategic jrpg enough alert
maybe yeah maybe
do you play any strategy games ever
ah sort of
there was one that i uh an mmo
that i like to play cool for a while i
stretch it's called no
ah it doesn't that is strategic
yeah it's turn-based game so you have to
use strategy
because like it's it's kind of similar
to chess like uh you have a movement
points where you can only go in it you
can only move in a grid
like like like chess i'm taking it i'm
taking two again
you distracted me oh and i'm
i was just trying to make small talk
i could give you one because i will also
take you afterwards but
yeah boy now take me
no why can't i move here you have to
you're forced
to you're forced to sacrifice yourself
that's stupid
the kiala fried phoenix army is
succeeding
probably ahead by three
show me your detective skills amy
i just might i know you're doesn't count
i'm running on two hours of sleep uh the
leg
there's legacy that's probably because
of the
the time traveling you did before you
know probably like
influencing the current timeline with
that
yeah yeah something like that
[Laughter]
oh oops
yep thank you
i can't go backwards
you're not a king yet i has a king
this game sucks that
i don't like it
[Music]
wow i'm like actually smart today i'm
i'm impressed
[Music]
i told you i'm dominating you in the
beginning i said so
oh i don't know what i'm doing
thank you
i think cara's just lucky he's not he's
not strategizing
what he's just getting lucky
excuse me that is not true
[Music]
ah with this one you're you might even
end up being uh becoming a king
with that one ah because i cannot really
stop you
down there if i move up here you capture
me if like move up here you capture me
i cannot move backwards and
i'll just let you become kin it's okay
can't you kill me are you going to kill
me though
oh oh yeah i guess i i will
how can i become king uh yeah sorry
mistake i'm always winning
just end it already
[Music]
victory is mine
you see kiara cheated because i haven't
played these games on here before but
but while
before the stream she was like i played
i went and played because you played
with inna so i played some of the games
against the pc so i already know how to
play so of course she's gonna win
he has experience okay i haven't played
it before it doesn't count
let's play a game that you played with
inna before that i did not play
uh okay how about the where is that one
how about foreign okay
but i mean everybody's playing this game
yeah this one i played in my childhood
too
is there any any other game that you
played with eno that i didn't play i
wonder you come to try and get four in
ah
but now here we have the same chances
right we don't need the voice right okay
play another chance for
miss amelia
bottom right detective versus bottom
left phoenix
okay well i haven't played this game in
like ages
so i have no idea what i'm doing um
the music is really distracting for me
in this game
like you can do for uh also diag die
die wait this is only diagonal
honey anyway anyway okay
hmm
why does it sound italian to me
i'm not salty
it's okay i like salty things
like kfp fries mmm potato fries
uh in minecraft i'm making potato fries
very soon thanks to the potato that you
and me
grabbed together from glenn's place yeah
actually like fries
oh i don't think so only like grilled
potato but that's also good
reminds me of my childhood oh
not little spiders did not remind you
uh sornovia hmm
diagonal now you can go anyway really up
down
left right okay
really on me or are you trying to
deceive me
what no i'm telling the truth okay
yeah all the angles
[Music]
thank you for the super chats by the way
ah
i think we're like we're like pretty
much like this
the same amount of smarts when it comes
to this game
we'll see
yeah i think this game can also end in a
draw
if we just don't manage to get anything
together
yeah ah chiara
[Music]
yeah okay this happens when you're not
careful
well i love one game for you out of out
of here yeah
i'd come back because you're a guest i
let you win one game the one game that
you played before
thank you thank you okay
you want to choose another game that you
played with uh enough before
[Music]
uh oh okay keep going
let me see um
chess we can try if you want
i i've told my viewers before when i was
a small phoenix
i was in the chess club so you would
think i was
i'm good at chess however there was a
chess tournament
where my chess club went to but i was
left behind because i was the worst in
the group
so sad now this
this will show for real who is smart and
who is not
i like chess if i win this game
i demand a promotion from bottom left to
bottom right
so each time we can't let her win
i think we know the rules right yeah
[Music]
my alignment on the chart is on the
on the w
english am i white
yeah yeah okay
i can do this i will win
okay i believe in you
i like the the chessboard it looks like
chocolate cookie
i was more thinking the figures look
really fancy
well i i don't remember much so this one
is the tower that can only go straight
right
yeah the horse goes like one front and
then one to the side
right and one two diagonal uh what was
this one again does it only go
this time goes diagonally okay then the
queen
goes anywhere and uh yeah she can do
she can do the night bishop and the uh
yeah yeah so straight as much as she
wants
and diagonal as much as wait only one it
let's ask let's ask chad what is it what
does the queen do again
queen can't do nights okay
so she does the bishop bishop
and the tower ah
wait who's the knight the horse that's
the horse yeah the knight the knight is
the horse
isn't it wait when i'm confused i
thought i remember these things
queen can go any direction yeah okay and
not only once
you've got as many as she wants
wow she's like she's like wow
okay i think i i think i remember
like can i go 2-2 oh i can
my memory from the chess club times is
getting refreshed
[Laughter]
when was the last time you played chess
um actually not that long ago like maybe
two two or three months ago
[Music]
for me it's been like years
probably like million years
well you have high chances then but i
want my promotion to bottom right
okay maybe not all the way right but if
you win maybe go to the center
you gotta you know you gotta move a one
a one axis at a time okay
i don't i don't know what i'm doing i
don't have a strategy do you have a
strategy
not really in chess i just do i just do
like whatever until i find an
opportunity
and then uh about to take advantage with
these pawns
uh you go diagonal to for kills
only for kills okay okay okay
okay no problemo
oopsie
[Music]
well i don't know
what's that again a pun
it's called a pond right a pawn yeah
yeah fun
unless you call it something else do you
call any of them like different
words yes but you called the horse and
knight right but in german we call it
just uh
the horse oh no no we called it that
maybe maybe we called it the jumper
springer
what do you call the tower uh
i just call it a tower i don't know for
it no uh
fortnite no uh rook
rook does that even mean in german it's
uh the tower
i shall move with the tower
i gotta do some deep thinking here
wait so it can go like like that right
yeah
wow then the museum really makes me
think deeply
reminds me of like animal crossing like
in the museum
ah oh you've been playing animal
crossing
well not lately i haven't played it in
like
two months
[Music]
actually i think i think my town got
deleted
how is that possible because i i got it
i had to get a new switch and then when
i tried to transfer everything you can't
transfer like
uh you can't transfer just like the sd
card
oh yeah you got a helmet oh
but now everything is working fine yeah
yeah i got i got actually got the animal
crossing version of this which is really
it's really pretty yeah that one looked
really cute
i'm also thinking of buying another
switch because
in my stream yesterday i was talking to
my viewers about
buying a ps5 for my brother but
turns out he is a man of culture and he
prefers
over a ps5 he wants a switch
so you're gonna give him your old one no
no no no no i'm gonna buy him
a new one of course because he wants to
play a breath of the wild
he's a big zelda fan what about such a
big game
yeah i didn't i didn't play breath of
the wild yet but
i watched a full full clear
playthrough i want to watch you play a
game that'd be funny
what i should play the game yeah
no thank you wait what is that that
thing there
i don't know it can go diagonal right
yes
[Music]
well let's see what you do
okay
[Laughter]
what what
we both don't know why why who got
checked
am i checking you what
how what what oh no
oh
[Music]
i think you're safe there
ah
well that that music got real intense
there
i felt so threatened
i'mma threatened me with my life
oh
why are you trying to do ame i don't
know
by the way if if i move the horse here
does it only take
what's here or what's in between yeah it
only it only kills what's on their
ending spot
huh
i'll go for it hopefully i will not
regret it
yeah yeah yeah i didn't want to do it
actually but i saw a chat
and uh i decided to do it you did what
the chats told
you to do yeah i'm not i'm not even
looking at the chat i'm too focused on
i cannot multitask like normally i look
a lot at the chat when i play games but
as you can see in minecraft i'm like
really really scattered
scatterbrained like i keep on forgetting
what i'm doing
is cheating no
why did you move no you didn't
oh all right i'm not reading chat
anymore because you guys made me make a
bad decision
i don't think i have to sacrifice it
tell her to do something bad
oh wait thank you
[Music]
yay oh my god am i promoted to bottom
right
yet oh my god is it finally coming it's
a day here where i proved myself to be
smart
because people had a discussion about
whether or not i mean everyone is
certain about me being bottom
but there were discussions about whether
or not i'm smart or not and people were
like uh well she can speak a bunch of
languages fluently but it doesn't
necessarily mean that
that um she's smart right well i see
what you're doing i can see i see what
you could do
well thank you but i also kind of agree
that you don't necessarily have to be
smart
uh in order to learn languages but today
i will prove you i am a big brain
big bird brain smart person
phoenix i think so you just have uh
some bad luck sometimes
i see that i see what you can do with
that voice i don't know if you see it
but i see it
but i haven't seen it happening but i
think i think you could stop me before
uh um wait
can i can i the pun
can move in any direction i will protect
myself
okay
excuse me i just wanted to laugh like a
crazy person
do you have something planned no not at
all like for real my mind is blank
but i'm just enjoying this nice board
game time with my number one detective
with with the pawns i forget can you
kill in any direction or only diagonal
oh only diagonal ah
yeah yeah they wrote it uh down there
when i killed some
someone of yours it was written there
you know okay you know that the last
game that we're playing today
as a strip poker ah
look at me i don't know how to play
poker
do you know how to play yeah i don't but
it's just about tripping
okay okay just kidding just
[Music]
what does this one do again it just goes
diagonal
oh
am i am i doing something bad for myself
though or
hmm
why are you laughing why are you
laughing
i don't see any way that i don't see any
way that you could take me from there
if i go back before
i'll do it
i was hoping i'd throw you off with my
last
ah bottom right here we go well okay
sure
wait does this mean that in the next
turn you can take my queen
no yes it does no it doesn't it's
i mean okay wait oh no i guess you can
go to here and to here right
i guess i counted one one fields too
much
okay then it cannot
think think think kiara
i i'm gonna i think i'm gonna go back
[Music]
check
[Laughter]
ah
uh
wait can i i cannot jump over you right
i mean you can kill it but if i can't go
you can only do uh i think you can only
get one kill right
i don't think you can jump yeah yeah
yeah but like uh like only one kill but
i
have to stop where you are right now
right
i would have said check if what is that
check if you could have killed the king
immediately
um well which one is the is that the
king and that the queen or the other way
everywhere
yeah that's right oh
wait let me try to think of the
possibility so if i go there
the queen can go diagonal and straight
right
so you can the queen cannot hurt me
and the king can only move one at a time
so i'm still too far away from him but
uh
he could if if you would want to move
the king from
there to get him to save space does the
king
he even i don't know if he can only go
straight or also diagonal but even if he
could
go diagonal he would only have one
choice and that is going here
uh unless well you have to move the
queen first to let him move somewhere
else but wait could you in any way
take my when i go here can you i tell
you
i don't think you can take me if i go
here like the horse is too far away
oh my god am i winning am i winning
check
here comes the intense music again
well well i mean if i take your queen
then you
definitely weakened you will after that
probably
proceed to take whatever this figure is
named
can can the king go diagonal
but only one at a time well only
straight
one uh diagonal two okay
yeah that sacrifice is probably worth it
yes bye queen
checking checking you out amen
thank you that was worth it
beautiful this is beautiful this is
beautiful i feel so smart today
what is this figure is this the same one
that just died
[Music]
i have you on the radar miss amelia
watson
now probably you want to move your horse
again
so that's a good idea
um
thinking thinking
oh my god i hope i didn't move too fast
i'm safe oh my god oh my god oh my god
i feel so smart i feel so smart god damn
it
[Music]
ah not worth it not worth it not worth
it
not worth it because then you take me
from there
you go my friend fight for me
[Music]
what did you do
why are you laughing detective
i'll take this then you you can take me
with
with that i shouldn't tell you all the
moves but
uh it's pretty obvious i guess
[Music]
well yeah
oh no no probably not but i can still
threaten you with it
oh wait
tactical retreat and check
oh my god i'm so smart
holy damn i keep on checking you out but
this does not mean that i
i lost interest in cali okay
hmm doing a big thing
huh
can i do something with this boy
oh wait yeah yeah no okay he can only
kill diagonally
diagonally uh what can
ah can he move diagonally without
killing
oh i can go here
and this one can only ah but then you
can take me with that one
well i'll go for it i think
do i want to go for that i think i do
checking again
okay okay okay okay
huh hmm
hey what what's wrong what's wrong
what's wrong
oh i was just stretching okay okay
[Music]
do i want to move these boys i have i
still have so many
units that i barely moved down here um
well if i move here then you can take me
i think they're still kind of useless
oh what do i wanna do what do i wanna do
what do i wanna do what do i wanna do
[Laughter]
this is intense i do not want to lose
because i want to be bottom right
i'm sick of being bottom left people
underestimate this phoenix too much
i got
i was thinking to i was i was i was two
two two two uh careless there
got it goddammit no i was still
what the hell did you just drop
something now
my cat knocked over a bottle your cat
yeah you never sent me a picture of your
cat before why
yaha i have oh
or maybe you did when i sent you
pictures of mine
yeah you were like follow up cat here's
my cat yeah
that's right now i remember that's like
a long time ago
ah when we were flexing our
yes pets indeed pets
okay
all right focus focus
okay let's see let's be smart let's be
smart here okay
let's be smart um
come on there has to be something that i
can do no no no
what is this again diagonal boy right
[Music]
oh
i cannot think anymore i lost i i
already used up all my brain power
like a throwaway move a throwaway move i
already just
threw away my queen
[Music]
i want to do something meaningful
oh
meaningful that's what i would have done
too really
huh yeah they still have yeah do you
have it
you oh no oh no you didn't
[Laughter]
oh no oh oh yes you did
oh oh yes
oh no how will i ever escape
[Music]
well yeah how will you escape
nom nom nom nom
i hope i didn't do anything bad oh my
god
no
you have challenged me i shall unleash
my chew power
chess is so intense this is why they
didn't bring me to the chess tournament
when i was like five years old
it's pretty early though to be playing
chess that's pretty cool oh probably was
a bit
bit older maybe not like nine or
something
i've noticed that's still pretty early i
guess that's around the time i learned
how to play too
my brain was not fully uh
uh developed yes
please don't take me
i want to live a more fulfilling life i
want to marry before i die
holo life chess tournament oh
that sounds like an interesting but very
boring stream as well
what did you just move the king
god dammit i lost such good fighters
i lost two of my diagonal boys
[Music]
no
ah
[Music]
why not i think you can only do that in
like the first few rounds
or like the first move from the pawn of
the pawn from the beginning
[Music]
i don't see many smart moves that i can
do or not at all
[Music]
this boy just i cannot set him free
that's like
oh wait
[Laughter]
sorry
i'm coming for you ami i'm coming for
your position
we shall switch bottom left and bottom
right
okay
huh
this is so intense this is that this is
the most intense fight i ever had in my
whole life and i was like
i wasn't i was a part-time i'm i'm still
a part of warrior i
i was fighting giants and and all that
kind of
weird you know
that was using your your your brawn now
you got to use your brain
i'm using it the whole time moment
ah wait okay one good workout for your
brain yep yep indeed indeed i like this
this is challenging
we're like if i'm not
uh gonna win that i would still say
we're equal
let's oh
no
[Music]
but i don't want you to take my horse
what if i go here
i don't really wanna i don't really
wanna move backwards but
[Laughter]
come on okay we gotta make them
don't kill me don't kill me don't kill
me
[Music]
okay go ahead check
smart well yeah but you will keep on
following me won't you
oh
[Music]
bye
well we're just eliminating each other
here
oh could i have taken the tower
goddammit could i have
i keep on forgetting if the king can go
diagonal
well well well well
well well well
stop it this is bullying this is bull
oh no no wait
wait wait how can i how do i save myself
now
wait if
yeah i think i have to sacrifice my
horse
because uh if i move away then i'm
checkmate
or let's check about
okay if you want to play this game
uh then let's play it from here
or
or not
[Music]
wait can i do something smart you will
we will end up just taking each other
here
because you will take me i will take you
and then and then what happens then dear
amelia
watson what happens after that
i guess we'll find out
tactical movement
eh
make it end
oh wait i know
uh-huh
[Music]
oh i cannot go back oh
damn it i
think think no wait but yes actually yes
actually yes oh we'll be in the same
position
oh yeah that's funny hey
that is interesting
and i could take your horse but you
probably run away with the horse first
you probably go here
[Music]
or you go here um
but then but no you you can't because
then i'm
next turn i want to take your king
what else are you cannot huh
you're in chat
well i was looking but it wasn't really
telling me anything good
oh we're in the same position
[Music]
hmm
that's why i like to play like fast
but i get messed up a lot when i play
fast
[Music]
ah
well well no i shall ah
this is really intense i didn't think it
would take us this long
well chess yes your chest usually takes
a while hmm
does the horse take what's in between
your jump or only what did what's on the
left
only what it lands on only what it lands
on
thank you i hope so
oh my god are we gonna let our horses
and our kings only fight each other
yeah we're pretty even right now yeah
you only have one
one more pawn than me
oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god
oh my god
so what could you possibly
do if i do that
just run away
[Laughter]
[Music]
i wonder how long our chess game is like
already like it feels like an
hour uh
i think it's been that long oh no
chad place your bets now who is gonna
win
this intense chess game i saw some
people saying it'll
it'll be a draw i don't think you can
draw in chess though can you can you can
you
i feel like it could end up in like an
endless uh chasing
one king chasing the other king oh wait
what
what if only two kings are on the
battlefield is it just over
chased each other forever what they're
saying amen
do you have a higher chances do they see
something that i don't see
uh i don't know i don't see anything huh
wait
calculating calculating i shall chase
you the way you chase me
[Music]
hmm
oh come on
i can't i keep on forgetting can he go
diagonal
yeah yeah move in any direction but only
one space
[Music]
oh my god oh my god oh my god
oh my god
ah
my my brain is about to explode
oh
[Music]
well it should be ending soon no
stop checking me stop checking me i mean
i like you too
if you really want to check me out that
bad i mean i'm hoping for it but
does the game warn you like if you if
you put yourself in a position where
you're checkmating yourself
i wonder no that's you
[Laughter]
[Music]
what happens if i go here ah
well it'll be my turn next and uh i
don't think it'll work out too well for
[Laughter]
you
well i mean god damn it
please please oh
i think it doesn't it does keep you from
checkmating yourself there
oh yeah yeah true nice thank you again
thank you now we know would have made a
bad decision
see now that that alone should put me in
bottom right
because if the game wouldn't have
stopped you
well i i just uh oh i just play fast
like when i play chess i like um
i like to make my my moves immediately
like try to see how fast i can calculate
even if
even if it puts me in a bad position i
don't know
it's probably not how you're supposed to
play chess but i just like to go fast
aha
zoomer i get it
make it end
please make it end
are we gonna fight each other with the
pawns now
i mean
[Laughter]
okay um we're like almost like
in the same position again like i just
don't have a bathroom
we're just rounding after each other is
this a draw
it's not we we can uh probably need like
another 10 more minutes we'll finish it
up yeah
oh god oh god oh god
yeah why would you know
woof
he gave me a shook there
[Laughter]
hmm
wait what happens when you get to the
pond at the end does anything happen
um no no noah
i didn't know that what
what it it did
this is this a new rule for for like
zoomers
this doesn't didn't exist during dinner
time
chad was telling me to pick queen but i
just picked not queen can you pick queen
i don't think that was an option was it
it didn't look like it
no don't
[Music]
that's why they kept saying move the
pawns move the pawns
no there was nothing either essence when
does this rule exist
no no no no no
[Music]
sacrifice
goodbye horse i loved you very much and
i was i believed in you i believed in
your
strength and believed in your power
thank you for everything you've done for
me you will be
feeling better when you're up there in
horse heaven
then at least you will not i hope you
will not be made into
a burger or something like that because
i don't like horse burgers no that's not
a good thing
i'm sorry for what i've done for you i'm
so sorry i wish i could have given you a
better life
i wish
thank you welcome horse is still alive
and promotion okay you get two
promotions or only one
that's also a good question okay
[Music]
wait did they say only one what i think
you can get two
well i mean but you
you didn't choose queen because of what
reason because it was to
embark uh
i have a reason but i'm not gonna tell
you you have a reason
what could that reason be isn't the
queen the best like she can do it all
there's no reason for that you're just
saying you had a reason just to look
smart
i sure about that yeah
[Music]
onyo
[Laughter]
nice queen you got there wow
nice shiny new queen for my collection
parting my harem now have two queens
you could have killed my pawn and you
would have been safe
i i i'm pretty sure you were in a right
position to kill my pawn that's what i
thought you were going to do
[Music]
what would that have given oh i guess i
could have kept you from
yeah yeah no no no
no no
i was so good in the beginning but now i
paid a price for like
being smart
we'll see you still have a chance don't
give up do i
you could still outsmart me somehow i'm
sure i'll slip up
no i don't see it i don't see it
[Music]
[Laughter]
copyright strike incoming no it's a
phone alarm it's fine
oh my god oh no
is this is this still winnable for me
promotion
no
don't do it ame no
no oh wait oh it's my move oh
and
i don't see how i can turn this around
i don't because if i go here you kill me
with the pawn if i go here
you can leave the tower and then you
also check
checking on my king
[Music]
what do i do
i shall retreat and hope for something
good to happen
please give me a miracle no no
no no no no no no no no
no no bad
detective bad detective no none
no no no no i'm in
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
[Laughter]
do you have a plan uh
[Music]
i'm thinking of one
please scott
oh my god jump scare dog
oh no
[Laughter]
ah
i do not want to give up i don't know no
no no no no no
i will not accept my defeat i will fight
until the bitter end if you take my
horse
and i'm only a lonely king left
that's okay i shall i shall take that
destiny
and i will fight like a real king on the
[Laughter]
battlefield
no no no
[Laughter]
am i losing viewers because of this
endless chess game
no thank god you guys are into this
aren't you
you guys love lots yeah they love long
intense
things what uh okay
i am i am top fried i'm top right i'm
top right i'm top right i'm top right
i'm top right i'm top right
i wish i i didn't i didn't want to say
it that way i did not want to say it
that way
i don't know i don't know what i said oh
my god
make it stop i mean just kill me now
just kill me now
okay give up then no
never i'm never gonna give you up
[Laughter]
check no
god i'm double checked now you're double
checking me
no your trip oh if i moved on your trip
oh no
no no no no no no
oh no no this is just me escaping from
reality
oh no
no
[Laughter]
oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god
oh my god no no no no
no no no no
it's not it's not a checkmate because
she could have killed me with her king
if i went forward
is true she could have killed my queen
no no no
no no no couldn't have
is this oh well is this how it ends
wait you have to make a sacrifice
oh can i play something
damn it but i was gonna check you too
there
nah i wait i waited of course i well
i can still win
i can still win i can still win
in some different timeline i can still
wait
[Music]
no no no
no no
no no no no no stop it no no
oh
huh
i might as well save this one
yeah no no no no
no no no no no no
don't do this to me i thought we were
friends
there are no friends in chess
[Music]
just gonna keep running huh
i'll run a little faster okay
[Laughter]
i'll let you live this time oh
for what you just want another promotion
don't you
huh huh
goddammit god
no please no
i love the office have you seen the
office
yeah i've seen all the episodes
best serious
however i have no not learned anything
about chess in that series that is a bit
unfortunate
stop selling kiara
i will retreat in my fortress
and wait for my death to come okay
now no
check
come on
[Music]
i'll let you get away this time
well you're not that's not really
helping me because every next move
literally you can take me here you can
take me here you can take me here
not that one god that one
[Music]
check no i'm in
come on out there
[Laughter]
oh man have mercy with me queen honor
queen amen have mercy
going back home yeah
am i please
see i i could i could i could not even
surrender myself because i would it
doesn't allow me to surrender
yeah if we were like uh in real life
chess
i think uh you probably messed up a lot
more i would have messed up
yeah yeah
[Laughter]
that's your third promotion that's your
favorite promotion alma haven't you got
promoted enough already
no i crave more power
check oh my god
the game um because of the way it works
it's like it's hard to
because she can't put herself in a
position of danger but like
it's hard for me to to line up multiple
ways to kill you
without you messing yourself up
you know what i mean yeah
check uh
well current player must defend the king
and what am i supposed to do as long as
the game does not want me to quit and
give up
check i will i will also
wouldn't it be a miracle if i would win
this
no it's not possible yeah
she can't she can't move into like a
move so like i feel like
we're stuck here how am i supposed to
make
how am i supposed to make any moves hmm
where i kill her if pretty much i have
to wait for her to set it up for herself
i guess i just have to get checkmate
yeah
and that only a smart detective can do
anyway in the next round i'll take one
of your one of your
boys
the child is asking to end their
suffering
but no we will suffer together until the
bitter end
oh yeah i guess you can have my horse
thank you
you're welcome i can't
i cannot oh
give it to me how do we end this
if i can't okay she's not putting
herself in danger so i don't know
i will um i will not just check
what i will not do is just end the game
without letting it end properly
it must find its end on its own
check i can't just check me it doesn't
let me
[Music]
i can't move two pieces at once
i'm coming for your king now you can
check
i don't know i don't think so i'm coming
for your king now
better be careful better watch out
okay
but you can't even move there see i
would have killed her
i'm coming for you
uh
oh damn it
okay i think this is um
24 hours later
just die no all right chad i'm going to
ask chad for help how do i
check meet her hey i'm also going to ask
a chat how am i going to survive this
how can i win this check
force her move
[Music]
help me too you can't kiara
oh come on then then why does the game
not like tell me that this is a draw
as long as the game doesn't tell us it's
a draw there must still be a way
you can't get close to my kingdom
because it's because it's your move
yeah you're always the the next one like
if i get close
like right next to a king then you would
have to move the king by yourself how
about you do that
how about you move your king for once
huh
stop relying on your queen always on
your fake
queen
[Laughter]
i married a commoner so what
i hate this no actually i love it i
actually love this
endless chess game with the detective
well how do i how do i check vader
help am i not checkmated
no no yeah you're cornering me now are
you happy
are you happy it's not like i got a
choice
i don't even have a choice well now
we'll just be jumping between two fields
huh
no why is the chad not helping me why is
the child only helping others
your lost cause kia
[Laughter]
i don't want to accept that
oh come on
i know i checked baby
you're saying to move my king but i feel
like that's a bad idea yes move your
king
i mean i don't think you can do anything
anyways with it
let's see well maybe not
[Music]
yeah that doesn't that didn't help me
are we just both looking at the chat now
i'm i'm concentrating
check uh
no
[Music]
i can only go back i can only go back
i can only go back in this direction
no no no no no no no no no no
no this is the end of me
no i have no choice well i'm going
forward again how do i check my neck
[Music]
i will still turn this around just just
watch me
what do you mean go to the end they mean
to go to
bring me to the corner but i move
forward again that's why because i'm
smart
we should have never started a chess
game oh
no nice try
[Laughter]
i thought you like quick desk
no no
[Music]
if you can survive 50 moves without
checkmate it's a draw
i might restrict her squares and you
easily win
well it wouldn't be a win oh yeah yeah
yeah
oh god damn it no yeah
i think uh it's over yeah
i want to
ah
check me
[Music]
well but still overall i'm leading my
dear friend watson
that's true that is true and
and i must say this this chess game you
might have won but
i didn't really see many pro gamer moves
from you
well you see early on i made a lot of
sacrifices because i knew
like i remained calm the whole time you
know how you killed a lot of mine early
on
um because i knew that eventually you'd
put yourself in a spot that i could take
advantage of you because i was baiting
you with all my pieces
now i mean here's the thing it's either
you
accept that you generally lost today
and because i it's three versus two or
you play one last quick game with
me we can play one more game but that
could lead to a draw
so yeah i mean for you it's a win-win
it's either a win or a draw
yeah okay what's a quick one what's a
quick one
there's the there's a matching card one
matching
with the magnifying glass
yeah that's pretty fast okay okay that's
fair that's fair
let's do this pretty much luck luck and
memorization
speed can we play matches shut up
[Laughter]
and do we want to change the rules after
match flip again
type of match two cards okay yeah
standard rules flip again
the last one i'm in this will prove who
is
bottom right and who is bottom left uh
okay although i guess this doesn't
really have to do anything with
intelligence
yeah well sort of it's memorization
well i'm not very good with memorization
maybe it'll be different for this game
what is this even called i don't even
know what the cards are called
oh nine diamonds nine diamonds
four dollars it doesn't matter what um
type it is by the way it could be four
like uh what are those called again
it could be two hearts or uh spades you
know what i mean
as long as a number matches essentially
okay
seven hearts um
god i it doesn't i already forgot what
the first ones were
did the only the numbers have to match
yeah
oh my god yeah i already forgot
everything that we opened
[Music]
thank you for the super chat
[Laughter]
did you see a five
oh shoot i forgot which ah no i did not
see a five
did you see a four uh
[Music]
i never saw a six before god damn it
no no no no
[Music]
wait i forgot where the eight was it was
somewhere here
don't look at the chat i'm not looking
god damn it goddammit no
i'm it i don't remember oh
wait hmm
listen to me listen to me this is either
a win for me or a draw for you
don't we want to make one person happy
here tonight
thank you for not losing
oh wow you won this time
hey you got some cards nice stack of
pile you got there
i wonder whose is bigger though
[Music]
you broke me you broke me
well it's a draw so
yeah yeah it's a draw it's a draw so we
are both officially
now bottom middle
[Laughter]
father little
thank you amelia you helped me promote
myself
you also look a little bit demoted
yourself
uh i'm not sure if that's how it works
but
this is how it works i mean at least
we're equal
it's free everything's free yup unless
you ever challenge me again
we will forever be be by the middle
okay okay okay and i'm happy actually
because i like being close to you
you smell very good
oh thank you thank you you smell like
fried chicken
yeah that's i i actually have some in my
pocket
oh that's why well uh thank you everyone
for suffering together with us it was
much longer than uh we expected it to be
yeah the chess game yeah went on pretty
long but i hope you guys still
enjoyed it and sorry for the travels at
the beginning but everything was fine
after all and then now we finally
are equals i think this is a good ending
very good ending to a lot of
suffering yeah we tied up pretty good oh
well thank you amelia for uh challenging
me tonight and playing with me i had
lots of fun
and hopefully yeah in the future again
maybe no chess but maybe more other
things
yeah i'll play i'll play more and thank
you for
inviting me just call up thank y'all
anything you want to say like about your
own streams or so
um i might honestly stream later but i
might push it back because i still have
to sleep because i haven't
actually slept since the last time i eh
i thought you went to bed i slept for
two hours oh god oh man
take a little bit i'm gonna take care of
yourself for real oh my god
wow but then before that i slept for
four hours and then before that i slept
for six hours and if you already lack so
much sleep then you probably
shouldn't be playing minecraft and
you're off stream time
i'll do what i want i like that that uh
silence for a moment there
all right i'll let you sleep now i hope
you have some sweet dreams and i'll see
everyone tomorrow on my
uh streams as well so good night
everyone e
and in german we say do you know what we
say in german
ah is it type what
no we say auf wiedersehen alfredo
alvida
[Music]
bye
foreign
[Music]