[Music]
thank you
oops
[Music]
oh I know I know I know
hello
[Music]
let's go
foreign
[Music]
oh my God yes
Tesla bread has been released and I
think some of you guys are already
playing it
uh I had to wait
for this stream
uh unfortunately but I finally get to
play it too yeah finally I mean it
hasn't been that long since it has been
released but you know the excitement to
uh finally play another one is too big
did you enjoy your nap book so I took a
nap before the Stream
and in order to make time go by faster
and I was tired too so I took a nap but
you know I dreamed that uh like my my uh
Gmail account got hacked
and um
that I missed this stream that I was
late to this stream it was already like
time was going by it was like half an
hour late 40 minutes late one hour late
and I was panicking and my manager tried
to contact me but I couldn't reply to
her I couldn't tell anyone was going on
I I was freaking out it was the freaking
nightmare being being hacked oh my God
and I woke up and I was like oh my God
oh thank God I'm not hacked and I'm not
late to my tails of a rice stream oh my
God
that is that is a nightmare being late
to this stream would have been such a
nightmare I'm safe thank God
I would have I would have oh my I don't
oh my God imagine that being true oh my
God
worst dream ever
oh yeah big big big anxiety
anyway so thankfully that didn't happen
uh I will play the game for you today uh
before we do that we have a little more
things to announce as per usual as I
wrote in the pinned comment
um until now this is the fifth tales of
the rise stream that I'm doing as the
official categorized ambassador to the
English region this is the fifth one and
the last one
that I'm doing as an ambassador I will
still play Days of our eyes after this
stream uh I will I will stream it I will
continue streaming it
uh however let me just say here I will
not be able to stream it until the end I
think I think
that according to the
streaming laws of sales over rise there
is like a certain point in the late game
uh that I am not
supposed to show because big big
spoilers coming up I think but that is
in the late game so we'll still be
playing it for a long time I think yeah
so and
I
have some special things to show though
uh but I I I was very surprised so
um
[Music]
the tales of the rice team has prepared
some things for me so I am I am to let
you know that number one
uh how do I say this the tales of the
rise team
um is is gifting me a surprise gift for
my quote-unquote tireless efforts as the
tales of the rise ambassador to the
English region tireless efforts oh
wow
exclusive Master Core replica this is
something that's like in the game you
know
uh
apparently apparently
only I am getting this or maybe like
maybe some other special people like
voice actors from the gamer so I don't
know but apparently
I'm I'm at least one of the very very
very few people who are getting this
apparently
so they sent me a video for this too
shall we take a look at it
[Music]
stop this one and let me hear that down
monster core video this one now I should
be able to hear it and you guys too
oh
I'm watching this for the first time
[Music]
whoa any astral energy collected passes
through a spirit vessel on its way to
being stored in a Master Core
a mastercore huh is that what it's
called The Jewel in her chest so you see
the master cores of the receptacles in
which the Lords store their power
without me to adjust the flow of Astral
energy the sword can't take a physical
form a sword Sears the hand of he who
wields it
healing are to meant
a man numbed to pain and a woman whose
very touch deals nothing but
[Music]
hey that's so cool
thank you thank you thank you I'm
looking forward to putting that on my on
myself I don't have much decoration in
my apartment yet to put on my shelves
and stuff so I'm excited to put that on
there yo prank the core
that's so cool I think like once we play
the game we'll get a much more deeper
connection to this master course so
looking forward to that but that is not
all that is not all uh next up
so this is not going to be on sale this
is uh given out to
specific people
and I am one of them there's just guys
there's a freaking chess an exclusive
acrylic chess set an exclusive Shaker
keychain what happens when you shake
them does it change color or what I'm
I'm curious but oh I'm excited to play
chess on that and there's like uh let me
let me make this a big bit bigger
shut down I don't know if you can see it
but like the right side uh figures are
like in the pixel style super adorable
and so many Hoots over at The Hoots are
there
um The Hoots the hoodles are
the the pawns
oh those are the most adorable ponds
that I have ever seen in my whole
millions of lives and re reborn mints
[Music]
Army couldn't bring me down that's
actually is that seven
seven no that's eight
yeah yeah
unboxing video perhaps mmm we could
actually do that maybe I'll do that and
then I'll play a little bit of Chess
against myself thank you
this is cool I'm gonna put the chess set
also on my shelf I think and the
keychains oh my God I'm gonna put them
on my bags
no but that is not all and the next
thing is is is is is is
also insanely cool
are you ready are you ready well I
needed to put on music as well by the
way here there you go are you ready
commemorating the leadership
me
from our friends at the alphys
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh that quote-unquote these are gifts to
commemorate your my successful
ambassadorship for Tales of arise and
that they are sending hoodies for
Halloween talents and staff even
whoa look shall we look at that closer
because it's a somewhat small pattern uh
only one second let me look at that it
looks so comfy look look at that that is
cute
[Laughter]
so cute you can turn it around and then
and it doesn't like it looks great on
both sides yo I'm getting that
and there's there's Hooters with uh
mustaches
mustache noodle
sick trip man
yo they look they look really comfy and
high quality
well I'm excited to wear them throughout
the the Autumn and the winter is they
look really cozy
I can't believe it says commemorating
the leadership of takanasikara so I I
think this means
this is super super exclusive
[Music]
hmm
that's me the moment I saw my name and I
was like what
thing I wanted to mention is um we are
playing with PS4 because well uh uh I
was kindly gifted and sent a PS5 uh by
Bandai Namco us thank you so much
however it has it has arrived but it's
stuck in the customs and we've been
trying to you know get them to send it
to me but they're being a little bit
complicated
so yeah oh yeah by the way the stream is
sponsored by Bandai Namco you guys
and forgot to say that if it's not
already obvious but yes
um
and before before we get started one
last thing uh
disclaimer potential spoilers during the
gameplay
throughout the whole game
so uh I know a lot of you guys are like
yo I want to play the game too
spoil me but I want to watch The Stream
So what I recommend is that well we're
not gonna play too far ahead today so
you just watch the chicken with me and
in the next few days you play ahead of
me and then once I stream tails the
Horizon again you're gonna be ahead of
me and be able to watch My Stream easy
easy
then shall we get started
[Music]
let's go oh my God I'm so excited I'm
sorry I'm nervous I'm nervous I'm
nervous I'm nervous to play the game
it's it's been what five years or so
since the last one but it's there bears
area
you can get it on PS4 PS5 uh PC uh Xbox
as well so you you'll go get it on your
favorite platform I'm playing again and
PS4 but I will be switching to or I try
I will try to switch to PS5 as soon as I
get it the PS5 okay stop okay okay okay
I think now we are ready to go
oh my God I'm planning ah
oops I'm planning to pray and like
um two hours today
uh not too too much but in the following
streams it will be like my usual jrpg
streams where I stream like for five to
eight hours understand what is it with
this still oh there you go okay
okay okay
[Music]
I'm nervous
why am I nervous I'm just like I can't
believe finally finally another tale's
laugh game is out there yes let me turn
on the music and
well we'll be playing in the English
voice dubbing today and in the future we
might switch to Japanese and we might
like switch back to English
and all that let's go
ahead difficulty normally yes
yes okay for now I think all of this is
probably fine
um
totally agree yes yes okay
save it again and
oh
my God
ages long past it was believed was
indestructible and everlasting
Rena on the other hand was supposed to
be the domain of the Gods a paradise
where the souls of The Departed could
rest forevermore
oh how wrong we were
vibrating
[Music]
it's soldiers huge shining armor armor
reminds me of kitada's armor known as
zugos
and Bounty of Dana all but disappeared
overnight oh my God right now give us a
freaking break 300 years ago a long time
ago
rule
and its new Masters split the land into
five distinct Realms
there's a Birdland
orbis calaglia
okay you mean
that's calyland I don't know what is
Brooklyn that's a tyrant ball sound
sounds
dude I saw you today in a trailer that
they put up on Twitter I was like who
are you fire scorches this Barren
Wasteland
dust storms course over the rocks and
clouds and your relief is to be found
from the oppressive heat I love this
intro
the Denon people toyless slaves day
after day holy under the ruthless
oppression of the renin soldiers
[Music]
death anyway no that's so sad family in
death is there Agony finally brought to
it but that's still fitting for Calliope
land though
death is the only option what it means
to be free
so complete is the renin's domination
[Music]
they definitely asserted dominance
they did they did
whoa
oh
are you our boy now
[Music]
whoa
are you okay
she not okay
she is
struggling
that's that's Serena
so there's two planets run on Dana
oh dear
put them back into it embedded
how can you expect him to be able to
push that
oh often elephant
open Iron Mask our friends
why you
let me
huh what is this some kind of slave
support group mind your own business you
work with my third Squad time to regroup
go on get moving
[Music]
ah
hey wait for me little boy
mama boy are you okay nothing's gonna be
like Iron Mask because Idol that's okay
cool cool no I'm fine
I know each other I'll ask you you're
bleeding
we need to get you looked at by doc that
bad huh is he wearing an Iron Mask
he only does it in the beginning I think
didn't see him wearing it later on
cool it was funny because in German
that's a cabbage or something like that
okay your next destination is microphone
star symbol the number of distance isn't
the destination
ah over there okay oh can I only walk
right now oh slow oh are you okay buddy
let's see um
[Music]
sport okay I gotta go straight to the
school okay hello
I'm so sorry Iron Mask you got hurt
because of me don't Don't sweaty cage
it's not like I felt anything but that's
why doc tells it to be extra careful
doesn't he yeah but at the end of the
day I chose to stick my neck out for you
and I don't regret a thing so don't
sweat it cold okay okay thanks Iron Man
okay I gotta go to the dog I guess
I like what he sees
what what is it are you armed you got a
big big slash Slice on your arm you do
are you dark
hello
hello help me
ah you again it's me sorry to trouble
you darker
look after yourself and there'd be no
need for stories would there now sit
okay
so still unable to remember anything I
take it blank as always
nothing but that strange dream oh no
face no memories unable to feel pain yet
only too eager to take on everybody
else's
protecting his curse of having no
memories
you may not be able to feel pain but
that doesn't mean you can't be wounded
just like everyone else important yeah
more careful you'll wind up dead without
even realizing it one of these days I
watched another slave die today
corpses then I care to count
unfortunately that's hardly a rare sight
around these parts danans are always
dying and the retins just watch
eventually they're gonna be no more
damage yo let's continue why doesn't
anyone stand and fight cause they all
weak as hell
got no food
got no comfy band will you
we have to fight
them we have to
if only it was so simple
there have certainly been uprisings all
right three centuries worth of the damn
things
as for all the good they've done take a
look around and judge for yourself
nothing nothing I should just about do
it now do me a favor and try to stay out
of trouble so the wound doesn't open
again doc back when I knew nothing you
were the one who taught me just how
things work around here
you know I'll always be grateful for
that but I can't just race as one by the
calm and the steady you're still young
you have time
wait for the right moment both for
yourself and the world
work will be wrapping up for the day
soon enough don't sit around here go out
and feel the breeze against your skin
even a slave's entitled to that breathe
then that breathe from the fire all
around profile right the air over there
is probably really bad enough
all right
all right oh
guess I'll go back to my room I have a
broom okay hey cool what's up are you
okay thanks for saving me oh yeah I am
fine I think
okay I think oh hello side quest
huh the brat eye stick these weird
Stones oh no ah the hand on the hand on
our bodies and then work us to the Bone
until we did and as if the routine
beatings from them weren't enough when
they're in a really bad mood they like
to stick their zugals on us
oh slave just like everyone else here
oh hello big man come on I don't have a
spirit core oh yeah I don't have that
thing on my hand everyone else does for
that matter yeah why not
what are you looking at you're looking
to get your ass cake too oh no thank you
you can they're not moving
I think that person might be dead ah
navigation map in the upper right corner
of the screen shows information about
your surroundings press
Where to view the full map okay aha
oh
am I going there no I'm going that way
right now life of a slave
whoa activity records this way you can
check your main story and subquest
progress it also lets you view the
rewards you get from finishing subquest
sub quiz
Dynam people have been enslaved at the
hands of the renings among them as Iron
Mask a man with no face no memories nor
even a sense of pain who spends his days
protecting his fellow slaves from the
Wrath of the renins and occasionally
being saved from himself amidst an
endless cycle of forced labor in the
kalalian heat okay
gosh let's move on let's get going
oh out here this is what they talked
about
when you uh resist too much I suppose
they're gonna send their dogs
to you
to take care of you I should get some oh
we actually do have like houses
something like that
all right rest let's go
I wonder how many people stone is a
pillow mine for now but for how long
[Music]
another day
shall I that's very comfortable
[Laughter]
there's gravel underneath that the
blanket that would probably be better
no fight
yeah I better head to work
go to work okay so I've got business
with freight train today
to decorate business of the freight
train train
time to start another day toiling away
for the Rams yes let's go do this until
the day I die
um no
we're gonna take care of that don't
worry okay
okay what are we gonna do here we're
gonna Escape through the train how about
that look Lively slaves let's see some
work around here
did I take off my mask no oh that was
someone else with silver hair
oh
five five people
ah okay but they do have some anime
oh
God
look at that
there's a plant attack
dudes what was his name again
look
oh
she's here
hello you are you alive
can you really break change that easily
I'll remember that
what the hell
chill
Can't Touch This
[Music]
don't let her Escape you came here for a
reason right
[Music]
what is that a wall
leap of faith
well we lost her I mean that wasn't
that was not often chasing her but still
ah
did you find anything
not yet sir
what do they expect from us on such
short notice
hey you're
over there
go now hurry get moving but they're
gonna find you
oh still you caused us a lot of trouble
you know now we can do this she's so
pretty or not
now we're gonna do it's a difficult ways
[Music]
with her
it's you
oh my God
[Music]
you gotta do some work too
come on
[Music]
where did you learn to fight Alvin
oh those stunts what
okay bye bye bye bye oh that was close
with those oh dear
oh we got some help
to the rescue
the close-up just to the mask
take off that damn mask man
you probably can't tell Canyon
but
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
wow
is continuing
sick oh is that the dude you missed your
chance to become Lord
which means you lot live and die for me
the Mighty ball sass
y through your skulls now hurry up and
bring me Shields he knows her name
famous
is she from her life even the drinks
lost its appeal
someone's in a
yeah
Lord of wolves a ruler of orbis kalaglia
but its wild beast you prefer isn't it
do forgive me
gannabelt valkyrus what do you want
from what I hear you seem to be having
some trouble over there in calacular
whether I could be of any assistance to
you enough with the false pretense I can
tell a rat when it's sniffing around
forgive me I can only imagine the
emotion the most distressing sorry I
think I pushed a button
shut up it's none of your concern
the crown contest is preceding a pace
and so quickly let's hear a little bit
before the
Throne is the news correctly forward to
it and you can be sure I won't forget
our little chat
what a huge oh oh dear oh it looks
pretty oh what's happening
[Applause]
how did he do that
what
was did he do it out with his with his
thumb
yes is this me Alvin who is you
is this my memories from the past
guys if you want to get the gaming due
to the heaven yeah it's in the
description use the link it's a referral
link for you with my name I'm the
medical officer for the Crimson crows
hello you're in one of our safe houses
thank you Crimson Cross I've heard of
that
don't tell me you've never heard of us
we're the resistance
yes we get in the way of the bright eyes
best laid plans
[Music]
the Denon resistance
I didn't know such a thing existed
oh we exist all right though I guess
we're not as famous as I thought we were
she's cute seems like I know more about
you than the other way around Mr Iron
Mask
oh is it true you can't take that thing
off
let's give it a try
worse is that I don't even know why I'm
wearing it oh dear
why are you in his woman I was with I
holes oh yeah she's quite the character
isn't she
is the main character in The Slammer as
we speak you locked her up what why go
take a look for yourself if you're so
interested
how are we gonna see that cutscene from
that we saw before with her being
chained up again they're interrogating
her this is what the hell is going on
yeah what is going on
if you want to know something I'll tell
you what I can
oh you ask something well we know this
we noticed we kind of know this
um but let's ask about stuff here he's
it's the Crimson crows leader he's not
just physically strong he's got real
smart and he's indispensable to us if
you want to know something I'll tell you
what I can
okay ah who are you fine
I'm fighting who else the red is rolling
over calaglia the ones that came down
from Lennox have been giving us hell for
the last three centuries of course we
can't even reach neighboring towns much
less living is so our current Target is
the red ends in kalaglia and their lord
Balsa ah we gotta take him down first if
you want to know something I'll tell you
what I can okay no it's okay I'm good
I'm good I'm good I need to go and find
out for myself yes I will
oh it's very close it's over there
why did you take my woman
so it wasn't a lie the slightest touch
is like being struck by lightning what
are you doing so you're finally awake
huh what's going on here what is she
ever mind your business
this is my business
you'll see
so even if you don't mean to hurt
somebody if they touch you they get
electrocuted huh
it doesn't seem to be poison or magic
it's got nothing soldiers were after you
she's so pretty the last several days
balsa's forces have been getting pretty
restless
when we looked into it deeper the word
thorns came up over and over again
and now we come across Miss prickly
herself
drop the attitude did you really think
we wouldn't find out anything about you
Miss Shion imaris I meant
what's her name
wait is this the first time I hear her
laughed out already
yeah I feel like this this lady's got
herself a surname which means one thing
she's a Remnant our enemy yeah but she
was being chased by running soldiers so
then why that's exactly that ends up no
it's your name
after all aside from the clothes they
wear there's only one way to tell a
Dannon from a Remnant and that's whether
their eyes light up or not ah oh hers
dude guys oh you're someone who can't
even use astral Arts embedded
well you ripped it off there is
there is couch to mouth the day we swore
to rise up against your kind
not to rest until every last
may not be capable of using asteroids
but it looks like those Thorns of yours
won't do you much good in escaping here
either
still inflicting pain on anyone who
comes near you that's one hell of an
ability
you're wrong oh
curse some kind of great ability
fair enough all I know is balssef must
have his eye on you for a damn good
reason and until we find out why
an ambush you're coming they must
attract us down evacuate his plan hurry
you're so happy bring the girl
she gives you any trouble wave a spear
in her face you got it hey Iron Mask
sorry but right now it's everyone for
themselves what about you I'm going to
welcome our guests don't go dying on me
and don't try anything funny
that's a very Rusty sword
can we get a proper one
adult sword okay escape from the mine
okay
secret items here
no
I shouldn't go this way but I am I I
want to
Applejack let's go
well it was worth it that was worth it
okay uh saving and loading oh please
blah blah blah to open the menu where
you can save and load your in-game
progress from the system section ah the
game will also along with your room data
and the story I automatically say thank
you wow handsome
[Music]
I have to find an exit and get the hell
out of here oh good job killing that
zugu
I'm getting the hell out of here you can
fight grab a weapon damn how did they
find out about this place have these
kinds of battles been going on this
entire time
just didn't know you didn't know
he knows nothing
stop right there
oh it's just a Denon yes you there
where's the running girl who was here
I don't know well I
spit it out I want an answer insurgent
ask this for an answer
[Music]
Ed soldier that way so I'll show you
infinity
give me that sword give me that sword
okay fighting tutorial basic comma
controls press R1 to perform a normal
attack
R1 debt one yeah at first you can swing
up to three normal attacks together but
by learning certain skills this limit
can be increased characters can also
attack in mid-air after jumping
Arts aren't so special actions performed
by spending part of your AG art Scotch
press Triangle Square or X to use the
arc assigned to each button while AG
will gradually restore automatically it
will restore more slowly when attacking
push out and press R2 to evade an enemy
attack if you time it well as an enemy
attack is approaching you'll perform a
perfect evasion allowing you to avoid
taking any damage yes yeah the PGM is so
good isn't it I can listen to that for
ages ah
Go violin
die so much for playing nice
do I already have eyes I do
real fight spirit I have to do this
[Music]
and he did
smooth
oh wait oh I'm fine
wait that was automatically uh pushing X
the whole time but it's our one I run
perhaps it's about this no matter what
it's a bit unusual but I got used to it
in the demo as well easily
I know my my
instincts made me push X
constantly
Apple gel Apple gel
it's always worth to looking in the
corners guys
no I I think I think I'll go with it I
don't think I want to remap it I think
it's fine oh you want to find let's go
okay I won I won
oh he wants what are you doing
[Music]
are you a magician
attack you
nice
[Music]
okay
push out push L as you hold L one wait
let me to change your current Target
I think I did
hahaha
oh
last second this way he could finish his
charge or whatever he was doing sharp
thing for fun finding is so much fun in
this game
[Music]
she got her gun
that's a long name I'm hereby detain you
in the name of his Excellency Lord Balsa
that ain't happening
and then she's like oh he doesn't kill
let's wish those are armored soldiers
here shut up and get out of here while
you still can there's a side slave these
are running affairs
hey we've got a better chance
I don't much feel like being incredible
fine suit yourself oh my God
[Music]
actions strung together with no gaps
normal attacks have a set limit while
Arts can continue until a g Runs Out
normal attacks count separately on the
ground and in the air using an art to go
between them can thus extend the combo
did that make sense
diminishing returns and combos during a
combo with the same art is used multiple
times within four actions its
penetration will decrease and enemies
will cover from it sooner
continually doing so will raise their
penalties making arts half as effective
as at their harshest
okay so just don't spam the same attack
is what you're saying
easy
[Music]
don't expect any promises
finish
this
combo
Rising Phoenix
why did you help me oh skip
skip guys and Dan and like you possibly
gain from helping a renin like me I
don't know I have time trust me too much
time
guess I'm just not as consumed with
hatred as some hmm
what
have we met somewhere before oh man are
we friends with a Dannon can't say I've
had the pleasure well she really doesn't
like Dennis even though we're helping
him yeah silly question
I don't remember anything about my past
I don't have any clues to go on either
not even my own face let me get this
straight you don't know what you look
like but you thought I might somehow
recognize you
well God
it's my helping you back there wasn't a
self-sacrificing as I made it out to be
besides I can't feel pain anyway so it's
not like
wait you really can't feel pain
yeah yeah
it's just another thing I don't have
pain no face no memories damn boy you
know one thing about myself
that's that I'm a slave what about your
name you must have one oh did you know
your outfit Iron Mask no your outfit the
name from the person who found me said
that this way I wouldn't forget I had a
real name out there somewhere oh
see
so where to next
silly what do you
think are we in a team now
stay sharp we're going in we are
okay okay okay items any items no no
wait I'm supposed to go this way
yeah subscribe oh hello uh I'm I'm I'm
not escaping together not at all glad to
see you made it I heard you managed to
escape
but I didn't expect to see Old Iron Mask
with you in any case we're all wanted by
the remnants it'll be easier for
everyone if you both just come with me
um okay
where are the others
they're waiting for us up ahead come on
oh no problem
stay where you are dissidents
badly
yeah
apprehend the traitor
the lord of the rest
[Music]
you missed
oh
they should sell a mask look that is
merchandise
[Music]
stop the fire today
chip shop
blazing
y'all I don't know how you put that in
there though
good question
the mastercore he was embedded within
her all along no matter kill her if you
have to just retrieve the core
they wanted to pull
[Applause]
we got a better sword now
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
why was that glowing though
oh
whoa
spy extreme successfully
yeah that's really cool
what the hell happened oh his arms
your arms
oh yeah she's like oh whatever yes it's
just as well actually come on dude
you're not an Agony she's like ah no
problem
hold still oh anyway oh she can heal oh
yeah right she got Healing Arts
what a perfect couple
I stand
it's one of my Healing Arts
I like her facial expressions here's the
hand of he who wields it and a Healing
Art to mend hmm a man numb to pain and a
woman who's very touch deals nothing but
I stand
thank you
ah
all right let's route the bastards and
finish them off before the surviving
stragglers have a chance to regroup
Iron Mask you're coming yeah of course
I'm not about to go back all that way
alone
so I guess you're not planning on
releasing me huh sorry
you're coming with us
in that case there's one thing you
should know no one uses that flaming
Sword without my say-so well you need to
worry on that score I doubt many of us
could get close to it in the first place
or would want to
interesting
[Laughter]
she does seem safe a Blazing Sword
this might be strong enough to match the
power of a lord no maybe even to surpass
it yes are you sure you're okay
what do you mean
you're wound that Soldier nailed you
pretty good not to mention those Flames
bursting from you
they only hit my Master Core so I'll be
fine and the Flames weren't even hot you
were probably because they're just
screaming and crying
honestly I'm more surprised that you
really are incapable of feeling pain
you think I was faking
no I believed you
I guess seeing you stay calm while
bearing those Burns to your hands just
really made it hit home I like her
English voice that's ironic
I have no problem hurting anyone who
touches me it's calm and as soon as I
try to wield that sword it's me who gets
hurt
do you wish you were impervious to pain
too
he realized you could burn your fingers
off without even noticing right
so what all I need right now is power
went up until now I haven't come across
anything stronger than that Blazing
Sword the whole time I've been doing
this
you really don't care what happens to
you as long as you get what you're after
do you
don't talk like you know me
oh yeah
you be nice to each other you're right I
don't get
quick to throw it all away
not when us slaves have never had a
choice in whether we lived or died
oh
it's fighting style she unspecializes in
gun based long-range strikes and astral
Arts use her to hit enemies from a safe
distance and to use healing Heights on
allies of low HP Healing Arts costs CP
to use for my UCP total
when auto mode is enabled student will
primarily Target flying an astral art
wielding enemies as well as both with
lower HP during combat now the hotel
kill points Heights with healing and
support effects consume cure points in
addition to AG CP is shared across the
party and can be restored with items or
by staying at an in or Campground oh
yeah that's that thing you can uh as far
as I know you can heal yourself after a
battle in the in the normal menu with CP
it can be raised by leveling up or
finding specific items not a hotel okay
uh get away from the mine okay so
so that way right
yeah
bright eyes when I use Israel astronauts
their eyes give off a fan light the
atoms have come to ah
Coco sand in those ravine
whoa I want to look at the scenery whoa
there was a skit No I missed it maybe I
can still look at it
wow
wow oh
I hope he land
of Brimstone and swirling Ash orbers
kalalia
here we are
no one following us
Granite Castle oh stronghold are you
seen there self-imposed ruler of all
calaglia
I've never seen it from this close
before
that's it all right wow
wow long look while you still can't
that's quite some Castle tear down
the only thing standing between us and
freedom
wow I
left let's go
damn
skit
good time for you guys don't worry you
can see out of that thing like at all
good question of course I can how else
do you think I managed to avoid I'm
wearing the holes where are the holes
what is that thing anyway
it doesn't look like anything Dan and
I've ever seen
it's me I don't remember anything about
my past when I came to I was already
wearing it oh
if I could get it off I would
damn thing makes it hard to eat I can't
scratch myself wait how do you eat it's
the worst honestly I'm just impressed
you've managed to survive this long
looking like uh-huh I'm sure you attract
attention wherever you go
most of the other dannins don't pay it
any mind
it's in everyone's best interest to just
keep their heads down and focus on their
work and pretend they don't notice what
about the renin soldiers such a weirdo
the guards they're more the kill first
ask questions later type
be in the wrong place or step out of
line and you're dead ask her no mask
that's sad as long as you keep your head
down and don't cause trouble they mostly
ignore you
honestly sometimes they don't look all
that Keen to stir up trouble themselves
a friend of mine said it's because if
they kill us without a good reason you
could delay the work and put them behind
schedule Oh at that point it'd be their
necks on the line okay you should know
more about all that than me though right
I don't serve any of the Lords
look at her hands movement after three
centuries of run and Rule without much
upheaval it's possible the soldiers
might be losing their Edge I
might be the first excitement they've
had in a while
well I don't plan on getting killed for
their amusement
for people
skate that's off games
thing since the beginning but skits used
to be uh used to look very different but
um this way they're like way more
detailed
and I want to look at something by the
way am I able to
wait a second outfits
bunny ears okay do I have my
oh was that not didn't I where's my DLC
where do I get that did I not you have
to claim
that's later on gotta download oh I I
did I think I did
okay well I'll get it ready for next
time then understood oh
[Music]
literally everything oh my God girl
can I has
[Music]
oh minimalism
is this all mine
[Music]
acquiring data
looks like it's for the take for taking
on noise ah okay
but wait okay I'm not looking into that
right now
we fine we're fine uh is anything else I
want to look at all right so art screen
I screen you can assign ice that you've
learned to each of the different buttons
you can set free Arts to use while on
the ground plus an additional free to
use in the air for a total of six secret
portable Arts and press L2 R2 to inspect
the Arts you have available
characters are set up set to Auto can
use all of the Arts but you can press
square to uncheck Arts you wish for them
to avoid aha oh you can do that too
oh okay so
we only have these uh free skills right
now
so that's okay
cute okay
nah anyway let's continue oh
attack
oh look how cute they are chilling there
changing controls during combat during
comic press options following the menu
to change your character's control mode
semi-auto automatically moves until an
attack range manual full control and
other fights based on set strategy
Sammy Automotive is designed for players
who only wish to casually dabble in
combat meanwhile manual mode is for
those seeking full control while animal
lets the game take its brains okay
are they
yeah
wait wait oh my God
that's my HP right here
swallow bladder
indeed wait a second I realized
something uh
I should put me rash here you know
I know I can't that one is for jumping
only okay okay I think starting an
ending battles making contact with him
oh that was that went way too fast all
right
makes sense if we try to take them all
out there'll be no end in science looks
strong hear me complaining he tells me
to avoid all enemies I don't have to
fight
that that looks strong what should I do
easy really a live ball is great oh
thank God you found something good I did
was like that I got a core in the like a
part in the back that's his weak spot
let's try to fight him
don't get careless
[Music]
who said he easy
coin that chat said he easy
[Music]
[Laughter]
wrecked I I don't want to waste all my
don't get it
okay I'm gonna I'm gonna use one life
bottle but that's it okay if I die again
I'm gonna leave I'm out here
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah that ain't okay
wait he's almost dead though
oh
[Laughter]
she can't resurrect
Israel
where's it oh damn it
[Laughter]
[Music]
well okay then
okay
let's stop a moment to catch our breath
oh campfire time I barely worked up a
sweat oh really you just died two times
what do you want a medal
doesn't look like we're being followed
fail to grab these rare moments of quiet
when you can you'll end up regretting it
later
you're the boss
I'm the boss I'm Daniel
uh and once again
okay camping out resting at a campground
Willow story you'll find his HP and CP
while resting you can watch skits and
cutscenes as you've previously viewed
noise we should take turns standing
guard for this first time I'll watch
over things so you two can rest easy oh
thank you and we have a skit available
Zephyr why aren't you access
okay no that's not that but
really you said you wanted to fight so
that's a really good face
at this point that's all that matters
but he has been turned out you were a
renin his whole life I think frowning a
renin
so we know who you are we can't rule
anything out
besides we've already got Shion with us
at this point what's one more renin as
long as they're on our side yes yes so
you don't see every renin as an enemy no
our goal isn't to hunt down and kill all
remnants shouldn't put them all in one
box you know just as much as we need to
set ourselves free if you
if you let every denim agrees with what
we're doing either you can if you
believe it enemies among the canons
yeah
they're just not up for rebelling per se
the thing you have to remember is that
everyone has their own path
I'm not sure I understand
that's okay just focus on what we have
to do right now however the time will
come when you'll need to decide what to
do for yourself
really can I decide
oh there's another another one another
skit how come you don't have a scar on
your hand
scar what do you mean he didn't have the
stone to begin with as in Crows all tore
off their own Spirit course
but your hand doesn't show any signs of
ever having a core like theirs why not
I don't know
I don't remember anything about myself
from before doc found me
seriously you have that math you don't
feel any pain and you just happen to
know how to fight with a sword no way
you must trust them girl
I'm not lying if that's what you think
believe me I wish I knew who the hell I
am but I don't
it's funny how I didn't have any time
for soul searching while digging up
rocks okay okay chill sorry
are you saying you've told us everything
about yourself
[Music]
when you've got plenty to hide yourself
uh-huh
you
heard about my past too it's like a dad
and his children
you're a real man of mystery I'll admit
that said I'm not one to dig around in
someone's business just out of curiosity
if you remember something and feel like
sharing you're free to do so for now I
think that's good enough what her hand
movement I love it
yo he's a he's a very good man though
this is a fairy dude it's very decent
and now that's good yo so this whole you
not feeling pain thing is that for real
why would I lie about it why would you
care anyway
you know I can't imagine what it's like
that's all
it's advantages and disadvantages
oh
on the upside when Ren and soldiers push
me around I hardly Flinch the downsides
that I get injured without even noticing
which means I could be knocking on
death's door and not even realize it
knock knock knocking on death's door I
may be numb to pain but it doesn't make
me Immortal or anything just like me I
do like knocking on her door I noticed
any of this if someone hadn't pointed it
out to me well if not for my fellow
slaves I belong dead lying in a ditch
somewhere
um
okay we're done with this kid so let's
rest
and then continue
a Master Core huh
now I see so that's why balsa's cronies
were so desperate to catch her cronies
is that what it's called The Jewel in
her chest
oh right you don't remember a damn thing
do you
ah fair enough I guess it's time to fill
you back in
cronies
fill me in tell me huh you ever wonder
why we danons are made to work ourselves
to the Bone day in day out well when you
put it like that I always just assumed
we were mining resources for them
and don't you think it'd be quicker if
they used all that high-powered Tech
they have I guess so why go to all the
trouble of relying on weak humans
asserting dominance
listen I guess what the run-ins are
really after isn't resources or minerals
power
it's astral energy ah
listing the astral energy that sleeps
inside all matter in life forms
and they're doing it the same way they
have for the past 300 years using us
dannins as mere siphons
so those coins are those uh things have
machines for minerals
requires Spirit course are giving it any
astral energy collected passes through a
spirit vessel on its way to being stored
in a Master Core whoa
[Music]
oh they milk people magic go to the
trouble of collecting all this energy in
the first place do they really need all
that juice just to use astral Arts they
want to blow up though it determines the
sovereign
is that the running ruler
exactly five Lords each doing whatever
it takes to gather as much astral energy
as they can and store it in their Master
course ah whichever of them manages to
accumulate the most power at the end of
their contest has crowned the ruler of
the renin motherland
a new Crown contest as they call it is
held every decade or so
so you see the master cores are the
receptacles in which the Lords store
their power and we dannins are
sacrificed so the renins can choose
their new ruler that's insane you're
telling me that's what our people have
been dying for this whole time makes
sense you're not the only one who's bent
out of shape about the whole thing
there are two things that I haven't been
able to get my head around yet
what business would a renin have
stealing a master Corps and what's the
deal with that Blazing Sword
I think the sword is a physical
manifestation of the master core's
astral energy
as for why it took the shape of a sword
well I don't know any more than you yeah
because he wanted a sword and that not
that Rusty and that stuff creating your
permission to use it what was that about
I'm the only one of us who can control
the master core to some extent
without me to adjust the flow of Astral
energy the sword can't take a physical
form
what do you want out of this you may be
one of them but you don't strike me as
the ruthless oppressor type
you're so cute
I'm going to take down all of the Lord
yes
and then become Queen how about then I
think she would be a good Queen
um I thought I'd say this but I like the
cut of your jib Brennan do you have a
name
very well
as far as working the struggle continues
either way and with that sword on our
side our chances of Victory just
increased that is of course assuming we
can count the two of you in
[Music]
um
look at him he got nothing else to do I
know me after all it sounds like we're
after the same thing anyway
taking down the Lloyds I
honestly I'm still a little confused by
all this of course you are
being a Slave
when I choose to
Fang We Stand then it's settled
together we'll overthrow the running
Lords yes first up on that shopping
block is balssef the wild beast
sound good sounds good to me
[Music]
no more resting we ain't got time to
rest we can't let the people suffer no
more
that was in the video
girl you okay
oh
I've gotta hurry
okay
that's fine by me
[Music]
we have another secret hideout in
ulzabek
should be able to meet up with our
comrades there comrades let's go oh wait
a second I hate camping out
any any secrets
I got an eye for these kind of things
I have to build a strange power from it
we should gather as many as we can find
okay I think we're gonna skip waiting
for us
cut it out didn't anyone ever tell you
it's rude to stare I know I already
asked you this
but are you sure we haven't met someone
yes duh that's so hard to understand I'm
renin you're Dannon there's no way
besides I'm from lenegas it's just in
love wherever you were before you lost
your memory we've never crossed just
like me lennogus
you mean the same lenigus that's up in
the sky
I've heard it called the renin's castle
I never imagined people actually lived
up there well then where did you think
we all lived didn't you see the renon
Lords descend for the crown contest
and how long ago was that
well the current contest started seven
years ago so
and I wouldn't remember
just how far back do you remember
about a year give or take that's how
long ago doc found me one year he's a
baby then no I'm sorry but there really
is memory of one year ago he's a baby
okay
wow
I love this area
we should be able to eat this can we
find some make sure to grab it can we
make some bread out of that
good to know I'm sure because we can
cook in this game oh
kind of scary but
wow
[Music]
all right oh
I see no more items I don't think we can
take it right now
okay yeah we might come back to that
when we're stronger
Smash Bro S I hate mushrooms
are you are you hiding a treasure chest
here
we're hiding this that's for sure
but I don't want to get too close to you
no I don't see a treasure chest okay
look strong I suggest you don't yeah I
thought so but let's find those dudes
down there
and get the weeds
it's like level 45 yo what
no the demo
[Music]
the enemies are pretty strong
nice skill that you can only use in the
air at Ariel all right
[Music]
no one after another they die like
little flies
orange down
I
okay moving on
I polluted the area oh
before we go to the gates let's go here
important things or parallax
I would like Stone what is that
Tales of gel
it's over
yeah uh Jones are the healing items in
Tales of games in case you didn't know
and there's like the most basic ones
Apple gel orange style and then later on
you get like pineapple gel and and what
else a grape grape gel or something like
that everything's coming up Zephyr
Lucius okay I have arrived open up lemon
gel mmm Peach oh yeah right there was
Peach too
pineapple pineapple pizza
pineapple
cutscene coming
are you winning I am waiting definitely
oh
on the back oh
I live here peacefully it seems no
guards and stuff
oh
nice I'm surprised they didn't take down
the city okay people this is it
membership welcome no sign of any
running Guardsmen oh yeah the renins
aren't as populous as the dannins
probably figure stationing guards in a
place like this would be a waste of
precious Manpower oh so for now this
city has been kept the next safe house
is
upright
um
I guess so that is assuming anyone
actually made it here before us
yolkata
nice
okay head to the Crimson crowns hide up
yes but can I explore it
uh oh climb climb oh I bet there's an
item or something up there
oh no there's uh more people
oh
[Music]
pretty cool though oh we can get water
here
and how do I jump again there we go
can I have should this really be here
yeah oh Apple gel oh that wasn't even
water
[Music]
oh oh it's an in it
normally in towns of caves when you
sleep at ins
uh you get like special skits and stuff
sometimes when you do it for the first
time
so you should always try to sleep at
them even though it's a little bit
expensive and sometimes unnecessary
because of
already being full health and all that
[Music]
it's raining this town oh then we might
want to stay there for a night
I always forget to go to Indonesia me
too
most of the time except for you made it
unless I'm sorry there's no way Zephyr
would have kicked the bus tells me to do
it right
so what's the plan what is the plan we
take down the Lord I've got an ace of
Our Sleeve and the enemies in disarray I
say we strike while the Iron's hot yes
so we're finally going head-to-head with
ball theft yes we are that's right we
can't afford to mess this up because now
or never then now it is we've all been
waiting for this day for far too long
leave the plan they are motivated in the
meantime
what are we gonna wear
is is that that when she gets her main
outfit but honestly that is even flashy
of what she's wearing now stay right
there okay don't tell me you're giving
her the main outfit
haha
the main visual
why are you giving us clothes like yours
to those Rags I told you it fits like a
dream oh
her clothes didn't change
I'm afraid we don't have any renin
clothing I could find you some Denon
outfits yes please
but something tells me you'd rather pal
look into it is this really that
important
in case you need reminding I'm here
because our interests overlapped nothing
more
okay no point did I say I've given up
being a renin now now let's play nice
how about you ask Nate and see what he
says he's our One-Stop shop you stand
out so much stuff he might just know
something
well alphan is looking nice ocean blue
battle guy bull sounds good stuff here
suffer is gone
Sophia join my party did I just hear who
did I just hear hoodle
that's
I just heard a hoodle
are you outside
who
a
where the hell is it
can I open that door no
where is The Who
wait maybe one
oh
what else is this on the ceiling
maybe you have the hoo hoo you're not
only new hey you don't remember much of
it oh right well if you got any
questions
um no I'm good I'm good I'm good thank
you do you know where the Hulu is
where is that
yeah
cool
I feel like I'm being chased
it must be maybe I can get out there
from is there are there are ladders on
the map
I didn't see that ladder it Blended in
so nicely
who
not here
oh I hear you I'm Coming For You Ah
there's another one here
what
are you a bunny oh
how freaking cute are you
ready
oh my God okay we sent that an unusual
bird oh it's an owl they're often used
as a symbol to represent ancient Dana
hmm one second we have to immediately
put on uh
the
the wait it's not here is it uh
well I gotta do what I gotta do oh my
God look at those ears so cute they
really suit her
okay
it's good time
many skits oh it's nothing
only running around here you know pickle
I know pickle I was just thinking about
how communal it feels here even though
it's only supposed to be slave quarters
oh yeah
when you put it like that I guess it is
different from heavily patrolled muscle
for you expecting something more
depressing
it's likely a sign that ball Seth
doesn't think you guys can do anything
to him pickle
what pickle I mean if both have thought
the Crimson crows actually posed a
threat to him he'd figure he'd be trying
harder to suppress them you
ah
no
you're probably right about that
all the other dads that aren't with the
Crimson crows except
from the day we're born
probably even before that it's been
drilled into us that the only purpose
our lives have is to help select the
next Sovereign
I see it differently that's just me
bagel the star isn't getting into my
head right now talk about things the way
you do
I won't deny that among my fellow
renin's power and Status are everything
however that isn't what this is about
for me
I have something I need to do
and I'll do whatever it takes and use
whoever and whatever I need in order to
get the job done wow pickle to hell with
power okay pickle pickle
okay
she is uh
an interesting character indeed
so we got the hotel our first who taught
usual okay nice jumps there platforming
let's go uh parkouring I mean where are
we going
shall I go here
oh shouldn't you be oh I guess so thanks
for the hint yeah that's where it came
from
going somewhere else what let's start
oh
thanks game for the hint oh dear I need
your help
never the Manpower when you huh help huh
what kind is it urgent well I want you
to look at my ears well in that case
would you mind helping me out with
something first the work's really piled
up around here
what is it you'd like us to do
anything you can manage
no one cares about us slaves that's why
it's all the more important that we
stick together and take care of each
other
checking with that guy over there okay
and okay in advance
okay no problem I'll talk to him
by the way I'm gonna be playing 30 more
minutes but he's watching us
for today
hey
they've sent us he heard you might be a
little short-handed
you could say that didn't think he'd
send over the Iron Mask himself though
that's me that's a bright eyes review
you sure we can't really trust her
look at those ears pekko of course you
can
she's on our side Sofia can vouch for
her
if Steph is good with her then I guess
we don't have a problem yeah what the
hell the name's dyron Darren Darren I'm
the one who runs his lodge this is a
launch but we already have our own beds
oh
we don't sleep on straw and rock hard
dirt around here oh the Crimson trailers
have their fair share of folks who are
evil knocking on death's door or can't
otherwise move around openly that's why
this place is here for to give people a
place to rest up properly before they
head off the site
everybody needs to rest if you don't
rest you can't hope to fight the bright
eyes at your best or is this their way
of introducing the ends to me make sense
what do you want us to do then I need to
help Paul in some cargo I have some
friends who are on their way to collect
it from our hideout in the Zion mine
the mines is that really such a good
idea after the red and snuff the place
out these Valley these are valuable
items people risk their lives together
we need to get at least some of them
back it should be down around the
sadness Ravine at this point made up of
them and help bring the supplies back to
this Lodge got it okay
oh thank you I can sleep for free okay
we started a quest so suppose this is
not the main quest but a side quest
s okay we'll earn your rewards you can
accept as many of them as you like noise
I guess we shall do this one
or I don't know
I sound pretty thrilled by that thrilled
we have to I think for in order for the
main quest to proceed oh now that not
everyone is rolling over for the
remnants
all right
and now I'm supposed to go outside again
right no
oh
you want me to sleep there first or what
it should be down on the sound of this
Ravine hmm
oh is it the other way isn't that where
it came from
yeah
wait a second
uh this way
perhaps
okay
um so that way and then over there ah
Wednesday I had are inhabited by nothing
but ziggles for Miles if you don't have
business owned
what ah down there oh yo
oh it said itself
all right let's go
sandiness Ravine oh they have some fancy
clothes there they're renins people of
random stock
okay
what's up hello
killed how they're playing around there
oh you can see the
um materials items to pick up over here
noise
[Music]
I feel so nice to play a tails off game
again
Tales of bazaria was quite some time ago
the graphics yeah they're so nice I
can't wait to play it on PS5 though
they're all dead
you see we can't start from the
beginning with PS5 but when we switch we
can see a difference Maybe
nice comparison mask
s
19 no no wait no no way it's about 16. I
think this area is really ill hang on
it's no use he's already dead
don't you have a resurrection skill
though she though so many of us and it's
still not enough can you not use that on
him despite until they've wiped us all
out like pests
that's how she has a resurrection skill
combat only well then let's fight him
and the resurrection is something about
those bushes we should check them is
this a cooking pot what but what is it
doing here let's take it if I had to
guess he put it there to make sure a
renin wouldn't steal it why would they
steal it
so even though he knew he was dying
chose to use the last of his strength to
hide it
believing somebody would come for it
what
I guess you think it's stupid getting
killed over a silly trinket huh
no
clearly he risked his life his love or
something he believed in ain't block
someone for that okay however
will be up to us to figure out the
purpose behind his dying act well maybe
his job is being we'll make sure it
wasn't invade
nothing else
we'll carry out your will it's see
through to the end
and we better get going we don't know
when those soldiers might be back to
make another sweep of the area
okay so this is what it means to fight
the record sounds like you're kind of
scared to me of course I am
if I'm gonna die one way or another I'd
rather go down fighting
just like a hero
am I going the right way
okay
I guess that was was that already it we
picked out the material so we're going
back to uh give the quest back
that was an easy first sub Quest but I
think in the future it will not be this
easy I think it's just like an
introduction
to this kind of
OS okay I already took that
[Applause]
there's a hootl in this area
oh I'm gonna go get it
where
do you know approximately where because
then I want to check it out
gotta catch em all
you gotta catch them all
I need all the Hooters
oh
is it here huh or here
turn right turn left
Sarah would have heard it before I know
let's see
come on wheat
[Music]
just follow the rail it was there
wait what about here
oh oh dear clear of that Google yeah
I weak huh
let's fight first let's do those on the
rails
it's over
here
[Music]
thank you
thank you girl
I do owe you one
ah she's
she's a good sniper man work is done
here let's move
it is
I didn't hear anything I passed it
foreign
than I thought oh this will be the
biggest mission of the game to get all
of them
okay so you know what we're gonna get
rid of the rabbit ears and give him the
dog too oh
there you go
[Music]
peace
I can't wait to meet all the Hooters
I wonder when that's gonna be
introduced to me properly hello you got
a child with you this time why
is she a daughter
damn so nobody made it huh
I'm sorry if we arrived just a little
sooner we could have and these things
happen it hurts but this is the world we
live in I'll take good care of what you
brought back it's the only way we can
respect the sacrifice of those who we've
lost she is cute Hey when's Daddy coming
home he's out to get milk girl he's
never coming back
oh no no
uh yeah yes let's just tell her he's out
for milk yeah
hang on that whenever grown-ups looks
bad and say someone's gone they always
mean they were dead
daddy always want me that this might
happen one day he told me to stay strong
and be brave oh
this isn't right poor kid shouldn't have
to be dragged into our own mess let's
report back to knife and then get ready
to fight
press conference oh
German accomplishment
it's rebellious
[Music]
skill counter Edge oh
yeah
I got a new skill after a perfect evade
no perfect guard press R1 to trigger an
immediate counter attack yo
okay as you fulfill certain requirements
for each of your characters you'll earn
titles for them which unlock arts and
skills that they can then learn making
fights easier you can view the title or
unlock requirements from the skill panel
you can span skill points to learn arts
and skills from unlocked titles all of
which Grant powerful effects making it
worth your while to spend SP early and
often oh the skill panel can be accessed
directly by pressing right
and skill notifications if there's a
skill you want to learn but you just
don't have to SP for it yet highlight it
in the skill panel press square doing so
will turn on an alert that will notify
you once you have enough SP
okay uh
a home
hmm
okay
I
will have to look into this
so speak to Nate no problem gotta go up
here he's somewhere I feel like
somebody's watching us
is it a hoodle I already got that one
you're back huh it's like it was a real
ordeal out there which is I hate to
admit it there aren't many of us who can
take on those random armored soldiers
all we can do is make sure we remember
those who sacrificed their lives for the
cause they won't be forgotten
glad to hear it now what was that favor
you wanted to ask me oh right
well so then you're wondering if I know
of any places where you can find renting
equipment well
anywhere with those damn bright eyes is
going to have tight security of course
you can't just go carelessly poking
around
unless
across the Wilderness outside uzibek
you'll find the Fagan ruins there's some
kind of old renin castle out there what
would it being impenetrable I forgot
who knows maybe you can find some way in
you ask me though it's a lot of trouble
for some running racks if I were you I'd
get comfortable with Dan and garbs
heard that she on
change your clothes look like the ruins
let's move are we really going in there
yes yes move
and we have a skit let's look at it
hey Sheila where does your gun come from
what do you mean where does it come from
when you're fighting it looks like it
just appears out of nowhere I feel like
I heard to skip before that's transferal
technology
when I don't need my weapon I submerge
it in empty space and when I do I summon
it thank you for that game logic kind of
breaking the football sounds pretty
amazing it's a question that we all all
Wonder
invention
you realize you're praising the
technology of your enemies right
so technology is technology it's not
good or bad in and of itself
I guess that's true
I I love that they talk about where in
the hell she got that weapon for uh from
where the hell she got it from wait
where are we going
uh visit the fangan runes well where
where are they
are they uh do we go through here
[Music]
oh but there's a there's a
um like a leather icon here
do I have to get that first
one of those areas right yeah okay let's
check it out we we don't have much time
left so okay it's not that one
so I wanna quickly go there uh I think
wasn't there another area here yeah yeah
okay we can go there
seems so
now that is our subquest it letters for
the level 40 Dragon oh
the big bully oh dear we're not ready
for that yet ask for some lousy Club
there are circles here too
and cupcake
don't always assume there's Doodles
anywhere you go they're one of the
reasons I need you all we're a team
after all and that means you need to
pull your weight
so when I call for you I expect you to
clear out any enemies around me okay
girl why do I have to do all that in
exchange when you call for me I promise
I'll shoot down any anyways around
YouTube okay
yeah if I don't get in the habit of
speaking up during fights that'll impact
our impact moral and our ability to
combo together so make sure to do it
often okay in just a minute
it looked like the anime spotted us time
to get to work wait
Francis
yeah I was thinking that's how you're
gonna tell me about that okay you can
summon allies in combat yes yes I know
how to do this I think
yes yes I know I know I know okay
okay I'm excited iron boost attack
let's go
to Target yourself
with that blade in your strength the
average Google shouldn't be a problem
and there we go
can we get shields as well
another one
[Music]
oh ah where did that one come from she
was supposed to attack I know I know
thank you this one's mine I'll shoot
them down yeah I'm waiting for you I'm
waiting for you
ah there we go this one's mine
[Music]
fancy success
very fancy very useful oh no now it's a
real fight
wow
[Music]
so often
nice
nice I think I'm gonna remap the normal
attack from R1 to R2 I feel like in the
demo it was an art film that's a little
bit easier
I felt a little bit smoother
wait a second how to remount
um
[Music]
button findings
um Archer ah
a but evade Garden is there what should
I where should I put that I guess I'll
put it on R1
ah
[Music]
say it and go back okay
okay okay
this could be useful
you can hardly see anything from here
why don't we climb up higher and see if
we can get a better View
stand
l248 is nice too okay okay I'll try it
out maybe
potato
potato wait a second I should go left
first
mayhaps
open
oh yeah oh these are the Fagan ruins
oh how'd you figure a place like this
turns derelict your guess is as good as
mine
I didn't even know this place existed
until we heard about it all that matters
to me is whether I can find anything to
wear in there why does she care so much
about her appearance
good question I would like to know the
answer to that too
I mean I care about my parents too
do you like that ball damage
my controller rumbled a bit but I think
there was no fall damage
today I'm just farming stuff at this
point because everything and sparkles
looks fancy to me
I'm so glad there's no stamina though
wait we should maybe check out the house
there might be something in there
schools
let's dispose of the trash
yeah that's better
it feels easy at least but I might hmm
might still remap again and try some
other combinations out
hey eat this
finishing it off with Mirage feels good
yes
okay work is done here oh let's move I'm
right behind you
um
where the hell am I going
uh am I going all the way over there
this map is big oh
people
oh oh
apple jam
it's so big
but I almost left well at least that was
my plan
so I feel like yeah but I want to
explore more
I want to wait maybe now we can try to
fight that dude
um
I want to continue the story a little
bit though
I'll take that thank you iron chunk
where are we now aha
Maybe
don't howl at me no no no no no
oh
someone's running at me
I see so many items everywhere but I
need to campfire
okay you know what I'm gonna fight the
big one
that one is level 42.
no way
no way gives us time to catch up that's
that's true yes where was it again
where is it
it's a big boy
oh there you are that's not level 40
yeah the Mantis
this one's level nine you get careless
okay that one killed me so often
not this time
oh
[Music]
okay
we got him
that's what I like to hear fun
that is a fun battle system I gotta say
Applejack
wow
I don't have time for you guys
potatoes well let's see what's over
there
sorry for waking you up I guess
oh I guess we're eating fish tonight
um grilled carp oh
can you play as the other two I can play
as any any character yes Pagan ruins
below us
shouldn't be too much farther now if
that's cool
oh hungry
pickle pickle pickle pickle
don't worry about me I'm used to working
while I'm hungry it's no big deal it is
a big deal you should eat whenever you
can that finger tapping is you Keeling
over in the middle of a fight just
because you didn't eat never thought I'd
get lectured on eating by a renin
foreign
what do you mean I thought
this isn't about me
now are you going to eat or not I don't
know if I can hold back playing this
game off stream but we don't
actually I have a little bit of food on
me oh you've been carrying that stuff
around this time where were you hiding
this now be enough for the both of us
though
that's why we're going to cook it
instead
and you cook the hoodle excuse me
what kind of question is that no
anything like that before I mean you can
probably you shouldn't be honest
we've got to make something out of all
this so might as well try all right is
this how to cook tutorial number one
oh
walking automatically
yes yes
teaching us how to cook nice
or maybe not for your clothes are all
about function over form you should
think about sprucing them up a little
um no you should think about your
functions we're having it I guess you're
right
exactly nope I just think you look good
with a little blue thrown in somewhere
all right are you blind are you
colorblind
oh we can't go at camps and ends you can
cook meals comparing temporary effects
when eaten
more blue
new dishes can be made by finding
recipes while ingredients can be found
at collection points and General Stores
eating a new meal overrides any previous
effects favorite meals depending on who
in the party Cooks a meal the extent of
their of their effects and their
duration will vary as such it's wise to
rotate whose own cooking duty based on
your current goals and the party's
overall status status yes no problem
porridge okay I'm not much of a fan of
forage but if that's the only thing we
can do right now then we got no choice
it makes defense go up
this should definitely keep you guys
full wow 12 feet
on that picture
um you really do eat through that mask
of yours huh how you should
get used to it after a while how the
hell do you know that still I'm glad we
decided to stop and fill our stomachs
I've got a newfound respect for cooking
now okay it's easy when you're used to
eating everything Raw
it would have been perfect if it had any
flavor hey
hey palette
oh no that wasn't a knock on you I was
just
sorry that's not how I should thank you
for cooking for me uh-huh you got me
curious now is it just pain you can't
sense or your taste buds shot too good
question oh sure my taste buds work fine
oh although apparently what I like tends
to be a little out there
how so what's so unusual about what you
eat well one time I couldn't get enough
of these things I picked off a plant but
everyone else said they were way too
spicy doc thinks maybe I crave spicy
food to compensate for the lack of pain
I feel a masochist maybe it's best I
take charge of the cooking you know just
to be on the safe side
I can't guarantee it'll be to your
tastes though
I said I'm sorry
look I'll learn to tone down my tastes
in the future so let's just put that
slip of the tongue behind us already
okay
[Music]
oh good spot to end it for today as I
said future streams will be longer
oh a speedy shell
um
okay future streams will be longer
and but then also as I said we cannot
play it until the end there's a certain
part in the late game that uh apparently
I need to stop there but I'm still
looking forward to going on a long long
long journey together with you guys
and the next few weeks I'll be playing
almost only this
so you guys better catch up with me by
getting the game
and playing it ahead of me you got some
things time now like three days time or
so until the next oh four maybe until
the next sales of arise Stream So if we
didn't have uh if we didn't get the game
yet go get it a link in the description
and thank you so much Bandai Namco for
sponsoring this stream and the four
streams uh we got in Tales of horizon I
did before this one thank you so much it
was really an honor a huge honor
um what is that you ended exactly the
part we're starting for a live stream
later what watch
[Music]
but that reminds me ah I have a panel a
Calgary Expo
yes Calgary yes yes yes Calgary Expo in
a few hours so maybe I'll see some of
you guys in Canada
thank you
uh for today thank you for
this great opportunity Panda and uncle
and
events that we introduced in the
beginning for everyone who came in later
let me show you quickly oopsie
is playing the video oopsie so for
everyone who missed the beginning uh
look at this
team hat is so kind to uh send me these
goodies
commemorating the leadership of
takanasuki Anna I can't wear too I can't
wait to wear this all the time
yeah and also this can't wait to play
chess with this
exclusive acrylic chest and exclusive
chica keychain thank you so and and of
course the whoops the master called wait
no no no no no no no no no I want to
show the picture
ah there it is
replica oh I'm excited for this one I
want to put that
on my shelf and look at it every day and
be like yo I was the official Tales of
her eyes ambassador to the English
region and it's like a dream come true
yeah
I
one year ago yeah one year ago I debuted
it as a member of whole life English
first generation and back then in my
debut stream I wrote I told you guys my
favorite game
was the tails off games
and back then I I didn't quite think
that I would get such a beautiful
collaboration sponsorship with them
I I did not expect this at all but it
was so worth it it was so worth like to
to to share my love of tales off and and
keep on playing jrpgs on my channel
really happy that one dynamical decided
to go with me for the sponsorship and
and I I'm so so so grateful so also
thank you everyone of the viewers who uh
a lot of you I think uh didn't really
know much about tails off but through
this uh series of streams
um I hope you learned to love it as much
as I do and got an interest and maybe
you want to start playing some of those
games some of the tales off games
yourself I would definitely recommend
them there's so many
so I'm sure there is at least one tense
of King that would be to your liking and
especially maybe Tales of arise
yeah so I wish I had a better PC well
maybe you have a PS4 or a PS5 of a piece
I don't even have a PS5 yet
but uh Xbox as well
Symphonia yeah I started with Symphonia
so
uh it's a long long time ago that I
played my first tails off game back then
I played it with my brother who I talked
to him yesterday uh and he was also
really excited for Tales of arise really
interested so
um I'm gonna get him to play it as well
yeah so looking forward to playing more
of this and maybe future corporations
with Bandai and uncle and Tails off as
well I would be honored I will I will
I'm there whenever you need me
yeah so uh guys I'll see you uh tomorrow
for another stream and in Germany we say
Alfredo said sorry I can't read the
super chats tonight and there's a little
bit lack of time but
um we should be able to read them
tomorrow hopefully yeah sorry guys I'm
so sorry I'm so sorry oh yeah blue blue
protocol is something
um from Bandai Namco that has caught my
interest wink wink since Bandai Namco is
watching right now I've been saying I uh
whenever that comes out I want to play
it on my channel as well if I get the
permission so
let's see what happens
just leaving a few hints there
I played the closed closed Alpha of blue
protocol
so I'm really curious to how it ends up
once it's finished yeah all right
thank you so much so much I will
um never forget this journey and I will
never throw away this sash I will wear
it proudly
until the day I die which uh
I don't know when that will be but I
will revive surely so I will never take
it off I'll wear it in my sleep
the sash stays on yeah
maybe I'm allowed to still call myself
the Ambassador afterwards
thank you
bye bye
[Music]
foreign