[Music]
me
now
[Music]
do
hello
let's test everyone's volume everyone
say things yeah
good everyone say something
[Music]
that's what i thought um
seems fine no one's complaining on my
side
are you good i think everything's good
yeah
mario good job
everyone
is is everyone already in the holiday
mood
jingle jangle it's all right
[Music]
hello are you guys uh is everyone in the
middle at the port can we all meet up at
the portal oh
everyone running at the board
yeah hang on i'm turning up everyone
full volume
200 everyone
how can i be quiet
let me turn down my mic okay maybe this
is okay
go yeah
someone going back and forth in the
portal i keep hearing it now is that 200
volume
i have like 12 i think
but then again there's never such thing
as two minutes okay your house is
looking
good now thank you amelia added a nice
touch on top
i don't really know what it is it looks
better yeah it looks
better what is that yeah i think i
definitely made a big contribution
did you get rid of my chickens
oh yeah i ate them oh wow
i think the answer is clear if you have
to uh ask
here's my sword here we go hmm
i trapped him he came out of the wall he
came flying out of the wall
uh i don't really know how he did it
don't you think that you should elsa's
cat maybe
uh no they didn't have a collar yeah
there's water entrance to your house
why is it that when gooda walks all this
dirt comes up
cause i'm buried
[Laughter]
you didn't come here too but that
doesn't mean you're not going to be
is this your christmas tree oh yeah
let's go see the christmas tree
over here who is doing that yes
christmas tree oh
[Music]
i'm hungry
yeah if you look in the box there's like
a bunch of different decorations and
shears
so you guys can make your snowmen and
they'll be alive
[Applause]
here that have snow and they have the
pumpkin if you grab a shear from the
chest and you
uh use the shear on the pumpkin and now
you have a snowman you can take off the
pumpkin
what cool how do i get in here
you can jump up so my first snowman came
to live
and then you can take the pumpkin off if
you want to or you can leave it
oh my god and i always try escaping
i have to put a fence here that's so
cute
is that a mod or is it actually in game
a feature
that's an in-game yeah
and what else do i want they're trying
to escape
i saw that one snowman that you made
was these snowballs what do i do with
them
uh you can throw them at people can i
build another snowman
i messed up yes how do you build a
snowman
how do you do it again right click with
the sheer on the on the pumpkin
pop
oh yeah you just need like a few
snowballs and you can make a snow block
you don't need like a
a crafting table to do it and then you
can um
put
i know you already prepared a lot of uh
decorations on it but
i also prepared a bunch of pumpkins so
that i can also contribute so i'm gonna
put some pumpkins on the tree yeah my
dad yes kelly make whatever you want i
just picked some extra stuff like
these snowmans and if i do
oh but it's gonna be hard to decorate on
the other side when there is literally a
cliff there
um that's what we have scaffolding
until i've never used that before yeah
scaffolding
girlfriend is nice because you can just
click on the ground and it just spills
itself
i don't think you can build really high
yeah
and they break with like one one hit
it's like like and then breaks all down
it's really good yeah
oh they hit the baseball and it goes up
look at that
when i use the snowball it just uh it
just makes me throw it
yeah and you gotta make it in the in the
blocks
oh yeah yeah when you press uh is it
to the i don't get it going to the side
is not built up once hey watson like
press
the ground like watch it watch it watch
it yeah aim it
you have a shovel you can also uh you
can dig these
the snow on the ground what happens if i
put a torch as a light on the tree does
the tree burn
if i put the torch so if you have like
these
glowy i can't put it i can't put it on
there anyway but yeah we need to lighten
the tree up as well
oh don't set it on fire
whatever color i think it works yeah oh
as you bring it
all over the lines i'll bring some
hollow that i've colored all over you
put them wherever you want
to climb up this elevator thingy
should we build a star on top yeah yeah
yeah redstone lamps or i have these
shroom
lights either work it's growing so
pretty
damn can you not put the scaffolding on
the bush
contemporary dirt block or something and
then put on top of that
is that because i use the red lines does
anyone here already have a tree in their
home
cali how are you gonna do that
let me turn on my music let me get a
battle music
you mean i can put i didn't bring my can
i put them on the vines and i wonder
yeah on the grass it's not that's right
you gotta put it on sideways stuff like
uh on the wall
like this oh
[Laughter]
this is not over yet
i'm sorry
[Applause]
the crimson roots wait who are they
throwing snowballs
at what a shame oh they're zombies
oh wait can we have a snowball fight oh
yeah
that's what i'm putting up
[Applause]
oh
the words come in handy the ones i
taught you oh yes
delicious where'd you go
where'd you go oh boy
where did you come from where'd you go
where'd you come from kotnai joe
huh huh
i see i need to bring some stronger
weapons
tara hasn't spotted her yet
i won she's going she's going to get
more weapons
i mean that's what christmas is all
about right
fighting fighting fighting around
christmas
oh no i need to eat something oh no oh
no
do you need some steak did you
oh that might be nice actually maybe i
can at least put some bones oh wait no
hold on oh no now all these weird rocks
are in front of our tree because i tried
to make a big a big
tower so i could i could put the star on
the top
i've ruined it to just be able to like
jump around like if you come this way
kelly
yeah follow me i think we can get to the
top like this you just jump on the
blocks
yes oh okay maneuver around the tree it
should be like a little stairway
okay did you call a uh taco eats
my inventory is a little low so hold on
let me get rid of something
snowballs i don't need them i wasted it
i wasted it
wow what is that
what are you plotting yeah i was just
setting something on fire don't but
don't worry it won't be the christmas
tree
i just want to put this bone somewhere i
can't all the things that i want to put
down i can't put down
when you press e and you you click on
your inventory you can drag it out
and then just oh drop it just drop it
somewhere okay cool
i'll do that yes you make the star with
glowstone it's like close
oh yeah yeah well there's also the
there's also redstone light but i don't
i'm not sure how to make it
red
oh wait i'm just gonna bring more
scaffolding from
some more snowballs
my contribution i don't realize how much
torches were around our town until now
i put some bones there they're just kind
of floating well they disappear i wonder
yeah she's got the chickens
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh where is she
[Music]
let us have a snowball fight those are
snowballs you goober
they look like them
i mean what the hell oh no the snowman
is escaping
who's that
[Music]
okay scaffolding here's zombie
oh there's so many chickens i don't know
why you tell me why
ma'am
they also want to celebrate
[Laughter]
celebration i mean they do eat a lot of
kfc in
uh japan for christmas yeah they do
i don't know what so why on christmas
but
i eat fried chicken nuggets every day
hello
girl is the star girl is the star on top
of the tree
now i am oh she's down there i see yeah
thank you
thank you for the information no but
hey thank you
will you yeah glowstone hold on let me
get all right what is that i have like
i have some glowstone i have 20 80's
like a bit of it
uh if anybody has redstone dust i can
try making like a redstone lamp
okay gonna think
no i'm reading your house for redstone
dust okay
i forgot where i put it but it's in
there somewhere
oh
um
bringing out the battle axes that's how
you want to play
[Music]
now ladies let's not play fair okay
we're going to be using nakayoshi
yeah could you take a backstab just not
towards the cliff
a little bit of room for the star thank
you guys
guys have i ever thought have you ever
thought of the theory that enderman
might just be enma song
our manager ah enderman
close end impossible oh what
is that would be quite a twist
what's your building i don't know
oh oops hello
all the different types of lights yeah
look
at this more sense in my head
but stuff's breaking here
it's gonna be a scuff scar i want to see
how it looks from afar
i need a little bit more yellow here
wow wow it looks good
looks good looking good
yes i just can't put them anywhere else
i wonder if we could have like
a few more color variations in the
decoration although it looks kind of
cluttered now
so i mean should we add more
i think a few more colors would be nice
though maybe i can anyone
yeah i think that'll be good i'll put
mushrooms on it
pink
some of my fancy white glazed terracotta
on it but can i have it back when the
tree is gone
maybe maybe not because i got them from
far away lands okay
i didn't want to lose them i think i
could blow it up with tnt
they're really fancy that's a nice idea
we can make lots of tnt we can make
fireworks and we can send off the phone
but before we blow it up i want my
terracotta back
there you go oh it's pretty blue nice
okay this is easy i can do blocks
the roots i can't understand i can't
make them work i tried very hard
it's not working either they don't want
to go in the style looks good
it's a little scuffed but we can improve
it later
it's nice i can't get up the scaffolding
ow
who pushed me it was crazy little wasn't
me
it's a chicken no no no no no
i'll eat you don't blame it on my
employees
[Applause]
legs
wait does it is the tree lopsided or is
it just me
i don't remember being like that but
it's possible that
i may have forgotten one side
i can't make progress how do you get up
there
oh man i can fix this
what did you guys want for christmas
[Music]
well you had to ask but what about
everyone else
i want sleep
that sounds good i want just a free day
how do i get up here
oh wait do you need leaves i have like
like i wanted
a fruit oh yeah leaves yeah you have
leaves yeah i do
oh god i need them we can make the tree
even bigger
you won't believe how many leaves i have
oh
i have birch and uh oak and i have a lot
of spruce
are you on the tree i don't know if you
like spruce but
oh are you on the tree birch and spruce
no i'm at my house
oh i'll come to you my house
we're gonna have a very mixed
tree though yeah no this is fine
do you guys like uh when trees have like
themed ornaments or do you like when
it's
uh like a bunch of handmade different
colors oh
i like colors that's like a more
personal layer to the trees i think
um
are you are you guys even gonna get a
tree this year
i'm probably not getting one because uh
i i don't want to get rid of it it's
kind of annoying in here
in you have to japan
after the trees a lot so it's easier to
get a fake one
especially without a pet okay where are
you
oh sometimes your pets like to hide in
the tree in the chest
thank you okay i'll hide in the tree
yeah yeah when you have cats and a
christmas tree that's fun
yeah i had some kittens that were hiding
in the tree when christmas it was very
cute
thank you thank you
[Music]
if i make the star a little better it's
going to be like bigger than street
i can't wait to see oh wait it's
glowstone that means it's gonna glow i'm
so excited to see this yeah
[Music]
oh it's fine
i wish we could make like different
colored lights
and so can you oh we can make a we can
make stained glass
oh i have a vanilla nice idea i'll go
bring some
ah my trees
i'm trying to make it a bit more spacier
[Music]
we can put even more in decorating it
yes exactly facts but
them being individually beautiful that's
what makes them special
i literally have no idea what i was just
saying but okay i'm glad you're like
that's a lie you
no i mean i brought some stained glass
i'll put in the chest thank you
[Music]
i only brought like two of each because
that's all i had left over but if you
need more
i have more at home
[Laughter]
how do we light up the stained glass
still can you light it up
i guess you can put it like in front of
a glowstone light so if you look from
the front it looks like
different color maybe what if we put
torches on the tree
will it catch on fire
they don't even place on the on the
leaves um
oh i guess you'd have to have a block
well what if you use something like
um what if you put it on an ornament
is it getting too much now
does it look still i thought i put
torches on like the pumpkins or the
terracotta
oh yeah it's missing a bit of clothes
over there okay it doesn't burn the tree
it'll be fine okay
if it burns and the sun is setting
this time
should we put something under the tree
like a carpeting or
something like a carpet sounds nice
maybe maybe i can all right
the tree looks so yummy what it's like
what color should it go under the tree
guys red
oh that's nice yeah red okay
uh oh i'm sorry i'm trying to move yeah
oh i'm gonna hurt myself
are you okay are you okay are you okay
[Music]
[Applause]
oh i want to see hang on oh that is so
cute
oh my heart wait wow look these are so
cool
entrance there's like a perfect spot for
a photograph
for the tree as well i want to stay on
here oh my god
until after because take off your armor
though oh my arm is done
yeah so you look you want to see me
naked the photo
oh you want me to be there naked okay
okay
that's what i like to see as well i see
our tastes are very similar
that's why we are both business owners
taco bell and kfb
hell yeah exactly oh i think we could
use
one more stone way up there okay
[Music]
let's see let's see we can make a
christmas card and then we can sign it
and then we can post
it yeah yeah it looks really pretty
that's a great idea i like that
i need a toy let's do it then happy
[Music]
while i eat these potato chips i will
provide a view of the christmas tree
forever do you eat anything besides
potato chips
is there a reason to like potatoes and
bread
that's that's your favorite food i'm
gonna order some vegetables later for
lunch i wonder what i should have had
i mean potato is a vegetable right yes
yeah
therefore potato chip is vegetable
healthy yes
agree i also agree that fried
chicken is healthy and pizza is healthy
that noise oh oh we gotta sleep we gotta
sleep
oh you gotta sleep
what was that noise that reminds me of
our first healthy
somewhere i bet you
i love you everyone good
come back and fight me like a real
phantom
that's what i thought
wow these guys are safe another day yes
i feel bad i wish i was there to help i
tried to go to sleep
you guys remember the first minecraft
collab where we all just got at the
start
how times have changed how they have
there's a party what's going on in my
chat right now
oh yeah hiding party come on doing this
pudding
he no tony just reached 1 million
there's
[Music]
i'm ready for battle maybe we should
sleep they what if they destroy our
tree they'll just destroy our lives
that's okay that's expendable we can
take them thank you carefully
thank you i love you guys oh sweet
there is it i see it and then he spotted
i'm just going to slip he's pissing it
oh this isn't
the cat i don't think it likes the cat
oh wow
i'll go ahead are you sleeping or not
i'm gonna go to sleep i go to sleep okay
sometimes the best option in a battle is
just to sleep
mm-hmm does anyone need to i will i will
also sleep
i'm sleeping on your cat's bed okay
are you sure you can cause the phantom's
around i think so
i'm gonna sleep to the the calming
sounds of their hissing
thunder just pretend they're um cats or
something no
it's like it's like a dolphin or whale
sounds you know
very relaxing from the ocean
[Music]
some people don't like it
thank thank you
thank you everyone oh my god they're
still partying
party party party oh they're gonna burn
to death
okay
let's go inferno
they look like phoenixes except they're
dying instead of coming back alive
okay oh my god
the reverse is infertile
this is going for me you're cute all
right
neckonomicon second edition yes i love
that
i'm getting so many how many pets do you
have
uh yes
too much about the party but yeah
[Music]
i think we're gonna have more and more
cats because of the uh
thank you i mean i'm fine with that
they're so cute
thank you for supporting wait what is
this can i ask what this is
like thank you
i really appreciate it viewing platforms
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
such a surreal number such an
insane number you would like to do it do
you want to do it
thank you i love you all so much you're
the best people i could ever ask for
the best employees i could ever ask for
[Music]
in the hood i think i'll just climb it
the old-fashioned way oh here there's
some scaffolding
who tried to shoot me while i was
partying with my employees
who tried to shoot me zombies you are by
the edge
oh really oh really oh really oh really
gouda
you really think i would shoot you while
you're having an intimate moment
you really think i'll watch the archive
i'll see
what happened there okay guys this is
unarchived
quick get rid of the evidence
it's okay it's okay um it's okay i like
being shot
it feels good oh yeah she's used to
dying no
i like pain i'm a masochist yep
okay merry christmas but it looks
beautiful
i wish we could add one of those how how
do you stop it
how do you call those hanging things the
the hanging ones
i tried so hard because the vines didn't
work out
yeah i kept drawing those my bed i
thought they were
what i don't actually go get the uh
good vine separately oh low powered
emojis
what i have vines that i can bring i'll
bring him
i'll go get him well what they want
the game has stuff like that what
oh not not it's not a tinsel are you
talking about like tinsel that you wrap
around the tree
or something like yeah oh it just hangs
down
but we can yeah but that's cool
yeah why do i hear a zombie is there
anything you don't have
i'm telling you guys there's zombies
everywhere
i keep hearing them just like but
there's no there's no caves
careful they got arrows too they'll
shoot you you sure do
they'll get you
what's for christmas dinner by the way
oh my god the sound of
the sound of snow when you walk on it
isn't it amazing
can't crunch crunch up anymore
cornstarch exactly
you can only have 16 at a time it seems
good
i have to tell you something from a
distance
no no from from very close look deep
into your eyes
let me tell you one thing you look
beautiful
i wish the snowballs would do some
damage so we can have like an actual
snowball fight that would be fun
and we could throw up we can throw some
uh arrows at each other oh yeah so
almost a snowball
until we die maybe we should build that
we should build a coliseum
yeah for snowball and we can fight to
the death
wait didn't you held the ring yes i did
you bought like a fight yeah it's over
to my house
do we want to have a battle a christmas
battle lord
i'd like a christmas battle forget the
christmas dinner it's time for the
christmas battle
yes the christmas battle that's what i'm
concerned about
bring us back kfc and yeah exactly i'll
just bring you well
actually that's not really my job that's
kind of my job to keep you from coming
back but uh you could
you could just just wink and just
you know let's buy for just one what's
this today 12 deaths of christmas no i'm
really lagging
watson is suspiciously quiet has anybody
seen watson
i'm in the tunnel
i'm going to get vines and i'll be i'll
be back in like four minutes but i
thought vines only take six seconds
okay oh my goodness
wasn't that funny but that's not funny i
mean
okay that was good that was a good one
that was really good
i'm so proud of myself
after a while i took cause like half a
second and i'm like
abdul i am a comedian
oh my god
i can't stop myself oh my god
i know my potato chip bag pushed it up
like i have a potato do you like my
crust
yeah i like it
uh i can't tune you it it hurts my heart
i just wanted to say crossbow
or were you going to make an attempt on
my life no no you were going to make an
attempt on my life you don't have a life
you're
you're deaf exactly that's the point
which is why it wouldn't work
i don't know why i feel like battling
good albums
oh wait are you guys oh so you're
thumping
this looks so good i really like it
i'm adding a little snow to the top
ah a frosted christmas tree frosted
idea like guy fairy yeah yeah that's
right
like that guy tasting around the
christmas tree
all right coming back with vines yay
that must have been a lot of fun
you killed him no man do your thing oh
he only
you gave him a life yes i saved him from
i don't know no the snow
how do you put it down uh oh do you mean
yeah snow man or snow no
on the ground on the it's like uh what
is it
not a snowball right now you take the
snow balls and you go in your inventory
and you line them up in a straight line
i think that's how you make them
oh mayweather okay you just fill your uh
crafting spots
and then you get snow blocks got it or
you can get you can get like the little
little snow guys thank you so much what
the hell
thank you
oh my god thank you
thank you by the way i have some real
lag here
i have quite the lag i love you all
i love you i love you
i think all the snowman just fell down
anyways
can you put the snowman on a lead
oh it's a good question can we put a
saddle on him
and we ride the snow and we make a snow
horse
hi so cute though that'd be so cute
very merry
well at least there's still more and
more snowmen just jumping up and down
thank you nice they're the kids for our
christmas
dinner
i got an idea oh we should get the those
red bushes
they're like holly we can put a holly oh
yeah
[Music]
no you're right here maybe right here
um i'll make it here it should be fine
are you making an igloo yeah i'm
i brought some red yes um
[Music]
should we make lanterns for the well i
thought the torches look like candles
but like
i was wondering if we could make like
bigger candles with like uh
oh yeah yeah yeah there we go we have so
many coaches
and then that's the missiles of some of
these this idea
here
do your worst phantom oh my gosh
are you fighting them all right nice
nice nice don't provoke them
i've got five shots do they ever drop
something good
oh it'd be nice to drop anything oh god
oh god ooh
cute box in here hello
friend [\h__\h] nice shot
nice shock y'all
[Music]
hey the tree looks so good from the
distance too
doesn't it it's so colorful so pretty
christmas cake that's going to be a cake
yes what wow we're making a cake too
cool i have a lot of wool as well if you
need full
yes i have uh too much wool
but yes shouldn't the
ground layer be i mean
okay it's all going to be out of cream
okay i like it
why not but we could have it layered a
layered cake it could
the ground like a blank yellow and white
oh this cream on top with strawberries
yeah and then you can have the sides
showing so you can see how strawberry i
think this is the plate
oh yeah now you can build on top of it
okay you have yellow for cake oh this is
the i mean i have pumpkins
does that look like from the side like
it could be
what we want it to be do you have uh a
layer of carrots
like a layer of what
it's just an image it's just a visual
yeah
just a visual uh
right well sarcasm
you see this vine here yeah i guess
it'll blend in
i don't know it would hang you can hang
it off of oh
let's give it a try okay let's see what
happens
go get him tiger cool it makes an
interesting
it looks interesting oh that's i see
they're only in green
uh yeah except for the ones from another
but i guess you can't put those on the
tree for some reason or maybe i grabbed
the wrong ones
oh i'm gonna hold all the save
huge enough
the msg please
um i'll put some on the glowstone
that'll look neat
oh i forget how much i heard sound oh no
there's nothing there no where is it
spotted oh three o'clock by the way
oh no i'm not good at it who gets it who
gets it get rid of hundreds
[Music]
i got one shot left that's not good guys
oh
don't ruin her i have my battle axe come
closer you know
who's i cannot yet one two
three four come closer come closer oh my
oh my oh my
oh my
it's too followed because it could just
stop
doesn't even care about us it's just
it's just chilling
you don't wanna dance afraid of the cats
oh
is that a thing they don't like cats
some moms are afraid of cats and like
dogs and etc hello
all the more reason to have lots more
cats
thank you
i brought yellow does this look okay oh
is that too yellow
okay whoa
very good i'm gonna drop something for
you
what is that
phantom membrane what is that oh
it doesn't make do you want it i mean
you kind of killed it no it wasn't
really me
yeah i did it yeah i know i don't know
what that is i don't want this sounds
gross
i wonder what you can do with that
membrane
oh and we used to repair electrodes
[Music]
does anyone have an uh elytra yet no
what's in the label we have to do and
then you can fly with those
you go down a long way
an enderman anime
that she got for free when she wanted to
swim in the lava
our tree no get away from the tree
everyone we lead them away let's fight
we'll not do such a thing
go away i'll try and drag them away oh
can we can we
kill them with snowballs and stuff it's
fine it's almost morning we need to keep
them distracted
[Music]
thank you snowman missing everything
what's this guy doing
going the wrong way man the battle's
this way what are you doing
cute thanks guys we're helping you
nice snowy dudes big snowballs
put down the base where we
start how many blocks jeff
uh start right right here
here like where i'm standing one more
hang on yeah i do it so that there's
like one one um yeah
i could have sort of had one one white
block on the very edge
i think that i'll do you got it
no that doesn't work kelly do you wanna
die so you wanna come up here for a
second
for what just to see it look at the tree
no i'm good though
anymore there's going to be a little
more crazy
than that please yeah yeah a little more
creative
but what is this i will wait for you
[Applause]
oh
i think we need one more here
and then one more here oh oh you're
actually making a proper thing amen
that one
yes beautiful oh yeah i see
okay beautiful i have i have these red
these red things
here that we can put we can use them as
as uh
as strawberries yes yes
that's a really nice bright strawberry
oh yeah
you know like a strawberry yeah it sure
does so
let's use those as strawberries i'm
hopeful very good are we done with the
tree itself it looks done
are we only making another i think now
good mm-hmm
christmas cake no i will not burn
everything dude where's the pizza sama
what the [\h__\h] you're getting weirdo
no danny devito i will not burn our
christmas tree
excuse you they're asking the one person
they should ask them
they should ask the phoenix right
exactly
like oh i just keep scaffolding closer i
have a little addiction when it comes to
fire
i i enjoy fire a little
they do another cake layer yes
i'm curious you guys sure do a lot of
things in this game huh
but they're all diligent will you burn
it for 10
no no amount of money do you you're just
going to be wasting your money dead
dudes you'll be wasting your money
any more cake ow hey
sorry i thought that was a chicken leg
that i was hitting you with
sorry are you guys hurting each other no
we're playful you're playful uh having
fun
high fiving each other
we're being good buddies and good
buddies like to touch each other
every once in a while
what what
what what's bad about touching what's
battle touching come on
i mean yeah i can't focus somebody's
making the
cake baking station hostile i can't
[Laughter]
now we need we need more cream oh hello
it looks
really good i got the i got the i got
the uh
the whipped cream
[Music]
of course we are what the hell
body touching is there's nothing wrong
about that
okay
[Laughter]
do you burn it down for a scooby snack
no would you do it for two scooby
snacks
well let's make it three awesome you
said two
just cuz
we're good for this job right now
and oh you got to do it like a like yeah
like a clock right like blink
yeah drink and then drink like i didn't
take screenshots again looks tasty
oh was it f2 f2 ah
yeah oh yeah oh yeah
gotta get some making off photos here
what
i'm leaving this area i even i don't
even care if i hurt myself
what the hell what no no photos like
that
what i'm just taking a photo of the
progress what the hell
wait do we only have two strawberries
said
don't you do that to me i thought what
maybe there's more i'll check them
i should have more i think you said
making out
photos no making off photos
just come here you heard that the way
you wanted to hear it
that wasn't how i wanted to hear it no
it wasn't
okay
you want to make a [\h__\h] no
stay in the closet until they're done
wait this isn't gonna work uh
we gotta improvise i got some more
strawberries
how do we we're struggling right right
here they really look like strawberries
oh yeah
yummy wait huge
we got one for each member one big one
should we i know this is not a birthday
cake but should we put candles on top of
the
strawberries oh nice strawberry looks a
little weird
you think it's acquired tnt is not
exactly a strawberry
that's cute can you burn down the tree
for unprotected hand holding with kiara
what the [\h__\h] is what
i'm gonna cut down this tree any
objections no
i'll die sorry no no no christmas kisses
no christmas kisses
i put those trees down because i was
gonna hide anvils at the top so when you
guys cut them down they would fall on
you but it didn't work out
so yeah that would have been funny
though come on think of the content
for the content yes let me usually come
on
oh wait i got an idea
hmm christmas steak
hold up i got a very special block i can
light on fire
ooh i forgot where i put it though
oh there you go second cr if i made a
second christmas tree and burned that
one down
make for a cozy fire
just make a bonfire
[Music]
this is cute
no you finished you
like a chicken dinner uh-huh
and there were no chicken dinner wait
bye-bye all right
i am
[Music]
soulfire that sounds interesting i want
to see
hold on it's nice in here
there you go inside the cake beautiful
yeah
i'm just chewing it's like the uh you
know when you make like a marriage
proposal and then
you marry me it's your it's your
it's your wedding cake ellie
this is how you eat a cake normally in
my country
don't ask me question kiss my quote
unquote
wife
i spit it back out i put it back on the
cake it's fine
oh that's kind of your slice
why are you guys scared of some shark
cooties is that what it is
that sounds so weird
[Music]
what else can we build as christmasy um
no i messed up
can we get some cats in the tree what
are you doing to my candle there
cats in the tree yeah that could be fun
if we put one in the cat like
let's put some cats on the tree like his
little decorations
i don't want it yeah you know you have a
ton of cats right can you grab some put
them on the screen
i know we can do it we can get both
sides
we can go sledding traumatized
yeah on the on the ice there's an ice
biome at the end
or somewhere
skating rink we can transform the
fighting ring into a skating ring
just put ice on the top of it a little
bit maybe yeah yeah
that'd be pretty good small yeah i bring
a lot of
[Music]
yeah will you give me permission to
build a giant chicken on top of your uh
i mean we can build it together because
that's what i wanted to do anyway
um there's a blueprint for it oh yeah oh
yeah please
yes i got a lot of will uh wool as well
so let's do it together majestic yeah
majestic chicken i'm gonna make the ice
glue but the thing is that
we gotta make it look like a little bit
like a phoenix so that
my my employees don't misunderstand what
it actually and what we actually sell
but it's it's laser chicken
i just realized the christmas tree is
right above my home
oh it is it's right on top of my cave
nice
you can never lose do you still not have
a proper home
let me check it out i mean i worked you
can come see some of it i worked on it
yeah yeah you can come take a look i
still don't have a proper door but you
know your zombies
i got super lucky i picked it up as a
gotcha oh my
goodness oh there is a zombie and then
there's a [\h__\h] in kitchen up here i'm
still working on it but bitching
catching
me is this your pet or kevin keel
oh the zombies
because it has a color and do they all
have colors
color colors
thank you i have your salmon buddy hold
on i'm just saying
your cave has potential
and cali you're gonna have to light up
the snow otherwise you're gonna have a
lot of
friends give you one a name she was told
that before but she didn't believe it
i didn't one i listen i just didn't want
to do it because they told me to do it
listen she doesn't want to be told what
to do she's a rebellious teenager
don't tell me what to do this is not a
face mask
let's get you a adore
i'm getting ice but i already have a
bunch of eyes so i'm just picking it up
and then i'll be back in like
four minutes okay okay baby
uh door
yes cali i got the perfect door for you
punching bag really love that salmon huh
shut up
punching bag listen i don't know how
buttons work in this game
so on occasion when i try to feed my cat
the sam and i end up hitting the cow
with the salmon instead of giving it
i
it's a nice color too thank you nice
nice a real door hooray thank you so
much did you say it's uh
adorable how's everyone doing okay oh my
god
where is
it's raining sharks and squids
oh cool can i fight can i go kill some
more fish i need more food for my kitty
yay
need more employees here
not enough people working at kfb why did
everyone quit their jobs what the hell
oh i don't know i think you need to look
at yourself mad in that respect
why did they leave i wonder if you're
looking good i don't know i've heard
some stories
tortured every now and then they'll love
me they would never leave me
it wasn't me or did the zombie not have
a face
they would never leave me i think it was
just you because
you had a face for me it was in the back
of their head
i couldn't tell it was looking at me
maybe i think you're going on the side
of it yeah
look how good this looks this is so good
i have some ink sacs
sucks i have some anvils
nice your house has a nice rock salmon
on this tree and maybe the cats will
come to it
do you like it i've been told it's a
finger apparently
it's a very interesting hat yeah maybe
maybe that's how they say hello to each
other oh we're on this road
where are you coming in
the uk it's not how they say hello okay
hello wait let me try hello i'm okay
hello
hello is that how it sounds
i will present my chickens i will not
let them be hurt by a stupid zombie
protect
[Music]
they're going to kill me people from the
uk i'm sorry i don't mean any disrespect
oh yeah i can't do that
subscribe to my youtube channel
oh my god it's not working
[Laughter]
i love youtubers
you guys sound legit
amazing
all right anyway how's that ice coming
along i'm almost back i'm in the tunnel
on the way back
i have 52 ice nice
cool you like to make a long slide or
something instead
a lot he's got an egg yeah maybe he's
gonna
make us breakfast oh wow i don't want
that that would probably taste really
bad
zombie breakfast
just the side of rings hmm
delicious no i need
i want to see if i can uh
[Music]
raw flesh i like collecting that
kiara i i i'm just
uh admiring your beauty when the sun is
coming up you you shine even more
beautifully than ever
oh oh my god
[Laughter]
cutie oh we know nothing's as beautiful
as you like
oh the cake looks beautiful
where the tree the cake is almost bigger
than the tree though
there's really nothing wrong with what's
wrong with thick cake yeah it's enough
for everybody
exactly
[Music]
oh yeah you should probably get rid of
this uh
thank you people thank you new audience
do you see our delicious cake and our
beautiful tree
[Music]
and where do you guys think we should
build i have all the ice but where
should we put
like an ice maybe an ice slide because
if you go really fast on the boats but
then
who is building something on the
mountain
[Music]
oh that's good that's good but it's what
is called a building up there
[Music]
actually nothing but we could build a
slide that goes from the
from the mountain down down there yeah
nice idea can you go down ice like that
is it so slippery
oh you're right ina it's a cutting board
just
thank you thank you she doesn't need a
cardboard
she doesn't need one she is the cutting
board all right i'll
i'll put stairs let's go up there
okay heading on spider who will kill
them
up there do you guys want some
scaffolding
what the heck man oh
thank you oh what's happening
why are you coming after me amelia what
is that
you're using you eight-legged freak
what's wrong with you
spider-man
what is that where is that going to be
and what is that pig
doing here that's way faster we'll just
use this
okay spiders have eight legs right
[Music]
yes okay why else has eight legs
because i caught them in eight like a
week and i'd like to be correct when i
installed them
all right that's good i was never out
here before
i like the view from here nice the tree
looks also nice from here
hi that's a weird treat oh yes
oh the tree on top of your house
looks very weird
you know what i think it looks weird
what what is it what looks weird huh
what do you think
[Music]
i have the same thing we all have the
same thing except everybody
no i'm getting one i'm getting one and
i'm getting
the same mic as several of you
so we all end up having the same
equipment same microphone same go
xlr hello
somebody do like this side with blocks
like dirt or concrete on the other side
and then
uh we won't fall off when we when we go
really fast
oh you mean like uh you mean like you're
gonna need a little
uh offense to make sure we don't
die wait that might be the fun part
who gets the furthest without dying yeah
that's all the different curling bodies
we'll do it over this uh this ditch here
you know so you guys
uh it's more fun that way wait hold on
pick up a little pool of water at the
bottom
so we can like wee into it ah
yeah or maybe it should maybe i should
it's a it's an icy diving board of death
walk the plank fun
i'm gonna put a sharp turn here oh
[Music]
ah
the leap of faith i'm dropping i'm
dropping a bunch of boats if anybody
wants to pick up a boat
i'll take a bomb you don't want to like
uh
you don't want to like put us put a put
some stuff on the side so we don't fall
off easily
now i'm bringing some dirt now though
guys but
that's the fun part oh wait i can make
it safe
this is not regulated
[Laughter]
[Music]
wait i'm gonna put away my diamond stuff
somewhere
oh i wish you could bumper you off
that'd be like
safe i will make it safe so help me
and i brought that i brought extra dirt
so help me poseidon
i already died oh my god
you don't like you take fall damage oh
oh this will fall off i'll get some
water
yeah i'm excited
i like blue yeah your color is better
yeah it's pretty very nice are you gonna
make this longer or will it end there
whoever falls off first is
oh there we go
[Music]
the curve kind of slows down everything
i'm gonna leave this boat i don't want
to mount it anymore
how do i get out of it how do i get out
of the boat
shift shift
yeah let's make another scaffolding
going up
my mind my mind oh my god
scuffles i'm sorry no more stuff
right my
more this is actually kind of fun
it is unfortunately your boy actually
has to dip out
i have a meeting i thought it would only
be an hour 30 minutes for this
okay okay okay
[Music]
if it was here i was gonna accidentally
break the ice block that's all standing
on top
of it
don't worry about it okay let's go uh
take a picture yeah screenshot
screenshot time
okay should we go down to the middle
yes can we have the tree edge the cake
on the
picture oh i wanna probably find an
angle we can do
that i'm coming
i'll go
oh it looks kind of prettier during the
night should we wait until it's night
oh i think this one is setting right now
isn't it yeah
flower and salmon yeah let's go on top
of here
we won't get both on it but let's at
least cut the tree and we can get two
angles yeah let's have a go
f5 f5 there you go
f5 is the change thing yep yeah
you can do f1 get rid of the uh hud you
want to take up your
your uh uh my equipment good idea
pretty oopsy my mind
i'm in i'm down i'm here i'm coming
oh you're dropping should i what should
i do go get it
no if you want sure it's gonna be there
it's fine
no worries hello oh it's all dead four
oh how could i have forgotten
maybe we can all uh crouch
yeah how do you crouch with uh shift
shift
oh shift yes yes
yeah cool crouching in front of the
christmas tree it's perfect
maybe one more should maybe one more
person should be uh downstairs
let me uh shorties in the front
that's you all right all right down you
go girl wait wait
wait wait wait okay okay okay one second
oh it's nighttime oh it's perfect right
now
like not too dark okay crouching cheese
please how can i get rid of the ui f1 f1
oh you know you want to crouch again
what screenshot again f3 f2 f2
okay other side cake signs
do we want to be on the cake
oh it's so easy let's just
sounds good are you able to get up oh
okay
hi
[Laughter]
[Music]
you guys have fun okay enjoy the rest of
your time together
oh no i mean i think we're all on the
yeah yeah
i think we wanted to drop it up here we
did a lot of stuff
i would suggest that we leave the
christmas tree forever
[Laughter]
yeah i always like christmas it's a
plastic
it's a plastic tree it will not go bad
yay that was fun all right everyone
bye see ya bye
[Music]
happy holidays oh my gosh they're here
no no they're killing me they're killing
me
leave homes stay safe
stay safe happy holidays
goodbye uh guys
so uh wait a second
okay
are you guys still streaming or
okay okay
[Music]
everyone are you still here
i just wanted to say thank you to all of
you one second
[Music]
huh everyone
you guys are so sweet i love all of you
thank you so much i was so surprised
that we reached 1 million during the
collab what the hell so
unexpected thank you guys so much 1
million views on hinotoni
thank you to everyone who tried to share
it and loop it or whatever thank you so
much i love you all
don't forget it's not only on youtube
it's also on spotify
itunes and where wherever so if you want
to support me a little bit more you can
get it on whichever
music music thingy you're using um
uh and yeah i don't know super chats i
i don't know should i read them now i
feel like
you guys you want to read them now i
could i could do that
uh what stream do we have tomorrow
what is this what am i doing tomorrow oh
okay okay
i see i seen should i read the super
chats
the stream is kind of the chat is kind
of delayed so that's kind of annoying
but i could read the subject
it's my alarm for spotify thank you i
played in my cart thank you
so happy to hear that
i think eurobeat is amazing but he know
tony also
probably gets close enough separate
stream should we do a separate stream
for
super chat reading
[Music]
maybe we should do that yeah i feel like
probably um you know in youtube when you
start a stream you can set a setting for
uh how on time the chat is
uh i think i probably didn't change that
setting this time that's why it's so
delayed
read the yeah yeah i have the ones from
a way out and the ones from this stream
[Music]
but since you guys are already here
since you guys are already here if you
guys have time i could read the super
chats
better than another stream um
i don't know your separate stream okay
i don't know when though right away
right away
most people already leave well that's
okay
stop the stream start another one okay
okay okay we can do that we can do that
all right i'll see you guys in a minute
then we're super tattoo
let's get those super chats going and we
can have a little bit of chats because i
didn't talk to you guys today much
because of the collab
two collabs actually yeah never can do
much uh
chitty chatting with you guys all right
see
[Music]
i love you all thank you so much for the
support i'll see you guys in a minute
auf wiedersehen
i love you
[Music]