foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
the universe is fun now
it's not alone
[Music]
I'm not alone
foreign
I know
[Music]
[Applause]
the universe is
over
[Music]
foreign
million subscribers uh
celebration outfit reveal
yay
[Music]
um this was revealed last week
um oh God I already I want to apologize
uh or Paul I really apologize but just
inform you
um my throat hurts
surprise
um ever since I woke up today I noticed
um pain in my throat
um I've tried to not talk the whole day
until now
and I have been drinking tea
um
it's just so you know
my throat hurts that's maybe why maybe I
sound maybe at the moment it still
sounds fine I guess to you guys but I
feel already at the first thank you
I know
um
last week I revealed at the document the
event where I was a special guest at for
the second year in a row I revealed that
I will be revealing a new outfit one
week later
yeah yes yes but actually this outfit
has been in the works for quite some
time now
um
uh I want to explain it oh God I I think
now I can perfectly do the tomorrow yeah
um I want to first of all explain this
because some people I think are confused
about this because maybe it hasn't been
like mentioned so much
um the thing is
your whole life
is very nice and plays Santa Claus when
we reach Milestones big Milestones like
1 million
subscribers and uh uh we can however
choose what we want and they will see if
it's possible and the other girls in
math yes they have also reached 1
million but they asked for different
things just so you know that's why I'm
the only one revealing a new outfit
[Music]
in English
um
yeah some things you may have not seen
yet some things you have seen already
like for Ahmed the paladins announcer
pack oh my God the announcer of paladins
Amelia Watson
yes
yeah but I felt like what I can use
um well I can make a use of what what is
useful for me
um for my activities or the most would
be a new outfit and there was something
specific that I always wanted oh my God
so yeah who knows what it is no there's
more things that I want if I could I'd
have a whole wardrobe of outfits
but yeah it takes time to make these
outfits
um so it has taken some time
and we've been working on it for a while
and yeah now I finally got to announce
it at dokomi and here we are one week
later I can show it to you
and because
um well it's free I am in Japan but I'm
hoping that there's gonna be you know
people from all over watching so I'll
speak a little bit more Japanese than
usual maybe
um oh my God [\h__\h]
the problem is when not talking the
whole day in order to not hurt my throat
you can't really
um guess how bad it really is because I
didn't test it out I don't know if you
guys hear it it feels it like um
it's bad
um
but one hour is fine I can take it for
one hour I'm fine oh I have some not
really good tasting tea with me
you and I have a fruit candy in my map
so we'll get through this now I'm not
because balance an answer
no I I couldn't no no no I I would be
ashamed to be in the same ranks of the
famous paladins announcer Emilia Watson
the one little thing before we really
get started holy [\h__\h] time passes by
fast is um
happy birthday to both really and
um yes
happy birthday and sign up without like
such a lovely song oh my God
oh and I think I think it's a certified
Banger because it's been staying in my
brain
so good yeah
yes so uh
I think you know today for this outfit
reveal I'm going I guess for a bit more
of a classic outfit reveal
um
uh I tried to make things uh original in
the previous ones but
I'm gonna be honest I didn't have many
ideas this time although I did there are
some things but in general it's gonna be
classic so we're going to start out with
um looking at uh
looking look yeah I'm the only one
exactly so maybe it's okay to do a
classic one so let's look at some
uh
um assumptions no guesses
[Music]
starting out with one from choco cookie
or two
this looks like
a uniform
[Music]
that's definitely like work inspired
maybe waitress maybe flight attendant or
something like that
um this one was my favorite oh
yeah I can see um
let's see it's definitely something you
would wear at work yeah oh my God
I also made a version of without the
jacket
and a ponytail version
I do like this high ponytail very cute
yeah and this bird what do you call it
bro brooch brooch brooch
um
left side feel like Arrow Hostess yeah
yeah I think the blazer with the golden
um edges makes it look like that yeah
holy [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I'm so
I plan the long stream for tomorrow
doesn't get worse until tomorrow
[Music]
I'm so [\h__\h]
um by the way I also I'm planning on
doing a super reading super super chat
reading catch up on Monday we'll take a
whole stream for it so don't worry about
it we'll catch up
tomorrow
no [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I want to stream Wind Waker oh well
this is really cute
um
I I don't want like
um like a working uniformish thing yes
so um
no who knows
next
this is very casual this is from Alder
Green Berry thank you very much for your
um submission I I like it reminds me of
um you know when me and Ina did the
designs for
um the council members for the casual
dresses and I feel like this reminds me
of the mermaid dress a little bit not
not because it's very similar but the
style I feel like we could hang out
together with that
feels like we went shopping at the same
store or something
um yeah
so I like that it has
is this I like the colors and the Blazer
uh makes it look a little bit more
proper like I can totally see
um me going to I don't know a summer
date like this
or also something more proper I don't
know do people go to church like this I
don't know but
um or hanging out with the girls uh in
summer oh it could be many things I like
the hairstyle
hmm
nice nice hairstyle
um I should take um notes
I should take notes about this hairstyle
like I like these kind of braids
um
this is nice I like it I also really I
just gotta say like
um art skill wise I really like the Boop
Shadow yo it's so so much contrast
because obviously Boba very big so need
big shadow
um
thank you very much I like it also I
like the lipsticks up here they're like
egg colored so it could be just eggs
with wings
maybe it's not even chicklings it's just
eggs with wings cute
cute
next up we have a
um teacher uh Style
outfit it's from Alex Keller five
[Music]
so nice yes teacher I guess like yeah
um the top three guesses from people
where number one
um uh like what uniforms do with this
whatever uh number two diendo number
three something like a teacher thing
because just because of the the shape
and and I guess like a wait what did you
guys say like a Blazer uniform whatever
because I guess the shape of a jacket
made you guys think so
um
[Music]
yeah teacher would be nice indeed
because I've been teaching whole life
girls quite a lot about English about
Japanese about German about dancing
about it had to be an idol all kinds of
things
so it would be something very useful and
it does give me proper glasses I have
sunglasses for the outfit I'm currently
wearing
but
not normal classes that is a difference
would be nice to have that
wait a second
hyper chat are you okay I bet you come
back to me
oh you think Applejack also okay yeah
yeah and I do also um like the hairstyle
I mean it is um that style of hairstyle
that up to feels like
um very mature I'm not quite there yet I
will say that maybe in 30 years
next up
this is from Cardinal crowbar thank God
it's very edgy reminds me again of the
designing outfit designing stream that
we did
um
yeah yeah very cool oh the The Ripped
tights the black nails oh the Joker yes
because if you haven't noticed I always
have a choker in my outfits so that's
something we cannot miss out on this is
not a face no I think this is a face
[Music]
leather jacket
hold on
[Music]
I I could wear something like that maybe
um the skirt should be shorter
um but that's like you didn't have a
choice because you were going by the
silhouette
um but if I could change something I
would make the skirt shorter
and hmm I know I don't know change the
hairstyle but once again you went by the
silhouette so can't blame you biker
quinoa biker
biker oh like oh my God a couple days
ago uh on my way from hotel to airport
at dukumi and there was like a
that was a dude next to uh my my taxi my
cab uh it was like really loud so we
looked outside it was like he stopped
right next to us at a red light and he
was on a Harley Davidson and he had a
helmet with flames on it
yeah we were like first when I heard the
the noise coming closer to us I was
getting like pissed like yo do you have
to make so much noise on the street
because these people do they I don't
understand I never drove a car before is
that something optional or when you make
noise on the street is that something
you do on purpose can you not go quietly
but so first I was getting like pissed
off because like dude you're so [\h__\h]
loud but then I look at it and we're
like oh [\h__\h] he has Harley Davidson I
heard of that before they do it on
purpose okay I thought so
yeah I mean especially if you're wearing
a helmet with flames on it I mean come
on
motorcycles like it because safety what
does that mean safety because the people
hear you coming so they will move to the
side
that sounds safe
is that one you meant
God [\h__\h] my throat oh my God
[\h__\h] it's getting worse oh my God
yeah
any holy man face watching only besides
Only Wanna Say hi
[Music]
um
I'm drinking tea right now
[Music]
what do you think about this outfit I
could go out with edgy fauna in this
outfit
hell yeah
we could be this could this could be us
so true thank you for watching I
appreciate it hello I'm Hollow Man no no
no no no don't lie to me I know my hello
members
I know them very well
okay next stop
okay this is like extremely the opposite
this is from wait did I say the previous
one yes but this is from Caro Rock four
two three two I think that was a Korean
fan
yes this is I like pretty much every
single person made this thing at the top
into chicklings chicks but this person
made it into small bunny ears
and the whole thing kind of now look at
it reminds me of I think my Animal
Crossing
um
outfit time-wise at some point I was
having I was wearing a hat like this I
think
um
so it seems like I've become something
like something like a bunny girl but
not quite not the not when you think of
a bunny girl you probably wouldn't think
of something like this but this is like
a magical I have to say how would you
describe this because it feels like
I've seen something like this before
yeah and it's not really matching though
very cotton candy I like it I love the
colors
um I love the color scheme Easter yeah
it gives me Easter Vibes and kind of
oh what is it I can't yeah Alice in
Wonderland yeah excuse me Alice in
Wonderland Vibes but
ah a tour guide yeah
but to Candyland
could be so many things
hello 80s
oh maybe
cute yes so that gives me Easter and
spring Vibes indeed
um I like it I like it it's very
original and you made something
completely unexpected out of the things
at the top whatever that is
and thanks for the ubu mouth
ah
pink Crystal one yay
cute you know
I have a lot of pink items
um and pink clothes and all that so
people ask me do you like pink it's like
is it your favorite color and I say no
actually not
um it's just that like the I like cute
fashion and I like cute things so but
but the problem is that most cute things
are sold in pink
like when there's like for example also
with phones for example let's say you
buy a new phone and there's like three
colors there's like black and silver and
and like you know rose pink gold or
something like that for example
um now I would get the rose pink one
just because it's a girly option and the
pretty option not because I love pink
but I don't get any other choice like
people don't make much out of like other
pastel colors like lavender I would love
lavender things ah yeah or orange or
yellow I don't know
[Music]
but whenever people make something cute
they will turn it into something pink
so I buy everything in pink and then
people think I it's my favorite color
it's not and what is your favorite color
I'm not sure I like pasta colors and
purple and orange and white and beige
but it depends like on what page I like
um not with everything I like beige
cloves sometimes
yeah anyway we're tangenting off here
I also like red and I like gold but that
that's like with clothes baby
I shouldn't talk so much my throat hurts
[Music]
um
so this is by lme 39 project
thank you it's very cute so this
the Blazer and the blouse gives me
teacher Vibes but the skirt makes it
look more casual I do love that you made
my feathers pink and it makes me want to
write that down for the future
foreign
[Music]
and I like the contrast of the bright
yellow flowers in my hair with some
sparkles nice so cute
I love also how Derpy the the chickens
look cute yeah looks like office manager
it looks like a very girly office
manager yeah maybe an office manager
from
um an office that's very girly like I
don't know
like I don't I don't know something
girly
laughs
some job that's very good ice cream
parlor manager well yes for example
Barbie doll office wait for example yeah
cute
flower shop yes
yes all right
how are we doing with the time all right
good good next stop this is from Sean
heel and
it seems to be
inspired by Daniel and I would say
inspired because
it's not quite what a traditional
dandelion looks like but I definitely
see
um the inspiration behind it
yeah it's cute I also like that you used
more traditional colors like for dandel
um where everybody who doesn't know
Daniel is uh
traditional dress for several countries
in
Europe mostly I would say it's
german-speaking countries like Germany
and Austria maybe partially Switzerland
Maybe
um but there's like uh many many
variations like of colors and length of
dress and like blouses and blue
[Music]
I like it it has um some more down to
earth toned down colors and that can be
very nice too oh it's like um for
example like to Oktoberfest girls would
go in like flashy Daniels and then to
like I don't know official serious
events people would go to more longer
and original looking dinos and then
there's also worked handles for some
more traditional hotels for example the
staff would wear toned down calm down
um not so flashy dandels at work yeah
yeah yeah there's so many different ones
and there are many yeah
oh
wow very detailed and this one also
definitely has dandel vibes
yeah uh because of the apron obviously
and something that looks like a corset
and a jacket as well the jacket is
optional for dental by the way just
saying but it is definitely nice to have
one
oh and I like that you implemented some
like green greenish stuff in my hair and
you gave me some purple highlights I
like the colors of the jacket the pink
beautiful and I like the the apron
pattern very nice and the lace around
the Boba
pretty and glasses
this these glasses I like they're very
round and very big
and it gives me more money girl style
perhaps maybe money girl I'm not talking
about color be more I'm talking about
the fashion style [\h__\h] my voice
foreign
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
oh man it's like I feel like wind like a
weekend is obviously cursed because at
this point we might cancel tomorrow
[Music]
I wouldn't wake awaken why are you
cursed like that are you almost there
yes I am all right uh that one was from
honeydraws thank you so much
oh yeah we have um flight attendant kind
of outfit from ishki Zone thank you
thank you kids you put in my you copy
pasted my face in there it looks nice
beautiful wow and it's more than just
two chickens on the head this time I
like how they're all chilling up there
very cute so many variations of Jenkins
nice KLM I love KLM I guess it does make
me look a little bit okay A Lot really I
mean Caleb is definitely blue
um
but yeah flight attendant I guess
it's interesting that people many people
thought it might be a flight attendant
outfit I did have some flight attendance
stories until now and also a flight
attendant video last time I did an
outfit reveal
but is it really do you really think I'm
gonna get myself a flight attendant
outfit I mean it would be fun if it was
like I would maybe do it if I could do
if I could get outfits like five times a
year
but that ain't happening so I gotta be
like very very very careful with what I
choose if I if I could choose anything
and get as many outfits as I wanted then
yes
um but yeah please please continue to
drum in flight attendant outfits because
I like the idea for people who don't
know I once applied and was accepted as
a stewardess flight attendant to one of
the biggest Airlines at the best
airlines in the world
um and I was about to start working but
well something went wrong and then it
didn't happen but I would like to think
I like to think of the different
timeline where I became a flight
attendant yeah and then years later I
would have been [\h__\h] because of the
sea thing
uh and then be like [\h__\h] I have no work
left
let me pour in some more hot tea I have
a whole
jug
[Music]
yes t-a-smr
here we go that's probably too hot for
me to drink
so I gotta wait a little bit but I also
have water do you hear this raspiness
[Music]
um
what about this is this is now a little
bit more of a chill as we reveal the
small cookie Hannah
so now we're gonna have to happen I
never smoked a cigarette in my whole
life and I'm proud of it and I never
will
um
and we'll stay away from from it for the
end of my life
guys thank you
this is so funky James too
James to draw something for my outfit
reveals it's very funky and stands out
so much
wow very original maybe this is inspired
by the fact that I recently put out
femini tonight up there you see it
fibonac yeah are you streaming it please
listen to my new song favorite night
it's out on Spotify Apple music Amazon
music YouTube music Etc and iTunes and
you can also listen to it on YouTube the
music video is really really flashing
and nice and hot damn with a lot of cool
80s inspired outfits
um so this feels very funky too very
very funky maybe not exactly 80s I don't
know but maybe not some Inspirations
because like I don't know the fabric and
the the low-cut top here holy [\h__\h]
that's a very low cut you know I
wouldn't get this because YouTube
wouldn't allow it probably
also the purple lipstick is quite an
earring
quite difficult to rock something like
that and the hairstyle holy [\h__\h] what
happened to my hair
wow oh I like the stars in it though it
gave me a shortcut
a shortcut
cop lad
short
what I do like is the glasses and the
low-cut uh shirts I don't like it I wish
I could have that low cut
yeah nice nice nice nice very very nice
I'm gonna die help let's go
next one oh dear
five four five eight nine five one nine
gives us this version of all the live
summer
takanasikiwawa which feels very forced
because you still gave me a blazer
when you when you um are giving a
silhouette where someone is wearing a
jacket but you you really really
desperately want whole life summer to
happen for whole life English then this
is what happens
but
you made it into something original and
I like it
yeah
I mean I would not wear this to the
beach but
[Music]
but it feels like kind of like um
like
a skimpy
teacher outfit or something like that
like a cosplay like a sexy skimpy
teacher cosplay
I'm sorry that's not an I'm not saying
this as
an insult or anything
um but I mean come on
the tide
[Music]
it's what you learn for conference calls
yeah when this is the meme where like
when when you're when you're at the when
you're at the um when you wanna enjoy
your vacation until 3 P.M but have a
office Zoom call at 4 P.M or something
like that
thank you Ken next up we have Kumo G8
thank you I like this very much
it gives me Vibes of a girl who likes
Lolita and Harajuku fashion
um I love the bag
really really like the bag a lot I feel
like bags like that definitely exist
and once again pink not my favorite
color but I do like pastel colors and
combined with the contrast of black I
think it looks very nice now we gotta
speed it up oh my God how many more do I
have left I don't think so many
because are you okay thank you it's kind
of small but uh we have again something
kind of like uh uniformish
but with flower elements
so I wonder why you imagined me to wear
this I Wonder Maybe
[Music]
looks like something like a hotel
uniform oops it's like a hotel uniform
in a
um in a special I don't know honeymoon
hotel place I don't know
flight attendant again you think so
best girl at the wedding Vibe definitely
like some maybe like a wedding staff
member or something like that
yeah
nice so cute futuristic it does have a
few futuristic elements I agree with
that yeah
okay
I like how you like
used the art style of my hair and
implemented this into it
oh my I love that it looks so soft
you worked with my with my hair thank
you
now this is kind of like school girl
style from
Island Moon something like that
and different colors than from the
others we have a dark blue I like me
some dark blue school uniform very
classy but
um it seems like a school uniform for
um an expensive private school
yeah and a girl's only private school
[Music]
s thank you soon
next up we have another flight attendant
outfit
this one is more simple but you know if
I attendant wanna look serious very
orange so this is like kfp Airlines
um uh possible uniform
in the future from luti unders go under
bar underscore on the bar Lop thank you
ah Arc Hotel Concierge yes true I can
see that too
or I can see many things with this
because it's so simple so it has many
ways of using it underscore there we go
your Museum your tour guide or bus guide
[Music]
there's a from my favorite island group
there's a song about
um being a bus guide
and my favorite Idol group makes a lot
of weird songs
ah it's really cool I should show you
guys
[Music]
feel this tea is not good
but it said um that's 90 which is like
um Pharmacy something Dr T yeah so of
course you can't taste good
let's go next time
oh come on
this is like oh this is like the the
feminine teacher in the school that
everybody has a crush on or likes
everybody likes this teacher in school
this is from Milan and blood
yeah this this I can see like
this this teacher teaches probably
either
um art class or
um mother tongue class whatever it is in
your country
or I don't know maybe it's like you know
how I don't know if it's the same in
every country but
um we had like one teacher
um that teaches us a subject but also is
like the main teacher of the class who
takes care of the class and is there for
like anything
so I feel like this would be
this would be that kind of teacher yeah
or kindergarten yeah homeroom teacher
yes yes homeroom yeah yeah
oh sweet I want to meet this Kiana
oh and you made it into a fluffy Beret
[Music]
I love me Berets yeah I love the Blazer
the high waisted skirt with the belt the
blouse everything I like this
very girly teacher I like it if I were a
teacher I might I might wear this
love it
and ml0 L7
thank you for this also seemingly dandel
inspired uh outfit [\h__\h] I'm really
running all the time yeah it's okay it's
okay
um very cute I like the colors you gave
me the the turquoise uh apron that's you
know turquoise is one of my main colors
um
very cute and the hairdo I love the
brains
and you seemed to take the stockings
from my main outfit the default outfit
very pretty I love the pattern mmm thank
you
very very cute
and we're I think
[Music]
we're almost done
um so here we have again a very um
um toned down maybe like um spring
version and not spring uh fall Autumn
version you didn't see anything Autumn
version
um yes I like the colors I like dark
brown in Autumn I like to wear dark
brown and Autumn thank you soon m m m i
n underscore DK thank you I have to go
faster now this is obviously what I will
be revealing to you guys I'm a little
bit disgusted at the fact that you
combined pizza and uh Bolognese pasta
with [\h__\h] seafood crab hands evil
that's a no-go from me the rest is fine
but change the hands what the [\h__\h] the
meatball
the things that the top became meatballs
man
yummy now I'm getting hungry God damn it
thank you my dookie waifus next up we
have nor Chen's world or norcens world
thank you
uh wow this is like an idol
version of a candle I feel like I've
seen Idol outfits with like Blazers like
that I really like those
and then the stars in the pattern of the
main dress give me that Idol Vibe too I
like this idea yeah making an idolish
version of a dandel
definitely a good idea and and oh my God
the chickens at the top are wearing
leader who wasn't in a dandel too oh my
vacuum I love it one of my favorites
thank you and you got the the shape of
the dental with the the ribbons here
right good job
uh I think oh my God we're I think we're
almost there almost there a nice day
underscore r
this gives me
um
uh what's it what was it again the Alice
game that we played
this gives me those vibes for some
reason
I'm not sure if it's the art style or
the outfit
but nice spice yes
[Music]
castle for rice and no I don't see
Taylor rise in this or find them no no
no no no no no no no
steampunk yes no I don't mean signal
Alice the ass game that we played on my
channel oh well anyway yeah yeah I like
the style steampunk very edgy uh some
armor some actual armor going on here
wow with the I like the rose pattern on
it very cool nice and you made the thing
at the top into roses not many people
made it into something besides oh yeah
Alice madness Returns yes uh into
something besides chicken so Props to
you
uh next we have sign underscore zero two
five thank you
I love this
this is actually so cute
this is like
uh
so cute
Harajuku Style
I don't know how to describe it cute
cute cute cute baby baby colors I love
it
and Shojo I like the art style it's so
Shojo I love it
and and and and and I don't know I don't
know what to say anymore I don't know I
love it so much I don't have I can't
explain why it's like like uh what do
you call those parties that you throw
when someone gets a baby
maybe party
maybe this this is what I would wear to
that
love it thank you everyone
we're ending it with this one Shu dong
coyote Hawaii branch opening try the new
tropical Banana's Burger this is
foreshadowing the future thank you very
much I hope these are not spaghettis
oh
now everybody we don't have time so
please um watch this video
[Music]
[Applause]
so how was your first day so far
what do you mean it's perfectly safe
it's a relatively safe day here for us
questions fine you really want to know
why just look at her look at her
what's wrong with you look at that tummy
the legs
foreign
[Music]
yes and you don't think this is a
problem listen here you little [\h__\h]
being able to see Kiana and that outfit
is worth everything okay
[Music]
[Applause]
how's it going my fellow gym girl you
seem to be doing very well you haven't
got promoted to the supervisor afternoon
like three months
what's wrong
what do you mean getting worse
production is the highest it has ever
been
[Music]
something yeah and then their packages
sold to our customers it's popping the
circle of life
[Music]
she's the one true Queen she's Our
Savior she will guide us to true
happiness
[Music]
foreign
injuries
reduce
what the [\h__\h] since when did we provide
insurance
they're supposed to be
supposed to pay you'll pay me so that
you're allowed to work for me yeah this
is why I haven't been receiving anybody
from my bank account don't worry the
money is put to very good use
junkers
oh
I am being serious smoothie and tonkers
are my life and soul
s
we can always recruit more
solution fine the one that you propose
since you think you're so smart
[Music]
like what a bunny suit
I will hurt you
okay fine basically something that shows
less skin right is that what you're
saying
[Music]
how are those standard office clothing
that you see the ladies wearing at work
[Music]
[Applause]
it is let's go
oh
office
let's
take a look then
Sean Lee
okay
hi
[Music]
there we don't have time so let me
reveal this
we start from uh
[Music]
that's it am I doing this correctly yes
okay
[Music]
oh
and this is octaws
with white painted nails
so this means
uh no tights no socks
oh oh
[Music]
we have some pinks some blues looks like
pastel else Castle colors
there we go nice ankles beautiful ankles
wow you want to see more
Hot Tomato
[Music]
make myself a bit smaller than
now it looks like I'm wearing like a
leggings or something white leggings
[Music]
legs legs legs beautiful Chihuahua legs
wow
actually yeah
this stage
hi commissioned recently
to get it in time for dokumi
but maybe that wasn't my only intention
to use it only for dopamine maybe they
were more intentions
[Music]
now this this is this is the important
part
all right whoops I'm gonna cut off here
maybe it's time to uh
oh yeah
you saw
[Music]
so much for office attire
uh let's stay a little bit closer okay
[Music]
what kind of office where's that
yeah
looks like an apron
turquoise green color cream we haven't
seen much before on kibawa
oh now I want to say beforehand I
explained to hooky Papa the thing about
the ribbons it seems like he has
misunderstood me
um but let's just say that I am married
to my audience my chicks because when
the ribbon is on the side that it's
currently on it means that you're
married and if it's on the other side it
means that you're single
uh so it seems like there was a
miscommunication
[Music]
um but I don't think it's something that
can be fixed at this stage so
yeah
um anyway that's okay
all right uh wait um Let me let me pull
this down more here we go
[Music]
wow oh [\h__\h] damn it why did I do that
okay I'm coming down
[Music]
it's a blazer
what I can't take it off guys [\h__\h] it's
not moving the same way
I can take it off guys but so please
wait it's even cuter when I don't wear
it
[Music]
[Laughter]
are you feeling the The Vibes now are
you getting the theme now I Bamboozled
you I brought both of you
[Music]
okay never trust your boss
you've been quite possibly bamboozled
all right all right let's see more
nice ribbons nice corset you know what
is very important for dental
it's the boobs the boobs
I'll be honest here the focus is on the
boobs
oh
don't look
so long okay
ah what choice do I have
Bobby Bobby is
[Music]
please by the way I post screenshots and
tweet about it with hashtag kfb or
hashtag
[Music]
oh my god oh
what buff
looking respect yeah I would hope so
[Music]
after all look at where my ribbon is at
okay we're getting closer to the face
but before we go to the face I want to
show you that I can take off the the
jacket and maybe something else
[Music]
you wanna see the no jackets
wow
cute it gets cuter though it gets cuter
[Music]
wow
yeah I have some head poses as you might
have noticed
I'm so embarrassed on you on you
here I go
here I go wait I'll come a bit closer
[Music]
come a bit closer
okay wow
face reveal thanks
[Music]
hello hello hello
I'm cute
[Music]
so embarrassing
made the ribbon on the wrong side but
please don't misunderstand
shock
shocker
wow impressive later hosen you got there
my friend would you like to go eat some
pretzels pretend with me
okay
now wait there's more
but wait there's more
so we can do this with the Blazer too of
course and we can change I requested
[Music]
a Korean heart pose this is a hard pose
that they do in Korea yeah do you see
the heart shave cute
[Music]
um
cute this neck very cute isn't it now I
can also take off the flowers and the
Joker and the birds if you want but I
think having all of this on looks the
best but in theory I can do this on your
naked neck oh no no no no we don't want
that no no but I can take up this or I
can pick up the hair decoration but I
love the one of the flowers so that was
not a nest guys it was flowers yes
you want to see everything together
this is the reason why I wanted it to
make it in time for
um for docomi because docomo is in
Germany and you know traditional outfit
oh wait there's still an announcement so
wait for that but here I am in my full
form
[Music]
yes this is the real deal yeah I wanted
it to be close
um or like as close as possible to like
a traditional one and so it's a little
bit lengthy but I hope you like it still
got the beautiful blue window
oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] I'm not
fine for you
[Music]
okay wait now it's kind of too late but
um
I can't do this
sorry
well so how about we do the announcement
now
I'll announcement will be something
related to all of this
yeah you didn't see anything no no no no
no
What could
[Music]
well for a while now
it seems like I've had kind of kind of a
monopoly over Europe uh the European
streaming times and whole life
and sometimes you guys also ask me to
speak more German and to be honest I
don't know I don't wanna and even like
doing like German streams feels
embarrassing and
but I also don't want to fill up my
Channel with that so in any case I
decided how about we separated
[Music]
German Channel open now yes
I have created a sub Channel where I
will every you now and then
I'm gonna stream in German or upload
videos in German uh Clips or
translations perhaps as well and so
that's why I I am why there's this cute
art with the German flags Austrian flag
Germany flag I'm from Austria doll yeah
don't make no mistakes
and I think manager's son is gonna put
it up on the chat and pin it is a pen
is it paint yet
you can already subscribe now I'm
currently kind of busy so there might
not be a stream immediately uh or a
video immediately but look forward to it
by subscribing you might want to call it
the whole live de but no don't call it
that because I didn't get um official
permission to call it that but it is a
German channel so it won't be used for
anything German and if you can't speak
German then well you might still want to
subscribe because it's exclusive content
and you might learn some German there
who knows thank you yes yes but I
thought you know with all the tokomi
appearances of me you know is a German
convention and I've been to like two
times now
um I thought it might be nice to like
um bring a bit more
of my you know German knowledge uh to
the world to Holiday fans and all that
there's not a big audience German
speaking audience but
um I don't know I still wanted to maybe
make use of that a little bit even
though I personally feel kind of
embarrassed about it
um but yeah here's again no Blazer
version
[Music]
anyway
and you know I really wanted to handle
for a long time now and we made it
happen it's like very personal to me
um yeah because it's from my country
so I hope you guys like it I'll be using
it a lot in the future
it's so cute I love the flowers ah I
didn't take off the birds yet did I
here this is like uh oopsie this is
without everything I guess wow I look I
look very normal like this no no beer
man because I don't drink alcohol
I could be serving it to you I guess but
yeah no no no alcohol
what's your favorite without the flowers
I love the flowers I think the flowers
make it very very cute and the birds of
course they have to be up there they're
more than before it used to be only one
up there now there's two oh my God
they're multiplying
[Music]
so we can do a collable in general
outfits
[Music]
which is well maybe maybe Kotori has uh
a girlfriend boyfriend now
[Music]
yes all right guys it's already been
over an hour hope you guys enjoyed this
uh outfit reveal and my new outfit and
please post your screenshots on Twitter
thank you very much for watching I will
have to see what to do about tomorrow
you know what I'll sleep at night and
then decide what to do when I wake up if
my throat feels better or worse we'll
see about that
much for your supply and everybody I'll
also be doing a Super Chat rating on
Monday perhaps So yeah thank you very
much for the support and I hope you will
also be supporting my new channel the
German Channel yeah it will not be used
every day but I would like to do some
content there every now and then yeah
and maybe with that we can grow the
audience in german-speaking countries I
will do my best
[Music]
I know that you guys all know what we
say in German right you know
I think you know it very well
and in Germany
[Music]
he's somewhere cute cute poses oh
yay
[Music]
love you guys love you very much
lava
[Music]
okay I'm out of here I'm out of here
foreign
[Music]
messages thank you thank you guys
seem like you're still typing messages
so I'll keep it open for a little bit
[Music]
thanks for the sweet words
yeah I'm so happy you like it happy I
can kind of like represent my culture
like this yeah
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
sweetest
most cutest Community ever I'm so proud
of you guys so proud of what I've
created
[Music]
oh please drop banners
I want to say that earlier
now they're gone please drop fan art I'm
gonna post pngs too
on Twitter
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
people while they're still riding the
Super Chat messages they're still coming
in
I don't want to interrupt them in the
middle of a long message
you guys done
are you see saying the long message is
still coming in I don't want it to be
like sorry sumima sorry this stream is
over and you're like [\h__\h] I I was
thinking so long about what to write I
wrote this whole paragraph
now it's canceled
[Music]
I think I think you guys are mostly done
okay
my beloved Simpkins and yes
um
don't don't take the the position of the
ribbon too seriously
I really told him I said I think the
problem was I said on the right side is
where the ribbon needs to be but I meant
from my point of view right side not
from your point of view
oh man I even explained the reason
because yeah if you don't know uh
yeah
right side for my Bonneville is single
then what was that I think in the back
means you're you have your um what's the
word your husband died
uh what's the word forgot and then left
side is and take Mary taken
I think there was a middle one too I
forgot
a widowed Anna wait the middle is
widowed and the back was waitress or
something I don't know
but in any case right and left very the
very important
[Music]
it's confusing me too
it's on your right side yeah I mean and
then I mean the other way I don't know
I'm confused I mean the other way
I mean oh man
uh DeAnda
right button
there we go
yeah on the side this is currently at
means I'm taken
I'm thinking
with
um buy my job and buy my beautiful
chickens yes I am very busy and taking
care of my beautiful chickens oops it
myself yes yes
yeah yeah
and my cats yeah
married to me specifically now
no
I'm married to The Entity
of whole life members in chat and the
jaws and everything as an entity how
about them
trying to make excuses you know
[Music]
oh
all right and I will stop talking until
tomorrow hopefully gets better bye-bye
[Music]
tomorrow
stream Astro girl