[Music]
Y
OGOG
[Music]
Everyone, Koko Azuki and Kikkeriki
Kikerikikiki Kikerikī So today's
Amogester is our guest Chiara-
chan Yay, yay, hello to
all the KFP members too
Kikkerikki Koazuki Azuki-
senpai, after all, we're home  It's crunchy, it
's crunchy, it's crunchy I wonder if it's true I won't be able to get
in. It's okay, it's not going to come in. I'm streaming it.
But you're looking at OBS, it
's amazing, it's moving smoothly, but I'm the
one who feels like the camera is really choppy, but it's
true, it's like, oh yeah, it's better to stand up, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no.
Oh, yes, yes,
yes, yes. Oh, Papa, I'm sorry, Papa, and in the meantime, what are we going to do today? Yes, I
'd like to talk to Chiara about what we're going to do today.  I'm going to
adjust the camera a little bit to see if we can see it together.
Today, it's Geo Guesser.
Thank you, Overseas World Tour Ost.
So, today we have
Chiara from Austria, who is from Austria, visiting Austria.  I'm
really looking forward to traveling. Traveling in Australia. Hey, I'm really sorry.
What's going on with what I said earlier?
Hey everyone, that's right today.  I've
said it for a moment, but I
'm not from Australia.Sorry, Lee.Yes, it's not Australia, it's Austria.Thank you
.
Okay,
okay, so Australia and
Austria are similar, but what do you think
about this? It's like Chiara-chan. If people
mistake Austria for Australia, it's
like they don't even exist.
Well, I wonder what it's like in Japan.  is
often mistaken. When I
say that I'm from Australia, people
always say that it's amazing Australia, so that
's true, but it's a completely different place. It's
far away, but
Australia is a big island near Japan.  Austria is a
country in the middle of Europe that speaks German,
and I'm from Mozart, and there
's no sea in the area, so it's landlocked to begin with.Austria is very
connected to many countries,
but that's how it is today.
Can I ask you for some information on Austria? Yes, I've
been looking into it. I want to know. It
's about the size of Austria, but it's about the size of Hokkaido in Japan,
so it's about the size of Hokkaido.
Everyone, please remember the size. It's
a little embarrassing to receive it.
So why is it so
big? I want to know how big it is. It's
small, but it's
fine, but Hokkaido is big.
That's right, but it's about that size, and 60
% of it is Alps 300, making it a mountainous country.It
has a rich natural environment.That's
right, that's right,
that's right.  But
Mozart, the capital of music, and a
place called Jesus, which is frozen, are the capitals.Win is the city.Yes,
Win is the city.Eun,
everyone has heard of it.
Well, Mozart
's songs and Utobe's songs are famous
and I think everyone knows them, but they were made in
Makoto, which is an amazing country.Molto
is my friend, Kira-chan, my friend.
Yes, I've lived a long time because I'm not a mayor,
but Molton was my best friend.He
was a strong, strong prankster, and Momiji
spoke German.
Today, I'm sure you'll see a lot of German words on signs and
in all sorts of places.Yes, I
wonder what the word German actually is.It seems like a
lot of dialects are being used.So,
if you're in a slightly different place, the
words you say are also different.  I heard that it's like the Kansai dialect.There
's a dialect in Japan, but there's also a dialect in Austria.When
I was going to school, I wonder what that was.  When I
went to the same school with kids from really rural areas, and they talked,
sometimes I couldn't understand what they were saying.But you know,
even in Japan, there are people who say things that are really difficult,
so yeah, it's the same in all countries.  So,
different countries have dialects.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, but with this, it's pretty
easy to
tell which one is German and which one is Australian. Listen.
The pronunciation, the intonation, the pronunciation, the intonation,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, that's right. Well, you won't understand unless you say it, but I guess you can all speak English pretty well, right? Well, this is
really only true in Australia.  I
think it's the same in Germany, and
in most countries in the center of Europe, I
think everyone can speak English, but in addition to their native language, they can
definitely speak English, so they study English.
Yes, yes, it's true, yes, at school. The
teaching methods are good.
Yes, everyone can speak English, German, and English. That
's amazing. The
education in Austria is amazing. Yes, it's
possible after Germany.  Even if you don't have that,
by all means, if you go to that pickpocket, you'll be able to communicate in English,
so I'm sure you'll feel at ease.Yes, I've been looking into
that candy, and that Sachertorte in
Austria is the blood that caused the Sachertorte.  I've
been looking into it, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
but I've eaten
that Sachertorte in Japan, and I think there are some restaurants that
put a lot of effort into desserts.  It's
chocolate, isn't it? Chocolate, oh yeah,
it's chocolate cake with apricot jam in the middle.
But I'd like to try this authentic food someday.You
know, when I lived in Japan,
that 7-Eleven temporarily
served Zahatre as a dessert.  The
taste is just so
different.It was close, but it was different, so it was similar, but it
was so different.There
was a time when Starbucks was selling something like that.Starbucks
' Harte was 100% different.  I
guess I've changed a lot to make it more palatable to Japanese people.I
see.I see.I see, I'm feeling a little unwell today,
and I feel like I'm feeling uneasy,
but I have faith that things will get better.
Can you all hear me? Can you hear me?
Chiara, I'm not feeling well today. I'm
starting to get stuttery. Don't
worry, I'm starting to stutter. Yeah, I haven't changed any settings, but it's okay. Husband, it's
okay. It's better than standing there.
Yes, I'm sure if I go to Depachika, I might
be able to find Haru there.Oh, I see.
Well,
that's what I'm going to do today. I'd like to go around Austria with Chiara-chan
on Geo Guesser.
Thank you, Chiara-chan.
Thank you very much.  I would like to start with where I will go out.
Then, the start of the game
start Kira -chan is also seeing the same screen.  It's
like, no, I
tried the Austrian version, but it
's really annoying every time, so it's a little boring.But
everyone, it's the first time I've seen that Japanese person,
so I waited a long time and
looked at this bus station.  Look, what's this
written on Shimoda? Oh, I
don't know, but if you try hard, you'll see this.
Buses running in the city go back once, go
back once, and see that reflection of this bus station.
Who do you think they are? I don't know what kind of people they are.
Yeah,
they're great. No, these two are famous comedians from Oria.
Oh, they're comedians. It's
funny. For comedians, they're wearing suits. They're
kind of royal.  Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm
laughing at that old story about Austria.
But that guy on the left looks like a tsukkomi and the one on the right looks
like an idiot.
He's actually a famous comedian. Yeah, that's pretty funny.
Yeah, it's interesting, I'm
curious about that place, or rather, Austria.What
makes people laugh?Oh yeah,
yeah, yeah, what kind of bus is this?
Ah, but there's a Chinese restaurant here,
China.  There's a lot of restaurants, there
's culture from many different countries, there's a subway,
there's a subway, there's a subway,
uuuu, that blue, blue, coming soon
mark, oh, here, I can see it, I do
n't really understand this station, but I don't know.  I
see, left, right, left, left, left, right, it looks like it's going to be a bit of a mess. Look to the right, is this the entrance? Go back and go back once. Yes, why did you
cover that hard gas with hard gas?
Where is it? But this is the
subway.  When I say city, where in Vienna does it
run? Well, it runs all over the place, so I'm
looking for the number everywhere, but that's not written down
.  That
looks like a subway, a subway,
this looks like a bus, but if you go a little to the right, you'll find
this, and that park on the bottom left. It looks like a
park. I wonder if there's a park here and there too.
No, oh, oh, it's difficult. That
's right, it's different.  Ordinary train Ordinary train Waiting is difficult
Ordinary train There is no subway running near the ordinary train
Right here, without moving, use the mouse to
go up a little, go to the upper left,
and on the left there is a U. To the left, a little more to the left.
This is the subway mark.This is the subway mark.The
underground mark in Suria is written as U.That
's right, if you look for it, you'll find this.  It's
not the end or the beginning, but yeah, there's nothing beyond this, I'm going to go down, I'm going to go down, I'm going to go down, I'm probably going to go down, yeah, but this is probably not the center, and it has to be that U2.  I
think, oh wait, there are quite a lot of U's.Kouuu,
yeah, yeah, yeah, but somewhere, etc. You
shouldn't use them,
right? If you give me some hints in the comments, is there a
risk?  Let's go a
little bit further.This
is a really important hint.Let's just go around this subway station
a little more.Let
's go around it.Well, we've come all the way, so when we come to this big road, it's that big road.
No, it would be helpful if you could understand the difference between different medicines and different functions.Akanai
There are many things like Meguro Shokudo in that Tokyo.If you
understand Janunkuku, then I can understand.It's
easy to understand, but it's divided from here.I think it's
good, I think it's good.This
place has become a rotary.  Let's go out
here, let's go to the left, let's go to the left, go here,
okay, anywhere is probably okay,
but senpai, when we're going around like this, I
remember where it all started, somehow.
But somehow this time there's a station, so it's
like a school next to the station. My first goal is to go
to the ground. There's a normal
train running, too. Yeah, I'm sorry.
Look behind me.  That blue building, poop,
yeah, Austria, write the address properly, it
's the 22nd ward, the 22nd ward, the 22nd ward, yeah,
so try opening the map one more time, yes, it's supposed to be
22, so it's once.  Zoom
out and be near the river a little above. Uno.
[Music]
192019 Oh, that's not it. I do
n't think Unku is here in the first place. What are these numbers?
What is 2222?  I wonder if I did. Well,
it's probably across the river or across the street from 22.
But yeah, yeah, I guess I should
check out all the subway stations around there.  I do
n't remember if this is the way to go.
No, I don't think it's that far away.
There's a possibility that it's a little closer.
Yes,
it's a
normal train.  That's right.
Ordinary trains also pass by.
Ordinary trains have this mark. Ordinary trains.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I guess.
Yeah, that's right, here it is. You're
wrong about Leopolda.
Hmm, it says 22 here.
Well, 2022, 22
steps. It's
not that close, but there wasn't any greenery either.
That liquid looks pretty big.
Hey, I tried to pick it up, and there it is.
A little further to the right is something. To the
right,
down, down, down, there's a subway here as well. That's the
first station.
Arase, I wonder if it's a baba. It was Air Air. I remember Hade. It was like that. It was like that.
Hade, I remember it very well. I
remember it. This is still different, but here's what I remember.  Side, I'm
not bald. Yes, I'm bald. Oh,
there, there, there,
Owazuki-senpai's free game.
Yeah, this is the normal train.  That's
right, that's right. Haha,
once I
got home, I was home, and if I could go back like that, it wasn't here. I
just came here and there
was that bus station on the left and right.  I heard that there
was a school there, yes, there was a fukusire,
and there was also a restaurant in China that said "Fukusire Maria Freedon",
but I wonder if it's the same here or here.
Go back and look at it once. I
want to know the name of this school. Ah, it's the school's name. School,
ah, I can't read it. Ah, I wonder if that's wrong. It's not there. It's
a little bit further on. Ah, here, the name is
written. It's written there.
Yeah, I'm graffitiing it.
What's that name
? I wonder where the school came from. It looks
like this here, but
there's also a school in the bottom left corner.
There's a restaurant here, right here.  Maybe  It's
called Usendofstrasse, which looks like this. It's
in the back. I see, it's
here. Oh, it's here. It looks like this. Yes, it's
wrong. Okay, this isn't a school. It's not a school.
This isn't a school.
[Music]
Pooh, this is the name of the school, the name of the school, it
's in that town,
it's
here, it's the supermarket, it's all different
Ah, uh, this is uh, uh, uh.
Well, it's a hospital. It's a hospital,
but it's around here. And
then there's my house. There's a Chinese restaurant here. I wonder
if the name of this town is somewhere. I
wonder if it's attached to my famous house.  This is attached to the house Oh
yes, this is here, this is here, this is
it, that's it. That's the address. This is the address of this house. Wow, that's how the name is written. I see, yes, this is what it is, so this is it. 1
1Kono 12Koremoppo 1
[Music]
Ah, I wonder where 44 is. I
can't see it, and I can't even see the name of the house,
but there's a road in front of it,
so I guess it's here.  A road, a road, oh, it
looks like this, it looks like this,
yeah, this is a road, is this a road?  I
wonder if I'm going to the 12341223rd place.I feel like it
might be that car.It's not the right road, so it's one place ahead on the map.Yes,
this is small, so this small
road to the right is small, so it's behind.  Oh, there's a road, it's
so big, it's
this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this,
this, this is this, this is this road, this is that big road, this is that big
road, okay, that's it.
Just this way, yes, yes, yes, here's the road.It's
amazing how you do it in such detail.I didn't do it in such detail.Okay, then
this is the bicycle path.Okay
, no, no, okay, let's
do it here.Let's go.  Let's go.
Well, I'd like to be the first guest with Chiara-chan. She's a
professional, so she's a professional. Really,
Ade. Maybe there's a possibility of going this way.  What do you think?
It's okay, it's okay, I'm going. It's okay, I'm going. Let's go. Let's go. It's okay. It's okay. It's
fine. It's okay. Then next time, this will be a bad result for Aki-senpai. No, I'll get
5,000 points.  I want to
get 5,000 points in Austria, so
let's do our best to be 5 ahead of Ki-chan. But Kia-chan
has given us a lot of amazing information, and here we are.  I've
arrived at the subway here, too. I
understand, and yes, it's amazing, but it's the
center of the city. Also, there
's always a sign on the building, so it's
written there.  That number at the beginning of Win
should be K. Okay,
I'd like to go to the next one.
Mt. Nekie, oh, it's so beautiful. There's a beautiful mountain
spreading out there, but I think we can move on to N.
Hey, Igi-chan, that's nice.  It's beautiful I like it
Okay, I
feel like I've been there before, too. Ah, I feel like there's a place there. Ah
Siamgas, the name of the place Siamgas. My name
is Mi's name. It's so detailed, I don't know.
Oh, isn't there an address written down? No, please write it down.
No, what kind of shop is this? Ah, a
shop that makes windows. I wonder if it's a shop that makes windows. Okay, yeah, but
this place is beautiful, the house is cute, and this is
pretty Australian. Yeah, yeah, it's European. It's
full of people.  I
've heard that if you go all the way north, there's a good chance you'll only get a 90% chance of winning,
but even if that's the case, it might be a little outside of that, or it
might be right next to that.
What's up with the expressway? Ah, it certainly looks
like an expressway.
Yes, the cityscape is beautiful. Please come and visit us.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I got it, I got it, it's a lie, I get it, it's
all around Salzburg.Salzburg That's probably
true, Hallein is close to Puch.I heard it's
all about the cities I've heard
of before.Salzburg Salz is actually Salzburg.Salzburg is inside
Salzburg.I understand.Salzburg
For example, there is a Salzbrok in the Kansai area called the Salzbrok.  The
name Ku is Salzburg in Salzburg. I do
n't know, but it's something
like that. Yeah, yeah, it's like that, but what is this called
Salzburg? It's
not a city, it's a countryside, it's difficult to live in the countryside.
No Salzburgsi.  It's so bad that it's coming. It's
so bad. It's so well known. But it looks
like all the place names are Ad Ad Net Annette Pof Ova. I wonder if it's Oberarm or Hallein University. Which one is the main one?
Let's open the map once inside the city. Let's go to Salzburg. OK, you
can see the Hallein a little above. Eh, a little up, up
, left, left, right. After this, now, right now, where
the mouse was, there was the Hallein. Over
there, down, down, down.  I'm going to go down, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right.
Which way does 2.1km go
Wait, wait, Oba was the closest
0.7km Oh yes, that's
right Ober Am is there,
so which one is Ober Im?  If you
look in this direction, what
direction is it? That's why Oberam is in the west-west direction.
Hey, 700m, it's around here, wait,
wait, there
was no high-speed buck here earlier.  I'm
not around here. I
don't know, but I wish there was a river. Is there a river?
Or can I see the river?
Hmm, it would be nice to have access to the expressway.
Wait, go home once, then go back there.
Now let's go to the other side and see that it's pretty far from the center. Now that I've got a rough idea of ​​the center, I
think it will help if I look at the names of the towns and roads, so let's go a little bit to the
south and look at the river, ah,
line, here, here.  It's
here, it
's that, it's that, it's that, it's that border, it's border border, it's border border, it's
somewhere, it's border, it's there, it's there, it's there, it's
there.
So, yeah, is
there a border? Is there a border? Is there a border written? What do you write?  I wonder if there's an address posted.
Oh, I see. There's a river there, but wait, I'll put it on the bridge right now. It's
between Oba and Hein. It's
here, so there's a river on the bridge.
Well, it's not this big skin,
it's different, it's different, it's different, it's different, it
's a small one, it's this moopa, it's this, it's
like this river, it's this, it's
exciting, I'm excited, I
might be there.  It
's small and skin-like, but it
looks like this, but wait a minute, but how is it
facing?S ah, it's a little different in shape, yeah
, it's between the hare line and the overeye.It's in that river, it's in this river.  Let's
go a little further. Yeah, I
want you to look at the address of the Hallein building over here. It's
the address. The address is right here. It's on the side of this building. I wonder if it's
here. Hmm, that
blue one on the right. Wait a minute.  Little read
Hey read
Hey, I can't read it, it might be Hamata
Hamas 6 That's mahama
Chis this but wait A but that
's fine Oh yeah the shop is here Ohhh the
shop
It's a big road,
so it's a big river, oh
, it's true, it's true, you already know it
.
Yes, store name
Yes, there's a roundabout all the way here.
This map is a sign. Yes,
Efra. It's big. It's huge.
Wait, it's obvious. It looks like this place, yes, yes, yes.
[Music]
Yes, it's dangerous, it's dangerous here, it's humming, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's
here, it's
here, it's here, it's
over here, it's right here, yeah yeah, yeah, that's what it's about.
Wait, there's one house here and another one
here, this looks like this, that parking lot
is here, oh this is this restaurant
parking lot,
by the way, this is a booth pavilion.  It's a
restaurant called Sausé's Aso. I
wonder what it's called
Pavilion. It's a pavilion. I don't know, but I eat resuscitated people. Yeah, it's
not all-you-can-eat, but yeah, it's a special restaurant. It's a
special restaurant, but it says Meaku. It's
another restaurant.  Mekmekmerk with the name written on it.
Yeah, that super supermarket. It's
like a supermarket, but it
may have changed. From this photo,
yes, it seems that it has changed unexpectedly.
Well, this is probably this house.  I
think this is this house, so I crossed the river a little while
ago.Here, I crossed it.Here, this, this.Let's
go to this river, that's it.Oh,
let's go, let's go, let's go, let's
go.
Shiwa I
did it. I want to get 5000 points 00m too.
0 This is fine. This is fine.
This time other than Mosaun, it's Zasalzburg.
Salzburg, Salzburg, Salzburg, Salzburg, Salzburg, Salzburg, Salzburg, Salzburg, Salzburg,
Salzburg, Salzburg, Salzburg, Salzburg, Salzburg.
Salzburg Yes, this
is also where Salto was born, and this is where famous songs
were born. Yes, yes, this is where famous songs were born.  It seems that
it is so good
that it is like Zenoga Yes Yes Yes Yes
Yes, I understand that the correct pronunciation is
Salzburg
Salzburg Salzburguii
Yay, no Moreranot
is no Morella no
Nobu, and I
feel like a famous song will be born.  Okay,
yeah, I'd like to go next time.
Let's go. Let's go again. It'll be Un again. This time, it'll
be Un. A more Un. A more Un. This bus is
running on Un.  I
don't know if there's a bus, but wait, wait, I don't know. Maybe it's different. But,
wait, there's room at the station. Oh, what's the
name of the one who used it? I can't see the name.
There's a bus, and there's a station.
Yeah, this is a big station, this amazing station building, it's
cool, hehe, it's pretty normal.
hand  It's
just the destination. Is it written in this?
Yes, yes, here, this, yes, Hadestrov.
Human center Hadestrov. I don't know Hades.
Dorf, Hadesdorf. Hades Doaf.
There's also a station called Hadesdorf Hades Station.
First Subway Railway Amo Station.  Right,
hmm, where is Hardestorff?
Let's find out. Let's find out. What
's this to the east? This is a huge
soccer team. Oh, it
might be the stadium. Oh, Gapi.
Well, I don't know anything about soccer at all,
but Gapi is a very famous team.It's an
Austrian team.It's a professional soccer team from Osua.Yes, if you
knew soccer, you
might be able to find the location using this.This is
home.Home is W.Yes, I know.  I wonder if there are people who
like it or not.
Stadion Ariane
Stadion Yeah, this was Un. That's
right, the name of the team. The name of the team. I see.
Rapid Un. I've definitely heard that word before. It's
huge. After all, it's soccer.
If it's like a stadium, it's definitely un.
But there are various things, but if you go here, you can
go to Linz.
Linz inside Winn. Yeah, Linz outside Winn.
Linz
outside Linz. Yeah, sorry about that.  Eh, look to the left Please, here
is the cat's blue 14th ward.
14th ward. This is Win's 14th ward, KK bra. Yeah, yeah, can we
go? How about Win in the 14th ward?  I wonder
how many wards there are from Nokonosa 1 to 23.
23 It's the same as Tokyo, but it's mostly made of that velvet water.
But to be
honest, I seriously don't know. 14 Where is it?
14 It looks cool.  12345678 Are
n't you going around in circles?
There's always a name in that number for 14. Is it
okay to look it up
? I'm going to look it up.
That's right, PEnz
in, huh, zoom out a little bit. It's
all right, uhm.
Marine Ado Serin
[Music]
Fabrifu Eh, somewhere.
This one was 22 just now, right? That's
22. There's only 2321 here.
2021222 Yeah.  That's the only option, so
it's either that or that side.  No, yeah, that's
right, Penten, ah, the stadium, too
, right there, wait, wait, over there, right
here on the left, right, right, right here, it's a lie, oh, it's a
huge stadium, it's right here, it's Kapits, it's over there where it
says Kapitskapits, it's right
here, it could be Debichertov or that big station.  This is
the station from just now, it's amazing, it
's huge, it's amazing, it's this
famous place, which way is it coming from?  I
feel like it's somewhere around here.I'm going.Then I'm going to
go home once.That's right
here.That means this road is here.Aaaaaah, oh, that's
where it all started.I see, it looks
like this here.The road coming in here is like this.
This is definitely a complicated road.It's a complicated road, and the
back is going to be here too, right? Rota,
yes, yes, here.
Oh, come in here. Come in here.
0 Can I make it? Hey, it's
written here as well.
Let me pull it. Oh, I'm sure there's a road going up there.
Getty, it
's true. Wait, can I go there?  I wonder how
long it will take. I'm already on my way to this path. Well, this is about it. It's a detailed work. It's a detailed work. But that's about it. I'm really
going to
go. I can't go here.  I'm
nervous about this front or here. I want it to be zero. I want it to be like this.
Then let's go. Let's go. Ose's guess. Wow.
Even lower. 5000 points. Yay.
Yay. Yay. Yay. That one.
If you ignore it, it's 0m. If you ignore 1, it's 0.
Well, it's 0. If you ignore it, it's 0.
So, let's go to the next one.  I've
never seen a map of Australia so detailed.
Really, where is this? There's something that looks like a castle over there.
But there are so many mountains here. It's so
cool. This, this,
this.  What about the house that everyone lives in
? Yes, they're
doing a market market.
Let's take a look at the Makibiun building. What is it? Yes, it's
2020. The 2020 ward is the 20th ward.
This is a Panya-like
role. I
knew it, of course.  I knew  I
'm 20, but 21 was here earlier, so I
wonder if it's this way, or maybe it's closer.Let's go and look a little more.Yes,
yes, yes.Yes, yes, yes.It
doesn't necessarily mean that it's close.It doesn't necessarily mean that the number is nearby.
Even though it's nearby, it's really amazing. There
are a lot of markets.
Hmm,
but there are quite a lot of shops. I wonder if
there's a station near the station.  It seems like it's
going to happen, right now, just go straight, yeah, yeah, that train, that's right, yeah, that's
right.  That
means there's a station, right? Well,
there's a station for this car, right? Well, there's a station for this car. No, it's not
really a pharmacy. This is a pharmacy.
Yeah, there are a lot of stylish buildings, so there's a
possibility that there are people living above the drugstores,
so there's a lot of shops on the first floor and
houses on the first floor.Heheako.  I
can't help but wonder where this station is.It's a
tram station.Where's the place to get off?It
seemed like
there was a place to get off.That big, big difference.  There's a
big thing, there's that left, that's right, that's
right, look to the left, go back once, go back, go back, go
back one more time, go back too far, oh no, it's
gone too far, left and left, yeah,
it's there too, that left
there.  It's all over here, right here,
right, right here, right here, right, right here, right there, right there, but what do you
mean
?  There are
already quite a lot of areas where streetcars run. I wonder
if there are quite a lot of them, so maybe it's hard
to narrow it down, but there are already quite a few. Wow, I
could see this from the back earlier.  This is it Oh, I
understand.
Also, the bus station is the bus station. The bus
station is red, right, right, right.  mosquito
Well, let's move on, Kuma, the bear is the bear, the
bear is protecting the egg It's true, it has the egg
What does that mean
?  Yeah, 20 But just now, it
's 2020, right? 20
wards, 20 wards, 20 wards, 20 wards. It's still
20 wards. Right, 20. 20. Ah, I identified it once on the map.
Oh, it's here, ah, Igasus U2, ah, U6U66
Gastayu 6 is Yu 6, you know, you know,
oh, it's running from the other side of that river,
oh, it's running from the other side of the river, so the 20th arrondissement is
near here on the river.  But yeah, I found it. I
found a beech. Eh,
just hover over the mouse, top left, yeah, right.
This is pretty okay. This area is Brigitte.
So this is Yuyu here.  Let's
look for Yuigashi, right? But Yunoyu,
Yuyua, it was warm, left, center
right now, it was in the middle.
Where did that come from? Well, this is far away
.  It's quite a
big intersection, and it's quite a big intersection.  The bear
's name is also written here. It's written there. It's got a bear's name on it. It's sitting. It's
sitting.
This is the
big intersection from earlier. It's probably here.
It's coming from here. Wow, how did it come? The river.  Where was it
? There was a market on the river, right?
There was a market. I went
back just once. I came back quite a bit, so yeah.
20 I don't go through the river, so I don't have it.
Maybe, but did you go to some strange parking lot?
Will you go back once? Yes, yes, this is here. This is
the place. I want to know the address. The address is,
uh, half of the 20th ward. It seems
likely.  It's not around here. I
can't find you idiot. How did you come here?
It's been all the way here, south, south, south, south, south, south, south, south, south, south, south, south, south, south, south, south, south, south, south, south, south, south, south, south, south, south.  I
mean, what does that
mean? What does it mean?
This is the Hanofa mark book. Wait a minute. That mark.
That Hanofa mark.
There's that Hanofa gas. There's Make and Leaf Maketo. That's
right, so
here it is.  So I came straight and came out on this huge road, and I
came like this, this is amazing, okay, okay,
okay, so this looks like a triangle, and I'm
sure this triangle-like place is here.  I
wonder if it's a parking lot, etc. Is
this a road? Is this a
road? It's good, but it's like this inside. I
spun next to the loser, right? This is it. There's a
run.  It's
a bit tingling from here, but this
road is definitely a road, right? Oh, there
, there, there, there, there, there, there, there
's a store building, there's a market.  There's a corner
on the left side of the market
where you turn backwards, so it's a dead
end. Is this a dead end? It's not a dead end.
No car can take it here or there,
so yeah, it's
pretty much right now.  I don't think
it's a big deal, but it's already pretty close. Should I
go? It's around here.
No, it's about 1 cm left.
Behind here, right here, right, right.
Here, yes, that's what I think,
that's what I think, let's go.  It
's steadily shrinking. It's amazing. After that
, I'll go to zero. It's the last 5. It's the last. I'll go to the next one. Kia-
chan will be the last one.
Next, this is bad. Isn't this on the expressway
?
Wow, waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.  I don't know
what to do. I can
go to Dara-men. Which way should I go
? Hey, my senior can drive on the highway. I
have a license to drive, but my
mom can't drive.
Still, quite a few people in Austria still
have cars,
but not as much as in the United States.I don't think many
people who live in those areas have cars,
but other than that, I think
there are quite a few people who do.  But
this is CA7,
that, that, that Chechek, dad, you can
go to the park, you can go to the park,
yeah,
it's called A7, right?  Do you
feel that way? Yeah, yeah, yeah, A6A6A
4 minutes
Ugh, how's that? Nose, ah, I found 7,
but it's not A7, it's only 7, is
n't it? 7, no, this is Cebu, it's a normal A4, it's the
one from Linz.  That's
how far it is.
Linds A7A7 is from where to A7.
How far is it from Lindt? It's so far.
Yes, it may be 1 here. It's
Notelinz. This is where I read it. That's
right, if I hit the book randomly, it's
this one.
No, it was 3kg to Linz. 3kg
Yeah, yeah, yeah, wait 3kg.  But
there was a sign for Kokochi, so if you go 3km south, you can
go here.It's so amazing to think about south, but I
can't even think about it.  It's
not here somewhere, Wow, it's 3 kg,
which is surprising. Wow, this sign is like this.
What's so funny about this sign
? This sign is 1 kg. 1
kg ahead, it's Prague.  Frasta and
Lenscentrum, Linz's Central News and
Satzburg Hirose 11.
Um, it's true, it's swerving to the
right, this is to the right, yeah, yeah, that's right, that's right, that
's right.  It does
n't look like this, it looks like this, Wow
, but it's super difficult to get zero with this.I
feel like it's difficult in the whole world,
so this is it, isn't it?  I'm
not used to it from there.
I think it's merging, and I'm being picky about it. The
way the map is drawn, you see, when you get closer,
something's off. Aaaaah, it's not merging, it's not merging here, oh,
oh, here.  It's a lie, it's a lie, it's a
fraud, it's a fraud, it's a fraud, it's a fraud
, it's a lie, it's complicated, I've been fooled, I've been
fooled, but here we part like this, oh
here we are, but we're just about to get together.
Well, when I think about it that way, I
still feel like I was spawned in a good place.I know this, so we're
going to be together, yeah, a little bit
higher, a little bit higher, this way, that's it, that's what I
thought, because that's the path that's coming from the right.  But it's
completely over I'm sure this is also a lot of fun I
can see this on the map
Well, this is the biggest right now This is the biggest right now Yeah
yeah yeah I see
[Music]
Oh, I'm going to fall into the swamp of zeros.
That university definitely did it, so I have
no choice but to identify it with my senior's professional knowledge.
But if you think about it normally, it's
around here.  Nako, this cut here,
yeah, I think this is where it's going to be. Let's
go ahead and change this to A7 and make it A7. Do you
believe that? It wasn't
0 because of me earlier, so it's already gone.  I'll
leave it to you then I'll go
Okay, let's go to the 5th place in Austria. Let's go
there. Wow, I'm not kidding. What's wrong with this? Don't get
too close.
Wow, fraud was more correct. Da double,
fraud fraud in the fraud fraud.
Well, I guess
it was better to see it from far away. Well, I guess it's a bit
difficult to see it, but it
was Linz, far away from here.
Between Zazbrok and Un, between Zazbrok and Un, it's
been about an hour since we said we're satisfied with this, so
I guess we'll stop at about 5 locations today.That's
interesting.I was
playing free games.  I
was completely satisfied with the 500m, not zero,
so maybe that's why it was so boring.It's
completely different when you do it like this.It's
definitely difficult to master.  Do
n't be too happy if you win, but Kia-chan
was with me today, so this is what happened to me. I
learned a lot today, such as the passage from 1st ward to 23rd ward, oh yeah, there was a sign for the subway, etc.  Now, I
can go sightseeing in Austria with just one more person.No, wait, I
want you to tell me a little bit more about it.But
no, I haven't done it yet, because I just went there today.
Burg Salzburg Maybe other than that, there
's also a possibility that Innsburg will show up, but that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right,
Innsburg, just the left side of Innsberg.
Where are you going?
Even in Austria, this airport is
n't used. Even if everyone goes, it's
always a good time to go. Yes, here, here, at the airport, somewhere
around here. Anyone flying from overseas must come here.  I
just saw on the news that there is a plane that can take you from Tokyo Narita or Haneda to Winn in just one flight, and it's back.It seems like an advertisement, because I want to be a
male.Yoya-chan is growing up.  It's where I was born and raised, so I
'm really interested in it.If I
go to Australia, there's probably a place I should go to.Well,
other than Winn, of course
[Music] There are
a lot of places in Winn Town.
Well, to put it more roughly, I
definitely want to go to Salzbruck, so yeah,
there are a lot of really beautiful ponds around Salzbruck, and
although there is no ocean,
everyone is beautiful.  There are a lot of ponds because there are many famous ponds.Yes,
there are many famous ponds.
Yes, that's right,
there are 3 mountain ranges in the Alps, so I just
went to Salzburg and saw what the mountains look like.
But yeah, Oria. Is it cold? It
gets pretty hot in the summer, but for example, it's about
30°35°, but it's pretty good.  It's
so hot, but sometimes I go up there,
but I don't get those bugs, so yeah, that's
nice. In Japan, it's
pretty cold and snowy in the winter.  The
snow that piles up is quite thick in the fields, and those
European people who come skiing like that, and
they often come to Austria and
take vacations there in the winter.  You can do it pretty much anywhere,
but I think it's pretty popular around Salzburg, too.
Yeah, I
went skiing there last year, too.
There's a pretty famous place there. It's famous, right?
Austria is an international sport.
Austrian athletes are quite good at sports. That's
right. They're strong. On the other hand,
ours only really do snow sports in the winter. So,
go home. You know, I
don't swim or anything. I don't really do that.  I
see, no, but even now, I still
feel like I want to go to Salzburg.Of course, when I listen to music, I think that's true no matter where I go.That Salzburg is like that every year.
There's a famous music festival, music
anywhere, but it's the
place where The Sound of Music was set.
That's Satsburg, that's Satsburg.
No, I really like Sambu music, and I
've seen it many times.
Yes, there is a tour that I also participated in.
Yes, that third meek tour shows me all the places, so it's nice.
I can understand Austria even better with tours like that. It's quite small.
After all, if you're going to go there, you'll have to
take that train and take that train.It's
easy to access a lot of things.Yes,
that's right.You can go to Salzburg from Un, in probably 23 hours, two and a half hours, three hours.
Oh, there are quite a few, but yeah,
yeah, yeah, you can go there. It's not as good as the Shinkansen,
but yeah, yeah, yeah, but you
can see the scenery and feel like you can go on and on while looking at the scenery. There's a lot of scenery, too.  I
want to go, Chiara-chan. I
have a passport. I
have one, but it's been too long
since I can't travel. I haven't used it at all. I want to use it.
Yes, I want to use it. I
want to use it. Please do it this winter.  I'm
really thinking about it, and I think I'll ask
Chiara to show me around. I'll
be waiting for you. I'm really happy. You
can stay at my place or the hotel.  It's
okay to stay there, but it
's cold, cold, and cold in winter, so why don't you ask me? It's
cold, but it's beautiful. That Christmas
market. Ah, Christmas. It's Christmas
time. I want to go there. I want to
go to Austria.  Come on, I
was talking to you earlier about Kihara-chan's use of Osaka dialect and Kyoto dialect, which I thought was amazing, but I used to live in Osaka,
so that's amazing.  No, no, no, no, no, no,
thank you very much for introducing me to Austria and showing me around today. Please come and play with me
again.
Thank you everyone for listening. Thank you to everyone at KFP as well
.  So, it's been a while since I last
saw you, but thank you for showing me the fun part.
It was really fun. It was fun to learn
more about the area with someone who knows more about it. So, if you'd
like to see me again, I'll see you next time today.  teeth  I
couldn't go to Germany, but Unki-
chan talked about going back to Germany,
so I told her that if I could do it again next time, I'd
like to go there as well.I didn't know
much about Germany, but I didn't know much about it.  I do
n't know much about it, but I
think if we work together, we'll find it.Today, we
both pushed it and got close to it,
so next time we'll aim for 0m.Let's do
it.Yes, thank you everyone.  Well, I'd
like to end today here, Kira-chan,
thank you, thank you, yes. Well
then, I'd like to close it with my parents.
So, will you go with me?
Yes, let's go. Hey,
Key.  Wai Wai Wai Bye Bye Bye
[Music]
Yo DET