[Music]
do
and welcome to our super saiyso stream
of the
of the of the day of the night
[Laughter]
and here we have our wait
same fight senpai can i ask can i ask
you something
yes yes yes what animal are you
what's that phoenix oh
yes around me my flame aura
and phoenix nothing else out of phoenix
okay but i'm good with shape-shifting so
sometimes they turn into a snake
sometimes i turn into a frog
today i turn into a girl wow
so um i'm rainey from hollow life id
second generation
and i think um can you introduce
yourself to the chat
yes and i am a takadashiana from whole
life english first generation nice to
meet you
indonesian friends i am happy to
take elena's collaboration
of virginity
it's kind of a tradition after all
because when i
had my collab van lifted after one month
i chose subaru senpai as my first
collaboration partner
and supernova senpai is as we all know
a duck yeah so we started the whole
hollow birds holotoy thing and and then
once you debut that i was like another
addition to our holotoni
collection
i'm very happy that that you chose to
continue our tradition and ask me to be
your collaboration partner
of course we have to we have to protect
the whole of
tradition even though i think we kind of
shapeshift a lot
but even our hearts were on birds yes
that was what i was about to say
yes see it's it's it's the bird you know
bird heart thing together we are
connected
we are connected exactly telepathy
telepathy
telepathy exactly
wow wait which one are you in this game
oh let me see you oh
i'm red i think i'm why
today we originally wanted to play
something else right but but
this game we're going for this game now
it's super cute
cute and i think it matches right like
i'm blue and you're red
yeah now it matches no we practiced a
little bit
but but before it didn't it didn't match
very well
when we tested it out because you were i
think red and i was blue
yes that's okay i'm gonna shape shift
the rattle so i can also
uh change colors you can also change
colors okay
wow wait what are we supposed to do
we are supposed to work together and
do stuff how do you look back again with
that button okay
all right
where are we gonna go straight okay yeah
okay
we are doggones i like goggles are you
are you a cat type of person or a dog
type of person
then an important question important
question i think i'm more of a cat type
of person what about you
cats can't skip but i like dogs too
uh me too i like i like a lot of animals
i like dogs i like cats
what about themselves or cats that's not
kids
okay dogs
one person said it i don't know do you
want to check the audio with the
audience if they say it's time
oh all right is the is the audio fine is
the audio file
because it's
oh a bit loud
a little bit a little bit the game audio
is a bit loud
oh okay okay okay let us you should
sleep i i'll lead you to the victory
i'll lead you to victor oopsie oh oh
wait ah
so if i pause the game does it also
pause for you
yeah oh oops audio settings
master oh maybe
music we can keep we can keep the the
barking out
oh yes i think
i think this is fine and i think they
say
you should raise your voice a little bit
i should raise my voice a bit
hello is this okay
okay all right
this reminds me of the duck of the goose
game
we were very aggressively uh being in
ducks back then
wait wait what did we do oh we we
to bring this wood down so that we can
transport the boat
all right
they're saying your mic's a bit loud
my microphone is too loud okay okay
how about now how about now
is it okay um i think it's okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
i think your voice is always beautiful
no matter what
it is i'm just always loud that's just
how i am
wait oh okay we're gonna we're gonna go
okay oh no maybe not
i think you can leave it there oh okay
i'm sorry i just can't let go
just like the dog you want to keep your
bowel you'll be sad if someone takes
away the ball i understand i understand
why are we going through those what's
what's it called
pipes oh yeah wow here we go
oh okay okay oops oh wait wait wait
sorry okay ready to go
i always forget to let go it's just
sometimes you just have to relax let me
tell you as your senpai
yes it's important to be able to let go
and just relax and let it happen you
know
where it's from a wise a very wise
senpai
but i think one more time we have to
scare the butterfly okay
[Laughter]
okay okay okay let's go we have to wait
for the one we have to go
here we go now we can get there maybe
yes
i think we have to go down again
[Applause]
[Laughter]
super long
it sounds like a balloon yeah
really
why
ah oh and then we gotta do the teamwork
thing again
oh yeah what what are we doing we gotta
we gotta push not push pull the thingy
that just spawns
okay i take i take right side you take
left side
looking good through the pipes again we
go
oh by the way yes uh we're using the
whole toy holo birds hashtag again so if
you guys want to tweet out something
you're welcome to tweet with the
hashtags
so
i think can we get there i don't know
can we can we get his tail
oh i think we're supposed to swing over
there oh
oh oh
oh so one person oh
okay i'm not 25 oops
wait wait wait wait i think we could go
downstairs never mind
oh never mind it just runs away from us
[Music]
i think we did something wrong out there
i think we
oh what's downstairs oh it's the
previous area nevermind
maybe both of us
okay
can we really not get his tail i wanna
die
let's let's expand okay how do we expand
oh wait oh here we go
can we extend like upwards now under
there oh i wonder
um it's kind of bullying anyway to grab
his tail
nice we love peace we don't want the
neighborhood to hit
us right if we grab his tail they might
put us in some
places it's a dog
[Music]
it's nice to be a dog dogs are always
happy i aspire to be as happy as a dog
always
[Laughter]
wear like a piece of noodles
[Music]
collaboration everyone's calling for a
third duck in collaboration oh i've been
yeah i've been reading it
oh
[Music]
um what about the butterfly does the
butterfly matter
i don't think maybe i don't know maybe
it gives extra points oh there we go
let's just try to go out and try the
problem with tur duncan is
well you're a turkey so that's fine wait
wait hold on wait
am i no i'm not i'm i'm not but
it's fine wait hold on
and somebody sent by is a duck so that's
fine yes but i'm
not a chicken i'm a phoenix okay oh
you're not
no i'm not i'm not a chicken oh
today i learned something new majority
turkey
and insanity is a duck so that's correct
this is just my part isn't very correct
um but i thought oh okay
thank you what did you think no no no no
because i totally thought you were a
chicken but that's right
i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry that's
just what it's just
that's just what i heard thank you thank
you for correcting me
if you want to collab with your senpai
you shouldn't just rely on what you hear
you should you should actually like
research on what your family actually is
i'm sorry kevin can even do this
hello my my my phoenix senpai kiara
don't mess it up okay i will do my best
i'm having so much fun with my love of
coffee and exam by kiara senpai
my phoenix senpai kiara senpai is a very
nice person and loves a very
supportive phoenix senpai
that's what i like to hear that's
exactly how it is yes
yes yes you hear you hear that chat uh
my my my lovely senpai kiara senpai is a
phoenix
so you know ah wait
wait wait i'm
we're doing actually quite well at this
game ah
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh we have to move oh there we go
you like roller coasters i do i do do
you
i don't you know
they're kind of fun but every time i get
into one
that's a little bit more extreme i just
i just feel like i'm gonna die
oh yeah and i lose my voice and i scream
so loud that i can't scream anymore
i'm not the best one at roller coasters
ah
yeah good job good job
but the buck's just
so we gotta be fast maybe let's grab
grab today's walls
i won't let you go quick for the next
one
okay okay
we look like a snake
okay i'm grabbing to this one okay okay
okay i'll
go and i'll try to go here okay
do you want me to grab the
okay let's go downstairs
oh
do you want to grab the next part or do
you want me to oh okay um i'll do it
since i'm
uh send fighting just relax
[Music]
okay okay i'm coming
my neck
[Applause]
we immediately go downstairs okay go go
go go go go go go go
wait wait i can't
oh we did it that was fun oh
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
i actually have uh two cats i own two
cats really
um yeah but one day i also want to get
one dog maybe
i want to get a big dog a big fluffy dog
that's good what do you have any idea
what
what breed you're getting or not yet
i want either a corgi but that's not so
big
corgi or samo yet i don't know how you
say that
something like that something big and
fluffy or or
you know someone else are pretty
pretty cute yeah yeah
oh i'm not a moot oh my god i know this
oh
oh it's scary
it sounds yeah it looks scary but that's
huh what is it oh okay okay
pick the other side okay and then open
it
we can unlock stuff
[Music]
oh so that's what the bones are for okay
so it's like currency to unlock these
what is that that's a that's a diving
not not a diving it's a
the mask for the yeah yeah i think i
know what you mean
this is what is that bad berries
suspicious oh my gosh
[Music]
[Applause]
did you have pets i used to
where do we go
did we clear the game oh
no i don't think so i don't think so
where do we have to go
oh maybe another place
oh like this
[Music]
okay let's go there oh level 2 is inside
uh okay
it's purple wait did we get in
what's going on what's going on
um
oh it's pretty it's pretty
oh it's like an underwater world
oh like a like uh what do you call it
what do you call this kind of
pop oh it has green patches
[Laughter]
it's so pretty here i really like the
the cute graphics of the game
you might need to dream details
oh it's a level let's go down there
because she likes to sleep so much
[Music]
oh
why does it look it's fine i guess yeah
it didn't hurt me
what is this what are you what do you
want
i doesn't line up he wants he wants us
to uh
repair his lamp oh yeah maybe maybe
maybe
how can we help you sir we are many
helpful dogs we will help you i don't
know how but we will do our best
oh i think we have to light up this too
yeah
[Music]
oh
do you want to light all the other lamps
yeah let's try maybe we get something
from that
but does it reappear yeah i think it
reappears once uh
once we oh wait a second what's there
can we go to a new area with that oh
maybe
oh
should we go which direction do we go
forward
there's a bell oh
is that it maybe oh do you want to check
out the other area
let's go to the other side okay
looks so cute it looks the same as the
lamp
the lights that we're holding yeah
oh the camera doesn't look to the other
side
ah that's where we came from oh okay
okay yeah i think this is the way
okay
[Music]
yeah yay surprised you're so good at
this game because from judging your
super mario 64 gaming skills
my own super mario 64 gaming skills
we're both really bad
games wait the lights are not here with
us
yeah oh no oh well i think we got
to decide oh what is this oh wait what
are we supposed to do
maybe one wrap is onto it and then
nothing
i think we're just gonna get yellow over
here yeah
we're gonna get back to it later
are you not gonna rate quit super mario
64 yet you're still going with that
uh not yet i think oh wow how far did
you get
going oh i don't know but i think it
feels like you're doing it already
longer than me
oh really yeah
oh we have a another light source yeah
i gave up quite early when super mario
64.
i think for me my problem was the
controls
i mean yeah
the camera is so bad which direction do
we got in there
oh there they look it's the i think it's
for this
oh oh it's not oh it lights up but what
does it do
maybe we'll just leave it there for now
maybe we can go back
i mean not go back hello oh what do you
want this time oh he doesn't want
anything
does he want the lights again i'm not
saying anything
so probably not but sometimes people
just don't
talk about their emotions and what they
really want
sometimes they don't talk about it and
how about we give it to him
maybe we can like that does that make
you happy yes
oh that does okay
let's get the light let's get the light
yeah because if we get rid of the bubbly
thing maybe something comes out there
we need the dog bone okay
[Music]
oh there's a bone downstairs i don't
know how we get there though oh
bone downstairs wait i'm gonna try i'm
gonna try to get it okay
i'll stay there
we were too greedy
wait maybe we can maybe there's like a
secret path or something but i don't
know i don't know i'm just going
to
one second i'll go down here oh my god
i could be that smart huh come on
just a bit more just a bit more can you
also
try to get longer or is this maximum um
maybe this is maximum
cause idea idea idea
can you swim
part wait no but then you'll fall
is it gone i don't see it anymore no
it's gone
wait it's gone no no no it's there it's
there but what
maybe you can come down now because now
the light is on the other side
that we didn't get first but i don't
know how that helps us to get the bone
oh i know we have to ah we go through
that hole
can you try to get yourself at home yeah
we solved the regular things yay
[Music]
game
now i think we have to get the the ball
again
yeah this this one is weird because the
the pacing is like
where do we go next it's like we have to
search for oh what is that
what is that big big gate over there oh
yeah i was thinking if we find the light
over there
uh okay can you hold on to that again
yeah i am i'm holding on to it i'll get
the light back
okay
because if we bring it over the bridge
it will disappear right yeah
okay
almost
[Music]
did you when you did the the collab with
the whole live indonesia second gen
together the karaoke collab
it wasn't a sleepover but
maybe one day we could do a sleepover
together
let's do a pillow fight get yourself a
pillow wait wait wait do we have extra
pillows
let me is this can i grab it no
maybe in the back let's see if i can
find it oh
[Laughter]
two sexy birds doing a pillow fight
yeah maybe
[Music]
kind of thing
someone in the chat wrote when we both
laugh they don't know
which one is laughing
[Laughter]
oh he wants the he wants the uh
the
yeah we have to activate something we
can go over here
okay
it's so beautiful i want my roof to look
like this
i know
can i think we have to bring it over all
over the bridge
[Music]
wow you're so sorry
of course i am of course i have smart
what did you think oh and now he can see
the fishies oh that's so pretty
nice oh he's like thanks
thanks dude he's using it's a fish
it's his face
there's a light switch is that a giant
light switch to make it daytime
it is oh wait actually no it's just to
make it light up
it's so pretty i think this one we can
leave alone yeah
oh maybe not wait yeah cause if it's
daytime there's no
the bubbly oh
yes to the hotel now to the hotel
that's how it is it's smiling should we
do anything with this no no
can we take it again no no it's uh yeah
what is that
thinking time we have to
maybe look over here there's a smiling
oh fishing oh we got that
oh oh can we we're fishing for something
oh you want to go down there can i can i
can i grab the uh
i wonder i wonder oh no oh no i can't
i think we're just fishing for something
yeah
let's make it long enough and spin spin
spin
what do we get oh there you go we got
something and now we're bringing that
up oh
[Music]
yay
wow
how do we wake up the uh
i gotta make it daytime so this
disappears and the
thing can gong the bell
do you think i can go over there and
make it day time
and i stay there
i don't think we can be long enough
because one has to stay here right
oh yeah you're right
through the light and the other one has
a flashlight out of the mouth
oh yeah that makes sense okay
wow oh now we're ready to go
i'm not a chicken yes
do you hear that do you hear that
then i might not be so smart but hey
we've fulfilled the whole level
oh with all the bones
all the bones do you want to try one
more
yes yes yes one more month oh it's
opening its mouth for us nice
nice we are ready where where will you
take
us shoes
this is the previous one but let's see
if yeah ah
okay hello hello
will you okay
[Music]
but didn't we visit this one to the one
in the middle because this is what the
with the the sand
ball really did we
i think this one this is in the middle
oh oh no
listen with you oh what a cute place
but it has hot wheels what what's it
called what's it called what's this one
called
you something like that like a cardigan
yes yeah i am excited
me too wait breezy beach
do you want to go to the beach
[Music]
one day you become greedy as well maybe
ah that would be so good
you would probably be like super tall
and elegant
ah i wanna see 3d elena hey
i want to see 3d kiara senpai but can we
put something here too
hey whatever is nothing
nothing maybe wind
[Music]
um
look it's a bird it's our comrade it's
our nakama
oh i'm trying to get up but
i can't i can't get out
[Applause]
what is this what do we do here
you stop it oh
[Music]
you just gotta let it let it flow
oopsie
what can we do here
oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god
but i think we would have gotten a beach
phone a little bit
a doggy phone if we would have given him
the beach ball and now we can't go up
anymore
wait we can't maybe maybe not
yeah it's gone oh i'm saying to me
i was thinking
it's okay i'm not hungry anymore anymore
[Music]
it's a seagull can you make a seagull
money
i just how does eagle sound i think it's
something like uh
no it's like my lap almost
you have to practice your bird noises
can you do a chicken
noise take chicken nose wait
yeah uh i don't know how to wait baby
hold on
was somebody was somebody here
oh really okay
[Music]
but the star on the ground is so cute
by the way chicken noise you you you
didn't do it
okay can you can you can you can you can
you give me an example senpai oh boys
[Laughter]
oh
oh he's just chilling there nice
i feel i still feel sad about the beach
ball
because i wanted
[Music]
i think in fairy we can probably reach
right a level
we could we could we could move on
it's important to look forward look at
this
oh that's so you know like these are all
beach balls except with legs
like same thing right yeah
we can play with them we can use them to
play around right this level is so cute
that looks so much fun i wanna i wanna
make
i wanna go on vacation there uh it's
gonna be so fun it's like
imagine it's like an amusement park and
then you just take
you just stay somewhere near um just
close to it
and then every morning you can go and
try out all the rides
oh swimming raining oh swim swim swim
can
[Music]
hydration check everybody
[Laughter]
by the way i can also make a cr
crow crow sound crow sound
can you can you do it can you do it yes
okay three
two one
[Applause]
[Laughter]
we were black doggos
[Music]
oh
i think there's only two colors
it's not the right color
look on the top of that there's no okay
we need the there's triangle and
and the square oh okay i think they want
both yeah
oh you need this one a red one
yes
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
and turkeys and and phoenixes
yes and phoenix's yes
oh we can open this one yes yes i'll
take the other end
oh
i think that already leads us to the
next level oh wait that was quick
but there's probably more to do here
maybe oh what is this
oh oh think there's a star in every
in three areas okay i think
so the green tents we can try the green
tent now uh-huh
it's on on the left side uh-huh
oh there's one in the train
oh my god is this
like you have to shoot like one of us
has to be like
shooting oh my god how does this work
[Applause]
oh this is difficult this is difficult
okay let's wait until it's in the middle
or like
oh yeah how do we shoot it
i'm gonna have to let go let's go maybe
oh something
oh my gosh
maybe we gotta aim a little bit down
yeah
oh that's so difficult oh my god that's
so difficult
[Music]
we can do this one we can do this
ah when we're both on it it's easier to
to
uh aim i think okay
let's try let's
[Music]
i'll go you can try uh
hold on let me wait
[Music]
okay i'll just have to be extra powerful
maybe almost almost maybe not i'm not
not up enough
oops sorry
[Music]
oh we only have to do it one time thank
god
[Music]
yes oh thank god
oh maybe we have to pop all the balloons
for the star look because the balloons
have a star pattern mourinho
oh my god okay
[Applause]
[Music]
oh you were the one
[Laughter]
this is so hard okay
[Applause]
the aiming is so hard it keeps i don't
know why i don't know i don't know
what's happening
no
[Applause]
no it's not strong enough very close
let's try together let's try together
okay
one two three
uh i don't think it's strong enough if
it's just it's just me
oh oh oh okay oh
okay okay one two three
[Music]
[Laughter]
let's try the last tense there's one
more tense where we should check out
and the the purple one i think there's
something inside the train
yeah we should try to ride it
is it here oh yeah that's that it's not
really a tent but okay
what do we have here air oh we have to
okay i'll turn this on okay
nice okay nice
oh
i don't think i understand this yet yeah
is there a way we can go in
what is that
oh maybe i can can if i grab this can
you go off i don't know
maybe not no but oh
oh look at that oh we just have to go
around and move the ball
[Music]
oh how do we go continue from there um
this one maybe yeah maybe
i'll go there
oh
oh okay we have to release when it
reaches the ah
wait oh no that was correct
[Music]
[Applause]
in the middle and i'll do this and then
i'll do this
nice nice wait one million points
not yet one more time one more time one
more time
okay go go
[Music]
maybe how do we get air from that side
um
maybe back there i'm not sure
where's the air where is the air
not this one maybe oh this one i'm not
sure
but we already used that one though but
we use that one
the last the last one which one is the
last one maybe here
again
no maybe maybe that one the finish line
okay if it doesn't
try one by one one by one
one by one
okay let's see if this works
how do you say a good job in indonesian
how do you say that
you can say heba it kind of means
something like erai
[Laughter]
[Music]
i do i do i like godzilla very much yes
you do like katja very much i spend
some money on gaza games every now and
then sometimes
yeah it's okay it's not an addiction so
it's all good wait uh what's it oh maybe
this is kind of like a you are here
instead of a there's a star yeah there's
only three stars i think
but what happens if we ride the train
can we do that
[Music]
um is open
yeah do you want to try maybe there's a
way
don't don't get run over
oh somebody wants chickens
if we wait up here until the train comes
again maybe we can jump into the train
and get the last seat
we just have to wait yo how where are
you going my friend where are you going
it wants tickets
you can't wait you want to drink
[Laughter]
you don't have a picnic you don't need a
ticket you can just ride the train
anyway just jump in buddy
get ready get ready get ready
[Music]
we have air now
grab it
i almost got run over
[Music]
okay
we only have two out of five though
well that's okay interesting i think we
did a great job
we completed the level pretty much we
missed some bones but we completed the
level
we got over there let's check it out
oh there's a boat over there look oh
oh we have to jump i think so oh my god
okay
we're gonna fall somebody needs to hold
on to
something oh no you can i guess
yeah but let's try to jump
oh but maybe we can go from here maybe
[Music]
oh my god you can fall i don't know i
think there's the edge of the
of the oh god oh god
we are safe we are safe it's fine
okay one more
i slowly slowly slowly slowly let's go
slowly on the on that side and then
oh okay that's fast he kind of bounced
off of the water in there
okay let's just quickly run over it like
that
style over here full speed
do you want to um be longer like
no i don't i think we should be short
okay
oh that's the other one doesn't like
like drag
yeah maybe maybe maybe i think we should
be
short okay we should be sure okay are
you ready
i think we're missing two but i i think
we got
i'm i'm full
it's okay we got three stars we
we can eat in moderation that's fine
[Laughter]
it's not done no i think we've done
whatever oh
it's just like an angle yeah oh
wait we're not oh
there's a funny mirror oh
no was it because of the air oh maybe
oh somebody's relaxing oh there's a
secret
we're just missing the uh missing the
beach ball but i mean that's fine i
guess
that was the one in the very beginning
what's going on here oh i have to okay i
have to
open the air okay okay
oops okay
[Music]
oh
oh we have to go on here we have to go
up here through the uh
the oh
how do we get up again oh no no oh wait
how do we get up
here let's go
that's just to make the thing to go back
we go back i'm not sure
[Music]
do you want to see what's up here yeah
oh oh mirror
oh really nice thing
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
okay okay that's fine i think now
there's air again
okay
[Music]
give us give us the gacha give it to me
now
what are we supposed to do oh there's is
there something back there
oh yeah oh my god wait wait it's an
invisible lever
oh my god
[Applause]
let me get the other side okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
that was a nice vacation that was really
fun i
i like this place a lot yeah
it was fun i like this game
oh it's giving us another level but i
think somewhere
around here
[Music]
we ate so many bones
i'm full now
did you have fun i had fun i hope you
had fun
yeah it's such a cute game so much fun
it wasn't it wasn't that hard either
although i must say maybe it was hard
maybe we're just
too smart for the game we are too
big brained combined together
our brains are bigger than the universe
it's the power of the hollow bird with
the biggest
brains can you imagine what we can do
when we combine our powers with suado
senpai
it's gonna be we're gonna it's gonna be
the smartest combination
all of olive i don't know what what
what species what other species are
there
birds are superior that is it
birds are the superior race
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my god it's sleeping it's sleeping in
water
i was just you're chilling you're trying
to kill me i'm sorry okay let's
okay let's let's let's let's just dress
swimmer i'm not a good swimmer okay
okay okay okay let's let's let's let's
just rest somewhere here like the tent
it's
a safe place to finally rest and take a
break
we did some good work together we did we
did we did
look the dogs are sleeping it's also
time to rest how was it how was it chad
how
was the game fun did the game look fun i
hope you enjoyed it
i think it was great some of them were
quite impressed because they didn't
expect us to do such a good job
don't underestimate us i think
we did good oh it zoomed in it's okay
what was your favorite stage
senpai i did the dreamy uh sleepy stage
ah
it's it really does how do you say it
it's like
if you see it it's like oh i want to
have a sleepover there and just
it looks super comfy yeah want to sleep
over
with my whole life english members one
day if we can ever all meet
in one spot that's so because yeah
we're scattered all over the world
unfortunately
but maybe one day i hope you can one day
yeah uh sleepovers are so
fun with uh anya
and and ollie i know she'd do a
sleepover we could we could we could
anya will probably be
sleeping all the time i'm sorry anna
well i mean sleepover and sleeping is
it's a good combination
although she'll be sleeping and you and
ani will be fighting each other
yes i guess so i like the uh
the carnival mo the most
it really does it really does remind me
of porkas empire
oh now i'm super excited for tomorrow
yeah i know right at night i think yeah
yes yes yes i'm so excited for it
anyway since it's time to rest
the dog is the dogs are also resting i
don't know are they
cats or dogs yeah
everything we are everything yes
have confidence we are everything that
we want to be
although the possibilities are endless
endless
we can be anything
maybe next time we'll come back with
another shape we never know
yeah but
anyways ah thank you very much kiara
senpai for
you know working together with me
solving all the puzzles and becoming
dogs
no problem i'm so happy that i could be
your first collab partner it was an
honor and if you
if you ever want to talk about something
you can always rely on your verb senpai
you can always message me and say kiara
please i need your advice on something
just come to me and i'll help you out
and i'm i'm a phoenix i will help you
i'm smart
i will thank you very much my favorite
next time for my very very smart
phoenix senpai
yay do you have um do you have anything
you want to
say to chad today uh
oh next week um next week today in one
week
and i'm finally coming back with polo
talk
and next week i have a very special
guest i will put out my
my schedule for next week um i think
tomorrow and then you guys will see who
the very special guest is
oh have you been hello talk with mine
uh yes yes i think it's very interesting
program
one day i also want to have the
indonesian members on holocaust
that would be nice
and yes i think i think everyone i think
most people here everybody here
is subscribed to kiara senpai but if you
haven't
please subscribe to kiara senpai
and follow her um the her youtube
channel is on the description
so please she's very amazing she's a
very nice and supportive
and very smart phoenix senpai he could
exactly think phoenix phoenix yes
i have to apologize though that i i i
called you turkey like automatically
because everyone else
was saying that but then while you were
getting angry my brain was like oh wait
wait wait she's not she's not a
turkey
that's okay it happens it it happens
sometime you know even for
a bit confused um it's okay it's just
confusion sometimes
even for um very smart phoenix's like
you
are it can be a little confusing it's
just one of those days maybe
right
sometimes even i get confused by my own
chat and by
also by my own actions but sometimes i
don't even know anymore
what i really am i get like an
existential crisis sometimes
but it's okay we all know we all know
that you're a phoenix right chad
i am i think i am recently i feel more
uh connected to the frog race
but yeah if you ever if you ever have an
existential crisis
i've been through it so feel free to
talk to me about it
okay i will keep that in mind thank you
thank you very much
and then it's a it's been a great day
it's been a really really fun day that i
spent with kiara senpai
and it is time for us
to sleep like the dogs
every fun day will be ended with a very
nice sleep
yes i hope you have a very
nice
you can sleep if you want
okay dream of us you will you will not
regret it you will have beautiful dreams
if you dream of these two birds
right like everyone should go on twitter
and write what they thought about the
stream on twitter with hashtag hello
birds
[Laughter]
yes anyway thank you very much i hope
you have a good rest
and i'm going to be uh do you have a
closing catchphrase
yeah i say in german and in german we
say auf wiedersehen
ah what does that mean uh it's like
see you again in germany okay then
then then i will say mine and then you
will say
yours okay okay uh
okay thank you very much for your
attention
and in german we say
[Music]
bye
you