a
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
a
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
n
[Music]
oh oh
k
k no not sick just like eating so much
chocolate right
now it's making my fruit
[Music]
chocolatey no chat
is chat is just as
always no not with the strawberries m-m
I don't have so
many they
are rare
resource I'm
back let's
go I came back from Thailand
[Applause]
yay yay yay yay yay yay let's see if
somebody played with my audio settings
again
huh I don't know if they
did we'll find
out looks a bit suspicious to me but
might be
[Laughter]
fine Thailand Thailand Thailand
[Music]
SAA yeah yeah yeah yeah I'm back we can
talk a little bit about it don't don't
ask the questions
already give me tangent time for
later
I I might not necessarily have too many
tangents though don't don't expect too
much I
was I was just
there I may not have much to say
[Music]
well we are so back and it might not be
a super long stream though because the
game is
like um calling for a shorter type of
stream which I think is good
because
because that's fine we need some shorter
streams
but I always say I'm going to do a short
stream and then you know what happens
but but I don't think that I will play
the game for that long really like it's
a rhythm game what am I GNA do it's like
Fall Guys Fall Guys rhythm
game and um I don't think it's going to
be that
long but I wanted to play it you know
because we just finished a really
long jrpg
Yakuza so you know right now uh before
we go on to the next one is when I'm
trying to do like smaller short streams
oneoff games and all that and
Headbangers was on my list of one off
games that I want to play in the
future you're streams are usually still
four plus hours well by my own
definition yes oh why did I stop
moving what's
happening restarting the
app oh there we go I'm so back
but
oh it just changes my
clothing to whatever is on the app okay
let me put my sunglasses back on I am I
am I am you know trying to be uh I want
I want to look like I just came from my
vacation yeah I mean it wasn't a
vacation though I wish I wish it was I
wish I had time to go to a beach and all
that because Thailand has so many
beautiful and cheap cheap cheap cheap
chep cheap cheep um places man uh like
beaches kind of a vacation Paradise yeah
famous in Austria for being a cheap
vacation
Paradise yeah I wish I I wish I could go
why wish I was going to go like I wanted
to extend my
vacation so that it's an actual
vacation in in Thailand I wanted to
extend it but then the flights
uh would have had to be completely
like paid Yeah by like from zero again
basically substituted for Bali but
that's the thing so I I was going to go
to Bali this month that was the plan and
then we moved it for C uh cuz I didn't
want to move on with the plan I felt bad
uh if we just leave Cali behind she said
we can just go without her that's okay
too if we want to but I said
nah nah I feel bad so B was cancelled
when I
already like I no Bali was I was
Thailand was planned when I thought I
was going to
Bali so I thought oh I'm going to keep
the Thailand trip as short as
possible because I will go I will be
going to the Bali trip so I want to make
sure I'm not aw for too much time for
you guys so that it's not like oh I'm
I'm in Southeast Asia for the whole
month I wanted to keep this one short
and then finally was cancelled but
Thailand was already booked
and and I was like ah I wish I
could
[\h__\h] uh ah I couldn't have
T sopi Asia for a whole month would have
probably killed me I mean holy [\h__\h] hey
I told you to like not make me tangent
right away and what happened you made me
tangent right away how dare
you yeah the heat like oh my God it was
like
40° uh
Celsius with humid weather that's like
45 up to 50
50 and oh my God now I'm back in Austria
and it's
like 15 to 20° C it's like half less
than
half no but it was a little bit warmer I
think when I left but now right now it's
like a little bit of a cold front right
now in
Austria uh so I was surprised by Rael
cold weather
uh
so if I get
sick no I don't think so no no no the
this like weather difference no also cuz
like you know recently I went to uh
insanely cold
place but the Austria was also cold at
the time so it wasn't crazy but I also
didn't go outside that much but
still yeah no generally no I don't think
so no but one thing I it's not because
of the change of temperature but
40° C plus in humid weather under the
midday Sunshine was certainly a
challenge I was uh starting to get heat
stroke at some
point I I was feeling it cuz I was
getting dizzy and really weak and
feeling a little bit like I'm I'm
starting to feel like I want to throw
up uh yeah and that like once I noticed
I was feeling like that I was like oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] thankfully in that moment I
got a ice cold drink so I sat down and I
drank that but it took quite a while to
feel somewhat normal
again I was like wo whoo whoo Who whoo I
think I was feeling like Delirious or so
sunburn no and I barely put on
sunscreen so I was a bit lucky I guess
uh that I managed to stay uh without the
sunburn cuz I was under the sun under
the under the really strong
direct
um yeah noon noon Sun but that was only
for one day like the other days and
mostly like okay just Just For Those few
hours I was like outside and really
suffered but the most of the other time
I was like inside a shopping mall or
inside a restaurant and so
on cuz that's how why am I tting already
hello hello but that's how uh Thailand
people spent their time and uh like uh
mostly they just try to stay inside a
place place because it's so [\h__\h] hot
outside so I was just you know
culturally
adjusting but I was thinking okay here's
my think here's my funk here can I have
a penny for a
f first as an
exchange penny for a fault that's how
you say it
right I'm
waiting I would like to have a penny for
f just so that this phrase makes
sense not a pebble no a penny please
[Music]
uh
Penny penny for f a scent maybe maybe a
scent a Euro or a Yen or a a penny
[Laughter]
no that's 100 pennies I don't have so
many thoughts thank you thank there we
go there we go thank you okay okay thank
you okay stop that was enough
pennies but stop
stop you took a while guys you kind of
scared me I thought there was nothing
coming I was like
H did did I is everybody
like like really really broke right now
that they can't spare a
penny oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] the super group is
[Laughter]
collab oh okay I'm not downloading no
I'm not I had this game
forever I'm just
like I probably will be focusing too
hard on the rhythm game anyway so it's
good to get out the tangents but okay
okay stop stop so my my fault maybe it's
not even worth all those
pennies [\h__\h] uh but let's just take it
as a down payment for many future fs and
also for the previous FS thank you
uh no okay okay now now I'm feeling
pressured the the only thought I had was
um because I remember when I was in
Indonesia it was really hot there too
and then the IND Indonesian girls they
told me that in in in Indonesia they
also just they they just stay in like
shopping malls like because when we
talked about sseeing and all that they
said oh we just we just go to shopping
malls and all that you know we just stay
inside because of air conditioning and
all that it's hot outside and I was like
when I was in Thailand and they the Thai
people told me that that's what they do
all the time I was like oh this might be
like a southeast Asia thing where in all
these like hot as [\h__\h] countries
they just they just can't bear it so oh
I stopped
moving they just stay in the shopping
malls all the time and that's why now
listen I'm waiting for myself to move
again yeah it's a hot country thing but
Japan and Korea is hot as [\h__\h] and humid
as [\h__\h] trust me I suffered pretty much
almost the same amount there it was not
nice not pleasant and summer but they
don't spend that much time in shopping
malls uh seems like the app is taking a
while what was I saying uh yeah I think
I want to say yeah because the shopping
malls I saw in Thailand they were
insane so like there was first of all
there's so many second of all they're so
crowded holy [\h__\h] so crowded so many
people uh crazy amount of people and so
much traffic in front of
them when I would drive with taxi to uh
shopping mall like the trip to the
shopping mall is okay until you get to
the street where the shopping mall is
because that's when just a a a one
minute access to the shopping mall takes
suddenly I swear 20
minutes yeah I don't know this [\h__\h]
app
hello I'm restarting
it oh but I wanted to say they're crazy
they're so modern here we go they're so
modern and they they're so beautiful
yeah the shopping malls that I saw were
crazy I went to Icon C and Paragon and
maybe one more
something stuff like that I don't
remember yeah those are the ones I want
was there one more I'm not sure those
are the ones I want for sure but the
icon C was a new one and and it uh was
like whoa the food market floor was
crazy
shees yeah really really really cool and
thankfully there was air conditioning
there but yeah so I was say yeah they
put so much money into their shopping
malls because they all go there spend so
much time there n hold oh okay that was
my
fault and it's a southeast Asia thing
not a
hold no I have the game I
swear I was just you know you got me
started don't even get me
started uh I just had one question
should I play this with a controller or
with my
keyboard I I feel like it might be a
controller kind of game right
oh [\h__\h] controller God Dam it okay well
I have the cable here uh and the
controller PS5
controller let me connect hopefully it
works right away where every
P oh my my chest hurts from
laughing ah Xbox input it doesn't matter
like when I put my
controller uh connect to steam it's like
never the butt prompts are never what I
want them what I need them to
be so it's always Xbox they always show
me Xbox inputs I'm used to that too much
FS no my FS please K FS okay
careful okay but no more pennies
also does that mean no more pennies if I
have no more
FS how am I going to survive how will I
pay my money and my my my pay my money
pay my food and and I don't know my
cat's toilet sand
and okay let's try let's hope this
works
launching running install script
Microsoft VC
redistributable
uh-huh open the [\h__\h] game open the
game you guys can play with me by the
way if you don't have the game it's
pretty cheap apparently uh like on sale
in some places so hello game hello hello
hello hello
hello Takes a Minute [\h__\h] slow hello
hello hello hello hello
hello grab a controller and kick
back grab an Xbox controller a dual
sense controller okay yeah I have
don't you know I have one connected
dude okay here we go woo oopsie sorry
put your headon and grab the
controller
[Music]
glitches
what who the [\h__\h]
gra
myoll and P and blue blue Bluebird blue
wait they're not all blue actually
oh okay so this is ribbon game where you
can participate and I think uh as far as
I know I can make a room so let's find
out how all this works this is the first
time I'm first time I'm opening the
game hey
I they sound like me do like exactly the
same oh [\h__\h] is German
uh wait I think we can change
it ready uh 2
[Music]
one okay no it is X I was thinking maybe
I'm pressing the wrong but no X is X so
[Music]
far it's so bright the screen is so
bright
oh what is this
moving or something on the screen the
the the buttons looked like they were
moving to me I have 15 me milliseconds
uh apparently is it just not wait are
you sure it's not just me being bad and
skipping a few times let me try
again
German 2 1 x x x x Twitter Twitter
Twitter Twitter I will not call it x no
matter no matter how many you know how
much you push it into my face Elon
Musk it's [\h__\h] Twitter give me the
blue bird B oh wa wa it looks like it's
moving the screen is
crazy okay see now we're down to 10
milliseconds Twitter Twitter
Twitter crossplay activ
activ
yeah uh B
English also it's loud in my
ears oh
okay do you like this
[Music]
volume okay I'll turn it down a little
bit
IM imag IM
[Laughter]
IM
oh h
[Music]
Lo
ly
[Music]
latency oh can't can't read okay
English and
vibration resolution full screen vsync
frame rate wow my English is
crazy
crossplay favorite region oh H does it h
probably if I'm like randomly matching
with people it will match me with it
would prefer to match me with people
from that
area
okay I don't know why I I I know I can
just lower the master volume
but uh
okay I will crush you oops sorry
oh don't cry ta voices really is that
really
necessary it looks not so
[Music]
cute okay okay we have only a few
choices to
customize oh oh the p is so cute and so
wobbly what his SP shakes oh
cute hey
this is like a like a A Kiss reference
right this is just you guys and this is
I don't know what this is
Shake oh I stopped moving again the bird
is moving so much in the game that I
lost all my
movement
oh oh oh wait I want this cuz it's
orange let's see how orange we can get a
but actually this is my color too
do
M hair would be nice but oh I can kind
of make it my color and then oh oh I
have to choose between hair
or headphones what do you think is
better hair or headphones or is just
no no I think maybe
headphones like
this yellow ostrich no turquoise ostrich
no T turquoise P pigeon
oi you know Tanaka karia is the ostrich
oi right that you have and then uh takak
Chan is the turquoise pigeon streamer or
rithm gamer how about that turquoise
pigeon Rhythm gamer
takan that's who this is
I kind of like it but no how about oh no
no don't lead me off track this is good
oh play Eight Games wait I can become an
eggplant
what I can become a not this not a
violent right it's um I would say that's
a cuz it's so big it's what's you what
do you call the big one oh my God a
[\h__\h] volcano what are these
costumes wait that's Yi cosplay at the
end a cello yeah cello
cello okay okay whatever I don't know
why I started from this side but uh
let's start try starting start trying
try start both I guess start trying no
try starting
[Music]
okay what the [\h__\h] uh do I choose like
how do I make my own Lobby do you guys
know is it here
uh-oh oh
no no that seems to bring me to
random matching can I make a
Lobby you can't okay then you guys got
to try getting in with
me well wait don't I have like Europe on
right
now here we'll switch maybe none okay
none
none join I'm going to go in 3
one go
tournament Works quite well okay okay
okay oh oh [\h__\h] that was fast oh you
have chicken
[Music]
costume hello if you are uh one of us
then Shake no if you're one of us then
nod nod nod nod
nod nod nod
yeah no not there's some nding chicken
the ones in the the two in the back are
not nodding oh oh [\h__\h] not
not not not not are these randos or
what let's go I don't know how this
works and I feel like what do I normally
just press x one mistake cost one heart
the 20 survivors are
qualified okay is it just X all the time
cuz in the here it's also X
is there some dead beats you think
so are you guys in it's always X oh okay
that's easy at least for now
okay let's go dance party
woohoo should be easy 2
[Music]
1 yeah
that was fast that threw me into the
cold
water
[Music]
hi
what here we go oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] I changed my grab of my controller
I'm only holding it with the right hand
[Music]
it's so sudden D the [\h__\h]
D oh it's
[Music]
okay this is
fun oh it's so difficult
though is someone
[Music]
dead
y yo that was rough I'm six let's go
first try and I'm six oh there's some
kfp names I think oh that's but they're
[\h__\h] Bots you guys didn't make it in
or what okay here we have kfb is this
also kfb this is kfb this I don't know
so many bot what the [\h__\h] get in here
guys why are the Bots
surviving and why are they called Bots
like that's not Bots provided by the
game is
it it's kind of Dead online then you
guys got to get in look at the images
which correspond to the sounds you'll
hear
the it's like a memory card game what
you call it like when you turn you turn
it around and you hope it's the right
thing
the not rhym game
anymore remember the
noises
[\h__\h] you select to listen and
memorize
okay but training
right
dance oh what
what
what what I don't understand round two
no
what ah I'm looking for the
monkey but what's this what's the
Turning oh
sh
uh monkey rot how do I get up how do I
get up
I know
[Music]
that
H
disqualify
what what what there were two
sounds
[Music]
what I don't even I don't understand how
game works I have to turn them around to
to find the sound right but then I
couldn't go like into a different Row
for example when I wanted to to check
the others or so and also I don't know
how to log him in do I have to log him
in I don't get it they needs a better
tutorial
yeah I could have spam but like what
spam you you mean spam opening up the
cards you see the images first then hear
two
sounds uh you see IM and hear two sounds
then you match the two sounds and find
the the images I didn't see the images
first you mean they showed them all to
me I didn't see
them each row is the order of the
sounds what I don't get it maybe I have
to try it again you need to get the
first one right to go to the second row
ah okay tournament let's try again guys
come in come in come in come in come in
come in come in I didn't warn
you
[\h__\h] come on please join
me S this is like always like I never
warn you guys
properly but hey it's not it's taking
some time to find you guys
so and not not not not
politely are the naked on Bots or are
you guys just new
players wow that one's fancy
looking like a tree with some
flower like it oh I tapped out of the
game
oopsie how the [\h__\h] did I accidentally
tap out of the game
[Music]
be as big of an issue unless the Bots
are taking over yeah it seems like seems
like we can get
together quite easily are you guys
getting the game or what like if you
don't have the game yet go download it
now oh here we go welcome to the
Bots that's me the shark where's the
shark where is a
shark I don't see a shark I'm bagging
now okay I'm waiting for you pick the
pigeon who fits the music as quickly as
possible okay okay I think I can do
this pick the pigeon fits the
music you mean fits the music as in the
outfit
[Music]
right not the Rhythm
or stere okay stereotype them
yeah is this the music already no right
or is it wait for it waitting for
it
uh ah that pierces my heart okay but who
is choosing the last one you Fe e who is
choosing the last one please tell me
it's the Bots but that's stupid Bots
then oh my
God ah the punk one I
think I'd say the punk one
not so much a rivon game anymore but I
like
it I think him
oh most people choose this one it's
funy woo I need to be faster but I want
to make sure I'm not
[Music]
wrong him I think him I think him ah
what the [\h__\h] was that the I saw
something about that the R2 I have to
press R2 did I what what's going
on it's got to be oh
okay why did it take me so long it's
alien and accordion
[Music]
interesting wait let me get that one too
distraction wait I'm waiting
uh him yeah that's like classic music
mixed with like disco or
so shees I like it the
mashups him oh it's like Ry and country
that took me a moment to realize that I
was like what is
this nice idea
oh wait I love that that's so
good oh
jeez like
what Irish hip hop does that
exist I'm
seven why the [\h__\h] are you guys so good
at least there's no Bots better than us
oh yeah the bot bot the Bots are really
bad good good good good good good the
Bots lost that the the the first losers
were all Bots pretty
much okay
okay round two please let it be a game
that I know how to play not the one with
the card Super Striker what is Super
Striker
n hit the balls on the last note of each
Melody the more tokens you accumulate
the higher uh hit the balls on
the
oh this is like uh like yakyu uh English
baseball
[\h__\h] okay I'm not good at that I'm not
good at that cuz they come with
different speeds right oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] oh
slow fast
slow
hi oh actually it's the the the table
soccer ah
I got the bonus rounds what the [\h__\h] is
that advertisement ponio junor D pigeon
I can't see you [\h__\h]
tards what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
got that one what what what it's on
purpose like
this how the
[\h__\h] the faster ones are actually
easier
[\h__\h] just slow
one ah
no come on come
[Music]
on I don't
know
[Music]
disqualify what you're saying I was that
bad
nah
nah no I was
not
no the music I was just looking at the
speed of the ball I was relying on my
eyes okay I'll try it differently next
time
[\h__\h] are you guys leaving the game when
I leave or are you staying in for the
points or
so yeah I thought it was a eye
[Laughter]
thing for getting any balls P those
thank you I feel like for the fast ones
it was easier at that
point
she are you ready I'm going to press
it I'm going to go
in
tournament what the [\h__\h]
man see I saw that grab an item box of
L2 R2 but is that all I have to do like
press R2 or do I have to like aim or
so please let me in let him
in oh no uh
no I want to shake my butt how do I
shake my
butt I can't shake my
[Music]
butt you have to spin the stick which
one and why someone left well no this is
not shaking my butt this is just shaking
my
head how do I how do you shake the
B press four no
way no pressing for it doesn't do
anything
no is it get some help get some
help isn't that like ky's phase or so I
don't
know
what G party is that the first one we
had the normal rhythm game yeah okay
okay
okay I think I can do that one
easily okay okay
okay it is right
let's
go party
party party party
[Music]
can I put these on my
soundboard naap good
[Music]
naap hi
there what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay I only have two hearts
left
what okay I'm fine I thought I
died let's go 14 is not as good as
before but that's fine that's
fine damn you guys good what the
[\h__\h] don't make me lose okay if you're
so good you know I'm going to lose in
the later rounds so chill Tassimo
Tassimo always like losing so early you
okay they may have played yeah I mean
look at the outfits they probably did
Super
Striker I'm not the first Holo to play
this
so ah no
is this one okay I'll try to do it
differently on the on the last
note on the on the last note how do I
note what's the last note if I don't
look oh good luck thank you
[Music]
how
it ready I think I got it but
[Music]
oh oh no no no no
no no
[Music]
I I I get it I get it I get it
no I get it though I understand I was
trying the last round is so difficult
gold
no I'm
trying I swear I'm trying my
best that's brutal I was focusing even
my mouth was open the whole
[Laughter]
time I was I improved right yeah I think
so
too you got better at it I think so you
can see the Improvement oh
pineapple oh the shark now I see a shark
and the
taco and of course the chicken sorry I
didn't warn you that I was going in I'm
so
useless I have the Irish hat Irish Ah
that's
you nice butt shake yeah keep on shaking
that butt oh also there there's a chef
with a egg costume cute your your belly
is so
yolky who's that sumo dude who keeps on
joining us who is that wait there Sumo
dude his um his head his uh
worms
thing was that a collaboration or is it
even the same
Studio I'm the egg Chef oh press
R1 no no no no no no no get out of my
faceh okay okay
yes why' you make me press
that team team seven it it is oh say so
same select the music until you hear in
each musical excerpt as quickly as
possible oh [\h__\h] me oh God no some much
similar
though
no
no okay okay someone got
noticed oh I'm going to I'm going to
lose I'm going to lose
oh
God oh God oh God
help ready no 3 2 1
listen
gu
uh
yes it lets me it lets me listen to it
that's good I thought I didn't get to
listen to
it hi hi hi
[Applause]
uh okay EAS
it yes
[Music]
no uh okay okay okay go
okay what
no [\h__\h] I I don't know they confused
me I just guessed at the
end
uh yeah so last
[Music]
seconds yo yo yo
yo okay
[Music]
do y yo I got the D so fast because I I
know that one we owned one
[Music]
before I don't know it free
[\h__\h] how was that was that bad
[Music]
I'm okay I was like why is there
minus is there oh is it because there's
two 12 and then they jump to 14 but then
why is it not 13 I don't know I'm same
rank I guess okay oh thank God
you shoter did we have that before I
don't think
so oh oh reproduce all the Melodies as
quickly as
possible
but then I have to kind of
know which sound I don't play the
piano yeah there there's been kiking the
keys all this time right and look at us
sitting up there or standing up there
we're so cute have fun and
relax they light up okay okay no talk
listen okay okay okay okay hi I
try two
one listen I'm so
cute I need to
[Music]
aim you're so
cute I wish should had motion
control cute
no stop being so
[Music]
cute it makes me
happy I want give me the
gift oh they move now that's
[Music]
evil they so
cute don't don't don't
separate stay
together you're better when you're
together who wants a separate
piano not me indeed wait who the [\h__\h]
said
that and
how Okay one
[Music]
more I think I did well I mean it it's a
bit difficult to aim with the
joystick w i oh I almost I didn't miss
any though you guys missed probably cuz
you were f you were trying to be faster
I mean look at you you I me look at your
M I had zero misses
round I'm barely
what I better not be losing because I
didn't do so much in a bonus
round oh my God okay ah this is just
extra points for my overall like bread
score
okay next next next game the perfect
shot I never made it this SP five before
I
think let's go photog grab Dolphins when
they're framed by the sun ahuh okay so
do I also hear something there doesn't
say anything about listening but
probably
first time round
three photograph the Dolphins when they
hit the sun with which one all the way
up there right these ones are not
jumping that high
memorize
[Music]
memorize yeah okay almost that was a bit
too
early no
[Music]
oh disappears a little bit that little
[\h__\h] it's it's toxic
[Music]
close
enough I didn't miss a single time is
this
okay
what [\h__\h] you
guys get out of here motion with your
Elite
score what the
[\h__\h]
what I I was too early yeah but I mean
that was my first time but it was
fun
she you hate to see that so
[Music]
truee uh can I buy something with my
bread
crumbs I have
3,100 bread
crumbs I
he oh damn it's all
expensive oh that's so
cute I can
buy no they're saying
bye-bye I want to
buy I want to
buy cuz they don't have that much choice
right now anyway and I'm I mean the
pacifier we can we can totally do that
but can I combine it with my hat uh with
my
earphones yes there oh wait I could do
orange but mine is actually pink anyway
okay that's
me one reason that I use my pacifier
again I never have a reason for my
pacifier this is great okay I'm going in
guys are you
[Music]
ready free two one going in I'm going
in
mhm I do need a reason I should get a
real pacifier yeah for immersion so that
I sound like I actually have a pacifier
in my
mouth p
wa blue you're so
blue why are you
[Music]
leaving not not not not not not what's
the first game a new one or one did I
Know
piano this is a new one play the music
in Rhythm each type of face corresponds
to a specific button
how do I
know
how how do
I is
it cuz the mouths don't have the shape I
first thought it might be the shape but
is it just
uh the smaller one is the first one the
bigger one oh maybe
[Music]
that I have a bad feeling about this
X is small square is not so small square
is mid
[Music]
oh
cute X mozard is my oi
I'm so getting kicked
out this is not my
forte when they get rid of
the
ah when they don't show me what it is I
am so
[Music]
lost
okay now I'm finally feeling it but it's
too late
probably it's so
over how bad was that I think I'm
getting kicked out of the I saw it on
the top right on the rank let me retrive
pleasei
no oh
no no you guys have just played the game
like look at your outfits obviously you
played the game many times before I want
to redrive re run
retrial was a good try I I I will be
better next time I
swear com in guys come in cancel your
other game where you're currently
winning cancel it and come lose with
me do you get a penalty for jumping out
of those games like canceling them so
that you're in with me
again hopefully not
I didn't give you
time okay next time I'll do a proper
countdown but it seems to be pretty easy
to get in a group with
me come on I just got home
[Music]
hello the dump memory game was
next I I I will never know how that one
works so I hope I'm not getting
it had to forcely okay but do you get a
penalty are you okay you got back in see
there you
go it made you join another Lobby well
there's only yeah
well unfortunately there's no private
lobbies let's go
guys give me this give me that one from
before please I want to yes wait that's
the is it is that the yeah that's the
one okay
the game the game is listening I get a
second
chance yeah I can
[Music]
redo oh [\h__\h] she can redo oh [\h__\h] one
day there will be
the
successor where I think I can redo
[Music]
yeah I'm I
am okay it starts easy starts
easy oh the music is
different oh no maybe not no it's the
same
[Music]
what's this song
again I mean that one looks like
unrecognizable
sometimes [\h__\h]
[Music]
[\h__\h] you that one is difficult the
middle one but it's a long one it's not
so clear which one it is to
me no I'm out again no I'm in I'm
in I I saved it at the end there
maybe Redemption Arc no more
retrospective the successor will be
called Redemption I think that's a good
title actually and then it kind of fits
the theme of I can
redo let's go Fitness I think is new
workout I
guess
aha not hold we're we are memorizing and
reproducing
babies no uh the moves and the
Rhythm okay just with the
mhm okay I'll try should be
easy oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah 3 2 1
listen listen
L
okay up up up up oh I was a bit
late left down
Up 3 2 1 listen
[Music]
up
down
up down up the no I get confused like I
get conf
[Music]
[Laughter]
up down up down
[\h__\h] up
down up
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I'm
out I'm out I'm watching the
leader but
[\h__\h] like when once it gets like faster
and all that it's
like it's too fast my brain
cannot catch up at the release like
sometimes I think it's starting already
but then he's still doing more but in my
mind I only registered the first one or
so oh sh I got 100% accuracy on
one
[\h__\h] I would be so bad at this game I
mean watching if you think that just
watching it then try playing it and
you'll you'll feel pure despair or like
you're part of dangan rompa or
so probably didn't even hear that one
did
you I'm very bad at this me too we're
bad together let's
[Music]
go okay I'm going to go in guys I'm
counting down now five four
2 one
tournament yeah there's some that are
without releasing right I didn't realize
that until a little bit later but it's
usually the super super fast ones I
guess but then oh my God it's just too
much to
remember and then I like I feel like cuz
the rounds switch like they go from the
one to another so fast that my brain is
still remembering the one from the
previous one or the previous previous
one but we're already moving on to the
next one so like it's all like
scrambling and mixing in my brain you
know what I
mean it's just too fast listen then
reproduce your music is this the one we
did before yeah okay okay okay this one
is one of the simplest and easiest
ones you get it okay okay okay oh man
facts okay here we go the first round
being something easy at least brings me
further in the future nice sweater by
the way Mr
DJ 3 2 1 hey Mr DJ jump on the
[Music]
replay oh someone died
already oh nice did you see all stars
[Music]
what's that
Melody yo K
FP family
[Music]
yo
sexy
o oh I love it
[Music]
I love that
synthesizer that would be a good bgm for
my stream
[Music]
I think that was really good this time I
have a lot of stars number eight you
guys are getting better too but Hulan
what are you what are you doing down
here you
guys good job guys this
dude is not one of my viewers right this
is some really good addicted player
right is it one of you round
two I wonder
faster than
sound faster than sound wait this is new
too oh we're in the wild west and image
is shown for each round the sound
corresponding to this image is hidden in
the music what find it and draw faster
than your opponent to win what each
round uh-huh the sound corresponding is
hidden in the music
what what
what oh wait I think I understand the
will show like some instrument or so
when I hear it I press or like yeah like
a pig sound ready round one
okay find
it oh
God I won you win [\h__\h] this is
interesting round two
watch find it
I was like what does that sound like
okay it's a
[Music]
Bo a [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
me damn it hey did you not even press
too late too soon okay okay okay thank
you snip shop find
oh I was hearing the ah the paper sound
so often I thought maybe it's that but
okay right after I pressed came the
scissors who was matched up with
me no I think I lost or was it
tutu was it tutu round oh there's more
watch horse okay find it who you
[Music]
course yeah you win
yeah wa I was really focusing I even
looked
away what the [\h__\h] does a pina colada
sound
like oh just drinking it
final round oh [\h__\h]
you baby okay find
it I I was thinking that must have been
it but like ah oh
man there's so many
sounds sheeg guys you lost two
congratulations I I want to try that
again
she listening so hard but they make so
many sounds and then they make you wait
so long and they make you also because
they they when they show you the picture
they don't even let you know what it's
supposed to sound like which maybe is on
purpose that it makes it even more
difficult but come on like I don't
know that you want were looking for a
slurping through a straw sound for the
drink I was like
H I mean yeah now in hindsight I'm like
okay makes sense but you don't know
unless you have played it before you
don't know what to expect if you played
it before you definitely have an
advantage on this one play the baby
giggle I heard million times before
that so it was kind of obvious I mean in
the other rounds they were using the
baby sound a lot yeah thanks for the
membership welcome okay guys are you
ready for another
one 5 4 3 2 1 basically when I start
counting you probably should already
click to go in like when you hear me
counting the drink could sound like a
glass yeah or like I don't know like
maybe like a PE if you like pan clada
kind of like I don't know tropical sound
I don't even know if it was a Pina col
to be
honest or is that new it might be
new promply reproduce the commander
orders aha oh okay X is Jump square is
turn stretch is up Peck is right with
with the circle turn is left turn is
Left Right is Peck stretch is up jump no
yeah jump is X oh God oh God oh God oh
God
PE
turn jump stretch Peck turns jump okay
okay okay here we
go how F how much we just do it right
away or when do I do it
what in in Riven or just
anytime anytime I think hey as as fast
possible I
guess kill
it is this how it is in the army
[Music]
I don't know why I did that I didn't
expect
it [\h__\h] the speed the speed is getting
to
me did I get in did I get in
or oh y y y I'm restarting the app again
by the way
I made
it even though I [\h__\h] up a few
times oh thank
God look at you guys look at you
Jo round KY knows how to follow orders
you have to you have to remember them
too that was a that was a bit confused
uh I wasn't sure like what do they want
me to time it on the Rhythm or just
right away as soon as I am
ready but I think it was just whatever
right away the the earlier the better or
so
oh oh no it on the last second count to
five oh
really cuz then was the timer and I I do
it but everybody was doing it as early
as possible I think okay
anyway Oh you mean this one is on the
fifth node right
you don't mean the previous
[Music]
one ready 2 1
harder ready 3 2
[Music]
1 [\h__\h]
a oh not bad I missed like two
times yo so close I can't believe
it okay the app is really not working
today it's now it's locked me out [\h__\h]
you come
on no I'm not I don't want to put in my
password now and don't know that hard
after look it up okay chill guys until
we're done
here
[Music]
yay you almost eliminated round one a
man I'm I made it I'm so proud round
three please guys let me make it to the
last round please be so nice to me oh
it's a new one that's not good like what
if I don't know it's not PC only it's
also crossplay so um play the correct
notes as quickly as possible
okay yeah it's on Steam and on play no
Xbox I don't know a lot of platforms
look it up Google
uh
training oh God oh
[Music]
God the length doesn't matter
right Len
[Music]
they're not always going to show these
signs
[Music]
okay yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
I just need to look at his neck
get me out of
[Music]
[Laughter]
here oh my
God oh my God
oh what the [\h__\h] zero
Miss sorry that was so funny to me just
now that got so funny because like At
first I was feeling confident but then
again they throw those [\h__\h] curve
balls at
you oh my God
oh my
[Music]
God let me put uh let me try to revive
let me try to revive the
app sheesh
I that was that was really joyful that
made
me
feel like really funny
oh it's too
joyful I want to join and joy and
joy okay my
password
uh what is going on why are they kicking
me out of the app
[Music]
man what am I typing
it uh
it's not what you guys think it is no no
no okay and
and
okay that was so funny that was oh I
live I live to see another
day oh oh
wait o
o o there okay stay
moving
okay I think we got
it okay are you guys ready I'm going to
count down uh from 10 I guess and you
press at I don't know maybe right away
10 9 8 7 6 5 4 3 two 1
T I want another try at that game we
just
played I I I don't think I'll do
necessarily better but I want to try
again it was so funny to me failing was
so funny who would have known that
failing is just so that it just can it
can make you so
happy it might just
yeah I did get bored why did I stop
moving again all right all right I'm
going to Riot I'm going to
Riot I'm going to turn into a gaming
company and it's not going to be
Nintendo you know which one it is right
cuz I said it just now I'm going to
Riot she that was actually good
RI that was actually good ah this is
giving me actually a good mood this this
game is giving me a good mood
round oh you guys with your taunts man
you get some help oh new game I think
that if you laughed then it was not
terrible ah this one I
think generally I was not too
bad I yeah
[Music]
it's going to be okay I
think I love this guy I love him his
hair his suit he's got so much going for
[Music]
him Bring it on I am feeling the
Rhythm a cl cl cl cl cl
[Music]
easy woo
relaxing uh isn't it too oh it sounded
[Music]
lower two instruments let's
go [\h__\h] sorry I just saw
[Music]
uh uh what what was it I forgot I I
forgot I forgot I forgot I'm still
in what was the second
one I already forgot my
brain oh
[Music]
no did you do
no no
[Music]
no okay oh so last second oh my God
please okay okay I'm in I'm in oh no
[\h__\h] I
missed oh oh did I did I make it oh my
God I'm so confused this is so fast
everything's so
fast but oh I'm in oh they're drawing
right now um
I T you made it in finally
I I forgot what to say but sheesh uh I
my brain is trying so hard
and it is rough it is rough out there
let me tell
you oh my god round
two it is so rough out there I was worse
than the first time I played it I
think oh this one again I I I'm getting
I got better at it actually I really did
okay I'm going to [\h__\h] nail
it I think I I am
at the end of the last one I realized I
should count along I I was just like
feeling the fifth one but now I'm
actually I at the end I realized I can
actually count until the fifth one in my
brain even if it's suddenly faster or
slower in the beginning
though it's not bad if you just look at
it though oh my God kill me please I
should not be
talking 2 3 4 4 5 1 2 3 4 5 1 2 3 4 5 1
2 3 4 5 1 2 3 4 5 1 2 3 4 five okay
see 2 1 3 4 5 1 2 3 4 5 1 2 1 2 3 4 5 1
2 2 3 4 5 1 2 1 5 1 five five two 3
five five five
five okay okay okay okay serious
business 2 1 3 4 5 1 2 3 4 5 1 2 3 4 5 1
2 3 4 5 5 1 2 3 4 5 5 2 3 4
5 2 3 4 5 [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you
I can do
better I can do better I swear I know
better I swear my I'm again not
moving
[Music]
no all right now now now I'm
moring what
do I I did not do better I had more this
is done before but I I felt I was able
to
count [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] oh sorry guys I didn't
count I'm so
[Music]
angry counting a lot will mess me up
maybe um no I don't think it was
necessarily messing me
up [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
let me let me redeem
[Music]
myself this game is
addicting tilt
que me counting messed you up oh my God
that's actually amazing because you're
listening to my stream but then even
the just hearing that should also [\h__\h]
you up
though but let's go short stream oh
we're already almost a 2 hours like in
minutes no but I'm having so much fun
right now but my throat man let me take
a fro
candy this is so much fun I want to play
it every day why is this so much
fun I can't comprehend it's so much fun
holy
[\h__\h] oh no wait I don't like this one
anymore I liked it before and now I hate
it I've changed my mind about it
it's so
fun it's so
[Music]
fun but I'm getting more and more try
hard as more time
[Applause]
passes okay you know how professional
sports people they stretch right before
a game that's me right
now no two
[Music]
one uh beautiful
beautiful I'm so good oh very
medieval the bad that was a
[Music]
Bano kind of like that
okay wow wow I'm number
[Music]
one oh really
really uh uh no I almost going to choose
that
I
[Music]
what what
what finally it was more quiet
[Music]
again nice nice nice nice nice
nice
uh no uh I don't know
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] I stop moving again
[Music]
what was the last one
[\h__\h] oh thank God oh thank God I
couldn't take another
one at times I was at the very top did
you see at the top right you can see
um
who's where I am if I'm losing or
winning right now if I got to step up my
game or not I was actually at the top
for a little moment for like two
instrument rounds or
so y nice burger let me let
me but I'm probably standing somewhere
else on your
screen I love this game I I sto moving
again I guess today I'm just uh yeah PNG
WWA I'm so mad memorize oh the Colt one
was I good at this one I think
yeah but then you guys some of your
comments confused me I wasn't sure if it
was okay to press it right away oh
actually no wait never mind I got really
bad by the end of this game ah it was so
difficult
no perf
oh bit too
early up left right
oh
um this one's [\h__\h] confusing again 3
2 1 L
ah [\h__\h]
[Music]
you down
[\h__\h] up
down
okay down up down
[Music]
up down up down okay
okay no
pleasee okay still1
ribon
feeling I did I did
I I was so it yo I actually I had so
many
100% ah look at you losers look at you
losers [\h__\h] Bots and and some other
los actually mostly there's not so many
players anymore at this
point wow round
2 never saw this
one oh
oh would have known that you have to
[\h__\h] mash the buttons when you're not
telling
me finish results I am 460 cm tall best
play was
huh how the
[\h__\h]
okay oh my God what's it going to be let
time the stunt moles that's also a first
one
oh ah okay okay yeah that makes sense
uh you like Bonk Bonk Bonk Bonk and it's
good that they're aligned in the same
pattern as on my controller that should
help me me in my brain unless there's
suddenly more than four holes I don't
know I don't think they can do that
these mes are professional
pigeons what
I thought they were moles what the moles
are pies or the pies are
moles oh
training okay
yeah okay let's go let's do
[Music]
this oh
God o oof oof oof oof 2
1 okay I like it so
[Music]
far 1
oh my
[Music]
God I'm
winning die die
[Music]
okay but until that last one I was so
good and then the second to last one I
only missed like one yo I I mean this
might just be my best game even though
it was first try on this one but I can
keep up with the big
boys I had the most perfect
scores even the winner only has
wa oh my God I'm in the finale but I'm
not going to win there's only going to
be one winner right or that's 7 race
that's 7 race that's a
reference play all the knows on all four
records oh God okay this is more like a
typical rhythm game I
think the way it looks like
[\h__\h] yeah there's a 70s Show that's 70s
Show never saw it though I think welcome
to yeah this is
classic I don't like classic ribon
games well okay I'll
[Music]
try
oh I shouldn't confuse myself
what I didn't realize I had to memorize
it but
[Music]
okay
stop get out of here
what how do I press both I'm not a r
g
okay it's so what there's
more hi hi
what more what why am I the only one
standing oh did they already make it and
what what
[Laughter]
what no let me out of here I don't want
to what do you mean well done why am I
still in here
[Music]
is this always the last game I don't
ever want to do it
again I
[Music]
don't no let me go home I want to go
home I want I I want to see Kaa play
this as she played it before right on oh
oh my oh my God oh my God I can focus on
run on in the time
really wait wait I wasn't I mean 9978
isn't even that different but oh
damn it is this the maximum 12 122
or plate
she only the color once the second time
what see the game didn't even tell me
that I didn't know I thought i' have to
do it again and again and again and
again and the the colored ones were just
hints or so that oh by the way this was
what was here you're getting one hint
I'm throwing you one
bone oh come
on no I thought they were just throwing
me bones because sometimes you know they
show it and then they don't show it
anymore maybe they're just showing it
again because I was doing so bad or so I
don't
[Music]
know but now I
know I see you had to learn that too see
yeah you found thank you it's not that
obvious game is just assuming you know
it after the first time though like all
of these things you'll find out after no
oh no actually no I wouldn't have known
unless uh chat would have would not have
told
me knowing is half of the bad
exactly she oh try another mode like
this one that's the only other
one I guess we can try cuz at least we
made it to the last round once it's
really fun how is this what don't tell
me it's like typical rhythm game though
am I going to match with one of you guys
H sheesh guys sheesh that's a big sheesh
for me
[Music]
where's my where's my partner H where's
my
opponent come on you too scared huh you
little baby you're too
scared you don't want to get up against
me don't you who was you who was you
dance against me I'm a dancer okay I've
been putting out those dance shorts
these days yeah not relying on MMD or
something
or or like a pre-existing animation no
no no no I'm doing it on my own well let
me tell you it's kind of difficult to
dance in the accents straps and stuff
especially the shoes like I taped The
Trackers to my shoes because I noticed
they're like super wobbly it's a [\h__\h]
bot you guys are so scared ah you're
chickens after all okay uh okay oh no
this is typical rhym game
what is the what's the left one this
Arrow ah oh God no
no no
[Music]
no oh sick music
though he's a king why is the bot the
king why does he have all these
items two to
[Music]
Rey no my way not your way no crumbs
baby oh [\h__\h] oh oh I thought he has to
play them for some
reason cuz they were on his
side okay feel the
music okay I'm feeling I'm feeling
it oh
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] oh I love
[Music]
it huh
am I winning
no oh
[Music]
God why is he dancing so much he's so
happy someone shoot
him shoot the bird
[Music]
I can't I'm not a r
gamer oh I live I'm standing I'm not
dead that's one thing oh so I get around
to do I
[Music]
get b c maybe it's the slower one but do
I get full HP or do I have to go with
what I have no ready oh no I'm so
[Music]
dead [\h__\h] you what what I mean the the
the final one yeah I get it but the
other ones why was I getting hit for
those [\h__\h] you bot I want to play
against you guys then I have a higher
chance I can't win against a bot the
robots they're going to kill us all this
should be a lesson to you guys don't
give the robots too much
power going to give it one more try but
I'm so bad at this because this is like
I'm glad actually that most of the games
in the tournament style are not like
typical rhythm game style because as you
can see and as you have seen in other
ribm games that I've tried which are not
many but as you can see I'm not good at
that it's like no as as soon as I have
to press two buttons at once it's so
over
[Music]
[Applause]
I will be a
downfall [\h__\h]
man oh please tell me that's one of you
guys and you're not too good at the game
please
[Music]
he's one of the top players every game I
don't think that that it's a viewer then
right it's just someone who's really
good and plays it all day
right or is it moon dog it's not moon
dog
it round
one two the
[Music]
this let me leave my Nest let we go yay
we're leaving the nest with this
one sorry I'm so
excited we're turning like
ballet
[Music]
oh oh
no
stop not as bad as
[Music]
before how can I dodge
it I sense on your back oh
[\h__\h] oh
[Music]
oh your wings
I didn't do as bad compared to
him
[Applause]
she I don't know they're all good I love
these
songs ready I'm going to lose anyway
though cuz now it's more difficult you
know it's
over chy we're in the
jungle yeah [\h__\h]
that [\h__\h] that I'm how how did heina
like how did he lose so much HP in the
first round but now you your HP you
didn't lose a single HP how how how were
you just trying to make me feel
safe what the
[\h__\h] oh
man use keyboard you think it's easier
people generally recommend playing on
the
controller I want to do one more
tournament round okay going to count
down from 10 more guy more guy last all
one last tournament is the final
tournament I love this
music it's such a
banger 10 9
[Music]
87 6 5 4 free
to
one bamboozle
[Music]
hold have Ian's Instagram posted my BBB
is that even do we even
have I don't know that we have
one I don't I don't think we have one
[Music]
Follow by H what is the hon real
though
really I know we have a official Tik Tok
and I know some members have like ID
members in particular have a
Instagram I didn't know Ian had
a Instagram
really you got in let's
go you got too let's
go please be
nice gu that's new I think
o okay but first round usually is easy
pick the patient who fits the music as
quickly as possible oh wait we did this
one before okay okay okay okay that one
was not too
difficult a John following okay but who
says Anan is
real who says Anan is real H nowadays
I'm seeing a lot more noan than aan
around you know maybe aan aan was never
real to begin
with you know ready I don't
know here we go I need to pee wait for
it fast oh this time last time people oh
more people were picking a different one
but this time she I was one of the fast
ones I
think
yeah easy I was again one of the fastest
ones one of the five fastest look are
you seeing this C
be sheesh
[Music]
sheesh let's
go uh uh you God I don't uh
Amigos took me a moment to realize what
the [\h__\h] is the next to him though
what's that supposed to
be I don't recognize
[Music]
that
o woohoo yeah you are guilty you're so
guilty wait for it
[Laughter]
[Music]
let's
go punk Irish punkish wait for
[Music]
it what what the [\h__\h] is that second
genre I hear the the the Disco or
whatever that is wait for it what the
[\h__\h] is that
[Music]
huh [\h__\h] oh it's like oh his lower body
is Irish I was wondering what those
clothes were the hat is more
recognizable so it's like zombie and ah
[\h__\h] christas the Christmas SPS are
really really
recognizable
nice guilty guilty indeed you're honor
oh man that's funny this is so funny
yay I'm
10 yay look at you guys look at you guys
look at you
guys look at you guys look at you guys
look at you look at you look at me now
Look at You unknown
no no what happened
[Music]
unknown what happened with
you oh no come back to living
ones okay okay I think I was really good
at this one I was indeed really good at
this
one right I was I was rocking
this he I haven't stopped moving for a
while too that's that's a good
sign ladies and gentlemen welcome to
thei take and relax just made me so
happy they make such cute noises it's
not
fair oh God 3 2
[Music]
1 uh okay
yay oh God I'm not sure
[\h__\h] first
[Music]
mistake oh my God I I can't [\h__\h] see
you [\h__\h]
idiot it was not as mean
[Music]
before okay close though my
aim oh I have been rescued but I think I
would have I would have been fine I
think so close to
losing why am I doing worse the second
time in these games sometimes
yeah he taking the L taking that
freaking
[Music]
[Applause]
L
yay let's go let's go let's go let's go
give me the good one
o I think I liked this one that one was
fun until it wasn't
anymore but I think it was generally fun
for the longest time it only got a
little bit difficult at the last round
right taking the L now they're calling
me cringe you're going to hear all
saying
loser you're a
[Music]
loser oh yeah focus focus on the
moles I love this game
I love The Melodies man I'm like a baby
[Music]
hey
hey hey
[Music]
hey
faster it's too early
[Music]
okay okay okay okay y even harder
no oh
[Music]
God it's so
over I was
before what happened what happened to
the
champion
[Applause]
no I had more perfect scores than you
sucker okay but you are pretty good and
you were pretty good
too why why must it end like
[Music]
this I can't become crocodile alligate
wait let's just say it's an
alligator oh but no I don't know
[Music]
oh wait oh there's the cloes what the
[\h__\h] why are you hiding
them why are you hiding them so
low oh my
God what what I thought there was his
only voices there what the [\h__\h] is this
a p
here it looks like uh animal's
nose [\h__\h] off fly just because it's the
only room with the lights on doesn't
doesn't mean you can come in in here get
out damn the Sumo is so
expensive what the [\h__\h] washing machine
though toaster oh
cute oh you can become Irish or medieval
wait that wasn't supposed to be Irish it
was
medieval wait I think originally I it
gave me Irish uh medieval Vibes this is
Irish yeah yeah yeah yeah now it mixed
together Irish Irish music do be feeling
CL of mediev it surely has been around
since the medieval times
so I wish it's
Irish okay now I can put on
on the hat so that I'm no more a pigeon
I don't have to pretend anymore to be
something I'm not let's
[Music]
go but I think I should end it
here I've been
having an illegal amount of
[Music]
fun I'm going to read Super Chat Super
Chat yummy time
wait is this like was there oh yeah we
can choose a soundtrack for super
chats oh I like this this
chill oh I completed the challenge card
you know what where where are the
challenge
cards here I I I I I
become eggplant if I want to but I don't
want
to ooh oh
sheesh yeah sorry what was I saying I'm
I'm I'm looking for
music this one's really good too I think
but maybe a little bit too fast of a
rhythm
[Music]
maybe this one I think it it's uh maybe
maybe the most fitting for like I need
you know we need like a slower
ribon okay guys thank you for playing oh
if I Tab out it
will never mind never mind I think
because I I think I'll stay tapped out
so forget that we're not playing your
music but I was going to say thank you
for uh tuning in if you want to stay for
the Super Chat you're welcome to stay
you know usually we are indulging in
some tangents while we're reading the
super chats you know here and there a
little bit just a tiny bit speaking of
super chats I forgot but then I was
reminded that for tomorrow's members
only stream I said I might have to do a
super chat rating stream remember
because we have a lot of members only
super chats that need to be read from
the previous stream um so we will be
doing that but I have one more like of
course we'll be talking in between but
uh I also have one specific plan uh that
I would like to make with
you you'll see tomorrow but you'll have
to help me with
something but yeah we'll we'll just be
reading super chats I mean we're doing
weekly members only streams so one
stream being super chat reading when we
actually really should be doing that
because we have so many should be
forgivable
I think we really need to do it we
really need to do
it does it involve the usual room maybe
for
Me Maybe for me okay let me try to find
a
BTM wa is going to the usual room what a
Twist guys what a freaking
twist what does that mean what does that
mean
okay let's let's pick
[Music]
something I love
this I have chosen
immediately okay uh we go
here oh it's girls talk mode
[Music]
welcome to girls talk only girls allowed
so everybody else
leave just
[Music]
kidding I guess I'll stay in the
KATU but I need to be
smaller hi hi
[Music]
Get Out Boys no
stay
okay it's a little bit distracting
actually oh
chill hi Super Chat where do we read how
do I
read how to read how do Super Chat
how how
see it's good that I tangent it in the
beginning because I think you have
noticed it was a little bit impossible
oh thank you to super uh to read super
chats H what
to to tangent sorry Brain Brain Brain
Brain Brain Brain
[Music]
Brain it was a yeah not recommendable
either to tangent during this kind of
game I have no
regrets okay yeah I'm at the fif Sim
[Music]
stream I have a cat hair on my
nose y' my cats have been so sweet
especially smoothie I mean chunky wonky
came around too pretty soon like right
after the
Tweet yeah we've been cuddling plenty
but especially Smoothie has been so
clingy so
happy they're doing
great yeahum and my strawberries are
thriving so what else could you be
asking for although I wish I had more
now I'm really thinking man cuz my mom
okay you guys are praising me for the
strawberries but I I think I I didn't do
much I just gave them water like almost
every day I I
think and my mom gave me the the base
plants like she already grew them to a
good
stage a pretty good stage thanks for the
membership
renewal that's all you got to do I guess
so but but I I think if I would have
grown them from the seed stage I don't
think I would
have done so well but my mom has been
growing a lot of strawberry plants and
you know she offered to bring me a few
of them oh so why not right I took them
I took them in but it's not that many
I'm not going to get that I realized I'm
not going to get that many strawberries
from it especially cuz one of them the
one that's not on the picture uh has
been growing way
less way less strawberries than the
other one
has way less fruit on
it do you prune your plants what does
that mean is that the the thing that the
bees normally
do I did that before when I was uh
growing berries
before uh from an earlier stage on and
those uh I I I if you call it that
that's pollen okay well I tried
pollinating a plant before cuz my mom
told me to do it what what if it was a
prank can you
[Music]
imagine listen what you going to do is
you're going to take a little brush and
then like a [\h__\h] idiot go to your
plant and brush brush brush every single
tiny Bud yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah no you
totally have to do that imagine if it
was a prank now that I think about it
that's really um realistic a funny
little prank but uh no it does sound
like a prank right but no it's real I
think I mean unless I got pranked but no
I'm pretty sure yeah they
yeah no but what's pruning like
cutting I I didn't cut anything I cut
like U yesterday I cut a little bit of
one of my indoor
plants cuz it did have a lot of a couple
of Dead Leaves since a long time
ago it has accumulated
some m
to a bit bits of but you only cut away
bits
that are dead no well I guess in this
case you might want to cut bits that are
not looking like they're going to carry
fruit cuz they don't have those like
buds or
so
[Music]
uh huh cuz so then they don't soak up
the W but but I in my case I don't know
if it would have helped I think that
other plant just doesn't have as much
potential I got lucky with this one but
now I wonder like if I
leave uh dear gardeners any Garden
experienced people here if I leave like
a red ready to eat
strawberry on the plant for too
long will it
mold or is that or is just stay
good until like the whole plant just
[Music]
dies it
will so I should eat it once I see it
[Music]
ready but it will take a little while
right not as long uh it will take longer
than when strawberries are just
like yeah like picked in in in the
supermarket
like when it's I would imagine when it's
on the plant it doesn't take as long
make it over rip okay I guess I'mma eat
it all when I see it I'm not going to
make anything special of it I'm just
going to eat it like that as a snack as
a little reward nice sweet
strawberry
randomly just because I don't even have
that many so I can't make that much out
of it
anyway yeah I had uh like two I think I
had two so
far one last night and one today they're
pretty good they're very
um red inside and
outside the taste is
sweet m not the best strawberry I've
eaten so far actually but really
good amazing self-control
yeah I might eat more now though now
that I realize that I should eat them
faster cuz you never know they might die
before I get to eat
them so once they're red I'll eat them
okay two crops somewhere from Strawberry
you you talking about you're talking
about a certain game we
played and then I just I just pick them
off of the plant right I don't have to
pick it in a special way
right have you read any spats
yet
hey hey you you guys we haven't spoken
in a few days so we need to catch up you
know I need to put up the holot talk
question
thing yeah and after the stream can you
guys remember remind me if I forget
after the stream I'm going to put up V
question
request afterwards
yeah it is it is a short
stream you know yesterday I felt really
motivated I can't believe actually
yesterday is the day I got back because
the day was so long for
me it felt like 2 days recently actually
the past 5 days all felt like 2 days in
one oh
man cuz yesterday I arrived in the
morning and I took a long ass
nap but then yeah then I did a lot lot
lot of things and then and then and then
I I started I partially unpacked my
suitcase today I almost finished it but
I have so much stuff don't know where to
put these
things um but I I'm all over the place
right now with my
thoughts
uh uh uh
[Music]
so what was I just saying oh
yeah now what was I saying I don't know
but yeah I was what was my point what
was my point I was just saying the days
are long the days are very long oh yeah
and that it's weird that I just arrived
yesterday I feel like I've been here
longer already
no it was just
yesterday yeah dot dot dot dot dot dot
dot dot dot dot I'm not okay oh okay not
okay oh yeah yeah why did I say that
because we haven't talked in a while and
I was my point was it feels like we
didn't talk for a long time I guess
because every day feels so long right
now
H but actually I wasn't gone for that
long
H I spent a lot of time of me being gone
in the air and on at
airports oh my God can I tell you
something that really pissed me
off oh I have tangents oh do I oh boy do
I have
tangents I need a
map of the
airport I think
is
[Music]
this actually I don't think I can really
tell by this
but
um um wait should I tell this now
um should I tell this now maybe yeah uh
you guys remember in terms of Airlines I
have one sworn enemy thanks for the red
super
chat yeah I'll save some of course but I
have one sworn enemy
remember there's one airline that I
never want to fly with ever
again yeah yeah Turkish
[Music]
Airlines
somehow it's just so happened that this
time I had to fly with Turkish
Airlines
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[\h__\h] and I will say the flying
were good uh I actually I flew business
class thank
god um there would have been direct
flights too but I had to fly Turkish
Island um and I stopped over in
eastanbul right so the first flight is
like pretty short it's like 2 hours or
so to eastanbul and then it's like on
the way to Thailand it's shorter on the
way back it's a bit longer but but it's
like around 9 to 10 hours from eano to
Thailand and in between I had uh on my
way to Thailand I had like 2
hours approximately maybe 2 hours 15
minutes or
so
oh
[Music]
what you mean you you worked as an
inspector for Turkish
Airlines what that pretty long that is
as it turns out not long I thought it
was actually from my experience anything
longer than 2 hours is kind of
unnecessary at most airports uh also
just because it's just like
blah anything below 2 hours depending on
the airport might get stress 2 hours is
actually
perfect yeah so first flight to
asemble was fine was nice actually I was
quite pleasantly surprised their cabin
was really nice the seats were really
nice so now I've actually experienced I
I want to do like I kind of want to do a
ranking now that I've had the pleasure
the luck to be in business class in
several Airlines
already uh in the in the first
fight the uh I really really liked
the um cabin the the seats that we had
they were really uh modern and like dark
style uh they felt really
new they didn't have like some of the
business class seats have doors so you
can completely close off and be private
some
don't this one did not have the door but
I still felt pretty private in it from
the the way it was styled this I can
actually I want want to draw it for you
or actually maybe I'll find a
picture or maybe I should I don't know
when I'm talking badly about an airline
maybe I shouldn't use their
pictures about
that let
me but I don't really I don't really
have anything bad to say this time about
the airline not really not much actually
have more good things to say maybe
maybe
maybe you're lucky you're getting off
easy this
time
okay so let me draw this a little bit
here so uh the cabin um it was like
sometimes there's like straight seats
right but this time
I'm uh there's like there's these seats
where okay maybe your head is
here and your
armrest and stuff like your table one of
your tables cuz you usually then you
have another table that comes even from
here or from in front of you here's a TV
okay here's a window let's say you have
a window
seat so you kind of uh you can lie down
fully flat and then your body is kind of
uh
diagonal right and then the person
behind you will be the other actually a
little bit more cuz like here there's
another like sometimes there's a table
there sometimes here's your dinner table
and then you push it pull it forward or
so but your legs will end up being like
underneath because then for
example uh although it depends it
depends then actually so it should be
like this the person behind you is like
this and their feet are I guess that's
under your seat and so it goes like Z
dang like this right like a
braid get
it then seats these seats I actually
like them um I've I've seen these seats
in several Airlines now and they're
usually pretty good and often they have
a
door
here and if you are in the middle then
usually it's like two rows and on the
window it's like one row but in the
middle is usually two row rows of people
usually the couples go
here and then in the middle between them
there's a divider if you want to use it
and then there's a door but sometimes
there's no door but the divider is
usually there
okay okay okay so this is the basic what
of the the cabin the first one this was
Turkish Airlines uh the the cool one the
modern one the food was really good okay
I want to say that because it gets even
better later in my flight back I had
generally one of the best pieces of meat
I've ever eaten let alone in an
airplane I I ordered some like beef
stuff and I didn't expect it to be so
good but the beef was so like really
tender there was no like flaxy um uh uh
uh fatty like pieces that I couldn't
chew no it was really good the meat was
really good and also they had good
desserts and for breakfast choices and
these flights this time for once they
had like sweet options like one time
they had a kuu with like crap with
apricot and inside and vanilla sauce and
the vanilla sauce was actually like it
really seemed fresh it wasn't like
starting to develop some skin you know
what I mean and then it was like
pancakes uh and stuff like that like
actually sweet options I was so excited
cuz I love eating sweet for breakfast
yeah and then uh on I I changed in e but
okay here's the thing Turkish Airlines
is I think
TK and my second flight in this case was
Tai which was
Tai what's the short do you guys know
actually for their Airline tha Air way
or Airlines it was something with t TG
okay was it was it
TG T okay I believe you yeah Ty air is
TG so that's really similar right okay
so here's my problem that happens in
eastan oh I'm so mad I'm so mad okay I
arrive and
I uh when I arrived there was no gate
yet for my second flight so I thought
okay I'm going go to the business launch
and check it out and business launch is
a really uh impressive actually really
big uh lots of like live cooking
stations now I have seen some other
business lounges now and they did not
have live cooking stations and in
example they had it's actually quite
famous their Lounge they have so many
different options and they're all
cooking life for you I mean they're all
the same dishes like for many years now
they don't change it up but apparently
it's really good I didn't try any of the
food I only tried some desserts
but they have a lot of uh
snacks and apparently they have I didn't
find them but they have someone running
around uh who will massage you for free
for 15 minutes man you must be so lucky
when you find that
guy yeah uh so they have that okay so I
went to the business launch and I wait
there I wait for my uh uh gate and I
think it said something like uh let's
let's say I don't know the exact hour
anymore but let's say
15 is when the gate would
show and then from there until boarding
starts and I think it was only like 10
minutes or
so mind you Eble airport is
big but until it leaves it was
still I think maybe 1 and a half hours
roughly or one 1.2 hours or so
roughly yeah it's an employee yeah yeah
yeah yeah it's real
so anyway I'm chilling in the lounge and
I see I I keep on looking up to see if
the gates there
no
okay
finally I see flight to
Bangkok
uh they
they they show a gate and I'm like okay
I guess uh now that the gates there I
can think about going there soon I think
I didn't I didn't get up immediately but
pretty soon after because boarding would
start
soon so okay the airport is kind of
like apparently shaped like this I
didn't really when when you're in it you
don't really know where you are it
doesn't feel like it was shaped like
this and I don't know exactly where's
the business Lounge in this can I see
[Music]
it ow know but let's just say cuz this
is how it felt okay let's say let's say
the lounge is somewhere in the middle
probably and the gate I had to go to was
here originally I it felt like I came
from somewhere like here and when then
all the way it took so long until I was
in the lounge so I make my way starting
I started walking really slowly because
it didn't say that not really slow just
normally because it didn't say that it
was boarding yet
and it took a
while and then I reached like uh like
around here is when it says start it
started boarding I'm like okay well it's
okay I don't have to be the first in the
airplane they're going to be boarding
for a while right and
then so I started walking a little bit
faster but immediately here they say
like two or three minutes later I
noticed the signs they suddenly say last
call in red and I'm like
what
what what and I was carrying a lot of
[\h__\h] I was carrying um a bag with uh my
laptop but thank God I didn't bring the
heavy laptop I brought a more
lightweight laptop my old one laptop and
uh an iPad in one bag then a small cross
body bag bag really small but I forgot
to buy I wanted to buy souvenirs
beforehand and then put them in the
suitcase but no I forgot about that and
then just bought them at the dutyfree
and carried it around so I was kind of
carrying like free
things and biggest mistake ever I
thought it might be kind of
comfortable to wear flipflops
have you guys ever tried to go fast when
you're already exhausted and carrying a
lot of things in
flipflops can't can't run with them yeah
really
difficult uh this was one of the worst
experiences of my life because the last
call was stressing me the [\h__\h]
out this path maybe looks short here but
it was so long actually and it didn't
even feel like it was just one r right
and one left no not at all but
okay but this was a this was a long
paath and like they they give you the
gate I started walking slowly and then
immediately last call I'm like what the
[\h__\h] is going on and it really stressed
me out but then the last call I went
like here up up until here maybe no
maybe more like here and then I realized
something first of all the last call is
going on for quite a while thank God but
then I realized something
here I thought I thought I thought my
second flight was also with Turkish
airines cuz like my whole tickets they
all like look like Turkish airine
tickets but no it was actually
TI I was going towards the Turkish
Airlines flight to
Bangkok [\h__\h] fly right in front of
me [\h__\h] you I was going I was rushing in
pain with my legs dying thanks to the
flip-flops towards the Turkish Airlines
flight the first one was Turkish Island
but the second one was Tha to Bangkok
same
destination which was 5 minutes apart in
departure
time to the ti which was also not just
same destination and almost same time
but almost same writing
tie flight to Bangkok but I realized
this thankfully early enough but already
after so much exhaustion I realized it I
I look at the board and I'm like and I
was like wait wait a moment something
feels wrong and CU I saw a different
Bangkok flight on the on on the board
which was like just the thing is like
it's it even is written so close
together that Bangkok yeah and then
there's something else here and then
there's Bangkok again and this is like
TK and this is
TG and this is like the boarding time or
so it says like it's just 5 minutes
apart
dude like it's so easy to make this
mistake yeah so I realized it
and my real gate
is here
here completely different letter like
this was maybe like uh like G or
something and this was like a or b or
so it was on the complete other side and
at this point when I was here or like
here my real flight which was 5 minutes
apart while this was already last call
this was thankfully not last call yet
it's said uh I think it was at bard
or or it was just about to start I'm not
sure but it looked like at least I still
had some time but I was already so
exhausted on [\h__\h] flipflops yeah I
think without flip flops this would have
been way less exhausting but the flip
flops and the stuff I was carrying and
then oh my God so I started making my
way back and I'm like [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I can't
I can't miss this
flight I finally I finally like get
closer but already this time already
earlier like by the way I make it back
to the same area where I started off at
is when it says last call so
now now I
have supposedly more path ahead of me
for the last call and I was I was trying
to walk fast but I really my legs were
it felt like I had huge stones on my
legs I could barely lived them even
walking normally like they they had like
huge crabs in them and I wanted to I
wanted to believe because I noticed that
this last call was going on so long like
what the
[\h__\h]
right they they they just call it way
earlier than necessary I think makes you
think like you have to go really fast
turns out you
don't Crocs I should have won Crocs
maybe [\h__\h] flip-flops I thought that
was like comfy but then I was of course
also getting blisters yeah I was getting
blisters I my legs were cramping like
hell I was out of breath I was so sweaty
I was so sweaty
too it was really
bad but around here it was still last
call it was still last call and then I
arrive and okay it was really close it
looked really close I was The Last
Passenger to enter I looked behind me
there was no one
following there was no one following it
really looked like the crowd was
completely uh gone like the moment I
entered like in front of me there were
three more people but I was like behind
them the last one I was really at the
end and I [\h__\h] finally made it I get
in and they still stand there for ages
and they still have the doors open for
ages why do you do the last call thing
so early you're stressing me out so much
I mean barely anyone boarded after
that some people did still a while later
but I'm like dude I had so it wasn't
even medium
yeah I had so much time are you [\h__\h]
kidding me
no they should um the thing is I should
have looked uh but I was I was
scrambling I was so rushed and stressed
but I could have just checked the ticket
um I was the whole time I was wondering
okay when does it close when does it
close though uh it says on a ticket it's
it closes 20 minutes before but even
then the last call was like 40 or or 15
minutes before it takes off so I was
like maybe
what is it really closing that
soon it scared the [\h__\h] out of
me go I just go where the ticket say my
ticket didn't have a gate yet that's the
thing I had to wait for the gate to be
revealed on the on the screen and then
it was like two really similar flights
to the same destination with similar
names to to Bangkok with 5 minutes
apart
yeah but yeah I made it and I had a lot
lot of time to spare even though I was
the last one to board almost like at
that moment there was no crowd there
anymore and I was sweaty and I needed
some ice cold water right away and yeah
the Thai Airlines cabin was much older
than the Turkish one I've noticed but it
was the same kind of
zigzag
pattern they were nice and all the food
was okay
and yeah so I made my way to Bangkok and
on the way
back I flew only with Turkish
Airlines no tie which I got excited
about because I really liked the first
cabin and then it turns out this cabin
was so different on my flight back the
cabin was so different it was so lame it
felt like I think it was an older cabin
basically this one had only
no no none of these like solo seaters no
no no they were
two then the the path and then
two and then the path and then again
two and the two had like an armrest in
between and the divider and then there
was a big like here's the seat there's a
big space and then there's a TV and like
another footrest which worked as like
you can open it and then put your stuff
inside but like you're sitting next to
someone no matter what no matter what
and it was overly overall just not as
cool of a cabin but whatever I I still
slept uh generally quite good on these
ones except for it was [\h__\h] hot and
dry like in the
Sahara but yeah someone was um only on
one flight someone was sitting next to
me on the other flight there there was
no one but on the flights back man I had
the best meat ever it was so good the
food was so good so I'm actually I don't
have anything really negative to say
about Turkish Allin this time this was
on me although I have to say it is
purposefully confusing and the last call
is unnecessarily
early uh and the this cabin was old and
I I would have preferred having the
first cabin
um but the food was so good
sheesh sheesh Turkish alens Redemption
so real oh and I got a really cute bag
you know in business class you get these
like goodie bags uh where there's like
hand cream and a dental kit and socks
and an eye mask and all kinds of things
in there and and I've got several of
these now but the Turkish Airlines one
was the cutest I've ever seen I've seen
these Bang these little bags they all
have cool
designs when I flew to uh was it Abu
Dhabi yeah Abu
Dhabi their bag was really nice too but
this one was pink and and more spacious
than the other ones and the fluffy socks
were also pink normally they only put
like like plain plain black socks in but
this one had pink fluffy socks with
those plastic stoppers on your
souls I
genuinely would will wear them at
[Music]
home Plain As in that they're fluffy not
just plain Fabric and yeah not black but
pink plain plain no I mean that's what
I'm saying I'm trying to tell you they
were fluffy like fluffy Fabric and pink
and I think guys get like a uh like a
different not the pink bag and the pink
socks they get a different one but they
gave me the pink one and I was so happy
those are so cute everything was so
cute those are high quality socks yo
fluffy pink socks with the No No slip
thingy yeah sheesh they're cute I've
added them to my sock collection
not sock collection sock
[Laughter]
collection what happened to the flip
flops after the boarding yo I was dying
I had so many blisters by the time I
arrived in in
Bangkok my feet hurt so much the whole
trip long my feet were hurting so
much the whole trip I I was suffering my
feet were
suffering yeah but it's okay on my way
back I I wore super boring sneakers
that
uh have since a while ago since I first
mowed my
lawn have a green tint because I did not
realize how
much the
grass dies whatever footwork you're
wearing I did not know and I cannot get
like I tried to get all the grass off
yeah but the somehow the color
[Laughter]
remains why was I not warned about this
Rie
mistake
man I I can probably somehow get it off
if I give them a deep clean but how how
do you deep clean shoes I have to look
up some YouTube
videos yeah I need I need some shoes for
outdoor for like la lo lo the mowing Lo
the moow mowing the lawn but yeah sorry
for flexing the business
class it's just exciting it's
exciting and the food is so good the
food was really so good
man surprisingly
good
H they had sweet stuff
man rain boots should do good
a I do have rain boots but they're
fancy cannot are they really um I can't
cut into them
right well my other shoes are fine and
these ones are fine too probably but
they're white my my rain boots are white
[Music]
man an old pair of black sneakers I
don't have uh black sneakers don't put
the
don't put ever in the W you mean shoes
of course I'm not putting my shoes in
the wash
machine
dude I would not do
that I I I I have I have one pair of
sneakers that I don't really use for
anything but those I have now taped The
Trackers on for motion
capture and I don't want to put them off
but I I realized okay first first of all
that was a genius idea but then I
realized when I was like dancing in them
uh I didn't do that for the practice
stream I did that for my own motion
capture session
afterwards uh where I took the shorts
outside of the stream but I
realized it made it easier but at the
same time it felt weird I I taped it
with like packaging tape right all
around the shoe the shiny plastic tape
and now it's like making sounds
constantly it's
like you
know like this every Every Move I
Make Every Step I Take I just hear this
sound I can't drown it out it's just so
loud nice
improv no it is duct tape no no no
actually no it's not duct tape yeah duct
tape would would have been better yeah
now that I think about it that wasn't
duct tape it's just the the shiny
plastic packaging tape
yeah isn't binding it into the string an
OP no no no no no no not really no um
I've tried to put it under the shoe and
then tying the shoe above but uh it's
unsafe it doesn't stay in place and I
got so sick of it so I just taped
it and my fum track
I also just taped
it the one that fell off did s the I
sent it to them uh I think n saw my
message and then said oh my god oh I
watch it after my stream and then I
don't think she did I think she forgot
about it but she got really excited
without even watching
it and suici I was like oh I saw it it
was really amazing and then she asked me
oh what what uh what
3D Hardware stuff are you using you know
everybody's getting
curious everybody wants the
xense I just got it because I know I'm
not in Japan and I can't use the studio
ever
yo [\h__\h] huge ass fly you've been
living here red free for too long I will
kill you one day the day will come
[\h__\h] off [\h__\h] off it's so fat it's such
a fat fly I would mind less if it was
smaller but it's disgusting how fat it
is oh
man imagine if you get other holos to
get suits
too then I'm setting the trends again I
don't know if I
actually I don't know right now this is
like the one thing uh I have where I can
do something cool that others maybe
can't do as much but I realized actually
somehow everybody's doing dance shorts
right now I don't know how they do it
uh I think some of them are using like
motion right but somehow everybody's
doing it it's not even that special
right now that I get
to do it with my accents with oh you're
on my screen now aren't you I will
punch my
screen it survived and it flew towards
me [\h__\h] off [\h__\h]
off why are my cats not killing
it
anyway yeah I I I'm telling them when
they ask me but uh I'm not keeping a
secret or
so but yeah I I would like it to be my
special thing for a little while longer
ideally also it's not I don't know if I
even want to recommend it because it's
not that easy to use I've been like
struggling with
it it's not perfect
either the motion capture I've been
struggling a lot with
it what what you mean they don't have B
of FS who know how it works what wait
what are you talking
about yeah we should read super chats
yeah
sure I'm just you know I was gone for a
few days Oh you mean go ah ah yeah and
it's more like gosu staff than
go wait that reminds me of one thing let
me just let me just check really quick
okay okay okay uh no no the thing is the
goo collab will not happen until I get
my model converted into a format uh that
works with
go uh software
uh and
that normally the conversion like you
can do that in like a day uh but I'm
requesting it to be done like it's
something I can request within the
company so that I don't have to like
commission someone or so to do it but
they told me it might take more than a
month so it's basically we're waiting
for that model and then we can
go yeah it's just the model conversion
it's this actually so that's the same
thing as remember passort two
two pass part two
two
so that's also in order to use you know
I was trying to get my model into that
in order to do that I had to convert my
model for that too and you know I uh I
saw because Marine Senai got her model
converted to work in the game I
saw that that's a possibility so I asked
about it uh if they can do it for me
and and then they said yeah maybe two
three four weeks or
so and I'm like
oh oh interesting uh what about manai
and she got it right away and they're
like ah like it was like a like a test
or something I don't know I'm like oh
okay then I tried to get it earlier
because the game just released and I
wanted to do it like ASAP right not wait
ages so uh I got I asked who who was it
Kudo or someone else I I had them try to
help me they converted it but then you
can't just convert it for passport two
it had to be under a c
certain uh threshold
of MB or GB or so right the
size
so this was of course post MMD mhm it's
it's not that long
ago so we were trying to make it smaller
and smaller but then it it didn't look
so good so in the end we gave up because
we couldn't get it to work properly we
got the model to kind of go in game but
then it was like buggy and
glitchy yeah did you ever get the
approval for doing the Pokémon dance uh
when I asked originally and I was told
um this might be
difficult and then a few days later
someone else did it right and then I was
like uh does that mean I can do it and
then I was told oh yeah I guess you can
do
[Music]
it so yeah I'm I'm just like
I'm going to probably do some motion
capture this week I want to do the poked
Dance I'm late now Yoo could have done
it
[Music]
earlier yeah PES to so basically was the
same conversion but uh we just gave up
on it and then I just played it normally
because it would have taken so much
time uh and yeah the poka Dance I'm
going to take the poka dance Maybe this
week and I want to do one or two other
dances I still want to do the mikoi
dance and I want to do another one
that's secret oh I don't another that's
many there's so many dances right now
that I have to
do so many dances
man K want K I was thinking about it but
the K I don't see like a full it's like
a really short one it's not the full
Horus I don't know maybe maybe she has
like a full reference cuz somebody must
have made the Coro right maybe she has
like a video that I can use as a
reference no for the go single one it's
not no file size limit but I didn't want
to like bother with asking other people
annoying them again so I asked if the
company can do it cuz it is something
they can
do it just takes a long time
but in theory if you guys have the skill
for it you could probably do it in one
day you can easy collab go on EAS Island
yep once I have it then there's nothing
in the way also at the time I was still
trying to figure out uh the exent
software and like getting everything to
work so I was like well I might need
some time anyway to get all of this
working and then I'm going to Thailand
and all that so I have some time before
you know I can wait a little bit is what
I was thinking
it's okay I I can wait I'm just the
message I just wrote is just me making
sure that they're actually like on it
that it was
actually you know that my my request was
relate to the right people just checking
up cuz I haven't heard about it in a
while but I don't think it's been a
month
yet or hasn't been no not quite not
quite maybe it's been like two or three
weeks
now
yeah
what shash sh sh shash the the the daily
random you want me to end the stream
right now or
what
concert no once I get um going I might
want to if they if is like Idol releases
a new song I want to do a dance cover of
theirs as
well yeah but yeah first I'm waiting for
my model so so so so so it is still
short yeah and I have much to talk
about so
yeah that's how things are right now I'm
going to probably take some motion
capture this week I hope so I think I
have some time I
think bye by the latest I think I have
some time on Sunday because on Sunday
I'm starting the stream uh again at 7:00
p.m. right so I hope I can get some
stuff
recorded yeah yeah I I see I see the BB
DEA did quite well now we need
to see
nii one do well too but so far my dance
TRS have been doing okay so I'm quite
happy they do better than the clip
shorts well which is fine but that's
telling me I need to do more dance
shorts It's motivating me to do more
dance shorts lots of Japanese comments
in the dance yeah I wonder it's just
because maybe suici fans are showing up
or so I don't
know no I don't have a Tik Tok I don't
have a kiala Tik Tok I don't have any
Tik Tok
thank
God uh I don't know I don't want to make
one I don't care
no the difference between you and most
other people is that yours is real Mo
but not MMD no no no not all of those
are MMD though but uh not all of the
others are MD but
yeah yeah I what I can say is my mine is
motion captured by me with my Accents in
my
home so so I I need some time to learn
the dances you know it's uh I mean you
know one course I I can learn it pretty
fast but I need to find still I need to
find some time to put on everything and
yeah find some time in general to learn
a
dance in these busy trying
times
and but yeah but yeah but yeah I'm
trying my best to follow the trends I'm
I'm trying to speed up now that I mean
the premium on were still kind of
testing
phase actually those are the first ones
anyway that we did those are the first
proper products besides
Chimera yeah cuz I was also still
testing live streaming for uh my motion
capture so we were still in testing
phase now is when we get
serious now like can try to follow the
trends public dance streams in the
future
M I might
wait uh a couple months for
that about vertical oh I can do a
vertical dance stream yeah let's go but
I'm not quite happy with the quality
of it yet in live streaming uh
option because of those weird there's
some weird movements that happen in the
retargeting process right we talked
about
this that I don't like
and the goo team is making a software
that will fix it but it's still taking
them a while and then they'll let me use
it those freaking
Angels now no nobody besides me uses
Accents in cover as far as I know as far
I even asked them if they can help me
with it nobody uses it I can use it with
my app but nobody uses it so there's
no reason for them
to like make our app uh fix that
retargeting issue there's no reason for
them now go company they're all using
accents so they have a reason to work on
that so I'm I'm actually going to wait
for their
software yeah that's that's the only
thing I can really
do it's it seems to be a pretty
difficult
thing they're working really hard on it
doesn't seem like such an easy thing to
fix it's like only happening
when you send the data from the exent
software live to another program like
our app or theu app where you can see
then the motion live on your own
model that's where the retargeting
happens that's the only only place where
reason why it happens if it was only if
I was only live streaming the screen of
my uh accents motion capture software
then you wouldn't see those issues I
think I think it just looks uh normal
and then it sends the motion cture data
live to the other program and that's
where it [\h__\h] it
up they are MVPs
yeah uses ACC and programs it have they
fixed the retargeting issue though but
that the thing is like I need our soft
where I need to be able to use some
software with my model where the
retargeting issue is fixed but whatever
this is all too Technical and I I I have
uh something inside so it's okay I'll be
waiting for that and until then I'll
just be doing my little dance shorts cuz
um as long as I don't live stream it
it's
[Music]
okay okay okay i' I've tangent it enough
it's enough no more
what do you
mean you and other Hollowman play Thief
simulator Thief was free on Epic store
recently any chance you or someone else
will stream that well I
did as you say h what do you
mean as you say I
[Music]
did oh a different game called Thief oh
you're saying H you played Thief
simulator do you want to play
Thief oh
thief thief
game
oh yeah I think I've seen this one
before it's a good one
right epic store wait what's the epic
store
again is it free on Steam I want it to
be free on
[Music]
steam can I buy one t no naan no go away
but by the time I read your super chat
it will be a different stream anyway
let's be
honest okay let me read
them y I will read them I will commence
the reading
well change
music jacob7 d py d oh my God I'm doing
it oh my God tip thank you for the red
super
chat one two for you and you gave me one
too wow I'm normally not the one on the
receiving end thank
you m than you soon down
aluda I hear so rarely from you nowadays
that it makes me think you're gone but
is I'm so happy to see you're still part
of kfb [\h__\h] fly on my
screen Dodge Dodge Dodge thank you Alita
as I said I'm really happy to see you
this is the best radio
station is the best radio station in
Austria or in the vtu world you might
say we we W radio station I don't I
barely listen to radio I can't really
recreate it so sad no not UDA aluda a l
y d a Auda also eludes us
though yeah thank you aluda for the rest
of Chad nice to see you I missed
you good to see you Jackson FB d
oh for the pink Super Chat
[Music]
sorry fly flew right at me
yeah okay so that was Japanese Super
Chat so I replied in Japanese well you
can probably tell what I was talking
about yeah or Corgi corii
miss most of the stream I can tell you
missed all the
fun I don't really like small dogs they
because then their eyes are like popping
out and they're so like
[Music]
it's
just
[Laughter]
[Music]
stop that's not true for some of them
which
one which one which one then which one
tell me one that's what that's not
true you might be right but I I have to
think about
[Music]
it n okay maybe their eyes are not
popping out but they still have that
energy wait Hulan wait I have to read
this wait you already oh oh
wait wait hul
[Music]
is this wait did I is this the first one
I can see why you recommended it to me m
is gold
unseen wait he likes it he likes it
guys oh [\h__\h] okay sorry I'm so excited
to read your super chats but okay okay
okay I'm not going to I'm not going to
I'm not oh but I'm happy you like it
let's go let's go let's go let's go
woohoo you guys should watch it too yeah
yeah mij masel is her name
mij there was one more before okay oh I
see I see I'll read it later if the fly
lands you can clap your
hands oh my PC lagged oh there it
is look go
away I cannot kill it it's just too
Dynamic Broken Man D J Monkey D
furlock
sappy Arch alen thanks for the pinky my
KY backpack arrived last week yay and
I'm really happy with it it arrived just
in time for me to test it at a
convention and because I was wearing the
backpack I was approached by now can't
free chicken and we got on well straight
away of course you did yeah Mak sense
thank you I'm happy to hear that my uh
backpack and
the how did I manage those are different
from different uh merch sets right the
backpack and the beach bag
are from different sets but they have
the same color the turquoise same color
shade wow I actually
somehow matched
them probably staffed it the ones that
designed it but uh anyway so I have them
both but I gave the beach B to my mom I
thought she might really have good use
for
it because um I can't I I wish cuz I
have no proper big backpack so I wish I
could use the backpack but I kept the
backpack um but in any case both of them
me carrying it around
is
problematic not that we were never
told by the company that we can't use
our own merch outside but I'm just like
you know
thinking it's kind of yeah uh
maybe a given that it's a stupid idea so
I don't but I could yeah I could just be
another
fan but still I don't want to invite any
trouble so I'm not using these things
outside but and at least nothing that's
visible I wish I could use the backpack
though but I'm keeping it for one
day maybe one day one day when I can use
it
and such is the same thing with all the
other merchandise like jackets fromo cat
and so
on and yeah I gave the I gave the beach
back to my mom told her feel free to use
it in like your own home like around
your own home should be okay cuz she
lives in the middle of
nowhere yeah
and she she really liked it she really
likes
it she used it right
away so yeah hope you guys are enjoying
these
things thank you AR Ellen L Moonlight
thanks for the pinky kiaba truly knows
how the human mind works if you want to
hide from them go to the place they want
you to
go is that how I was thinking sass
no wonder in the usual room is so
effective he truly mastered the mental
games well well well I am your tental
after
all just dye your hair
[Music]
yellow no I'm not allowed
to I need to keep my hair
orange thank you Lou
and M
Chong I hope I read it right I feel like
I'm more and more forgetting Korean I
need to do Korean dualingo stream
dualingo might not be best but it's
something
[Music]
p
s oh
[Music]
I remember that word study
lord well there a there's a translation
right next to it I'm just trying to read
it but it says K scream stream best
choice after finishing today's study aha
I saw the K
comp I I can read K and I can
[Music]
translate
gks Dr video
Messiah
BR Sky D logical Paradox thank you for
the pinky thank you for the fing stream
tal it really brought back memories of
when someone tried to break in with a
brick while I was still
home uh you're
welcome compared to that experience this
stream is way
better oh well I have a similar
experience I've been uh not thed but
broken into you
know yeah yeah yeah
yeah I told you before right when I was
small relatively small teenager W yeah
in overseas in
Morocco yeah that was really traumatic
but it's a long time ago so I'm way over
it yeah I guess I'm lucky nothing
happened since then I mean ah I've been
actually yeah I lost or I've been stolen
my phone
twice in my
life oh once in Berlin and one time in
Austria in a train because I left my
seat that was really dumb I trusted
Austra too much I left my seat for like
2 minutes my phone was somewhere on my
seat come back phone is gone the Berlin
one however I just had my phone in my
pocket of my
coat when I was getting into a bus that
was really like crowded around the
station
and the train one I was really young
though I I barely had experience
traveling on my own at that point
still
yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah I don't know ah the one in
Berlin yeah that was a new phone I I
just got it and then went to Berlin and
then it was stolen I was so [\h__\h]
pissed off and I didn't want to buy the
same phone again I was like
contemplating what the [\h__\h] which phone
do I get now I don't I don't like the
other options I have in terms of new
phones but like I don't want to like it
makes no sense for me it feels like
weird to buy the same phone a second
time it was so
expensive I think I ended up buying the
same one
though but I think I then ended up
upgrading it like cuz it you know
usually these phones now noway they have
like free options in like save space
like
GB and I first went with a lower one and
then I think the second time I went with
a higher one so that at least something
was
different I just wanted something to be
different
man I would have felt so dumb getting
the second phone the same phone a second
time man yeah but that's pretty much
about
it in terms of having stolen or so I
think lucky I guess but damn that tweet
that Super Chat logical Paradox man
[\h__\h] trying to break in with a break
while you're still home that freaks me
out man
ah oh
man ah sheesh spuz
[Music]
choco M for the pinky since everyone
wants you to play Mass Effect you can
play it right now for the Super Chat
choose an option red blue green or tell
the child to stop
yapping yeah you guys would probably
choose to tell the child aka me to stop
yapping and just read the [\h__\h] super
chats
right I don't really see a reference
here cuz I haven't played a
game but you guys maybe are seeing
it Mama Told would have laughed at that
one good for her good for
her you like my yapping but today I may
have yapped a little bit too much I may
have over yapped it just once man this
just once I may have over yapped it so
much you guys were once again telling me
although you do that all the time you're
like K weren't you going to read super
chats really makes you
think I F you guys wanted to I thought
you guys liked my
tangents you even give me pennies for my
thoughts which is literally the super
chats that I should be reading but then
you you were paying me for other
thoughts so that's that's that is
shreding and Super
Chat oh my God realize it do you realize
it wo
who w w it's so
so mind
[Music]
confusing I don't even know what I just
said I
cannot reiterate
[Laughter]
it you want to get rid of the Super Chat
pile well well
well if it isn't the
consequences of your own
actions because you guys are the ones
who sent them even though we already
have a pile of
them thank you yeah yeah yeah I I know
it has nothing to do with
it thank
you I'm not the one who's sending the
super jets you see I'm far behind for a
long time and you still still send
them
so well you don't have when I asked for
a penny not like you have to listen to
it and give me I just asked for one
penny and how many did you give me how
many pennies did you give me when I
asked for one penny for one
font did I ask you to send me 500
pennies nuh-uh
uhhuh
uhhuh I have a point and I have many
pennies turn off super no no no no no I
don't have a problem with with um
amassing the super chats you are the
only ones who have a problem with
that you're the ones complaining I'm not
complaining I am enjoying the pennies
for my
fault it's your fault yeah it's your
fault now let me read them super chats
okay otherwise you're going to get mad
at me
again
delar Elsie
Lain sand thank you for the penny it
literally says pen as your currency what
is this pesos what is it is it
pesos hello K thank you this is a red
one by the way hello K this is a day
it's a special day for me because it is
one more year of my life that I still
see you my
birthday is oh pz is MXN
oh uh per
beos and I can say that I love it I have
the confidence to continue watching your
streams with the same enthusiasm as the
day I saw your
debut
oh I love hearing
that that is a great thing to write in
your Super Chat first of all happy
birthday how do I say happy birthday in
your language I wonder I still don't
really know what it is is it
is but in any case happy birthday
congratulations
M and thank
you thank you you know a lot of people
move on and that's totally
understandable but you're still here and
you say you're still as enthusiastic as
in the beginning so that is
amazing I I hope a lot of you guys feel
like
that put Peruvian Souls as pen uh-huh
uh-huh uh-huh
a penny for my
thought thank you so much for the sweet
words I hope it will continue to be like
this perhaps until your next
birthday thank
you get
better maybe I do maybe I do I might
that might be true
art of BL D black FR thanks for the
pinky hey W I have some birthday money
from my bonus I got from
work wait are you saying it's your
birthday
too that sounds more like it's my
birthday is it my
birthday love you lot and will love
watching you play New Vegas W love thank
you
o was it your birthday black are you
here
it was your birthday well I guess that
was really the only option that made
sense happy
birthday
congratulations yeah New Vegas huh you
want to see me
play yo I'm back now so we can start
whatever we want
soon I guess it's going to be New Vegas
but I wanted to watch the show
simultaneously right you guys said
though it's not related
[Music]
right the show and the game I want to
play not really just the same universe
or
so super train
TR maybe I'll start watching it today
then for like my
nighttime
sleepy
Showtime although I won't get really far
I I I really noticed my a age aging
because I these past like one or two
years I've been falling asleep so fast
actually I think it's really mostly the
past one
year falling asleep so fast
man my age is
aging thought Family Guy was it is but
even when I try to watch something and
stay
awake these days it's impossible for me
[\h__\h] I I didn't know it was going to
start so early the the getting falling
asleep so fast I brought that's more of
like a 60s
thing now my shoulders and my back they
always
hurt that's also something you would
expect with being 60 or
so man no sleeping fast is a good thing
yeah
it's just I want to watch some shows but
it's not I don't have much to watch
anyway like maybe it's good
because feel like I've watched
everything there is to
watch age of 60 is in theand yeah it it
is who doesn't want a nice Grandma I
don't have a grandma anymore and even
when I had one they were not really very
present in my life my
grandparents so I will say 60s 7s are in
[Music]
theand just like me my oi yeah we let's
get old together we are oh my God this
is so romantic guys
listen
listen we are currently
growing old
together oh oh we're doing it we're
growing old together right now at this
very
moment isn't that what you want in life
to grow all together with a person you
love which is me
La I feel it every every day hold you
turn I never let
go we we are growing all together wow
who wow maybe maybe I should do a stream
where we sit together on on like a on
the on the p on our porch um in front of
a white picket fence and uh on the
swingy bench
FY
[Music]
yeah growing all together sitting on our
rocking chairs no not the bench I want
the the rocky
bench now that is alive oh this is the
life where you want to go where you want
to go
[Music]
yeah I might just be the ultimate GF
thank
you queing for the meet and greet with
Cy no cuz she's not doing that job
anymore
[Music]
queuing for Callie's
colleagues the
[Music]
Calles sorry uh naan CAU on things with
a pinky that's very true T always
notices when we change our names she
just chooses not to call us by them
sometimes
exactly exactly like sometimes you guys
change your names like I I mean it's
it's specifically spankenheimer
R I forgot what it even was originally
that
one that one I accepted I guess but now
I'm thinking maybe it was better before
because jro Ru is hard to
say I said jro R so e how did we go from
sodin to
jar was it not jodin
or how did we go from San to
jar where does the Geral come
from
H
weird
a I want okay so once M mispronounce it
to H sadin to
geroin J so sodin geroin
and then I think the r was added way
later though you went with jerone in
then and then it became Just J R
afterwards
yeah was a
joke damn I completely [\h__\h] up your
name you just I just I just took your
name and I said
nope nope we're not going with that [\h__\h]
that
your name I brainwashed all of us your
name always was jar always has
been anyway thank you Nathan thank you
so much your name your name has been the
same I
think correct me if I'm
wrong thank your art of
BL every another CL F to the
pinky currently a jur duty I'm going to
tell that my oi streams for hours every
day maybe that'll get me out wait wait
you're
joking first I thought you were serious
and wait were you
serious like were you at least a jewy
duty recently
you did have jury duty for 4 days wow
okay [\h__\h] flies on the screen
again I don't really want to catch it
anyway with
this be disgusting fly squashed on my
screen it flew away again ah there it is
again oh [\h__\h] fat
[Music]
fly you fly so much do they not like
burn calories when they
fly interesting question cuz like we
burn calories when we walk and all that
and flying is like they're walking right
do
flies no no no come
back no there's no
answer hey are you back guys say
ah okay I I was on Google Googling if
flies burn calories when they fly and I
didn't find uh there's not many people
asking this
question uh but there's one one person
who asked it on Reddit no stupid
questions but there's no
answer
so how the [\h__\h] will I
know how the [\h__\h] will I know there's no
answer to
this eh
of course it yeah they
do so why is this [\h__\h]
fly not well maybe it's not the I guess
I'm thinking yesterday I saw the same
flight but wasn't in my last stream this
fly here but it's probably not the same
Fly By the time from the last stream
which which feels to me right now like
it was yesterday cuz of this fly chasing
me but the fly from my last stream a
couple days ago probably it was not the
same flight if it was then it must have
lost some
weight but it's probably not what am I
why why am I like this why am I like
this
why am I like why am I why am I like
this why
am I like
this who
who who thinks that was that wasn't even
a shower thought that was
like what kind of thought was
this maybe more like a drunk thought or
I'm [\h__\h] high thought but I'm never
drunk and I'm never
high but seems like a thought that you
would have when you're drunk or yeah
when you're a
[Laughter]
Stoner
Man wow I'm
wow why DN I like this but I'm curious
why is it so
fat anyway okay okay I finished those
super chats
hooray I shall Now read the ones from
infinite Dragon
finally this
one y
[Music]
infinite
sh a [\h__\h] off like [\h__\h]
off I'm
I'm
I I can't
[Music]
I just I just drained my own
energy with my energy but I guess that
just happens when you use energy so
anyway Jacob with s Dan space waterall
Dan is this the right one yeah you're
still talking about fief CH human
explains for the pinky coming home from
my Japan trip made me realize that I
can't sleep while without the wa blanket
and stream really
the W blanket you need the stream I
understand but can't doesn't it work
with any other blanket I regret now
buying two of that so I so I bought free
F plushies this time surely F will
protect me when I sleep
right I'm not sure if it will help you
sleeping like the blanket
does protecting she might
do a you always bring your blanket man
the thing is you guys don't don't even
use it for sleeping I see it out like
conventions and stuff on the floor or on
the walls you guys just you just expose
my blanket like that to the
sunlight and the
people uh you just like display it which
is okay but you don't even use it for
its real
purpose I use it when I'm sick keeps me
warm a I want the world to see
honestly I mean it's a great blanket
so oh yeah you let you let freaking
Elijah Wood carry the blanket and he
just looks exactly like
this while holding
it guys what are you doing you're
freaking him out
stop eh
his face is a Discord
sticker this face like I don't know if
he's really trying to look like this or
if this is nowadays just his default
face his his H is that his happy
face he has crazy eyes
guys he might just have Crazy Eyes by
default this is default face
huh I feel bad now now but it's kind of
kind of crazy
eyes
flying yeah it's like he's he's either
like what the [\h__\h] or he's
like there's so many emotions in that in
that
[Music]
face being the ring bear I will do that
to you
yeah he's been for for a lot guys have
you seen those Orcs have you seen gollum
have you seen those screeching flying
thingies or the screeching horse
people I
mean have you ever put on that ring and
then saw the eye in front of you like
man that [\h__\h] does things to
[Music]
[Laughter]
you a heads up yeah yeah yeah don't
worry don't worry
the
nazul NZ has done [\h__\h] to him take my
two box thank
you Andy Circus who's Andy
Circus and the
circus
oh oh oh wait that's the Golem actor
oh ow
wow he
looks
cool I can see the Golem in him but he
looks good I mean he looks
fine he's so so like somewhat handsome I
guess his hair is
nice why did I I mean other the other
other actors's names I can recognize
somehow this one I I
haven't immediately been able to
[Music]
recognize seems like he golum is not the
first time he was like motion captured
like that not not the only time like he
also did like some
monkey oh the Planet of the Apes I never
watched that before some monkey
so
monkey he did so
monkey motions the captain
[Music]
stop
okay where was I
uh where was
I here I didn't get really
[Music]
far for the rested of chat we don't just
like you we love
you thank
you you're making me blush
tiple you are cute aren't you simply h h
I'm in a funny mood today sorry the game
was so much fun I can't help it the fun
is carrying
over unknown things to the pinky I hope
you know that your voice is extremely
cute and
unique it's one of my favorite things
ever if I have to choose only one thing
I can listen to for the rest of my life
I will easily choose your voice over
everything else voice
bre well you are really always listening
to my voice I
know most streams of wa music of all
time thank
you no
man I guess there's you know it's it's a
it's a matter of personal taste
right there's some people who don't like
my voice but it's weird because my voice
is pretty normal at this point so I
don't really get it but you know there I
think there's the one thing I understand
though is like um having a thing for one
voice more for the
other like I
really like certain voices in the whole
life
too some are like more like catching me
than
others but I think that's mostly with
like special voice I think I just have
like a normal voice normal
very normal I don't think I really have
a voice that really catches you like
that I don't know maybe I'm maybe it's
really like
um individual thing
[Music]
deep deep valley
girl I only know normal valley girl what
do you mean deep valley
girl like um this is like not really
deep this just normal valley
girl right
I don't think I've ever done a deep one
unless you mean like voice
changer
ew I don't like using voice changer I'm
perfect the way I
am
yes
[Music]
Queen the one from
Zelda okay so that one was the one with
the voice stranger yeah you like that
one then that's not my own voice anymore
hey
I like hearing you speak Spanish vamos
[Music]
Amigos
Bonita
Cita mama
[Music]
did you
sayos yeah is it wrong
[Music]
I know how to say the but I don't
know just right now I didn't know it was
right in that word I know how to
pronounce
it I was just throwing out random words
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh now I move on because I need to read
super chats guys as in case you haven't
noticed why are you guys tanging in
Spanish
stop you are so off topic we are reading
super chats hello did you
forget
guys come on get your [\h__\h]
together sick with Co get well soon
apologize for going off rail trail track
train
yeah track not
truck mhm good okay TI
oh yo I also add
today I
unpacked some merch too that I got from
the company I got the connect the world
hoodie
now a million years
later and the like a
special big package of my
uh honey
works the the the honeyworks CD thing in
the big package like a special one is a
big with like merchandise
inside uh I got the same thing for the
Deo 27 Deco Nina project because I think
because I participated in both of them
yeah limited edition and they gave me
the one with the to 10 with the special
thingy for me and Kobo song
M no no the de one I got long time ago
no no I just uh brought it up because I
got it back then as
[Music]
well pre-own limited edition thingy I
think so yeah it's pretty big so I
display both the dickle and the
honeyworks one on my
Shelf looks
nice I really like the design
really like the
designs
yeah Lord EV D not a good username
D map eight D for the
pinky hey you know that part of bakam
the dam part I've always imagined a
sharks in it
Sam did she never K when refighting the
shark in the DLC
ah
on thanks for the rare weekday RPG
stream T you good luck yeah you're
welcome question
mark I know I should
uh I know I should send I I should uh
stream these long streams on the weekend
but we had no choices time at least we
got it done
yeah gooa has oh good
good good did she sing Dam or did she
sing
s it was so long guys man it was so
painful but it's good that it's over I'm
glad we finished it
[Music]
I guess there's a reason why DD is on
Friday and buck on Sunday well in
handset I was like ah I could have done
I I could do it the other way around and
I could still switch it around
but I don't
know it's fine where it
is it's fine it's fine
[Music]
right it's fine right you don't uh want
me to switch those two do
you or do
you it's
[Music]
fine I might still switch there's still
a chance of I might switch it depending
on how the prep goes for whole talk if I
feel like I need some more time to prep
but I don't think I will honestly I
don't have that much to prep it's just
the questions like translating them um
although I don't even have to translate
it myself but I recently do and yeah
just choosing them translating
them yeah just not really much I think
so but if I feel like think I need more
prep time then I will probably change
those two games switch
it I hope H talk will become more
regular I don't think it will ever be as
regular as it once was but it might get
more regular as it was
recently for a while and then it might
go on a on a break again I'm not really
like you know we don't have to rush
because there's always new members
joining and I'm giving them time to grow
old uh and have more to talk about and
yeah
no it's
fine yeah I mean honestly the the
current Gap surprised me too it wasn't
on purpose I wasn't trying to take such
a
long literally Gap year for holot talk
was not my intention it just happens the
time passes and there's so much stuff in
between I don't know I don't know how it
happened I honestly don't
know Holo hacks let's
[Music]
go I just didn't really feel like I had
to rush Hol talk so it's okay
[Music]
V I don't know how to say your name but
D
Sanji joyful Wild Horse D oh and also
vaku I did not not applicable than for
the pinky technically my birthday now
25th in my zone got to thank you long
streams I feel nothing but gratefulness
towards you and kfb thank you for
shining so bright that it lights and
inspires my path glad to have you as my
t o she love always not applicable
I feel like you haven't sent the super
chat in a while too so I'm happy to see
you not it's not about the super chat
but it's like the super chats are the
moments where I often realize oh you're
still around nice to see
you
happy
birthday belated but
congratulations I'm so happy that you're
still here here spending another
birthday with me I don't think you're in
the chat now but I hope you're hearing
this at some point I know you're here
I'm still in chat mostly okay okay okay
yeah I mean I don't know in chat it
doesn't register as uh clearly in my
brain as with super chats so I'm
like cuz mostly I I look at the comment
not at the name so
much I I mean I look at the name too too
in the chat but it's like not
registering cuz he's so fast but super
chats St you know that's where that's
where I really notice oh this person
hasn't been here in a while but that's
really just the super chats like oh it
just hasn't they just haven't super
chated in a
while
yeah but sometimes sometimes it's really
like they don't chat
either it's just the super chats that
they send for some people so that's
really the only place where I see
them but yeah happy birthday I hope you
had a lovely
birthday I hope you were celebrated the
way you deserve it yeah tweat
yourself thank you for still being here
with me makes me happy
Thomas
Lord exactly like that
you Chanel
spanking
[Music]
hi than for the pinky okay I'm home and
ready to watch theall
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh yeah I streamed really late on that
day that was the right reaction spanking
I'm must have felt
confusing I streamed until like 2 a.m.
or so normally I ended around
midnight h
yeah I stayed up so late because of that
I so so
tiring free oh my God
free it's just never ending it always
felt like it was ending and then it just
everything drags out so much longer than
you
expected with that game in
particular
crazy sorry for dragging you guys
through a long stream
too I just really wanted to finish it
man the thing is it was not like
difficult
really most of the time you know like uh
that like when I suffer through an
ending like with that one Zelda
game that's yeah not
nice but Yakuza you know it was
comfy the game was just long it was not
me suffering through those 10 or 11
hours I was just uh you know getting
tired at the end
but the difficulty was fine
[Music]
really yeah pretty hard it was surprised
first try I feel like other fights were
more
difficult I know I mean yeah there were
some so like he had really strong
attacks right he went really fast from
one to one to one another right I'm
trying to remember right now yeah rubu
meu was really suffering but more so
offre stream when I that one run was
really
lucky roboo was the real end
boss yeah Zelda for Zelda yeah the the
the biggest problem there was the
difficulty with the [\h__\h] motion uh
not capture motion
control h and then the time pressure cuz
I I didn't have to but I felt like I had
to there was no rule but I had to I felt
like I had to end the stream for Ena uh
I think outfit reveal or birthday stream
or something like
that yeah and then yeah I was so close
and then the [\h__\h] boss killed me and
I was
like yeah and then less time made me
more and
more stressed and more and more bad at
the
fight but I really wanted to get it done
cuz I was so close to finishing it you
know cuz I'm not going to start another
stream for a 10-minute boss fight that's
the thing that triggers me you know Cy
wouldn't do that either Kelly has the
same kind of like brain worms in terms
of you know why not
because it has also to do with like
YouTube algorithm
YouTube short of
you yeah it's like because a 10 minute
stream it
will Don't make me say
it it will have like no views and then
maybe the YouTube algorithm will think
up
uh no no
no
yeah no I don't think I'm overthinking
it YouTube works in mysterious
ways what it's my job I have to care
about the algorithm it's my [\h__\h]
job the joke announcement room yeah
those are different because like it's so
ridiculous like when I do like a joke
stream like oh my God
emergency and then I announced that I'm
going to the gym or so like that [\h__\h]
gets views because it's like
ridiculous you know but the last 10
minutes of uh 10 episode RPG stream if I
make it its own stream
when it already is not doing so well and
then I separate it into [\h__\h] 10
minutes it's not going to do well okay
that is just
uh a matter of
[Music]
fact then scared you I'm
sorry I'm sorry side quest and read
super chats that's yeah not really going
to change anything in the performance
but it's yeah also just about I don't
know everything all together anyway
whatever I I just don't want n
no no I want it also for completion sake
I want it because maybe a tiny bit of
OCD or
whatever reminds of when you swapped the
sad music for your letter on your first
Ann anniversary and everyone got scared
what but I I really felt like I wanted
it to be an emotional
moment yeah it was supposed to be
emotional it was
emotional reading a letter to thank you
I'm not reading a letter to say I'm
graduating H why you got worried about
that no I'm just it's just it's so
supposed to be touching I'm supposed to
say thank you so much for supporting me
for such a long time that needs a nice
touching emotional music in the
background calm down
Chad yeah I was I was setting the mood
but now you that's just you guys
overreacting or Doom posting you're just
Doom posting you got it from your mama
you you got it from your mama aka
me you got it from
[Music]
me okay let me finish this please stop
let me finish
this where was
I which one did I
read did I read the naan cotton one I
don't think so a yeah here SP
Ty Jacob
47 twice SP D
Cruz oh this is when I finished it naan
C thanks for Pinky congratulations on
finishing your another game T improving
your s endurance stream of Ian here's
the next one well I Prov that I can
still do
it uh but yeah 10 11 hour streams were
more common back in the day right I was
playing so many long ass jery
there are more common back then honestly
thank God they're not as common anymore
on my
channel
but I
still have high streaming hours though
if you look at my streaming I haven't
looked at them in a while though oh wait
how were my streaming hours in
April the new month just started I still
had plenty right didn't I do a bunch of
things didn't I arrest or so in April
and but then I still caught up with a
lot of long streams
anyway wait what's that there's like a
Twitter right that posts like streaming
hours or so something like that what was
it is it it was isn't it Hyer like a
Hyer
Twitter wasn't it them let me check
media oh maybe
no which one was that Holo data I
Holo Holo how do I with this keyboard
how do I do the
underscore so don't I'll just copy
paste okay they must have it what oh
yeah okay so what's
this this one whole live streaming stats
for January to April no I want only
April how much should I
stream April
April whole live streaming
statistics I
streamed 81
hours more
than a lot of my wait let's
see fauna 42 Bale 74
50 from M how much did cie stream Cali
streamed a lot Cali has been streaming a
lot 114 hours
shees yeah but I'm still I still stream
so
much still one of the top most hours
no but what I feel like what did I do in
April I feel like I was gone
for or was that no that was March right
I was in Japan in
March didn't stream as much in March but
April was maybe more was it more was it
normal it's just a lot of Yakuza
right yaku Z be adding those
hours oh
man also does it count the member
streams cuz now that I do weekly member
streams that are also relatively long
sometimes yeah that's not being counted
and the others don't do weekly member
streams as far as I
know
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah it doesn't
count them H you got to keep that in
mind my hours should be a little bit bit
more but
[Music]
yeah okay we are well fed fed chimp kins
yeah I think
so even when I'm like gone a few days
like if you look at my overall stream
hours
then I stream more than average in Ian
so I am doing
fine yeah fat chickens yeah I'm
overfeeding
you yeah thank you I am
insane yes
I can never stream under 4 hours we're
already at
4:20
to
again but I'm I'm going to end under 5
hours I will show you I will show
you w w w h there there's the
Stoners there are the Stoners just
kidding just
kidding wa was
I ah here Nathan Nathan calling me the
endurance streamer is how I got to that
tangent I just already forgot
again g d my own D Cherry d
d oh you're welcome c z c sir D El La D
Tim Tracy D thank you glad you enjoyed
it Jacob 47 D thank you I did rest I
think
plenty up thank you
py
SMY hi oh switch Yeah and Shake
yeah hi did you go to the toilet or why
are you here
huh she was taking a
nap I know because I left her napping on
the
bed oh she's so soft M
Mia I don't know I didn't touch her butt
just now just touched her tail and her
ears
slightly I will find out
[Music]
soon I watched a video of somebody kind
of like making felt or so something
similar to felt of their cat's faur and
then out of that they
made little Adidas slippers for their
cat and I really want to make it
[Laughter]
too obviously I mean they're not going
to walk around that it's probably going
to fall apart and they're not they're
not going to walk in that but just for
the moment they put the slippers on
their
cat and it just looked amazing handcam
idea well I was thinking about that and
then I felt like
M I guess I'd have to say it's not
chonkers or
smoothies it's
Bonkers I guess that works
cuz um I don't
know about the color yeah my my raccoon
yeah
raccoon
yeah Bonkers I haven't seen Bonkers in a
while but surely bunkers is somewhere
out
[Laughter]
there but then I have to be patient to
actually get all that hair in one place
is m i don't know if I can get it so
nicely into like a felt kind
of texture because
like I think that cat in the video was
short hair
and my long hair cats the little pads
that you basically can peel off the
brush they don't really look so
FY Peru V and
V2 place a color
filter
H I don't
know difficult but I have other ideas to
we don't have to do this I still want to
do the hot glol
stream I will I will I'll totally do it
this summer I'm going to do
it I want to make I want to glue myself
some hot glue shoes and maybe a hot glue
M small bag or hot glue phone Cas oh
yeah phone case was one of the things
hot glue phone case hot glue Fork
Perhaps Perhaps a hot glue cup um on
under table
thingy what you put under your your mug
yeah uh hot glue m
how about no how about
yes I mean yeah coaster yeah hot glue
coaster hot
glue hat can also make hot glue hat for
my cat can make hot
glue shoes for my
cat or hot
[Music]
glue I'm
thinking I shouldn't be thinking
thinking I'm not even getting paid right
now for the thought so let's not think
let's read Super
Chat where was
I where was
I maybe around here
Copan the
[Music]
gamer thanks for the thinking would you
think for a penny maybe maybe oh no I
think I've done enough thinking stop
please don't leave me alone I don't want
to think anymore Cong C you for
finishing another jrpg I hope you get
some rest after this thank you rine
you're so sweet for thinking of me I
definitely needed that rest after that
long game it's not even oh oh there's a
cat oh so sweet suddenly
smothie suddenly smoothie robing where
did you came come from rubbing against
my
leg
baby suddenly the
softness against my tie
pants hey she's trying to rub herself
against the cables but the cables stay
girl you need to rub against something
that stays in place the cables are just
moving away from you
that she heard yeah me talking about
making hot glue shoes and stuff for her
she's probably like please
don't tie pants the tie yeah tie pants
the elephant pants I have so many now
I'm going to wear them every
day every day every day they're so good
so perfect for pajama pants and in the
summer I guess I can wear them outside
cuz they're really flowy Airy thin
[Music]
fabric I have so many tie
pants my own anime or feature film in
the future yeah cuz that's really
realistic
right baby come here
okay I'm almost done while I am petting
my cat with my toes let me proceed J
SW don't go okay she's
gone ARA thanks for the pinking thank
you for playing and congr on the clear
bus fun stuff is always loved
strategizing fly strategizing even if
brain hord was prevalent sometimes
racing you to beat it myself hi The
Experience too
oh oh hope you get some good rest here
well sorry for then I I was like rushing
you through it
then sorry you don't have to why did you
do that I didn't want to rush you for
your own game
experience I guess you didn't want to be
spoilered and you did not want to not
watch My Stream I guess that was your
your
problem W flying go
away no it's not so many flies it's just
one fat fly oh smooy is chasing it can
you actually catch it please yes yes yes
yes she stopped she's looking at it but
she's oh oh
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah go go go go
go oh actually choners is the better
fly
killer
oh she leave with chunkers but she
hasn't really been so interested in
killing it for some
reason smoothie is trying her best or
not well not her best I wouldn't say
that's her best she should try
harder yeah no no chonas has a
[Music]
surprising oh [\h__\h] off
surprising energy when
she really wants to you know especially
with bugs she's really interested in
bugs and killing them and torturing
[Music]
them okay okay okay I'm done I am a te
beep T you got my
T sky space waterful thank you jro
[Music]
thanks for the pinky congratulations on
finishing the game it was a lot of fun
and I really enjoyed the series with you
and kfp bit sad that it's over but
looking forward to the next Adventures
have a good night thank
you yeah well Yakuza is always a lot of
fun but this one really felt like there
was a lot
of it's just like dragging out more than
in others
which was really just because of Kyu
which wasn't bad
like it's I think it would have been a
lot more meaningful to me if I played
the other games of
course but even then it felt like I
don't
know the game could have worked without
that on its
own it wasn't necessary for the game
so that kind of almost makes it a filler
but yeah I saw people say the keto pots
are better than the ichon parts I don't
agree with that I
don't Yeah the more than that I would
agree that they the fights but that's I
don't know was that really just the
problem with this one I don't know if
the fights were really so much more
lengthy and
often than in other Yakuza games there's
always a lot of
fighting people didn't like Bryce versus
E I mean some things they kind of Al
also missed out on but then I I guess it
makes sense the thought that I had that
they probably are keeping the Ebina
Ichiban Showdown and all that for the
next
game when he gets out of
jail they
were probably purposefully keeping them
apart so that next time we have that
special meeting moment and probably
bonding I think they will bond they will
end up being friends first they will
fight and and then they will be
friends yeah also fighting after coming
out of jail
like that's like what what is he going
to get up to why am I already fear
Rising next game better have yanl
oh I love him I really liked him a lot
like I learned to like him in the
beginning he was so evil he's like
really pissed me off
but somehow
he became one of the nice guys he was a
good C
yeah the Crowbar guy you like the
weirdest man well I
mean he was like Charming because like
it it just feels nice when we were in
dire need of some support and then he
was there to provide us with that uh in
in quite a powerful Manner and yeah he
was he was
really supportive and protective H he
actually kind of became a gentleman
[Music]
H but it's kind of crazy how how someone
can seem so evil and then seems so nice
on the other hand I don't know if does
it actually make sense does his Char
character development actually makes
sense I don't know maybe I've been
gaslighted his voice actor I don't even
know the voice actor but I really liked
his voice I can imag imagine people who
know the voice actor must have freaked
out
though looking for realism again well
that's what makes you feel like a game
is relatable and having a game or a song
or a movie feel relatable to you is one
big factor for making it likable to
you so yes I will always
always be looking out for something like
that if you want to play a filler short
game is always Q me one well yeah I
think at the moment I I have other games
on my list that
will go
first
anyway a
yeah thank you arer yay we we played
together basically I am a te
T did I read this you getting Mike tun I
feel like now I read it I read it
already oh sky
space thanks for the pinky
congratulations on finishing the game
was a lot of fun I really enjoyed the
series review in kfp bit no see I read
that yeah okay I read it right I read
this before bit sad that it's over have
a good night sorry I went back in time
[Music]
RS p
and okay okay okay okay
okay it's done this is the the like a
dragon Arc is over it's so
over tomorrow
members only stream Super Chat
reading um I'm sorry it's just a Super
Chat reading but you guys are you guys
like listening to me Super Chat reading
for some reason yippity Yap Tippy tap
and I think we'll have some chitt chat
in between anyway um yeah same time as
today
and yeah yeah uh I will have to write
the waterme
tweet and I have to eat
yesterday wait I forgot to tell you
yesterday I was so motivated even though
the day was so long now I think I know
where I'm going I was so motivated yeah
I was going to tell you that I cooked
goulash I was like oh yeah I'm I'm going
to cook something nice
today uh I cooked goulash and not the
sausage version cuz we have a s simple
sausage version but I made gulash with
um proper
beef uh chunks and is the first time I
think that I made this kind of
gash also without like hellofresh stuff
just you know just went to
buy stuff on my own and went with like a
recipe and then the recipe I had even
though it's like really common to put
red wine in it the recipe I was looking
at did not have red wine in hindsight I
feel like I should have had red wine in
it it would have tasted better little
bit regreted spaghetti but if I have
bought red
wine I wouldn't have used the whole
bottle right and then I wouldn't have
used it for anything else either and it
probably would have gone bad before I
could uh use it all
up should those be stream no no no no
it's because the members stream
recently got a bit of a crazy amount of
super chats and those members super
chats I'll be reading in the members
only stream not Public Super chats I'll
be reading members only super chats in
the members only stream
red wine
vinegar Red One vinegar uh
uhhuh I have white wine
vinegar that I used a little bit because
the recipe asked for it
anyway there's red wine vinegar I know
balsamico I know white wine vinegar I
guess I guess if there's white wine
vinegar there's red wine vinegar too
I guess there is there's Apple yeah I
know I love using apple vinegar and
salads isn't balsamic a red one is is it
is
it I love
vinegar very very refined Fred wine
vinegar
oh yeah I love like apple like any kind
of these like vinegars like apple or
like you know there's like there's some
fruity vinegars having those in a salad
is so good
sheesh but anyway I I wanted to tell you
because that that kind of gulash takes a
long time you cook it for like 2 to
three
hours and I did but like I feel like I
was doing things wrong even though I was
following the recipe it kept on
like I have I had to keep on adding
water because I feel like cooked away so
much faster even though I had it on low
heat and I had the lid on and everything
but it was fine I kept on adding water
in the end uh it was not I wasn't really
following the recipe anymore but it was
fine and then when I ate it I felt like
it tasted good the
first bites but then more and more it
just felt more and more unsatisfying to
me like it wasn't bad
but it
just underwhelmed me in the
end but I still have some leftover so
I'm going to eat it
now I'll give it another try sometime
kind of bland yeah that's what I was
thinking maybe the red wine would have
been nice even though it wasn't in the
recipe something about
it n not under seasoned no not really
but yeah it's it's all right it wasn't
bad I don't
know I don't know I don't know if I want
to spice it up I don't know anyway I'll
go I'll go
meow smoovie is here waiting for me to
end my stream yep Cinder Wawa is upon us
okay see you tomorrow members and no
members guess I see you at Dragon's
Dogma finally for real for
real
OHA oh OHA I'm not going to put ketchup
in there
no whoo whoo whoo wo wo
[Music]
flye today was fun man let's play
Headbangers again
sometime that was fun bye-bye low energy
W bye
sleep under KATU
[Music]
for