[Music]
me
ah
[Applause]
i'm shaking
hello everyone welcome
to streamed
oh thank you kelly thank you thank you
thank you
i don't get it
i'm shaking guys i'm shaking okay did
you all come to the video premiere i
hope you did
i hope you watched it i hope you're very
on time everyone who came in later and
only saw half of it
either go watch it now quickly or watch
it after my stream
oh yeah bye actually i
i'm so i was so nervous i don't know why
i knew i knew the song is great i know
it myself thank you guys for the super
chats
i know it's a great uh song
did you like the song was it fire
like i promised you of course it has to
be fire because i'm a phoenix
i'm a phoenix it has been
uh quite a few stressful days for me and
preparing the song
we did not have much time but i think
the outcome was
great not only the song but also the the
music video which kelly
did for me if you take a look at the
lyrics at the
uh credits kelly made the music video
but the art was made by mama lonnie
i love her art so much and um
thankfully she accepted me asking her if
she would draw
some height for me
very fire uh
um mostly i want to talk
about this i feel like i'm like i'm like
we
we literally just started the stream
it's three minutes um but
i i got some stuff i want to like talk
about and um by the way this stream is
going to be one hour i'm kind of like
all over the place right now and kind of
nervous and shaking so sorry normally
i'm a bit more chill
i'm shaking
ah um so
i want to talk a bit about the
creation of the song oh
by the way do you hear the background
music i have in the in the background
there the karaoke playing
do you hear it is it too loud or too
quiet i hope it's all right
[Music]
did you like the guitar solo it went
like
i can't hear it's very subtle oh oh okay
let me turn it off
that karaoke version now if it's too
loud let me know
i turned it up no no no no no no
guitar goes
so basically um
one of my goals during my debut
was to make my own original music
but it's still quiet what the hell
what okay how about now
how about now how about now
but now you can hear it don't lie to me
no bgm oh there we go now we go okay
just gonna leave that in the background
so yeah
my goal was to make some original music
and i didn't i originally didn't plan to
still quite goddamn it i originally
didn't plan to have it
so early but
i couldn't i couldn't hold it back
anymore i wanted to make music so
one of uh one of the producers that i've
liked for a long time who does some
choco stuff he has a circle
called sink arts
um
so this sink art is a touhou project
circle
and i thought that it kind of fits
uh like the style that i want for my
first
song so
we worked together on a song with gojo
sang
[Music]
it making this amazing song for me
he also honestly didn't have so much
time to make this
but he did such a such an amazing good
job
and for the for the lyrics by the way
uh they were written um not by me but i
wrote some i wrote the english lyrics
and
if you if you noticed
they kind of suck i'm not a lyric writer
and um
[Music]
actually we recorded the song like what
was it like
last week or one and a half weeks ago or
something like that
very good and cute really i was like i
was like thinking maybe i should ask
kelly for advice because i don't know
how to write lyrics
but then again i knew you were busy so i
was like i gotta do this on my own
and actually while we were recording the
song
um you know that part where uh before
the guitar solo where it kind of like
chills down a little bit and actually
right this part
but they keep pushing and pulling me
a straight cool this part this part
actually rather
while we were recording this part was
not planned
this part was not planned but i was like
i was like
i kind of want a d medal uh
that was like d milo is like the part
where it like calms down you know
because it didn't have it originally it
was like
i know we're recording the song right
now but can we make it d metal
uh and d melo melody d melo at least in
japanese it's called that i'm not sure
what it's called uh
in in english but
a breakdown oh is it called a breakdown
so he was like hmm okay
so while we were recording on the on
the same day at the spot uh i was
writing down
some random lyrics while he was trying
to create a new melody
for the d melody for the breakdown for
the bridge yeah it's a bridge
for the bridge
so spontaneously and uh yeah so i had
like i had like only
a short time frame to write those
english lyrics
it turned out very very emo very
emotional
and also the last the last line
kelly you're watching right now so let
me say it the last line
where i sing uh what did i say
[Music]
i promise i will find you
something like that the last line of
course
i sang for my cali
yeah i promise and and in the next life
too
i promise i will find you that's i put
that in for you kelly
since her first song kelly's first song
had a little
reference to me where she dissed me and
called me ksotori which is okay i
totally
love her her first song had that in it
so i was like hmm
i also have to put in some kind of
reference
in my song as well so
when i was writing the english lyrics i
was like okay okay i'm gonna put it
right there
and in the next life too i promise i
will find you
but generally i wouldn't say the song is
about uh her
it's more like um there might be an
english translation following sometime
soon
uh right now i don't have it
because the japanese lyrics use some
really difficult
terms really fancy juniper words in
there that are hard to translate
very fancy wording in those lyrics uh
what was i going to say oh yeah the song
generally is about
you know fighting because i'm a father
i'm a warrior
yeah and about surviving and about
finding uh the meaning and the goal of
life and
uh about like not knowing where to go
but
like yeah i will find my path that's
basically
that's basically the theme of the song
so very uh full very positive
very um
how to say very motivational
but also kind of like a little bit
emotional as well
but of course it's fire more than
anything it's fire
what did you guys think about the song
everyone i was checking the the chat and
uh
in the premiere and it was going like
because i turned on the live chat and
not the top chat
i wanted to see what the live chat was
like and oh my god
the live chat was insane
thank you for the super chat thank you
thank you thank you
thank you
if the comments were insane i could
barely read them was i going to say
i could barely read your uh comments but
i did see
many of you were like oh my god this is
like an anime opening
right right kiara
the phoenix the anime
coming soon on your tv channel
okay so one thing i need
to let you know and i thought
originally i thought this was gonna take
more time
but uh the streaming services
will release my song
uh at midnight not all of them right
away
i think i think it's only spotify and
itunes
and apple music but later on there will
there will be some more i thought it was
gonna take a week
more or something but it's actually
gonna be at midnight
[Music]
yes yes i already scheduled some tweets
so as soon as it's happening i'm
tweeting and i might still be streaming
but uh midnight up midnight here so in
like half an hour half an hour half an
hour
in half an hour my time my time
so i would be very happy if you would
consider
listening to it not only on youtube but
also
on the streaming services whichever one
you're using
a bandcamp no i don't think so i i don't
know about bandcamp but i don't think so
it will be on spotify and itunes and
apple music in 30 minutes
thank you and uh very soon on some more
as well because i personally
use amazon music i think it's gonna be
on there as well
you and if you need some more time
if you need some more time to uh enjoy
the music video you know
you can always go to youtube and check
out the video again and see
how beautifully well done it was made
also the art from mamaloni i love it so
much
she's so good at all right the body
street
did you see that ass did you see that
ass
did you see that butts though
did you see it
as well i'm not a big fan of armpits but
i think some of you aren't there was
some good armpit content as well some
good
belly button content as well it had
everything it had
everything
what do you mean there's nothing there's
nothing rude about that
nothing nothing nothing
so yeah in 30 minutes it will be on the
streaming services
at uh as well as
do i have it like here
that's the wrong one but we can put it
there
no uh right now i have the blue thingy
this one uh the both voice pack the
booth voice back
down oh this will probably be a bit big
one second oops
yep i thought so i did this before
hit the screen there we go uh voice pack
also in 30 minutes
but this will not only be on a booth
which is i think more easy to use for
japanese people but also it will be on
geekjack
so that should be easier for you guys to
use
kelly my first voice bag are you gonna
get it
do you want to listen to my voice
exclusively
it's a thanksgiving as well so actually
the release date
was on purpose i was like i told you
guys this before but
i was kind of scared of my life for
thanksgiving i mean i'm curious
don't hide your feelings otherwise
we can just call uh and and i'll let you
hear my voice privately kick
yeah so uh thanksgiving yeah i was
scared for my life honestly
because people keep on saying i'm a
chicken or
a cherokee or whatever and i was like
damn it they're gonna eat me
on thanksgiving the americans are gonna
eat me
so i decided to
to get your mind off of eating me
i shall release a song so i told
gojo-san the producer of the song that i
needed until thanksgiving
and yeah so i think that's a really good
release because it's kind of my gift
to you all it's my gift to you
for thanksgiving i mean it's it's uh not
every country
celebrates thanksgiving i actually also
don't celebrate it
but yeah i mean it's a good opportunity
i would say
so thanksgiving 2020 best thanksgiving
ever i would say
the song was great i love you thank you
thanks for the amazing gift you're
welcome what's the voice pack oh yeah i
guess i should explain that some people
don't know
um basically uh the
the japanese hollow life talents have
been doing this
since ancient times it's basically like
i mean it depends there's a in my case
it's the situation voice as you can see
it's a situation where it's a kick in
the morning at kfc
which um is basically
uh well i mean get it you should just
buy it to understand it um
how do i explain it without spoiling it
it's like uh
a couple like it's a script that i wrote
and read out you know high quality in
the studio
and which is kind of like towards the
um keana fans out there it's like
yeah like a drama cd pretty much but
shorter not not like an hour or
something it's just um
it can be up to like 10 minutes or
like 5 to 10 minutes something like that
but it really depends like some people
do longer ones some people do shorter
ones some people do like
shorter smaller ones and put them all
together
but mine is like mine is not like a
situation where it's like a drama cd so
it's like a
uh it's not something you would set for
your alarm or anything and i i don't
like
uh it's not like single tiny
like cuts it's one big thing you know
and then there's also thank you message
that's also a voice message
and it comes with uh the karaoke vision
of my first original song hinotoni so if
you would like to
cover it i would also really uh be
excited
to hear that but you will have to get
uh the boof or the in order to get the
uh off vocal version the karaoke version
but honestly even if you don't want to
sing it the instrumental version
is so good i'm playing it right now but
i'm talking over it so you you shall not
you shall not
appreciate it it's to its fullest until
you get it
yourself could it get something oh yeah
it's not it's not
a release yet it's uh in 30 minutes it's
gonna be available for purchase uh
wait actually i think it's the site is
open now but you can't buy it yet you
can buy it in 30 minutes
so let me give you some links right now
they are all gonna be available in 30
minutes let me
let me write them in the comments
available
in 30 minutes
there you go ah manager son
can i post them in my chat now
i think they're the the web page is
already reachable
but uh doing i told you guys already two
times
yes it will be it will be on spotify
okay i can do it
there you go okay three links
the first one is booth the second one is
geek jack the third one is uh the
streaming
uh stuff
i know
just look up there the instrumental no
the instrumental is exclusive
for the voice pack but yeah
like i was trying to say i'm speaking
over it now but the the instrumental is
really damn good
it's like it has really nice drums and
guitars
whoa it's like so fire it's on fire
fire
can you reach the links do they open
gig check won't work oh okay maybe and
maybe try again and
like for i will i will be streaming 40
more minutes and the links should work
in 30 minutes
side brook did it ever work though
did you crash it oh dear
did you crash it i think i think you
shouldn't eat too much uh
on thanksgiving you're too heavy you
broke the website
you have to go on a diet
quality
is gone how is that even possible
i can't imagine so many people joining
the science
right now
oh my god you gotta all go on
on a diet
just eat vegetables every day no more
meat for you
no more
promise me you gotta lose weight don't
break my websites don't break them what
you gonna do you can't reach them
but yeah just try again in a little bit
also
um while we're at it
i wanna announce uh something you
already know but i got the thumbnail
ready so i'm just gonna show it right
now
uh in in about 12 and a half hours
i will try to sleep in between if i'm
not too excited i'm still too excited
when will ian friends stop breaking
servants
for real everyone chill
come no panic always come in twelve and
a half hours
this is happening
i've been waiting for this and i think
you also were waiting for this
look at this cute foam billboard this
was also made by mama looney
who also did the music video art
i think she already uploaded it on her
twitter the full version because it's a
bit bigger it's not just
the heads it's a bit bigger actually
prepare for travel and make it double
we had that before with super simple
so basically one of my debut goals
was the song right uh original music and
one of one of my other debut goals
was collab with piccolo senpai
i'm taking all those goals off
so ah
skipping snipe swinging but it's really
um i will be streaming on my channel
and my guest will be decorating
[Music]
who is if you didn't know my favorite
senpai ever i love her so much i think
she's streaming right now and she's like
preparing something for me but i'm not
allowed to watch
she's streaming right now we're gonna be
playing on minecraft
um
then
i was like wait am i allowed to watch
this probably not but let me just
let me just see if it's something i'm
allowed to watch
but i'm so excited for tomorrow the
thing is though
uh me and takura senpai up until now
have only chatted via text
we have never had a conversation via
voice
yet and it seems like
we won't have time
until right before the stream usually
when i collab with my japanese senpais
i um i i i like
talk to them like someday before the
stream to like you know
get to know them a little bit personally
due to time scheduling issues
it was not possible this time
so i might still
be very much in
how do you call that that state of
pure excitement
um yet
it's like a blind state pretty much yeah
maybe fangirl mode as well but also um
everything starstruck yes exciting yes
euphoria yes all of those together
panic very much thank you for the super
chat thank you thank you thank you
i'm so glad you guys enjoyed the song
thank you
thank you thank you thank you
thank you for supporting my music i
shall make more i shall make much more
ecstasy yes so
uh it's gonna be a minecraft stream i'm
gonna be visiting the
whole live japan minecraft server
because i always wanted to
like if i was gonna visit it oh wait i
just noticed why didn't why does no one
ever remind me of fixing this
there you go the background was kind of
like
on this it was not in the right position
anyway
i always wanted to visit the japanese
minecraft server
i'm sure that she will pull some kind of
prank on me
but i know her all too well i i think
she
she cannot deceive me if she's gonna if
she's gonna pull some kind of prank on
me i will know
i watched literally every minecraft
stream
of her at least before i debuted that
after i debuted i did not have much time
but i'm sure fall for it
but i will i will fall for it but i will
know that i'm falling for something i
already know i'm prepared
to die by explosion or something
yeah i know exactly what kind of person
she is what kind of
bunny she is what kind of crazy rabbit
she is i know it looks like
geek jack is up you mean the website is
back or
you mean you can buy it already
wouldn't that be a bit too early it
should be at midnight so in 20 minutes i
think just the website is a
sleep and then never and when i was
doing that i also knew what i was doing
still can't access stop breaking the
website
what about boof though it's just um
it's just a a digital release so there's
nothing
uh like physical i know you want to get
physical
let's get physical i know i know but for
now it's only digital release
so you should be even even able to just
buy it on booth as well if
kickjack doesn't work but i guess
nothing works right now
oh well i mean yeah it's you can't buy
it anyway yeah
so don't don't stress about it is there
anything else i wanted to mention i'm
too nervous
but i'm so glad we have a song now
my own original song which i can like
perform at a 3d dw if that day ever
comes
i will get myself a choreography as well
i'm planning to
uh commission a choreography and be a
pure
cecil idol yes
i like dancing so i gotta i gotta give
you guys the full package although i
must say um
to this kind of song i wonder if the
choreography
really fits that well because it's more
like a
to me it seems like a very rock rocky
song
uh but i want the choreography anyway so
i'm gonna prepare a
choreography for when the day comes
that i will be in 3d performing the song
for you guys live
[Music]
yes yes yes ah
but i have to fix my stamina until then
sorry by the way um the super chats from
this stream i will read
tomorrow in a separate separate
spontaneous
uh super chat reading stream because i
have to try to
sleep early today i know it's impossible
for me
what is she holding i'm holding my sword
what do you think i'm pulling
it's my sword look my sword in my shield
did you forget i have a full
full armor full weapon
my story i'm a warrior after a while
don't forget about that
shut up it's real armor it's popsicle
shut up real armor i tell you
i will slice your fruit
if you touch kelly
welcome to the membership
i was thinking since my my fire dope
lit super lit song is releasing today i
shall i shall present myself
to you guys again in my full form with
my
with my sword and my shield and
everything
will you be listening to this song all
day for thanksgiving yes you will
really be listening to it every day from
now on yes you will
100k views already really
already
thank you thank you oh
thank you so much thank you
[Music]
that's amazing thank you so much
i hope you guys really enjoy the song
i i already i already told kojo san
that we need to make more songs
and he said yes let's do it
there will be more hopefully so i can
give like a whole concert someday
that would be my dream to give a full
concert
only only repair kiana songs
1 million next stop let's go let's go
1 million one million phoenix
a hinotoni album that sounds amazing
let's go
but i do also want to try some different
genres as well eventually
like um something more cute
and like a black like a slow song as
well
you don't
people are still very confused about
this there's there's such a
a big uh a big part of the audience that
is new to whole alive and new to
victories and they just don't know what
what
voice packs are it's so hard to explain
again it's basically like a short drama
cd
like a audio book like an audio book
yeah
then i'm lost i can't help you
no no no death metal no no no no
that will not happen i will stay true to
myself and only seeing the kind of
genres that i really like
but um you know what i also want to try
future future future base what's it
called
that's cute stuff the cute stuff
i want like i want some cute song as
well some really
really really cute song
is it called future face yeah i keep on
forgetting
kawaii future bass
that's the good stuff but for the first
song i wanted something to show you how
cool
how badass i can be because i think many
people
see me as a funny
emotional girl and maybe they don't see
me
as a strong phoenix i wanted people to
know i
am a strong phoenix
comedian chicken idol excuse me
i i like my my pecora senpai but
she is the chameleon bunny but i'm an
idol i'm not a comedian okay
don't put me in the same drawer
i mean i guess i i can see it though
comedian idol it's okay
it's okay i'll take it i'll take it
you can be cute and strong at the center
oh thank you kelly
yes it is me the strong
and badass but cute as phoenix
it is me tata kiara nice to meet you
taka
kickstank is up you keep on saying that
but like
do you mean you can buy it you shouldn't
be able to buy it just yet
just play it should i play it no i'm
playing the karaoke now
as background music
are you guys gonna be with your family
today on thanksgiving or not
if you guys are with your family let
them listen to the song
let them listen to the song and tell
them is it's on fire
spread it to the world spread it
everywhere
a song is harmless you can spread it
keep on spreading it
nope what do you mean no
ah i don't think
excuse me why don't you want to share it
with your family
and share it with your friends share it
with your friends okay i mean that that
shouldn't be so
so awkward or are you guys um
hiding your hobbies from your friends
and your family
did you not tell them that you're into
holy life are you hiding that from them
is that a is that a yes that you you
told
you did not tell them you're hiding why
would you hide it be proud of it
be proud tell the world i mean now it's
getting more and more
mainstream anyway
[Music]
i wanted to yell guitar before the
guitar solo
but i think that would have ruined the
mood so
maybe maybe if i perform it live
[Music]
kind of the same thing as you're not
feeling proud of naked babs
hey that's a different thing
that's so different that's not the same
thing
kick jack sold out it seems like you
guys keep on breaking and it goes up and
it goes down and it goes off and it goes
down it goes up and down and up and down
that's a bad comparison
you should do a duet with cali
[Music]
well maybe there will be something like
that in the future maybe
i don't know
maybe we meant but i feel like that's a
destiny
it's supposed to happen
oh oh
kfb anime opening oh
kfb anyway opening kfc anyway that seems
like something
um that reminds me of the anime working
do you guys know the anime working it's
a really good anime i really like it
it's about working in the family
restaurant
it's really funny i can see something
like that with kfp
since that since all the employees i i i
hired
all the halloween girls as my employees
so that could basically be the whole
cast of the anime
and we could be working in kfp and
that's just the whole the whole theme of
the anime
oh someone please make this a reality
please please
i still have to watch that oh i really
recommend it
it has like a a couple of i think free
seasons three seasons maybe
anime just get to work that's a big
project
that's true that's true
yes yes
yamada is best girl um
hashtag not sponsored she's my favorite
yeah that's my favorite
pop pop she's so adorable yes
yeah oh actually yeah
i could i could i can see that i mean
there's still some differences in their
personality but it gets close enough
language kiara you want me to speak in
japanese
or german language okay
see this is how i this is how i counter
that now
every time you tell me a language kiana
this is my country
of torts
you fell for my trap card
kiana read me i love you to see me i
have seen you i have seen you i see
all of you it's just too many comments
for me to read out loud but i'm
constantly staring at the comments don't
worry about it
[Music]
also did you know there's some there's a
there's a part
uh where i sing what was it um
don't don't what was it was it don't
don't speak what was it what was it
i forgot my lyrics i don't break and
one other there was one other thing and
did you notice that uh
if you listen closely maybe maybe you
only notice if you
put on your headphones but um i did back
up that lyric
with a whisper voice
of kiara did you notice
there's asmr in the song
it was like don't break
kelly of course you noticed you were
listening to it closely of course
of course you were expecting no i
expected nothing less of you
yes i know this really secret asmr is in
the song yeah
arigato
i heard this song a thousand times wow
thank you so much again kelly for making
the video for me
kelly is a very very busy person but
very business very very busy reaper
but still she took her time out of her
busy schedule
to make an amazing video for me thank
you thank you thank you thank you thank
you thank you thank you i love you thank
you thank you thank you thank you didn't
hear that i love you did you thank you
thank you thank you
i love you no problem
trying to stay cool how would you help
happy for you
giving me flashbacks
yes yes i said we were um
i will do what whatever she says in in
exchange
i told her if there's anything i can do
for her i will do it
i will do anything
but she doesn't seem like she wants to
ask me for anything
yeah let's go to the spa again let's go
really uh i'm i have i had like a
very um exciting week
the past few days have been very
exciting and
kind of anxious for me uh mentally
and it continues tomorrow because of the
peculiar symbolic collapse so i kind of
need a day where i
just shut down everything
i have to shut down my brain for a day
spa episode number two
the arc arc
it's it's uh almost winter in japan
beach episode seems a bit cold at the
moment
bit cold we would have to go to
australia
cali let's go to australia oh wait i
don't think that will let us in right
now
i don't think they will let us in
i think we we can't go there right now
so for now only spa
that would be hard yeah but one day i
want to go to australia which
sounds weird because of course i am from
australia wing
wing wink
um
[Music]
um i will end the stream
in 10 minutes 12 minutes but in two
minutes everything should go online are
you guys ready
although i wonder if you if you will
crash it again
two minutes and one minute one minute
one minute
streaming service uh streaming services
you should also check
one minute oh my god can we count he
know tony
release content did you guys check the
hashtag there were a bunch of really
funny
memes mates in the hashtag
release countdown thank you all so much
for hyping it up good job good job
oh 30 seconds 30 seconds kick jack's
still broken
[Laughter]
no no 20 seconds
15 14 13 12
11 10 9
8 7 6
5 4 3
2 1 it's midnight open the gates
float the gates open the gates open
release on spotify etc
and voice kiara first ever voice pack
release
[Applause]
[Music]
yay panty money monster mustang
let me end let me
in add a quest again
well let's take it easy
let's let's uh take a calm pill hmm
with
as well hacking to the gate
just hack into the gateway reference to
my papa
hacking to the gate let me stream it now
let me buy the voice back
i really need kia let's voice
i love you congrats kiara thank you
kieran your song is beautiful
thank you son of spotify
what is the voice bag oh god
i need like an official explanation what
is the voice pack
just um trust me it's uh cute
actually the hinata track reminds me of
strandscape really
well that is not on purpose
someone was able to purchase the voice
pack on both now
[Music]
ah i think maybe the release time is uh
only like you know there's a time
difference i think
is there a time difference like um
yeah i think it's only in japan now but
it will come later
i'm pretty sure that's how it works
though so
ah it really is 12 pm esc for america oh
it's written there
it's written it's made that for every
region
ah so you guys have to wait more
no no
okay for now all you have is youtube
i'm sorry ah you have to wait until
midnight
oh no
that's how it is i see
midnight and everything i thought it was
up every okay then ignore my tweets that
is coming up in two sec
two minutes ignore my scheduled tweets i
mean don't ignore it
share it anyway but it is it's um it
might be a bit
misleading i have a tweet scheduled
for five minutes after midnight so
17 hours for midnight oh no
damn it damn it geek jack's so broke oh
dear
we should do a stream where we just wait
for kick jack to come back up
happy doesn't it totem unhappy
well i mean there's no need to be sad
there's no need to be sad
loves in cea
what did you expect if you put a phoenix
voice back
on the website of course it's going to
be on fire
it's lit it's too little
oh no well you guys uh you guys still
have a whole day in front of you for me
the day is ending uh so well you guys
have the whole day
to wait until it releases
on geek check for you guys and not only
on the spotify itunes
amazon music apple music wherever it's
gonna be there
sometime soon believe in it
for me however the day is ending and um
i have a collab tomorrow in exactly 12
hours
from now see the family longer i will
make a reservation for this
after the stream so you can chill in the
waiting room over there as well
and let me just say um
it's i i will try to make
some little translation here and there
but i honestly think there's not gonna
be much english in this collab i'm so
sorry
but first of all i think i'll be too
nervous in this case
honestly normally i try to keep my chill
normally i try to stay
calm but for this collab i don't think
it's gonna happen
and piccolo senpai also talks a lot just
like me
so there's probably not much time for a
translation
yeah i'm sorry don't mind just have fun
thank you
thank you thank you i'm so nervous so oh
my god
i was already like super
starstruck when i first talked to madden
senpai
on the phone which is quite a while ago
now but the first time i talked to her
on discord
i was like screaming i was screaming
i was literally screaming i was like
my mind is really you
mine is in my ah because she's like my
also one of my favorites senpai's
so can you imagine how it will be
oh my god
i will try to at least talk with her
like 30 minutes before the stream
30 minutes should be enough to chill
down right
it should be enough to be calm right
i hope
i will have confidence yes don't spook
her i will try
i will try
oh
have confidence
someone just said that piccolo said muna
would also be in the collab
will it not just be us too what
i know nothing of that
i want my i want my i want to be a
little bit bigger
and fine it's my first collab with faker
i want to hear hey kiana
uh i hope i i'll not be too tired
because i probably still can't sleep
much because i'm still too excited
i probably can't sleep i hope but i
think
even if i'm too tired uh the excitement
of talking to
my favorite senpai will probably get me
up to
200 2000 percent hype maximum
so anyway thank you everyone so much for
your support thank you for the super
chat i'll be as i said reading the super
chat tomorrow in a spontaneous stream
that is not on the schedule
it will be um maybe around this time
just a little bit earlier
a little bit earlier than right now
um and i'll take my time to read all of
your lovely messages
thank you so much for your support
song is pretty good better than i
expected
thank you kelly did the animation yes
she did she did
okay okay okay
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you thank you
so much and keep on listening to the
song on youtube as well
let's get to 1 million one day that's
my dream that my first song reaches 1
million ah
that would be so amazing
okay so thank you guys so much for
being with me for this special special
occasion
thank you for celebrating thanksgiving
with me
okay everyone i'll see you in the
super super super special collab with my
classified
tomorrow in 12 hours 12 hours from now
and in german we say
thank you so much i love you all
see you soon wow the ending of the music
is perfect let's go
[Music]
don't start again
i'm so so so happy that you all liked
the song really i
i i was too nervous in the stream let's
talk about it some more in the super
chat room
i love you all
[Music]
happy nothing
ah kelly is doing a 700k celebration
after this so
check it out if you need something to
watch
[Music]
you