[Music]
me a
song uh me a song
hello hey guys howdy howdy are you guys
ready
foran enre Ian Rec I still really don't
know what this
is I guess it's a game we're all
supposed to play together or something
like that we've been doing a lot of
gaming together though recently haven't
we dead beats it's kind of
like I don't know it's been fun but I'm
tired
it's just Minecraft they say yes just
Minecraft right should be easy simple
just
Minecraft oh that's the word on the
street right but yeah I don't know part
of me feels like hey you know maybe we
should just go outside for some fresh
air and stuff this looks cool and
whatever but like I don't like the idea
of like you know losing my memories and
becoming someone well even if I did I'm
sure I'd still be me just without
knowing my friends which is my least
favorite thing to think about but I
don't really know what to expect so
let's maybe just what if we hear me out
what if we just kind of ditched all of
this and just went outside together what
do you guys think it sound like a good
idea huh what do you
think no oh come on there's nothing
wrong with
grass right let's just I don't really
know what's going on
right and so for that reason I think
today we're just going to go take a nice
walk out in the park does that sound
okay to you guys that's what we're going
to do all right we're going to go take a
nice walk outside the dead beats you're
going to you're going to like it I know
that grass scares you in a way but
you're going to like it going out for a
walk
Jesus you know actually going outside
and touching grass with you guys is not
something that I thought I would do this
summer but I feel like it's necess Neary
you know I mean I've just been gaming
nonstop is that really okay guys for me
to be doing that maybe not it's not
healthy I told myself that I was going
to make a resolution to get more active
this summer and into fall so that I can
be the best me that I can possibly be
and take more lives with affection right
so I think that's what we're going to do
where should we go first this park seems
pretty nice I don't know about you guys
but recently I've been a really
good and that was how Mor's enigmatic
recollection
began without knowing what the heck was
going on really
truly all that I knew at the time
was it's time to be chuny as
yeah Fri
uping closer now bring it on get
down Fearless Step It Up step it up now
we got stop above the fire but up inside
so nothing brings us down no matter what
we're going to break through next stop
got to keep it going n and we go CR the
we going Break The Rules no can do what
we can get up and mo break all the rules
now move into the Grove keep it extra
cool we're extraordinary got them under
control they up down let go way louder
louder to the be higher higher to the
hey now we no time to waste your heart
reality I heard a whisper calling me
calling me I see it now we found
ourselves
[Music]
[Applause]
that again we're never going to
[Music]
stop let let itow on here we go
superal need go stage the
taking over keep it going
on reach out to the Moon there left to
lose got something turn it up into some
new world we are unbreakable we are
unbreakable now
[Music]
huh
uh
Hello
whoa go the hell am
[Music]
I
hello can anyone hear me
oh who's this new
chick is that my name new
chick my cap oh yeah this does look
pretty cool whoa hold
on
Dad
cie
[Music]
Mory I guess that's my name
Mory who are all of you skeletons
watching
me I feel so embarrassed I get so
nervous about all these eyes on
me I
think that's strange my mind feels a
little fuzzy and I don't really know
where I am but maybe maybe we should try
exploring
around let me
see where the heck are we this is
strange
range oh I think there are people
[Music]
here huh oh what is this strange
logo that's odd hey there are a couple
different logos
[Music]
here there's a red one and a blue one
too oh
wow wait I don't know if I should show
you the red and blue
ones that seems important I'll hide it
for
[Music]
now where are
we at least we won't remember G's
Christmas tree I don't know who that is
oh how do I speak to
you maybe with
this
huh hello can can you say that again oh
oh my God whoa there's a pretty Orange
lady God oh you guys can talk I mean
scared What's happen yeah oh my God my
hands every what happened to my hands
they're so
blocky this is strange I don't know why
my body looks like this it's so Square
everybody s so Square what happened s oh
my God too yeah you you look everyone
looks like squares oh my God
what I think I hit my head what happened
who are all of you hello yeah I that's
what I want to know I think who are you
people my heads you hit your head too w
w I hit I just hit my head I don't see
any cracks though are you sure I'm very
durable but it was damage very durable
want to stand in the corner there's a
person in the
corner did
you I can
hurt hey hey
you how do I talk to those
people also some of them are kind of
loud what's going
on that's the loud one I feel no pain
that's the loud I feel no no nothing in
my
bones their mic they Hur me their loud
voices did you see give me a
second oh my Lord
I I got kicked from the server is it
because I called them
loud I'll
rejoin it looks like I couldn't get back
[Music]
in let's go back to my my cozy
space give me a
sec you guys all seem nice enough
[Music]
I I like you guys a lot because your
your voices don't scare
me small skeletons all over the place
hello do you mind if I Pat
you pat
pat should we try going
back kind of
[Music]
nervous I like you a lot too pink lady I
guess I am a pink lady okay I'm going to
try to head back in there but hold my
hand if it gets too scary okay if you
hear a bunch of voices don't worry I'm
right here
okay uh
enter okay about you oh my God the
voices are I don't I'm a
rat what so loud oh my Lord it is really
loud here that's so noising you will
have to figure out
later I'm going to turn down
everyone this is so much talking yeah
that's why we were like muted originally
I I guess I guess so well hey you know I
found something kind of crazy I don't
know but I'm hearing
voes hey did you guys know that I can I
can see their names i l ofus
I think that's me telling me about you
good good things bad things I don't know
there ask me if I remember
you will it make will it make the people
watching you feel bad if I say that I do
not no because I also don't remember you
oh okay well then we're Square I I guess
it's probably no problem if we don't
remember what is your name hey I like
you because your voice isn't isn't
Jonathan G loud really I feel like
that's not really what it you can stay
in the corner and maybe that's not
really what others right now I get
nervous around people that I don't
know I thought maybe your was let me
turn you up cuz your voice isn't too
loud are you
insane I wouldn't be surprised this room
seems like a room where you put insane
people into true like an asylum yeah
that's what yes
yes why are we in this box wait a minute
can we get
out let us out of here let me out let me
out let me
out so much anxiety what's up who are
you going to
stop I'm told my name is
K I seen you somewhere before I don't
know you look so familiar you kind of
look
fatherly you a fatherly VI why would you
get that
impression supposed to be a cute girl
right I don't
know what's your name again
I don't know if I can be a dad though
that sounds like a lot of
responsibility trapped we trapped some
of the others are hiding in Corners
too what oh they're speaking in a
language I don't know oh I I think
that's a dream maybe maybe I drun too
much yesterday
[Music]
and those
what if I want a corner I deserve a
corner too you
think what a strange world we found
our what should I call you guys by the
way skeletons in the chat have
L I don't know what I am the last thing
I remember a
[Music]
big Kia
people nice to meet you Kia
people oh Echoes of Forgotten memories
hold on that seems
cool press sneak
key is
that who am
I the world I live in
what's the sneak key I don't know what
that
is and more than
anything
yeah the people I hold most
dear who's that though
I don't know anyone except for these
weird skeletons in my
chat those people in that room they all
seemed like insane
people faced with the Oblivion I feel
empty
relieved
perhaps d
dra maybe I just really have to
be I do not
know but I get the feeling I'm at the
sneak
point so much I don't
know and yet so much I don't know I
didn't I just say that who is that I
just say that and yet the bright light
calls to yet who's saying that that
bright light yo someone's talking it
calls to me that one they can hear you
that maybe I should make them be
quiet I don't want to listen to other
people's
conversations that bright light calls to
me I'm in someone's head
oh am I conjoined by Fate to this one
person
maybe there's a way I can I want to move
to go toward the light
yeah are they talking too hey
wait
yo hry
careful huh is this a hole can you die
here that would be awesome turn around
it's not a hole it's not a hole not a
hole
they scare
me
is
[Music]
Bri
flashbang liestal
Castle
oh you there what what are you doing
here you have the look of Outsiders
about
you me Outsider
bying wait could it
be quick send word to his
majesty no I would not like to turn on
sticky
keys the heroes have arrived at the
sanctuary
hero not your
boy right right
away oh
hello Royal audience
chamber welcome Heroes this is the
kingdom of libal and I am its king wow
what a small little
guy not exactly what I would assume to
be king
I wonder what's for dinner why is that
funny to me the guards who brought you
here have informed me that you remember
not but your own
names yeah well technically the
skeletons told
me
um h a side effect of travel between
worlds no
doubt
okay maybe between worlds where' I Come
From This Must ALL come as a surprise to
you but parken well it was I who SU you
here you see an unprecedented Calamity
now threatens our
world our world they call it sticky keys
I mean it is it has sewn the Earth with
corruption and driven us from our
homes this blighted land now gives rise
to creatures of Shadow known as stains
oh okay so it's not sticky
keys we call you C for short that sounds
a lot cuter than kiai
I like
it this Kingdom of liestal and its
surroundings are now the only safe place
left to us libaston
but should the Calamity be left
unchecked it is only a matter of time
before it consumes the entire world who
that sounds difficult oh it's
approaching me the
thing faced with this Prospect I scoured
the ancient text for a way to combat the
Calamity and therein I found
one what was that
to summon a bunch of people who don't
remember
anything the ritual of hero summoning
okay pretty
close I'm probably
right the ritual of hero summoning is
what it's
called am I a chosen one I don't think
I've ever been chosen really for
anything in my life not that I can
remember you who hail from another world
have been summoned here by me to become
the saviors of Libo another world
my head does hurt and my body does feel
sluggish like I got hit by
something did that have to do with the
tra the the
travel I do wish that this strange
sticky key spell would stop would stop
go popping off like that because it's
really
annoying that's
okay truly I'm not annoyed I'm unfaced
I'm Mory
KY and so I ask you will you
oh who's
that your majesty hey it's that green
that green
logo what is
it a great a great host of stains has
broken through our defensive line ooh
maybe I can help but I don't have a
weapon maybe
not I don't know I feel like I like to
be helpful maybe that's my thing no no
we are rushing to mount a defense but
the situation is dire your majesty must
get you somewhere
safe oh yeah definitely protect the king
cuz you know Kingdom without a king is
pretty
beu who's that and who are these
[Music]
strangers oh mine's Cap's locked oh God
that's really embarrassing
[Music]
what's say you Heroes will you accept
this
Destiny could be
fun there is a great power within you
will you use it to save us to save this
world I can try my best I feel like I
was definitely strong in some other
life Elizabeth is my name
we don't
remember don't remember guess Elizabeth
and blood flame is my here of
course voices are
back I'm going to stay over here what's
what's it say about my
head it says raven
Croft
really yes I guess that must be myname
then gu I have a wooden sword is this
what I used to
fight yes seems like a very long name
yeah come come here come
here who are you how very
sorry above my head I don't know if I
want to find out I have to ask one of
them any any can you Pur she told me my
name was Mor KY right so maybe if our
names are about our heads then is this
kiar Holo
Ian what a strange last name I'm
ready call my name oh no no no is that I
just thought that was your name cuz
that's what is written above your head
all well are you
more I guess I guess so that's what I've
been told my name is well can I call you
I promise for sure oh yeah it is a long
and tedious name isn't it yeah it's a
pretty long name I got to say yeah cool
oh
man what there's a damsel in
[Music]
distress there's a damsel in distress we
got to go save
her you must
face hello are you in distress
Madam someone was killing me someone
some some oh it dog no no I I adopted
her she's a cat I'm not killing her tell
me okay wait there they're talking to
like a dog like a
dog not even the mighty Le Castle can be
to
be that must be where we
are
[Music]
uhhuh Dy to defend the king to and raise
her from another world let us go this
valid and fight no I was listening
to is that the
enemy I feel like I was strong Once Upon
a
Time so perhaps I too should
fight people scare me but enemies
don't no way
impossible that guy sword is really
strong I don't feel like this sword's
very strong though I'm not going to
lie here I'll lead this one over
[Applause]
here no no
way one H this one H this one okay no
way we're going to die
I can tell I was strong killed them
don't give don't give up don't give
up hey this bread restores my
health
comat that was a big a ground pound
maybe believe in yourself believe
in defend yourselves
[Applause]
ladies ground
pound jumping the ground pound archers
you got to take out the Archers first
get the archers
yeah that's the Strat get the
archers thank you I will remember this
other there's there's no end to them
this Kingdom really is plagued huh so
many St get the
dog no no focus
focus oh this the
use help get him get him flush bang ah
it's so
bright shout Revelation hold your weapon
and
click
Revelation maybe it's not working
Revelation let me try again revelation
this is definitely the left CLI
Revelation I can't move any further my
body it won't
move
Revelation I can't get any closer to the
enemy
[Music]
Revelation maybe I'm not cut out to be a
warrior perhaps I need more EXP
perhaps the spell is
broken
oh oh
[Music]
no well that was strange skeletons I
thought for a minute there for
sure we were going to go on some kind of
adventure maybe my Revelation was too
strong do you guys
think oh well I did my best but that
doesn't really solve the problem of
how are we going to get back to my world
or wherever I came from cuz my brain is
still really F foggy and if I'm stuck in
these strange clouds that are kind of
billowing up behind me that's probably
not really a good life to
live
so
well maybe this is what they call the
bad end
you came
from
Texas is that a land further
Yonder I've never heard of such a land
all I know is that I came from someplace
dark memories are slowly coming back to
me but they're all very
foggy it's the holoen bad end holoen
that was that orange woman's last name
Holan Kiara Holan I'll remember her
maybe I'll go stick around
her yes Miss Holo
Ian I've ye my last ha is that the
phrase of my
[Music]
people ah it would appear
that I might be able to access that
Kingdom again pretty soon but do I want
to seems really scary I kind of like
being
here with you
guys and just chatting with you cuz
again your voices aren't
scary
yeah who else did we meet there was a
cat that that Miss Holan said that
she adopted then there was that
ninoa what a short name I wonder if she
has a last
name because I seem to have a last last
name
well maybe we should return to the
Forbidden land of
Mojang it seems that the kingdom needs a
little bit more time to refresh itself
though before I might be able to
reenter and then perhaps we can try
shouting that spell
again the hopefully I can get something
better than just a plain old wooden
sword
right uhuh that was the best that the LI
the the libon could give me a crummy old
wooden
sword give me something sharp give me
something powerful something dark I feel
like that would fit with me don't you
think I mean look at me look at my look
at my Garb do you not
think that I deserve something dark
like uh like a scythe or so yeah a
pitchfork oh
maybe you need a battle spoon a battle
spoon perhaps such a weapon would beit a
smaller friend I don't think that a a
battle spoon would work very well for me
the spoons are only good for like eating
curry
rice curry rice I remember that's one of
the only things I can make
probably shouldn't admit that in front
of all of these
skeletons I take it back the fists are
good enough says you guys uh someone
said that you are known as chat so
that's what I will call
you chat says that you could eat an evil
soup
soup I'm
okay I prefer Curry rice no we're cayia
people Ah that's
right darn it I forgot some people said
chat and some people said Kia people Kia
people makes a lot more sense I
think the name Chad sounds
familiar huh both Works no we're
boners huh why do I feel gross when I
say
that the bone
ERS huh that's kind of fun though I mean
it's got a nice ring to it it's a little
more short and simple than CIA
people
huh
wait the Kia people are having a strange
reaction to this this word that I've
said maybe
not oh no they're reacting very very
violently okay maybe we scratch that
one well
it is what it
is it looks as though we'll have to wait
a while longer before we'll be able to
go and try and continue to have an
adventure of some
kind so sorry that you're stuck with me
[Music]
here tell me more things about myself
wait that sounds really pretentious when
you say it like that
um if you guys have any idea of my past
can you tell me what you remember about
me okay boss boss o am I someone's
boss you own two monkeys tutu and Ghost
Monkey monkeys aren't those a bit hard
to take care of I must be really really
troubled to take care of two
monkeys
huh you're dad someone inside the the
other world said so to too that I'm a a
father but that can't be
right I'm supposed to be a cute girl you
love lemur oh that sounds right lemur I
like
those you are the king of jumping oh
well my legs are pretty strong now that
I'm testing them out I can jump very
high that does seem to be my
specialty huh perhaps I can use that to
Aid in the adventure and help the lib
SS Kiara Holan is your
wife that doesn't sound right wouldn't
we have a stronger connection if that
were the
case you are an amazing sharp
shooter
huh that doesn't sound right I feel like
if I'm not using a a blade of some kind
my hand eye coordination is not very
good
H you're the last Apprentice of the Grim
Reaper I think the very last
one I must be pretty young then oh
gosh a young
Reaper huh actually now that you mention
it I think I do remember being a Reaper
of some kind yes the taker of souls but
then all of that
changed maybe that's about where I lost
my
memory you ha ha Persona 3 what's
that
no when I say that word I get a warm
feeling inside of my
heart you are a Reaper and a rapper
huh
rap as in
like as in like music
rap rap
music that seems a little specialized
huh
strange
well I'm sure that I'll figure out more
more answers to these questions thank
you for letting me know a little bit
about myself the some of those things
were lies well let's go back let's enter
the land of Mojang again did you know
was that a dream we we failed to save
the world once that was that was the
that was the world oh my God
wait is this like a
differentes have turned back the time
Y is this some kind of thing where we
you can go back we're going to have to
redo everything until we get it right
can get me out of here that is very
correct many people are coming back
still here reset who are those two they
look very similar
but they look and and we're back and and
they give a similar Vibe but they're not
the same oh God she's approaching
me you are you
Blessing Me Oh there's no need to blush
sorry you can call me cie though
everyone seems to call me that I'm
apparently a very strong Reaper From A
Distant land nothing but torture
From A Distant
land what about me a sweaty do
I falling down my face it might just be
because I'm nervous I get really nervous
around new people nice to meet
you
figure keep my eyes on the seems to have
how do you feel hello she told eating
bread you seem sturdy oh I I think I am
pretty St we could be like a rock
of they they look like rock candy oh
please don't
eat oh my
goodness please don't eat my
feet wait please
oh what' you do you stole my sword
tast
good W wo wo wo wo wo wo the crazy red
one away away away away why are those
two kissing in the corners I know them
that's the cat and the
Nina what are we doing here I I'm
looking for my breads you I heard you
stole my item pink
cat stop
I protect the
weak did that get me
banned ah yes I think I've done this
before it's like Groundhog Day this
trade request has expired did someone
request a trade with with
me cie killed the
world well if I was a Reaper I suppose
that makes sense
[Music]
right right
the people I hold most
dear who's that I don't even remember
who I hold most
dear part of me wonders if
it's the people around me here do you
think maybe we all knew each other in a
different life or
something probably your monkeys my two
pet monkeys tutu and Ghost
Monkey
yeah perhaps distraught or needing to
pee I do not
[Music]
know cats are better
yeah you sure monkeys aren't better cuz
if cats were better I would have bought
cats surely I have that kind of
sensibility about
me the bright light it calls to
me go toward the
light oh yeah I remember this look at
those pretty
lights it's beautiful I am why do I feel
like I've been here before strange what
kind of name is GW
that was very rude I should strive to
not be so
rude especially amongst people I don't
know but isn't it
pretty
wow hello hey that looks like the pink
one I looking for some I'm looking for
some food do you have any fluffy fua wa
is that your
name you say B bow just like the pink
one I'll give you later you're so cute
can I give you a p on head have you
talked to I moo yeah Moco was her name
she was cute just like you and then she
said that I was sweaty and it was very
strange I don't think you're swe you
don't
really I kind of I don't know what to
think
of I don't know she has a tail like me
though yeah oh can I look at it I'm not
going to touch it I just want to look
wow it's
pretty I tried
to tried to
[Music]
no I'm not going to touch
no yeah hey look I'm a I'm a good Reaper
I'm not going to touch your tail I'm
chill what's your
name did I just make a
friend I think I made a friend oh we're
back in the castle all right guys let's
make the right choices this time and try
to avoid any sticky keys by pressing the
space bar every once in a
while I have the look of Outsiders about
me did we just make friends I think we
did but who can I consider a friend I've
only vaguely interacted with some
people send word to his
majesty yes the Heroes Have Arrived I've
seen you before okay listen there's
about to be an attack on the castle you
have to believe me quick quick tell the
tell the green ones they seem like the
strong ones you must tell them they
won't listen to
me okay you're the King right you don't
even need to tell me I know that you're
the king of this land listen I saw
something most distressing the guards
who brought you here have been informed
that you remember not but your own names
I remember meeting you something strange
is a foot your highness and there are
monsters
about a side effect of travel between
worlds no doubt did we travel to another
instance this is strange please your
highness an unprecedented Calamity now
threatens your
world I'm aware of that you told me all
of this before but you seem unfazed
perhaps the king doesn't believe me one
in doubt attack everyone and everything
I don't know if the king would like that
and he's staring me down right now for
saying
that oh I knew you would approach me
sorry I didn't predict did I don't know
how else to make the king believe
me King long ears please I like that
name thank you very much Kia people King
long ears please listen to
me only you have the power to save our
world and so I will ask you will you and
then a guard's about to bust in no I was
totally going to predict that the green
one I mentioned the green one veridis
that's the name of the green guard what
is
it the kingdom is under attack
a great host of stains has broken
through our defensive
line I said that no I knew you would say
that the CIA people came in clutch your
highness I offer to assist you I'm bad
at talking to people and it's hard for
me to make
friends but my fighting prowess is
unmatched I am from a world of Darkness
far away and I wield a sharp item she
knew that I needed that that endless
loop we have to do it right this time
thanks that that sword that's a nice
technique you got there help thought may
hear the voice know each other either
I'm here to save the day oh I hurt
myself who says that I know her she was
trying to beat me
up no bullies
allowed I will use my sword as a weapon
of peace
I get the feeling that that's what my
sword is for person I have food now here
you go take it it's a weapon a piece
right people if I was so strong I'm sure
that in a past life I I helped people as
a Reaper right that's an important job
don't you
think violence yes wait violence for
good though right surely Reapers help
people in their their time of need
Reapers should help people
you ruled with fear
huh your sword is for
justice honestly I think so too what are
these guys names
rubius Celesta I'm calling him right now
hold on can't hear you from all the way
downside the should be here any moment
if M serve me correctly you doing that
yes we've been
here yeah it's all a loop what is this
it's like a groundhog day situ
talking I'm maybe just
like she looks pretty to smells like it
you are one
yous I think there's an imposter about
it walking about there's an imposter a
foot right you are rubius it seems you
have eaten a fair Maiden they're
tricking those two newbies oh no the the
dialogue Is Res
not Ru
that's she's tricking that red
one The Lost Child of of
our what I mean I don't know who I am
you are my my father
[Music]
mother why just CU they're the color red
the
[Music]
please listen please
listen I think you hit your head pretty
brave Heroes From Another World let us
go forth with Valor and fight together
I'm ready to take on the enemy head
on let's do
it long live the king wait that's not
quite the right refence
oh that's a very strong enemy lat
this wonderful thing called watch you
think that we can truly
win last time they defeated Us by doing
nothing oh that's a big
be I've memorized one of your attack
patterns hit him from the back and make
sure you
jump jumping is my specialty after
all there's some Heroes over here just
is he taking
damage down you go I did not do it I
miss we should take out the small fry
first they're only going to get in our
way Come
here hey don't hurt my new friends oh
boy oh so cute there's a little
dog a strange Diamond appeared that was
odd you think maybe what if we use bread
instead of Swords what if he's just
really hungry oh go I'll save you from
this evil dog is it a goat it's a goat
yeah I can see why you might feel bad
aren't you also a dog oh boy I don't
think that we can survive this The
Archers
no AAL beam I don't remember what that
is defeat the King stop that he like
a the W they're too strong in fact they
seem stronger than the last time are
they going to get stronger for each
Loop stay away from friend foul
Beast ow oh God oh God oh God that hurt
oh
no yeah get him the fuzzy one or did we
meet the fluffy one I don't remember oh
boy he's going to ground
pound you can jump through it this is
impossible wait a
[Music]
minute okay here I
go revelation
yes why is everyone saying
Ricky the stain host has been
routed I have a weapon huh oh you guys
where are the other ladies you fought
bravely kind Heroes I pray you are not
injured uh a little bit Bread's almost
gone but that's fine no problem that
Mighty arm armored one must be their
leader the stain King fast fasinating
Most
[Music]
Fascinating well I see why they call you
Heroes whoa British right British isn't
it the distant land of
Britain I'm glad to have been of service
I shall use my weapon as a tool of
Justice cuz I'm sure that that's what I
did before
right
right we sustained minimal d damag
thanks to your Valor our kingdom is in
your debt thank you oh you're welcome
green one I like the color green by the
way lots of good things are green I must
hasten to inform His Majesty of our
Victory will you accompany me okay you
can count on
me I did it your highness I told you I
could see the future now please I humbly
request that you allow me to join your
your kingdom cuz I have nowhere else to
go
I heard the news though we called upon
you suddenly you Rose to the occasion
you have my deepest
gratitude you're welcome don't mention
it it's what I do you know I think is
that what Reapers do Kia people first
try they say yes my followers say first
try what interests me most however is
the strange power you manifested during
the battle with which you were able to
defeat the stains
yeah I mean it just kind of I shouted
Revelation and then it came into my hand
that power May well be the key to saving
our world from
Annihilation according to the heroes the
power came to them like a forgotten
memory when they spoke the word
revelation does that mean that I used
that weapon in a different
life it must be but once they used it to
Route the stain host it seems the power
vanished Without a
[Music]
Trace but it's gone now
does that mean I won't get to use it
again maybe I shouldn't join your army
then that's bloody brilliant isn't it so
what are we supposed to do to the next
time the the stains attack says the
British one it's bloody brilliant isn't
it why are they British I think they're
they're Li
lians revelation we must uncover the
secrets of this phenomena if we are able
to Prevail if we are to Prevail against
the collapse
what if I just shout Revelation again
surely then I can defeat a stain a big
one like the one that we took out
together many questions remain but one
thing is certain the kingdom of libal
still stands today thanks to you and the
others too right where' they
go why do I want to see them again I
don't even know them here here so Heroes
I ask you once more will you lend us
your strength to save libal from ruin
yeah I've said a couple times I have
nowhere else to go and I'd like to
figure out what my purpose here is
so marvelous on behalf of all liviston I
thank
you you're
welcome we are blessed to have your Aid
kind heroes yes kind that's what I do a
kind Reaper who helps
people allow me to introduce the four
Great guilds which are responsible for
ensuring the Kingdom's peace and
prosperity the he The Haven for the
Curious where the knowledge and
creativity are valued above all the
Scarlet wand ooh Scarlet wand the home
for Glory Seekers with ambition and
vision where closest allies become
fiercest Rivals the Amber coin that
sounds perfect for me I'm ambitious I
think right I have quite a bit of
ambition the sanctum of healing where
the Spirit of empathy and devotion
thrives the Cerulean cup maybe for nice
people I'd like to be
nice and then the beacon of the
righteous and the loyal where great
threats are faced with even greater
courage the Jade sword I don't think I'm
very courageous though so maybe that
wouldn't be a good fit for
me I think courageous isn't a word I'd
use to describe myself at
all I mean maybe in battle but with
making friends not really one of these
guilds will become your home during your
time
here okay let's hope for Amber coin or
Cerulean cup Beyond this door lies the
room of Truth therein the will of the
ancestor shall decide your
guild fear not inpection is a vital step
on the road to Enlightenment excelsia as
I always say ever
higher I do like the color red though
red would be good time to roll the dice
e be seeing some of you locked down the
Amber coin Guild hole
let us save the world together maybe
Cerulean Cupa be good the room of Truth
awaits go forth with
Valor okay the room of
Truth okay I'm ready to accept my
fate step on the platform and receive
the will of the
ancestor here I go and I've got my
trusty Ricky with me
right here I
go I'm ready
[Music]
amidst the Raging currents of the heart
seek the peaceful Cerulean
flow
Cerulean but why is it
[Music]
green jade
for the Courageous
[Music]
one Dawn the cloak
this
oh armed with the unwavering will seek
to defend the soul of
Jade
a getting mixed signals here but maybe
it's cuz I wanted the Cerulean cup but
Jade is what I am
really really supposed to
be sorted
into
courage got a name what's your name John
Watson tell
me I see it's them from earlier is it
one
name are all of you oh hey I met you
both of you that's a big
knif oh it's not a knife it's called a
scythe a scythe has a a farmer uh farmer
no I think Reaper so yeah a farmer but
farmer of souls maybe a sweaty Reaper
sweaty hey I'm not sweaty jeez cut it
out boy hey oh you always have really
long fingernails yeah you're right you
going to clip those
play oh wow okay oh I see so they
weapons I them what's up have is
a w hey how do
that oh it won't use again I guess our
magic is only
temporary that was a big
sound I think and this is Jonathan uh
Jonathan this is your we don't want
don't want it's a bubble blower or
something who are you going to hurt with
that know Bub
uh I can smack people in the head ah hey
I will defend myself nice Dodge that was
a test
[Music]
Heathen I'm a Reaper so I'm strong
too a Reaper I see I used to kill name
no my name is myy kipy but you can call
me cie that's what the the bone people
in in my chat say the kayia people yeah
that's what they say stay back though
okay I'm I'm soft I'm fuzzy oh your big
sword do anything can we talk to them H
I'm imagine it
does can you show I want to
see this the
headquarters I this we is here hey hey
nice God I have you guys on my team
you're so powerful
together well I imagine you are also
powerful Jonathan if you are part of the
Jade
sword I think I have to level up a
little bit uh you can challenge your
friends to walks here at the arena I
don't want to fight yet we'll be working
with but a spar might be fun a spar that
could be cool test our strength against
each
other very true we could we could train
yeah I suppose we're all in the same
Guild since we're all all here in green
so going to fight the St oh yes the
ancestors bestowed upon me the Jade
sword we have to do Quest together I
imagine that's is why you here your
sword is red the
quest that's kind of weird why would
they put you in
ch uh maybe they ran out of green swords
maybe that's why I mean red quite suits
me I think uh I think so too but I guess
if it was green it might be like uh
Christmas colors or something guess that
might be kind of weird you look
nice just just
saying why am I so socially awkward my
home arena duel and rules we live
together now we live together with
people we don't know
Elizabeth yes we live together we live
wait where's our bed yeah do we have
like a a place to rest maybe cuz I think
I'd like to go there door oh it doesn't
go anywhere
not that door that's
a I talked to V he said we had to
find Quest board he said Quest board
maybe it's out
here
maybe this looks like a main area of
some
[Music]
kind must be around here I wonder if
there's a map somewhere if I could pull
up a map sh map I'm going towards the
quest Master did everybody go
sorry we're trying to look for the quest
board but I have the map here we could
go this way oh you do all right lead the
way
way yes joh Jonathan I think everybody
else's Nam speak to your Guild's Guild
Master oh I have to speak to the Guild
Master hang on
wait these are all just Guild me oh hi
this is the headquarters of our Guild
and I am the Guild Master though you
would barely set foot in our world you
agre to lend your Aid to the defenses of
libal for that you have our deepest
gratitude henceforth you will be working
with us to repel the stains and save
this world okay but first you ought to
familiarize yourself with the kingdom
and learn how to accept and perform
quests out in the town you will find a
quest board yeah where my friends
friends are please go there and speak
with the quest Master mayhaps you can
explore the town while you're at it
complete a quest speak to the G okay go
to the quest board then I'll be quick
I'm quick like all of them yes did you
find the quest
board find the quest I don't
know John Watson knows where it is go to
the quest speak you want me too I I
don't have a shield yet so I might come
to depend on you bye good thing that I
have these guys with me cuz I can't do
directions I really
can't
Ed what's his name how do you like I
don't know cute more
people I just are they in a different gu
like a different
[Applause]
Castle a good eye you have your name
sweet one they all got their weapon look
at
that I don't
know was supposed to be
hon I I don't think I was supposed to
find you guys it's about how you use it
of course for the sake of improving our
relation going on never felt special in
my en life so you must be one
of
remember so Jonathan you have spoken
sure that sounds fun I want to help
people reapers are supposed to help
people hello there we are part of the I
must go back to our Guild and speak to
the Guild Master I don't
know I made the same mistake you must
have Sten do you check the where do you
check the
quest's a lot of chaos how did she get
that
creature this looks like a
perfect it's a wonderful stallion hey
what's up girl complete the
side where is the side quest apparently
we need to go
to doesn't look like there are any Quest
on this we run
you can help
usaly I've accepted the quest aced the
you accepted the quest maybe right click
on the maybe I don't know
where how about we get started with
complete the
quest this looks like the perfect job
best of luck off you
[Music]
go o materials needed thees thees we
running low on raw material Quest do you
care to join
us are we're on the same Quest join
us materials needed at the Smithy I
think everyone's doing that
one is a job for another worldly hero
shall we try and make a
party ohse
board get
where trade or invite to party I shall
invite you to the party do we all have a
voice everyone is invited to my
party is there a way we can fix just
type accept would be a Lota if you press
T and then type accept there groups
there's
group it didn't work can we start a
voice chat group it says you're in my
party oh yeah we can start a voice
that's a good idea there she
is is the missing red one back oh there
she is I shall free you I
will mayhaps instead of typing accept
you click on accept is my humble
opinion you click on it oh press T and
then hover over accept and press
it you joined my
party welcome m look as I did it right I
charge my spell
device thank
you or Revelation reation let me invite
the red
[Music]
one accept the quest the I have invited
you to my party I have to talk to the
guil master I skipped them we'll wait
until
she how about making a group a voice
chat group
that
grp I got a hor I think it was this way
I think I think it's this
way is my horse cool how'd you get that
that's cool an
egg wor from an egg yes I have one
too oh my
go oh she's back wow goodness egg
horse frightening don't want frightening
Ste how do we get off the
horse um that's a great question shift
shift how does one
find um I don't I'm not sure I couldn't
find oh wait I see it I see it now we
got to go this
way I think we're going to use our horse
to get there faster nice idea let us
ride oh mine changed
color let's go wait is everybody here
we'll wait for everyone
b b bow as they say here she comes he
changed color
[Music]
now oh that was cute a color changing
Steed I don't know if it's okay to ride
this way
Elizabeth do it do I not need to accept
a Quest from the board or is it that we
are I wonder because we all accepted the
quest but does that mean that well maybe
you should go ahead and accept the quest
just in
case is there just one up here yeah if
you if you do the the uh the right click
on the board it should come up if not
you haven't finished talking to the
quest Master then opens up Social menu
for trade oh yes I see materials needed
at the Smithy I see Smithy and my master
says we're running low on ra materials
okay okay ah Quest accepted great okay
let's go to the Smithy then
right away we go um who's the one with
the map it's not
me yeah I think uh John Watson was the
one with the map well we shall Venture
forth and
see where is John Watson say yes where
is Jonathan John
Watson John Watson maybe John Watson's
already at the
Smithy oh maybe they would ahe
perhaps I can find a
map let me see I can find a map um John
Watson you found John
Watson talk to this guy in here oh let's
put voice is this
the hello little guy I may look scary
but I'm chill you saw the quest to start
could oak logs oak logs
okay okay 10 oak logs sure oh we got 100
coins just for talking to this little
guy can I talk to you again and get some
more coins for talking cool wow easiest
cash I ever made oh
yeah okay I'm sorry s do not worry about
the horse that just appeared in your
face what's this what's this what's
what's
this what did you find a spell
book oh
wa what does that do you cannot use the
enchantment table right
now I hear voice but I want to use it
I'll wait outside this place is getting
busy
hello people scare me not a fan of big
crowds
Jonathan I think me and Jonathan are
going to be good friends then y all
right shall we go to the forest I think
the gate is that way right says we have
go to the that does look like the exit
I'm not sure where we
go it
ends what go to another location yes go
yes oh oh oh we're outside now I don't
want to go to another
loation hey enemies enemies enemies boys
oh my gosh was this correct oh gosh oh
gosh not the bread use this
chist wish we could catch them capture
them in
little get the demon
doll I like that I'm not sure I like the
way they they
cry yeah it is a little well I actually
wanted
to do this
one yes wait no not that one um how
about this
one
yes a chill adventure with my friend
my new
friends yeah get get some
exp right I'll get maybe
not oh my super attack is powering up I
[Music]
think oh I see you time it with this
with the sword bar filling
up like
that maybe I should focus on the
log oh yeah I totally forgot about that
we're supposed to be getting trees need
there is a cool down
yeah maybe each of us need to get 10
logs am I
a
oh who did
[Music]
that oh well these trees grow back
fast oh
hey I'll save you oh thanks with the
sword with the sword meter filling up I
press it once and then it I'm on cool
down hold
on yay where' everybody else go feel
like I knew how this worked once upon a
time and then I
forgot
hey right I have I have 11 wood ready
am I going to level up
hey there's a lot of
them oh yay got eight coins hey if if we
beat the enemies we get coins oh nice
nice yeah we could grind and buy maybe
some new supplies or something yeah or
like some armor or something like that
yeah yeah let's see how much how much
wood do you guys have I have 11 I think
we just need 10
oh
[Music]
okay going to explore lands I see
because the tree grows back so fast it
hurts
me really yeah kind of
crazy all right let's see how much I
have 13 logs so I'm done we get the
logs yeah I'm finished I got I got the
logs oh if you press e you can
check you can check your inventory N I
need one more you need here I have one
more you can have we'll hold off the
enemies at least I think we
will I definitely need some food
though these guys move very
[Music]
strangely woo they are strong
too I'm trying to time it
but ah I think I figured it out I foul
Beast abomination
yeah get
them I really could use some
food
right give you oh we have to trade oh
[Music]
here be careful about the tree growing
back there's so
many maybe use the sword while Scythe on
cool
down yes Scythe is still stronger I
[Music]
feel I'm sorry F them all
yeah oh no nice we work well together
nice job
though very nice
job well I I have 10 I have 10 logs me
too let's turn in our
Quest let's let's go finish this Quest
[Music]
okay have to
Dismount uh-oh
[Music]
I would like to to go
inside open the
[Music]
gates open the
gates click the thing behind you oh is
it this
ah I see thank you very much k people I
was very
confused isn't the Smithy right over
here otherwise you're going to have to
go
like I just came out of my
mouth yeah let's go turn it
in uh complete the side quest and then
speak to the oh whoopsies I'm sorry
about the horse why won't you let me
talk to him St
to Great you brought the logs your
master if you bring the raw materials to
him he can make all sorts of tools and
items for you
you can craft logs into planks and
planks into sticks from your inventory
logs and
hand sticks seem
useful
[Music]
like a
pickaxe a wooden
shovel oh but you needed certain things
like 20 coins three Oak planks and two
sticks what do I do
um H oh oh oh maybe I can make the
sticks myself now
what we can craft them from
inventory
oh said did I make it o planks I can
make somebody else just see sticks all
right
before bring over 10 oak logs there's a
bunch of trees not far
the town that you can chop outside of
the
town all right I figured out how you
make a stick make a stick well I have a
crafting table if we really oh that
might work too but you can also do it in
your
inventory can you yeah make planks first
and then sticks oh yeah planks then
sticks oh I made a pickaxe and a shovel
two two logs makes a planks and then two
planks makes a
wow so they wanted us to make the the ax
and you got to make it in your inventory
and then give him the materials does he
want the
planks and stick and stick you can make
sticks in your inventory by using two
planks yeah just stack them on top of
each other like one on top one on the
[Music]
bottom I don't think I can fight again
until I have something to eat though you
should definitely eat something
Tommy sticks I made stick they're very
excited about making
sticks oh wa well they oh puppies do I
got a stick yeah true enough how many
sticks does I am a member of Jade's
sword after all so I'm going to put this
here what does you
want Jade sword huh my inventory is very
full I don't know about my placement but
I and you talk to this guy wants the
pickaxe those two are very silly the
pickaxe that one's very smart oh I made
it to me like that oh I purchased it
wonder if she's alone or like you can
talk to this guy we can be
friends why do I
want craft the wooden pickaxe did I buy
it I bought one I SP quite to bought
it oh no I didn't want to it's okay I
also bought one I thought I was making
it scam I don't think it's a scam I feel
like you can actually use it I you maybe
we can make one actually how do I make a
pickax I have a pickax but when
I maybe
not uh yes it seems we cannot nope you
got to buy things fair and square you
got to buy normal humans yes humans buy
things with
money oh this I know is a fact our Quest
or do I don't
know
well maybe I have to turn in the quest
then do we go back then oh yeah to get
the coins huh complete the side quest
and speak to the quest master so yeah
take the quest Master yeah let's go talk
to the quest master and then if not we
do Cobblestone cobblestone oops how do I
make a
pickaxe you can't make one you have to
buy one bring the material
can I mean mine was made immediately do
you have the required materials cop a
wooden
pickaxe wait what my master
we completed we can go to the quest
Master yeah where's the master
especially if you need coins wait do I
have to do something with them everybody
have their pickaxe yeah
completed I
[Music]
see amazing how I drop them oh you have
to trade oh yeah make sure that you
trade with the the uh the person in
charge trade request okay trade I
thought we had to buy from him we have
to trade too yeah it's both you trade
your coins you have enough so typically
if you think about it every time you buy
something at the store my group You are
conducting a tra must I might have to
resort to the violence against The Rock
why oh you must do it yourself okay good
I don't
know I have low confidence and self all
right we'll check with the quest Master
but maybe we need to do another Quest
I'm not sure okay okay shall we
go off we go back to the quest
board hello Quest Master we did your
quest looks like the perfect job for
best of luck off you go okay I think we
also need to collect Cobblestone now I I
don't know if I finished
it we need to col Cobblestone oh God
damn it there are more
quests oh there was Cobblestone we had
to get to yeah I think this is like the
next part of the quest so that's why we
need that's why we need the pickaxes
gotcha I only read one page pickaxe to
get cobblestone that makes sense let's
go get this this John Watson character
is definitely this the smart one in our
group so we should definitely follow
what she
doeser I'm
not you're not done oh it's okay it's
okay I to him we're going to get cob to
go we're going to go get cobblestone
let's go no not yet what happened did
you not have a pickax potato salad I
don't know they have some
bread it's part of the quest it's part
of the quest yeah it's part of the quest
traded oh hello hello I'm not too I what
is cob I'm supposed to get cobblestone
now yeah let's go get
cobblestone puppies I've never heard
that have you have you been asked to get
Coby
Panic follow
me to The
[Music]
Apprentice coblin D is a special
material
go oh well I hope that they can make
their pickaxes
I think they already have them right
yeah so it's time to go get cobblestone
I think okay I think D yeah I think so I
went that way are you okay now fuzzy one
I think so I don't know though brandish
your pickaxe and let us see oh yeah
let's see your
pickaxe now swing it from side to side
side side to side pickaxe pickaxe oh no
that's that's an axe h Huh that is an
axe it's a different weapon of mass
destruction what that is an axe it is a
different weapon of mass I'm going to
trade with you okay is not one you pick
your noses accept
myl it's quite foul I don't really like
thinking about that but you're not wrong
I have the oh okay is it in your
inventory I have one but work one
second there you go I I trade worked out
I I haven't finished the quest yet
that's okay we got to get cobblestone to
finish the quest follow me follow me I I
don't I talk to the
Scarlet they'll figure it out they'll
figure it out but when they say Scarlet
it makes my ears pack oh true is that
part of your name red
one I don't know maybe it was a nickname
cuz it says e blood
flame above your head but
my friend Elizabeth blood flame like a
Scarlet people keep riding their horses
upon me oh I wish they would
cease hey these days no
manners watch where you are plopping
your horses oh
it's something something deferred that
one of those legendary horse girls oh
we're doing oh wait they don't hear us
do they I've hey I'm just saying I've
heard of your kind before no
problem back off I will defend myself
you must Spa if you would like to Spa
you must come over to the Jade sword
area they G they're gone that's all
right you know people talk a big game
not ready getting excited I thought that
knew were going to Spa yeah some people
can can talk a lot of s word but they
can't actually take it mine
time I'm ready to mine whenever you guys
are
wait I'm sorry oh that's okay did does
fuaa have enough materials by chance to
make a pick the trade
box she can't open it Master
right do you know how to open the TR you
should just write uh let's see right
click when you talk to the quest or the
blacksmith
person yeah
SMY yeah you just go here and then black
and you right click
and then you talk to this little guy
where is oh where
go please submit your guys the quest
isn't done yet we have to go get
cobblestone when we talked it here let
me show
[Music]
them my name is Iris and I don't know
anything else besides that name oh IR he
sounds so helpless and weak crafting
Quest didn't submit honestly it makes do
you know what cup you're in you go a cup
what do you mean cup I got a new Quest
what what quest what do you mean cup
what group are you in myce not the quest
Master
Apprentice where's that
here okay let me talk in here I will
talk to them the blacksmith's
Apprentice oh I see okay now I can talk
to oh I see now it makes sense from now
on when you find new materials drop by
here and talk to my master the more
different materials you find the more
things be able to
make now it's completed but my master
will make you some cool stuff the wooden
pickaxe huh completed yeah I already got
the stuff from I don't want to talk to
him then you arrived right as we were
losing hope uhhuh okay wonder what would
suit you best can you bring 10
Cobblestone next you can probably find
some lying around in the same place you
use your Oak planks did you buy did you
buy I I thought it wouldn't to the The
Apprentice again yeah
you to talk to the gained 50
exp the to my
Apprentice I see figured it
out nice thank you bone people okay
people why was I supposed to talk to the
blacksmith then to buy get
pick okay why can't I just use this on
the stone okay maybe it would get dull
let's see your pickaxe let me see that
thing that's no good
oh that's not a pickaxe it's a horse are
we going to go somewhere can hardly tell
the difference unless the horse's name
is pickaxe we're not leaving until we
see your pickaxe I think that's a bad
name until you show us your pickaxe
young
lady all right we're ready let's go get
let's go okay off we go for cobbly stone
the places are so fast
quick okay oh boy oh here's cobone hey
easy enough is this we got to Beware of
the enemies though because I haven't had
a meal in a long time okay I'll get off
my horse I'll protect you seems like it
isn't working oh that stuff can't be
broken I don't here away with me oh it's
turning into a different color it seems
you can't continue to mine it
it sounds like it's going to blow
up it does doesn't it I I
hate it does frighten me should I go be
the
hero clim up here that can we get that
get away get away get
away okay okay I now I'll use my pickaxe
okay oo lots and lots of cobbly stone
how much cobbly Stone do we need I think
probably 10 once again
yeah what the
heck we are
efficient stain is on
St all
right nice how much do I have now 25
that's a lot of cobblestone this is not
is is not right what's cob Stone maybe I
can give some to friends if they're low
what what when is cobbly stor cob stor
it's war cry Jonathan it is but war cry
think of it that way it is trying to
attack us
enemy a stained
rabbit I think we need more food soon oh
I got it see I knew that rabbit was
evil
rabbit
perish yeah this is what Jade sword is
all
about we shall become strong yeah strong
together mhm if if we
survive we will survive and as long as I
know how to love I know I will stay
alive why that came to mind strange
maybe maybe a song that you heard a long
time ago oh all the enemies are really
ganging up on us I'm going to go
back it's too dangerous the it's way too
dangerous yeah we got the Cobblestone
though didn't we yeah wait please wait
for me oh no it went away no waiting
they
good hope the red one comes back she's
probably still fighting though she seems
to really like
fighting have enough sticks oh do you
have yeah do you have money and sticks
bought the Cobblestone all how much
money do I need 50 I
got okay do you have
sticks okay o a stone sword and it's
unbreakable completed the quest what do
I want I want a unbreakable stone sword
wait 100 coins oh but I have 100 coins a
stone pickaxe but I can only
get hey just in case I can't use my I
have a sword rest in peace is what it
I'm going to go outside and make a phone
call three I'll be standing right there
all right I'll be coming with you really
strong my God what hideous hair you have
oh that wasn't very nice probably want a
pickaxe too huh stone pickaxe I don't
know what to do with my wooden any
wooden one anymore but I'm sure that
I'll I'll probably break it at some
point don't you
think that was a strange
crack we did it we did it well where's
every hold on let's check where
everybody else you have always seemed
cool or looked cool yes oh did you guys
turn in your quest yeah oh wait no not
the quest we have to go to the quest
board still oh okay you talk to The
Apprentice right yeah we did cool then I
guess let's
go sorry for
chaos yes
yes okay Quest I feel pretty good about
about how fast we've been going Calamity
see you've gone and finished the quest
okay yeah help the common folk okay yeah
we can stop by and help the common folk
I need some food yeah some food I could
go for a
bitey find shops on
items the item shop here's a bit of a
coin to get you started oh cool 500
coins we're
rich speak to the
shopkeeper I can retire now on this this
yeah we don't even have to keep doing
this anymore we want to get another
Quest
no is there another Quest let's go we
have the shopkeeper we have looks like
cockroach armor next speak the
shopkeeper yeah that's true maybe we
should do that first oh okay wait
where's
Elizabeth where'd she
go oh red
one oh there she is you should let her
know we're going to you don't like
it he some red one did you turn
your oh yes
I have you got another another Quest oh
we're going to go to the shopkeeper but
it has to be after you submitted the
quest at the quest board then we're
going to get oh I see and all this new
found
money
peopley which way was the oh there it is
it's right over here trait request for
what
don't find out yeah if we speedrun all
of this I bet maybe we could go to a
dungeon that's how you accept dungeon
yeah I want to fight in a dungeon with
you guys and see how good you are yeah
see your SK did you pick up another
Quest NOP not yet oh that's
okay you need to climb it I'll
it I was going to pick it up after
visiting the shop yeah Bu from him why
don't we pick up the question since
Elizabeth has
itep has something for I'm a little
confused because it just gave me the
option of getting another Quest unless
oh the quest Master why do you have a
raw pork
chop because I killed a pig I'm so proud
of you go talk to the quest leader
[Music]
now are we waiting hell
hello hello hello there
Fuzzy's blown uhoh what were you doing
being
sneaky
500 have any nope I'm all
outar oh yeah I'll go to the time to buy
something I'm
hungry I'm going to die if I don't eat
something you please don't do that know
crazy that I
am help me leave my friends alone back
off now we have to speak to the child in
theard does that mean excuse
me stay away from my guild member
excuse me excuse me excuse
excuse to my like that maybe if I if I
buy all the food first then I won't have
to worry about there being none cuz
there really are a lot of people out
there
bartender mermaid
Chef a nice cut of stained meat some
salt and pepper put it on the grill Poli
buy s bu those at the shop oh
yeah sure but where do I buy
it drop by here if you ever want to
listen to some
sick can buy some sweet vins theop are
other dope records scattered through the
world to why does it talk like that why
is it so
familiar vinyls Benda if You' like to
order something ask the barid over there
you can really save the kingdom drinks
on the on the
house instant Health
regeneration jump boost
[Music]
interested we shouldn't talk about this
here they're listening instant heal I
like that I'll get one of those please
can't about this right
now use their facilities here you are
you stealing their
oven yeah dang we should have slain some
meat outside then wait the you are
correct I am from
Amber yes disgusting I am from that
place disgusting yes Amber is disgusting
the
bar pretty delicious ones do not Amber
talk to us don't talk to us do not shush
me Fair ma or else I will shush you in a
moment don't I know a way to shush
Marcus and Brutus
Brutus is very loud are you guys from
what have you seen who's here to save
the day thanks now I can report you
guys bring to
Liv it looks like there's just a barid
selling potions here I love I love these
seats they are made of chair these find
some
steak what's this how about in here is
this also a shop looks like we can't
enter from the back door maybe that's
legal can we enter the horse oh my
God she's
crazy H you maybe it's not this one have
I have 7 Brave hero thank you for saving
this town in all of our Lives welcome to
my humble little shop right on my body
sure what do you what have you sire all
you have to do is talk to and I'll show
you what I've got in stock isn't it that
easy yeah I'm afraid I can't just give
everything for free my dear make sure
you have enough coin okay you stop by if
you ever need anything or if you just
want to keep me company I don't think
I'll be stopping by to do
that children sure fighting stain all
day will be hard on both of your body
and heart if you're feeling wey remember
to take care of yourself have a break
and do something in the garden visiting
the guild Halls of the four Great guilds
for instance each of them has an
activity you can participate in many of
my customers are regular in
AR when you're tired from adventuring or
simply looking for a little diversion
maybe give some of these activities a
try okay just talk I'll show you what's
in oh why not visit the gardens that
does sound fun the children are tending
to them and I'm sure they'd be overjoyed
to meet a real hero such as yourself
yeah things will be
hard
children o can I get something to
I know I to eat I'm so hungry maybe we
should go
bimo
bimo here's an idea what if we go
hunting instead outside and bring the
food back and use their instant Health
there is an instant Health there
is I was thinking maybe we could cook us
something have you seen what this bomade
sells it is is amazing yeah potions but
only potions so I bought that oh well
done I got I'm going to hunt and get us
all some
food yeah yeah yeah let's go hunting
together shall we I saw a bunch of them
out there y right here yeah's here I
wonder if we have a a a chest that we
can store our food and such in back at
the GU I tried to steal oh oh that's
probably not a good idea don't you I'm
not sure I'm not sure the Guild Master
would
approve yeah they might kick us from the
kingdom to be
honest we're here to protect them taking
a couple things is yeah once and go joh
watch probably continuing the quest a
Jan Oh Boy do we want to go to the the
child I mean do you think there will be
food
there maybe there will be food there Wow
Let's go to the Garden quite small I I
have a small horse
oh where did you want
let's go to the
gardens okay yes I just wish I had a map
to know where they are Watson was the
map
holder I have a map I mean we we all
have a map do we not oh yeah I mean that
is true know how to read it I have to
pull it out let me grab it oh thank you
for saving this town welcome to my
humble little
shop let's
see what can we get what can we get all
right all right just give give me the
gun give me the gun give me the gun
why are they making them work in the
gardens it's kind
of think what the heck wait why do we
have to talk the kid I want the goods oh
so are you looking for the child so far
A little far remove don't like this
behind the blackith
to you for child I see it on the behind
the blacksmith you
guys it's this way oh
[Music]
oh you think they know where it is it's
supposed to be here
right
oh hey found the same way from point A
to point B I'm
embarrassed uh you both found the way
you think they have any veggies
here are you Lou all the best what the
what the heck is hurting me oh berries I
think I hurt a lot now golly you're one
of the heroes boy this must be my lucky
day here's the gardens you're free to
come and use them whenever you like use
them for what oh the child pretty Aces
isn't it my job is to keep an eye on
scare away birds and stuff let me know
if you you're one of the heroes boy this
is my lucky day this
is try
building where your Heroes can build
what building an empty past you you
Heroes can build whatever you like you
miss get bu
toay to do building or gardening can I
tell you a secret did you know there's a
place called The Pit the pit M say but I
can play a really fun game there you're
here I'm going to let you in maybe you
can check stop anytime you want to do
some building or gardening the P can I
tell you a secret did you know there's a
place in town called the pit isn't that
where the Amber coin people
go mom says kids aren't allowed to go
but I can hear there a really fun game I
of
bread okay did anybody else just get a
bun of bread see what sneak Oh I thought
to sneak the bested child to
the whatow okay oh go this child is
speaking to you you can go check it out
did the child get any else bread no I
didn't get any bread I would have loved
to have some bread huh yo kid where's my
bread huh excuse me hope to see you
again can I did you speak to someone
else to be able to speak I got 64 bread
too I did I did threatening violence
does
work why did you hit you hit this child
and got bread no I didn't do anything
like the kid gave me the bread out of
their own free will that's a lot of
bread oh
yeah look look look I get
bread oh I will give you head Pats J
what are you doing the best the best
salad skills ever look look look look
look oh is it that
easy I don't see
anything what are you doing are you
destroying the bushes I thought we were
making a salad yeah they
so does it really
okay where's the
salad
berries what the
heck hey did someone take my berries I
don't get any berries they're for my
salad salad I got some
scavengers yummy yummy I want infinite I
infinite salad hey the salad's good for
you yeah Violet on
the yeah maybe this isn't a great idea
all attacking at the same time but it
does seem kind of
fun maybe it needs to not be a sword you
mean like a pickaxe or maybe my
scythe noral
this is definitely a
[Music]
harvester maybe
not I feel a little
silly ouch ouch
ouch they gave us the bread so that we
can get hurt by the bushes H I guess
so bushes are dangerous this is a
dangerous Garden huh yeah we all got to
be on our guard
yeah I'm going to die from the
bushes are you guys being called Away by
something that sounds kind of
familiar do you want to try and go to
the pit first let's go to the pit yeah
yeah Mom can't go there was the child
can the child can't go there
okay on our speeds yes on horseback
back um I don't know where we're going I
think it's it the pit is the the Amber
coin area I'm pretty sure on the map it
says pit door does it not on let's see
I'll pull it up ambercoin the pit it's
next to the quest board if you go to the
quest board and take a
left I think they're gone
[Music]
I you are hey over here
right this is the pit that's it doesn't
look like a pit looks like a mansion
like a super rich person
Mansion why would they call it the
pit ooh bookie quiet is it for
racing oh H lucky lady lucky lady I've
got the game for
you I am a new
face yeah I don't know you this guy yeah
we are
heroes I think don't right nothing
nothing sh get
rich I like money yeah money's good you
can buy things you want with money don't
go I promise not shady saying but it's
okay Point yourself at your to run with
the Jade sword for I join the Amber coin
we wa the
party yeah when the guild Masters took
us out Co found some stains they also
taught us how to work as a team
ex just point yourself at your mate the
party oh come here and play around or
you get you can adventure together swap
items and
coins see told you it was useful didn't
I you'll thank me for it when you're
adventuring oh it'd be a lot easier if
you had some extra coin is all I'm
saying wishes to speak to us
don't again down here the pit and play
around or two okay
speak you see some poor s walking out of
your pennyless don't worry about it is
this are they asking us to do something
shady I don't know like roll the dice
for us maybe we're going to do like
under
town I don't know Guild Master wishes to
speak with you please meet him at the
Jade sword Guild
Hall that's where we're from right
yeah we know where to go
then Master yeah we're going to the Jade
sword
area is that I'll follow you guys yeah
oh oh looks are you sure the sharks can
drown though that seems confusing
I feel like that's not something that
should happen to go I must go my own
path for a
moment okay Elizabeth you said you'd say
by my side
forever maybe she's just a bit of a
loner I can kind of
relate I guess
what but you guys I like hanging out
with you guys I don't know where I'm
going are you sure you do follow
me I know where we're going
I don't know where's F though take of
each other we got to look after each
other no not here Jade's sword was this
way that's where we're
from sh Watson you're a criminal o
that's my friend you're talking about
you watch your
mouth
oh where are my
friends we're going back home yeah it's
this
way
okay really beautiful Town though yeah
honestly not the worst place to wash up
isekai is wait is it up here I do I know
that word
ohai
eai I don't believe Gigi by the way I
think you're cool John
Watson you're cool too ah man I'm
blushing oh gosh I got to look away they
I hope you familiarized yourself with
the town I did I did we learned a lot
about
adventuring we all lament what has
befalling the lands outside our
kingdom the Calamity and the stains it
has borne have turned most of the world
into a wasteland you must be shaken to
suddenly find yourselves in another
world but I pray you will be able to Aid
us in our fight our first priority is
finding a way for you to regain your
powers of Revelation you not include
sticky keys to that end I have just
received word from one of our Scouts
regarding possible
lead investigating the
Calamity our comrades Chas Upon A
mysterious ancient
ruin more over theer from the ruin a
light akin to that of the Revelation
which used to repel the stain King where
right here Scouts from our Guild are
already stationed at the ruins for
further
investigation I asked that you might
join it join them there and lend your
Aid
go forth with Valor no problem cool exit
the Town Gate head of the Plains and
speak to hastas of the Jade
sword so that's the next Quest yeah
shaken suddenly find yourself another
word yes yes I am shaken yes the poers
of
ration call
want that probably more COC and I need
to head off here oh you guys are going
away on a different Journey huh a little
bit of a different Journey but we'll be
back soon
okay well let's adventure together when
you guys come back shall
we well take care it was fun getting to
know you both today let's do our best to
sword Jord Jade sword strong together
trespassing
trespasser away with you
trespasser I am allowed to be here
bye-bye hi this isn't public property
now you're the one that was allowed to
be here staining the name of John Watson
and John Watson he's my friend so back
off this is a public space yeah back
off tell me where your leader is what
leader he's right over here we don't
have a leader on our team we're all
leaders not your team oh thank you oh
joha Watson even though you wish to kill
the king
huh the king uh
I'm trying to save the king I have to
kill him to save him wait John Watson
huh what you need to kill the
king no I said I need to save him how
will you save him by freeing him from
one second I must hang up my phone call
real quick be right back team I need to
have this call oh boy come back where
are you there they
go oh so John Watson did try to commit
regicide well I'm sure they'll solve
their differences
right oh J Watson do not run oh oh no
they're
circling so you can duel dueling does
sound kind of
fun duel what are the rules what are the
ruels the first participant presses the
duel button
okay whoever wishes to challenge them
also presses the Dual button the first
participant speaks to the arena
coordinator again after pressing the
start game button countdown will begin
after which The Duel between two players
begins you can also duel party versus
party in a party one representative of
the party should press the duel button a
representative of the other party must
then also press the duel button then all
the other party members who wish to
participate must also press the duel
button only the first person who pressed
the duel button can press the start game
button after which countdown will begin
and the duel between the two parties
begins that sounds
fun I feel like John Watson
and
GG good game should duel out their
differences but that's just my personal
opinion
well I guess it's just me
now fight fight I'll take on a
challenger I'm happy to fight
anyone I'll fight
[Music]
anybody if they'd like to fight
me let's see oh is this the construction
area mind if I test something
[Music]
oh some others are pinning the Jade pin
to their white coat I like that
idea I'll try
[Music]
that
hey oh this is the map you hold it to
use it
what should we
build this is the green zone perhaps I
should lay claim to a a certain
area build my own
home maybe the corner would be
nice but did you pay for that
property
no but it should be okay
[Music]
right this is my home
spot little small though don't you think
maybe a bit
wider just make a giant wood
Cube yeah I think that should work for
now it's modest but you know
it's it's good good
enough what is tax evasion I've never
heard of that in my
life it could be a small Cozy home but I
can't help but feel like I want it to be
a bit
bigger
H The Guild Halls humble
beginnings can't forget tax evasion I
think everyone will get to share
this area so I don't want to take up too
much of it but I definitely wanted to go
ahead and lay Stak to the
[Music]
corner yes it's very dangerous they say
pay your property tax they say this axe
is going to end up breaking isn't it
I'll try to be more careful with my
planning I'm sorry if it's a bit of a
waste exploring some ancient ruins
sounds fun but I feel like I should have
a team together for something like that
cuz if
not I definitely think I will
perish take up the whole space and give
no
explanation that doesn't sound very nice
oh oh hello oh is that you John Watson
I'm just going to call you Watson hi I'm
in the construction area kind of carving
out my own area for me oh nice okay I'll
try to find you okay sure just want to
see where you are oh yeah okay byebye
bye I guess that's how the phone works
huh a chest to store in would be nice I
wonder if there's a place I can buy a
chest I doubt I can make
one this will be a nice home and see
look there's still plenty of room for
the others cuz it's a very wide
space perhaps I will fashion mine into
the shape of a skull
can you call anyone I have phone anxiety
I get scared talking to people on the
phone and again I get scared talking to
people in
general well I figure if I can't go on a
big adventure with everybody
today then I'll just make a home or
something yeah maybe we could unlock
some new materials but I wanted to at
least res set the base area as this is
my plot and have it be
wooden you
[Music]
know get a new group even non- greens
will you think they'll allow me in their
in their
group yeah
worth asking that's true oh but Watson
was going to find me in the construction
area maybe I'll
just I'll send a
text I've lost my way
now again for the millionth
time let's see maybe I will ask to go on
a journey
you're in another
party oh no the
Betrayal they seem to take their
loyalties very
seriously you're in another party again
oh no do you think that my teammates
would also react so
[Music]
violently quina
you trolled us oh the
drama maybe Watson will want to check
out the
ruins yeah conquer the undead dungeons I
mean don't you guys think that maybe
that might be something
that that I might be experienced at
especially
me right
shouldn't that be my
specialty I think I don't know that's my
own
[Music]
opinion oh if I can find it oh hello
hello are you going to go on an
adventure yes mayhaps we are We Gather
our party members too oh do you do you
think that you maybe have some room for
more party
members we we have four oh hello maybe
only five people can enter how many
people can join our party that is true
only five people can enter a dungeon of
five five yeah I see so they've already
got their full party party of four oh so
you two must fight each other to the
death what no no no it's okay I'm going
to bed it's it's Siesta time oh it's
time for John Watson Siesta yeah well
take care John Watson it was nice
meeting you today yeah it's nice meeting
you guys okay may our paths cross again
goodbye oh thank thank you good luck hey
why would you say good luck I'm not a
not nothing nothing I'm a nice person I
I'm a great fighter too I'm strong
that's why I'm in Jade
swword yes yes yes yes would you be okay
with me joining your adventure yes we
would be okay you must come to the quest
board with us though we must remake our
our our mind party okay sounds good I
won't let you down I have a question
yeah which Guild are you in I hope it's
not ambercoin oh no I'm I'm with Jade
sword we are strong courageous Fighters
good good yeah what's wrong with
ambercoin though I'm curious what are
the rumors flying around about ambercoin
oh ambercoin oh we don't even let's not
start oh you don't like talking about
Amber coin oh it's it's whatever it's
pish po pish posh yeah yeah well we'll
find the board first okay let go let us
go let us go let us the de that's crazy
oh
man make haste towards the board I will
not let them
down sorry my my horse is very
slow py it
is ah I see one of my
people I too have uh some problems with
my map you see it's a bit hard for me to
read yeah it's uh definitely this way oh
yes quite yeah yeah yeah this is this is
the right way this is uh the the
quest most definitely
yes but of course oh did you find the
lost Leeson child Amber coin
uh amber coin I'm on leave me alone I'm
on the
phone
oh she's she's actually she's a jade
sword member though I'm confused really
yeah that's a jade sword member lied oh
uh maybe she is Amber coined I don't
know I don't want to get involved in
this oh no it's just oh hello hello hi
there who are you people beautiful pink
lady WTI
um oh gosh these two are exhibiting an
aura that I've never quite felt before
are you what is your name
I'm I feel like your legs are calling to
me excuse me your thighs your thighs are
calling to me and I don't know why hey
your thighs are falling to me I have a
scythe I want to sit on your thigh I
don't know why I want to sit on your
thigh hey hey hey hey hey hey back off
back off I have a scythe and I'm not
afraid to use it y by by by I super your
Scythe is so sharp but you know I have
some sharp shuriken like this
amberin
wow I'm a poopy am ambercoin are you I
am Jade sword okay then you're okay
ambercoin
suck fine why is there so much uh Strife
between guilds I wonder why do you
dislike no idea that's what my gu told
me to say focused on well as long as I
can join you for your adventure I guess
if Jo Miss Maiden my fair Maiden can you
open your magic tombs and go to page
four weaps
sure and leave your party you whatever
party you may be in we are better than
that so don't worry I'm going to you to
you swine you did you do that my brain
is Tiny I know this place like the back
of my hand I am very smart welcome I've
joined your party welcome welcome to our
party welcome how do you know this place
I'm not abandoning Elizabeth she seems
to have made
friends what you we are not friends we
are not friends you're talking closely
to each other no no Sheed I was about
about to hush her gums a traitor she is
a traitor you can hush gums is
supposedly
ambercoin she's Jade sword like
this oh my God what was that I just I
just contacted someone she a harlot too
what what happened I have no idea what
happened the
Harlot you do not need to something wet
what wet where'd she go it sounded a
little wet don't you
think wait well you know let's let's
let's let's forget about you know oh
recollection recollection Revelation I
forgot everything that happened your
sword upgrade must be fluster where do I
the fluster the flusters seems nice are
you the beautiful hello I'm going back
to our Guild okay what will you do there
they're going to make more money that's
what they're going to do oh I see ah yes
I love money for I am part of
ambercoin are you sure you li you bloody
liar you bloody liar what does she lie
about what what Guild she's a part of if
you guys aren't ambercoin and you're not
Jade sword are you Cerulean
cup no we're we're the we're the best
team in the world and you should join
you should join our our our call our
call on the magic radio what is oh right
we have the magic call in our yeah
you're not in the magic radio you don't
you don't need to you don't need to
possibly join what is the magic radio
this this this thing that's in our hand
right here and then you you click on it
you right click on it and then you ring
ring with the diamond thingy I don't
know if it's a diamond thingy but the
thing you right click Diamond thingy oh
actually I don't know it looks like a
pile of dust to me right click I'm
trying I'm trying to recruit the pink th
the beautiful pink thighs to join our
call oh I in it yay us
meet the castle Gates
everyone Gates I understand everyone do
the quest up until the follow
me follow me up until the uh the ruins
the ruins yes no I'm still at the Smithy
Quest wait wait let me let me finish
that real quick yeah okay definitely do
that is there something we wanted to do
after that I'm assuming we speak to well
like you got to get to the quest first
cuz our quests are not sync so okay okay
wait wait wait wait sorry let me let me
do this real quick
uh uh could you bring us 10 Cobblestone
okay okay okay okay yeah yeah it's so
hard talking to these um these leeston
that you have to like you have to like
Crouch like crazy and the sticky keys
the force of the sticky keys comes on
and makes it very difficult why is
everyone falling I think they turned off
sticky keys actually Cay people maybe
I'm the only one that gets the sticky
keys prompt we were aded I haven't
gotten sticky keys in a long time but if
you press shift six times
though I have not been getting sticky
have advised to turn off those sticky
keys before how do I how do I give it to
them true I want to give it to them help
I am being swarmed at the castle Gates
there are so
many oh I only have eight hey how do you
get cobone can someone tell me how to
get cobblestone follow me follow me yes
my queen what
KY they hurt what what
happened what your quest my quest is to
exit the Town Gate head to the Plains
and speak to hastas of the Jade sword
okay we're on the same Quest Iris wait
is your name Iris your name is Iris yes
my name is Iris what yes follow me here
the special all very special let us go
we are full of empathy mind you okay oh
my god there our middle name oh my God
this world is so large what all of our
middle names is empathy cobblestone is
this
way see over there oh it's minecra I
mean it's stone is what is
Minecraft
Minecraft I I have no idea what I just
said how do you craft their mind yes
well I guess I'll do some yeah bully
that puppy bully that puppy it's making
puppy noises we are not bullying him we
are freeing him of his they're quite a
different crew B why are you trying to
kill the rabbit yeah it's a dark
one what's wrong with the dark one I
don't know evil AR alone the rabbits are
the blue full of no it's not what about
the cows rabbit can we can we can we
make meat out of the cows wait sorry
instincts I want to get off the horse oh
there we go wait let me
Revelation Revelation Revelation not
ghost stories Revelation the cow didn't
die from the Revelation wow this cow is
strong wait that is a strong cow that is
a strong cow die
reation
Revelation oh my God I didn't mean to
kill those oh God why did I oh it didn't
drop anything they are pretty strong
even drop any meat these guys I will
help you
nice hey the monsters Dro coins they do
hey we are rich
Rich
iose no we are not to be full of greed
that is not us we are full of empathy
okay I have no idea what empathy means
anymore what does empathy mean can
someone give me a definition of empathy
passion yeah compassion peace empathy
that's what it means are you seruan
cup yes we are all ceran cup we are all
ceran cup yes nice to meet you just
what is what is Jade all about huh what
is Jade all
about don't be so
aggressive we are courageous fighters
who fight for what's right oh wow oh
okay you guys seem like the actual good
guys okay yeah why good guys we are good
too the actual oh yeah oh yeah you're
right you're right we're full of empathy
and we force empathy on people by
killing them
right okay well everybody's got their
way way is that taking things into your
own hands I
guess is that oh excuse me sorry my
horse is a is quite a um you know Rowdy
fella you see I I don't know how to
control it oh oh what a Ry horse I'm I'm
talking to I'm talking to a ambercoin
member right now and who the ambercoin
member this ambercoin member is the same
member that adopted many children and um
and is and loves money I wonder why Liz
said that
who she must love money cuz that's what
she says Liz who is Liz you know the the
redir money for breakfast does does it
taste good you seem to dislike a lot of
people on my team she was very oh wow
what kind of money do you eat every
single for breakfast lunch and dinner is
it different every single time where are
you are you in the I'm at the Smithy
you're at the Smithy I'll come save you
copper flakes oh what about silver when
do you eat
silver hey hey hey stop talking with
that fake Amber
coin hey get out of
here leave alone get
out hey us CS are here get out of here I
was just I was just asking what her what
her nutrition D diet was she's really
not bad don't don't talk to don't talk
to her she's like a fake ambercoin oh
she's not bad I mean that's not a good
that's not a bad thing right I thought
we hated Amber coin yeah she's Jade
sword apparently yeah she not is she
actually not ambercoin yes she's Jade
sword I am oh I
actually I thought she was Amber too oh
wait you lied to me I thought you were I
thought you were ambercoin you kept
saying you Lov money that was just like
a fullon sign to you this whole time I
am part of the Scarlet wand how dare you
how dare you
I wait where did your teammates
go I have to apologize I was also lying
on her behalf saying that she was a
member of Jade sword yes she is not no
she wants to keep her her identity and
she not even Jade
sword oh she's
aass oh my God I also don't know where
she is from you look the first time I I
I met the you were trying to threaten me
so so isan she's in the red team I mean
it makes sense hey you don't talk to hey
you don't talk to my killed member like
this stop stop it you shut your mouth
hey do not raise your voice at me I am
the next Queen in line you Willam you
will
respect you put your sword away she is
to
[Applause]
on the ground there is PVP I can show
you where there's PVP there is would you
like to follow me yes there is that's
our Guild the Jade sword I will take you
to the Jade I will take you to the Jade
sword Guild what your at the G Jade
swword Guild it's right this way follow
me so she is Jade sword Jord I don't
know what's going on is she Jade sword
was she not Jade sword I should just
remember this stuff welcome to the Jade
sword ARA guys are we are we going
dungeon I would like to do the dungeon
I'm just showing you where the ARA yeah
you're right we should go to the dungeon
if you would like to fight later on
there is the Jade sword Arena whenever
it's waiting for
you I do battle the only place I do have
courage is on the
battlefield I need to do my quest you
guys can I need to do my quest wait uh
what was the next Quest I need to go
back to the quest Master Miss ninoa
where is Hast at the planes you can
check the map where left shift oh is he
onwards I need to get check the map and
I should show you the NPC need to go to
next I know we've got grave duty but I
hope the quest time I not see on my see
him he's very far south oh you are here
get your started yay I'm money speak to
the shopkeeper I think it's just
straight where is the
shopkeeper the shopkeeper is right
across the the Smithy okay I thank you
yeah I am here he has been expecting me
is it just straight AC oh no what is
this Jade sword I think I see shopkeeper
shopkeeper shopkeeper shopkeeper or
South huh am I just supposed to talk to
the shop
maybe across the plains I see
oh hello we must kill all of these ooh
gold do not be so easily
distracted I'm sorry my my empathy I
must return to kill them all you have to
do is talk to me and I'll show you when
I've got in stock then select what you
want to buy isn't that easy I must put
the stains down do stop by if you ever
need anything okay you've been expecting
us have a break and do something okay
you can try visiting the Gill Halls of
the four Great guilds for instance each
of them have an activity okay oh the
great ruins do I have a lot of quests I
need to do which one are you at not many
the
sh well these are all side they're all
you're
like watch out for that enemy I okay
have to go talk to the the kid in the
park you got some time you Vis the
gardens the children are tending to them
I'm sure okay the children children
let's stalk some children oh wow wait
wait while we wait for friends I'm going
to go ahead and pin my my jade sword out
emblem to my C where's the children
where's the children lead me to the CH
where's the
children in the garden there's a child
in the garden is it the is it the place
with the Amber coin is it where um Liz
was trying to take us or is that a
different place no if you if you check
your map you'll see a red marker for the
next empy you need to talk to do you
want me to help you wait let me see if I
can figure this out why does it say I
don't have any side quests huh I thought
I did about
did I like where should I pin it I'm
coming to find you where are you I'm in
front of the shopkeeper and I'm just
like wait I thought wait do I so I
talked to him he was like oh find the
children but then like now I don't have
a quest and I'm just like where's the
children um so like just follow me I I
think yeah it should be I think it
should be around here maybe it was this
way
yeah I think are these the
children uh there there's a child like
in the middle of the garden there's a
Gard sword yeah there's a garden
garden wait maybe this isn't it oops
speak to child yeah it's the Leeson
child and it's in theid must be one
important child to be called the Leeson
child I know right it's the child of
I've got an ey patch where did where did
crony
go I thought I was following you and
very cool thank you isn't that a pin
where's the sharp part going into my
eyeball the bestle child oh found it I
found I think I see the Leal child wait
oh really I think it's it showed up on
my map now it wasn't there
before okay good thank you I can't find
it I will now make Jade sword a part of
me the bestle
child let me talk to you I just want to
say hi Leal
child Leal child
yes it's the best child ever wonder SP
if we end up perishing in battle in this
ruin oh
wait is that the the best little child
it looks like any other kid what makes
this one so special lost the ruins oh
some have reported hearing a strange
voice but we know not what to make of
it Souls of stains open the
way looks like our team members already
figured out the the
riddle there a riddle
I mean yeah it says oh slay 10 stains
and then we have to speak how find you
want to do some building or gardening
got it leave it to me I'm
ready cannot proceed yet oh yeah you'll
we'll see about
[Music]
that I've been slaying stains this whole
time dang
it speak to the best in child okay speak
to the pit Dorman okay now I'm at the
pit Dorman okay pit Dorman okay you
found the pit Dorman where was the pit
Dorman again was like in it was in the
yellow area right no was the green wait
was it what the heck is
this I remember crony saying she wanted
to see the pit dorm 20 minutes ago so
yeah who is crony I I mean I mean the
queen I mean Tam Tam Tam oh oh okay wait
what is your
name Tam Tam Tam your name is Tam yes oh
where did that come from oh I mean
Jonathan Nam me Tam Tam stand for the
your maiden C for short I see now hold
on it makes so much sense why yes yes
yes I'm so soaking in all this
information maybe I didn't use it right
oh no not the map want to get rich I
know
you who is Tam that's strange that's
me we all have been in the same party
for tens of minutes you just revealed
your name isn't that a bit odd huh
I was told that the
faker are you talking about Liz yes she
Li to about her affiliations why did she
yell at me then why would she lie then
she just doesn't want anyone to know we
gamble here apparently she's in the
arena but I can't find
her The Guild Master wishes to speak
with you please meet him at the perhaps
she's just a bit confused oh this one's
really D speak to the Jade sword master
Okay Jade sword Guild Master can we ging
sound fun maybe after our Quest hello
hello n shell
breach wait oh never mind you're not
master you look Harlot hold on I got to
I got to drop out of this call for a
second excuse me why is everyone a
harlot oh the whole call
dropped I hope everyone's fine well I'll
wait here at the ruins
since we came all the way
here I'm almost done slaying these
so well maybe I can re-enter the
call
oh you want one Harlot yes there's only
one Harlot it is Liz the Harlot oh I see
that's the har
okay she's a harlot gotcha you guys
called wat a harlot as well she did
never call her that okay if she Watson
is pure of heart she did kiss me yes who
kissed you Liz yes she she she smooched
me and see and now I can sing a song
about kissing a girl now oh wait
congratulations will you sing now I
actually actually no I can't remember
the Melody I couldn't possibly remember
the Melody I just remember that words I
kissed a girl and I liked it the taste
of her cherry chest I did not
like no no no I didn't like it it's just
the lyrics you know and I like it lyrics
The Taste of her cherry chapstick I
don't think she was wearing Cherry
chapstick would taste like Wax
personally yeah I think it would
probably many around you I will help
I Calamity and the okay okay
must I pray
okay finding a way for you to regain
your powers of Revelation hey I
[Music]
just what see she's so mean to
me I will have a word with her do wish
we could all get along you're over 10
now oh there's no such thing as getting
along with everyone what are you talking
about oh true enough I have to drop this
call to give her a piece of my mind
there she is
go you I you mean the loud one you
disgust me what what was I
thinking I know it's only five people
per dungeon but maybe we can come up
with a compromise where we take
turns believe I'm sure Jade sword would
love to join maybe we split up the team
is she is she good would you say she M's
in my heart Callie is in my heart
me yes I'm honored thank you
okay leave me alone she's honored she's
in my heart I love all kinds of friends
so yeah of course I'm honored hey red
red thing I am Elizabeth oh Elizabeth
red red thing I'm talking do you not see
me talking to this this no I didn't hear
you talking red thing apologize to
Jonathan Jonathan Jonathan
withy key is What will open the portal
it seems she is making her war
cry underworld we shall secure the
surroundings you may proceed undisturbed
what am I supposed to do apologize say
sorry I I apologize that you are
sad investigate the underworld dungeon
then speak to the J apologize that you
were a lesser being
here have some of my melons ladies we
all share the same
goal where let's not forget we're
supposed to protect the
land you
know it seems I cannot give you my
melons why are we talking about the har
is talking about melons now why they put
me into Jade sword I have no courage I
tried not courageous at all these melons
are Stu to my hand
what let us partake of her melons for
not giving you my melons can I have your
melons
too I would try but I cannot give it to
the why why how can you try and and fail
at giving melons I I I am using the uh
the mus the musle the Q muscle is not
working oh my
God
okay pretend I didn't hear that and just
go oh is this a shared chest
expecting you you have do you see my
stuff our initial for
the no way enter the ruins we are gu
everyone can use it some have reported
hearing a
strange good you have to slay 10 St exit
the town head to the PLS speak to slay
tens SLS then speak to H it's okay okay
I think I'm almost at the the dung every
get chest this corner Barrel will be
mine I do yes I will slay them I will
take this corner Barrel from
me okay I'm going to go I guess they did
get rid of the
recipe this corner Barrel is mine don't
stop
right wow do we
have they must have entered the dungeon
already where is this dungeon it's uh
you can get a key for it if if you slay
enough enemies and you can enter Oh we
must speak oh we have to investigate is
it this thing it is this thing I got a
key for it but not everybody has a key
for it I don't think okay I will wait we
will
wait uh-oh hey I wonder if only one
person maybe the party leader needs the
key maybe everybody needs
[Music]
one did Ena go inside well I have no
doubt she could clear the D d by
[Music]
herself but thing is you have to be in a
party know how far it goes oh my God it
barely does anything I think yeah
they're fairly weak oh sorry this is
youran I Revelation it what are you
talking about I didn't kill it I
Revelation it's different
yes I'm
[Music]
dying two parties of three is also what
I was thinking but some people said that
five is it's probably too hard do
without five and you are Elizabeth I am
Jonathan with a
G yeah it's actually Jonathan G we have
a we have a Jonathan in our Guild too
but I do not know if it is with a G oh
that that is fine wa does that mean you
are gathan no no no it's pronounce
Jonathan maybe we could do three then
oh I
see well gathan I shall give you my
melons another time fathers have cleared
it with three
numbers to accept oh why are you eating
your melons in front of
[Music]
me did I just be that way I'm build that
way what do I do maybe I can trade my
melon with
you through the power of my empathy I
forgive you I know it must have been
very rough to have fallen in hard
times
ow I'm I've made up with
her oh yes I got the key I got the
underworld key thing I okay me too yeah
shall we what should we do it yeah I'd
like to go too but don't we need to be
in a party I can go to the dungeon
now all right does everyone have the map
I mean not map does everyone have their
key yeah I think Ena already entered
though didn't she can we go in I think
she's doing it
alone she doing water then key up here
uhoh I did leave the party call let me
get back in has this key where is the
dungeon anyway I can hear you guys now
oh my gosh or you guys can hear me sorry
about that oh this one right it's at the
end yeah I got the key um did already
enter no I'm back at the to just
chopping a bit how do we know how many
we have slang I see it you have to use
the warp and then you go all the way to
the
end what if we made you think wooden
swords is enough what if we made two
parties
you think that would be good H should we
do two should we buy stuff should we buy
[Music]
upgrades well we don't really have iron
you know what let's Let Me Mine a bit I
see gold right here want to stay with
their
group oh that's mine no what are you
talking about what do you mean that's
yours I was almost done I was almost
done that's mine actually no get out of
my way get out of my way you was almost
was almost oh no that's what you did to
me you will never you will never
successfully dig that one out you will
never no no no no I I will not allow
you you know what it's probably faster
if I start it appears there are people
in cut scene in front of us or they're
seeing visions in their head and they
are reacting to it well they must be
crazy then oh boy they must be crazy
then wait I I think they cleared the uh
cleared the dungeon okay do two other
people want to enter the dungeon
together maybe let's enter the dungeon
enter if five of us go then one person
will probably be left behind really only
four can go only
five yeah we have five yeah but I feel
like we should also what about Liz she's
not in our party a we can go into teams
of three we can swi yeah we can split
yeah I think that would be the best way
everyone to meet
inside oh can going to go are we going
to go in with um with wooden swords I I
think I should probably upgrade stone
sword can I can can you possibly be kind
so oh so kind to um throw me a stone
sword gathan beloved I will have to
return to town to get you a stone
sword let me make haste let me come I
think we have to split the party before
going into the
dungeon there's a area in there that we
must make ready checks I think we are
allowed to split the party before we do
our ready checks okay you say so away oh
there they
go all are repeatable I think yeah oh
okay so I am here Fair Maiden
Iris oh gathan
my lovely handsome gathan yes yes it's
pronounced Jonathan after we clear it
the first time not comically large it is
uh just pronounce i i mispronounce many
words it's okay comically large please
except this trade this is how a normal
sword looks like that's not even a
normal sword yes oh Bo stone sword you
may have some raw beef thank you I will
eat it in front of you to show how
appreciative I am yes please eat the
[Music]
raw s Liz would you like to enter the
dungeon with another one of us we're
going to split the team into three
groups or two groups I think of two
groups of three no do not don't split it
do to me it's okay oh you don't want to
enter the dungeon
together I mean I it would be fun if you
want yeah i' like to enter it with you
yeah I I wish to INE oh no one Minds
yeah they they agree that we should do
that so I think it would be best that
way don't be such a
loner large sword woman yeah no need to
be a loner not loan I'm doing my
quests Yeah by yourself
ye I ain't got to relate I was behind
just
can't oh what
oh oh no don't go yet don't
go
[Music]
no no she's still slaying she's
slang do we do we have to do this quest
to be able to do the next bit yes you
kill 10 if you kill 10 then we we can go
to the next thing yeah Elizabeth
let me find a mystical
sounding seems my my freakishly large
one is is wonder what I can do with the
stone freakishly
weak freakishly weak
sword
Revelation oh
boy I finished my quest I'm just doing
it for fun now I love
killing what I love killing things love
what killing things this sound right I'm
a grim reaper oh but not you guys I
wouldn't hurt you empathy wait you're a
grim reaper how that yeah that's what I
did before is what everybody told me
wait really who told you oh the kayia
people they're these bone skeletons that
float around in my head Liz completion
so she
can I think she needs to kill a few more
stay by the way by the way Liz it won't
tell you if you kill 10 you just got to
you just got to know how many you
kill there's one over here I'm going to
go dig for some more stuff
while yeah I'll go I'll go farm some
more coins while we
wait yes
okay
ow how dare you hurt my new
friend I'm getting good at this I wonder
if we can make stuff with their
hide oh yeah if we mine the ore on the
cliff side then maybe I can make even
more amazing walls for my
home or I can make iron items
[Music]
checking our level aren't we level
14 so how shall we split the groups it
just ends the whole thing how shall we
split I wonder are we all call it does
drop yeah it might be in a
call where' everybody
go I'm sure they'll be
back I was told I had one more oh one
more you got this no I've never done it
I've done it now but uh it did the gods
didn't tell
me nice that's in the end yeah I'm glad
to hear
that
yeah nobody's riding off into the sunset
oh maybe they're going to shops to
prepare ah that is a good
[Music]
idea sorry there's the party call I did
not mean to hang up the phone call oh
it's why do you keep hanging up my
connection I was entering a tunnel uh
the tunnel seems that the magical
connection between our brains causes it
to to drop the call you mean this is all
this talking is telepathic yeah talking
directly into your head oh
wow Sasa magical world yo more enemies
die how do I throw oh wasin okay yeah
recycle lady recycle you may be a queen
but you should recycle copine what what
excuse me I don't think I've ever been
called called something so foul hello I
no maybe I have but that's definitely
very
yucky the Smithy won't let me make about
your H may have an autograph I don't
know what she's talking about what a
pleasure to see
everyone oh hey we are
incoming okay with many people okay
awaiting you I
[Music]
seen yes yes friends are here
really what really what promise okay I
trust you as as a member of the Cerulean
cup I trust
easily wait don't do that blue Maiden
appeared and said
what there's a wall oh okay there's a
lall I are you
sure are you sure I think she needs to
join the party can she join the party I
can't jump
it's not allowing me to only available
to party
leaders to inv what's under here we'll
split into into groups of three in a
minute we're going to split into two
yeah party is different than the call oh
okay I see okay also no caps please
please do people if you use all caps I
have to get rid everyone inside the
dungeon um oh okay are we going in the
dungeon right now first and then we
split yeah no we yeah go inside P the
bridge and then we can split our party
yeah okay okay pass the bridge so around
here this area where we're waiting in
front of the dungeon pink lady fwell I
passed by something fwell maidens yes T
Tanashi K
kii where where your you pink lady Tashi
this Tashi we just saw doing something
yeah saw in workings of your brain I
don't know what they're making me really
uncomfortable
sounds pleas leave me alone I know I
know everything have issues with people
I am right in front of this at the edge
of the bridge group chat okay maybe we
should get out of the call group chat
can I this the oh
my leave me alone I just want to go in
the dungeon with my friends please
explain the vision I don't know what
you're talking about please leave them
alone you seen it already no I don't
know what you're talking about I just
want I just want to go into the dungeon
with
my I I have I have I have questions I
should get out of here who is preventing
you guys doing to my honorary enter
already hold on there's a person that's
being very rud let me get rid of
them put them in time
out that's right I'm in the toilet so
what should we go should we go
inside no no no just just come come um
that's not the dungeon yet you
it's the path going toward the dungeon
so you can go
thank you appreciate that what is crony
doing in a toilet hey like I said group
chat assemble stop hanging around in the
toilet wherever you
are in the
toilet how what what what what are you
letting out that you're taking so long
in the toilet just wait where are you
hurry up and hurry up we're where're
we're in front of the dungeon I'm in
front of a dungeon what do mean you're
not in front of a
dungeon you're the only one that's not
here what the we aren't we at the
canyon no click the thing to go in after
you get the key oh
okay
henceforth known to all we must enter
the dungeon okay God we must split and
enter the dungeon yeah we got to split
up I don't know if Liz knows that we're
here is Liz does Liz know
here okay okay let me go let me go see
if I can pick her up I don't know if she
can read Global chat let us go to the
dungeon towards the dungeon if we're in
a private call can she not hear us I
wonder let us go in Dungeon no she can
hear us if we are in a radio call okay
yes yes all right let us I am going to
go to page four of my magical to okay we
can make a new group and disband this
party yes party
disbanded I'll make a new one then
um who would like to claim your three
two claim your two my two claim your two
was my my two claim your who wants to
join Mor team Kopi claim your to yeah
okay yeah oh you guys y oh my gosh
they're very frightening but I'll invite
them what do you mean
frightening I invited them me grab Miss
ninoa okay and let me grab Liz who I
have forgiven I mean aren't you also the
aren't you also perhaps like something
that might be connected to this dungeon
we have a cheat code yeah huh I mean I
do get a familiar feeling entering this
place
now invite Miss Liz we should probably
out of the radio I suppose so a new
radio call then
yeah okay okay is everyone
ready the dungeon oh there we go stand
by we're going to do amazing yeah I'm
sure it be great stand faster than the
other teams yeah we will enter the
dungeon no players standing by you got
to St we got to ready up do we have to
ready first yes okay okay enter all
right your party
enter we're ready yo we made it wasn't
there something we needed was there
something we needed to kind of like I
don't know play play play play while we
enter I don't think so no don't worry
okay okay the
underworld oppressive Darkness hey as
scared as it is unavoidable it holds a
final resting place for every creature
that walks the Earth yet even in this
realm of the den there are those who
acally skipped everything ski a skip I
read for you you know that feels very
familiar to me I think you're supposed
to
death that's such a that's such a scary
concept death H also yeah also the other
let me explain to the coai people the
other two are are gone because uh
they're in a different instance SP they
facing in a different dimension yeah we
split oh my God
this oh no no no please hang on are you
okay you bad should we build a bridge
shut up uh uh excuse me I just had a
little slip a little slip oh there we go
there we go good good good nice nice
okay there seem be a light over there's
okay that light seems promising I'll go
towards it too um oh wow that's a bit
should we make a bridge uh can we make a
bridge it might be the safest beted to
make a
bridge all right I too shall try jumping
they say I'm good at it oh yeah it no
yeah it won't let me no placing blocks
huh well then we'll have to be
careful how about maybe over that no
that's where we came from let's go that
way
okay lead the way hopeful one let go
that way and then we go this way and
then she seems to know where she's going
I totally know where we're going oh yeah
there's another yellow thing over there
yeah yeah is there wait wait where are
you where where are you where are you
over here yeah it's like a some kind of
like
Obelisk what is whatever that means
where's cron where's where's I mean
where's Tam oh there we go Tam why are
you
call say above her head Gander who's or
cron okay if you say so I'm a little
confused new checkpoint checkpoint so
perhaps if we die if we happen to perish
we'll respond here that sounds promising
pretty a you know this is
promising oh I think we need to go over
there that yeah that looks like the next
Church o I think that's a castle that's
not a church that's a castle it's like a
sky that is in the sky yeah Okay jump
jumo jum oh so that's why so many people
are
D yeah oh the Myst solved that's the one
thing I we will not die even once we are
we are better than that oh for sure
exactly we are what they call gamers yes
we are totally Gamers uh person who
plays games
well yeah games try not to bring the
team down oh you're a gamer me your
checkpoint heck yeah checkpoint wow
we're just speeding through it huh I
know yeah I know right and then we go
this way and then we go this way and
then we go this way whoa she's really
quick I mean you seem to know this place
better than me and I feel like this used
to be my home or
something yeah settled down buddy oh boy
oh she definitely doesn't know where
she's going no I just it was just a slip
of a slip of a hand I'll be right back
I'll be right mean more like
yeah wait she'll be able to make it back
I'm sure no no I'm right behind you
right behind you yeah a speedy teammate
would definitely be right
back you can chill at the next
checkpoint
maybe right behind you
who that looks really
familiar okay it's not this way it's a
not this way I get the
checkpoint well I don't know if it's
working for me but I don't need it
because I'm very used to this place I am
so gaming wow you very I don't even know
what gam what does gaming even mean that
sounds like a that sounds like a word
that's only for people who Who games
game yeah it's a term that only I know
wa you guys don't play gam just in your
free time just for fun you have free
time know what gaming means
I'm just curious thought everybody has
Hobbies right A lot of people game you
guys see you know what your hobbies are
you remember what your hobbies are
jumping apparently yeah they say jumping
and also I'm apparently a Reaper so
probably killing people I think who told
you you're a Reaper you're you you must
be you're more you're a goddess not not
a Reaper you're a goddess godd what why
do you say that it makes me really
embarrassed when you say that but why do
you think that he's a goddess how could
she be a Reaper no huh what about me
screams goddess to
you I'm going to die which is
ironic I died twice already in no wors I
never died cuz I'm the queen well that
doesn't matter that that won't matter
you will die soon trying to take the
throne no no no no like the The King and
I oh man I can't believe I have to
explain the story every single time are
together we locked no no well they
locked is the king and her no we didn't
go that far what are you saying all
right I mean hey live your life I have
she's really yellowing no wait not like
that it's supposed to be like a
political thing okay oh a marriage
arrangement of convenience a political
marriage where I gained the throne
because I mean look at the king it's
easy
oh he's pretty old I guess but I I could
definitely at him behind the scenes man
man look at this lady talk oh we're in
the dungeon oh in the D okay
oh get in here it's dark it's time to
fight okay I'm ready whatever enemies
may come our way oh my God is that a
demon oh yeah it was too fast Revelation
Demon's everywhere get
them yeah oh my God oh my God bad wait
wa wait wait I need I need to equip my
sword let me get him Revelation crits
crits exist nice nice job team are a lot
of I think we got to keep I think they
keep spawning so we just got to push
through them maybe do we have levels in
this in this world well I'm level 15 but
oh this one had an
item maybe we retain our levels even if
we they have like they have rice balls
what are these things I think they're
shapes they have shapes they have like a
like a star shape and oh my God they
hurt yeah they do hurt quite a bit they
hurt quite a lot oh my god
oh oh my god oh my god wow this is
really tough oh my God where are my
friends it really
hurts it's quite a maze isn't it it it
it's
amazing shut up it also feels like home
a recollection oh my God they don't die
they don't die from the it's reation
reation waa that area is way too dark
wow wait where are you
guys oh wait I found something found a
door oh I found a door is it a door a
door I'll watch your back where's the
door okay there's a triangle
key oh how do I you know some of the
zombies are actually holding these
things oh oh y you must have picked one
up
hey there you are you found us yeah we
unlocked the door nice one team yeah
let's go I totally did something I'm
sure I did you way can we ride the oh we
can't ride the horse here okay no around
I've definitely been here
before ooh so you must be a goddess yeah
yeah if this is if this reminds you of
your home then you must live in
a castle W look at those
chandeliers oh I want to swing on him
whoa she wants to swing from the
chandelier never mind
chandelier that's where did that song
come from I can't remember know I'm sure
we heard it somewhere what do you think
this thing does is this a puzzle I think
this is a
puzzle it looks like maybe it's a movie
screen maybe we just jump into it oh no
never mind you usually jump into movie
screens I don't
know oh it is a puzzle oh okay wait it's
like it's like one of those things where
you like eventually make everyone
everything light up right by just
clicking on it like randomly um hey I
got this side
uhoh but all the s the other sides
affect each
other this might take us a while maybe
one person should do it then a Boop a
Boop oh I don't know I feel like not
smart enough for this kind of thing a
Boop a Boop you're doing good you're
doing good yep yep yep a Boop Bo boop
boop
boop this is hard a
Boop a a Boop are you why don't you do
rather than just you know why don't you
I me usually for these for these puzzles
um only one person should do it cuz
otherwise yeah we'll definitely be
screwing each other up for sure side of
Boop you know could Boop another side
you know there's four sides to this
right yeah yeah why don't you go Boop
another side and do it faster than me if
you're you know I'm not sure that's how
it works want to but you keep messing it
up buddy really is it changing the other
sides
too
yeah that's okay common mistake don't
even worry about it oh okay I thought it
was a one I thought each side had its
own puzzle I didn't you're cute so it's
forgiven yeah it's it's
okay yeah oh I'm bashful oh no I'm
embarrassed now why did I say that what
a weird thing to
say beautiful pink lady likes me what
she doesn't like you what she doesn't
like you she she doesn't no not like
that her not like that well hurry up and
hurry up and solve the puzzle then hey
man tried to take my time
here meanwhile oh man this is I will
mingle with pink lady to hurry up me oh
hi you know you're pink too actually
it's really nice I know that I'm soling
all this puzzle by myself I'm hot pink
yeah I guess you are really beautiful
eyes too they're different colors yeah
yeah I'm hot pink oh oh my God not just
pink oh what's wrong what's wrong I
thought you were going to solve this I I
am oh she's Violet I don't know it's
it's like a I think yeah it is like a
hot pink Violet is color it's very
beautiful pomegranate oh thank you a
pomegranate what is that that sounds
delicious it's a really Juicy Fruit oh
wow you remember your fruits I'm so
proud of you oh yeah I mean I remember
basic things just not my history hey
guys yeah like the bonding time is great
and all but do you really want us to
help you with this do you really like
you know I mean you know cron are you
sure I think we're just going to ruin it
for you wait I think you're close I
think you're really close though
wait
wait we're really close maybe we need to
move them over you figured something out
probably I'm going to ruin it aren't I
no no you're not going to ruin
it you feel like you need to switch it
back hey all right now we're on to
something I got this whole part here
dark okay okay this this part is filled
in no no
psych oh one part is filled out wait how
do do you I I can't see the pattern
honestly you can't ruin something that
isn't even close to solve say this says
the C people that's true okay that's
good wait wait hold on hold on hold on
hold on hold on hold on she's getting
it's getting
there I think that the way we need to
end it is yeah just one unlit one in the
in the
corner there's a bunch over
man
huh oh
whoops I can't go much higher than
that what a strange
Cube maybe work both sides to one side
just keep wrapping it around maybe if
you go from one side wrap all the way
around and solve it that way oh no the
one side that was full is no no no
longer full I wonder if it was my fault
for touching the
cube forbidden
Cube Cube
actually can I can I try it again you
guys can can you can you guys kill time
while I try to kill time oh all right
are you saying are you saying we weren't
helpful no no no no no no it's just that
like you know like uh I like I like no
no no no like I like solving puzzles no
I like solving puzzles you know like I
don't know if you guys like solving
puzzles so you wait I think I'm starting
to figure it out wait oh really
okay never
mind that was weird let me know if you
want help I feel like I might ruin it
though no you're not ruining it like
she's she's seeing the way yeah yeah I
know she is over watching over us
overwatching us oh
yeah okay what if we just stay on the
same side and work together on it and
then just slowly sound like a game
name that's
crazy oh
wait yeah if you think it's wrong you
can always switch it back yeah
thankfully that part is good that's what
I'm
trying I think I'm started I think I'm
cooking guys oh yeah oh okay
okay
oh
sorry I'm hearing news that the other
team used to quote unquote bug It Out by
spamming lights oh my God they bugged it
out yeah I think we should maybe avoid
doing that though I'm getting I'm I'm
cooking I'm cooking she's doing it
nice just toggles a plus shape is what
it does yeah it's a plus
shape yeah
oh I'm cooking I'm cooking I'm cooking
yeah yeah she's doing it she's doing
it yay Iris the genius I'm the genius
genius genius you know I was I was
doubting I was doubting whether I was a
genius or not but now I remember I am a
geni remember that you're so you must
have been really smart in your past life
no yeah I must have been absolute like
like I must have won the Noble Prize
whatever that is no a Noble Prize I
don't know but it must be something
special if I remember
the word if you're noble yeah cuz so I
must get it soon too if you're no you
need to be you need to be smart and
Noble and I don't know if you have both
I think those at the moment well you're
saying I'm not
Noble oh wait not all you are noble oh
noble people should join Jade the
huh the
skull hey hey this way this way this way
you guys see the skull in there this Hot
Topic in there wait I don't know what
Hot Topic is oh wow that's beautiful
that's so
cool Hello Father wait I can't eat maybe
not my dad but that guy looks I want to
be friends with him oh
oh hey wait no why would you do that
what's what's wrong with your dad why
would you do that not my dad I don't
know I just got a weird Instinct angry I
just had a weird Instinct that's
all oh boy oh we're stuck here oh no
we're waiting I'm waiting died oh oh oh
hello hey uh huh this is the checkpoint
from before
oh oh who what is this place it's a
mushroom we fell down do we eat it wait
don't eat every every strange mushroom
that you
see oit Bone Heads can I eat it no I
can't pick up the bone can I cut it no
oh he he revives yeah that is one very
very persistent skirlington am I
supposed to feed the mushroom H him or
something I
wonder ah hey hey back off
boneman oh know your place oh you're
supposed to kill him okay okay okay
wait here his bone meal will drop and
make the tree grow yeah it all makes
sense yeah yeah it's gr grow the tree
this way this way you
fiend he is only father yeah for our big
tree y yeah is it done now it's getting
so tall are we supposed to climb it all
the way up
maybe I think we should let it grow a
little more I think we need yeah we
probably need to grow a little so the
branch spread out you killed it in a
weird spot I'm so sorry my help come
here
here up here up here come here up here
up here come here come here there we go
you think it works I think that's it I
think that's it I think we can climb it
now can you make that jump do you think
oh no no we can climb the vines oh the
vines ow I'm bad at climbing vines how
does one do that do you hold space or
shift yeah you hold space I'm going to
die I'm going to die hold on a sec let
me kill this
guy don't spam don't spam oh what's what
what someone something just hit me okay
now heal yes I must first so much for a
noble Warrior all right up I
climb there we
go
oh this is interesting I've never had to
do something like this before oh yeah
first time for ah less underworld and
tree climbing first time for
ah first time for a even in the
Underworld I was never one for climbing
trees I don't
think uh this is not very
familiar hey not bad though nice
nice we can make it
work I wonder did we go here maybe and
then up here and then and
then tree is hard to climb yeah I don't
really know where to go to
next I'm having a hard time yeah
figuring out oh maybe
here did you find the way oh yeah I
think I found the way too here here this
way there are two mushrooms we got to
kill the skeletons really we still got
to kill skeletons here wait
wait Cy Cy come here here oh no I after
we climb the tree don't worry no worries
I'll be don't don't climb it all the way
to the top
oh yeah there there are two mushrooms
here
oh just not much of a climber you see
you see where I am I'm so bad at jumping
this let's see one moment let me see
where you
are hang on control maybe I should work
on the quests while this is why this is
why the Minecraft like those Minecraft I
mean you know I have no idea sorry I
don't know what I'm talking about it
must be
crazy I did it I did it um let's see
where crony
is I'm
attacking oh I see you oh you did it
they're ahead of me before I Know It
wait
wa yay wow you're so quick what a a
gamer what was that about you not being
a
gamer oh I am quite a bit of a gamer Oh
wrong oh okay
I think royalty should not be playing
games true we should be taking care of
you your highness no no there's a
royalty that plays games you should have
time you should you should be spending
all your time making the citizens lives
easier that's what your job is right as
royalty anding I'm not royalty yet but I
throwing dinner parties well so that
means you're only playing games while
you're still not royalty and once you
become royalty you'll be you'll be um a
slave to all of the citizens you'll be a
Slave to the Citi what
yes that's that's a very negative way to
look at it well there's some truth I
don't think you're ready for for
becoming a slave to the
citizens a slave excuse me I think we
can climb this now or do we have to
connect the trees like why else are
there too connect the trees yeah they're
still they're still spawning okay come
here come here come here they probably
continue to spawn regardless though even
if the tree isn't complete do you don't
you think
maybe but like why are there two trees
yeah I'm also curious about that hey hey
hey don't follow me come here back away
back up back up back up back
up okay I think we can climb it now is
it
climbable I think we still need to do
one more oh boy everybody's getting
slain by skirlington huh oh
dear can you can you can you kill them
this way this way can you kill can you
kill oh I can kill can I kill oh I can
kill kill yes don't spam though okay
okay one more hit one more hit one more
hit probably there we go nice good job
nice nice nice oh there's there's
there's
Vines cool I'm going to climb the right
side cuz why not yeah uh-oh maybe I'll
climb these this seems right this goes
quite a ways
up maybe this isn't the
way oh
hey this is the way they're going got to
be right probably this way probably this
way lot of platforming and then go this
way ow maybe that's how I got so good at
jumping like platforming too I like
platforming she might be a jump King
what what could that ever mean that's
what everyone was saying to me and I
didn't get it but now I think I do oh my
God I almost died if being in the ah me
too if being in the Underworld requires
this much
jumping perhaps that is why oh I'm
looking up your um Cape you're looking
up at what cap nothing at your cape it's
very
beautiful thank you you're welcome you
guys looking up yeah yeah it was very
lovely she's you know her life is
looking up that's what that's what's
looking
up yeah oh God I'm so
embarrassed
wait and then okay okay
okay
fall oh what are you talking about I'm
here already oh oh you know you think I
was going to fall while I'm here first
new checkpoint unlocked maybe I should I
was an over AI I climbed way too high
not surpris you know I mean you did say
you were a gamer but you become you're
going to become royalty so you don't
need those gamer skills anyways you're
going to be a slave to the citizens okay
okay that's the word on the street what
does that to the Denis of the Underworld
the light emanated by Souls was vital
they needed it to survive in this ever
cold and dark environment yet among them
there was a heretic who called their
Customs into question do we really need
to take others lives to sustain our own
no there has to be another way sounds
and so she stepped yeah I know right
into the plane
above wow what a dummy why would you
leave all these people down here to
suffer and die she was selfish what a
heretic
it's this way I'd never do something
like that personally if you asked me I
know I believe
yeah oh we did it tiny the power of
Revelation has grown stronger yay level
up maybe did we get the treasure of this
place and now we sneak again guys we
love
sneaking a portion of your memories you
recovered a portion of your memories ooh
nice a memory well want a
memory am I going to remember how to
spell things now oh hopefully click here
to watch video
oh
what click here to watch video is it a
oh I got it are you sure you want to
open the following
website this is where we
um can we watch it will it will it Auto
play or do we have to play you have to
open chat press t
Okay shall we take a
look yes wa is this is this okay to show
on Screen Pro probably right or should
we
just good old security warning wait wait
let me double check don't do it it
steals your security your social
security number there's a download
available so we can we can play it
ourselves you know think it is okay to
play it yeah we can yeah we can play it
but the only thing is I
think all right I think I'm just going
to use the one that I will show you guys
a portion of my memories I will sh yes
we will share the portion of the
memories that has unlocked yes yeah here
we
go
yes I'm going to silence myself
here we
[Music]
go a Reaper's job is to end people's
lives and take their
souls that's how it's always been the
spirits of the underworld need their
[Music]
sustenance but I keep wondering
is this the right thing to
do no it's not
[Applause]
[Music]
what's going
[Applause]
on look at
that turns out we can also use people's
emotion we don't need their souls at
all Reapers should help the
living not take away their future if the
others can't accept that that's their
[Music]
loss I'll do things my
way
huh uhoh
that doesn't seem
good I better leave before the others
come back to their senses they're seeing
the same vision that I saw if they find
out that I was the
one that betrayed
everybody they won't want to be friends
with me
anymore I got to
go I was the heretic
It's All Coming Back to Me Now that's
why I got mobbed I got to go I got to
run did they all see the same memory as
me wait what if they saw their own
memories
though we were in the
Underworld I got to
go me are you sure that was me
though
huh wait so you don't care that I
betrayed all my underw fellow underworld
Ians to help
people not good Parenthood sorry I'm
sorry
yeah yeah I'm not sorry I'm not sorry
then yeah do do you guys forgive me of
of course of course you were we we we
went through this dungeon together we
are nakama whatever that word means
nak nakama nak are you sure Hakuna mat
Hakuna mat mat
Hakuna how do we know that it means
Hakuna means
was family was it family Matata family
also that is not an
explanation oh well I guess it's okay
then everybody seems to be in good
spirits so we have done an amazing job
perhaps I'm I'm in the clear well if
that was my past it is what it is it is
what it is I'm glad I ended up being an
okay person okay the past don't matter
all that matters is the present and the
future but I feel like the underworld
definitely don't like me though super
duper beautiful who are you beautiful
Raven lady oh you have such a long
spear than thank you for
noticing such a beautiful spear oh I
just realized guys my My Little My star
thingies are shiny do you can you see
the shine are they no I I see themar
they're sparkling on they're sparkling
on my screen ooh Why pretty is it cuz we
went through a dungeon I think so maybe
I mean I don't I don't see any other
reason call yeah pull out pull out your
weapon mine oh hey mine's sparkling too
Sparling too I can't see it cuz I
haven't done the dungeon yet you want to
do the dungeon I can uh we're going to
me me and beu and and those two
mysterious looking dogs are going to do
it in about 30 minutes together oh how
fun yeah
that sounds like a fun time whatever you
see in there though you know take it
with a grain of salt is all I'm saying
okay let's just say it's a lot of
jumping yeah there's a lot of jumping
and also it's apparently my home so I
hope that you guys enjoy your time there
I guess I I'm sure we will it sounds
like an enjoyable Place yeah I'll take
care of the dogs too they are also of
the Jade sword so I have a lot of
respect for them
yes I wonder if that means ladies
Revelation Revelation whoa can you do a
beam yeah I'm a beam Blaster I'm
stronger than Goku whoever Goku is I
don't know who that is I don't know Goku
I'm going to experiment on this chicken
Revelation oh did it really deserve that
stuff going on behind your head when you
did Revelation what was that
I don't know I you your head just
exploded when you did a revolation what
was oh dang
okay I you're using brain do you use
brain cells every single time you re you
revelate see
Revelation oh wow my mind is Call's
Revelation looks kind of cool yes this
is my trusty Scythe Callie's Revelation
looked kind of cool not going to lie
yeah it just needs time to warm back up
but yeah my Scythe of death and
destruction I will use it as a sword for
peace
I'm waiting for my Revelation to wait
ooh hey why don't you revelate again
please revelate for
me what no I mean why why is it all in
caps ah what if she wants to hurt me you
guys are a lot Kinder I
think your memories no it's okay so that
that one's really aggressive I feel
though the orange the GG One the good
game one she's really aggressive no no
no Jonathan is part of the Cerulean cup
and we are all very full of empathy so
it's yeah that's why we're in the
Cerulean cup cuz we're full of empathy
and kindness and we think about peace of
the world she really job guys hey we saw
your memories yeah they're kind of
embarrassing you remember so interesting
I do but did you guys just clear or did
you guys did something else it's a
little embarrassing no everybody seeing
my memories we clear and we were just
like waiting and we just having you know
just having fun
did we take that long we were did we
take that long you did oh yes we we oh
yeah we we finished wait 3 hours ago
even we didn't dungeon 3 hours ago it
Wass ago what time flies you know oh
yeah we could turn in the quest yeah oh
yeah did you guys notice that your
Revelations are sparkly now after the
after the dungeon they
sparkle oh we're too far they can't
guess it wasn't a bad memory right guys
they sparkle now Sparkle
yeah they do check it out later on
they're so shiny
[Music]
right
cool I am on my
horse we're out now where do we give
this myse is
amazing the Jade
[Music]
swordy it is sp my horse is better than
your horse a there's no reason for that
my horse why am I always trying to be so
kind my horse my horse my horse horse my
horse is better that's a nice tune yeah
I know
right oh yeah should we rejoin the big
call now maybe oh yeah oh
whoopsies I don't really know how it
works maybe they're not in
call this cell phone is not very useful
you actually it is
useful oh what what's a crony my name's
Tam wait I'm going to I'm going to qu
the call one second bunch of people are
sleeping now but let me we have to turn
our Quest
the
hello well now that we've got a moment
together Bon heads um Kia people
whatever I might call
you I got to say I'm still feeling
really confused about that memory and I
don't know why everybody had to see that
that's really embarrassing having people
see memories that you don't even
remember yourself right
uh
well it is what it is as long as you
guys still accept me for who I am and my
strange Jade eye patch what do you
[Music]
think like everyone seeing your dark
past well some people think it makes me
the good guy but I don't really know
about all of that I think that's
debatable I kind of betrayed my people
but it felt kind of good to do it for
something like music you
know I like the eye patch match with
monkey tutu does my pet monkey tutu have
an eye
patch oh I'll turn in my
quest oh investigate the underworld oh I
had to speak to the Guild Master oh my
gosh I think that we may have all not
realized maybe it was just
me I should thank them for the for the
chance to explore together though if I
get a chance I feel bad just kind of
leaving
everybody I think everyone sounds like
some sort of
chicken I think they are close
friends well I'll quickly run back and
and turn in my quest maybe the others
also quickly realized and ran
back what a journey you know I
wonder if we saw my memories at that
time maybe we'll get to see other
people's memories too
like recollect them together it would
feel a lot more fair if we could see
everybody else's memories as well you
know just
saying anyway Quest
complete oh The jadur Guild Master sorry
that's not where the Guild Master is
that is uh one of his
peons I like riding on on my
Steed so no worries
future dungeons will show other people's
memories you
think the strange bone people in my head
have a point it's very likely whoa
copine have you seen the vision aan yeah
I did does it make you think less of me
no it it makes me feel uh like very very
connected to you really I kind of didn't
want everybody to see one of my own
personal memories but like if it doesn't
make you hate me or anything like that
then I guess it's fine it's very hash
relatable you think so yeah also why is
your St uh sparkling I don't know I
completed the the dungeon and it started
sparkling oh it sparkled after that yeah
a cuz I didn't notice a sparkle before
yeah interesting strange what about your
weapon is it sparkling
too oh yeah it is yeah I didn't notice
that even maybe it gets more sparkly as
we complete dungeons oh oh wonderful
that would be cool I wonder if we'll get
to see your memories too I wonder I'd
certainly like to see them yeah do you
know what you did or
anything I don't remember but it's
coming back to me like step by step
surely little by little right yeah well
I hope we can figure it out together
maybe yes if you want we could also um
check out the next uh dungeon tomorrow
yeah I want to do that
depends on the time that you would be
streaming though oh just the usual every
day the same time which is today really
same as today yeah are you sure I
checked your Google calendar and it
didn't look like that oh was it wrong oh
it looked like you were starting yeah
they had something for me to do oh man
why do I know your schedule better than
you I know right I forgot that thing was
tomorrow well probably 2 hours later
then I'll be doing it but if you want
enter a dungeon with other people that's
fine and we could do a different one A
different day yeah a different one for
sure yeah let's do it yippee yipp take
care bright orange one beautiful one oh
me everyone's so
kind thanks for the quest today I don't
know I actually don't know anything else
past that so oh tender it was very fun
not tender dander dander oh hello tender
you're saying this on purpose there's no
way you're saying
this
call slender tend your name is tender
you just she's harassing me because I
cannot see her difficult name oh those
are my friends they're in my party
though I guess I ought to disband the
party so that you guys can get back with
your Cerulean cupm
mates all right well I'll disband it for
now click to disband yes you are
free you are free of your obligations to
your boy I'm sure that we we'll Brave
another dungeon together someday I hope
so good luck on becoming
Queen not good luck it will happen oh
okay then I look forward to you becoming
Queen yes I don't want to make her mad
she's my friend I I guess but you know I
don't want to make her mad you know you
have any friends that you just really
don't want to make mad because they're
kind of scary you know
uh let's see now where were we supposed
to enter the
arena ah it's
here hey
[Music]
there I did as you instructed sire Brave
hero I am hardened to see that you have
returned unarm unharmed pray tell what
transpired at the ruins um my memories
came back I see to think that the ruins
held such Secrets a crystal deep within
that when touched returned a fragment of
your memories to you memories which in
turn reawaken the power of Revelation
albeit at only a fraction of its
potential that your summoning and
discovery of these ruins should coincide
so closely there must be some connection
between the ruins and the power of
Revelation I really need to fix that
strange curse Brave hero seek rubius The
Guild Master of the Scarlet wand his
guide has also been searching for
strange ruins a guild his Guild has been
searching for strange ruins in the lands
of Libo mayhaps they have discovered
something hopefully the Cerulean members
can get back together oh yeah turn in
your quest yeah oh I need to keep
talking to him I think but I completed
it seruan good old days
eh then speak to the Jade next speak to
the Scarlet wand Guild Master
it's rui in tears what do you mean my
maiden uh-oh back when we all bonded
tell me your location oh boy the drama
continues I wish to go speak to the
Scarlet wand Guild Master and maybe get
ready for oh that my memory uh was
glitching back in for a second that was
very strange Scarlet one should be right
next to the Jade sword Arena so it's
probably close
by that was weird no more of that please
oh this is the oh over
here empathy connects us all wasn't it
apathy maybe it's a little
different
anyhow let us
go oh hi there Scarlet
member I can feel I'm an empath everyone
thinks they're an
empath where is your master
ah oh that hurt me we need to avoid
doing that ever
again oh maybe they're all the way up
there should be a chunky
guy oh yeah this map looks easier to
read rubius should be around
[Music]
here oh rubius is out front I think I
think off I
go pardon my intrusion I'm now
[Music]
leaving I keep walking past him no
there's no way that I'm missing
it yeah out in the
courtyard oh they're all gathered here I
see aren't they cute cute little friends
I hope we can really help them
ah good day to you hero return from
investigating those ruins are you I've
gotten the gist from viridus more or
less yes I now sense within you a trace
of the power of
revelation we leaving you behind
Tam oh no I hope that I can go on
adventures with every single
different person in this
world I'm looking for the Scarlet leader
oh boy I have found them we of the
Scarlet wand have also been
investigating near the plains oh hey
wouldn't you know hey there to Tam who
knows my deepest
memories hope that you're enjoying your
quest yeah so off the coast they found
something yeah talk to the leader
there's some interesting stuff going on
yeah that's fascinating traveling to the
coast they're hard at
work good luck and Excel here o go to
the coast really like saying it's cier
yeah they like saying
that looks like that's the next
location good luck in a
kelsier okay go to the coast where is
the coast I think it'll show on the map
maybe where you need to go
next but probably need to leave from the
main
[Music]
gate H let's see I wonder if I'll end up
meeting anybody at the coast
Jade's sword has good Synergy with other
guilds I'm inclined to
agree I think so as
well perhaps I'll head to the coast and
just see what's going on you
know let see if any friends are at the
coast I'm
lost let's
see
uh-oh maybe this is the cross Crossroads
I'm supposed to go down no that leads to
the
arena maybe there's a different
Crossroads from the arena oh wait I know
where it is I please believe me I know
where I'm
going I definitely know where I'm
going see look here's the main area
found
it maybe it isn't this might not be the
main
area oh hello they're
[Music]
rosarians you all are um followers of
Elizabeth a fellow Jade sword
member yes yes
welcome welcome welcome we're going to
the coast and seeing if any friends are
there get more
oh hello are you the big cat
e hi are you a
how H nice to meet you nice to meet you
I am I am a big cat are you
ambercoin I'm not going to tell you oh I
don't trust no one I see it's because
you that answers my question ambercoin
members think that nobody likes them
because there's been some weird rumors
spread by Cerulean cup is that right
what yeah the weird rumors are that
ambercoin is not very good
how does that make you
feel that's right I think they're right
you think they're right I think they're
right oh you're not a big Amber coin fan
are
you I hate Amber coin okay it seems
everybody hates ambercoin huh all righty
well I I still am not going to hate
ambercoin just because everybody else
hates ambercoin but well I don't eat
Ember coin either because I have my own
opinion yeah see I like you I feel the
same way I feel the same way I'm going
to the coast where are you going I am
going to farm
and I don't know actually I
need hey how dare
youo nice it's gone I saw re
Revelation did I whip Revelation I I
think I'm going I think I'm going to get
some side quest on maybe okay enjoy your
side quests fellow traveler I'm going to
the coast yeah and and remember that
also Amber coins deserve some love some
time I think so too I I am not against
Amber coin just because everyone seems
to be against ambercoin why everyone is
against ambercoin it's it feels like
it's propaganda spread by the Cerulean
cup but I don't know I don't know why
they don't like you so
much assuming you're Amber coin but it's
okay I got you I prefer I prefer to be
open-minded you know I want to be
friends with everyone that's
right well take care fellow
traveler there goes the big cat I wonder
where the coast is aha it's in that
direction we'll need to head this
[Music]
way ask her where the coast is you think
she's been to the coast
oh there's another
traveler I wonder if they're all going
to the coast
[Music]
too it's just a little splash splash in
the water oh hello are they taking a hi
we are dipping we are dipping the
water's cool I feel like I remember your
horse's name but it slips my mind oh do
you maybe from another your horse
another time what letter does it start
with an a uh yeah I think so I think I
feel like there was a strong connection
between you and the horse sadd yeah I
just can't remember the name Adam oh
Saddler get away from the
queen she's remembering she is remember
Adam Sadler she's remembering she did
see her memories
yeah that must be it all right are you
guys ready to go to the coast this is do
you have room for one more
traveler yes yes we do hold on how do I
remove oh be episode be episode I wonder
if there's a sub Quest we must complete
before we might be able to take on this
area's
[Music]
dungeon ow let's see
you mean our our banished member right
banished
member there was a banished
member let me reform our party odd yes
we must reform I must reform okay okay
sounds good take shape to a new form yes
I will accept
curiosity
mumbling I'm just reading
yeah you got to open your mouth when you
speak crony what are you reading sorry
sorry okay no need for the S spicy no
it's okay I get spicy when I make
friends oh spicy spicy yeah the spice
must flow yeah oh I left all my stuff in
a different Barrel well maybe I'll put
it in this corner Barrel too if I'm
allowed yeah I always take the corner
Barrel breathe underwater we believe
this is no M rumor as the Guild Master
was able to find cheex what does it mean
I don't we're going to be able to
breathe under water came into my mind
yeah I think we're going to be able to
breathe under waterer I think oh next is
Atlantis oh
whattis I have did not say that properly
what tantis
aant starts with chtis true ch where you
come from
Tam were you originally from were you
originally a mermaid
Tam maybe that's that's why she's
marrying the king it's like a marriage
of different
countries different species you
meanes different species and countries
lestans and mermaids they are joining
together she's a mermaid can they
reproduce I'm sure they can all right
let's go back to town guys to think
about that if you talk to the uh the
thing we got to go back to town okay
okay Coral shards huh is what we need
where do we get the coral shards is to
gather them and then speak to the Guild
Master do you think back in town yeah we
need 10 yeah where do we get the there
are some Corals in the water nearby I
don't know should we go look wait why
why we try to go to are you are you
leading us to them are you mayhaps
leading us to the coral
you
flying the I thinking that you guys
didn't see where was I see Coral yeah
there is
Rainbow are we collecting it h oh yeah I
got four oh oh yeah these areain I'm
returning I'm
returning yo I can't tell I have how
many I have check your
inventory I did it I need Coral in the
water easy enough yes so
delicious uh-oh yikes big fire I have at
least it's not dead coral yeah s like
the coral is still alive and fresh which
means that the sea is very clean and
healthy we got to go back to r r the one
that knows not us where there's no more
Coral I need more Coral they're too much
of a plean it would seem you can always
go back oh speak to the Scarlet one
Guild Master m
I make haste back towards the kingdom me
too let's go let us ride together W be
Queen yes we run it's just me but Rubi
remind of another hry
up thank you
ter she's fast what's your name
pink hot pink hot pink yeah what's your
name though you could call me hot is it
South you're not
hot wait a minute
excuse me which direction oh no you're
excused
farewell wait wait only
[Music]
rious right the Scarlet one is he not
the Scarlet one he is the Scarlet he's
not rubius though this is good maybe
Iris will know the way oh okay okay Iris
will go my way IR will guide your way
yes she'll guide my way huh
she has we got go here and she is I'm
not
alone yeah literally okay that's crazy
guys know so
crazy oh please oh please let me go
back yo you guys follow you guys
following uh I'm going I'm going to in a
in a minute if I can oh I see it it's
right over there you see
it um it's a path right there's a path
need me to lead you here where are you
no no no there's no you go right ahead
it's a it's a a Sandy path right okay
let's see and then rubius is right over
there there's rubius yeah yeah yeah got
it don't worry about
it you guys don't have to worry about me
I'll find my way I have a map right
she'll find her way are you guys
digging you have to dig in a tunnel dig
in a
grave they're digging a grave
could be I think they're digging a grave
heck yeah yeah I
think where's this grave
diggers our next task would be to
explore but I think our path is blocked
you're digging me yeah it feels like
maybe I don't know am I am hot per if we
give enough time the path will open on
its own the path will open on its own
eventually hot pink yes what
Fair the well yes Fair the well goodbye
goodbye goodbye lovely lovely gorgeous
ladies oh I guess this means that we
magic chicken disappear oh disapp oh
wait I didn't disappear right away oh
shoot I was I was planning on
disappearing okay exelia he's really
silly exelia
Exel they're all okay where's
the there we go right where where I do
something that calls my
name what calls your name it calls to me
a small blue
box a small blue box small blue box
what's the special we're not talking
about the manga right oh wait no no no
what's a manga what is blue what what is
a manga is that how you pronounce it I
don't think that's true I do not know
I've never seen one before for you're
right how pronounce mang blue I have no
room I guess I I can get finished oh
what did he
do rainbow Coral cluster an object only
red how do I use this waste bin oh I
know we become
mermaids oh yeah just like
Tam of course just like Tam
just like the temple she need this item
to begin with like can we
farm
farm we can Farm yeah I think that's
what the shovel is for growing things
yeah we can build at our Guild base oh
yeah oh yeah build a small Guild House
yeah
and some do some farming some wheat so
we can not have to pay gold to make
bread right can we can we should do that
we should make our own economy is
g g we can have like a guil chest
someone is calling me GG I am Jonathan G
Jonathan gathan I thought you were a
good game yes gathan what what is good
game one second I dro the telepathic
call it's going to drop it someone
else oh it's
gone no telepathy the call why did
gathan do that oh
well po shame it's been fun though it
has been fun I hope that we our paths
cross I want our paths to cross again
path our paths will cross as long as the
Stars alive yeah I think so too well
[Music]
peace they were
cool I liked them did I really make a
friend did I make a bunch of friends
make your own kingdom
yeah with the with my strength as one of
the Jade sword I will have my own
kingdom
someday you'll
[Music]
see or maybe not maybe I'll just explore
a bunch of places with
friends that could be fun too hey you
know what I'd love though my own bed
wouldn't that be
nice whoa
[Music]
Dismount grinding
materials seems like something I could
definitely
do you know like trees you think that
they would get mad if I cut tree well no
I'll go
outside we ought to go to the
outerlands the outer
lands and cut some trees mayhaps show
seems like a good hey look there's my
house yeah cuz I got to be able to build
my own home
right just make sure it's not a
Christmas tree why does why do you guys
keep saying that I feel like I now I
have some kind of bad past with
Christmas
trees I get the feeling that there's
some other members who will also be a
bit occupied until a tad bit later
tomorrow tomorrow maybe I can explore
the Dungeon with them if they'll have me
I think that would be nice if it was
possible oh it's the rock oh it's it's
the dad dad why does everyone keep
saying that I don't know you just have
that presence on you surely they'd
remember me for my strength and being
afraid of me my courage I don't feel I
don't feel afraid of you really even
though I'm the Grim Reaper oh you're a
grim reaper yeah I killed people well I
did that's cool I can you teach me how
to kill people oh I mean it's kind of
something that's it's not an open job
for just anyone you know it's otherwise
it's illegal in your world to do those
things unless it's the enemy let's here
look you want to learn how to kill yes
do
this come kill bad guys you jump in the
air you jump and you time your sword
swing so you can't spam it
can't you can't spam it okay yeah you
can't it's time to swing Revelation oh
it's got a bit of distance on it huh
Revelation yeah and then use your
special move cool oh Bow
Bow Bow Bow I have a bow bow on the
phone oh oh you should go to your people
oh yeah I know them they're in my guild
actually I I was I was trying to help
you bow bow oh me where oh where where
where are you I think she's talking to
them she's talking to my
friends a would you like to perhaps
meet yum
yum what is the third person Scythe
attack look like I'm definitely curious
I'm sure you'd be able to see from
someone though time for
steak yes I no you will be Stak for
me yum ah
surely I'll be able to save up a bunch
of coins to
get some good food in the
[Music]
like grinding materials grinding
materials oh that's her name oh yeah
that's her name
hello Fair n
Nina the stars have aligned already oh
are you co again oh can we do that
dungeon I think I don't think so but we
can maybe get ready to do it at least
sure sounds good to me I'll go all right
let's us ride let's ride ride okay Ride
Like the
[Music]
Wind wow I already have such a cool
team I feel
blessed he's in Friendship
beautiful off we
ride our colors match very well too I
just
realized I do
what I don't know what that means but it
must be something amazing oh wait o and
we can cook I mean I can cook
investigate speak to the I can stained
meat it actually yummy where is this
ocean
Temple did I put all my stuff Temple is
somewhere far out in the ocean and you
know we have this rainbow Coral cluster
so I think we can bre wait where where's
my rainbow Coral cluster oh yeah we
can yo I can breathe underwater let's
swim that's hey me too
did you find your Rainbow Coral cluster
I'm sinking inventory sinking Like a
Rock was my inventory
[Music]
full if you cleared the quest like the
they the rudus gives you one yeah but
put your my inventory was full oh no
this is a rainbow Coral Shard which was
used to make the thing do not
hunger ena's a coral rainbow Coral uh
cluster is missing oh check my check my
magical
book ah there it is where where was it
in your was it in it was in the magical
TB of greatness oh
okay thank God thank you yeah oh I can
breathe underwater now brilliant wow
you're a really good swimmer too I just
sink right to the
bottom that was a shut up shut up uhoh I
hate these so cold tamies or cronies
whatever it is I'm so sick of them oh no
be careful I don't think that the Bone
Heads are all that bad CIA
people they're a little silly sometimes
and I have to Bonk them but it is what
it
is sinking like a boo oh is that it
oh did you find it to the to the thing
on the map what's that that looks like
numbers arrow symbol okay we go down
like there's a thing on the map that
we're aiming for it's the dungeon I
think the Red Dot on the map these look
like
dice H what does it mean hold on guys I
got
to it's really dark in here I got to do
what I got to do what's
that what do you got to do oh
mine don't tell me I can't get these no
I do you have the right pickaxe
wow there is a lot of good stuff here
though I will
[Music]
say I was hoping she'd be able to mine
them oh she's finally joined Atlantis
must be down here
right looks like we can't enter
[Music]
maybe we
can you think it's through
here like a wall of water oh
hey you guys found it
she kept calling me Tam tenders for no
reason that is a strange thing and I I
do wonder why they did that yeah that's
not
very C tenders yeah slender and
tender what a weird thing oh yeah that
is pretty evil that's a pretty
evil why is your cape I bet why is your
cape that color that's strange
it's all
dark hey you know if we can enter
probably not
[Music]
huh
time it looks like we still can enter it
but oh join the party call
true whoopsies hi sorry I'm here
hell I knew you were going to say that
dungeon is still
dormant oh is that what it says when you
try to
enter yes it is dormant it is sleeping
enter just yet Perhaps tomorrow maybe we
need some sleep yeah yeah I think it's
about time I need to I need to get some
sleep me too yeah I need my sleep get
some Shi let's meet again let us meet
again R Vu when time opens opens up a
new gate towards the next when the gate
opens let us meet again I will be
waiting thean The seruan Guild Masters
will make us assemble right this
Cerulean assemble right I will send a
carrier pigeon and letting you guys know
with my pigeon you're a love you you
have a lovely carrier pigeon by the way
you thank you that's really cool yes I
will send a pigeon to your inboxes and
they will leave note to you let we have
in boxes you mean you mean our mailboxes
right yes yes your your
mailboxes I will car
pigeons yes yes
mhm I will send
note do not be frightened thank you well
have a great one
everyone take care take care everyone
farewell
fwell goodbye tomorrow tomorrow
I love you love you
Tom Str how do we all know this song
very weird I don't know did we come from
the same world that's crazy I hope not
maybe we oh why
not why do you hope
not has her problems Tam has her
problem is that really her name see you
tomorrow yes her name is Tam I Nam her
you say so hey don't put it like
that hey I don't like I don't like the
sound of
that I she allowed me to a suggestion
farewell goodest of buys what a silly
thing to say why did I choose to say
that although I guess it's kind of
endearing a little bit goodest of buys
this has been your
boy it maybe
I don't know oh yeah we got to go here
um I will
oh
yeah I'll head back
home well I had a really fun time
exploring this brand new world with you
guys I'm kind of curious though about
everybody else's memories you know it
was kind of like eh why are we looking
at my memories but
maybe other people also have their own
secrets to spill that's what I want to
see is other people's memories I don't
want to reveal mine to other people
that's
embarrassing but it seems
like
oh it seems like you know people are
pretty accepting even after seeing my
past I hope that the dogs those those
twins right I hope that they will also
be
accepting when they
see maybe it'll make them like me
more aren't there side quests there sure
are I'll definitely be doing some of
those tomorrow I
bet I wish we had our own rooms here
though that would be
nice feel like we have to build our own
though build my own house
huh get more coin
doing some solo side quest does sound
fun
though I would like
to as long as they don't mistake dead
beats for chew
toys you can now be the edgy loner
character yay I
mean
huh oh
well what is a dead beat a miserable
little pile of bones but this was really
fun I had a good time
private call I think this is everybody
who's on right now Big
Stretch CIA people how about
you well I guess if that's how it's
going to go I'm going to read these
strange messages that were being sent to
me oh what is
[Music]
this PR PR
odd I'm going going to read these
messages that you've sent to me these uh
super
chats what's so super about
them truly what is so super about them I
don't
understand it's been a fun I'm glad
you've had a fun
time isn't this a collab not to be read
does it really count as a collab I feel
like it's a bit unfair if I didn't
say so I'll go ahead and read them it
shouldn't take too long
anyway but I probably won't have them on
for future en recollection
streams just so you know I will probably
turn them off for future
ones yeah it is true that there are a
bunch of people there but I'll go ahead
and read them quickly should be
fine you can just have them no it's okay
I'd rather keep them off just just for
me just for my own
I just I don't want to have them on
light adventuring
magical there we go farewell and see you
tomorrow ah yes tomorrow I'm sure we'll
go adventuring again we've got a big
thank you to lumy and thank you to Kirby
Super Fan poo C ikuzo for Ian
recollection Minecraft RP
Minecraft I thought it it was the land
of
Mojang there's been a lot of ambitious
projects for y'all lately and I'm super
excited what a time to be a Holo Ian fan
have fun exploring this new world and
recollecting your memories with your
friends thank you very much to V faction
19 Holo live streamers
19 why does this fill me with anxiety
when I read this 19 long enigmatic
recollection
streams wanting to be
watched 19 girls wanting to collab
I think I'll move on from this one
because it makes me feel weird thank you
to jprs NSR much appreciation thank you
to G Harden and lur nut thank you lur
sounds nice Bastion 0589 thank you and
donger bread thank you do not eat the
yellow snow it does not taste like
lemonade not even like a a yellow snow
cone okay thank you to Jesus Vera time
for RPG first find the lost cat then
your party can find God fight God in the
last dungeon sounds about right for
something like an RPG but I've seen no
cats yet a big UPS to Michael C thank
you so much at a big UPS to Road Forks
you watch out for the truck truck I
don't recall seeing a truck thank you to
Trav the Hedgehog 7 appreciate it thank
you so much and a big UPS to Brutus
salad thank you and of Big Ups Too jprs
NSR R she died let's
go thank thank you so much too fky fky
supas let's go I'm also very excited to
see how this story goes thank you to
Handy fire it all begins here Mory got
isai thank you so much too GM whoa why
did my voice boom out like that that was
crazy it looks like there's a dancing
little bone man thank you so much I
really appreciate it thank you oh Big
Ups Too our boy shrugging
Emoji for the the
red cool
oh it's pronounced Jim gotcha thank you
Jim and thank you to our boy shrugging
Emoji what a nice Emoji to put next to
your name no way you started this with
the truck [\h__\h] hahhaa brilliant don't
really know what you're referencing here
but trucks are scary watch
out know they can hurt you if you're not
looking where you're
walking big scary bulky things iron
monsters even better at doing my job
than I am to be honest thank you though
thank you to wrench mol you're supposed
to say te te te why would I say that
that sounds lame thank you to Marcus
Maness s appreciate it thank you very
much to Mighty Bri guy for the five
gifted memberships and Nick Brown thank
you don't fear the voices they're your
friends thank you to B Bash and vampiric
otaku sker times too mommy where are you
we are ever so hungry oh my monkeys I'll
have to go feed them thank you to fky
fky you're a hero to me Mighty Bri guy
again thank you for the five gifts thank
you to The Rocker Reaper yeat him what
ises he eat when I think of eat I think
of throwing a basketball oh what a
strange word maybe a magic spell
speaking of spells sauntering
spellcaster thank you and thank you very
much to Jacob langlet thank you to Metal
Gear flaccid that's odd be faction thank
you skers thank you Michael corck thank
you so much I appreciate it it is
written only C can defeat Ganon thank
you so much to scottan Empire Big Ups
time to accept your quest
Adventurer thank you very much to
Klondike Saloon and thank you to Marcus
manes as well as Caesar T Tarango thank
you thank you a big UPS to Aunt bunie
18K congrats on clearing the underworld
dungeon C we did learn a lot more things
about me huh maybe it's better to get my
memories out of the way first though
because imagine that we watch other
people's memories right their own
enigmatic Recollections and it turns out
that they were not very good people and
they already made friends with everyone
wouldn't that be the ultimate betrayal
but everybody knows my secret from the
beginning right nothing left to hide
everyone's going to start getting so
nervous as we go
along
well I'll try to still remain friends
with everyone regardless of their pasts
unless they you know were trying to take
my job for me or something like that
they're probably all right or minor
miscreant that seems more likely than
not do you think anyone here might have
an evil
backstory maybe that good game
one go gathan or something like that
yeah very aggressive a big UPS to jprs
NSR looking forward to more and thank
you very much to Nan the whoa what a
strong word they say yo yo that feels
nice to say Danny the gunsmith says say
love you Mor thank you Danny appreciate
it yon young thank you for that sticker
Sombra P thank you n of thank you fun
time Marcus mines says thanks a lot this
is a chat but it's super GG for today
reap nice role plan role
plan yeah that was fun a big UPS to
Mouse
Fam thank you for the red message what a
lovely brick getting my super special
edition enigmatic recollection Super
Chat there it is there it
goes thank you for adding it to my
inventory I really appreciate it and
thank you for being a kayia person thank
you to deadbeat
508 why is that your name that sounds
like a way better name for a group of
bonee
heads dang it maybe next time thank you
for the wonderful and fun stream cie
looking forward to seeing what comes
next in this exciting project a big UPS
too
no renzel thank you so much interested
in the story of a rogue Reaper maybe
there's Rogue beats somewhere Rogue
Reaper going rogue but I would like to
make more friends for sure thank you
very much to prinny's role see you on
tomorrow Fair Lady see you on the
tomorrow bonee head I mean CIA
person truly I really appreciate it um
with that being all said and
done thank you very much to
Cherry have a good one thank you for the
two days of the concert you are amazing
thank you so much really appreciate
it thank you thank you I guess that's
about it
huh with all that being said and done I
am
cie it would be cool if you could
recollect me it would be cool if you
could recollect my
existence it would be cool if you could
recall my existence thank you so much
and a last minute Big Ups to thank you
big
UPS that's new crayon Canon why thank
you and Arnold FZ thank
you is a different C playing monkey game
fingers crossed if if they seem to get
the okay to do so we'll see you around
somewhere
goodbye fairly well
[Music]
e