[Music]
feel it R
me
intoxicating DJ keep playing
[Music]
and
dancing so emotion
[Music]
it R me
feel it R me
feel it like through me
[Music]
oh
honey night is
[Music]
feel it right through
me me
[Music]
intoxicating DJ keep
playing OT
[Music]
baby me
feel it rush through me
[Music]
R it me
what
H uh wait there's something weird do you
hear something when I'm not
talking is there do you hear
music is it the
game you hear bgm wait wa who who
[Music]
who it's coming I see an OBS that's
coming from my microphone that's so
weird why is it doing
that um
[Music]
anyway and I don't even hear it going
here oh maybe it's because cuz I'm not
tapped in but then why you
no K did I say that already K
hello something's
weird
uh
oh ah there it is I found the
music I found it at least
oh ahuh
changes it for you too why is it going
through there I have no idea but we'll
have to accept
it uh how are you doing boss I have a
bit of a headache right
now I think it's maybe from actually
from coming from my shoulder
actually um I feel
like something's something's pulling
pulling uh strings I don't know weird
way to say that to use that but uh
yeah um maybe it will go away yeah I
think
[Laughter]
I'm uh let me put this behind
Okay like a pulled muscle no I don't
think I pulled a muscle is just um
something like you know from sleeping
weird
probably try roting rotating your
shoulder and giving it a stretch are you
like a physical therapist or
something giving it a stretch behind you
all right all right I I mean honestly I
should really just be stretching every
[\h__\h] day at this point I'm an old
lady wait a
second [\h__\h]
off stretch just a good music to stretch
to yeah shut up I'm hearing so many
windows noises you don't hear it let me
let me make it Audible for
you
wait now it's ah there it
is shut up shut
up shut up shut up I'm not doing
anything I'm not doing anything I hate
this
shut
up shut
up shut up shut up it's been doing this
all day all
day shut up shut up I don't know where
it's coming
from maybe
okay you good you good you good computer
Chan we good maybe we're good
now I
think I don't know I don't even know I
don't know anymore
man it's
[Music]
okay stupid technical things I hate
things
we need a fresh install of Windows
yeah I I think that and I think many
other
things like I should do this I should I
should do this I should do that and
well I just don't do
anything
um okay we're going to play batro for
the first time ever
today uh I haven't ever played it before
but I've seen I've seen it it seems to
be very popular and well loved and well
known saw that other Holo girls played
it before too I
think which is
nice oh wait a second where am
I oh
here but I was kind of worried about not
knowing
any anything about cards and you guys
said it will be
fine so I hope that is
true now toata I'm waiting for my
download folder to load because it
always takes 5 minutes to load even
though I cleaned it
up it's
insane it is true okay okay you will
learn fast okay there's a tutor okay but
somebody said something on Twitter that
made so much sense like if if this game
needed you to know how to play poker
then it wouldn't be so popular that made
sense but I feel like everybody knows
how to play poker except me is what I
feel why does everybody know how to play
poker man why why why how how do you
know how do you know oh my God can you
load any slow and then there like
everything shows up except the one that
I need everything shows up early except
the one thing that I need I I I love it
this [\h__\h] hates me wait where did it
go what okay never mind it was never in
the download folder to begin with what
I'm looking for it was in my fan art
folder here I just wanted to put the
logo up otherwise it's kind of empty
down
there hey you don't know how to play
poker do you guys know how to play poker
wow a wild
card Wild Card good
song I'm horrible at poker no no no yes
yes no yeah poker is
easy it's
fun no no yeah okay it's like
mixed not the real version what's the
real version and what's the version that
you
know I learn and then forget the next
day
what is it not like riding a
bicycle I too do not know you can get
witch yeah I saw I saw it gave me the
option to do Witcher cards but I saw in
the Nintendo Direct they also have like
Dave the diver but it's not showing me
Dave the diver do I have to get the
switch version of this game if I want to
get the Dave the diver cards because I
love Dave the
diver but it shows me Witcher inant
options I only see uh
here The Witcher default The Witcher
default oh or is it
like
oh oh wait I thought you need all of
these in the deck
anyway oh okay but so we can have Wier
for
Spades do I end up using spad heart
club's diamonds like all of it or do I
only get one of them
it only changes those ah okay all of the
I use okay okay okay okay so amus I
guess why
not vampire survivors ah interesting how
all these games are familiar to me like
but vampire Survivor is only familiar to
me because of Holo kir but still they
they chose all the things that I know
dve the
DI which is so fun because it's also a
pixel Gam so this literally looks like
straight out of the game I love it shut
up shut up no was talking to you
Windows
hello shut up please shut
up what's high contract
oh oh this just makes everything
oh okay I see makes the the yeah okay
well it makes it hard to
contrast I don't I don't know what it is
that's why I can't switch USB ports I
don't even think it's necessarily
anything at
all it's just my computer being
weird Okay so yeah we're not even going
to use the original cards we're just
going to use these because that's
fun okay shut up
um I hope the music is loud enough for
you guys because if I make it any louder
today my settings are kind of weird um
I'll I'll be blasting out my own ears oh
my
God Windows is pretty loud though isn't
it I can turn down the window sounds but
I want you to suffer with
me oh my God shut up this can't be
real um okay you not hey hey
hey
mhm me restarting my PC would solve all
my problems I'm pretty
sure what is it Anyway like what what
what what what do you want what do you
want from
me what do you want
what is it that you so
desire what is
[Music]
it okay what do you think Windows did
that feel
good are you happy now will you shut up
now will you stop trying to have a
conversation with me
now we'll
see we'll see H so if I press play will
it give me the tutorial or do I have to
go so well
probably okay please teach me let's go
batro this whole time I thought it's
balastro or something like that and I
thought people were misspelling it or
so uh somehow I'm trying to auto correct
it I don't know
why read as B batro not balatro oh batro
is that a word for from some language
Bal B balatro balatro
bat bat it's Latin Latin like old
language
Latin balat
balatro Latin for Joker
oh
interesting nobody knows how it's
pronounced oh that's that's the thing
that narissa would
say Okay H hello there my name is Jim
I'm here to help you learn how to
play your goal is to earn tips to defeat
the enemy blind what does that mean
blind what does that
mean this here is a small blind you only
need to score 300 chips to beat
it you like my creepy voice eh why you
give him that voice because he looks
looks creepy
he looks like he might talk like this to
me also he's probably ripping me
off why so
serious wait so blind means forced bet
okay then what does that
mean see I'm I'm worried about me
playing this game when this here is a
small bad you only need to score
friendships to beat it uh okay sure oh
man I'm already not listening anymore
it's already many too
much uh uh think chips is points okay um
hey did you hear that or was that in my
head it'll be fine okay it's a score
Target blind is around with a score you
need to
beat you'll get the hang of it instantly
okay
um select the small bind to start the
round
how
okay wow pretty cards you earn tips by
playing poker
hands it's poker hand earns a base
amount of chips multiplied by some maltt
malt like multiplier I'm being framed
whoa whoa whoa why who why
you're also in my head oh no uh it's
earns Bas earns a base amount of chips
multiplied by some Mt okay you're just
saying that whatever hand I have it will
always earn me at least some sort of
money
um how well
whatever see your poker hands in the Run
info area along with other info about
your current run
uh my poker see my poker hands in the
Run info
area okay sorry my brain is like not
working right now I have to read
everything three
times let me drink some
Coca-Cola
hey what oh
oh so I do not have to remember this
[Laughter]
right
blinds what does that mean again I don't
know big blinds score at least
450 okay wait okay a straight flush is
five cards in a row with all all cards
sharing the same
suit uh you mean the the ass here like
the ace
right all right that's a no that's a
peak wait what's Ace again what's Ace
again no is this peak what I I mean I
mean what Pike Peak Spade what what's
what I'm
confused uh the what the club
the Clover is uh what's the
Clover where is it Clover wait I don't
know English
anymore the club okay
clever
Club okay uh all right all
[Music]
right I'm not okay help me
are we back we are back baby oh no no no
not the not the windows noise
again hello
hello I I got like a not really like a
oopsie not like a blue screen blue
screen but like a like the my middle
screen became blue and it said like
Windows or something like that uh in
Japanese yeah because my system is
Japanese for some reason it said uh yeah
there's there has been a problem found
we have to it's BS o d oh what was
that no it's not an update it's not an
update it's like we have a problem we
need to sh shut down immediately I guess
that's like a modern Windows 10 11 blue
screen blue screen of death oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] that sounds so
dramatic is that the like professional
official name for
that
yummy okay [\h__\h] yeah
tearing PC down do what I
wna keep calling me a got my cables
[Laughter]
Twisted I don't know I think it won't
happen
anymore I I I I I expected too much of
my
PC I
apologize yeah
I think it's because like sometimes okay
so I I start my
PC
uh yeah okay I you hear that good uh I
start my PC and then like I do something
and then I leave it
[Music]
and and then and then it goes you know
into like sleepy
mode and then I come back and usually
when I do something like streaming after
it's been in Sleepy mode without
restarting it it will be a little bit
funky um yeah B I'm CED
[Music]
today
e
e e
[Music]
n