[Music]
for
there Mor I'm
Mor everybody's
everybody's
o o we've got we've gathered the whole
crew
everyone's here
[Music]
assembled except oh wait are we this
wait can we hear everybody is there a
mic check can we get a mic check in
the che H might be a good
idea yeah no g g we can't I can't hear
GAA can you guys hear
G I Can't oh you can't hear gur cuz oh
that's cuz oh right okay I see that
sense yeah um I don't know how
to even though you watch for
her it's fine guys just everybody in the
chat go watch somebody else's POV I'm
sitting out the first round so so so I
can't hear gooda but I'm haunting
her oh wait what if uh what if you watch
gura but also watch my Discord as well
does that work I good
but will you get double audio I'm not
too sure yeah maybe like triple audio
don't worry about it I'll figure it out
you guys you know you're going to get
fired you know you have to make we can
we can also use Discord audio but I
guess I don't know when someone dies is
coming to kill
us is a lot funner but that's okay it's
just something that we're going to have
to deal with I guess because you I know
a lot of people have been mentioning
mods we can't use those we can't uh uh
no no Mod's allowed yeah it's not
allowed it's it's not allowed guys so
we're going to do what we can with what
we have that's what we've always done
that's what we'll keep doing
[Music]
dance it's not the
same surely we can afford one too right
well our we did just begin this journey
the quota is pretty small the first day
just got we find the accessing terminal
enter favorite animal going be our
obviously describe your role in a team
operation thingy there a lot of
buttons this
is help help
moons
experimentation EX exper can
find it's so clicky I you like half the
system so it'll like pay
us that's above my bay grade the auto we
are orbiting the moon oh which moon Mo
there are multiple ah we your moon
experimentation experimentation
okay let's go you want to see my we just
we just
go me I guess crank it captain
CR that bu who's the
captain be
Captain the captain yes you are you have
been selected as
Captain big difference but you know what
that's fine ladies I can leave the
charge here i' play only one who hasn't
played the game
yet lead the way you hav't play yet is G
the only one who didn't play yet or have
you played before consumed the content
but I've not played the game all
right
employee I no we just we just go and
take stuff scraps yeah main entrance is
Right dead ahead ladies just find a
ladder no no please no we the game bees
avoid the bees you have to spin in a
circle three times okay is that a real
thing or you just P my leg SP four three
it's real look the chat says it's real
right right guys chat said it's real hey
Chad I know what you're trying to do it
worked for G it worked for her look it
did work I'm
Invincible there's
over like a
li
cently Echo what do you mean
no it's it's like Five Nights at
Freddy's if you're on the ship and
looking at the cameras exactly oh um we
have nothing we have no flashlights just
find metal things and get out of here
okay only oh I found something it is
brave I'm going to
recycle I leave it
here oh we here am still by the way
because am is currently sharing her
audio over
Discord going to bring this over
directly
more jumping cuz she's uh she's watching
I think G's stream right now Discord
stream why is this pumpkin
here and yeah we're going to have
everybody sit out like once or twice
anybody can hear how does this work
again how do I drop it
[Music]
g guys I might I can't hear you by the
way nobody can hear you I might not be
super energetic today forgive me um I
don't
know but I am
here let's
go it's not modded we don't have a mod
CU we don't have perms wait the entrance
was
here wonder if someone's dead already oh
you got to right click go to right click
that's how you scan stuff you can see
stuff in the dark it'll show you the
value of items
nice she's back seating her let's
go very good to have am as a
joker I am back
in who whoa whoa what the
[\h__\h] is this the way out I don't know
where don't really remember where we
came from I think this is it I feel it
this place pretty big for like a first
area yeah wait where's more wait being
here okay we're fine where's the exit hi
is that the exit found it nice
nice I got headphones
on oh shark I got boom did you find
something hello no
no I found
you can I hear her are those footsteps
are those your
footsteps I don't want headphones
anymore what the [\h__\h]
me it okay
that's footsteps are those someone's got
big meaty claws oh there's something
over I'm scared it's coming it's coming
oh my God wait don't jump five times
that's how youo it uh what I don't know
where I
am uhoh where's the exit
[\h__\h] all okay I wouldn't mind dying
now nobody can hear you you're ghost
help
me did you jump five times in a row
that's how you get away from
one I told
[Music]
you wait okay I'm alive I feel almost
dead I'm just going to pray this I'm
like kind of like I see a blurry vision
yeah cuz we were we were hit oh we
survived
Ina I think GAA died at what cost GAA
was e
eaten consumed just
careful got be careful I can I can
totally hear you good oh nice yeah hello
Good's
dead ah how that
happened well monsters did you witness
it
footsteps and then death I mean I
definitely wasn't there you know I don't
know if you no but I'm a big old
deserter only got one item I brought the
I brought the bottles we got three yeah
we got three oh
nice kind of hurt yeah it's fine we're
not going in anymore are we are we are
we are we are we I mean unless you
anything else right someone should stay
behind regardless that's true it's three
clock a button is stuck I mean I don't
know if there was anything else any
other room yeah I didn't see anything it
was hard to see um hold on there we go
fixed get the bees oh Callie do you want
to get the bees
cie bees the be but you got to be fast
yeah you got to be FAS ask me if I want
to get them
yeah how do you get
get go get the be they're worth a lot
hold on we are
up on here hold on a sec grab it and
run can you Callie so I can watch don't
die though don't
youed penalty pressure's on huh God
speed I can scan
maybe anyone know where it is on the way
there right yeah on the way it's on the
way well you doofuses are going to tell
me to go grab the hive and not tell me
where it is oh I can see it from here to
your right yeah it's like wait I'll lead
you it's over here I'm basically Zoro
please you have to help this way yeah
good luck I see I think I oh oh there
they are
run wait did you grab it did you grab it
I don't know how somebody needs to
distract them you have to get pretty
close and press e you guys want me to be
no get a your
timeout oh oh she's gonna die she's
probably going to die
um she's uh she I think she she's
sparkling yeah she's probably um not so
alive I see her corpse I see her corpse
oh you might can you bring her a corpse
back what what she's worth $5 five yeah
but her body is so close to the
bees you could retrieve it you know was
your idea I'll give it a try okay it's
kind of it's kind of getting
late
I'm watching
you if you die don't die too far away H
Too Close
ah H what are you guys doing I I think
she
died
[\h__\h] well she she uh I could probably
get we don't need the
be oh wait why is it spooky why is it
spooky I retrieved one
body
wait that's not my home wa where's my
where's my
ship wait where's my ship I
[Laughter]
here there you go Kiara thank you that's
one body do I still have time bring
another body nah no n why am I alone how
do I even get this I'm at here you tell
me how do I how do I P the lever P the
[Music]
lever
y well the bees had to be
abandoned but it's okay it's fine at
least I have who is
this I can't see the name it's just a
body
now I
survived Kara most paranoid makes a lot
of
excuse me at least I survived 28 yeah
thanks for trying
to
dying oh we pretty much reached the
quota we just need like one more metal
scrap so let's try and save up to get to
this far away moons ladies okay honestly
we can sell like the clipboard and stuff
apparently it's worth something if
you're desperate but I think we can
definitely be
over over the the quota you know some
employee of the month
wait who here is anybody here part-time
or is everybody intern unpaid intern how
do I see do interns get
paid no um your intern you want to do
someon shopping for us G to
March who's
intern please enjoy your flight I don't
know do you think we shovels or
flashlights I'm a parttime warrior yeah
but what we can order flashlight no
there's lots of stuff if you go to the
computer and type in shop yeah
flashlights would be good you all right
I got this leave it to
me stop one shovel confirm we have to go
grab
it store and then we'll do
flashlight have like a little bit of
money oh I should do flash lights and
then a certain number okay store um
let's see Bo box I don't think we can
afford anything
else how many flashlights just one baby
single flashlight in a dream we can get
though and like a transporter and stuff
like that shall we go pick all
right land in the
ship
we where are we going where are we
arriving we're in March I believe we go
to the right we're in March is it h Fest
time already let's go true oh no time F
to fast wait guys it's a CL watch out
what what a c yeah look for the
bridge what there should be a bridge
someone almost went off the edge I saw
that was pretty funny don't jump into
the
water yeah I know you'll die for sure we
neither we need it
I'll be right there to
you all right check
it all right ladies there goes GAA
somebody needs to hold her hand we need
to put a leash on her where did she
go ice cream cream hi guys I immediately
hear
footsteps yeah I heard I heard it yeah I
heard it I yeah maybe maybe different ex
maybe a different enter entrance is
better no I mean the stuff we ordered is
uh
oh didn't pick it up oh we can is it
just us what happened to what we forgot
about
it yeah
oh oops that's my
bad just got a little
excited oh man let's see if it's safe
now
oh is
[Music]
she whoa whoa whoa are you good maybe
there's a different entrance we can use
yeah yeah let's go somewhere else uh um
what did you find where are the
others you guys forgot
to know someone's going to
help I thought you were for
real was bait time I recommend Ena be
bait this
time she come
out hey you want to go in there girl oh
oh wait where do you have the things
from did you pick it up from the
delivery wait was in there oh from the
the present there's a present in the
front room are you
[Music]
sure well I got a
shovel I have one piece of metal that at
least we piece of metal we can bring
back to the ship bring that back now
someone's got to be bait and it might
have to be me oh she's not coming out
that's what got me last time hit it hit
it the
shovel hit it hit
it I I go with you
prey we shall play with
it we shall go all in different
directions we should go all in different
directions and then you know make it
[Applause]
choose let's go let's go let's
go inter oh there's nothing
here I think can get through the door if
you guys just close the door can we trap
him in here close the door he can't open
the door he has arms he there's nothing
the other way there's no door no time
for baby C yeah we can lead him into the
other room right I'll have him follow me
and you guys look for
scrap who's got the flashlight I do
where I
go I'm alive wait I'm alive what again
again it
literally took a big bite out of my
ass what
oh no I'm alive right you got it I'll
actually bring this back now uhoh I
think GAA hit her by accident oh GAA hit
me nah I think it was the monster I it
can't hear me but I think it was the
monster is that my
ship main entrance main entrance why
don't we just go over
there yeah the monster was literally in
my face so going to kill
it
amazing double kill double I'm I'm the
double I'm the
multiplicator where's Ena is Ena Alive
You Killed Ena
too well I mean you got to cleanse the
world from the from the evil so
sometimes it takes the good with it I
don't
know so you know it is what it is
sometimes sacrifices have to be made
where was this main entrance that I
saw I don't know if we if I want to
still
go this
is I came from
there ship I think it was a big area I
think good is lost don't touch me bees
don't touch
me holy what are the odds still 9 hours
I saw like when I was scanning in that
direction I think does it do anything
like does it fake
swim something what the
[\h__\h] there
there don't disappear don't
disappear it
disappeared stay in the ship it's kind
of like
M are they still like in the area the
other
girls well I guess now it's safe to
go okay I at least picked up one thing
I'm so proud by the way Nissa is in my
place she already showered in my place
and we cuddled with my cats on my
bed yeah I
contributed and later she's going to use
use my PC to do
her outfit
[Music]
reveal she
dead she hear
that I don't know
actually that the be no I think that's
just mosquitoes like punishment oh hello
not oh dead body let's go
come in wait is that ena's body is this
ena's body well it's not mine did you
think it was mine I thought this was you
I was SC whole time no no well I I was
bitten by the monster but I quickly run
away and survived
somehow ni my a button's a little stuck
again every time I go to the ship it
ends up that way anyway I got the kettle
welcome were great really did do the uh
switch of Maru then sorry en rest in
peace look I found a fishal b let's go
tungsten fish that's a heavy boy oh
plastic still got value we're killing it
exit time yeah let's
go everyone keep your hands and feet on
the ride what if
I no no no no no no no no wait I really
think
oh yeah yeah better be inside when the
door
closes OH Close Call I sustained the
most injuries I think Ena sustained the
most injuries cuz she
died she's Lazi can you be sustaining
injuries I
can't shk looking
monster said I'm a
part rank up part-timer now yeah I'm a
part-timer what does that do me being
part
it just I means you take the most risks
in the next
Expedition I don't know about that the
group I don't know can't do anything
until we sell all right uh let's see
access the terminal all right
Mo yeah
see vow let's go to vow
vow yeah wow free vow with the V or vow
with the yeah with the V what other bow
read this sound like I said Bow Bow Bow
Bow Bow Bow don't think anybody said
that bow let's go I'm just trying to
entertain myself cuz I know I'm going to
be interned forever and I'm just
entertain
why why are you why are you intern
forever oh wait we have flashlights
turning off the lights you think you're
being it's it's my second shift I've
seen many many other other same
employees of the same group um they they
got promoted
and has
level you know we got to
go it's all right Ena you can prove
yourself now yeah sure surely this is
the day all right do we have like any
more any new stuff was anything ordered
oh did we buy stuff no not this time
okay where is I'm pretty sure this one
is either straight forward or to the
right okay kind of forget see a
bird bird oh I don't think you'll H us
thankfully let's try going to the right
oh there's the bridge oh good is running
off into the unknown good running off
into the
unknown she find way G do not not sing
the song po Marco Polo again I had this
stare at you before scream scream we're
getting L
now all right well girl can use either
Bridge maybe I bet she'll find
it we found the entrance nice oh I'm not
a
dummy oh it looks the same
oh he jumped is there fall damage in
this game not really um kind of Chad
says there is
ien can't see anything oh that's a fake
door don't think there's anything here I
don't like how dark it is pretty dark
over here ooh
bottles some you guys had a flashlight
but it's gone now oh I got one I found a
key
Io if anybody finds a door that needs to
be opened I have the key okay
cool oh this is pretty
big no now going to
what's GAA doing again G grabbed the
core what
no no I'm
stuck I'm lost wait wait you can't fix
that right once it's activated it you
can't fix no the monsters are coming now
Kar they're coming to get us
uh uh I don't know where where the exit
is I don't have anything the no scrap if
we stay to the right if we just stay to
the right oh that's nothing thanks
everybody if we stay to the right we'll
eventually find our way out of the
M
oh oh oh oh
oh I I opened this
door oh sorry sorry I did that o fish
fish I don't sense the radiation is it
really
happening um no it just means that there
are monsters coming oh okay all right
nothing else here just a fish
find our way out
together stay to the right we have to
find our way out eventually okay not
this way that means we just go did you
guys get any more loot maybe it'd be
good to get yeah fish this one's locked
too what's
that Monster go back
yeah K you behind me a it's a dead
end it's okay it's okay we go he I'm
still here
sh left as long as you don't see the
glowing
eyes it's just a loot it's fine that one
is not so not so dangerous where the
[\h__\h] is the exit I don't know K I don't
know you have the
flashlights it's there's no more
[Music]
battery now you going have to climb
OHA
oh we're lost in the dark together oh
help me we're so
lost so at least I'm leading the charge
into the
darkness creature dat what does that
mean I don't want to meet that
creature I spooked it run it's
locked you going have to go around I
think well if she screams like that
maybe she's going to get the monster to
her [\h__\h] why are we
always oh no oh it's just a loot
box why are we always going to the same
places I think
like that was nothing D just kill
me f Kiara I don't know why I'm the one
leading the way I need you to take
charge okay this way Teno our brave Teno
now leads the way okay this way she was
jumping on that thing like she jump on
the
bed f
run run Kelly
run I hope they leave without us I'm
dead thank you forever look kill me
faster why is it still sucking on
me let me
go okay did I make it day good just came
back maybe I wonder why Ena came back
they're still collecting cie
still stuck
oh they're lost they
lost oh no Kiara's dead she dropped the
fish she didn't
take Callie go a she thinks the the
other are still inside ran away bravely
ran away
sir did she make it out no Callie go I
made it go home cie but I don't know
about the others go home cie what time
is it
um yeah I know I had to sh fish out it's
being left behind wait for them until
the last moment oh she's crossing the
bridge
yay I'm to
leave somebody Oh I thought they were
leaving oh my God wait is
car I
think monsters are like oh look at this
new doll we got oh oh she's making that
yeah you went straight to
that oh yeah there a bridge I think it's
up
here yeah ship that's it is it there a
ship I'm here oh you guys are alive
let's go I thought you almost di oh my
God nice
yeah got the generator she bravely
walked before me and um and took a bug
to the face and we I can't believe that
happened it only happened after made it
after I good work we were I to think we
lured the monsters away from you guys
maybe we were we were pretty shallow in
the uh when it happened broke a bridge
oh with her yeah that happens too get
going going but too big all there is to
it but too
massive know I thought the tungsten fish
was I cleared the way jumping I'm proud
of it that's what I do part time Wario
stop jumping are they did you start the
ship hold on sorry the ship jump button
the ship door
open no
jumping open oh we're leaving okay
Goodbye Oh the bees almost came I mean I
feel like if you want to be sa before we
leave the atmosphere yeah close CH and
die you can die like that no unnecessary
Death it's like space for science yeah
probably I can see
[Music]
lazy I went back to intern because of
that what the [\h__\h] yeah if you
die took my R we got to go hand it in
time to go me to the company all right
I'll take us
there o what do I
bringing well I think we all know I
think we all know what happens when
somebody rings the bell right so let's I
don't do we need yeah I think
everybody's aware
what does g know you get a you get a
sticker when you ring the bell you ring
the
bell like a bunch of times not just once
like a a
lollipop yeah something kind of neat
happens why would take leave it leave it
just leave it
ah maybe the counter was kind of full
mhm she wasn't taken she was not taken
there you
go sells for a lot too and the fish fish
no got to say goodby fish anything left
oh yeah no I didn't personal token lost
one more thing one more thing I've lost
it oh wait hey wait wait
did it on its own I didn't was that you
ringing it over my shoulder n
my
[Music]
no what a
deal what a deal think we got it fish
not the fish you're going to lose the
fish can we Lo can we sell to post it oh
no she's ringing the bell and running
away I feel like we had so much more
money though more than 146 we barely met
the quota barely met the
quot yeah when I scanned it was like 240
something or another he ripped us off we
got
no oh we have enough month 300 out of
100 went back into the ocean
GA she went home she
went oh what
this can we get might find the fish over
there holy [\h__\h] what is this
F what is this
SC I don't know return to the Sea a
shark is all you Lev
be there's a lock here there was a lock
a journal
entry was it a will good not did we lose
her did she jump into the I think I
think she went
home no way
no way to the
ocean see on the ship but I got her
journal nice all right I guess we'll
leave that would be a good idea okay I
think that was lag okay Min is the minus
the
quota um probably
by prank something shoot
mon can
we switch members or should we just no I
wonder if someone left would I be able
to invite someone youing here I'm going
should I'm going should be able to play
next round this round is coming round
yeah is that how it
works I wonder if we have to the
sculpture recreate a room it would be
better not if we did not do that cuz
then we can't go to the further away
room but I wonder can can we invite from
here apparently some you can make it
saves an
orbit oh yeah that's right you can true
she dead yeah like I have a save file so
if we quit out of it it saves your
progress cool so I'll quit out of it and
reinvite people okay okay is is that
going to
work yeah let's do that go to orbit save
and then close lobby yeah sure to orbit
and then save okay go into
[Music]
orbit monitoring Big
Fish who's going to SP out she's in the
deep deep darkness of the
waters so dark I can't see
anything g g will sit out what did you
do you're new to the game everybody else
played it
B true oh maybe I'll sit out for well we
even got overtime B wait you can't cuz
you're the you're the host true maybe
I'll sit out the last though I don't
mind being the ghost
of New Year's past okay well I'll go
ahead and quit out then we're in orbit
now you were the ghost of New Year's oh
no I can't end my
joke for me a
coach you guys can't hear me or I can't
hear you guys right now that's okay
is how did you did you show the Discord
shair yeah yeah I just had um like
somebody's main POV and then somebody
else because you can watch two streams
at once and then I had both audio
playing at the same time and it wasn't
that bad it's kind of echoey but it's
not that
bad
okay wait am I not sitting this one I
can sit out I don't mind oh I didn't I'm
sitting out
wow ah
okaycome
hello hello okay so GL I explain what
were you doing at the
end uh I took my tungston fish and we
both went back to the Sea together it's
kind of sweet that is can one more
person also stream their
game
okay cuz I think if I do it like
recently when I screen share my my voice
gets like crackly and everything's
crackly
uh
Discord maybe I should buy one more walk
maybe two more walkies good who taught
you those dances
huh
you those don't seem familiar to me have
you cheated on
by going to a different dance
teacher no I would never do that
really I don't know those dance moves
they look unfamiliar to me I didn't
teach you
those it's okay it's just your old age
you're you're forgetting things my old
you g Cena that's
fine do a little gaslighting here and
there good just a little bit and good
fun B and
that's probably
it you guys can't even get out did you
just say she farted got to start the
game no got to light a match hold on I'm
trying
to
capture
Moon
Moon let's go to um the moon let's go to
the Moon let's go to Assurance again
let's go to the moon seems good off we
go ladies let's go taking flight your
lead I want to see the powerful skills
of Amelia
Watson show us your scrap collecting
she's hiding pretty good yeah Master
trinket collector hide collecting the
your trinkets that take you can't catch
me what she doing what she
doing did we buy
something we bought okay so listen to
Christmas cribo music
where is it your to the scow where is
it it's not coming did you really order
did you use prime there
go
oh
is here must or else it'll
[Music]
leave what is it walkie
talkies ladies for
everyone everybody and some flashlights
one
flashlight I think that was me I'm sorry
whoopsy doodle it's all good it's all
good no wonder I sunk so fast all right
where's the
entrance I'm follow the light in one two
you know sitting out right is she
sitting out
yeah okay spectating this
one she got a boom box hold on yeah it's
very important go which way is it all
right
where are you guys
going
for oh wait this is am's point of
view really embarrassing if we couldn't
even find found it found it this is it
way am it there we go forward
ho forward ho is it girl is it
Amad no this is z
me
I'm still in a
[Music]
dream okay we got to run and jump I'm
confused Run and Jump yeah Run and Jump
like
this onto
what I made it this is nice one that was
sick we SI I didn't even believe but it
happened yeah that's what happens when
you don't believe in
yourself I heard goba
hi come up
here she's oh here's a ey you can go
from here all right no fall damage right
I don't think so all good not at least
from this distance they're very very
lenient all right let's do this
run oh there's something right here do
you want it it looks like a flashlight
what is this I the PIP May it's a red
it's a laser
pointer my cat love it oh there's a
turret there's a turret be careful
there's a turret over
oh oh does the laser po to help with
anything did you get
lost Red soda ooh soda can Don't Mind If
I Do little soda IIs a soda oh that's
good heal sign hey I'm already full
inventory that's good
loot
good oh I can I can use this to hit
things yeah okay I'm going to find where
this is coming from and I'm going to
turn it
off
maybe this
is oh wait I'm just the master at
turning off valves this is my job sound
of my voice
Kelly I'm here I'm going kind of
downstairs I turned off the valve it's
easier to see
now oh
nice plumber waah good work I'm Super
Mario AKA kiata what is this I didn't
even know you could do that oh there's
another one there's another one all
right sounds like a job for
me it's already 220 p.m. and you haven't
entered the
building somebody still hasn't entered
the
building what the [\h__\h] it's [\h__\h]
noisy okay I'm scared I'm full inventory
I should
leave super san
Brothers oh no oh no oh no monster
monster a super saan brothers yeah we
might have to use it a hair brush never
mind okay the monster the monster
probably we could kill it with the with
the signs or whatever but o if we like
beat it together like yeah but Are You
full inventory cuz I am we might as well
go yeah and then they just went in will
they be okay yeah they'll be fine wait I
could give
them I could give them the flashlight
though if they're still there oh is
somebody here oh
oh I said I said it [\h__\h]
you the
noise B I think she got raptured no no I
think I saved her she's gone she's um
someone dropped her walkie-talkie oh
yeah I saved her there and gooda it's
okay she's alive we should go they're
all
leaving where is she she left leave W
she left what just happened did you guys
there she is there she is let's go let's
go what she's alive I thought
you
I'm I think I can get my title back
right guys I can
be
again she okay let's go let's go let's
go all good
over
yeah
do you guys need help carrying something
no is everyone
alive yeah BS and ship okay Bo we got to
be quiet
wow I'm in
wow
wow I hear the it's the here do go do go
do
go here boy
getting away from you guys you guys are
going to get me
K you guys going to get me killed I
literally saved you who's a good
[Music]
boy there's many steps here a good boy
oh hold on I'm open I haven't seen any
dog so far get in here wait I'm almost
there wait I'm almost there a warm wor
oh that's that's a worm yep I made it I
made it I'm here get inside get inside
get
inside
oh my God the timing is
impecable you get out of here who who b
a boom me it's important music is
important when you're lonely and on a
ship
SP play some T sing us a song You're The
Piano
Man
y hear any I dropped
it what lazy but most
wait how can you be lazy
and I mean I'm part time guess do seem
right seems like there's something you
just pushing your tasks to the other
employees yeah what no I I even I
literally saved Amy from Death a monster
was on her head and I killed it that's
the only reason she's
alive hero moment for Kiara big
hero I killed it on my own no you did
not my B is the proof it was the
strength of my will no my body is Thank
Me Later get down don't tell her does
she not know does she not know all right
sending I believe you Kar you're hero to
me thank
you let's go to Ren okay sounds good or
is it like French
it's I've never seen this before is it
cuz her face her screen was covered with
a monster she see too poor
can't
getas
to you little
[\h__\h] you're being ladies like a high
school loveby
duby little [\h__\h] y
new someone twerking in the over there
what's going on me I was twerking I'm
not I'm not what I'm not twerk what are
you talking about you were doing some
some movements behind the cabinet I
wasn't sure you know yeah it was her you
were uh right yeah it was her yeah you
sure that was me she's doing the Oinky
spy the yink spinky yeah I mean someone
could stay here in theory and direct
with the walkie talkies
back use
that why is it
what she
[Music]
hates guess I should announc from the
company please do not kill your other
fellow
employees I think I don't need to walkie
talkie so I'll leave it here cuz I need
more space in my inventory lives matters
in this company okay I'll stay here
sounds good let's go be good assets
though the great assets they definitely
value the great assets more what' you
say to me heard me no I did not call you
an ass a great ass SC cat I said you're
a great asset to the company little wait
wait walkie talkie wait wait wait wait
wait wait I don't need it's okay I don't
I left it on purpose have
mine all right she doesn't want to
[Music]
communicate I see how it is it's okay
I'm crying out to you in Peril and
you're not going to hear me no no I will
I will be around when you need me me and
when you need me the most that's when
I'll be there she says mhm not going to
respond to
that I guess we can go off to the side
there's a big bird oh K hates SM no they
hate
me untrue now you're just making up
fibs let's see oh maybe we can go up
here he good you're going to lead us
right to
the I'm so
slow wonder if we can jump this no I
think there's a different way we can
go I think we can just go
around this way she she made it you got
jump
it Calli gave up though before even
trying no I didn't
[Laughter]
I'm no coward parkour the rest
of you know I just the other day
finished my first ever like um platform
of Mario
game Odyssey Mario Odyssey yeah it was
very nice to me so cute it's a good
y sign is a bad choice what
why that's all right they're they're
just ignore it good you stay in sh they
can't where where is our third member
fourth member they where is our fourth
member I need some coms here where is
scoby clear coms clear coms let's see
dead down dead
down hello this is Morrison speaking
Grim Shady over
now bottles bottles of water nothing
good here literally can't pick up
anything
thing can we kill spider yeah sure
spider oh there was a treasure over
there treasure what
treasure the the tri Doritos I found
something I lied I found nothing there's
a door
though she's imagining
things no it's a valve nothing good down
here maybe it's hello nothing good down
here sadly yeah there's a green
oh oh did I see two eyes the it's the
generator do not touch Until the
End why is there no
items there is one there
Shadow sound
lightsaber muff
scream
two I killed one there were two
do res why is G is chilling here that
little [\h__\h] oh she's making a run for
it the [\h__\h] that was a a mom and a dad
where's K well I'm
[Music]
there why are they laughing at My Dead
Body there's one more thing hold on what
a that was overwhelmed by numb yeah
grabing the items why the [\h__\h]
is no it died it straight up
died what died the clutch the monster
wait it's dead wait what cuz I killed it
hello she directing who's dead who is
that she wasn't directing me cuz I guess
I didn't have the walkie talkie I am
afraid to tell you that
oh did gar die someone has
passed away can we oh yeah we have to
make the jump okay oh yeah can you be
careful with my body my God Kelly did
you pick up anything else did no sorry
couldn't be a good ass can you hear me
really was pretty Barren I'm not going
to lie yeah that
Hall Wait what did they just say about
me something positive I was like zoning
out she left us with a single a and then
pieced out pieced out of existence they
see the bodies of the monsters I killed
wait I heard them wait oh oh oh no hey
just kidding it must have been on the
walkie see I knew they'd be
useful I have uh K's dead body what
about Kiara's
sign D it must have lost give us a sign
oh I picked it up I got
it
up MVP what a legend all right let's Mo
on out of
here someone else CH where we next leave
it up to you
guys right on it CH can pick
two two where does chat want to go this
clothes is on its own right yeah I think
yeah would be pretty funny if it didn't
it will say say um we have about one day
left for yeah she stayed inside
how are you doing with the quter so
hi
check I'm alive
again Phoenix yeah we're at
26 comfortable because I brought back a
body like a noble a noble Spaceman yeah
thank you for carrying me you're welcome
I got lazy but I was Button
Pusher I mean that could I pushed one
button oh wow Assurance really is the
only one that we can mess around on
huh don't don't you do me please what
is take any damage
here oh well in that case all out Battle
Royale
[Laughter]
Doo your radio going run
Battery no yeah you got to charge it you
got to turn it off no you know what I
should also grab some flashlights wait
mine's on two I'm going to grab some
flashlights real quick and then we can
go
flashlight
F righty now let you I have a report to
make to
uh yes pleas being harassed
by harassed by
[Music]
[Laughter]
what
listening she's killing me
there seems to
be oh my
God excuse me you have a witness you
just crime here I'm reporting you to the
company report made
please
Kara so I kill myself though Kiara take
me really
are you kidding me no I do not I do not
deserve okay all right girl last day of
the meet the quot let's go
me right um I do what just happen
answered my
prayers I can't I can't hear cuz she's
dead I gained my title and I lose my
title I'm so sorry I mean it's because I
didn't realize you know you were hitting
me first anyway I can't go in there you
got what you deserve oh I got two
flashlights now oh yeah it was supposed
to be one for each of us but plans
changed clearly wait wait wait wait I
going drop his up yeah me
too how are we going to explain to the
bosses that two of our team well one
committed a crime and the other one
killed himself committ soku um a great
question the same person that was the
same person not think too much about it
no it's not the same person no
no de boss can I please I can't believe
done this W the raise that my it was for
love fellow employee was going to
get was All for Love get the lunch CP
different from the love I know can I get
that meal
ticket I'm
started I didn't do anything you
started any that was
we already left yeah like I didn't
realize we were out of
orbit see you're trying to blame they
all say Kiara I will sit out after this
to reflect on my actions I didn't think
that was actually going to kill her or
like a
dream all
right Bros to the rescue if someone else
is going to kill it it's going to be me
kind of thing you know good that was too
short like were too short to make the
jump it seems the baby she left she left
her I can't die here wat's going to
laugh at me forever if I die here cuz
she literally told me you die
here J Jump do
it the hard
job I had toight a dragon
sorry
Dragon but I live right
I was going to make a plan but I stopped
myself s
inside hostile hostile H hostile in the
area hostile it's just a bird hostile
I'm scared anyway yeah stick
jump did it oh
present let me open it what's she going
to do with it what's she going to do
with it oh oh oh
I the h hello oh she made it I'm alive
made it before I found a present I can't
open it for some reason I pressed y but
it didn't work maybe you can open
it oh Dar pickles that will help us meet
the
qu we got to we got to we got to
survive look like a
burger
a nothing in here nothing spotted
people full
nothing oh my gosh oh no way the worst
person to
find find something good yeah dude that
fish not going to believe it oh no it's
a [\h__\h] okay okay all right uh I'm
quitting the game I've had enough of
this I've had enough of this come here
come here come here come here come here
come here sit on it come
here oh my finger yeah there for the
content G pick it up pick it up pick it
up pick it
up
[Music]
really you know what you've made a
mistake G you're letting me hold this
now which means you'll never get it back
no it's only wor age it's not even
worse sometimes and
yep see how productive the bone Bros can
be there's a turret be
[Music]
careful all this say ass what does this
do K you can use that you know
glass wait it says
glass or flash it says flash give me my
whoopy cushion
El
need oh oh oh oh flashbang yeah throw it
oh
yeah did that help at all she
the I don't think the flash is the
spider I'm so proud of you yeah I don't
know if that helps at all like no
tomorrow did it did it work did I do it
did I fall I you did you did you
did I don't think that kills it though
just
yeah maybe it just got emotional damage
not
sure him and all his eight limbs can
suck my air
bubbles oh no pleas is that Kiara no
that was a Kelly oh chased by be K is
nowhere oh no oh
notine disgusting little creature
disgusting you need proud of
you I did
it he's not happy is he No Where's the
egit
come in uh Shady
over she not does she not hear
it is her walk talk
off the
ship almost there at least one person's
back at the ship
yeah with the whoopy cushion at the key
and some pickles feel kind of bad for
G
and then she'll be sad when we sell
it is she she's leaving she's
leaving she left she left over behind
she's leaving she was leaving oh is G
still there oh oh what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
she that's what she gets for leaving her
behind she's farting didn't even check
the cams real sorry about that one she
was so finding a way back you know on
the bright side I got save cushion for
you yeah I'll have you know I was
fighting for my life in there well
that's fine you wouldn't have made it
back anyway the dogs were
prowling I did a Sol
Flavor now we have maybe
enough are we all getting fired or it we
might be getting fired from being fired
there has been some alligations of
that's mine you
know members there's mine killing
members so true employee abuse body cell
for five each so if we got definitely
going to hear about this three Warm
Bodies that could increase the quot or
the quot amount you can actually use
it e there's no bathroom in the ship
just to let you know it
Poots
I figured she'd like
that that makes
sense wait so uh if we want to rotate
someone out we can this is a good time
to do it if we want to I can be the one
to leave before before we die I can I
can it's my
turn how is it your turn ah we're going
by the life to De order I'm next in the
row oh I guess it makes sense is that
how it works all
right
I guess we're going to the company
now we got to sell everything we have no
days left on our deadline I want some
pickles we can check if you meet the qu
or not first maybe yes yeah know I kind
of did take a look and I think if even
if one of us even if all three of us
gave up our bodies if three people give
up their bodies it wouldn't matter we
can give up our bodies for points for
money
interesting oh don't you only get like
five oh oh oh that's what you mean
[Music]
oh so maybe don't sell anything maybe
don't sell the SOP sign yet it don't s
the stop ring the bell a lot of times
yeah can't pick it up again
yeah darn it I got a
sniper a laser
pointer you get that oh I found that FL
I see the sell for a lot that's good
yeah if we sell the
who we can sell the boom box we can sell
the boom box we have to keep Spirits
High what about the boom box any
money
no I don't think the boom Box gives you
money does
it that's too bad oh it's the stuff gone
I mean oh 300 the qu holy the apparatus
is just doesn't show the scan I guess
you can feel free to keep your your
whoopy cushion I guess she was going to
keep it anyway she's going to keep it
anyway bot items okay all
right goodbye will be
chistian damn
it
for okay he he
ha get moving maybe we can go to some
better moves we're going to into orbit
and then we'll switch out is everyone
here
okay okay know is
everyone sorry I also didn't
sh I'm not the best Captain be a
reoccurring thing Callie all right now
listen here big apologies no no no no
the company doesn't need to hear about
anything anything of the sort quot is
going to start getting crazier though
from here on out um yeah so we're going
to need to go to further away moons with
better loot good you will be the voice
that everybody hears so maybe lead give
us no don't lead us but give us give us
give us useful
hints yeah like a a walk talk like a GM
now let's see what we can buy
first see store I can spell store um so
we have quite a bit of money in fact we
could get a transporter transporter
might be kind of nice what's a transpor
what's the point if the ship leaves
before you can teleport I mean good Al
that's a good point too but we we
actually can't afford it so I'm going to
grab some
shovels shovel mhm two we need two
fighters and then after that um I think
we should be using should
be everything mhm number one employee
I'm going for emplo that's really
expensive um all right what's the
cheapest Moon I wonder is it Dy by
chance we won't go there cuz it's
Eclipse but oh
no is
Ren yeah maybees would be
nice we're changing that's right correct
swapping out boss mhm say doodle okay
and I close out the room
now quit bullying
girl going dancing bullying
her
oh I guess I got to launch now
huh
yes so there you
oh that should do it oh I can un stream
now in the
[Music]
Discord
Callie did you see did you receive the
present it is
present oh the Ste I haven't looked yet
on Steam yeah you should check I think
it went through it went through excited
thank you needs another oh Ena needs
another invite you got it please okay no
problem's got your back all right youa
Jump On In yeah guys I basically did uh
almost everybody maybe except for one
Persona yes did you see I I sent you a
present over steam did you see I I
didn't see anything pop up oh it's
probably in your emails or
so wa you double now you're double I
can't go all right IED the
gift accept gift I hope you don't have
it yet do you have it already I don't I
only have the first
one please play it I want you to I want
to see you play
it okay I will I'll beat the artist arti
yeah I ended up giving her something
else guys than what I originally said in
the
Stream not notr other
game secret it's more fitting more
fitting yeah where make sure we grab our
stuff to two the second
one I'm glad she doesn't have it yet
okay who's staying in the
ship he can stay in the ship it's such
an
but I didn't know
she already had it learned that I'm just
like o pretty shapes oh right I tell
thema is double ena's echoing for me oh
sorry I forgot it's okay all good
switch
display how do I do it again wait is
there ship coming got look at the
monitor I think you can type in switch
view monitor yeah that's what it is is
hi guys sure you have are you staying
inside yes all right get out of here why
my my should be she's a
murderer chicken chicken chicken
[Music]
chicken at
Freddy's
mayet how watch two
streams press the little plus eyeball on
Discord oh my God all right
thank
you this is grim Shady are we not
receiving anything wait then I should
take a is there walkie-talkie
here this HQ no calling in break a
breaker then I'll take
this then I won't hear the one who's
staying inside
again uh where did they
go
ship um think someone has
one oh I hear GA but that's because
she's only over Discord
now Mantic
coil
um I'm alone oh o I see
entrance by the way guys I gave
Amit the Talis principal
right when she seems to maybe already
have
it like she never played it tell her to
jump on the bridge jump on the bridge
fun bouncy woohoo yeah jump on it a
million times she'll be
fine she still already accepted it so
found another who be
cion otherwise I would have taken it for
myself the collection grows larger I
don't have a I don't have a
walkie-talkie so I'm just going to stay
with fuel oh what is that I don't have a
walkie-talkie so I'm going to stay with
you hold on okay that Watson can you
repeat that
please what's that dust what is what
does it say it's an
air I should
probably r
ducky uh how to take it did you trying
to crouch dropped them I just dropped it
yeah I dropped it on purpose sorry I
don't think we can't take them anymore
can we what it doesn't say pick up there
you go okay there you go nice good
find yeah nice finds let me turn the
walkie keep the walkie
on Watson to let us know if there
enemies coming nothing here
uh-oh monster e it's like running away e
ew ew
e
fire oh boy I saw that
happen
uh is
gone they're
gone I didn't see that
happen bad yeah I saw that happened um I
I don't know what we could have
done so so ena's dead maybe Amma can
come in now to help oh slime slime slime
slime slime slime
slime slime is fine not messing with
that can I hit with this no but I can
use this maybe if an enemy shows up it
will stop them for a moment all right
here's all right so the enemy took this
is where the monster is Kara I'm going
to go forward and if it comes out I
see
need did someone just snaap their neck
what was that
there was a
snap I'm going to go ahead to the
monster and if something
comes have two
bottles Handle by myself if you wouldn't
mind coming to pick one of them up to
help me out I'll try to I'll try to do
both but okay know did you die by the
same monster get
there I got to figure out get I got I
got a nice hug and not a good hug oh
okay my neck my neck was SN which way do
I go chat is it this
[Laughter]
way oh it was the same
monster okay apparently apparently I did
I see it
okay
dangerous this way I did find like
bottles down I was kind of sad I was
like maybe I should bring it back no
I'll go back in and then I died oh oh
oh they found each other all right
sounds good Kell's bringing the stuff
back and am is going in
nice oh oh she's she's walking back with
the bottles wait uh bottles of water
right oh yeah this should be the okay
the water the water bottles
water that bridge looks way too
sturdy yeah this is the dirty one the
other one I think I think the bridge
will break if you're too heavy like one
the one you're on the right that one
yeah over Grim Shady
over who brought the far pillow I love
bread
rolls yummy yummy what what kind of
bread rolls though man I can switch
places I'll go watch the regular
time Kell not going in anymore I thought
they were picking up
bodies
monitoring I mean bottles and bodies
kind of sound the same over the radio
yeah maybe
misunderstanding I think my body is kind
of far in the corner though so yours is
a bit closer though I think so exit
yeah but maybe they took the bodies
press the right but right click right
click
it
is yeah does she know how to
scan what is that I think so she already
there I
big found home big Ste what is
that go let's go let's go let's go nice
one nice one Watson let's go brings it
to the far side of the map not oh
they're partying they're
partying dead and they're partying yeah
they're morning our death with a dance
got to check wow celebrating
early you're lazy
[Music]
again zero
exper
yeah the shame two days left we pulled
about the same amount
it's all right it's all right no problem
if we pull the same amount again um a
couple more times then we will
do easy
easy oh you got demoted I'm order some I
can't get devoted
[Music]
any the
Myers are ping me experimentation
haven't been to in a
while that's Kar she's mocking you look
at
her you're just an inter about to mod
there will be no bullying on my ship
KN K did it she started it you little
[\h__\h] you little [\h__\h] I am done being
your Gosling there fighting again never
again whatever I want to get coupl
srel they're like gross
grossing nice that was actually pretty
good so we're going to land and we
should look listen look listen for the
delivery I got flashlights for you guys
oh thank you I owe you my life make sure
you try
takies and use them
ladies all right why do we have so many
W don't wor it playing with us probably
oh true where's the Christmas tree
should
be
there oh nice that's the
sun yeah why are we all looking into the
Sun at the same time
he's bad for your eyes oh ra the sun oh
there it
is let me turn
off I just got flashlights for you
[Music]
guys where are we
going
that Way's moving real
fast still no Walky
talk don't need
one where it
go I will not die this time got watch
and speed running are they inside
already oh okay
all right nothing shady is there anybody
at I have
noie this a dead
end dead end just like my career in this
company M braid M braid we're coming to
get
you there's a noise
there okay I'll take care of
it
I fixed
it it's still
broken no I fixed
it can't see I didn't bring my
flashlight there's
[Music]
nothing I fixed it not at the
moment
oh why do I always just fix the
vales in every
game I got a door over here I need yeah
yeah there's I saw elsewhere also
another
monster mu
oh let gety is that s
[Applause]
us what is that several
usages I think so
M maybe it will stop a
monster maybe I don't remember the
exit stay with me I got the oh what is
that
e that sounds just got to follow the
toot on oh um ah there there she is
Jes I thought you were the
[Applause]
ship
[Music]
where's oh I I only have one item but I
might as well bring it
back nice fire we didn't find anything I
have this a big ass nail sound like an
air it sounds like something else stay
with
me this is almost better as the fart
cushion wa where's C
squirrel I'll bring it back before I die
I could go back I wouldn't mind going
there
again someone's there
right
hello
hello no oh but 2 oh for [\h__\h]
sake your light is that e e run oh my
God they're probably coming back in a
minute though I feel like I have this
feeling they are
escaping they want to
escape I wonder what we I
doing she said she might lay down cuz
she's sleepy please be a yeah let's
go thank you appreciate it oh you guys
are coming back
in we're all
alive Y what a miracle we had more stuff
but this is easy Christmas miracle there
nothing there was like nothing in there
exit Chad says oh [\h__\h] fire exit
the is still in
there I think she's dead no all right if
I don't come
back wait she's moving wait she's
moving she
lost want to be a
hero oh my God oh my God oh my God
GAA is oh my goding about something
what's
happening insane Ena is
insane got the radio K it's okay next
book Serpentine
maneuver
wow
hello
you okay I'm s I'm I'm scared hi ah oh I
was to look for you
too oh no I'm fine I just want to check
the fire exit don't check the fire exit
let's just go let's just go if you say
so you know it's been a long day let's
just go
home I even went
in pretty brave of
me let's
go we have we're going to have a
Minefield of whoopy cushions yeah at
this point anything wrong with that hey
well we know what we're selling first if
we're low on
quota
enough you should
Bey byebye mon me
monsters
not
52 actually a lot way more than I
thought a lot nice one yes no notes is
better than being called
lazy great
a great eight and back to part
time one day left one day left anything
you guys want me to buy cute
and I could use a walkie I didn't have
one yeah I don't have one either oh
really I thought for sure we had four
well people die and leave them behind
[Music]
all right
two stop to go to the bathroom or what
guess not we could buy a toilet imagine
something in
space toet you out there forever I mean
maybe there's a toilet that you can buy
I mean gravity helps right how much it
costs I don't know how would you even
get it out
anyway all right we're on our way
where's our next destination
March yeah all right let's
go to march in isn't that right ladies
I'm anyone stay in
behind there's a there's a hi nearby be
careful okay that's your level
[Music]
B you don't really need a flashlight
technically oh it's not really charged
no no you you can just go into the
darkness oh there's the
entrance easy easy going sec I'm just
going here's the Christmas
tree she ran
off anytime
now that it that's oh
is yay stop
she's Prince yay nice is that it I think
so
you waiting outside hurry up
swag
swag are they
coming
oh yipp
I'm here I don't know where the others
are
hello let's go inum the cliff go go
go let's
go nothing
here next door oh sh we need a key for
this one don't we oh place is big big
room
yeah big footsteps
oh yeah oh maybe those are just yours
there no no
no wait what's that I don't know did she
not see that oh wait how do I take
it oh oh hi hey how do I pick this
up what
this oh my God I got it good f
[Music]
help help help help help oh that's a
yeah that's a that hurt that hurt the
quot how do we deal with that
the storm that hurt that hurt do
someone's got to be B this qu I felt
something and then it was in front of me
you sure I don't mind being baby we
don't have a shovel though
way oh uh it's
okay I'm going I'm not
[Music]
scared okay
um yeah different exit different
entrance I don't know where it is but
we'll just walk around
careful gravery see they're confused
they don't know who to go
after
m i oh no oh no uhoh wait bring the bees
in there's another entr
there well what choice did I have
besides running
away
nothing oh did she die Kelly
dead where's the oh just going to bring
these things so that we have at least
something maybe the tut helps with the
Beast oh I feel like they would know
about that oh oh hello already back in
the ship someone
here yeah oh I don't see you need help
you're going to
[Music]
have
oh I'm going
back
oh what a hero oh something weird is
happening what is this
feeling oh oh it's okay it's okay I just
saw like Blurry
[\h__\h] things were blurry am I imagining
it is it cuz I saw see the fire exit
anywhere
nope
unfortunately I thought I could grab the
hive
but that's the entrance we used
H oh my God critical injury I should
stay I'm almost dead oh yeah I mean I
guess I took a big hit
sorry I'm sorry you got this girl you go
girl you better you better
H okay I'm staying I'm
H
hey found the fire exit over oh [\h__\h] she
did I'm
coming away with these stupid things I'm
cleaning this place it's ridiculous how
messy it
is go in here all the toys must
go the duck
to what just
happened okay the rest is probably too
big okay
clean
[Music]
um
that may I said my apartment is pretty
clean by the way like very clean
compared to other [\h__\h] she
s he's why is he
just oh
myu good is talking to herself she
thinks I don't hear her but I hear
her let's
see what are we seeing the red is a
monster is it bots on the outside
ena's no is Ena the red
oh nah
ena's
some Calli is alive chilling oh well
that's her being dead okay
okay ah and the other dot is another
body okay uh so maybe
uh I is planning on going back Callie oh
is that Call's but oh it's Call's
body oh so only a
it oh my god oh is she coming back or is
she going to the exit oh wait I could
ask
her
uh are you coming back hi oh yeah oh
there you
are wait SOA is dead in the in the
thing can't help it got to go I guess I
don't think we made enough money I think
it is this our last day yeah but we made
a lot of money before I think on the
previous
days it's okay it's okay we have I I
just cleaned we have a lot of stuff I
just cleaned it into the
storage sell it all we got to sell it
all nice work yay great ay
oh not bad yeah we're going to have to F
on the whoopy cushions a song for you
guys cuz you
died away with this away with all of it
well maybe they'll forgive us I don't
know I think we're going to have enough
we're going to make it
y I
believe I mean
okay is alive build all right do we have
something to hit each other with
and get the
uh have a shovel yeah you could buy a
shovel wait but if we buy shovel will we
have enough no it won't affect the money
that um okay it won't affect the money
I'm sorry I'm not really good at mad all
good I guess we can
land
question oh yeah question after this
should we maybe just like chitchat a
little bit and do the like talk about
the things we're supposed to talk
about yes yeah oh yeah we're supposed to
be uh yeah we're supposed to do
something that's
true CU I think another round would take
uh too long true
prob we'll get the big boy Moon someday
can play more
later yeah let's get a let's get a mod
let's get mod
perms yeah I want to I want to play okay
we need to ask what else is there
anything else we can sell where's the
clipboard all right now the shovel
should be
coming there it
is the shovel
shall that's
cool your honest work is invaluable to
the
company I think even selling our bodies
isn't going to
work what the [\h__\h] I didn't know it was
coming just never know
okay oh all
the hey got to sell you
Ena no no we could have used that
body I mean oh no ena's dead
[Music]
what what what you tell the walking oh I
don't think so I don't think I can
anyway I wasn't trying to how much money
do we make
plenty I would say plenty shoot oh is
this I
did I can't take it back it's okay
whatever it's
okay pretty aggravated it's fine I can't
take it back anyway it's okay we're
ending It Anyway take the items there we
go come on B
yeah we'll be
fine I mean that's that's from just now
right did we hit it yeah we did of
course we
did no we didn't oh no we
didn't okay that's a great our
bodies
or true enough do
it although it is a good ending although
it is a good ending it is a good ending
isn't it when if we get sent into space
that's a nice ending I mean that is
true but I could still kill you with a
sh you could but you wouldn't would you
hey hey don't I mean hey I'm not worth
enough
anyway need a more convincing argument
uh uh Takami
[Music]
Takami is the
arguments all right okay
okay what about a where the [\h__\h] did she
go for now for
now for
now did she jump yeah you know what you
make a really good point K should beat
up both of us am should beat up both of
us yeah that's her dream come no the
other way around we should beat
up did she jump into the water did she
go after
G
Watson
man hey
Watson I hear her I think I hear little
sounds or is it is that Gaa
Gaa Gaa I know you're like only in
Discord but say
something she's giggling probably she's
giggling see
yeah something she heard
you wait she she's like hiding
somewhere in the closet well no I
mean well what else can we do guess
we'll go I'm we're
leaving Amelia
Watson check the camera check the camera
o good idea oh it's just like in the
black what I don't know we're in the
ship she's H she's
coming oh what's she
doing being
silly hi where were
you hey hi yo
you
hey hey I didn't closed the door on you
that was I think
I'm I see you guys wanted to be alone I
guess no no
no she probably already sent the ship to
no okay wait something's burning she
bought something you can buy something
here get away for my
stuff it's mine what is it I take I
think you mean mine she wants to kill us
she I will kill you first I knew it get
her I took your weapon I took it you
tried to kill us my shovel we survive
you will not be the end of me take her
down no no
open up open up you little sh open up
you can't getting us that easily no I'm
dying
too don't do
this you can't do this to
us each
[Music]
other oh I mean I was going to show her
mercy but she was leaving so
wait did she order another one no uh we
should
go but ell her body first no I just
witnessed a cold blooded
murder let's take her okay I had a
planell the [\h__\h] at the end of the day
there's only room for one Sheriff no sh
she should bring the reaper s
that's a really good point K back
stepped me there's only room for one
Captain it's like the ending of a bad
space off back I ran away she was
killing you I was trying to save you by
getting a shovel
a save who he's doing what has to be
done to satisfy the
company look at that face the face
murder we're still twitching and she's
selling us while we're still twitching
she could still help us that might
help any whoopy cushions she doesn't
even want to watch everything maybe he
doesn't want these
things what are you doing
Mor did he take the
B why aren't you
hungry yeah he'll take
them the reaper is
reaping there you go eat up oh eat up
how much Mone we were she's like she's
like the antagonist at the end of the
movie that like actually took over the
world and just like well time for a
glass of
wine didn't want
to I'm not selling the boom box that's
for sure um with that being
said it's
over there's only one she just there can
only be one there can only off ship
right now
he has the boom
box dang
it you are a little [\h__\h] you are a
little [\h__\h]
225 you
are little [\h__\h] I was just doing what
needed to be
done we were so
[Music]
close Welcome to our
discipline I don't want
[Music]
to and that is How It
Ends all right
girls fire was nice was
nice
GG can't believe I got fired again oh
suddenly I leave the
game okay we we
wall you girls ready to
talk unmute Cy
unmute cie unmute pretty good I was okay
yeah cie won't unmute herself is
she in a
trance I know hold on hold
on hold on hold on why you crying
mate crying you look like you're sad
about your actions like you're
regretting what you have done to your
friend feel you know guilt regret shame
I feel remorse I do great okay I do feel
that for sure for sure for sure what you
don't believe
me yeah I bu a little bit I think deep
in your heart you don't want to show it
but you're so deep in your your heart
you have
remorse okay well yeah I would say I
mean that's apt that's about right maybe
a little bit I just had to do what
needed to be done you know for the sake
of the company and H we were never
meeting that quota but you know I should
I had the opportunity to take the ship
and leave you guys and kill you we
should have taken it you I wasn't going
to kill kiar until she killed you so
what were you up to God I saw you hit
her
so is doing my job
everybody
everybody first of all happy New Year
from
myth happy New
Year holidays
yay a year it's it's a new year it's
2024 oh my
God so I don't know do we want to um do
we want to say like what what we should
say yeahp things to talk about well okay
I have some pictures prepared ta a
reminder no it's just like you know the
usual uh the small myth stuff we are
here to
advertize the small small myth stuff
that is still on sale
[Music]
until oh my God no way cute cute a
little while longer um I don't know when
it ends it doesn't say
here but cute though it's been on sale
for a while so it will be gone soon I
also don't have it in description you're
hugging
them uh yeah there's a lot of stuff
there's uh the t-shirts where we're
where we're poking out of the the the
pockets then there's the small metal
charms there's also random stickers and
the plushies of course again are also
still on sale so I'm going to put the
link in my chat if you guys I'm waiting
on my shipment cover Corporation Hey
where's my small stuff some reason I
hang all of them on my my backpack but
then just keep it in my
house a you go out with that stuff no no
no no no no I just look at it I put it
in like a a glass case and I'm like yeah
cool nice also can't forget the plushies
yeah the
basementy give me all of these line them
up on my bed oh they are regular restock
item oh they're regular restocked item
oh there is no deadland oh nice so I
don't know whenever you want them okay
go grab them nice okay well well
well so that was just a reminder and
then there's uh I guess a re
announcement that we have yeah kind of a
a re oh wait hold on a sec first did we
mention the figures we've already talked
about the little figures
right boxes yeah they're part of dad I
guess oh they're part they're random you
mean those random ones right yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah they're part of that yeah
Okie doie well then there's another
thing you guys yeah um that other thing
being we announced something a little
while ago which is a brand new song can
we show the
picture yeah I showed a picture of it
okay everybody's already seen
it yeah well guys we finally have a
release date well release sorry for the
wait
sorry for theate you guys but the song
will be released a music video for it
will be released on Janu son of a you
would think that I would hold on no
January 11th January 11th
2024 12 a.m jst so when the clock turns
to January 11th hooray hurrah the song
will release on the official Hol live
English Channel so make sure that you
guys check it out I'm probably going to
do a little unarchived karaoke
beforehand to lead into to it so be fun
get you guys those hands check out our
new song C can you play it am on that
yele yeah play
it play it on there whoa the uke showed
up she's nervous wait that can you can
we can do that now yeah we can do it now
it shows up in the groups
cool let's go it's so cute her hands are
so cute
I can't it's a cute song I hope you guys
will enjoy it reunion kind of silly
silly one think you guys will like it
it's silly and cute and um exciting soon
TM many time somebody says
te flashbacks War flashbacks every time
someone says
te I'm being targeted
anyway anyway uh that's that's really
about it and then we also just kind of
wanted to play some lethal company today
together because you know only seems
fitting funny that we all join the fry
together that was that was a good time
someday we got to get on those more
expensive moons we'll we'll be able to
do it I'm sure maybe since this is the
first myth collab of
2024 do we want to say something nice I
don't know goals or so together down the
line um give a a not a speech Just Say
something I don't know just a short
comment this Nick who starts I should
start I should start you know what put
the pressure on Mory um because I'll be
the example okay because I was today's
captain and I did I did betray my entire
ship um I should go ahead and take the
punishment that is starting off um so
let's see 2024 since the number four is
included in the year I've decided that
this year I'm going to go
um 5 million per um hard and so I hope
you guys will support me real hard um
next month a bunch of things are
happening there's um a special stream on
Valentine's um that's going to be um
about love but not romantic love it's
going to be love for love love of
there's going to be a charity stream on
Valentine's Day oh came in for like 12
hours so look forward to that um I'm not
going to announce the charity or
anything like that for a little bit but
that's the plan right now so look
forward to that and then I'm announcing
something big next month um two big
things actually one is significantly
bigger than the other um it's it's the
it's the big it's the big thing um and
so I'll be doing a 24hour stream before
that so come check it
out and yeah yeah so look forward to
that I'm going to work really really
hard this year um and I love I love Holo
and all my friends and um I'm having a
lot of fun thanks to you guys and I
think this year is going to be amazing
um so let's keep having tons of fun
together and um
[Music]
yeah that's all I wanted to say
anyway next
up let's go by the line
uh well well well we have Rec it looks
so
stupid no you look perfect we have
recently we have recently expanded
gotten a new
generation um who are doing their best
working hard um but I'm I you know I
hope that as myth we can still do a lot
of fun things together it's a new year
so let's let's do some cool stuff myth
my cutest gen mates thank you for a
wonderful year 2023 and on to another
one with more power than ever more
energy than ever let's be strong myth go
stronger go home baby let's
[Music]
[Applause]
go let's not lose to the new energetic
girls all right we're still young and
pachy py we have it in our nerves and in
our jeans we we are we are the strongest
let's go let's go good girl let's next
you are wearing pants go good I I wanna
I want to actually get a mushy gushy for
a second mushy gy Mushi gushy I
apologize um I just want to I want to
say a genuine thank you to not only my
Miss girlies but also to uh everybody
watching right now for your patience
with me as I uh get my personal life and
all of all of its things together and we
wait for you I really do appreciate it
all of your sweet messages uh that they
do make it back to me and your fan mail
makes it back to me and my myth girls
who are patient with me and they check
in on me and they they say hi and they
they invite me to do things and they
wish me happy holidays and all the that
stuff I want to say thank you I
appreciate it very much and I hope to be
strong for my myth girls in 2024 because
I do I do want this to be I want this to
be a happy fun strong year
with so thank you
everybody happy happy new year happy New
[Music]
Year
nice nice nice good well said
Kuba well
said Ina you want to say something
too you
know hello no no hear you you're here oh
oh I muted her cuz like she was doubling
in the game and here wow
she yeah you were double at some
point you were saying things so far damn
it I miss I please repeat everything for
me anyways no I just wanted to say you
know um it's been a wonderful wonderful
time with you guys with chat with
everyone um I hope 2024 is filled with
more fun things and exciting things and
let's let's let's all do our best let's
have
fun thank you always
everyone guys love you love you
too
yeah love right back at you I'm I guess
it's my turn your turn guess it
detective yeah it's been really you know
the time has gone by so fast it's so
crazy to me you know fourth year pretty
much dear you know we've been holding
strong and we've been we've been doing
so much everybody's always so busy so um
I hope this year we get to have more fun
together and also get you know some a
little bit of time to relax and and
chill but also do stuff that we enjoy
cuz you know that's what we're here for
cuz we enjoy it y y
yay also I will be having my birthday
stream
tomorrow 3D special I'm
[Music]
birthday
birthday we're only 5 days into the year
what
the days I'm excited I'm birthday
everybody make sure to mark it on your
calendar if you haven't already tomorrow
PM PST 8 PM EST yeah tomorrow tomorrow
tomorrow I'll be awake I'll be there y
can't miss out on that okay it's gonna
be
exciting well after this you guys may
have seen But Advent kimono reveals have
been delayed there after they start in
50 minutes
right also w w w they'll be matching
with us yeah their first outfit so
cool I want to see yeah they're probably
nervous it's true remember our first
reveals we we just like oh God why am I
more nervous than
theevs know I realized something
recently now it's my turn to get like a
little mushy gushy I
guess in the beginning we like we were
really didn't know we were doing like at
all it was just five of us you know like
kind of fumbling around in the dark and
trying to figure out like what what kind
of identity is Holo Yen going to have
and now that it's gotten so big right
the group has gotten so big I don't know
it is kind of like a family to be honest
I didn't like saying that before but I
do kind of get that feeling you know
it's it's expanded our our little Holan
family has expanded quite a bit and I
really appreciate all of you guys being
here beside beside me and and all the
fans of myth to kind of like grow along
with us and grow together and I don't
know I'm just I'm really thankful you
know to you guys and to the fans and and
I hope I hope we can still keep having a
great time together you know and and
just thanks for supporting us for so
long thank you thank
you thank you myth fans myth fans you
guys are the best
thank you we love you thank you for
supporting us for such a long time yeah
thank you here from the beish star from
the it's okay you're still moving on our
hearts yeah yeah oh I guess that's about
it I can't seem to send everybody to
shiori's stream but I wish I could just
go there yeah sh is she first is she
I believe shor's First
yeah all right guys you know where to go
lot of screen give them give them lots
of support I'm sure they're very very
nervous right now they look so good they
look so birthday then yeah so please
look forward to it and um yeah thank you
for watching today everybody yeah thank
you everyone hope you guys have a
wonderful rest of the morning afternoon
evening I guess we can say ultimate
ultimate okay 3 2 1
ultimate thank you bye everybody bye-bye
bye byebye
bye-bye
[Music]
bye