we're gonna make a funny pizza the other
day I saw Little Caesars is bringing out
a corn called Pizza well it turns out
that was a joke I found this fruit and a
viewer of me even tested this out
tomato sauce
now I'm gonna place
I love pineapple and pizza oh wait I
forgot the hand then we spread some more
pineapple on it I'm going to salami now
on top we add the Mortal Layla last you
drizzled it with some olive oil we don't
want the butter to mix into the pizza
after all you know we just want it on
the corn cob only post on hashtag kfb
close and five minutes
[Music]
I turned a terrible idea into a nice one
I'm gonna bite into the corn cob part
okay this is amazing I don't have any
salt but that would improve her
pineapple pizza with corn cob crust