[Music]
will never change
no one expects me to rise
[Music]
playing games
if you wake me
[Music]
later time
no one expects me to rise
[Music]
playing games
if you wish
[Music]
feels like I'm singing six feet
underground
[Music]
no one expects me to rise
thank you
bruh
bye
darling
[Music]
you I was so tired
thanks for waking up so early for us
oh yeah we're rotating and this time
it's my turn to be uh yeah lack of sleep
and early wake up hello good morning
yeah but I will follow you I will be
brain empty but
uh it will be fine
yeah
well let's do this then yeah first we
should introduce ourselves I think just
real quick yeah who we're playing hi my
name is Maury Calliope and I am playing
this beautiful being from God
um this half work Barbarian Berserker
Barbarian named Mario pay
um she loves to smash she's not really
good at words this is not so smart
[Laughter]
yeah all right sorry that my character
looks hotter than yours right I don't
know what else to say okay I've just
been traumatized because I ran and I ran
into a scene where something similar to
you was smashing and I know what you're
talking about
how about you introduce yourself
uh hello I am the I think I'm a ranger
I'm kiwawa and I don't have a POV today
but stream POV in my new album point of
view let's go
[Music]
big brain
oh yeah thank you I don't know I'll pass
it to whoever takes a pass
tired
I'm sorry
lady okay uh hi um
[Music]
right now and I'm ready to get eaten
yeah you look like breakfast yeah
your face is right where the cheeks are
yeah
um
I am playing as narissa I didn't realize
uh when we made it that everyone was
gonna name themselves silly stuff so
oops but uh I'm this very uh sexy uh
looking deepling right here I'm also uh
currently a Bard might swap over I
haven't decided yet I probably will stay
as this so maybe yeah but being a part
is so useful so far man I know I I just
look I have a plan now that I've played
through so much of the game I need an
item and I feel like it will work better
if I'm a cleric but I'm not sure we're
not we're not the experts anymore
the rest of us I think wow addictive
yeah very addicted oh my God
yeah wow well then
but we have uh after last time concluded
to you know stay together a little bit
more right yeah and to go a bit uh a
little bit slower maybe of course we
can't look at everything but at least
we'll look at things together maybe this
time yeah and Cali will take the lead
today right okay
look at what what she looks at if she
looks at a cutscene or so moriope says
team huddle team huddle get in the
circle okay he's all right huddle game
plan how are we going to do this because
because we can make it a bloodbath or we
can try and be charismatic and kind of
like snake our way in there
yeah well can we be Charisma first and
then kill them later yeah yeah we have
the option to kill them at any time so
why not go in well first so then we can
uh you know talk to their Trader and
everything yeah yeah yeah and then
bloodbath right yeah yeah exit go in
click like an arrow go in clean pull out
real bloody and it's gonna be awesome
all right so who's charismatic forward
ho I know that I am charismatic
can't be too careful
was there a druid amongst these
Intruders
can't be sure
got one of them chained up below though
are we talking about Bolo
nah volo's human Druid is halson
yeah do we want to go straight to him
and start that or do we want to look
around first maybe we should look around
a little bit yeah cause there's like a
close by Quest that says rescue Volo it
looks like it's in here I thought it was
about Volo okay oh wait it's rescue he
might he might be yes
all right I believe we take a right
all right
oh they're doing some freaky [\h__\h] over
here
all right this is dangerous music yeah
help him maybe let's help this guy oh
he's being tortured okay give you a
piece we're about to find out
but no
you gotta keep signing down no don't
whack him with yourself right
please thank you sorry for the parade
no no no no no baseball
can you please put the clothes
I don't think I will
yeah
this looks interesting let me put him
through his paces
oh Jesus use your brain worm please
brain worm you think I should
yeah isn't brainworm bad no you could
add bonuses
good that is true you don't need them
okay not not now but yeah
I'll use my my brain powers
say that again please
is that a challenge
oh what you gonna do I don't know I'm
gonna go talk to him now I want to come
take a look
peace please
now I'm really thinking about it now I
do like to smash there's no reason for
this the last thing is is
very powerful but let's see
a good one no
he changed into a bear
I don't know if he's still alive oh bear
that's all it should be easy to find
then
please yeah get me out of here I'll
think about it
keep trying you'll figure it out
wow Jesus thank you so much it will help
you it's sleight of hand pick the lock
um Good Luck oh boy can I add something
here let me help yeah yeah guidance
thanks appreciate it big up together
are you out of your mind
really gotta be like that roll again
let me oh
are you kidding me
why does God hate me
I'm gonna give this one more chance one
more wait let me let me add a bonus
wait you can add a bonus
it's fine sorry I didn't see at the
bottom whether you could add one it's
okay I I was I think I was gonna try
next time next time definitely you
willed this to happen you forced it I
sure did and now I have no inspiration
left people pay for that later but are
the Goblins not gonna notice that you
just said somebody free you're you're a
true Soul what are they gonna do
um quick question do we share
inspiration
I don't think so because inspiration
comes from me and your different goals
okay gotcha in live yeah because we get
like separate inspiration to the east
okay okay yeah
oh but huh oh it is shared apparently
yes it is but we get it from different
actions yeah very sorry for using it up
I think we should ask no it's okay in
the future I thought we had our own
inspiration to open it let's just gets
more inspired more I wanted I wanted to
let him go we really really really want
to say okay I'm inspired I just got an
inspiration
we saved him nice let's uh let's go over
in the room to the left and here's what
happened all right okay yeah yeah of
course all right let's go to the room
here
no no no no Trump to the left of where
we entered oh okay okay
let's see all right I see you're going
this way I love this guy I know me too
cool hi
that's why you guys like
that
God is here is he a companion
you recognize
this man is a follower of little it
looks like one goddess yeah he does look
like he could be one
are you also here to uh he's got nipples
prisoner yeah he does he does
these goblins seem to thrive on the
crude and primitive ew pain without
purpose is a terrible thing
wouldn't you agree
I go off I guess who invited you a
goblin
what are you gonna do exactly I wanted
to beat my ass an intimate thing and
measured you two are a match
trying to discuss such subtle too can
that happens
creatures
maybe I'm not sure give me but
that look in your eyes
something terrible has happened to you
imagine just saying that excuse me sorry
because I saw some naturally sad looking
eyes
you guys are the same
trouble
suffered in these yeah is he flirting
with me
[Music]
I guarantee you a hug is nicer than
whatever he's about to do
oh as the maiden of pain the goddess
I think most of the gods are female yeah
Serenity maybe the likes of which few
experience God is a woman I promise it's
just like she said
yes Ariana yes
I have something
Exquisite
wow Divine possibly
handle pain
what is he gonna do oh you'll see him
big space
the wall
maybe the chancla oh boy he's gonna give
you a big hug from behind
not with that
no
[Music]
no yes and what did you choose
oh we can add still
I I'm not gonna assist you in this one
my friend this is all you
know that is
yeah
Big Game of Thrones vibes
turn around
so do we get to beat him on this I need
the blessing
oh this is so wrong Daddy
[\h__\h] him I want to kill him right now
don't kill him I need him I I don't
think he needs help I think she likes
wonderful you look tired should I take
over
wonderful you want more he's so into
this
oh
yeah
I just wanted to listen hurry up man
that looks really okay that's it
[Laughter]
okay all right another net
sure
why you gotta be so freaky about it
he's like killing you
that's okay all the pain
no no no no no I'm gonna get a buff I'm
gonna get a bus proud to have served you
this penance
oh
I said hi
I feel gross inspiring
she has deemed you worthy of her
blessing
I am disgusted
you have some acid dummies
I'm getting a blessing you guys what
kind of blessing
I don't know
yes
that is so creepy
eggs
yeah so heal yourself
hit points or less you get a two plus
two bonus to attack rolls with and
wisdom saving throws for three turns
pretty good
yum
and it's permanent you never lose it let
me get a hit
okay okay
I was I I was gonna do it on my face but
I was that seems broken yeah no I've
I've never I've I've I don't know if
maybe it's a glitch if you're supposed
to lose it but I've had it forever I I
did it once and I was like hahaha and
then I was like oh this will fade and
then I was like it didn't go away
and now one went away
permanent
it's kind of cool but like Forever Until
the End of the playthrough you lose it
in act two uh-huh okay I still have it
in act two oh can we all get it so I
don't know did I ruin it for everyone
excuse me I don't want it
that's that's valid that's Fallon All
right well he doesn't seem keen on
giving it to others that's okay
it's okay I'm his favorite or something
I guess so low follow me
sorry my brain is on one piece right now
let's go he's engaged
oh wow
can we talk to him let's have a chat oh
yeah you know are you the one okay we
charge here by chance
um
it doesn't look like we can chat can we
chat with them I'm talking we could just
kill her we're talking we could just
[\h__\h] living well
that's all right well I'm trying to
listen here's the thing if yeah if we
have if we have the doors closed
they won't stop us it didn't benefit the
cat I mean
of my career
he's asking really car and Lou to unlock
herself think about it
do what your heart tells you Liara
mm-hmm
all right I'll get you out
I'll wait nicely but
please don't cut it
all right do we have what if we just
anybody have an unlocked a lot thingy
lock pick no I'm not a stealthy can we
just can we just smack the door
um I think so but we'll have to kill the
lady in here unless she left I don't
care
I'll give I'll give her a 50 uh no no no
no don't we'll kill her don't kill her
don't worry the door is closed it won't
it won't it won't make anyone angry
okay
go down
too easy
okay go for it open it up yeah yeah
I'll pick up some of these food items
for our camp
sweet potatoes
okay what now Volo come out follow us
okay you know what else oh you owe me
that's your character
I'll do one better
tell me where we can meet each other
once we slip the goblin yoke and I'll
offer much more than gold
or something no way
hey Lisa did you save him in your
playthrough I don't even I think I
accidentally skipped him oh my God how
dare you I can't take him
[Music]
a tail
it turned invisible and ran away
we're now we now have to kill everyone
let's go it'll be a pleasure
well sometimes you gotta do what you
gotta do you fight yeah exactly right
now we gotta fight nice
mm-hmm
that sounds so strong oh not the
Wardrobe
you gotta destroy those
uh let's run
let's get out of here let's just dash
out of the goblin camp
aign
yeah we need to get we need to get house
then oh so do you want us to run
no we we we won't win but we can try to
fight this
out of my way
frenzy oh you hit so hard that's so nice
yes yeah that's what I'm here for I
guess I'll just end my channel
oops
oh boy
oh man what it's a big old fight I think
the boss is here too oh yeah this is
this is just one boss so there's three
different bosses here yeah
um if we kill them we get their brain
worms
yeah brain worms and we can eat them we
gotta catch them all love that gotta
gotta gotta catch them all exactly if
anyone has AOE I feel like that would
definitely be the move here can you
please I'm sorry can you please tell me
what AOE means uh
it's like big big attack that hits
multiple people I have one of those
yeah definitely use those when they're
grouped up together
yeah only Italian
Rags Lin aggroes the entire Camp I
wonder why these guys are aggroad at us
if that's the case yum maybe they
definitely figured out we committed
murder yeah
my wolf is somehow stuck like kind of
far away can't move him I don't know why
[Music]
it's okay I have an idea whenever I get
a turn again in a million years oh he's
being attacked by the goblin oh what do
you missed no he's having his own fight
over there
which one which one let's go for this
one
did I do why did she get so close to him
nice
nice hit
so I'm gonna shoot something out and you
guys need to not walk through it or
it'll hurt you okay are you talking
about the uh daggers platter daggers
yeah so good
push people off of stuff and they'll
take damage if they fall oh yeah but if
you knock anyone into a Chasm please
know that you will not be able to
collect any of their loot ah but it is
what it is you'll have you have no spell
slot
that's it
they say I'm looking at your chat
they say you have
it's not even my turn I don't know what
that means
I
oh my God they're right it's probably oh
[\h__\h] you use them okay I have some I I
might I have an airline
yeah
and 15 damage to me
I'm sorry I'm sorry
that's pretty I saw that coming
oh oh she's okay she's okay
we can definitely kill these guys don't
even worry about it let's see are you
sure yeah yeah it should be fine not
with me almost killing Kiana shoot me
okay
like
ah
all right to get ready to feel pain
dummies
nice yeah yeah yes keep in mind we have
the boss right behind me right behind
you yeah okay
she's got 40 Health yeah she came up
pretty quick
and she's very strong
I completely cheesed that Boss by the
way before Oh I don't know oh I killed
her easily let's go
hmm
I'd like to rage they're all on the way
oh my God there's so many but I feel
like we can do it we can do it yeah
we'll see you can take them
how I believe
we'll get a ton of exp I've I blame
Volvo for this yeah
you remember his name
is her name
yeah yeah yep
she's the true Soul High Priestess of
the absolute don't take an action
yeah
kick her ass b boom yeah is that the
boss sure what's up yep
I'm still blinded Ah that's a little odd
it looks like it should be out of the
smoke poke into the dark
I want to use a spell but I don't want
to use it when I have a disadvantage
well she attacked me if I won
oh it's because you're all in this dark
a class they have a little thing poking
at you can you get out of the cloud yeah
you just have to walk but you walk
slower you're moving okay I will for now
I'll do this
oh
nice oh seven I'm sick look she's so
shocked I'll work on her for a little
bit yeah until I get out of blind
we'll cover you yeah you got you got any
uh health potions you do I'm just
waiting for my turn to do it sorry for
killing you on accident it's okay
you're so good
there you go that's not much but a
little bit Yeah on your feet
oh maybe the guy in front of you if you
can attack
I hope it doesn't matter
good job
okay
after that
dang it [\h__\h] I want to save you but I
gotta focus on frenzy and raging out
okay I'll just go back to sleep
okay you and your cute animals I'll see
you in five
oh okay
all right just sweet dreams
don't let the team be wiped don't let it
happen please no party wipe
it's fine
yeah when in doubt do it Bart dance yeah
yeah maybe the enemies will start to
like a little easier on us yeah yeah wow
this will save us not very smart
let's see what we've got here oh good
we're no longer blind yep
mmm
reaction yeah sure why not
yeah it's cool
yeah there's another one of them I loved
everywhere
[\h__\h] oh no my strength my strength has
been buffed Oh weird poison
ing
the song of my people
Let The Bodies Hit The Floor Let The
Bodies Hit The Bodies Hit The Floor only
for strength checks
it's fine I'll live okay yeah do your
best just keep fighting ladies
[Music]
kill her yeah yes that would be that
would be the move
jump I'll jump to
Chihuahua yeah
careful there's acid on the floor oh
yeah cause you turn away from him that's
why he tries to hit you there's like a
red arrow whenever you turn away from an
enemy
no you can you can do it again you can
try again if it's still
then you can you can try again
nice
that was sick
okay get her nice background
very uplifting are you kidding me that's
rough
[Music]
how high was the percentage
yeah that's not really good I've noticed
that 60 is pretty much zero in this game
can do it
Kelly focus on damage right nice
thank you
I can't heal you though it's okay sorry
if you have potions Kiara I
uh
you have one one potion yeah I should I
still can't use it I can throw one on
yeah you might use it when you're in a
turn
so
don't die
is dangerous too yeah we're all we're
not doing so hot gamers
God that feels good
okay
nah come on I'm dead again
why do they all go for me because they
know you're too strong oh
I don't think we're gonna make it
still work out for us it's just these
guys we gotta beat up
[Music]
one two three four
maybe maybe yeah
yeah I'm gonna still try to get the boss
yeah
[Music]
I'm gonna miss
What if I
jump
dang it um tried to hit you
okay nice
[Music]
please
these are the big chunk of damage into
her she's almost down yeah
and she's out of there okay so I can hit
again hopefully nice
okay
[Music]
waiting fast I must heal
um
Volo
if it weren't for us freeing you
yeah yeah honestly this is all his fault
oh his fault all of it
I feel like their attacks aren't missing
us as much as they should be yeah they
have really good RNG like we're we're
missing a lot of hits we're them hitting
everything yeah
a downed party
yeah yeah and I'm about to die
it's all up to YouTube let's go game of
the century
do we you know yeah
nice swag nice nice okay now block my
way
people are you sure about that
oh my God oh my God she survived I can't
believe I lived through that you endured
that's wild
Amore all over again okay
yeah suck on that
all right it's my turn
no it's not
wildly five dang it okay okay
probably not
where are the Heelys at
4hb and gambate
full HD in a dream stop stealing her
all right
succeeding in my death froze
I I will not die what the what
companion yeah 26 HP okay
what the [\h__\h] compare that to my one HP
wolf and spiders and all that yeah
yeah
you know now there's the others
it felt really good though for the
moment that I was able to do it
we tried we tried okay
only short rest is available
oh we are attracted we are in prison
um okay well let's get out of prison
should we short dress at least
um yeah just give us a little bit of
help I can't see anything oh okay there
we go there's a key somewhere lock pick
somewhere
[Music]
um
wait what about the way the guy jumps
ooh hey look what's in here
oh investigate let's look at the body we
can eat them
yeah investigation
I'll pull it free actually
come on out I want to see something good
comes loose revealing a tunnel
[Music]
look at that
what what happened
oh yeah oh it's okay it's okay it's okay
oh let's go
[Music]
Good Luck Good Luck now we totally got
this they took all of our weapons what
what ah yeah haven't you noticed we
don't have any weapons
somewhere listen to you
uh
no spells either
yeah they took your magic ability away
yeah can we load it can we load it can
we load a save maybe back back
when we started the Stream
no auto save nah we should I should have
been saving it
was safe it's coming today
I can do the whole is that possible in
the hole the other way
I don't see the hole anymore maybe it
was above us maybe we can use our Flair
it's it's in the little it's behind you
I can't go in though
I guess we just punched them [\h__\h] it
guys we ball we have to ball
I have some bombs uh I have no items no
actually no okay I still have I still
have some spells I guess yeah we have
nothing they literally wow
frenzy all right I'll just Frenzy
[Music]
attempt
all right let's see go away
big on arm strike maybe there's
something on here too far away
all right
the skeleton has a candle and a ring of
poison resistance but that doesn't help
right
but I was thinking maybe somewhere here
there's a weapon or so
maybe the other sacrifagos we can pick
their their weapons up if we kill them
yeah yeah so good luck guys
okay here we go the one
what's he gonna do oh no no no no
we can still do it listen
what happens if we die here again do we
just go back into prison
of course probably
um
an Armstrong
no
well well if it isn't the consequences
of my actions because I think this all
started because of me
it's all right it's
cool it happens can I throw the candle
will it will it set them on fire it says
I mean if there's stuff on the ground
like uh as you know oil then yes
okay I'll still try it even though
there's no oil
[Music]
um
55 is pretty low
I need to hold on I know I don't know
what happened yeah
yeah I mean it hit I guess
that's
um most of what I can do
oh no worries it's fine
I'm taking a nice
nice
if we loot them after murdering yeah
let's go just one yeah
the arrow would it be nice
the bow
Nani
it didn't work
everyone wanted to say both if you get
me up maybe you can use me as a weapon
yeah I could throw you yeah oh yes yes
yeah what is this combo four yeah
but if I turn around now I'm gonna get
beaten the [\h__\h] out yeah
I can run to you I guess to get
this and rage throw
leather boots
I'm sure that that would work
I wish
foreign
however however
um maybe what we could do is you know we
could just reload and then what we could
do is all the scenes that we already did
uh everyone can individually go into one
yeah so I can go do the BDSM
en killed the lady again this time yeah
yeah we haven't done much progress
anyway so yeah yeah so I say I say we
just let's just get out of here all
right
what's that scrying iron
oh it just launches and it'll it'll uh
alert people it's so cool
yeah it's like like the sauron's eye
night Warden Min pharaoh who are you uh
she's the one whose underwear we need to
steal
all righty everybody we're going back to
the game
quickly get beat yeah
yeah I'll get beat and then we'll do a
long rest and then we'll uh you guys can
free the guy while I'm doing that so you
don't have to walk yeah
oh I'm getting a splash party t-shirt
for the Bingo rewards oh congratulations
I think that's just the ones with
everybody
did you get some
of it at all no a conflict oh
this is what it is all right now let's
onward to help Zorro
it's just another picture yeah I'll take
care of the guy the guy yeah
right all right and I go to my destiny
again
is the guy the guy is not Volo right
you're not talking about Volo no not yet
no he's just a random dude
all right you you girls you girls take
care of that rescue them a shiver runs
I'll talk to one of these trackers sorry
Mom okay
let's hope you don't fail twice again
let me give you guidance
thank you
no pain no gain I've never Play No Gain
exactly
can can we we can
we still rescue Volo though without
getting in trouble yeah yeah no right
yeah
okay cool
free
I wanna say follow
you gotta save the barn
before the catch us
do you need saving no I'm good I'm good
okay
good luck dude
there's a nice looking book here
be wearing of your mortal limitations
is tempting to allow Payne's ecstasies
to sweep you away particularly during a
delicious bout of self-regulation broken
bones Hindu worship of Lara made in
those pains
so don't go too far eh don't go too far
with the pain
what do you mean broken bones hinder the
Revelation or something like that
oh I'll be fine
where'd he go flagylation
why is he running outside
he's on a mission he's looking forward
more pain
please be afraid
hello are you crying
your friend I mean guys you'd be
frightened to me
and all that and then he's scared
what a baby
I don't know okay why don't you guys
go away okay but look it was kind of
insulted by that okay go save your
little guy
Callie do a save do a save
saved oh man okay cool what a chicken oh
he's running again
[Music]
you're welcome
ran away he ran away
where did he go he literally just ran
all the way yeah
he went up an iron ladder well maybe
that was just my way of protecting you
there was something why would you do
that to me because I love you don't you
know that catch one on your own
as the symbol glow
should I should I Authority
you know wait yeah I I encountered
Raphael
Satan
oh yeah that sounds like it you do
you climbed up a ladder in my station
hold on a second dialogue
I don't know
oh I didn't realize who you was what the
[\h__\h] I'll look at this guy alone
doesn't look like Satan
not yet all yours
yay okay I got volo's key what is
maybe maybe he will give you the pain
that you need to gain
he's he's just threatening me but like
he's trying to not sound like he's
threatening me oh no oh no please no I'm
in the middle of something Raphael
laughs
where are you going
oh beautiful is this hell let's go
home can you take me too
what are you guys seeing
the house support look at uh that's a
beautiful picture oh if I go to oh
oh I see a join conversation
enjoy your supper after all oh it's mine
hey it can't be a last
no
are you not entertained
he has 666 HP yeah I told you but yeah
his wings please respond I'm gonna kill
you no you can't you don't know
devil you do
I got it
[Laughter]
potentially
an adversary
conceivably conceivably but a savior
that's for certain oh let's go oh
I don't trust him because my compassion
is bound yeah I struggle is something
something else giving Comfort please I'm
in the middle of another cut scene can
you hurry it up dire need I don't know
why we just discovered this guy two
tenants
and no solution in sight
I could fix it all like that he sounds
really compassionate
yeah
what a nice dude look at that oh cool
painting wow that is madness but a
denial of reality still
I have a feeling you'll change your mind
before it's changed for you shut up
shop around beg borrow and steal why did
this happen to me every possibility
until none why did I climb up that
ladder he heard you like evil people
whittled down tonight
I mean yeah I mean in England I'm just a
tiefling I'm not technically an infernal
you know
okay can you send me back
send me back
this is what you get for for just
looking out for the pain
I'll be around watching you squirm like
a turtle throw a knife
symptoms he's self-interested but not
even in a fun way like hysterian is they
haven't manifested yet in a bad enough
it's just annoying he doesn't even call
me darling I knew I know I'm so mad I
called him he's just so funny you
sounded so sad when in the beginning
when narissa was like I don't like this
dude you're like I thought you'd like
him so it was like no because I know
narissa I was like of course and she
didn't believe me well here we are now
where's my pain guy
set him free
hello
I'm here to finish my cutscene please
come back
ah that sucks and I didn't have to kill
her this time sorry
this is the good timeline we slipped the
goblin yolk and I'll offer much more
than gold I got to skip like the other
fruit okay that's not too bad
nice
oh okay we should long run oh you got
the pain after all girl yeah he just
like randomly actually showed up so you
can share the flag of something
hi I'll stick away the ghost is clear
yeah see you soon I simply can't wait to
pick your brain
the buff isn't really permanent anyway
it's bugged is it really uh
yeah
we can rest now he he went away yeah
this time he was really invisible I
really didn't see him yeah
let's
go to camp
do you want to end the day yeah
yeah yeah
oh and let's save
yeah
why is there a cutscene
am I okay
you're gonna transform your fingers ah
sorry people you're about to become
you're about to become um you can't be
helped mind flare we're gonna have to
kill you sorry boo the run's over for
you
your hands Shake as they reach upward
your voice
oh no oh wait wait okay
[Music]
well I thought we were pissing your
belly yeah
I can
on my team
um
I have I have persuasion I uh
use my wrist
uh guidance to
Advantage roll let's go yeah is it a bug
When the Roll doesn't show up
probably I think so
you're just gonna happen again
yes I got 24. oh all right
I cannot trust my own mind
so it stamps I must trust yours I will
wait but Marissa is lagging now because
it's above no because it's the cutscene
okay I will end up since I'm playing it
alone I turned up I forgot I turned up
everything to the map okay wait we need
to revive a story in please
but Marissa if it gets too much you have
to like restart the game maybe no I I
can I can turn it down during I mean
because there's a there's the uh leaked
the thingy the thingy leak hey
my other bearded friend it's oh my God
the guardian
the memory leak oh yes
hello
dark man Mommy
hello Mommy
wow I know your voice I've heard it
before yes you have
I saved you before
go
mother Mommy
oh she's the she's been home
can you romance Your Guardian I want to
romance my guardian you will not I know
right myself yeah
not while I'm around I'm in my guardian
so hot like I'll protect you
you seems so nice she's so pretty take
the hand off her to you
now I'm worried the Beards will entangle
I don't care
we haven't people are saying technically
you can romance them mostly technically
Yeah you sort of can there's great
potential within you it comes nice
to resist the power it gives but you
must accept it nurture it
oh I know it's like she's telling us to
wait is he actually both of us
yeah no spoilers but the the point is
they're hot yes
I don't trust them because why not
because none of the other companions
yeah yeah
I don't know so it's not really a
spoiler because I don't know but um I
don't know
I like them me too I'm willing to take
help from anyone who's willing to help
me in this game
if none of the companions are attractive
for a way that you like then you just
make one you
want let's do the words like this
I will be back
so is this some kind of dream world or
where are we
the astral plane
isn't that isn't that the place between
death and life I learned it from charms
no idea
foreign
[Music]
I guess let's see
um yeah we're going back
I'm not giving him his clothes back
either he's okay writing the balance
foreign
[Music]
he's all right
yeah he's pretty I mean he I wish he had
more of a nose but and I trust suspicion
always
apparently let's talk about something
else very well wait uh I can only say
change class I can't choose revive yeah
ah has he been dead too long go talk to
him maybe maybe somebody else talk to
him
um
why can't I ruin my sweaters there's
just so much blood everywhere
no you did it oh he's been good morning
talk to me why won't he talk to oh he's
so beaten talking to him or she's
talking to someone oh
listen I had the strangest dreams I
don't even mentioned
me protection and all sorts of delicious
[Music]
Affliction I suppose you yeah man
similar dream
you can always see the bite marks pretty
well
exactly it was rip wait
I know
even when it comes to mind a parasites
now was there anything else
the Vic lives it's big so tell I'm a
magistrate back in this one from a ttrpg
we did with myths
the vampire NPC there's always one lamb
pie you always way more annoying than
him though
the Starion is nice sir
Mama's in the camp now
you have here
I'll just make you uncomfortable weirdos
[Laughter]
is my job my friend if there's anything
in the world worth knowing
I assure you
you do be everywhere
okay uh you know what I'll talk to you
more in my private run
okay
oh should we also talk to Gail because
he has a exclamation mark Hello set him
up
Moshi okay like Gail by the way I don't
think he's we've been traveling for a
while most all the romance options are
pretty good actually I mean but I don't
have time to do runs to romance all of
them to keep quiet but it's not always
for me
I have this
yeah yeah I'm pretty sure
um
a dark leaf in my bag do I
I guess I'll try that thank you for the
offer
but the treatment for my condition is
very specific what it comes down to is
this I know I know you want the items
yeah I tried to get a whole bunch of
those and none of them were good enough
for him and he got mad and ran away what
yeah
green one yeah yeah
he just took mine but is it even worth
helping him when we're not taking him
with us anyway really
[Music]
don't worry about him no no nothing like
that maybe magic isn't a narcotic to me
it's quite literally a lifestyle
he literally he should be just taking
anything really so high yeah as long as
I literally gave him the shittiest items
challenging for us
alone look I'm trying to help you buddy
since before we were abducted
[Music]
free anyway apparently
for now for now we can let him scream or
do we do we have something green let me
see him no I don't have anything
but I'm inspiring magic
one of us might in our inventory if you
click the tabs everyone can see of the
situation it only showed mine it's okay
we can just let him squirm for a little
bit yeah
calm down from his addiction anyway
I can spare anything right now okay okay
he's desperate
he's desperate man you have to
understand oh my gosh oh [\h__\h] what will
you do force me yeah
will he rob me of nothing I'm not gonna
use my inspiration
mind you that this is not something that
can be ignored forever
to enjoy it I'm trying to help him out
here and he's like I understand he's
going through something Jesus Christ
Gail God
uh yeah okay so it's Kelly's armor and
my necklace and then uh Bijou has an oil
of accuracy or those are just uncommon
but uncommons are fine right does should
I give up my oil
I think right
oh yeah you can take the armor I'm not
using this
you can't get potions okay oh okay
you wanna yeah it has to be an artifact
what's the difference what do you mean
an artifact I just gave him random green
items
yeah that's apparently cool yeah yeah I
have a sphere that I've been using I
could give that to him no no no let's
not let's not do I mean Cali said we
could take her armor so why don't we
just take the armor
okay
Gail come on
my apologies yes yes yes yes
let me just oh
perhaps a certain parasite that's
clamped its jaws into me regardless
you're right so what happens if you
don't get focused on the real world
problems and the fantasy of an easy
solution
he dies the most gratifying to hear
take it all in enjoy it before you
glitch out more oh it's uh he reached
out his hand but nothing's happening oh
wait yeah sorry
take it take it
this time wow weird little time
[Music]
what an addict
smells like you
taste the points out but no less
dangerous
dress ravages
you're welcome I was
yeah yeah yeah I believe you uh okay
I heard this before blah blah blah I'm
sorry my tower in water D was never been
so free of clutter
sincerely where is Water Deep I
understand I ask a lot from you with few
answers in return
it's not that much all will be told
is a functional addict my lady
how grateful he's so annoying he's no
fake
Darian is obviously fake okay
I think Australian's better yeah I'm not
gonna lie let's get vampire make some
progress yeah let's let's save and make
some progress yeah let's do it okay uh
save game game is saved let's return uh
leave camp
so
so we go
how fast
follow me ladies
I wish there was an auto follow right
lazy Beach
all right
automatically gonna be chilling and
we're gonna go
Awards
yeah chilling
we're just hanging out uh and we're just
saying hello we're not doing anything
here
these dudes real quick
hey guys
and here I'm gonna start the cutscene
yep
steady three bear
s
[Music]
make it squeal again
let's see what the hell's are you doing
the Beast came in here with those
robbers killed dink means too yeah
it makes funny noises you'll make funny
noises
you're gonna make funny noises when we
kill you give me that Bijou excuse me
she's ours let him out I'll take care of
the Beast
took you a moment
easy
yeah badass yeah I know
taking something never get back no see I
knew the worm is evil now of course it
is
one that's a true Soul you're talking to
some respect
sweet mom respect
now open the cage
for the cage do it now get ready for
battle guys
uh battle we still gotta find it the
best I mean yeah look at this bear he's
like ready to tear everyone apart unless
we're friends oh we fight the bear I
thought okay the bear um leave the bear
to the Goblins Mercy we can't do that to
him let me talk to bear I have yeah can
you talk to him now
hello
are you talking to him
yeah oh I am
um oh oops sorry
I don't know how to get out
okay wait wait wait oh there's an x
button in the upper right corner okay
yay bee boots talking oh okay hello
what
I can't listen in for some reason but
it's okay it's because Cali Kelly upper
upper right corner I am using a
controller
[Laughter]
cute laugh I'm just gonna let you guys
do your try B okay let me try B B is not
working
maybe left button
all right let me go here
uh I can't choose anything else
I have a dialogue on off
trigger do you see the X
no there I'm stuck I am stuck why don't
you can't you grab your because you're
playing it on your PC anyway right yeah
put down your controller and grab your
mouse for a second and click on it
does anything happen yeah uh there's
still no X
um I think he's stuck in the dial it's
okay yeah yeah it's fine he's just
looking at me okay just let's just
attack the Goblins we'll be fine right
yeah yeah
Welcome to The High Ground Bijou
we're attacking the goblin this time
we're doing it smart
we have a bear yeah we we've got a bear
so it'll be fine yeah it'll be fine also
no spoilers but I really think I think
we can do this
should we save right now before we start
so we can at least reload from here yeah
okay I'll make a save but that yeah make
one make a new one
oh
okay
I think we'll be fine this bear seems
very powerful
that was like 90 For Real
oh nice cloud of daggers nice
I suck my eyes that's okay it it's fine
yeah it is this is it the bug because
it's like not even on the Enemy No it's
just the I just they're too far apart I
made a mistake okay I made a mistake oh
maybe we can push him into it
no they're running to get reinforcements
it'll probably summon about three more
okay uh yeah here's what it is
you want to try and dash and maybe shoot
shoot him something uh let's see
oh do your best attack nice let's
freaking go
that range
amazing
absolutely legendary
what's happening
I'm gonna go
now I'll stay on The High Ground I won't
leave yet
okay we have we have a wolf tank up here
oh and he's leaving too okay nice
[Music]
can't reach destination
Connie
funny
nice damage damn
your crab is powerful maybe the wolf oh
[Music]
attack
wow look at you
all right
symbolism
destroy them destroy destroy them
I don't know I don't know how that's
gonna go oh nice one yeah
he'll live yeah it's okay he heals
himself all the time so yeah he'll be
fine oh is that friend bear oh no not
friend yeah bear Bear's friends
maybe not yeah oh those dudes are bad
yeah
oh
um
yeah right yeah
uh-huh
I thought this don't think I'll one shot
the kid
hmm
do you have anything to slow him down or
like
hold them in place I mean I I have I
have something that I'm pretty sure
could one shot the kid but I just feels
like a waste
oh you did it you saved this from
reinforcements
[Laughter]
okay
we got a bear
hold on
I love when there's no one for me to
attack
all right I guess we're dashing yes
hold on actually I can do a ranged
attack
um
there's too much stuff in my way less
bad guys
yeah
um there's one right in front of kiwawa
then there's one right by me and then
there's the ones in the cage again okay
bonus action frenzied strike
nope too far
and rage throw
yeah yeah bro all right let's see if
only it would last bulb
that hurt everybody I wonder
nice oh they're gone all right don't
need to do anything
I'll just skip
okay
see I knew this would be crab is on its
move
bear
we love a bear a bear
oh they're running
you can't bear to lose
yes Grace let's go
shoot the grace button
I want to
[Music]
yes yes those are smart
I did a ttrpg thing yeah you did yeah
yeah you did that was pretty cool
I wish I knew like of more things that
are like possible to do because I feel
like there's so much but I just I just
don't know about it I think outside the
box right yeah
um
crab get out of the Grease
[Music]
oh I can get both of them okay here we
go
who are we beating up there's just oh I
can get these guys
do it
[Music]
what
oh those guys okay thank you again
yeah good again
way way with you I am burning
that's fine oh that's fine I need the
fire to help enragen me
you you remind me of Carla right now yes
my job you're on fire I entered
I can take both of these guys I can take
both of them
yes you can I'm no easy what
oh okay that helps
that was pretty sick
spreading even more grease a rooster
[Music]
you heard her again
well the the grease can light fire so
it's kind of dangerous to be in yeah
when my my com my friends my animals are
there I wouldn't do it now
[Music]
oh I mean he might light it on fire 25
that's what I meant does the bear have
to stay alive because he just got 25
damage nah I mean I think it's probably
five
yeah
good combo yeah nice combination
all right oh
um
snippety Snappy
low percentage not good
oh cool she's zooming that was awesome
I'm here to help go get him oh
next turn I guess
right
it's so much easier using friends
instead of the PC
mm-hmm
yeah oh the fun part about Druids is
they don't lose their actual HP when
they're in Wild shape it's a separate HP
pool
ah yeah nice broken that's why they're
they're very very good times oh we shot
glasses
[Laughter]
yeah
you
yeah sure why not
right
[Music]
okay one more left sell this stuff
behind the behind he's like behind the
banner yeah ah
ah
yeah
almost there good thing good thing we
stopped them from feeling reinforcements
nice
hello
I will start talking to you
I'm already talking to you I'm sorry
that's okay you aided a bear without
knowing if it was flipped on all the
grease a true friend of nature or
perhaps a lunatic this guy's great oh
thanks yeah I love him I am the Druid
house big nice guy
parasites in your head
you have one of them
the dialogue is the subtitles
the game's a little broken
we gotta get this thing out of my head
house and
preserve you child call him Big Papa
you're infected aren't you a wooden
hinge the Mind flesh I don't think this
is a wooden end but
something's different
you're aware of the monster inside you
you don't bow to the absolute like the
true Souls do we're special I'm a good
girl
go back to PC no leave me alone
I wouldn't want to place all my faith in
blind luck
you weren't speaking lightly when you
said you needed help
let me tell you what I know I've been
studying these parasites for a while now
ever since I discovered these so-called
true souls are infected with them
someone is using very powerful magic to
modify these tadpoles they're using them
to exert control all over the infected
I'm sorry to say I can't undo that magic
which means I can't kill you well what
did we rescue him for then put him back
into jail because he's cool yeah you can
you can go back the way
yeah maybe I found out where they come
from that must be where these
enchantments are placed on them
[Music]
so all of this was for nothing
but I know where the solution almost
certain
um better help me captives to moonrise
Towers
true Souls come out
given that all of these true souls are
infected it has to be the source for
this magic
if you want to find a cure you must head
there and discover how the tadpoles are
being manipulated
okay
I wish I could but there's still work
I've yet to finish
blood I've yet to spill let's see you're
gonna help us
together but if you could help me I'd be
free to join your journey to moonrise
Grove the natural order must be
protected all right that means you know
what that means we gotta kill everybody
okay so now we do it with his health
yeah
there are three big bosses
holding these parasites together remove
them and nature will cure itself
that'll be rough my presence could make
things more difficult I can only
restrain my bear form so much
I won't be able to okay go away attack
goblins if I join you will likely have
to slaughter this entire place
oh no
oh no yeah
we should do it okay first yeah let's
okay yeah let's let's make well do we
need
it's too short yeah because I didn't use
I only used like that one spell of your
spouse all right I'll save yeah I still
have three all right let's go rattle
them
okay who do we want to kill first is the
question I guess we won't have much of a
choice it'll just be however we pop out
right into
mm-hmm is that what's good
let's do our best let's do it
I'm picking up stamps
oh are you starting already oh yeah we
we walked right out into a fight I found
a beast monster chain that gives you
animal friendship and free potions and
one big ass potion nice an ass place too
a big ass potion
something I I want I want that
all right I already saved the game don't
worry guys yes
good don't worry
oh I'm dying
yeah it would appears so I got you one
of one of the Goblins had a stuffed bear
yeah it's freaking evil
you gotta make it pay for that
jeez oh hello oh you mean stuff like a
cute stuffed bear yeah teddy bear animal
what did you think it was a stuffed uh
Taxidermy is what I thought oh what I
like about carlax Camp is she has a
little teddy bear at it oh okay hmm
26 days isn't this the is this the place
where we were before
yeah no not bee boo yeah this is where
we were before now we're growing up okay
it's fine they can call reinforcements
we're gonna have to fight all of them
anyway
all right this is the first one oh no
not her excuse me boss so she's the one
who's underwear we need to kill yeah um
her underwear
who's gonna heal those that have fallen
down we might need to focus a little
more on healing each other yeah
yeah oh you're already dead yeah yeah
how
they hurt me
sometimes that's all I targeted her
really hard
[Music]
I'm playing music try something I'll
just push him down yeah push him yeah
nice nicely done I have The High Ground
now
um if you push them into that Chasm just
don't do it to the boss but they will
disappear so if you have that option you
should move and push them in the
direction of where you see where that
bridge is
a hole in the ground
yeah oh interesting
so apart from the boss if anyone comes
up there you should try to throw them
that direction okay okay
oh wait uh my my lupus oh
attack
um
good boy
just missing a little bit more
[Applause]
it's always that one step
oh she's teleporting oh she's gonna hold
you there
what what why is she holding me
oh that's fine I want to stay up here
anyway
but I can't take actions either
oh no you didn't
I wonder where the most likely place
can you do the lender hand or help yeah
action can you can you help me Boo and
then I can heal her
it is not my turn
it's only my turn I see
um I'm not close enough
I think
oh really yeah
come on Bagel there she go it doesn't oh
yeah it does okay cool nice
oh that's good to know then looking
super swampy right
uh I am going to
go into hiding
hide out
and I'll take care of this over here
please don't kill Houston
nice nice mess
please don't feel healthy well it's okay
we'll just go back into the house reform
uh I have to I control halson
oh really
yum
so
hey not in my turn you're not at my turn
frenzy stuff
get him
leave Allison alone
oh boy I need healing oh
that's not fantastic
that was 28 HP just gone in one go yeah
[Music]
I couldn't even make use of my high
ground
[\h__\h]
sometimes one of the Rings isn't right
about everything
I was making them up here
and blast some I really hope I can blast
them
probably you can okay oh hold first and
make attack against you critical oh
crit let's see
thank you
you remind me of Gandalf right now a
really small candle with that life not
one of them
oh
powerful she's got the power the palm
what are you gonna do what are you gonna
do what are you doing so imagine
fly away I'm coming back though
I knocked one down
I have less HP so I'm gonna die if I
stay up there that's fine that's fine
you pushed him quite far nice yeah
foreign
okie dokie
stripe on this boy
down you go oh nice nice nice
do you want me to come and help you
okay
had an attack like I don't I don't know
how you can get how you can get him yeah
I'm confused because he like doesn't he
doesn't want to attack so yeah he
doesn't want to attack
like yeah no his his attack thing wasn't
lit up I don't know what yeah like this
one
he has 38 HP you can get bring him to
save koala because
yeah yeah I mean is he tanky
should have been further away he has the
most HP tankier than we are yeah
oh boy
oh oh okay
I mean closer to us yeah maybe that's
good it'll be easier in Disguise was
that supposed to hurt me
I'm just being bullied by these enemies
today yeah it's because they're so cute
I also is up here oh she healed him [\h__\h]
24. back to full HP
they're coming down
um
I love you
that's okay we'll kill all your friends
he looks dangerous okay uh I'm going she
does we should turn down the the game
mode to easy
oh yes maybe we should yeah you can do
that mid-fight that was that was the
original plan anyway right let me see
can you do that difficulty oh she
created oh you did you do that yeah I
made her away so I can hit her stronger
next turn
the Sparks
Sparks like the Flames yes
no no we're not on easy now all right we
changed it to normal for something
so I am going for the class hide back
here for now yeah we but we can we can
always just do that randomly you know we
can just do all the fights in Easy Mode
yeah dummy oh you're running away now
haha coward
so what what do I do I finally get to do
something
[Music]
are you kidding me
so there we go can I not use nice
[Music]
um
I wanted to do it from a distance but
okay what the [\h__\h]
she's gonna push me off as a scene wait
why do I why do we have so much HP right
now I just noticed it no I turned it to
Adventurer mode
[Music]
adventurous is that even easier than
easy
maybe or is that easy that is easy yeah
let's go
hacks
it's crazy that they let you do this in
the middle of a fight right their games
are not this nice
well I gotta be so real I I'm not even
good in Easy Mode either
I don't believe that are you playing on
easy privately
are you playing on easy privately yeah
just because I'm there for the story and
for the Romancing you know oh oh it's
okay it's okay it's okay she's a really
tough boss
but I really want to steal her clothes
for me okay
oh we're having a party up here
I want to try pushing her though
[Music]
okay I'm just gonna interrupt it Target
can't be restrained does that mean she
can't be pushed
chat what do you say
try try pushing her just try it it says
targets can't be restrained it doesn't
even give me a pause
yeah because the others give me a
percentage
okay she can't be pushed ah damn it
I'll try to get closer
for now
which one of the others
or else then [\h__\h]
oh
um
oh oh I'll give her a try yeah
I'm sorry I can't I can't attack her or
she will get thrown
having a party
um
I can't I can't get up the ladder
um I'm not in front of the ladder it's
the enemy the enemy
[Music]
okay okay it's okay
not me killing Kiana multiple times
it's romantic
yeah
push you
I'm shedding dim lights oh
sparkly I'm shiny oh
[\h__\h] she gets so many moves
that's the one thing that annoys me is I
feel like I always only get one move for
everything
moves yeah yeah they get like endless
moves I'm like are you kidding me yeah
it's very silly
you found
the guys
let's go
oh what's going on yeah
I can't believe that worked oh I also
did damage 12. even though it was only
60.
do it do it wait oh oh oh let's get her
yeah yeah
[Music]
sure are
wolf will go on a trip
but like I know my issue is she kept
healing herself which can be pretty
annoying so oh
I'm dead again
it's okay the eye sees me it's okay I
don't I yeah I see him
oh no
not gonna let her get away with it
it's okay I can still shock her again
um
so calming
nice okay she's got one house on HP one
HP
and a nightmare
oh that didn't work like I thought it
would
okay good luck when I'm alive again well
since when who helped me out here me oh
I don't want you to not have fun playing
we're all in this together I was just
chilling
thank you can you kill the eye if you
get a chance so it'll stop calling
reinforcement I currently
whenever I will try
don't shove her don't I mean you
probably could you could because she's
not as long as it's not in the direction
of the chasm
one
anyway but I'll try Target can't be oh
she can't be shoved oh okay can you hit
her
no
oh
something something to her
oh hey let's go you can do
what
no don't always push me no more
reinforcements please no wait
I leave Allison alone man you're so mean
it's okay we almost got it
you missed this time die
nice nice yeah
yeah hell yeah
he said friendly strike on this dude
okay
I won't take her underwear you can have
that no no I think I think we have to
pick up her body and take it back to
Camp to get her underwear oh but her
body won't be spawned I have her clothes
right here you have her closer right
no I'm talking about her underwear oh
okay I'll take her stuff anyway yeah go
ahead take her take all of her stuff
because I mean we all shared the
inventory so yeah yeah but I'm going to
just be aware I'm going to steal it from
here
she's in her underwear now I can do her
oh my God hold on
she's just hanging there looking pretty
oh
different color variation cute oh that's
cute yeah
appreciating the beautiful things in
life I cannot house in my way if there's
not much I can do there's a spider's
liar do you want the spiders liar you
you need to keep that it's a quest item
we'll need it later
mm-hmm
wakey wakey oh thank you
[Applause]
I feel like me dying all the time today
is just a reflection of my real self
from behind the computer right now
oh
meow meow meow okay so there's just the
two guys left the one who's hiding out
like a big baby and or do we just have
one he's all the way he's running
through the door there's just one guy
okay oh yeah okay yeah it's the traffic
okay
um
look at this close at hand yeah I'm
right here I'll stay here I can't detect
anything right yeah that's good
huh yeah
throw the Shelf though through the Shelf
come on it's not fair but I believe it
that is interrupted
[Music]
okay
okay is he dead no
he's got one Health left interesting
thank you
so we gotta be careful hey wait can
anyone pick up her body and fit it into
their inventory her whole body yeah you
need to pick up
I can't pick her up she's too heavy oh
wow I love how she's hanging off the
side all dramatic like oh that's good
that looks like somebody's mixtape cover
let's go yeah right
how do I pick up her body I'm in a cut
scene
um you should be able to right click on
it and then
I think I'm stealing I'm stealing her
click pick up I think I'm stealing her
dad home I'm holding her now yay rip it
out oh she's so is he still underwear
yeah you know no we can take her back to
camp and steal her underwear
okay should we go back to camp
wait I'm in a cutscene
I'm getting
ready
but I was already in the cutscene so
trophy that looks tasty let me just put
it in my pocket
[Music]
nice
you should have picked like uh a few or
at least one up off of her no from her
inventory
yeah did I or I mean I don't know if
it's because it's the first one if it's
doing it like this
I think I'm forced to consume the
tadpole eat it sorry consume I will
consume
um I like in my private run I like to
corrupt Astorian in his brain only so I
give him all the tadpoles oh
okay item received mind flare specimen
the climb the ladder is so funny
I'm just gonna really quickly check
through the
sarcophagus oh yeah there's a bunch of
stuff everywhere so okay
okay thank you for picking up her body
yeah
yeah that was like on uh over where Min
flower originally was there's a gilded
chest that's like yeah can we take this
is it gonna um
because there's no one here they can't
see it so you should be able to take it
just fine
what's in there I'm away now I love that
wolf climbing on the ladder there's some
shoes you can check in my inventory if
you want if any of it interests you oh
shoes
pretty water sparkers
oh but this is maybe something for Bijou
because it says free lightning charges
where if when the wearer stands in water
during combat it becomes electrified if
the wearer starts to turn on an
electrified surface they gain free
lightning yay take it from my inventory
it's yours okay let's save it
save all right next box I'm saved next
bus
we already did I think oh we do need to
already have uh uh no I think with
Freddie do they do they do more damage
as well
oh this is good use these shoes the
ragslyn guy is pretty tough but if we go
up to the rafters then we push them well
the boots of striding it helps
concentrations and spells I got them
nice okay well we're probably gonna be
doing the Priestess first uh it depends
where we go so we can either turn right
and then we go into the guy and we can
fight him and the nice thing is once we
kill him there's a treasure Trove from a
key we can take off of him but there's a
lot of people in that room and it's kind
of difficult alternatively we can go and
do the Priestess and clear the front
area that we were doing before out
um honestly I thought that that fight
was easier than fighting him so we might
want to uh since we've saved we might
want to go do this first and then long
rest
I have no spells do we how many because
I don't know how our camp supplies are
looking uh I got one from the lady
but it's probably fine we can do a long
rest
okay
okay sorry goodbye Houston okay go to
camp
where are you going we have worked
99 of cases long rest do not affect
missions
are you mad at me
[Music]
go to sleep I know
I'll get all right you better not
nice outfit Marissa thanks oh wow oh we
need to drop her body okay
okay I'll drop her right here
[Music]
I can see your bones
oh okay there you go oh wait
chat how do we steal our underwear I
don't think we can
you can you definitely can I don't know
if maybe it needs to be done when she's
in your inventory
eh revive her revive her
how do we still
we're under
General it's okay you can have mine okay
you could okay I want I want her
but okay Cali put the body in your
inventory again all right hold on just
give me a sec
okay yeah yeah yeah
all right let's stop doing that stop
stop crouching stuff at least has got
side boob
a very strong case of side boob
all right it's the sign booby
we have to we have to raise her no no no
no no I don't believe that
I'm pretty sure you can put it put it in
your inventory and then like can you go
through inventory let me see uh
or maybe maybe I can also do it from
your inventory actions
I don't know how to do it though
[Music]
I dropped her
okay hold on let me see
how are you gonna do it
she can't be resurrected yeah she's not
she's not on our team oh but you should
be able to take it you have to normally
they say and we did not know
oh wait that's when Callie put her in
your inventory all right
go and then click on your underwear slot
can you put her underwear on from the
underwear slot well let's take a look
my under uh underwear slot I have no
such thing
uh it's yeah it's on the right side
right below your travel clothes you do
below your shoes
oh I didn't know those were underwear
yeah myntra's underwear yeah there you
go yeah
I put it on all right they're on do I
toggle okay no I'm going yeah now move
them to your inventory
I'm figuring this out of butt there uh
yeah I guess that we hold on
put your clothes back
okay I'm gone
okay move
Mario is a exhibitionist he looks great
in those actually all right hold this
looks like it's like a she looks great
in anything pop star outfit all right
hold on I'm figuring out how to do this
sorry for the weight I just uh yes okay
all right so take these put your clothes
back on first okay yeah yeah of course
of course that would be okay
did I flash you
um
no it's not the nudity was off but it's
like you know it's still jump scare
really okay where has Lee are you
kidding me okay oh there's no way I have
nudity on
the ax covered it wait I don't have it
on either but apparently apparently your
ass showed but I definitely have it on
no no if you have if you have the
annuity filter on it filters like
nipples and apply the parts but it still
shows your butt it's gonna be fine don't
worry okay if Polo summer survives
YouTube then we survive YouTube I think
there was a belief okay there's a leaf
on there gosh never mind
underwear where did it go because I yeah
I think it's is it still how do how do I
do that because only I can it looks like
only I can choose to equip it or not
equip it yeah well okay drag it into
your inventory yeah yeah
10 minutes not letting me
all right you don't understand
when you have
have her underwear equipped add to wear
it
it's equipped I've equipped it okay now
drag the underwear let me just use a
mouse
you're good
very amused
hold on I'm let me just oh my God okay
how do I open the inventory cam
oh okay tab there's here it is I now put
it in my inventory there you go okay and
then the rest it can take it right
thank you
thank you so much for um doing this for
me
I need to put in my inventory first yeah
thank you all right now okay okay
at least I'm wearing yours now that's
all yours take your let me see it I want
to see how it looks on you oh okay oh my
God
I wear koalas then
look at that oh you don't like your
black you're with the cold blousers
Bloomers that's a Bloomers Bloomers I
guess I guess I should take my clothes
off too huh oh yes please save by the
way okay yeah
pretty bloomers
okay
how things are so shall we move on and
kill the next boss we are going yeah we
probably we probably should sleep long
long rest and you know
you gotta sleep
oh sleep
sleep
Supply pack
ing
don't do that to me
twerk for me boy oh what's happening
sir mommy again I promised I'd be back
Guardian it's your boy
don't worry
I have things under control
for now leave you I see you've been
using the powers the tadpole gives you
good um
to draw it as powerful as halsin might
be able to remove your tadpole
but he couldn't I couldn't desperate to
be rid of it disappointed
you're looking for Solutions places
until the source of the tadpole's magic
any attempt to remove it will kill you
there must be some
ways Beyond healers the parasites are
merely a symptom of a greater sickness
in faerun
this is so interesting hearing it
hearing the different uh perspective
because in my in my regular one it's a
it's a girl
some that benefit most that harm
but most importantly this enables the
host to be connected
the infected hear the voice of the
absolute and believe it to be a god
that is how the cult of the absolute is
spreading the highest of their rank are
called true Souls they carry a tadpole
just like yours sorry that's how they
receive their orders it is what makes
them obey okay and the order to
transform is given it will not be a
matter of days there will be mind
players in an instant
worried not for my protection so would
you
interesting Who Who Are You complicated
but I'm an adventurer just like Leo's
eyes are kind of Freaky Just Like You
crazy parasite
just like you
seek to be free of it
um I've been trying to escape from this
evil
once
I've been given a new chance
you can go where I cannot and I can
protect you from that evil with some
casual Dad if we work together
okay health
they need me
[Music]
trust her
the power I used
why am I clothed in my dreams but no
clothes in real life
but sooner or later I will be worn down
[Music]
are you girls still listening too yeah
yeah okay I just finished use the powers
yeah my guardian wants me to use the
powers
go
go she's not telling me dad depends on
it
she says go to moonrise Towers
we gotta go yes we're going some of your
companions remain deep in their Slumber
oh sorry I'm sleepy
future me talks a lot okay in the same
in clothing
okay I'm done
oh look at that
this is
it by the campfire nice oh ladies girl
sleepover
oh okay yeah
cute
they take your clothes back off get back
to how you look
does the Canon look for my character it
is I I only see you with the underwear
all the time yeah in my mind this is
your outfit yeah
I don't need armor clothes on me
a moment
let's go leave the camp
us
party time all right house where are we
going
all right yeah who do we want to do do
we want to go do the easier fight that
we lost at or should we save real quick
oh safe
and easy yeah easy so I I here's the
Strat okay
um yeah so on the right side when you
cross the cross right
um and then start going to uh if you're
looking straight across the bridge the
left there's that little entrance right
but you might realize in the corner by
that door there's also a ladder uh Kiara
it might be good for you to get up there
so you can do uh can you put a pointer
there I don't know which letter you mean
um
I can walk over there but it might
trigger the fight
well they're not so I figured honest yet
I don't think right
um he's gonna do what he wants but if
you climb up there then
um it it might be good for you to do
rain shots
um and then me Kelly and Bijou do rain
shots too
I'll stay up here oh it has commenced
the battle hold on he found us we'll
take him out really quick
eh why don't I have
oh no is it the armor I can't reach that
enemy from here uh wait no wait never
mind I can I think I can yeah we're even
where even is we just have one enemy
where are they
I guess we just killed this one we don't
kill him he might go tell us he's dead
okay good
hey wait apparently I can't wear this
armor because I can't cast spells and
that is honestly the most devastating is
that the issue I don't
know if you want I have no idea wait I
still don't uh
I still don't have the ability to even
after I take it off why aren't my spells
working
yeah
full that's really weird oh my God it's
the boots okay I can't wear the boots
sorry
[Music]
okay we'll do we'll do it later okay
anyways are we ready to should we Brave
since we just killed one random guy
oh yeah
take it from my inventory
yeah well we're we're gonna yeah we're
do we're gonna do the same people I mean
if you wanted we could turn over to the
right and quick kill off these three
people because that will probably
prevent um everyone else from getting oh
okay uh like over here where that guy
came from one second don't do it don't
go anywhere yet oh over there yeah yeah
I'll kill the chest oh Scroll of
stinking clouds
thoughts and scroll of cloud of daggers
nice nice scroll that's a good one I'm
coming back yeah but here's the issue we
need to close this door
um door
wait
what question is how
son don't you [\h__\h] this up yeah you know
he's not hiding
okay
okay cool I have The High Ground okay
um I don't know where you are yep let's
kill him
right
destroy
let's do one more time
move
um
[Music]
what does that even mean
uh my English not as good as your
English you must explain to me I I don't
know so you were asking the wrong person
I am only the number one myth speaker of
English so nice okay all right
um
why don't you talk to this little Goblin
that's in the in the cage you can talk
to him you'll have a little chat
hey little dude talk right
praise his throne of flaming iron
a tyrannical religion
annoyed followers or slaves I've heard
of that before
heck yeah
no I'm not as doomless as the rest of
them says you in the cage how do you
how'd you land yourself in that cage
uh formless I'm not the one behind bars
dummy yeah I get them yeah and be
wishing you
you end up being supper for the spiders
or the wolves
wow
spiders and works and nothing more
you'll be defend more self you wouldn't
be looking around in here at all they've
all gone by me brain isn't exactly my
thing buddy muscles
yeah your guy doesn't care about you
to this absolute I say products to you I
said
isn't that interesting he he doesn't
like the absolute
oh yeah yeah you can kill him yeah why
not
we should have a health bar on it right
wow oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
oh good okay there's three goblins in
here oops oh that's on me they saw us
in it's okay
he died
uh should we how do we should we eat
hold on what's going on over here
[Music]
um
Hara
I guess we gotta go down I think oh no
wait we can uh helson can probably
handle this if you just if you just want
to I'll just fill one out there's a
ceiling yeah just Skip it's fine
but then we if we can just do this after
maybe yeah
we can do maybe afterwards we can go
there
all right how's it going here
I wish I knocked him out of the cage
chat
I wish
it's fine though oh nice
or not really
got me missing I suck
skip your turns
please
I got nothing to skip
they're so far they are
why am I missing every hit
uh
nice
[Music]
you have to end it bear okay
and your turn
is ended mine's ended too
Chihuahua is it is it worth dashing over
there no no just don't worry about it
I'll do it I'll handle it no I'll join
you
this is ain't hell
finish it off please
my beloved Senpai coming to my rescue
mental support
oh wow see I really was only there for
mental support yeah I was here yeah why
not I want to talk to this rat hello
what's in here yummy things
oh wait
so sweet
oh we should save sorry save's coming
that's okay
you guys want to do a short rest or are
you good uh short short rest maybe for
me my house halfway down I do better
find somewhere to come soon oh the rat
does not do anything
we're good
okay wait wait wait wait stop
I'll do it God okay okay let's let's
prepare for battle I'm going up high
again yeah yeah go go up
me too
oh
and then when you guys are up me and
Cali will run out there and
let me know when you guys are in
position the middle room
you guys could shoot a random shot at
someone well I'm gonna try to shoot the
boss if that's okay yeah which one is it
oops he's got
um yeah I got yeah okay hold on let me
give me a second to set up hopefully
they won't notice water on them I'm just
hoping they don't notice Allison he's
not he's just standing in the doorway
he's a little loud there
okay it's raining so weird why is it
raining in here
I don't give us a good question
oh boy
oh
okay I missed
oh my god well it didn't aggro them so
you could try it for you guys oh we
gotta help
let's go let's do this let's get in here
and then
where is she
nice chill for now
Allison why are you chilling join the
fight get in here bear
I killed him nice nice that was fast
nice yeah okay
great
um we'll they'll get reinforcements if
one of them can ring one of the drums so
we just need to try and kill them as
fast as possible and we'll have less to
worry about
or destroy the drums
[Music]
yeah you could destroy the ground well
actually there's nobody around that area
so never mind yeah
but they'll run to it sure will they're
fast they're speedy
oh
um oh no ow I can't even see up there oh
boy wow
oh that was painful on there
oh Lord he coming I'll be fine
oh man
foreign
[Music]
oof
[Applause]
you little [\h__\h]
how do they should shouldn't they be in
a disadvantage shooting from down down
there how do they get you you think you
think right right that's what I wonder
too
every day of my life
yes kill that one he's probably going
for the drum ah come here
you're gonna have to fight me if you try
to run away
uh this little guy down here but just
focus on whoever whoever you can reach
yeah
yeah like uh I can read that warlock
grease warlock grease is a kind of High
Health ish okay warlock
he's over yeah yeah
boom baby
you broke him
perfect
what who's next
the evil guys
oh am I so far away oh nice
okay where are the rest of them
[Music]
okay I'll try to kill the warlock Greece
freaking go
oh there's one down
all right nice nice nice
[Music]
um
they're all like on the left side I
think right favorite like by Bieber
bye get them oh no you're so close it's
okay
very close very close
can't breach
bro
I push him
you are too weak to push that one I have
a noodle arms borax
I wish there was a way to Ping I'd
really appreciate being able to Ping
things
look what I mean pink so I can be like
oh they're here here and here you know
instead of being like yeah there's some
around
oh you can though if you mean just
marking something on the map
oh I mean like exact location
yeah I can leave
hey trying to push me too I'll show you
oh right click no you can
looks like all right click on the map
or something like that yeah that's what
I'm being told
yeah somebody marked something on the
map
why do I always do
oh
where are
your enemies oh there's one see
thank you I was blind and you helped me
um
nice
let's go another one in the bag
[Music]
totally clear how do I clear this Bell
do we just have to wait for it to run
out
so we can get the body loot from True
Soul guts I said parasite
um is there anything on the side like
the
right side of your bar that has the same
symbol
I found 183 gold you just get away
get the bag
yep it goes away eventually raid raid
other stuff in the meantime
there's lots of dead people around here
Here Comes the Money
have you seen that how's that go there
it is it's gone
okay
time to get another brain worm does
anyone want to eat it or do you who
who's against the brain worms here
brainworm
okay so here's what you're gonna do
click on your little inventory and
equipment there will be an lithid Powers
manage experiences and you can pick
where you want to go fast too fast too
fast inventory inventory look in the in
the top middle you see how there's the
four different uh equipment spell book
Alchemy and lifted powers
like a lithid powers
uh uh uh wait it's in the right
no no no you don't need you just in the
top one it's it's the fourth option
okay and then manage experiences and you
can just read about it and pick where
you want to put it oh wow yeah
which one did you choose
I do I have a so we all share we share
them we share them we all so I ate one
because I'm selfish
yeah
yeah I don't know which one to choose
um whatever would make you happiest
just whatever sounds like it it'd be
helpful to you ah concentrate okay thank
you chant
where do I put it
I haven't just pick it up and you put it
over the one that you want and then drop
it or you can click on disgusting okay
thank you oh so like consumers one okay
yeah
okay cool should we do another short
rest I can do it yeah
oh this is the hard fight so I don't
know if we want a long rest before it
actually
um
I don't even know how to see how many
spells I have left to be honest you see
the squares like oh yeah yeah it's the
squares I think it'd be a good idea to
fight up in the rafters and I think we
all should be in the rafters so that he
feels like he has to go onto the rafters
and then we push him off
Oh you mean so uh go up yeah
yeah good luck
I can carry him on my back we love love
yeah I haven't had a level up in a while
what the hell soon hopefully
gotta go all the way up come on
oh my God house and just turn into a
human why do you gotta make life so hard
and he said he's gonna bear it has a
bear before I know and now he's like no
can't get there
yum
jump okay
so um
let's see where are you guys you loot
this chest already
yes
it was just some silver trays um
after we do this there will be a room
from the Priestess that we can go into
yup
um and unlock yeah Cali knows uh this is
too high for all of us we can't get
there can you bless us with jump Powers
um what Kelly can you eat me oh yeah
that's too high for you girl yeah I'm
short only for Basil right narissa can
get up right no I I apparently not but I
was able to get up let me see you're so
special you bet bro
all right let me see I bet I can throw
all y'all wait why do I have to choose
an item
is it help
throw I I want to throw a person
improvised melee weapon
it's not letting me choose you it's
weird
let's see if you right click on my name
does it say thrall just use throw it
says okay just use throw and then it
won't let me choose the current screen
all right well
if y'all teach me how to use the
keyboard tell me what I have to click oh
my God just click me okay
it's West to move around and then q and
E to move the screen around all right
I'm clicking on you and then your mouse
all right throw
wait throw first there you go yeah get
up there
[Applause]
you want to be thrown okay my turn can
you throw me bro
looks like you're a little too big for
me
okay it's okay me and me and halson will
just um
we'll find we'll figure something out
um halson maybe is not good here so I'm
gonna just move him to the ground level
okey-dokey um so maybe don't start the
fight yet
um
there's a ladder down there that you can
eventually climb up if you want
yeah we'll get there yeah
first I need to just get house and back
on the ground so he's not useless in the
fight I'm gonna drop these uh these fire
things on them
yes goons below
Allison got no chill try setting up
again
yeah okay okay halson's at the door so
um I'm I don't want to open it I guess I
can since I'm human house and I can
sneak it open
okay let me know when you guys are ready
wait I'm almost ready almost ready one
sorry one more moment okay almost there
I just need to remember how to turn him
back into a bear
oh
hell we'll do it later okay let's let's
begin okay
who is that guy
nice
a stinky cloud
stinky Cloud yeah
nice time to fire the arrows or throw
axes throw axes
bro
well they're nice yeah they won't be
able to take action for a little bit
I'm gonna throw a goblin Scimitar at him
ah
yeah nice let's freaking go
[Music]
thanks Bill
I have to get on the ground too I'm not
even close enough to be in the fight oh
my God he's almost gone he's almost dead
yeah he's almost dead already
let's go easy
all right
um
almost threw my main weapon but I had a
Moment of clarity
hmm
sometimes that's just how it goes you
know
guys
he died
nice nice wow that was that was real
good
oh I didn't finish my turn I'm so sorry
everyone didn't mean to keep you waiting
yeah yeah
oh he's just running away
nauseous oh he's only a free HP okay
wow
[Music]
sometimes I get lucky wolf is stuck
outside oh
God oh maybe oh can he goes open doors
not that one I'll go to the other one
maybe I'll reach someday oh no the war
drum
uh it's okay are there even any more we
killed we killed everyone yeah I think
you go ahead and drum those beats yeah
nobody's coming to help you yeah
yeah prove that
yeah yeah wilding out
oh that's you sorry
I was thinking of attacking you for a
second
oh
I'm gonna throw nice
who did that hit
um
interrupted he's got three Health left
someone please take him down
go Bird go
whoa birdie time
okay die
what okay
I didn't even see that dude there
yeah he's successfully hiding
The Misfortune oh great oh angry a
little bit late for that
oh I totally didn't see that that was
him he was in the shadows
wait run through the uh let's run
through the desk please he was so close
it's fine but before anyone heals him
angry
oh
gotta break their concentration
ouch
he's on our team yeah we stole our kills
let me do bear again I want to be a man
a man bear
all right oh I want to throw okay only
three left not bad
yeah we're doing really good now that we
turned on easy mode
no no we're still totally on normal what
are you talking about yeah we totally
around normal
um
half is interrupted all right let me
move a little bit
if I move here
kill him
all right where's the other one where's
the other I only see one guy there's one
next to bear and one next to bird oh
that dude half is interrupted yeah you
got me [\h__\h] is it the cloud still I
think so
oh what am I supposed to
you'll just have to wait till next turn
that's how the cookie crumbles sometimes
calliope
who's Calliope
you haven't heard that one in a while
please
Marie wow
we both Miss
Cali I can't believe that caliope
cantaloupe
whoa
oh look he's still he's he's trying his
best oh no he's so cute he's arriving
soon
okay nice all right dead nice okay one
more
actually hits this time
okay
let's take a look
he's very happy
level four yes man get back to The Grove
selective feet
uh there's so many there's like a
million uh oh there we go
do I choose I know a lot of these let me
see which one I want for this
wait oh no
uh
Sharpshooter thing you call it oh okay
there we go okay
numbers
for throw damage maybe next time
now a team that we have oh yeah
so anyway
additional 10 damage but it gives me a
penalty okay
okay yeah
Supply pack
yay we need that
I could use that okay
just take all because you know what we
can always sell it later yeah
okay do you guys uh let me know when
you're done in here and then I'm Gonna
Make You Follow Me
I'm the queen now bow to me kneel to me
I'm on the throne that honestly it looks
like yeah not like that I'm from but
some of you some kind of prone from Game
of Thrones that's definitely that's
definitely a throne a throne of all time
can I take it home
no
sad
I guess I'll I'll stay with my
what's it called again
the fancy chair
the expensive office chair oh Herman
Miller yes I love it
potatoes there's so many potatoes
and garlic and carrots
oh I can level up
careful
oh hey
we cleared this whole thing now
yeah
no noise
only took us about three hours
hey you know
it can take a lot of time yeah
so that's not that's not all that bad
it's about as much time as like ttrpgs
take I guess yeah
I didn't see anything in that one it's
in my inventory oh inventory yeah we all
share inventory though so it's like a
long different again
oh those other clothes were her at East
clubs oh you're covering it up you're
covering up the good stuff
I know how could I am
as well when the wearer dashes or takes
a similar action during combat they gain
momentum oh this guy has some cool stuff
too I will put into the inventory
rings and stuff
hmm
saloons
chosen amulet and I twin magic Missile
thing
I was asking out loud
why strength because I want strength
don't complain this is my run not yours
sorry my chat's bullying me because I I
went with i i leveled up
I leveled up and I didn't do what they
wanted
okay okay
except
I think I'm leveling
I just want to hit
I took the shield and the boots out of
your inventory yeah what you mean
and then follow me okay I'll follow
Marissa okay where's Marissa uh I'm at
the door that we entered in well that I
entered in
we have one more fight we're not done
here oh we're not done no oh okay
are we not like taking
his body you don't you're not interested
in his clothes
no
I mean if you want them
everywhere oh that's a bit early I'm so
far yeah I mean this isn't this isn't
the fight but I don't know what happened
no we're just gonna uh these must just
be guards that missed out the first time
yeah
okay okay
they're they're sad they're like huh
what do you think you can get the fight
there's only three of them yeah
there's an Archer
over there
[Music]
oh Kelly dodging everything
how masterful
slow motion
[Music]
nice one let's go let's go can I reach
from here oh I can but 50 percent
it's not gonna make it what's that noise
hmm there's like a banging noise
not here too
don't tell me okay
I hear like wood banging like something
banging on wood oh
does it have a rhythm a consistent
rhythm
I don't know it just sounds like banging
on wood not the ogres again
are they playing their game again
I guess
now this is just a game I can't complain
I don't want to say oh
I don't hear the banging where are you
hearing us banging it's almost your
heads off now oh okay maybe you have a
headache
and then follow me over here
foreign
[Music]
drop them
oh okay okay
anyway follow me yeah get rid of him he
was still here
that's so funny
aligned with the goblins okay we're
gonna have a giant lady to kill in a bit
but feel free to loot this room first ah
she ain't [\h__\h]
right huh
people where are you
my screen oh my God is this the the
sound that she was hearing yeah oh my
God it's a bug yeah there's big wood
flying around back and forth
what what the hell what is that
what yes
you're crazy
and not just ogres doing their thing
again
I am happy
all right coming through the door I went
into okay and be ready it's already in
use hello defile Temple why is your
attitude
what is it's a big lady oh I'm going up
here
hello
oh my God
she looks familiar yeah doesn't she
your drama
Sharpshooters
nice nice
ma'am oh well if he finally gets a bite
and he misses
no no don't hurt lupus
oh you're gonna pay you are so gonna pay
don't hurt anything
animal is friends I love you just for
fun
not too heavy to shove all right
people your turn
it won't let me cast a spell
[Music]
I have a spell
oh
ah okay that's how you do it
um
I feel bad for ganging up on her yeah no
she deserves it
oh wow wow what are these what are these
things that my character is saying
I don't know cool bar disses
[Music]
all right and with that we've actually
cleared everything out that we can hear
him yay um yeah now we can just look for
stuff or loot
yeah I mean we could go and see see how
the thing resolves in the uh yeah all
the camp okay um
huh
ooh what'd you get that's just some a
little bit of gold I know useless
necklace
I also picked up the scroll of Mel's
acid Arrow so I can throw an acid Arrow
do you mean acid
oh here are you afraid to say ass
no yeah
ass ass domination
awesome
don't we all it's all right
oh okay nice
nice nice
so do we teleport out or do we walk out
we could teleport where does this go eh
wait follow me
I solved it he doesn't do anything wait
what's this puzzle are you sure you
spelled it correctly
now
[Music]
let me solve the puzzle
okay wait where did I come in from here
oh look
wait wait where did I come in where did
we enter from I need someone with strong
strength with me for a second
Cali has that
follow me for a second yeah well well
Norris is doing that puzzle okay
puzzle puzzle
what do you think this uh what do you
think never said what's happening here
can you go in here um we need to match
up things
you know I can't fit in there but can
you people oh you can't fit in here no I
can't thank God I'm not the puzzling
person you went inside oh can I move
stuff oh I oh never mind oh nice one
people
she did it come on let's go
oh hold on hold on okay we're waiting
we're holding we're holding
come on
well I opened the door so now there's a
chest that we can get maybe oh nice oh I
don't know where you are no I said
though I pulled a lever
um
I don't know there's a lever yes
yes
try try it
is it traffic
was it okay close do the lever again
it's a lever for the door once you solve
the puzzle
oh yeah nice okay okay
I found 254 gold okay
more money
this leads down to a ladder
let me go through the door yeah yeah
save save Kelly did you go here huh
did you go here oh there's no dialogue
now I think that I thought the puzzle
was what not what it was before
I thought you had to have all the black
circles in the middle but it looks like
a scared no this ladder is so long you
look very frightened
oh
oh whoa what's up here
Saloon night Outpost oh
whoa what's this
Holy Night
whoa and the Gilded chest
oh wow a waypoint
oh
wow where are we
we're in the underdark it looks like
under dark oh yeah the other pathway
Point says I think that's the other path
that you can take okay can I press it
yes
oh I opened the gate hey wait no no no
no no no no no no oh don't do anything
don't do anything don't do anything
don't move
oh boy
that's rough
what's happening two minutes over here
oh hey cute did he just come from World
of Warcraft or what yeah
nice
well
too close again and that's so strong
close the gate close the gate
hey everybody's almost dead we can save
him
yeah we can take him through here
can you yeah I think I can Cali already
saved shut up I already saved never be
saved you guys could come up to where I
am oops
why why is nothing happening oh my God
oh he's angry that's fine he's mad let
him be mad
be angry see look it's because that'll
kill him if he stuck
huh okay easy enough nice okay now you
can open it
oh oh wait but we might not want to move
through there because of that so let me
just
what does he have
I want to check this
oh whoa open lock Peak
um 20 20.
oh 20 what
I can't get a 20. what the [\h__\h]
wait can I ask you how was that attitude
Kiara
um
I'll roll again one time only I'll just
try one more time there's treasure in
there
ah so close 18 out of 20. oh I see
that's cool
um
I don't know if I should try again we
have no lock pick available
[Music]
come on come on it's gonna be even worse
probably
ah man
yeah I'll give up
let me try
ah
fly fly I mean you could try to break
through the door too no I can't I can't
wait nice nice
yeah wait
here let me try
where are you oh you're over here okay
I will try medium toughness oh medium
toughness I feel like
that
let's give it a shot
I was able to break for something like
that with with Carla what is that hand
and where do you want me to throw you
um hold on
night pink
up there there you can't just take oh
nice idea actually hold on I see
okay hold on create a ladder to the
ledge with the chest and the one with
the highest ramp can jump over it
a ladder to the ledge with the chest how
do we create a ladder
path is interrupted
oh wait hold on
it might be possible 22 damage to break
the game
there you go
[Music]
let's freaking go
like dead what's inside what's inside
get the chest oh it's locked
up
if you have him
yeah
I need to get a 15 and let me add my
guidance
it's worth it
you should use inspiration to do it ah
you can use this yeah yeah you
definitely should use an inspiration you
haven't been really using it too much
ah no fuzzy
okay one more time yeah yeah
can you put it in your pocket and take
it out and then we can just look at into
it later too if we can't get it open
right now if I if this one doesn't work
outside let's see
let's go oh it's a helmet of smiting oh
um maybe Cali can have it yeah oh okay
if it helps myself that might be good
when you only need something with one of
your Smite spells what's a Smite spell
might spell I don't think I have any
spells
um would not be good for me I love it
one of your Smite spell
oh it's for paladins oh we can sell it
for money yeah yeah that's good yeah
money is good
or we feed it to Gail yeah we're not
feeding it together
um should we go to the Grove and see how
that resolves yeah oh yeah sure
yeah we uh the way we are I got the
Waypoint I don't know if everyone needs
to get it I can't leave
um
because I can't I can't jump out of this
okay I don't think
I went to the emerald Grove okay uh so
yeah
um
on my way
fresh air
[Music]
need a shower
I'll take a bath oh remember this place
good memories yeah yeah
there's still the blood there too
yeah beautiful
oh yeah what will or whatever you still
won't join our team yeah oh well he
joined my team here oh will oh well
everybody's so happy looking I'm in a
cutscene yay oh
they're giving us some money
you can keep your clothes I guess
we're taking the money
do a nice thing he returned just a while
ago
we are not nice here
that's right yeah we did something big
we can't be doing this for free
otherwise everybody expects us to do it
for free yeah
they're gonna celebrate so um let's go
see what's happening with kaga though
you know
I'm inspired
[Music]
and we don't sell any any of the stuff
that we found yes I hate that he only
takes one person at a time what the [\h__\h]
I know yeah that is pretty annoying but
there's a is there a child uh salesman
around
here yeah
somewhere yeah
like Izzy
oh the kid wants wants some business
give him some business
I want to give him business
yeah okay I'm in business
the business
move
in the most say-so way possible because
that is a child
yeah see around here
I had some I'm just gonna wait for the
troubles with those kids in my private
playthrough yeah no they're kind of
nasty little little ones
they moved away oh well they steal
stuff
um
maybe really quick well maybe my Carlson
is talking to Gaga down here yeah we we
can sell our stuff Advance the story and
then that seems like a good you know
yeah
uh we're gonna wait for you guys down
here or yeah yeah okay I'm all done I'll
just sell my stuff next time before we
get started
oh yeah we can do it before we start
next time yeah
no killing the cow
why would I ever do that
all because of that croissant
croissant sounds good now
from this place
yeah tell her what's up I shall listen
to the explanation that you owe me
we do the story and then we can we can
go and do the tiefling party okay
silence
the right has been ended I will allow
you to yeah
you've forgotten the ways of the Drew he
tries to be feisty he's not having it
yeah
backslide I think we should kill her
Crush you
as you wish
oh okay it seems I can sell between
streams if I want to do bookkeeping off
stream okay okay
um you tried to imprison a check all
right hold on she did try it over prison
a child you were too lenient you'll have
your hands full with her it shows great
insolence but time will humble her
you should have beaten her up Allison I
take it back can I change my name
but enough of that for now I owe you my
thanks
you're welcome stands
nature we owe him our thanks to them
yeah he did help us out a lot speak to
wrath he will reward you for your
efforts
oh
uh what happens
entails
[Music]
but that's true
take some time for yourself
rest celebrate
come morning I'll be by your side
all right so we get our prize first and
then go to the party or just do the
party yeah okay
is in here I believe
father's teachings
oh now they teach me about the pink
system I already knew it
hello Ralph
you've done it
you brought house in back
thank you you're welcome no problem Bob
no
thanks is not enough it was fun
yeah all your days
I cannot imagine taking on a camp full
of goblins was a simple task
[Music]
true fair enough
I should not have underestimated you
let me show you on your map I also need
to check something real quick in the
Grove
before we before we leave I don't know
if we grabbed it before is it among the
pedestals but I think there's a Wonder
wolf glows brightest there's a worm a
worm
oh
okay where is Neddy again
Daddy's like here somewhere
[Laughter]
let's do a long rest are you guys ready
yeah wait what did he give to us as the
rewards
I have no idea
honor take off
everyone's in their underwear yeah that
happened automatically I didn't even do
that
myself I wish he'd put his back on
so many lines I don't need those two
things staring at me
when you look at it from the right angle
it looks like he's naked and just
covering himself with the books very
elegantly we killed some goblins to save
some teethlings
well I'm not giving him his clothes back
yeah that's fine
do you mind
wow we have no connection we have no
connection wow okay I'll try my luck
with somebody else
there's a board here I think is this
Larissa's Bard friend
ship eh we'll have time to spare for
that license
surprised you haven't had some housing
yeah dude
I really want to get
I'm sure there are
you strike me as extremely
resourceful
resourceful yes there are many grateful
people here who want to spend time with
you I must health and please yourself
that's what he's thinking
go yeah go go enjoy it it's the party
talk to whomever you please well which
Gale should I talk to I wonder if there
are two to choose from
hey
did we not have will it's strange we
really never recruited him huh this is
the saddest this is
what I mean it was better
people
like those refugees
I guess we try our lung he's gonna say
no that bunch in the growth oh we can't
we saved them I'm risen up I mean yeah
keep going good little service her
sounds like the Wine's talking Shadow
Hearts
she likes you
Shadow heart Trails off and glances
around at the party
turns back to you monthly surprised
I thought you might have wanted to
mingle with the others
oh trying to get rid of me yeah yeah you
are the company ID right now oh my God
I won't pretend I'm not surprised we
haven't always seen eye to eye after all
she's so cute I'm sure there's plenty of
people who'll be Keen to celebrate most
thoroughly with you what's that spot
uh uh maybe maybe I'd like
to celebrate with you yeah but I'm not
cruel enough to get your hopes up
in spite of what some might believe
um
I think I could win you over
I'm not some dewey-eyed tiefling Maiden
you just saved you'll need to do it
before I commit to any hip work hey
excuse me persuasion
[Music]
um
let's see
what some advice on how to make me more
bearable
all right if you like I'm not half as
mysterious as you might think
respect my privacy my opinion keep us
focused on British
if you do that well I see you know okay
wow she didn't say no she didn't say no
she didn't say no she said maybe later
so
okay
cool
[Music]
Tyrion hates me he hates everyone unless
you're a dick did he did he really just
it's not you it's me
biggest bottle
oh my my [\h__\h] now it's a heavy wrist
he's great I love him so much he's so
funny here's the best one-liners
it doesn't be so sour you know we could
always make our room entertainment
darling
does yeah
excuse me
oh geez I mean
I don't know are we is it is something
if you'd say please make him squirm
um
it's just me on my own on this one man
oh good luck streamer's luck
I'm done
what okay you're winning yeah
yeah good boy let's get together
[Applause]
no way no way you just ruined my life
can you get a room oyster I don't want
you to sleep with him
did I say just kidding
well maybe we should end the stream here
I don't know
rabbit time we need some privacy as they
like to say
I'm disappointed you what he was the one
that came on strong to me
you could have said no I could have but
it felt like you got a dumb idea by the
vampires
irresistible the idea of there being a
spicy scene between a Starion and the
biggest creature that I have created I
just couldn't say no
understandable oh my God anyway yeah no
one no one likes me no one no one here
is interested in me you're nervous I'm
so sad I know oh my God in in my in my
solo run everyone was so mad at me
they're like you're not gonna sleep with
me tonight what's wrong with you I was
like oh I didn't realize everyone liked
me so much WoW well
all right well alrighty
so we sleep so we end the day or does
anyone want to party
do I have just get it sends your screens
ready maybe wait wait I want to try I
want to try everything
I have shoes share private moments is
off I think
let me let me make sure for your eyes
there are private moments is off it's
off you will not see it neither will you
chat I'm censoring it
censoring it do you still have the ago
oh it'll be private or only only for
Cali's eyes I see I mean I don't have
nudity on so I don't really know how
spicy could it be
I mean or do they just do it with the
clothes on
uh it's it's a little spicy
hold on a minute
did I trade with can I give it to
somebody as a present like
a mistake
okay
um
still pretty spicy yeah
oh
well
everyone hates us I guess
um
free
you don't know you mean you don't know
that you don't no I've never seen
anything like that um
yeah I don't actually know how spicy it
is well obviously Marissa has seen it so
it's um yeah it's it's a little let's
see it's a little I heard a case it's a
little much
Andy she thinks I'm done streaming
because I stopped talking oh
she's so smart I mean it's probably okay
up here instead maybe
you know I just have my screen I just
turned the game screen off but I still
have the game sound on that's fine right
that's I mean as long as there's no
obscene visuals
all right share private moments on
let's [\h__\h] go right okay
I'm just gonna take measures real fast
I had to take measures I'm just gonna
make myself really really big
I think if you've probably talked to
people more so the they probably get to
know more about you so since you're the
one making like choices they uh are more
attached
I'm like the nicest one why is he down
to bomb I don't know he liked me too and
I was too nice for him so oh I guess
I'll go to bed
all right
let's go
hopeful rest show me your scene yeah
yeah
oh can we observe okay
look at Kelly's character oh my God
he's always loved me can you believe
that he's always loved this ogre I can
waiting
you don't have me yet say nothing just
let him kiss you
um just just let him do I am a ogre a
few words
do what you must sire
wait a minute hold on
see
Rising them up as always okay
yeah there's definitely tongue involved
uh enjoy yours relax enjoy yourself I
say you're the one who pinned him
against the dream I mean moriopa is you
know just a little a little frisky you
know I don't know what those teeth doing
[Music]
wait I'm pretty naked in there
I mean well no I mean I'm still kind of
okay yeah you don't you don't have
nipples yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
yeah your Leaf your lips yeah
[Music]
so how how did we think about that sir
is he humping you nah nah he did not
yeah
I thought you'd be exhausted lame
you weren't that good I say to him
leather I was holding it back if
anything
worried
to which base did you get good question
they went all the way
I wanted to ask you about your scars
where'd you get them isn't exactly a
happy story
spaces are kind of an individual in this
gate
home run
I'll kill him again
tennis smashed
Castle what
he captured me
kept me for years as his slave for sad
backstory sad past as we look at his s
uh yeah and a nice ass it is this was my
second sorry Chad oops when the Mind
flesh me up not a great Improvement but
you know he loves the ogre muscles
I mean how could he resist yes that's a
good one a poem to carry with me he
composed and carved that one over the
course of a night
he made a lot of revisions as he went
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
you certainly can't
you've never seen it uh well I've never
just checking a mirror can I yeah he's a
vampire I could tell you what it says
whatever the bastard wrote it won't
change can you read infertile no let's
go uh probably not probably not
if I was playing as a tea flying maybe
okay
before
[Music]
before yeah
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
well uh great we we made good
Progressive we finished saving the
growth which means we're moving on to
chapter two yeah
we can still go back and do some stuff
from chapter one though but especially
when we get to chapter three we won't be
able to go back so just so you know but
if we want to do like the Hague mission
for example it's probably better to do
that before we move on too far
yeah yeah we gotta find the hangs man
they become
yeah we'll find our way through you have
to have to moonrise um thanks everybody
for tuning in yes thank you thank you
for coming just by the late hour it was
a pleasure yeah but you'll run into the
Shadows eventually
I'm gonna take a huge fat nap yeah I'm
gonna go to sleep
I'm sure some people have announcements
for example I know Kiara you've got an
announcement
well I released an album yesterday
uh it has quite a lot of variety yeah
some edgy Emo songs some happy bouncy
songs
some cool EDM songs this and that uh
today is the release of the MB for DMV
of pineapple in in about seven and a
half hours so I hope you guys can watch
it
and you guys should go listen to it on
iTunes because I see it's yeah crawling
up the charts you guys we're crying
we're crying
yeah whatever service you prefer I would
be an honored please
thank you Kelly likes retrospective the
most huh great I don't know man great
wander is also really good those are the
two that I listen to a lot that's mine
yeah
I'm surprised
I thought Bijou would maybe like the
cuter songs they're all good but like
and I feel like sleep talking reminded
me of like a really cool like poppy
Banger that like I feel like everybody
can enjoy yeah sleep talking me too
so much thank you please sing them in
karaoke yeah
um so what else do you guys anyone want
to say what they're streaming next or
my membership's open today that's all
I've got
jail Birds jail Birds jail Birds my one
one month anniversary month anniversary
my first month and uh then I opened
membership so it's a fun day baby
he's not alive but debuted for a month
officially now
you babies
you girls are one month and me and Kelly
are coming on two free years
old that's so long
[Music]
um I'm streaming armored Core tomorrow
that's it um
I found my game I'm obsessed with it
really
[Music]
um yeah that's about it for me and then
I I'm doing it I'm not sure if people
can view the thing I'm doing tonight for
music first
um I have an appearance that I'm doing
I'll try and retweet stuff about it if
there is something online you guys can
see then you should be able to find it
there and yeah that's uh that's about it
interesting person let's go nice step
music first is that Japanese TV or what
yeah I think I thought it was TV but I
heard that it it's like an on online
that's on Japanese TV oh okay gotcha um
I mean I don't know I got a lot of weird
conflicting information from manichan
but I'll figure it out um
everybody will be there
[Music]
um so check my Twitter for info about it
if you're interested yeah thanks
everybody
thank you guys for playing I'm looking
forward to the next time we play yeah
next time next time different time again
next time
for everyone yeah gonna wake up super
early next time Kelly will sacrifice
herself 6 a.m so yeah so yeah thanks a
lot everybody take care of yourself and
yeah
yeah I'll see you bye-bye
peace out everyone
[Music]
if you wish
foreign
[Music]
no one expects me
foreign