w
[Music]
wow
w
[Music]
he
Dan
a
[Music]
n
w
[Music]
wow hi
darling hi darling hello
Darlings hello Darlings hello Darlings
hello shall we introduce ourselves so
people know everyone in the herum of
that is Nissa my
har oh what sorry sorry I mean our holy
Christian Club of course
yeah yeah yeah yeah that I never agreed
to be in a
harm I didn't
know I guess it just
happen sister V here at your service H
lives holy sister followed
by oh who whom you follow by me okay
when shoy you're still you're still
nunning it up I it's I will I will be
the nun until no nut November ends you
have no no n
November no
November okay good to know h k i Am Tak
I don't have a stream open so now I have
free chats open I have all of y'all's
chats open I'm watching
Everybody my first time playing the game
let's
go time yay first time power watching
you made me buy the game girls
oh nice sorry
well uh hi Darlings this is hello live
English Advent devilish Diva the one and
only narissa Raven coft
Dio welcome as we power wash she is the
harm owner
yes roses are red the fire of my heart
is blue also known as The Scarlet Queen
the harbinger of order leader of Justice
I I'm Elizabeth Rose blood flame lovely
to see you to see you lovely
L Lov do you have a short version of
your introduction too or do you always
do the long one no complaint but just
you always do that one
damn I know that's her intro there's no
shortening it well the rosarians will be
Mighty sad if I didn't yeah they'll cry
they'll they'll give a big war cry if
not do you think maybe after like 3 4
years or so of doing this you'll you'll
maybe shorten it cuz you'll get too
tired of it cuz recently I even get
tired or like embarrassed about saying
Kiki how could you get kitty
it's I feel like an imposter these days
come on are you
okay yeah I'm fine I just I don't know
the Kik key ain't Kik keying anymore a
but you're a chicken maybe you need
coffe what does that have to do with
anything you have to kiky it's in your
blood um uh well I'll try I'll continue
trying what if you do like a k oh
actually how do you say it I struggle
with that ky ky ky it's more like k k
Kitt K oh God K that is like uh one of
those trickster Rhymes oh K KY
they right tongue twisters
[Laughter]
[Music]
for right it's
okay just chill you have to be like do
you have to save water I have to save my
odd moments for when I mute scw the SC
not in front of senir ah
yes wor about anything just have fun
yeah the main purpose of this game is to
have a good time yes okay I hope there's
bodies I want toan up what but it's
Halloween a different kind of game shy
yeah I have to find that game then that
will be my comfort game Let's Mor
assistance for example oh I I like that
game I just don't like being
timed yeah that one's really
stressful oh I see I see like I would
play um that game without I wonder if
this will make
n
angry well sh it's time to make your own
game how about that about cleaning hpes
this game
developer we can play that game too the
viseral clean up thing I always can you
clean the tree ah we must water the that
cleaning corses yeah yeah actually oh my
God yeah literally you have to burn them
you have to burn the
bodies is that it remember to to the
flowers guys yeah you have to go through
a room you have to find them you have to
clean up all the blood you have to clean
up all the bullet holes you have to
clean up all the all the monsters so you
clean up the crime
scene yeah there's a game of that coming
out how you know something's like
completely clean does it have 100% here
stop and make a sound and go Bing oh
yeah what's Happ thing is I stop paying
attention um also when you hover over it
and when if you look up in the upper
left corner it says how much of the map
is finished but if you hover over
something and it doesn't have a like a
bar like a white bar that means it's
clean so I'm feeling silly today for
whatever reason I'm not getting any P
what is this I don't know why I got P I
got like four pink so far I
know and it's making me jealous so I'm
going to go do something else
on Discord if you want no it's
okay
already oh my God I can jump on them
like Mario my gosh the jealousy the
drama I rarely get pinked by Nissa these
days I don't think
anybody so you're not alone in
that have to that most I said
you please respond
you got to see him pretty much first as
soon as it was confirmed you were the
first person I sent the video to if you
don't continue sending me weekly updates
I will divorce you once I get him it's
going to be so over how are you holding
up herb while they
flirt I'm fine I'm just jumping on uh
clean uh kot senpai's head there we go
I'm not feeling anything you're so
strong
yeah oh she's light my pain tolerance is
very
high it's how firey
B holding me up um so gu Fire and Fire
doesn't hurt each other for first time
players uh if you hit the the tab Button
as Kiara mentioned it'll light up all
the dirt so if you're like missing dirt
and you haven't gotten a ping but also
if you hit Escape you can go through and
see all the different things that need
to be cleaned if you select to one of
those things that'll make it light up on
the map like it'll start kind of like
glowing in and out white so you can
actually then go and find if you're like
oh what's missing I have like 1% left on
this thing but I don't know where it is
that's how you can find it I need to M
while you're talking you're glitching
throughout my entire screen which I find
hilarious that's
so
oh actually like cleaning
then I'm not able it's okay we just Y
and she's a happen I'm part of Justice
I'm not you're not here to clean you're
here to Yap we were hired to Yap exactly
y y rabbit I wasted whole life oh this
is pretty light I like this did you guys
do anything for Halloween actually hit
by storm uh what if we did anything yeah
I yeah did you dress up or anything well
uh I did the stream we uh yeah I
remember the ghost we dragged you guys
to a a a haunted mansion oh yeah oh
that's right
and everything worked perfectly yeah so
I heard it was so there's a first time
for everything and you got to like you
know slowly ease into the VR world yeah
no wait at
all you know what the the Ian uh fandom
is very used to having to wait uh an
extended time for the streams to start
if it's a VR
stream they know there'll be more
waiting time then like if the official
starting time is like whatever 8:00 p.m.
they know it will not start until 10:00
p.m.
usually he that guys for future future
reference don't don't don't listen just
in case we start on
time do it you got to be ready at all
time yeah just make sure you have like a
snack an extra snack or something else
to do just in case you and 10 cups of
coffee so you can stay up yeah exactly
yeah get that Red
Bull mhm I haven't tried Red Bull before
actually what it gives you win s
monster oh my God I think that's good
because they're really bad for your
health and oh you shouldn't drink them
all the time but no no no no I like you
saying I like Red Bull every now and
again shei I'm going to leave can you
invite me back okay oh she's
everywhere do are you ready to be
invited I think I can join I'm joining
okay I fun yeah something's happening I
need a young priest and an old priest
right now they're coming
for power of of the Gods canare
you you know what I feel like I think
you need a I think you need a Red Bull
you
don't cuz I'm I'm um power washing the
uh tombstones and it's reminding me of
that girl who like cleaning uh Graves
from
people that one yeah with like not the
right products
yeah like kind of like like it can be
respectful there's people who do it
respectfully but that girl I don't know
she's just selling her product I think
so I feel like her right now no it's
okay these are just Halloween
decorations I mean in Japan right
there's a day where you go down to the
gravestones and clean them up M
everything's got to be clean in
Japan clean and beautiful I think that's
really nice back
to the graveyard in Japan I wanted what
you wanted to see a graveyard in Japan
yeah cuz they look a lot different cuz
they hones are like more rectangular
than ours ah there was like a temple
there I could have seen a mon and shiny
like I guess they are pretty different
yeah won't let me back in add beautiful
head what the freak she's trying to
steal your
harm yeah she's stealing myin
sucessfully she's claiming
it's I just I'm just so rible I guess is
the audio okay here let me let me try
again my
end very loud but it might be different
and it's just glinch out Zoom yeah thing
sorry everyone we we starting no I've
been cing so much no resume job yeah it
should save all the
progress how do I like get to the menu
though is my my question that's a good
question I have I these are going to be
bi I see you probably just have to quit
dang yeah this feels good I mean oh
there's a save button too is still like
zooming everywhere for me I'm not even
I'm not even I had to close the game
that's crazy okay I I invited you again
just to try it one more time and then
after this let's see if I can like uh go
back I can't monitor you if you're like
Zip zapping everywhere like it it won't
load you don't understand oh man okay
let me let me see career let me just go
to a random mode and leave you guys
trying trying to join you is crashing
the game for me what is online mode not
so stable in this game it usually is
this has happened before but a long time
ago okay sometimes the game's just crazy
I don't know the best way to leave this
thing cuz the menu is actually like a
tablet yeah everyone everyone completely
leave maybe close the game completely
and then reopen it okay all get the heck
out everyone I like wonderful
though oh oh got kicked out nice
yeah yeah I'm following her rules wait
are we completely shutting the game down
I did Cas yeah all right yes
ma'am I mean I'm not doing what you say
advin I'm just you know going with the
floor you know why would you do what we
say no I'm doing what I want I want to
close
it I'm
re me too I'm resuming the Halloween
Town
okay and then you can just send out
invites again don't it's a magic
day cleaning until you send out invites
as soon as you said Halloween Town like
a certain song came to mind that I
cannot sing out loud
and you say it out loud you can no I
can't I can't sing it out loud oh you
can't sing okay
yeah it's Nightmare Before Christmas I
hope it worked
oh
yeah is it not working oh it's it's
connecting slowly it's loading right is
also a good song
Dirt I'm gonna I'm gonna go clean I see
you we're in don't start we're in okay
okay hi have you had a good day I was it
was a very busy DayDay
changing I need a Red
Bull okay okay now we just I need to
make one of my potions the game won't
glitch yeah I'm I'm I'm slowly getting
in there herb herb herb she's getting in
her fan she GNA come out herb is the
word up the herb is the word yeah herb
is the worb there you go welcome back
back wow it saved it progress cleaning
zoink we're not going to have to
restart I raved our
game yeah
yeah
beautiful wow oh so I have this hanging
body in my place it's like one of those
fake Halloween decorations first off
okay that that's I nearly took out my
like notebook and I was like uhhuh
yeah and the in the hanging body like I
got it for like $5 it's supposed to
shake if you have batteries inside it
but it's kind of like it's not realistic
which makes sense it was cheap yeah
ground because of Halloween or just
because of for your own
Aesthetics
yes well I think it was on sale cuz it
was after Halloween by then yeah I was
going to throw it away and I left it on
the floor and my pile of throw away or
like a maybe donate but then my cat
manag to go inside it and then it was
like it was so cute it's like oh they're
hiding in the little body bag and just
like a butterfly so I'm hoping that they
do it again so I have a reason to keep
it around
a yeah I you got to keep it if if it
became the cat toy yeah I know I want
them to sleep in there
[Music]
more you so cute and unhinged
shy it's not even unhinged I just think
it's funny it's a little unhinged really
just a little your definition unhinged
is weird well you know we some people
have their Christmas decorations out for
another five months she already
Halloween on her
floor that's
fine my parents Christmas lights before
they kept it for a year cuz they take it
down that's Val
wait quess style are your parents put on
there yeah no she has her Christmas
things up all the time at least on her
stream
oh all the
time giving yeah you know that's how I
uh res that's how I initially learned
ABC
hello I was going to say Red Bull did
you know it's from Austria we learned it
really two ways the head
in
Austria
youg but they made us learn
it yeah yeah you can and like they
sponsor a lot of like Austrian um Sports
people and all that like I don't know
spor just say that you want to like get
drunk off your
thing get drunk off the Red Bull you me
yeah you want to drink it up guzzle it
up if you have aab bom
oh the thing is normally I try to avoid
Red Bull it's like my emergency solution
if I'm really tired because I don't
drink
cof only in emergencies red tomorrow
emeres I just feel the pain of tiredness
you already have wings you don't need
it me oh thank you oh no I mean was
about was about
Kiara oh I'm wingless yeah you can't fly
oh yeah it's a red bu for light blue
girl in Germany blue girl yeah happy
birthday
NE listening to her your Tex on your
birthday the
messages so that's that that's the
person who has paid you read the story
they'll tell you the L of why it got
dirty like birth random of the game too
lazy to
clean probably
do you see me on the
pumpkin I see you on there oh yeah okay
I see you baby your wings I'm to you
guys watch those hoarder channel
so I do too it brings me joy unmutes are
you a hoarder is anybody a hoarder no uh
I can't be the queen mother doesn't like
[Laughter]
it I cannot even if
I also try to control myself I've I've
stressed things in the past a little bit
but not like sickly yeah yeah yeah oh
they just like collecting a bunch
yeah like things from Japan don't
usually and now I'm hoarding like band
letters like after 4 years there's so so
many I don't want to like get rid of
them so they'll just get more and more
and more buy a buy a storage unit then
buy a
you know just a random chest it might
not be worth a storage unit yet but we
can work on that
right more more letters more
letters you can you can get a different
size ones usually when it comes to
storage units baby storage units yeah
you can you can get like one that's like
a
locker or at least in great Exodia you
can is ho like homework from like
previous years thinking maybe I'm going
to need this for my next class the next
semester and then once everything was
done it's like see you I'm out I think
that's kind of keeping materials from
previous years I think that's
not I'd keep them because I'd sketch in
them and I'd be like that's a cute
picture I drew then keep
it me
too I remember at the end
of people would clean up lockers mine
was pretty clean but everyone would just
have tons of homework on in theirs and
they had to get like a giant
trash and there'd be like a maybe a
rotting sandwich for some of their
lockers yeah we should power wash a
school it seems there's potential there
there
potential more money from our power
business
okay pumpkin are you finished
finally it's
good little bit here so relaxing maybe a
little dizzying actually oh uh hit the C
button oh I see yeah that feels weird
you can hit it and unhit it so it'll
lock she ran into my power you know
having your head you saw her she went in
Fr it's just
Frozen yeah saw the motion sickness
yeah she ran into my experience with
this game I love this game I was just
standing there wow one of my favor well
well
well well well well
Shori I
see you too hey ma'am huh what's up you
ever heard of a poisal
bubble personal bubble I'm on top of the
well for me uh where am I in your
screen
uh
yes
yous oh man that's fun you're interet
sucks maybe you're inet sucks you're the
one who's like glitching around you're
on top of the
well I was I'm I'm off now oh now I'm on
top of the well I didn't even know you
can climb up here yeah yeah you are yeah
yeah what's your favorite girls are you
lighting my
gas uh good I the yellow one the yellow
or the red
[Music]
one question what your favorite nozzle
is are am I still glitching on your
screen her herb
attack think she's hallucinating I think
this map is just haunted I see Shori
everywhere that house should be just
Shori I I mean I'm on it to you so it
makes sense that's true you're like a
stalker are you cheating on me her I
want say you what the
frak excuse her herb someone's going to
do it herb what's going on there I don't
know I think part of the job to monitor
Advent it didn't say monitor just
narissa yeah but I'm your favorite what
if I'm monitoring your back I mean I
monitor you probably the most but that's
besides the
point you need like extra watching this
why okay I guess I can share you a
sh you know what they say happy wife
happy life what you mean allow me to
share what what the frak it's my job the
higher ups tell me what to do this the
most awkward flirtation attempt I've
witnessed
from all of my flirtation attempts are
awkward what are you talking
about well I didn't want to say that but
okay did you see my my stream title for
this by the way I did I
did yeah I saw people tweeting about it
I just I was like it was a funny title
you said something about why why were
cool yeah what is it again don't worry
about it my title yeah your title yes
worry about it oh I I'll let your chat
tell you I I I'll let them surprise oh
copy paste it's my
Halloween happy
Halloween man I love
Halloween me too I'm a Christmas scy
it's all right I like Christmas too I
like Justa yeah you never sent me that
picture of you in your costume yeah
cleaning with girlfriend end changing
and dressing up after all it was I
remember agreeing to being a wife I
wanted to dress up like I remember
getting married the only one that's
asked me to marry them is dress up yeah
and even then that was aest but now I'm
looking for like I want to find a cute
dress to wear for
Christmas cuz I don't have one you don't
have one I'm sure you go
naked no you can't go naked it's
Christmas yeah it'll be like a Christmas
present no like Merry Christmas put a
ribbon around your
body that's
like type yeah like you guys are
sick for what you're sick no well yeah I
am sick
actually yeah well soon facts yeah what
about
it it's getting sick season again
everybody be careful I'm healing now
though thankfully I want to travel sick
yeah I don't want you to travel sick
either
yeah I think I need a lad there well
luckily there's tons around the
map I was in the midst of reading a
super where is all the water coming
from uh your heart does this not have
Collision I'm sorry what oh I guess only
you guys could pass
through I I cannot seem to climb the
ladder I will I will go save just in
case skill issue yeah skill issue maybe
I was the ghost all along did you guys
like my thumbnail it had Hearts to
represent
us I mean yeah it's cool it's cute I
mean
powerful it it's
nice song I Like The Realistic like
power wash I was like o I want to use
this
no all right where did my thing
go band that only I like
right I need to turn them back up oh no
that's the audio don't they have some
like famous songs I'm sure I like one
song at least yeah how soon is now from
Charmed is the Smith song ah there you
go there you Goa I recently finished
watching your in Echo V just want to
thank you for putting in the extra
effort and making it such an
unforgettable experience a thanks Ellie
it's funny I'm glad you enjoyed it I'm
happy cuz I wanted it
off the type of role play where someone
could like after like months and months
later go back and still enjoy it so
that's really I'm I'm really tough to
hear that so thank you thanks for
letting me
know I found fat and I was like are you
kidding
me this is where that song is
from to
resar yeah ah yes I only know my my
vocal
songs weeb
stuff you're my little
weeb oh I thank you you're my little
pony you'll always be in my
heart
wow okay there
Tarzan you're my little
chickeny I just Jo in you're my
little cheeky nandos that's what you are
you're my little cheeky nandos what is
that cheeky Nando what what we say to me
chicken nandos Chey cheeky have you
never heard of nandos before no like a
chicken nuggets it's a it's a restaurant
where they they mostly spicy chicken
with Perry Perry the best o it's very
yummy sounds yummy have you had it
before
goodp uh no but I'm aware of it's oh
I'll treat you one
day okay okay interesting to study my
rivals in the business I'm in yeah true
yeah yeah yeah that's it I'm coming
over yeah yeah
yeah I will steal herb from narissa
because I am geographically closer to
her anyway wow this is some
NTR who said she owns me what the
FR yeah I I I don't I don't just her own
woman yeah she just monitors me don't
you know
what if we collected like a like a
Pokemon we just throw a ball at herb get
there first well that work herb I don't
think throwing balls get in my ball if I
ask nicely please oh anything for you
sweee I'll jump into the ball for you
let me just squeeze on
in one foot then the other let's Sky I'm
going to write my twit longer right now
o your Google doc it let's go well
because i' get her B my experience with
oh my God don't is your account not um
verified don't you can't you WR write
long tweets on your own without TW
longer I but I feel like the twit longer
is more dramatic it is yeah yeah it is
and then like the white background yeah
like reading like my story and then a
link to twit longer is like so much
better than like you know opening up a
tweet and seeing that it's like a novel
and then you're like oh I didn't sign up
for this honestly whenever see those I
just don't click I'm just too tired same
I on time a good in between is um
posting a picture of your
notes oh yeah okay but what if
handwriting no no no no written on your
iPhone or whatever oh okay like your
notes
app that's how you do it where's the
evidence where's the screenshots
scord they just got to believe it gu or
or in the
replies proof in
replies yeah into
pudding this well isn't done well well
well well well well well well well this
well is not complete oh can I climb
these stairs oh thank God I
couldn't I just
I through
it me too
actually what hey did you climbed up on
the
roof no oh for the well one oh no no I I
faed through the the the steps over here
oh I fac through the ladder but I can
climb up be stairs near the
house like I said I'm just a
ghost ghost with the most easy
mode everything is easy mode for sh no
rotate the yeah use your um the R button
oo it's true sh is a force to be
reckoned with yeah she's scary she
scares me man I don't know about
scary we have two children together and
I'm still terrified of her I don't even
remember how the heck that happened I
just woke up with it you got CH are sure
oh she and narissa I B Urban Nissa I was
going to be worried she's probably going
to have children with her soon
yeah I saw fan art and it was cute but I
mean we actually did have a child
together K
remember no no that's a different
dimension that we're talking about one
that's a whole different universe and
two even then it wasn't real it was just
butter chicken it looked more like K's
child
are you going to be mad mad at me in
like Ian REO season 2 as well about that
still or you going to forget about it we
already we're it's already water under
the bridge right I think so well it
depends would would the Nissa of that
that realm
remember
yeah you don't remember anything that
happened oh I have a bad memory
so well got to rewatch before before we
get back into that in that Universe yeah
iated
sumary yeah there's still a lot of time
we'll we'll be forgetting even more cuz
it's going to be in spring right oh
that's too far for me I
want I remember I got left with a child
H who left you with a child it was it
was that one girl and then he stepped up
that one girl I
will
tuition yeah yeah yeah now I remember
it's okay I I gave you money remember
that's
true I can't wait for the college
tuition
Arc oh
frig wait you had a shiori of inreco had
a
child yeah yeah technically if you can
call it
that oh I don't remember what name might
gave it though to be
honest child a I don't either but child
a that's our baby now because I I wasn't
chaos I remember yeah
K hell yeah I want the K to be in
Reverse so it's like someone who who
didn't know how to spell spell
it why are you not mentioning who the
the other girl was maybe maybe she won't
remember we'll have to see m h it wasn't
me
right I I I I don't know if we'll have
to see K I don't think it was me
remember uh a fun night in town with me
no I don't think I was involved with
that many people
anyway my wives are going
crazy
spicy beo was
en's
wife it she we
comb egg yeah she I'm I'm getting I
didn't want to put pressure on her you
know even though I am totally
betrayed it's okay because now you have
a rich a rich Gambler wife
husband gambles away the college tuition
no I only get rich don't
worry it's my it's my my it's my lore
story now oh do you have a
strategy yeah is it a blackj
no I I make I make money through honest
means in andreco andreo Elizabeth was
poor because she was a KN can you say
gambling how's that honest I don't
gamble I gamble for fun I make my money
through honest means and then I gamble
for
fun mhm
I don't know if I can trust Amber though
what are the honest means then a potato
Sal prob at one Quest
yeah
ah salad go I'd love some potato salad I
know right you prefer potato salad like
uh in the version that is like mayoni or
do you prefer the one that is like
oily vinegar prob
mayonnaise I don't know what oily salad
is let me through shiori
huh I don't even know where you are
behind you you're over there you can
come you're different on my screen what
the heck it I'm literally right behind
you cleaning the door oh I'm not near
the door I'm on a tower theck remember
I'm a ghost
G get wet get wet what's happening what
are the plants if you see me just assume
I'm I'm not actually there I've moved on
it would let me move past you it was
crazy
I'm sorry about that I can't help my
ghosty
[Laughter]
butt
phenomenon
phenomenon oh I like to Wi the
C
difficult but you're doing great I'm
proud of you I'm pretty sure you can buy
a ladder can't you there's already
ladders on around the map you just need
to find them and then place them up a oh
yeah I should have to move them I see
you
yeah is there ladders that go that high
go moved on yeah she's moved on there's
if you come to the back of the building
there's a really really big like it's
not a ladder but it's like um it's a
w Wait I inter yeah it's like
scaffolding and you can move it I only
know this word thanks to
Minecraft same
what ladder well I'm going to I'm
already up here so I'm going to just try
to brood force it while I'm here you
know ladder cuz I break my legs anyway
scaffolding yeah oh scaffolding oh
there's ladders too actually there's
ladders what's your Minecraft experience
herb my Minecraft experience
uh uh I enjoy it after a while I get
motion sick but I enjoy it are you
motion third
person yeah I I did that smidge when we
when did in Reco but it was I mean you
were with me actually kiato when we when
I when we were uh going through one of
the dungeons cuz we had to jump around a
lot they got to a point where I was just
like I need to stop after
this man you're debuffed you have to
live with this debuff but that even more
skill ah
h i mean i didn't get Mission thank you
for telling us oh yeah totally you you
don't you were just you just messing
with I mean I'm still
powerful I'm still very powerful so it
doesn't really it doesn't really it's
not really much of a de you know I'll
just truck on through it I'll walk it
off you know yeah yeah yeah you walk it
off yeah so what you're saying is uh you
want to go to a fair together and go on
one of the really really spinny rides
and spin really really fast I do it yeah
yeah you can do it no you can just do
them back to back to back to back leave
her alone no don't let her suffer
through it no let go the teup handle it
yeah are you calling herbal liar yeah
let's go on the teacups let's spin yeah
we'll go we're going on the teacups or
the spinning Dragon you can just do the
Minion ride with me I promise it's it's
lighter the Minion ride is great A I do
like minions I think they're cute yay
nice want like
B bana you know in the in the realm of
the 40 shades of green green uh which is
very similar to Ireland there was
there's a a game called dizzy dragons
where you just
spin yeah I I know that cute I love the
Dizzy dragons dizzy Dragon I don't know
if I want my dragon to be
dizzy that's that's where I I the game
in my
youth
yeah do he
drag no she's still alive as you can see
I'm a ghost now just like Shori we're
all
ghosts ghost they're all haunting wow
yeah please don't haunt me scared of the
dark what a Twist
huh like oh am I the Scrooge am I
Scrooge make duck and this is the you
know the what is that movie called uh
you mean the Christmas carol what you're
talking about yeah
yeah I love the way you associate uh the
Christmas carol first with Scrooge MCD
there's a load of
versions that's cute it's the most
popular one yeah it's very popular for
like
kids there's no Barbie Barbie with the
Scrooge is that not you know no oh she
has so many movies I'm surprised I know
they didn't want to make her a
[\h__\h] that's probably true
actually yeah that is probably it Barbie
has to be nice yeah I like her in the
Nutcracker yeah I don't remember the
Nutcracker One I Love The Nutcracker
ballet man I used to play with Barbies
and I just made them all gay for each
other nice I see
it it was usually the Disney Barbie
dolls too like I ship them with the most
random ships like I I paired someone
with Ursula I don't know who though oh
wow yeah it's like enemies to lovers
let's
go it's
Vibe enemies how we going to get up to
the top of that uh Tower you got
legs m
Wings would help
more I can't activate them in this game
can't you see me on the top of the tower
that you're talking about well yeah now
I see you going up there I've been up
here I tried jumping
but that's a skill issue yeah okay now
I'm on there there you go you got
skills yay
you good yeah I'm fine don't worry
nothing I'm being a
professional okay yeah don't worry about
it okay she's so professional yeah I'm
leader Justice I'm professional yeah
very professional you're officially the
the
leader yeah she'd been the leader
realized now she's the henchman now yeah
sure's the leader of ad
yeah I'm I'm just the
babysitter hey I don't need to be baby
same let's do well technically you have
two babysitters
Nissa what
oh if shy and then you have me that's
true why do I have so many
babysitters well you want to be looked
after though you want to be like a a
baby yeah you're a baby
right Gaga Google gaga take care of me
Google gag
reminds the baby I enion reminds me of
an ASMR I watched
earlier oh is it the the Hat yeah I
tuned in I didn't know what it was about
I was just like ah nice Whispers And
then she translated it for me and I was
like oh
no that moment when the ASMR artist like
knows how to speak English too and
notices you in chat and translates and
I'm like ah
no she's like Li you want milk my milk
and I'm
like did you say yes what was your
answer we need a
know uh no
comment I like
milk I I always treat myself to like a a
pint of milk when I'm not recording or
singing and stuff I love
milk that's my
[Music]
I hate milk on its own love own I like
it that's cuz you're built different I
guess so I just like ice cream and
cheese when I was out with Justice in
the Far East I I like when we'd be at a
cafe I'd buy
milk drink just milk yeah just milk
wow just cuz I saw it and I was like oh
my God I could get this milk wow man I
always just got water when we went to
the to the east
mhm I remember like do you guys want the
full-on drinks the drink bar I'm like
I'll just get water I liked getting the
drink bar in Japan because they always
had matcha latte oh yeah it's good it's
good and I was like what do you mean I
can just have matcha latte whenever I
want I missed the drink bars I wish
there were more common here along with
like the iPads the iPads for service I
love not having to talk to people yeah
that's why I love going to family
restaurants and and I could be I could
be weirder because they can't understand
me they'll be like a city gu
no I love I love that I just love I love
not talking to
people not either
F oh my God that was so funny I saw the
clip of you and uh
Rea and you forgot she speaks English oh
my God you're commenting on her her her
personality her uh view yeah
yeah it's like I don't know English nor
Japanese let's
go oh my
gosh how do you pick up these
scaffolding things if you get close to
it you should be able to it should pop
up F uh you can't move it on the
roof I just want to like go around the
has a nice
view yeah I don't know it was for me
either and I'm concerned about it
because we kind of need
that we can fly we're at
96% 96 mine only says 90 what do you
mean oh
sorry I'm I'm adding another 6%
I need to learn how to say more than sh
sh
Nella do you want to host the next map
you want to host the next map oh my God
maybe she has such a cute voice oh my
God maybe it won't be can't ham me right
now no I'm sure it will be
anything it's it's going to be your
birth week after all it has to be better
you're true it is my birth week yeah one
day
yay n birth got just observe more I just
got monitor more birthday monitor
monitor monitor everyone except Shori
happy
birthday thank you wait hey we're
technically celebrating early then I'm
making celebrating the 2 21st oh oh yeah
yeah yeah why why do you not so excited
no cuz I'm gone on that day oh
on why is my screen like having an
earthquake now oh it stopped I guess it
did oh it's because you're shooting me
oh I
see I like why is there an earthquake I
don't know what you're talking about
M you just cuz you you know you've been
cleaning so much you got a bit on your
VI on my on my where my we
exactly my mask your head piece I don't
know your helmet I remember when I was
uh at the starting screen I just aim for
your crotch right there it's like I'm
going to stay here and aim at it until
she comes back how dare
you I was cleaning it I'm making sure
you're all well cleaned thank you I
appreciate it you know you're too sweet
you're welcome I know isn't she so
considerate
that is very considerate I don't want to
start the stream being like uh oh stinky
and stuff you know yeah I'm watching you
washing Away The Sins oh nice thank you
sister you guys should play cookie on me
to see how considerate you really are
apparently there's a new one oh yeah I
one there's a fourth one I saw it in the
game perms updates it said cookie Yumi 4
I was like hey yo I play first go go you
have so much to catch up they're that
doesn't mean you guys could call me
Stinky yeah they're pretty short but
they're fun I wasn't really
stinky but a job online a i it's online
it's a like multiplayer but you have to
be off collabing I think I think that's
sure maybe you have to be considerate to
each other and no no it's like a battle
of to see who's most considerate I see
you're not consider it to each other no
no no that would be crazy yeah you guys
smell a stinky
got them got them you guys smell stinky
socks stinky socks all of you like the
stinkiest oh my
God want to get up on the
hat you jump on the one of the boards
the bill boards jump on this rock I'm
King of the
rock I'm up y maybe
not try to billboard aha oh that works
Maybe
bro what's going
on we're cleaning you're cooked we're so
cooked what does that mean
95% [\h__\h]
oh but like you know without the curs
thing
oh we could almost
done so at this point if you can't find
what to clean well you can uh click tab
and then it'll show you what's not done
yet and you can go clean it
hey Co let me Stinky through a super the
FR is that's a skill issue but things
also just are like not pinging like it
said the well was dirty so I came and
cleaned it but it still you know you
guys smell of a stinky Idol meeting
because lots of people in a room talking
business very stinky some sometimes
I don't know where I'm going with
this stinky stinky stinkers I blame shy
this is all her
fault yeah it was me the whole time did
it I'm the one who would have gone away
with it too if it wasn't for
my the cooky kids
so chat reflects the Stream 99 well that
means you all I'm at like are very good
with your like why you ahead of like
washing and and you you like smellies
like me I love locked in I ran you know
I ran out of the other day since she's
running the game I think there's no lag
on let me turn it down for AE you know I
ran out of the other day I ran out of um
in the Far
East they have a particular limited
edition Body Shop body wash that was one
of the few things I got
and it was like Sakura smell I ran out
of it the other day I was like oh
no it was very good highly recommend oh
my God
hi that says
like okay Uncle AR is here I'm here to
babysit the
rosers
rough I love the plushies they look so
cute can get an I want my own
you can change the things for your power
washer and at the very least you can get
an extend you can
re I'm just not stinky uncle is here hey
don't tell him that I climbed there
before I can do it again start a new
conversation everybody said their own
rusa I mean the ver here take them all
there's stinky little
animals yay okay let me let me okay
rosarians you smell like stinky
Rosas how do you like those apples we've
gone up from stinky socks the stinky
Rosas I'm so sad there some body in here
but yeah I'm playing power wash with
what about
our and hi Darlings uh
narissa I hope you had fun R what I did
watch was awesome are
you absolutely
fantastic no I'm me
pH and for those who don't know uh uh R
who raided ruse Crimson ruse you should
check him out he's a great Entertainer
well and I'm his uncle you know got to
support the family I just I forget who I
am for a little while he comes back to
me but not really I'm his uncle yeah
yeah you know just Phoenix so yeah
support the fam
I can't
reach red
family I mean he is Crimson oh somebody
missed
a pleas your hot I mean my flame is
pretty
hot Bob's your
uncle no actually it's Ray Uncle Ray
Uncle probably two years or so [\h__\h]
that's my uncle
I opened the app for the first time in a
long time today and I saw I have like a
lot of credits so I bought all of the
Game of Thrones book readings oh hell
yeah and all of the Lord of the Rings
including the S marilan and stuff like
that hell yeah which CH you reading that
on
Kindle no not Kindle it's audible oh
audible right yeah yeah # moners
uh now I have like
probably o over 300 hours of stuff to
listen to that's
good yeah but I don't even like like
listening to somebody reading to me that
much but I got I'm going to force myself
cuz I don't like uh reading either so
it's got to be one of them reading or
being R to but say go pick
one yeah I'm going to be picking being
red too I guess I mean some of the some
uh what is it some uh audio books have
like like celebrities reading them and
stuff so yeah like stepen fry you
know this a celebrity I didn't know that
oh stepen fry he's a National
Treasure like Media stuff though isn't
he the dude from like Sherlock Holmes
based on what he
reads was
he well well whenever I see aable it's
like this is read by Steven fry oh
famous in the UK oh sure he's like read
like a bunch of stuff on Audible
probably okay Shi it's up to
you your game is loaded the most you
need to hit escape and clean
everything I'm Escape I travel I also
travel a lot to the realm of the UK so
we get we get um the TV shows from the
UK and great exia so how's your game
though are you at 99% what if you at 1%
was it Qi that Stephen Fry is on or
still on um you have to finish
it is this like your OCD stuff no you
have to finish
it my favorite so Stephen Fry is also on
a a uh like a funny talk show and U one
of my favorite jokes of his is like he
goes uh what is it I'm a little teapot
short and stout here is my handle he
puts his arm out and he puts his other
arm out you and oh no I'm a Sugar
Bowl that's my favorite he's a sugar
bowl
yeah a it's hilarious you know it's
better once you know you physically look
at someone during ever yeah of course of
course of course it's
hilarious well there's another one to do
with happiness but like I don't know
about saying that
one why is it embarrassing no I mean
it's it's mostly an accent
joke do it oh just this just about a
lady who's like I wish for
happiness
[Music]
oh I see happiness the dirt yeah it's
nice you know your
happiness happiness mhm Happ can't
get I
see I get it now got to say it
slowly oh oh you didn't say it don't do
it in your brain say it out loud no we
don't need to say out loud I've said it
once good I'm good I've said it once
it's oh man you know jokes on is funny
if you say multiple
times but then who nobody hears
them that's
fine I need to hear brown and sticky I
need to witness oh another one of my
favorite jokes not by steepen FR there
it's uh what is it um German Shepherd
jumped over my fence and pooped in my
garden any had a
dog what you need a
dog
because a German Shepherd jumped over my
fence and pooped in my garden and he had
a
dog and ah ah ah okay okay okay okay
took me a moment no I mean that was very
good you picked up very quickly
especially since I'm always like really
like uh um wowed by people who's not
that their first language isn't English
and they understand a joke so fast
especially one like that one where it's
to do with like the wording and things
it so nice just I'm just saying the
truth I'm going to jump I'm going to
jump sure he put us out of our misery
what's how do you check like the last
one I need you need hit the escape
button and then you will have a clean
the Halloween house you can go through
the list and scr through all them and
it'll say what ones are not at 100 yet
Apothecary lanterns then and the Pumpkin
shed chimney and red Tower wall is it
bad I want to Ping like we're inv
valerant I want to Ping like inv
valerant if if you click it it'll make
it light up so you can see exactly
cheating then it's not cheating
what I'll do the this one then let me up
does it show for you guys oh this one no
it'll it'll only show on your side but I
see are you at 99% as well yeah same
lanterns
parkour uh there you go parkour parkour
parkour I made
Lantern okay so that's the oh you've got
it there's an around the other side
house
base well I'mma die thank you forever oh
no fall damage no fall damage I'm thank
[Music]
you I'm a die thank you oh I can get
this one yay nice Halloween sign where
be
that maybe in the somewhere in the
beginning in the front it's the graves
actually yeah those are Halloween signs
apparently
oh this one's
GL what map do you want to do next by
the way a good question there's a
Christmas one for free well I don't know
what you
downloaded but we can let Cru ship and
the Halloween ones ship no please show
me the last piece of
ship herb language
no my sties are my treasures I would
never how could
you yeah herb what the [\h__\h] oh my
gosh r a twit longer last
[Music]
longer
Jee jeez
Louise so if you wanted to swear you
could get away with
it stor stor
I think it's more fun coming up with
other
words yeah yep I'm not so
creative ah I see one spot but it's at
the tower like kind of
unreasonable you got to use the extender
if you can maybe that could help oh yeah
you can extend yeah if you if you hit e
the extension you can put on a super
long
one long uhuh
oh
okay there a
[Laughter]
window the roof something at the
roof there's this game I wanted to
permise for it's like uh you clean the
house but it's haunted and that's pretty
much
it I see like it seems kind of relaxing
I want to play it see some ghosties
does it have to be 100% in order to like
get out of the map it's it's rea's
preference no it's not my preference you
do not win the game it is not optional
you have to complete it 100% you can win
the game sounds like the game has an end
oh it does just like uh you did it you
cleaned everything
yeah do you know why I'm on the
roof no cuz the drinks are on the house
oh I'm sending you to jail I'm sending
you to jail hey is this Dad humor she is
she's becoming a dad no I'm an uncle
actually
[Music]
congratulations come on shiori it's all
up to you I'm I'm working on
it I
believe where is the last B what do he
you hit the escape button and you can
look through herb but ours aren't
updating for some reason very well
Apothecary
lanterns but I think Shi already you
guys to do things at least yeah already
get the lanterns yeah may maybe for me
it's not done I I see the dirt on dirty
[Music]
still yeah yeah this is still
dirty what's wrong with it I getting
better we're getting there it has to be
this like this one
shingle mhm spamming my
tab maybe we just need to wait for it to
catch up I am losing it she's it's never
going to catch
up I got to wait a you you're so cooked
oh H let me just skip this one for now
does it oh wait but you have to do like
100% for each thing right right yeah
everything has to be cleared it's not
going to round up that's so weird cuz
sometimes it rounds up the
dirt yeah it it it it does if you get to
like a certain point even if there's
still like a little bit left it'll 100%
clear it come on it's 99% where are you
dirt so strict that's I
know no it's just it's being bad right
now because everything's glitching out
but usually it's not like this
okay now the
window what window though I need the
house Dormer window along with the eaves
whatever that
is
MHM I think I found the
eaves
me it looks clean to me now what's wrong
with it tab button oh maybe it's the I'm
spaming tab
everything looks
clean there's some tiny dirt on the
Windows Eve where are
you Eve what is an eve eve uh the area
between the roof and the house
wall so basically any Gap I assume it's
not a gap it's like a wood framing
yeah like under
yeah but where's the dirty Eve that's
the question it should light it up for
you I'm I'm spamming I'm trying to find
it it's a thing oh if you click on it
it'll just make it light up for you so
you'll be able to see what specific Eve
it is H oh no I i' I've clicked on it I
just don't know where it is essentially
where the I see it it's here but I
cleaned
it oh maybe just e that's a all right
Eve's
done now I need a random window
yippe
yippe yippe window which oh this
one uh house small
trim how small trim where are
[Laughter]
you this is a really cursed it's so
Halloweeny in every sense the of the way
yes okay did you find a trim I got the
Apothecary uh house entrance
e house entrance I can't find a window
oh wait what am I looking
for to the
wall chat do you see the small trim
wherever that is
oh spamming tab our suffering
go go go the front door you
think that looks like a big trim oh hey
there's ladder icons for some reason
now
God not oh wait can I climb the
ladder
invisible uh around the door by the
stairs oh my
Goda needs it to be perfect I don't need
it to be perfect that's how the game
works but how often am I going to play
this no it's just how the game works I'm
not making up rules that's just how it
works okay okay okay there there there
there bre how about we all leave and
leave shiori and then see if anything
fixes all right because I feel like the
map is clean we've all individually C
find tin tiny tiny tiny things yeah but
what I'm saying is some of the things
that we're cleaning are things that
another person has already fully
clean but it just hasn't pinged on your
map mhm all right so so go ahead and
manually leave then and maybe you can
come back safely all right okay I look
for a gargoyle leave Cup game time
goodbye goodbye So Long Farewell har say
I'll see you good night oh hey I can
finally climb the stairs now that you're
gone wow just cuz we gone no offense no
offense can you pick it up
now can can we rejoin now did go Ahad
are you able to do you need another
invite no it might be broken you just
have to finish it you have to finish
this shy oh man that's a lot of you're
putting a lot of stress on here for a
power wash game
good good luck round
control thank you for the gifted
membership thank you thank
you thank you to those who give to the
blood flame Kingdom you need to finish
this map more resigns using
emotes
simulator quick chat where's gargoyle
what looks like a guard to your [\h__\h] is
it is it the cat at the stop yeah they
got go I don't know okay let me get
anything on the roof first before I go
to the guard yeah red Tower wall all of
this looks like a giant red Tower wall
to
me you can do it I
believei that's me what do you want me
to do you want me to dance for you I'm
dancing dance what else you want me to
do huh I want you to dance for
me dance what am I my anxiety is so
yeah you've got to clean everything cat
on what if I what if I just say like o
100% let me Photoshop it
really hey I only have like a few things
I just need to freaking get the gargoyle
these things I you must you must clean
it all for justice yeah you got to clean
it all for justice I don't believe in
Justice what is this good you got to
clean it all for our
Rebellion I don't know about that that's
telling me what to do night are beating
hearts with the the power wash dance
dance
dance dance dance
dance come on cat Okay gargoyles clean
pathway post decoration what the heck
does oh I
see Rea has invited you to
play I guess oh I've been
invited yay I guess I'll wait is this
the same map what is this no just leave
I can leave she's finally letting me
guys oh she's letting you go we're free
finally wow 100% we did it we did it
yeah now we're in Santa's
work we are
everything is it orange this place is
very orange oh that's probably Christmas
Eve eve and not look forward to the one
special reason this is French Bob by the
way it's the last night that our
inventor Ivor Nida pitches the last
year's St toy to
Santa or next year's St toy what why is
everything covered in dirt we're going
to find out
from however was supposed to carry them
through Santa's office in a big box to
stop anyone from
peeking maybe they filmed a spicy movie
in here the eles they exploded The
Nightmare Before Christmas we knew that
had to be really
good the movie man no I'm I'm reading
I'm reading the lore I'm reading the
lore you see how you see what they do to
me
chat they don't care about the
lore yeah I don't know about if I care
much about the power wash lore I know
I'm just cleaning that's how you find
out how I got like this oh don't you
want to know so what's the
tldr I don't know yet every time we
clear a certain percent it'll give us
more of the story ah okay someone was
going to show they were going to show
Santa a new a new star design and
they're bringing it in a box and
everyone is really excited and then dot
do dot now we're waiting for the rest
yeah
probably probably like goo
[Music]
star I think they're releasing a Dracula
movie for Christmas I want to watch it
what yeah Dracula for Christmas I know I
was Bamboozled I am excite maybe they
wanted to release for Halloween but it
got delayed maybe Halloween was probably
too competitive have you seen the V
housing
movie I don't I don't know I might have
but I forgot I want to re at some point
oh yeah you haven't haven't you there's
a fair few vampire movies and stuff you
haven't
seen watch Dracula dos
musical do musical right dos I love how
you you you you make the D sound so
important
D ah yes German
articles
yes this looks like Jinx was in here
yeah but I didn't watched the most
recent like new ones the first three I
watched from the second season mhm I
haven't seen any of them what about
season one I haven't seen any of them oh
not even season one no I'm waiting till
it's like done done and then I'm going
to watch it oh oh that was what I was
thinking no Co I very recently started
watching Arcane and it's so good it
makes me want to play
amazing you should play league it's fine
my chat tells me I shouldn't they're
lying
to but like as long as it's with friends
they say it's okay oh league is fun even
when you play with random people they're
so protective they're like don't don't
talk to strangers cuz they're
evil I got kidnapped and eating etal so
yeah
yeah that's an e Eternal how evil are
they going to be in League of Legends
they're going to yeah oh no it can't be
that bad they're going to Flame you
they're going to be toxic they're going
to tell their mommies on you wow not the
mummies yeah anything but the
mummies that's my favorite that's my
favorite character I'm at 11 at 8% eight
oh God it's fine wait what are you oh 12
it's fine there's no problem with that
we'll just be you you just have to reach
100% Raa it's okay yeah you love
reaching 100% yeah you got a prove
yourself to everyone it's not about
proving it's how the game works Shori
Noll yeah but how often am I going to
play this game no it it doesn't have
anything to do with that
I love how Shi is makinga Rage love it
do more please leave me alone I don't
deserve this I'm just telling you it's
just 100% you know I don't care about
reaching 100% but that's I don't know
about that you seem you seem to really
care about finish seem to care a
lot like seem really important to you
indeed I know we're just chilling and
yapping I'm like we don't have that I in
fact do not understand we're just
cleaning Arisa we're just playing power
watch with you guys again except for Liz
she understands me when we play sh right
this I will invite you for more
power thanks and Rea could just watch in
the
corner is try Harding I know she's mid
maxing
in this
game maxing
power I mean she is a pro at this so
yeah that's she's going to go into the
power wash Esports I know it I believe
you you guys you guys are never going to
get to Atlantis and that just makes me
sad Atlantis is where is that where the
Championships are being held no it's one
of the maps ah
oh thought you want us to just ground on
the water don't worry never getting to
Atlantis is kind of a thing and my
I so I need to continue the
tradition I
[Music]
see and now we went from Halloween to
Christmas I love
[Music]
Christmas speed running 2024 be like
hell yeah
[Music]
H the entrance Academy still has
dirt
lies don't believe it
no believe it believe
it let's go Naruto let's go Shori
oh we're going to save Sasuke I think I
sang that song in ger before wish became
a
thing what's song does the believe is
Naruto song that's
not he's really cool Sakura beautyful
right it was in German but I did sing it
in Koka before yeah it's
funny did they say Sakura was
cool yeah no they say SAS he's really
cool sasura the beautiful
beautiful y you do we have lad this time
that we can use there should be some
somewhere I'm not sure you can also use
an extender no it's more like I need to
like get a different like from above POV
so the Extender on help there there
should be one somewhere he's really
cool Sakura sakur beautiful the
Beautiful oh my God there's a window you
can see outside it's so
pretty let's break it
open are we
stuck but also I got to clean here why
do you think we're
stuck because she wants to break it open
to see the outside everyone start out
work said top is a mess oh there's like
an elf thing here like a shadow that's
cute I leave that for
now bangs was testing the durability of
their rocket ships on the ceiling whil
mullet was fine-tuning the high notes of
the
[Music]
xylophones not a
rosarians
raders the blood flame
Kingdom this is you
in my
life this is you guys except you're not
[Laughter]
dirty except remove the D and just just
take the
compliment are you raising your chat up
secretly oh I I would never mute and
talk to chat I'm I see your chat
reacting very fondly what did you say to
them cannot share with the class I said
to them they were uhoh stinky and they
need to go back in the
mines you told them they're
stinky well I mean I was saying there
there was they were like stinky
socks wow they seem to think they're
present
oh I guess something sweet is going On's
flirting with them cute
unbelievable even though we're right
here you're them how dare you yeah how
can you get distracted when these ladies
are around you you know uh you know
takanashi Ki you should be part of
Justice you're really good at
monitoring you know I should tell the
higher ups to like high are
you all right okay you want a second job
side job yeah I'll take it I'll help you
guys out you want to help me monitor
Advent
you know geographically I think there
there will be some good Synergy too I'm
close to Exodia was
it
ex that's a Yu-Gi-Oh
card I know it gets mistaken all the
time wait why is why is it laugh why are
they laughing cuz you
said exod Exodia which is a Yu-Gi-Oh
card [\h__\h]
because you're super strong you know no
wait what is it called it's
Exodia exard how do you spell it great
exia uh can you spell it e x a r d i a e
x a r i damn it close enough it's okay
close yeah I'm sure the Yu-Gi-Oh people
would be very flattered you thought that
it was AIA oh my God yeah there seem to
be a lot of people all of your chats
that's how great exia was made by the
gods one gave their arm another gave
their other arm and another gave their
torso and leg leg and so on and so forth
and that was our great tardio was made
wow that
great that's why I say by the
gods have you girls played Yu-Gi-Oh
before yes I used to be I'm a collector
of the cards when I was younger I
collected it for the pretty boys I had a
frog
deck frog I only played Magic the
Gathering that's okay I see I never got
into that I have friends who are very
into it the cards look really nice mhm
they're very
pretty yes I want more mature the
Gathering collaboration girl do you
don't know how many times I tried to get
perms for the online magic the Gathering
they they ignore me how could they do
that you're so cute I don't know they
don't give perms to anybody I guess
stop stupid chats
stop let me play please let me play your
[Music]
game I'm trying to do things the right
way mhm give
us
please just want to play games for those
who are new to the kingdom we do not
they decided to go down into the mines
themselves they decided to go down in
the mines himself I was just joking
along I would I have never asked anybody
to go into the mines that was but a Gest
in front of the
girls I'm getting pings pings
pings wow
reach there there are some ladders over
by the entrance if you're still looking
for them no not I'm trying to like get
really low get low low
low low low low
low [\h__\h] sweat pants and the reox with
the straps with the stra
no
I truck simulator before oh yeah
I'm pretty sure I saw that game what for
Euro Truck there's a multiplayer but
it's like off SCH technically I don't
know if you'd have perms for it honestly
H uh I'm pretty sure the ID girls have
played the multiplayer
version I'm multiplayer no you just
drive
together yeah but not in the same
vehicle right no no no a different
you're just do exist as fellow truck
drivers
oh but that's it
fun well if you don't Ram into each
other then you don't even need the
multiplayer mode you can just play the
single player mode at the same time yeah
I can Ram into each other you just can't
share the same vehicle I think oh so you
are on the same M time to get sick but
you like I don't think do much I've
jumped around too much that's my I my
bad I did this to myself can race each
other I've jumped around too much racing
with
tracks might as well just play Mario
Kart I did this to myself I got too
excited physics no parking but Mario
Kart has blue shells and you can hit
each other with it I did it to
myself you sound
trti
Mario I always get [\h__\h] over in Mario
Kart you know that's why you try not to
be first you have to be back and maybe
you can get there I gave up on trying to
get good you know my favorite racing
game
is Wacky Races on the PlayStation
one ooh sounds wacky yeah never heard of
it you never Watch the cartoon Wacky
Races no maybe that's like a exard thing
no no it's not it has Dastardly and mly
in it in
step and it has Penelope pit
Stu o I love
Penelope you remember it so well yeah
they ask you how you are and you're fine
but you're not fine you just they just
you just bring off a cartoon and they're
like I don't know what that is and even
though it's a really good cartoon and
it's fine it's whatever have you muted
yourself again herb yeah she's
talking stop talking [\h__\h] herb I just
keep M and going po po po po
po that's what I keep doing that like a
mating call
yeah stop doxing
me
stop yeah it's a CL it's a classic
cartoon but they made a a game as well
of it it was very much like Mario Kart
but with the wacky racist
characters nice
yeah I read a comment the other day when
in some collab stream I mentioned uh I
think it was an Eden Eternal I mentioned
tont town and everybody agreed that we
like we didn't really understand we only
played it a little bit uh but it's
somewhere of memories and I I read a
comment that made me realize that and
remember that the problem with t town
was that if you're young I guess um the
the beginning area that's free to play
is free to play and if you want to get
anywhere else in that game you have to
pay that's why I like only was in that
beginning area and I didn't understand
like where's the party going on like
where is everybody yeah turns out it's
not free to play what the heck it's a
freaking children's game I heard about
that game but I never played it
hard yeah it kind of makes sense in a
way I guess even RuneScape like there's
a free portion of the game that you can
explore and like 20 or some free quests
but then like a lot of the game is like
you have to actually become a
member narissa taking all our money what
do you click to like stand still and
just move around
your thank you yeah no
problem anything for you my angel of you
you say I tried avoiding like spending
money back then like my first game was
probably Terraria and only because I
wanted in a
giveaway game was ter
nice what what about like Pokemon and
stuff like that oh no for steam stuff
like I would have my parents pay for it
but I try not to bother my
parents like I'll get this for Christmas
Christmas Christmas is coming the keys
are getting fat please put the penny in
the old man's hat what if you haven't
got a penny I hate it will do if you
haven't got a God bless
you you're just making things up now
yep if that is making up on the spot
then you should be a freestyle Raptor
okay a to the be to the Z to the
D uh sick I really love
[Applause]
kfp
wow we've got a winner there we go I'm
going Rap
God look out Callie don't real quiet
since you dropped those
lines Miss F more you're going to need
to come here and defend yourself hurry
up no no no I love how every time any
Hol member is like trying to rap like a
you know like a newbie everybody in the
chat is always like ah call is been real
quiet oh [\h__\h] as if cie had any kind of
competition well regardless she's like
so unique as well with her rap so I I
don't think anybody could even like be
like her in general so unique yeah so
special very true go cie go Callie go
Callie I'm going to be right back and
get some
water really really are you sure are you
sure that's what you're going to do yeah
no I am are you not muting and talking
to your chat secretly
no let her mute and talk to her chat
that is her right as a streamer talk me
a job now to observe so now I'm
observing that's true monitoring okay
he's going to regret it now I'm on a
mission now we're at 50% completed wow
I'm wow me and my
[Laughter]
40% this is fine this game makes me
sweepy relaxing right I know it's also
going to give me arthritis
don't get
arthritis well you can't tell my R to do
that it has a mind of its own make them
stop okay you do the rest of the work
then just get good you'll be fine dang
you can do the rest of the work get your
100% you earned
it that's not how it works we have to do
it together because this is multiplayer
dang I love how all of us are avoiding
the ceiling we're like [\h__\h] that oh no
no I was the ceiling oh yeah I'll get
there yeah I have my own ceiling
here your own little area mhm this is my
corner it was made for
me just like it is your hole that was
made for you this is my hole get out my
hole this is where I
live then I bought more tech gadgets I
love having more Tech like what yeah
what' you get it's um like another
gimbal but it's like tinier and more
compact than the one I have oh gambles
let's go
yeah what are you going to do with it
well hopefully I would like to Vlog but
it depends on the area and the people
who don't get the [\h__\h] out of my
way like get out of here I'm trying to
Vlog and then there's some your
relatives around how to be like get out
of here get out of my Vlog get out of my
Vlog
Mommy it's my turn on the
Xbox only the best Vlogs for shy MH
we'll see about that
it's lot people around do you also um
did you also get like a extra like
microphone for your vloging oh no I do
mine silent because I don't want to talk
then you do voice over yeah yeah I also
would be like very embarrassed like last
time when I was in Japan I did a little
Vlog for uh I think I announced my 2.0
for my life to dend of it I think um but
yeah I I did like a vlog in Shinjuku uh
gave myself some missions to achieve and
and all that and I was like well I don't
want to do a voiceover I want to like
you know talk that to the camera
basically but I'm like really shy and
also awkward about it too so I just
brought my manager with me so that it
seems like I'm talking to my manager
while I'm filming things and that works
that helped a lot that's cute yeah so I
told to always like walk right next to
me so that I don't look like a freaking
weirdo myself yeah I can't do that I
don't want my relatives like knowing the
channel or anything I keep as hushed as
I can about
it like I'm just some won't mind me just
some video
editor yeah that's all they
know what if something's like way too
close but I have no other way to reach
it either like when you're so close that
you can't like clean it you know what I
mean it's it's hard it sometimes it's
rough like that man what cracker I love
crackers I think I got I hate their
facial hair so why it's so soft and
fuzzy no I'm I'm A Yank
It okay Queen you live your truth yank
no facial hair in my world but noval if
you got facial hair you're okay it's
okay no no she said what she said
novalie she won't accept you she's gonna
y out your hair one by facial hair yeah
but I'm not going to hate you for
it no it's okay keep your facial hair
some you guys probably like
it yeah don't make them feel bad for
facial hair cuz I can do whatever I want
right just look better with facial hair
let's be real oh yeah yeah I think so
too but but not fictional characters for
me sorry you guys have to yank it
off pi to meet you with facial hair no
way get out of maybe not although he
would look less like a little baby if he
had faal hair I like being baby I like
nice
Demitri you like nice baby boy Demitri
yeah what he grows up into I hate to
tell you I didn't like that Arc I was
going to punch bunch of crap out of
it character AI so bad for what he turns
into there are definitely good-looking
characters that have facial hair
definitely name name a few name a few I
don't know does Sid have facial hair in
Final Fantasy I think he has like a
little bit Sid right blonde dude there
is so many different SIDS what s are oh
[\h__\h] right I
forgot the
Sid has some yeah okay depends on which
Sid but Sid has
some I guess I guess Leon from Final
Fantasy could be okay with SH you like
curs things now yeah let me give you a
good example you can't tell me that
Santa Claus doesn't look good with his
facial hair but to be fair s bab a
grandpa excuse
me wellow he's rocking it I I don't want
to say he's
like how dare you dissmiss Claus's taste
Nissa thank you for the backup I'm
saying he's my grandfather I'm not going
to look at him in that way your grand
your grand of course well that's going
to be awkward
now who knew Santa Claus was a demon you
going be Mrs Santa Claus I mean pretty
much everything you see that is like a
weird creature is probably like a demon
let's be honest imagine going around the
whole entire world in one night and
delivering presence you think anyone
could do that yeah powerful humans like
me you're
different Santa Claus could be human
he's my
idol he's your idol you got to make him
dance I want to hear a song
covers wow Santa Claus covers Idol
[Laughter]
he going to crack some bones po old
guy oh he's very
Nimble I read like some uh I think this
book called cringle which is before
Santa became Santa and when I read that
I just imagine him as an anime character
is Santa Claus real yeah yeah okay good
that we have established that it was
important why why wouldn't he be
[Music]
I've never seen
him well he you must be on the naughty
list yeah he doesn't want to get doxed
yeah yeah he's an idol M
yeah not very believable but
okay what if Santa is just like anyone
with a good heart yeah I like that
theory
yeah I think he's the guy that
goes oh what uh Tim Allen yeah oh yeah
yeah yeah I was think saggy from
Scooby-Do or
Scooby I do that a lot Scooby go
I I had a phase uh I think last year
where I watched from beginning to end
all of the seasons of that show what
Home Improvement yeah it's so good now
that I watch it as an
adult I think I just watched episodes
like randomly in random order when I was
a child but like now as an adult it it
gives you a whole new POV and you really
end up liking the
mom cuz I think as a child I didn't care
about the mom character but now she's
really I like her cool what exactly is
the show about is it just like this dude
who owns like a construction stuff and
he does he has a TV show doesn't he yeah
he has a TV show and he likes you know
doing stuff in the house and car and he
messes up his own house the whole time
too but they have kids they have free
boys and in the beginning of the show
you can really see the actors are really
young and so they grow up like a lot
over the course of the show they become
adult and yeah they go for life and and
puberty and the mom is like always
frustrated with her husband but it's
funny it's like really
funny you know
yes I heard that that was a show that
turned his life around cuz he he had
like a criminal record before I don't
know what from he got his [\h__\h] together
and then he started like acting and then
he became like a good role model he had
a criminal criminal record it probably
just like a DUI I don't
know you have to Google it nah no way
not him
oh what he was a deer he Tri his s
around yeah what oh my God he like walon
Breaking
Bad but he's learned he got his life
together he became
an that's crazy what the heck they're
bid in lore damn mhm the
archives can't stop
[Laughter]
grunting let's do it Scooby-Doo goes
I like Shaggy and
Scooby who doesn't they're cute yeah I
like them in the live action movie too
yeah oh my God the live action is way
too good like way better than it has any
right
being that's one of the really good like
uh was it cartoon to
IRL
um
uh uh adaptations I think it really is
because literally the Shaggy actor in
that went on to play Shaggy
for like a really long time as like his
voice
yeah after
that they were on point with the
casting yeah they were and Adam family
is another really good
casting live action
movies always it's crazy
yeah I think it's interesting because
Daphne's actress and Fred's act actor
are married in real life yeah
[Music]
cute it's
Buffy yeah Buffy mm I love Buffy it's
interesting cuz that's they just kind of
[\h__\h] around in the cartoon depending on
the version of it yeah
spicy haven't watched it can't judge
you've never seen scoy
dooo not
really there's like a different seasons
of it some are better than other
yeah the show definitely went through a
lot of like change changes yeah like
different writers
[Music]
voices around for a long
time true a
classic classic
Han I should buy like a a big giant
Nutcracker I was tempted before yeah no
reason I just like them should do a nut
cracking stream
[Music]
to crack nut what why not yeah I don't
know it's because they're not really
like meant for it they're how how can
you get
in why are they called nutcrackers if
they're not supposed to crack nuts maybe
people crack their nuts Oh Oh I thought
you meant you're not supposed to crack
nuts in
general well with them like you know
their mouth I don't think you're
actually supposed to put uh nuts in
there it's more just like
cute okay I heard they used to actually
be able to like take it
maybe I can crack them with my thighs I
don't need yeah hell
yeah always always done
that it's just how I do it eyes a steal
man do me do me
in my
presence for sister sh in front of these
present
wow oh this
chairman I can't get this slay to
Ping but I'm like I'm pretty sure it's
clean so I'm like
hello h
well we're having a fun time we got to
get that I'm thinking about it wait let
see like an actual good Scooby-Doo game
I'm sure there's one
somewhere I need to get um some point
and click Adventures of it I feel like
getting it mhm it's so ining I love
point and cck Adventures have you guys
played the wait do no I think that's is
that German only Angela Anaconda no I've
never you know it I know what you're on
about yeah they you know the absolutely
cursed game uh no but I but I do
remember it cuz they had Angela and AA
before the Digimon
movie maybe maybe it was only popular in
like
Europe I think it was made in Australia
wasn't it
oh it felt so C saying it's a terrible
show yeah they had this point and click
game it was so cursed everything was
cursed cursed point and
click I like the style of Animation to
like cut out yeah it was very original
very
unique never
mind
CH I'm so hungry you're chill you're
hungry yeah did you not eat anything
today m well I did but it's like uh
almost midnight now so the last time I
ate is a while ago I need to eat
din B and then I hopefully I need to
sleep early but I took a nap today again
I'm such a freaking idiot why do I keep
on taking naps but I was really tired
and I I did some stuff that that tired
out my arms too my noodle arms are like
so weak because I I carried stuff from
the from the post
office I carried plates some Maybe
honin yeah it doesn't really work that
well on me but um it's kind of like iffy
I'll still take it hoping that will work
yeah and maybe you can get those uh
heated eye masks maybe that could help
ah I think I still have them but uh I
don't know they're they're not like the
most am amazing thing for
me try it try it maybe it'll help with
I'll try one of my animation lectures at
Uni work the scoy car that's really
cool worked alongside Chuck Jones of
Looney Tes and 3D teacher my best uh
worked on Star Wars episode one oh wow
that's cool I'm going to try clearing my
backlog what experien
teachers that's an experience right
there I want to play my time at Sandro
we don't have perms for it oh P Baby W
yeah she's tired I mean a
game it's like a it's like a farming
game except it's not really farming it's
more like engineer I think yeah yeah
yeah the only crappy thing is I don't
like the the environment you're in a
desert and I think you're supposed to
make you're in a desert like grass yeah
you're in a desert but with your
engineering skills you might be able to
give it grass
M and you can marry people
oh
great well but why would you want to
marry anybody but
Dimitri because you can't marry Dimitri
more than once in a game and that's it
well you want aren't you happy with that
is that not satisfactory to you no I
need more content I got to I got to go
with the flow yeah I need to get my
adrenaline and my
dopamine my
serotonin wait serotonin is what like
the Happy thing right
yeah yeah dop and serotonin are both
there they're
[Music]
related man Santa needs to hire a
maid that's not us we are the the hire
help yeah we're getting paid for
this I don't know I feel like we should
demand a r or maybe more Christmas
presents yeah it's Santa so we he at
least has to for sure bring us a present
I know I better be in a good list I'm
bringing Santa a Pikachu this
Christmas I Pokmon released the dub
released like some original Christmas
songs back in the day no what I didn't
know that until a few years back when I
was just randomly on Spotify looking up
Pokmon songs and it came up with the
this like tunes and I was like oh holy
oh my God I didn't know that kind of
amazing I need to watch a new Pokemon
there's a cute a villain in there oh oh
yeah he has black and white hair too ooh
I hope he's competent but I doubt
it yeah in in Pokemon it's you
know yeah he's like you can for what's
his name is it Larry who's Larry
Gary oh my God no it's a Pokemon like
human not not an actual po no no I know
but if his name is Larry because
Gary
oh that would
be all I know is a villain and then the
new Pokemon has two protagonists like
some girl and some
boy
yeah I don't know is he not a a a mytho
let me check I miss Ash
already they're probably tired of voice
acting yeah it's a mytho then Ash's at
least English voice actress is still
going strong yeah who else are they
voicing um there's that one anime that
came out I don't remember what it's
called but it's like got that Russian
girl and uh the English voice for ash
she also speaks Russian fluently so she
got that role because that's a
that's one of the big things about it uh
is like she speaks Russian but like and
doesn't realize the main character can
speak it so she acts like she's saying
mean things to him she's like yeah yeah
yeah I see I see yeah all yeah all
yeah I know what you're talking about
not going to watch it but I know that's
Ash's voice actress it's
crazy Ash want a long way to becoming a
Pokemon Master to becoming like this
ring girl
now I didn't realize those was Gunk on
the
ceiling yeah yeah you didn't realize
until now no I had a Daddy Daycare
moment of you know when the kid goes I
missed and then he he walks in and he's
like oh looks around and looks up and
he's like oh God
[Music]
else go like like randomly I can't make
that
noise but cie does a
good close enough I also do like random
sounds like
uh no I don't mean to it's just one of
my things yeah I mean you could do ASMR
then cuz that's most of the the mouth
noises mouth
M it's your
destiny youren ASMR P ASMR
yeah just talk about your day I mean
that's ASMR too just whisper about your
day yeah oh I have a dead body it's not
a real dead body my cats live in it and
it's just you know I got it for
Halloween but it's not Halloween it's
for Christmas too you know so okay there
you could do
that I'm your ASMR
manager yeah she's going to write all
your scripts for you and then you just
have to record them do you like writing
scripts I don't mind if if I have
time yeah that's the thing yeah it's
time yeah so many
projects yeah yeah time is a precious
resource these days I
know I just want my time to slack
off I might be looking for a script
writer oh maybe what kind of script
writer oh no no
uh uh personal uh spicy movie you know
oh
movie wow are you going to
movie uh secret secret NDA m oh okay
okay well I I wish you luck I wish you
luck anyone who wants to apply maybe
she'll have a a listing for you yes yes
I'll be setting it out via DM yeah
mhm and I love doing random projects so
yeah I want to do this I want to do
that but why I just feel like
it hey that's valid a reason as ever
yeah
yeah the only reason you need to do
anything I want to mhm
yep well you should I mean you should be
passionate about you know what you're up
to makes the project even
better there no purpose but it's fun M
oo wow that side is pretty clean nice
nice I'm doing pretty good oh gosh it's
hours oh 75 you need to go
uh kind of
uh if you have to go get
gone
yeah get out of here it's just power
wash
we no I didn't mean that in a mean way I
didn't mean it in a mean mys and then
she just tells me to go away so over I
don't want you to leave how will I ever
live without you back to she Raven
wow she she used that same line on me
how am I going to live dad you and I
said you have Liz it's
okay me you have find yourself in a
pickle narissa how about how about Liz
make sh then come on Liz let's go all
right go ahead I don't care d
messages here she says she doesn't care
but I think she cares damn I know she
cares about that 100% too oh my God I do
100% we'll go we'll go out and look for
a cute Christmas dress for
you I like
shopping me
too I like we all like
shopping well I mean I know some some
people don't you know they don't even
like window
shopping yeah yeah I don't like shopping
that much anymore oh don't even window
shopping and great happiness now it's
stressful and I don't know it's like
hard to
choose
and yeah I love window
shoping clothes I love looking around
may or may not fit my tee also you get
your steps in walking around Mall yeah
that's true then you think that online
shopping will maybe take the stress away
but no online shopping has it own
problems like you don't know what you're
getting you won't know if it's
fitting too lazy to send it back was
look in
person yeah yeah but then there's some
shops that I really like there's one
shop in particular that I really really
like um but for me they only have an
online shop because like their real IRL
shop is in the country far away from me
but I really want to go there and and
try out all the dren you have to go then
come with me
okay okay that was easy that was easy I
mean if the clothes are cute it it
benefits both of us we can both try it
out right hell yeah I think you saw me
wearing one of their dresses before ooh
if it's what I think then yes I want to
try on their stuff so
bad oh I might not I'm not sure which
one what's your typical fashion for
stuff I remember you saw me in my weird
[Music]
dresses oh sorry well um H my typical
fashion I used to one that you're will
to share yeah no it's fine I used to
dress kind of like how bio dresses now
but that's like when I was younger
nowadays it's like a very toned down
version of it mhm
maybe I like to dress kind of elegant
now but have still like cute Vibes and
like frilles and stuff here and there
but not too much and less patterns just
simple they still cute
cute I've also become so lazy that I
just go in my pajamas everywhere
nowadays yeah that's how you know you're
growing up
I don't give any [\h__\h]
anymore yeah I mean especially if you're
just going out to the grocery store who
cares yeah I mean I still wear dresses
but that's cuz I don't like pants yeah I
like
dresses but in the winter
time a bit more difficult yeah I like
winter fashion like bundling up wearing
wear my dress pants I I double up on the
tights usually if I'm wearing a a dress
oh yeah yeah I put two
considerated ones uh I mean sometimes I
wear those
too
yeah I like those ones a lot but I
always feel like the the ankle area
looks ugly for some
reason yeah sometimes I want the pattern
like so that that's why I double on the
like pattern ones
dude yeah I need to eat after this I
just had Jag is my food
Jag you still have jug did you bring it
from Japan no no no no there's a there's
a some Asian
oh or like International Foods or
whatever I guess do you usually go for
the snacks and those shops like that
it's a small it's a very very small
selection so if I pass by the story like
I I'll get it
mhm not
whole yeah it's like oh they got this
wow one of the things I like to get from
Asian shops is the lamun
is like I'm of like fizzly I'm not
familiar I I I know the drink
though was it was it fizzy yeah is it
carbonated yeah lemon is fizzy yeah yeah
but not too crazy not too
much not like a fresh Coca-Cola I
thought it was fun to it I I wouldn't
drink it then but I like the look of it
just open it up and let it stand for a
while oh
oh carbon I actually like when
carbonated things have uncarbonated
themselves oh like the I don't mind it
huh I know some people are like oh my
God that's insane I like when they're
uncarbonated too but sometimes I feel
like the flavor is just weird and that
they rely on the carbonation to make it
taste quote unquote good I like uh
lemonade
uncarbonated yeah like
oh yeah sorry I I correct myself because
over in great exia lemonade is usually
considered like Sprite and 7even up and
all that oh uh and then the the uh
American lemonade is cloudy lemonade
over here cloudy lemonade you're going
to have to do like a lessons and ex it's
funny because it's or at least in in my
area it was it's considered like Posh to
have like cloudy lemonade
so when I visited like Fria and then
like the go-to was like cloudy lemonade
I be like w
fancy cloudy lemonade I love
lemonade me too it's my favor especially
I feel good for water though I feel bad
for calories yeah same got to be mindful
of the figure you know
M guys oh and then and then also for the
10 time in great Exodia SL what you say
shades of Greenland uh uh what what it
called when you have a
uh that's my code name for it at the
moment until I reveal more of the great
exian map uh uh uh what is it so usually
if you have like a bit of a an upset
tummy you like given a flat a flat
Sprite really yeah
that's so interesting yeah yeah that's
that's right over where you are it's a
ginger ale right that's the go-to fizzy
and all oh fizzy
oh no she she's saying that uh they they
do uh
give uh un busy spray for it oh as we
like here we do ginger
ale I just suffer
ging I don't really like ginger medicine
what the heck really I don't really like
most pops but I really like ginger ale I
still won't go out of my way to drink it
but like if it's presented to me I won't
say
no I don't like ginger ale wow I'm alone
in my I think I'm going sure what it
tastes like I barely have it I think I'm
POS going to hop because I'm getting a
little bit motion sticky so no me okay
thanks for playing with us yeah thanks
for having
me thank you thank you lots of fun thank
you thanks for thinking of me have fun
don't forget I'm watching you now oh
God all right I need to get this I get
out of this game before I start washing
more
things all right I can quit
uh oh
gosh holy moly
my tom
tom all right my
lovely who W I think part I think last
time me and Nissa only did like two
hours but I I was pretty I was pretty
much okay just one of those days just
one of those days who who would have
thought I'd need my scky bands for
power I did jump around a lot though I
was
silly I was silly and I jumped around a
[Laughter]
lot oh
dear all right we'll we'll raid over to
Shori uh we'll redirect over to Shi send
over a a wonderful war cry we're going
to war cry over to
shiy thank you so much for being awesome
as usual in chat and thank you ruse for
the
redirect uh I hope you had fun
rusos and the rosarians I hope you had a
great time too and everybody who's new
to the blood flame Kingdom thank you for
stopping by thank you for the
memberships the continued memberships
the gifted
memberships I'm not an artist but I'm
going to draw blood Raven art W well I'm
ex I'm always excited to see arts on Z
Twitter I love seeing everybody's art
and creativity I just love creativity so
you know we your Muse that's that's uh
that's really
cool that's really sweet yeah yeah yeah
I look forward to seeing it um but yeah
thank you for the supers and being so
sweet as usual
everybody and I hope you all have a
great rest of your evening your morning
afternoon
evening make sure to eat good Noms
hydrate and do something lovely for
yourself because you're all very very
lovely don't forget to do that okay got
to look after yourselves because you
know the blood flame Kingdom we are we
are strong together and we got to make
sure that we are also okay too
mhm uh I need to sort out the redirect
let's do
that that was really
fun it was nice doing the power wash
with the
ladies shiy
the mine will be safe with
us G Don
[Laughter]
it all right I will love you and leave
you parting is such sweet Sor but I will
see you on tomorrow I'll see you um for
when we we celebrate nissa's birthday
yay excited excited we're going to all
wish narissa a big big happy birthday
and have lots of
fun
mhm okay
[Music]
goodbye wait let my voice be your
strength there we go byebye
[Music]
w
he