kiana looks weird on her stream eh yeah
it's like kind of
pixelated
hello we have come together today
to the special occasion of the first
ever
collaboration between hololive
i am very honored to be here today
thank you so much you are legendary like
a
legendary card in the gaza game and i
would wait for you sealed well for me
with the with the rainbow frame and the
sparkly animation on it
you would spend your life savings on me
yeah i think yeah
i would probably even go in into the
miners for ya
i would take a loan and go into a deep
deep dab but
i don't know how to pronounce it
don't go into dubbed there's a bunch of
games from all over the world is mancala
do you know one color
no you know this one no you know this
game because i remember that from my
childhood i think
and blow no what do you think about
chess
i feel trepidation and fear and dread
i feel like an energy radiating off of
you
i am a chess master of disaster do you
know how to play blackjack
i don't know how to play it pretty much
all these card games
can i ask you something emotional yes
my heart i don't know a lot of these
games
did you just not have any friends
how did you know isn't that why we're
all here you're controlled by the way
color change i'm sorry that was pretty
that was pretty rough but
i i want to say hey i didn't really have
many friends either but i know
many of these games wait how did i get
second
because well luck
no more like uh um
yeah i am the absolute master
at this game i have destroyed so many
people of this game
i can't even comprehend what you could
be thinking right now
universe galaxy brain you have to stop
thinking like a cat
don't always aim right away for the box
think outside of the box think about the
line
yeah you already made a perfect pattern
for me here thank you
i'm gonna be taking those and i think
that's it for now
oh uh so i'll just uh draw another
normal line
no impossible yeah it is real have mercy
please
let me teach you for the future so you
can
walk in in my master of disaster
footsteps one day
do something in this area which you
could then continue because i can do
only one stroke and that won't finish
the box and you could continue then
finishing this
this this can go down that way right or
i could go here
and then finish that one and you could
then continue to finish it and get way
more boxes make sense
get it yes
i understand completely
[Laughter]
that's not very impressive that's the
latin name
for it it is a ancient greece technique
for lots and boxes
[Music]
that was very close you were so close
yeah it was really close game and i
definitely understood
everything here's a few games that you
might know how to play tennis
yeah okay i serve
let's go yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
i think some kind of time delay for the
game this is not an excuse
bro that's the power of the
phoenix oh that's
30 30. get that on perfect
wait isn't that a word for nevermind
you know english is really not my first
language by the way my first language is
german i was just asking you
for a little bit about it
[Music]
feeling my fighting spirit
i didn't feel like i was being like
mentally broken do you want to feel
mentally broken again
no okay then i guess we shouldn't play
chest and
[Laughter]
we are at a standstill an
unstoppable force meets an immovable
object
[Applause]
don't be scared to ask questions i'm
here for you
okay i'll get you oh
[Music]
okay did you just tell me to move
diagonally yeah
oh really are you sure about that you
think that was the best move you could
do
do you want to be my magic eight ball
i'll ask you a question okay in the
future
will i be living in the castle filled
with cats
shake shake shake shake and
[Music]
maybe you could have given me a yes for
that one
i'm a magic people okay let me i'll be
your manager now ask me a question
um will i have any friends
in the future
[Music]
but i don't know how to play any games
well that has nothing to do with not
like having friends though you just have
to ask them to teach you more games
you're right you're absolutely right oh
my god my
huh my hole do you hear me yeah i hear
you
did you hear me oh i got my whole
my whole pc just kind of blank
[Music]
hello thank you yeah you're back
we've been really nice
[Music]
i'm familiar with this one i played this
with the
rats in the sewer
i um that's the
oh i'm winning
damn it we're gonna do another one okay
that was too fast
you're not getting this one you thought
you were getting that one huh
or did you even not know what you were
doing i i usually don't know what i'm
doing
see this is not going to happen no no no
no you blocked me
of course i did we are forming one
big block see that this is beautiful
don't destroy it
it sounds so pretty but that's okay
thank you
oh god i got so smug
for one more game can we do black check
do you think i know how to play block
let's win against the cpus
oh they got 16 they're adding they go to
17 okay
oh let's see if you use one now you're
gonna draw because you got the same
number as the
pillar okay now you get the gist
yes i understand now i can feel my soul
being overtaken by the spirit of
gambling
don't don't don't let that happen that's
not good oh they got a 20.
12 15 17 and thanks to ow
oh you guys are wrong we got
uh at least more than the dealer yay
i'm gonna bet 30.30
i would love to bet even more 35.
i'm feeling a little crazy now yeah
if you get an ace and a queen then
you're automatically blackjack and i've
pretty much already won this round
lucky cats
[Music]
rub off on me a little bit so i can have
some luck
when you're wrapped rub against me rub
rub rub rub rubber
you have to look there you go i don't
have headlines i promise
okay obviously i'm winning this round
unless just
you're the only winner
are you kidding me rub on me more keep
rolling keep hoping
[Music]
and the final winner is
want to say thank you for collabing with
me
thank you so much for collabing with me
i'm so
so so honored i look up to you so much
you're so cool
and i love you and
she's amazing she's a legendary
i usually say something in german do you
want to say it with me yes i would love
to
the whole phrase is and in german we say
three two one and in german we say
au sweden
yeah okay
[Music]
you