foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
and I am nervous
yes I'm nervous now I should just keep
the loading screen until like 55 minutes
in
and then and then I show up and then I
show the outfit
imagine I mean advert reveals most of
the time
you can skip until the very end anyway
because
it doesn't happen so often that I can
reveal a new outfit these days I know in
the beginning of myths lifetime
uh it was like you know spammed we got
so many new outfits but nowadays it's
like one per year but my 2022 outfit
uh is the one I'm revealing now today in
2023 so there's been delays going on
foreign
Ohio
yeah
[Music]
I haven't I feel like I haven't done
this in
a long time
uh
uh oh God I'm nervous
uh also I realized I had to like restart
the PC right before the stream because
like something was
audio audio tech was being weird again
so I was like I have a five is before
the Stream I've restarted
[Music]
but everything looks fine and I'm
drinking Coca-Cola
uh to keep myself awake oh I'm pretty
awake I I could have honestly taken a
nap
I felt like it a little bit
but
for the snare oh
kincho
I just came
home in case you didn't aren't following
what I've been up to
at the beginning of this week
after like streaming once on Monday from
home
afterwards I left to fly to Japan for
like
basically four I don't know if it was
four days or four nights
[Music]
um
but it was really really short
my second Japan trip this month
uh yeah and I came back a few hours ago
um
[Music]
um I I just came back and I'm like you
know originally I didn't want to do it
on the day of my return because I
thought oh I'm who knows what's gonna
happen maybe I'm too tired maybe I'm too
exhausted
um but I mean for just an hour it's fine
just a short typical one hour outfit
reveal
guys why isn't Super chato Why why
thank you
ah
yeah oh god
um yeah I've been preparing this for a
while
uh this outfit
I want to I guess explain some things
but maybe I do this later after going
through the
um through the predictions
and then and then I mean you know I'll
make it pretty like classic but there's
one thing uh that's not so classic one
thing where I put uh extra
money budget into it
so you'll see that but
um yeah is it okay I don't know is it
okay to already start showing pictures I
don't even
I don't know how this stuff works
anymore
foreign
[Music]
should I should I okay well
okay ah I'm nervous
okay okay uh
[Music]
my review that is so true oh my God
or is it my reveal
[Music]
bye
I've been sent some pictures
so we shall take a look at them what
does it mean
what's it mean
[Music]
was this the right one I don't want to
make any mistake yep it was
okay first one
is from
[Music]
sinner made a really edgy dark one I
feel like a lot of people went for an
edgy dark look
probably because of the uh announcement
image
it's so cool though like I love
this part here with the belts of the
shiny stuff and all the Flames here
the blue flames and the the interesting
eye
the smirk
yeah this is this is pretty dope I like
the color combination of black and like
a bright shiny blue Isn't it nice it's
SUNY SUNY
I would say it's only chuni if you think
of this design and this you know girl as
someone who is trying to be something
they're not but maybe she this depicted
woman is actually really what you see
right there you know what I mean
you know what I mean
[Music]
she is just evil and dark and and I
don't know edgy by default that's just
her you know
um
yeah
but yeah I think like you know the the
silhouette had
many uh like elements that already like
kind of force you into a certain
direction so most people drew like you
see my mouse right most people drew like
something like Wings around here
and like the legs the type of shoes and
these like knee thingies uh usually yeah
everybody did like pretty similar things
yeah but this one this one's really cool
actually might be one of my favorites
actually surprisingly starting off with
one of my favorites yeah
yeah very specific shapes
so no
no no
um
okay let's go next though I hope I'm
going another good Pace I have I don't
know how many I have maybe 15 20.
next we have oh
spooky from Anna vistir alavistia
a prediction with white
grayish bluish hair
and really evil eyes [\h__\h] wow a gun evil
but I'll tell you guys one thing like
generally we are not allowed to do like
such a
huge change of hair color you know
like I I can change like you know the
highlights and everything but not the
base color so
I doubt that even though I wish because
that's like kind of my favorite type of
hair color
yummy nude
[Music]
foreign
yes beautiful then
um some some Burns fabric which that is
actually something that I've had in mind
for like other outfits where I wanted
that to be used
what didn't happen but actually I should
go back to that idea and have burnt
Fabrics would be nice yeah and lots of
armor again and of course these feathers
um
yeah well well well well
is this accurate or not I don't know I
wonder
sing though um
after immediately after I put up the
the the teaser image the announcement
image
I think it was because Twitter cropped
the image on my phone
the the silhouette after I put up the
silhouette
because it was such a narrow tall image
uh
it was like cropped and I think it was
this area that was like highlighted on
Twitter
and
[Music]
it immediately that was the first time
after I uploaded it when it was already
too late but that was immediately when I
was like
and I I show my phone to jenma who was
sitting next to me because I uploaded it
right after the collaboration right the
off collab and I know there's something
looks like a peepee
I didn't trip like that
thing on yeah
[Music]
I
[Applause]
I can't see it and jenma was like no no
no I don't know what you're talking
about I'm like no I I I'm sure I will
not be the only one who sees it
that what happened what happened why
uh well
we'll we'll Wawa end up having
a new attachment or not we will see you
soon
[Laughter]
once you go uh yeah okay moving on
oh this one is like one of the few ones
that went into a not dark Direction
going very white and pinkish cute
[Music]
still like some like armor stuff
although this this kind of armor
I don't know what it is but it gives me
I'm about to describe it
like it's so uh sci-fi-ish no I don't
know yeah right
[Music]
indeed I guess I could I could see that
I like the hair so fluffy
cute and I like this like light fabric
it looks like really light and sheer and
and flowy
um I do like generally I like this whole
top area quite a bit
yeah
this ribbon oh actually this is like
I mean it's just a draft but I feel like
one could make something out of this
this is from Bonnie AKA local duck head
by the way thank you for your prediction
very stylish it's pretty it's I think
I mean
my kimono was pretty like bright colored
right but
um
no I guess I do have a lot a couple of
bright colored outfits
but this is like the brightest that I
would ever be I think
very pretty it's like xion
like xion
[Music]
from Tales of a rice you say that it's
interesting that you say that
oh well that reminds me of something
actually
[Music]
let me do one thing
ah
porno classic I retweeted my
my my my outfits thingy
[Music]
I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll do
this
in a little bit okay yeah thank you for
the prediction how are we doing with
time it's 20 hmm
I did for me in like nine minutes
I think okay
I think we're doing good time wise
um
[Music]
so next we have from Captain meow
kind of a girl
[Music]
it's just like
this gives me a desk dusk that's the
word I'm looking for Dusky Vibes oh and
somebody's saying fire blood
I see
it's like uh uh those Riders uh like on
top of the flying flying horses
well yeah it could be a valkyrie
but again
cannot make such a drastic hair color
change unfortunately
but besides that generally a cute
Valkyrie look
um
oh yeah the like necklace part here
reference to my shield and everything oh
and we still have like this spelled book
kind of stands out to me
like overall
RPG Vibes but the belt buckle gives me
toy vibes
well it's because a lot of my
default outfit does look like a toy I
guess
um
yeah yeah yeah again we see again
repeating the
the feathers well who knows will it
actually be feathers I don't know I
can't say
oh wait it's The the hair piece
it's kind of in the shape of a
I would I would first say dragon but
it's probably more like supposed to be a
phoenix maybe because I'm a phoenix
because I'm not a dragon but I don't
know
cool yeah I see it here the head and the
the arms
spiky spiky Flames I guess or I'm a
hedgehog
maybe I'm a dark Hedgehog now
[Music]
Sanic Shadow Sonic or something I don't
know we'll never know
okay next up
cinnamonzanita
this one stood out a lot because it's
like so different
I'm getting like Street fashion Vibes
but also
Valkyrie Vibes but also I don't know so
many different vibes from this
I really like the jacket part
with the buttons and the badges and
everything also the jacket is on fire
the hairstyle too though
wow I mean I feel like these kind of
like bangs they're they're pretty
um
almost covering up one eye depending on
depending on the angle and win situation
maybe
yeah but I do like the hairstyle and
overall like there's a lot going on here
and you you didn't normally you know
fill out the silhouette you also did
like some extra
I'm cutting it off here but
the chicken some extra drawings look at
that chicken it's like a blob it's
melting it's but it's doing a rock and
roll side
Hawaiian
uh okay
let me fix this again
oh oh but I guess you know there's some
edgy Parts about it because of those
those nails and the lip piercing I got a
lip piercing
now that whole life is slowly bringing
out you know the 3.0 in an order that
seems pretty random uh
I think now that girls are able to put
out their tongue maybe in future outfits
we should some of us should start
implementing lip piercings I don't know
just an idea who will do it first
who will think of it first oh but ah
wait no never mind because I think uh
3.0 is only being implemented in the
default outfits
so you would have to have a
tongue piercing by defaults
foreign
[Music]
that's I think a bit different uh her
that's not 3.0 that's her getting an
update overall of like art style of her
default outfit because her artist's art
style kind of changed
that's a bit different from what I'm
talking about
um
to what default has a lot of questions
yeah so wouldn't it like actually kind
of fit if you know she gets 3.0 and then
bam she turns out she has a tongue
piercing
yeah well thank you Christina
next is
whoa another very dark one and this time
we got pants
oh
pants style and also like barely any
like you know Mia
sorry mommy's busy Mommy is an important
stream right now but I'll continue
cuddling with you in a moment
ah but like barely any Skin showing
in in this one which
isn't that nice too don't you think not
everything has to show like a lot of
skin don't you agree guys
[Music]
staring at me at me she's looking at the
outfits she's judging them she wants to
see it too agreed
okay good
good good yeah nice I like the the again
armor parts and the hairstyle oh very
angry eyebrows I love this artist's like
way of drawing eyes by the way like
stands out so much to me and also you
drew the the hairpiece also in a very
interesting design of like some gems
inside
super cool and oh
I mean there's barely any like Skin
showing but
I don't know where that chain is going
that's interesting
[Music]
wait like seriously where is it going
look
[Music]
um
let's not think about it too much okay
maybe it's the thing that's dangling
down at the bottom in the silhouette
spicy chain
indeed spicy
yeah thank you for this very cool
submission
[Music]
I want to see more more and more like
this
what
what you
may have had the most original idea for
what to do with the side Parts because
that that those are chainsaws right
genius how did you think of this this is
by deep deep upsaurus uh AKA drawing
debuff
[Music]
oh and my
um
that's what that is
okay
yeah like that kind of mask is like from
some kind of horror game or horror movie
that I definitely wouldn't play a watch
please no like honestly such a creative
and fun idea
um but I have to I have to decline
this is not something I would go for
um
I don't want to be carrying around too I
can't even like how could I lift this I
can only lift two kilogram per hand
foreign
[Music]
with the bangs to the side kind of like
it gives me kind of like a
I don't know lumberjack
[Music]
no
it's like looks like it's like gel to
the back I don't know
no I'm too embarrassed to show my
forehead no
no
now please know I'm too shy
oh
but it looks really cool
very very creative always happy to have
some creative submissions
um
[Music]
your submission wow I like how you like
the color scheme you went for and the
balancing of it
and still the hairstyle like everybody
has been saying Oh short hair Chihuahua
short hair Chihuahua but you managed to
make it into uh twin Tails like really
low sitting twin tails
oh and another like bird accessory
and we get a chicken like a secret
secret society agent or something like
that
very useful
cute
[Music]
I like the
what do you call this again
uh
this fabric
I forgot
lace lace and then what's chunkers is
being so so needy
I already cuddled so much with her ever
since I came back but it has only been a
couple of hours since I came back to my
home after the Japan trip so please
forgive her for being very interested in
me being back
I haven't even gone for that long well
yeah yeah I like it I like the shape of
it I like the ideas very creative the
cape
the cape you know
ah it reminds me of like
in games
like
this this part but like longer for
covering the whole body
kind of reminds me of like um
Saint characters I don't know yeah Mages
right
yeah yeah yeah you get what I mean
um
white beige I don't know something like
that yeah priests
I feel like I've seen something like
this before move out all the lace and
all the other stuff of course
[Music]
next we have Hikari elmi oh
dark dark fancy fire background blue
fire so you went with
lots of Skin showing and being barely
covered up with some feathers why not
I mean honestly like
I feel like we've always like ever since
I never talked about all kiwawa needs to
show her true Phoenix form but can't
unleash it because belt cannot be
unbuckled
well this this could be something like
that though right Phoenix form half bird
or or maybe who knows maybe that's what
what I always have under my tops and you
just don't see it normally but actually
my boobas are covered by feathers you
just you just don't know because you
normally don't
um
but nice tie Gap nice boots
interesting boots design
um
now overall I like the idea it's like a
mix of
you know bird naked bird and a leather
armor mostly leather armor I feel like
this is mostly based on leather stuff
half woman half bird all Phoenix
too much skin really
once y'all appreciate all levels of skin
exposure
Honestly though I feel like you that's
really like you can enjoy
skin exposure on every level
there's always something nice to see and
to appreciate um
[Music]
agreed thank you thank you yeah nice
nice garter belts too
okay okay thank you for the submission
we got next door am I going too fast
[Music]
so this one is not so dark
and so
silk RPG Adventurer style I would say
lots of leather and oh a little bit of
armor here oh cute when you use things
kind of into Birds too no it looks like
a bird to me
the thing sticking out of the kneecaps
um
and you make my feathers pinkish cute
did I ever have pinkish feathers before
until now
mmm
wow did I I don't think so I don't think
I did
do you hear my cat chunky monkey
[Music]
she likes this one it seems you like it
don't eat my potato chips bag
[Music]
it's just a empty bag
she likes plastic
very cute cat is cute art is cute
everything's cute Chihuahua cute chat
cute
you guys cute
yeah I like the boots actually I think
the boots are my favorite part
the shape of them
yeah and the color
I like these boots
I would buy them 10 out of 10 especially
now that my shoes were broken but I
actually got them fixed
more on that later in the news
[Music]
yeah yeah and of course short hair
Chihuahua
you think it looks good on me guys
who knows if I'll actually have short
hair we don't know we don't know yet
can't say for sure until the end
[Music]
yeah
everybody's exciting for
manifesting short hair Wawa hmm
[Music]
ate with the manifesting music
next we have
oh bright one from
more armor but this time it's like
white-ish silverish armor
the breastplate has got like this huge
Phoenix of a gem inside that's really
cool
I like the
the shape of the bangs and the hair and
everything
this is maybe a flower
I think
oh my my
this is just a feather okay oh we gotta
tell me oh we gotta tell me when
tankiana yeah this is
um this would probably be
um which class what do you think
I would say Paladin or like you know
depending on the game what we have
available
with like more basic ones I would say
Paladin
but if we can get more creative of
course this one should also be sitting
on a flying horse indeed bird some bird
bird Mount yeah Pegasus night yeah let's
go
clerican armor
oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah but isn't that a Clark and
armor in the end gives it just Paladin
vibes okay
paladins you know they heal and they
Bonk and they tank
um
[Music]
saber
Clark and armor pal that's that's what I
was thinking yeah
but not necessarily the exact same thing
I guess but yeah give her a mace oh
weapon weaponism
ah
wait that reminds me is through one more
thing oh God I can't forget uh remind me
remind me of the thing
wait you there's no way you can remind
me
no I guess actually I do have like some
remind me at the end to show you
progress pictures like drafts because I
did get permission to show some off
again just remind me because I didn't
save them yet on this PC
um
so I'll do that quickly later I just
don't want to open anything on that
monitor over there
by accident
so this thing you know there will be
like drafts at the end if you want to
see them
very interesting development
um
behind the scenes stuff
okay uh thank you for this one next we
have Lena Lena Roo thank you very golden
and golden armor with like a corset and
some satin this looks like Saturn to me
with the shading and the highlights
satin blouse oh
interesting very interesting oh the
color combination
golden Wawa
gold gold armor is like so
fancy
so in your face
this is a paladin this is a paladin I
don't know I feel like Paladin needs to
put some armor on her chest too though
but I guess we're talking unrealistic
RPG armor here
yeah very extravagant but you know it
still has like some Elegance even though
there's a lot of armor going on still
still we're serving some Elegance
elegant moments here right
pretty the hairstyle too I like I like
the the way the bangs are styled
um
shoulder pads look nice oh we got like a
little Spike here
oh yeah that was like something standing
out there indeed
um
yeah pretty cool pretty cool I like it I
I can see it this is my underwear
I should pull it up so you can't see it
eyelashes cute yeah the eyes are so cute
[Music]
things now
some upper ear side piercing I like that
looks cool
and this wow I already had some battles
I guess because something's chipped off
here
gotta be careful
no no one can ever chip something off my
armor that's unrealistic
okay yeah battle damage already on there
I suppose even though it's fresh out of
the oven
thank you for participating
next door is oh
yes well uh in case you guys don't know
um my original artist is
who is the artist and creator of Black
Rock Shooter so
went ahead to do some BlackRock shooter
references to put some Black Ops
shoulder references in there I can see
them everywhere hell yeah let's go I
really love BlackRock shooter designs uh
ah the eye so fancy the Stars the color
theme
maybe maybe
black book shooter design needs more
skin exposure
they do tend to have a lot of skin
exposure I think
not all of them but a lot of them no not
the no melon tan meron tan
your belly button
belly button I love this like
this stuff what's going on here like I
mean you kind of made me flat
which is kind of sus
I don't know how that happens why did I
suddenly get flats but the jewels and
everything that's really cool
I I don't know is it put on with skin
glue or is it like coming out of my skin
growing out of my skin
that is pretty
pretty quickly pretty edgy I must say
and the the whole like hair gradation
oh
would you still call this short hair
when most of the hair is short but then
there's like some strands that are
longer and it looks really nice
pretty wow good job yeah no yes no we're
split on that one it seems It's a hybrid
yeah
love the boots by the way
okay
oh we're already 45 okay okay I can
hurry up a little bit okay okay okay
next is by pikoi Art pikoi
whoa yo suddenly I have baked badonka
doings again thank you and this is so
cool like this could be like Loki Like a
Phoenix inspired
armor piece and it's holding my boobies
up nice support nice support system
wow wow wow it's really cool I love the
color choices
and how the contrast works with the
bright pink
it looks like it's like kind of
corrupting
something nice I love the leg designs
this part
whoa whoa and this mask so edgy so Edge
this looks really cool
[Music]
fell Dragon Wawa fell Phoenix
oh my my
my elbows are in elbow prison
I have elbow cages
I mean I guess it's like bent outwards
so I can still bend my elbows but that's
funny I've never seen something like
that before
oh and also fight prison why would you
put my
put my cocoa Kono design I'll sort of
the fact that it's like half bright and
half dark
also here on the on the sleeves as well
damn
I guess yeah it's the side oh it's it's
clearly split in the middle because like
the mask
and here's the corrupted things
only one side is like that
whoa good job picoy that's really cool
nice one next up
oh
scary that smile is so scary
for this super cool
idea concept wow
I don't even know how to describe this
like
there's like so many details in this
like armor
but it's more like I think it's more
like clothing I don't know is it like
solid armor I'm not sure but it looks so
cool
like it gives me like skeleton Vibes but
in a really fancy
feathery way I cannot explain it
um
yeah but very evil very dark
and yet you made my hot hair really
bright
interesting choice
wow
wow yeah this is really badass
[Music]
isn't this so so
edgy necromancer
Necromancer vibes yeah yeah yeah
definitely this is like a villain
this is a villain if I've ever seen one
12 minutes oh I don't even need to like
end it at the exact time nobody told me
I have to do exactly one hour so don't
worry about it a couple minutes over is
fine too
um but I think I've I'm I'm at a good
time let's go
this one is from samikitiki senki
another armor one but oh we've got like
a high cut leg thing going on with
tights
again barely any skin exposure but you
are exposing quite a bit of my
my hips and thighs
[Laughter]
but hey yo I love platform heels
thank you
yeah another
another uh armor type but it kind of
also gives me circus
um like
what's the word circus ladybugs
something about this like a leotard
outfit
with the big
things in the back
ringleader
helmet is that the word ring Master Ring
Master that's what that is
now I finally understand what the class
ring master in life of fund meant
[Music]
yeah like the healing class I think was
called ring master and Fly for Fun I
never understood like where that comes
from
it's like free anime MMR proceed that I
was playing
so nostalgic yeah
yeah circus Vibe let's go circus
circus hero
next
[Music]
oh my God it's so pretty
I love this artist works so much as you
probably know
how can you do you do this in such a
short amount of time huh
but oh you know what my first thought
was when I saw this
Senpai like this these the colors and
the armor parts
it reminded me a lot of noise
maybe this would be takanasikiara if she
was uh
related to noise I don't know
very nightly yeah beautiful holy [\h__\h]
this is so freaking gorgeous oh my God
foreign
[Music]
oh my God
look at them boots
[Music]
all the ornaments and oh here's like a
little bit of an homage to my weapons
and all that
wow you absolutely nailed I mean it
doesn't look at all
like what it is but you nailed it in the
sense of it looks freaking amazing like
I would buy this
you you you nailed it but you also
absolutely missed it
I love it beautiful
thank you sovonne next is Timmy Billy
Bob I don't know how many I have left
but it shouldn't be so many
this one I think was one of the earliest
submissions
and again [\h__\h] your revives don't you
think I don't know
because of the white and the gold I feel
like I'm from like ancient Greek Greece
or so
really cool
nice golden armor
and protection of crotch
oh this thing is kind of interesting
the gems I feel like this is like I can
touch it and it activates something
I didn't have a tummy window
but why you show my forehead
why don't shoot my forehead no no no no
no no no no no no no no
okay we gotta hurry a bit so let's go
next or maybe it's the last one I think
wait is it
[Music]
okay uh how do I do this do I do the one
thing first or the other
[Music]
um
should I first tell you guys who the
artist is or afterwards
[Music]
um
I think I'll tell it first because then
people if I do it afterwards people will
leave and won't know
no I think I'll
hey
only if you promise you stay guys
because out of respect you guys should
find out who the artist is okay
well let me take at least like a
screenshot of the Twitter for now so
that I
[Music]
show in a moment
I know
[Music]
so out of respect to the artist since
it's a new artist that I've never worked
with before and for the first time ever
an outfit without and my original artist
please stay until the end to find out
who it is yum
okay then
okay
I will change and in the meantime I have
a video
for you
which makes me so nervous
um
okay uh
see you
in a moment
let's go
um oh wait how did I wait one more thing
let me check one more thing uh
how did I
okay we'll just hide this and we'll hide
this and we'll hide everything
okay
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
I well well well well that video already
maybe gave away some things here and
there but actually that video was
created before the outfit was even
finished so
uh Maybe not maybe answer or not
we will
we will descend
where am I
[Music]
ah wait okay ah okay I get it I get it
are you ready
let's start with the tippy toes shoes
with cute ribbons let's go oh it looks
so cool already
driven and we already have armor on the
shoes whoa so maybe really there is an
armor theme going on
more armor by the way the video was of
course by manzu
who made the the myth bad ending that
you maybe recall
and then I commissioned music to be made
exactly for that
uh like adjust it to the video by
Harless
made me uh orchestra music
backdrop yeah really cool
perfect it turned out so nice
anyway here's more and more of my pizzas
ah what was that oh
yeah that's like I can't hide that for
too long can I
or can I
[Music]
um
well here goes my shins and something
that maybe looks like feathers but I
don't know if it really is
more and more leg so much leg
um I might be on the heels
yeah this is some cool lever and then
more armor let's go I'm not wasting so
much of your time oh my God body moves
so much holy [\h__\h] well
actually I need to do one thing
uh I'll tell you now there is
hairstyles and both are amazing like I
don't know I couldn't really decide
which one I like more so
stay for that too
[Laughter]
look how cool the eyebrow
I was so freaking
high quality and look how it's like
shiny shiny do you notice the like
subtle oh there you go I think this when
I look up you can notice it better
the subtle reflections
oh
nice proper proper reflections
[Music]
okay
we've got a five situation going on
should I like scroll out perhaps because
like this is my limits or you will just
see
certain parts
okay
yeah um we're we're getting uh higher
and higher we're looking at
the fires now oh
you can see my handsies
and yeah it's not
it's not it's just yeah one of those
feathers
yeah do you guys like it so
it's like you look really honestly like
so nervous I did not know what you guys
would think of it
if you like it so far
it's not so cool
dark alter Wawa from different
dimensions alternative Universe has
removed the normal kiwawa and Center
to a different universe and now we got
this one here
[Music]
yeah look more freaking sick details we
got like three layers of skirts
basically
and I feel like my thighs are thicker
than usual but I'm not sure you tell me
ha I can compete with Ollie now in terms
of like skirt with with
[Music]
I can squish them together
squish
lower lower and ears for all the sick
[\h__\h] armor parts I mean they're
everywhere but look at this
look at the sick belt oh my God let me
scroll in a little bit for you guys
thank you
the gauntlets yeah
and everything's properly shiny but look
at the belt oh my God
damn
you saw something you shouldn't have
seen I will now proceed to take your
eyes
I'll rip them out
[Music]
Warrior
okay
I guess this is it we're getting there
ah
[Music]
um
by the way
uh I've I've got kind of a new hand pose
I don't know when I've only used this
but it's kind of like a
um interesting pose
so
I'm gonna put the bag down because I
don't need this post oh wait
there but before we go up because
apparently I didn't have the jacket on
here's the jacket
I didn't I wasn't wearing the jacket
there's with jacket and with no jackets
and laginashi umagiari and we got like a
zipper dangling around
yeah the jacket is tucked into the armor
pieces
jackets versatile yes
okay I don't know should I put it and
take it I'll take it off right now
because I like the sheer fabric
um
[Music]
okay
oh
[Music]
turn down
Hello nice to meet you I am takana
shikiara from alternative universe
it seems like
we have possibly changed worlds and now
I'm here to talk to you guys
hello
I'm not done yet
second hairstyle do you want to see the
second
yes you do and of course I can also
remove this but I like this fancy hair
piece hmm
my intention was to have this be wolf
wolf hairstyle
um
with the front longer than the back
kaboom
it's ponytail long long side curly
ponytail and the bangs are different too
on this one
look
me they go down
uh I love them both it's
hard to decide you know
[Music]
hey
this one or this one
I feel like with this ponytail because
it's in the same direction it kind of
resembles
um
Cali's casual ponytail
laughs
they're nice aren't they let me show you
full body
uh is that full fully on there
oh yeah
[Music]
so we got this and we got this and we
got this and we got this
um
and possibly a little bit of this
I can go like
oh wow
oh
yeah but I don't know what to do with
these hands
hmm
so uh before you guys leave let me show
you show you show you show you
[Music]
the artist for this I've mentioned
before that the artist is uh someone
from uh a game that someone who drew
something for a game that I played
before and that was Tales of a Rise
um this is how I I kind of like looked
into the artist for the first time I
think not the main artist but this
artist did a DLC outfit remember the
super super edgy dark DLC outfit for a
Tales of a rise that we got to see
ah that was drawn bye
swap some
summer
is my artist for this outfit
Suave does like so many cool edgy armor
like kind of like futuristic armor
things
if you look through Suave Summer's work
you will see that and we've worked
together on something really freaking
edgy and cool yeah
foreign
[Music]
cool things and now I want to show you a
little bit of the like progress
quickly
I got free images
[Music]
you know I was really nervous about
going with a new artist
um it kind of had to be like this this
time
and I was nervous about whether or not
it would look like you know fitting
on the base of UK Papa you know with
different art styles you never know
okay so oh I think this one should come
first
[Music]
so I think that was one of the first
drafts that I got
it's like originally uh there was the
idea of a weapon so please feel free to
draw me with the weapon because it's
really cool
yeah I didn't have enough blank
space in resources to use to be granted
a weapon unfortunately so we had to cut
that out and sacrifice it for two
hairstyles priorities
but yeah originally I mean in swabs or
actual art style it all overall I think
looks a little bit different but this is
how it started out
we combined some things and then it
became closer to what it is now
[Music]
um
please feel free to draw me especially
with the like left one I think my
favorite is the left weapon
the a weapon it's kind of like a lance
or the big double sword but the it's
like so thin
very interesting need to see more
and then we have
um
oh this one this one was interesting
because I mean most of it is still kind
of the same but this is where we were
trying to fit it onto me and then the
shows
I I think you know swasama on the way to
making this made a lot of changes so
like the shoes are not quite the same
anymore not exactly
that's why it is some things also looked
a bit different in the video that I
showed you
um
but these were some some drafts going on
yeah
and then one more
[Music]
one more one
this one
oh yeah
oh yeah so here some more armor was
added and like in a more detailed way
and we figured out some more things
about the hairstyles what to do
um
yeah you see here where we decided to
add some actually completely this was on
Suave summer
so yeah he added some more cool armor
parts gave it a lot of detail which I
really appreciate the hairstyle
um a
change the bit because I requested for
the ponytail to be visible up at the top
because I thought it would be cuter hmm
so that changed a little bit too
[Music]
um
yeah like
so if someone was like it felt like he
was really trying everything
to please me to like make it so that
it's according to my to my wishes and
implemented everything that I wanted and
and and ah it's so cool it turned out so
cool I'm really happy with it
[Music]
um
and I got two cute new hairstyles and I
thought that this would really uh look
good for like upcoming uh jrpg streams
and stuff don't you think
foreign
so cool
dark Ultra Wawa so I called it alter
because
um the lore is she came from an
alternative world and so on Yeah Yeah
from the alternative
World saw the snare I will upload the
video uh on the channel separately if
you want to watch it again
as that I think turned out really really
nice and beautiful
so yeah
actually
was like so fast with making the video
yeah thank you so much Matthew
and heartless for putting the music
together
um
oh and oh my God the background look
got a new background from Eden exile
so let me take a seat this is like
inspired by the uh video the office in
the video that you saw
[Music]
here
for sure
welcome to Wawa new office so whenever I
stream like this I think we won't be
using the other rooms we'll be using
this room now we got like a a map and
the feather uh ink thingy really fancy
cool chair
um an ax and the I don't know if you can
see but the the all the all the candles
are moving hmm
[Music]
so do you like it Sun bgm change we're
ready for quest yeah ready ready or are
we uh not really because in the coming
week I'll be going to uh the UK so I'll
be a little bit busy uh still a little
bit too busy to start uh any jrpgs but
we'll be doing that in the future and
um looking forward to using this outfit
a lot
and thinking about which hairstyle I
should go with let me get rid of the
chat for a moment so you guys can take
some screenshots maybe like this
what do you want huh you come here to my
office
and say [\h__\h] like that
you will think I'm gonna welcome you
with open arms
absolute [\h__\h] get out of here
yes yes here one more
you asked for an audience with takanashi
kiwawa
what is so important that you feel the
need to talk to me on this busy day
Speak now or never
and fast and with confidence
I don't speak this language I don't
understand what you want
nail
I think you guys thank you for all the
love and support
um as I told you I just came back from
Japan a couple hours ago so I'm still
kind of exhausted and tired uh tomorrow
on Monday I I do want to stream a little
bit maybe like a short chatting stream
catch-up stream
in this outfit so I hope to see you
there maybe
I still have a glue from the uh I think
it was the Super Chat reading stream
where I put you guys on the ocean
be so kind muchos muchos fan art if you
guys like it enough to draw fan art um
[Music]
and as I said uh gladly with the with
the weapon
thank you again to swap summer for the
super cool outfit for working so hard on
it for putting so much love and detail
into it
[Music]
foreign
like when I was looking for artists
um
who I would consider to draw an outfit
for me I wanted someone who brings
something fresh and special to the table
and if you go to this artist's Twitter
you will see like very very very very
original art like this artist likes to
do a lot of like really fancy
unrealistic sneaker designs too
yeah Suave is like really special artist
with a really distinctive Style
uh yeah so that's why I chose Suave
summer that's why I asked to have
swasama do my outfit this time get
something that you know if I have to
choose someone else a different artist
then might as well you know get
something someone really really special
to do something really really special
hey
rigor oh I wasn't told actually maybe
the rigor uh would probably maybe upload
a tweet
saying hey I rigged this afterwards
I actually don't know
we'll find out later maybe
mystery mystery
mystery lives
foreign
[Laughter]
we'll find out we'll surely find out I
want to see like uh you know I rigged
this kind of tweet with like a animation
from them would be nice Okay so
so I'll leave it at that let's keep it
short and nice and compact So yeah thank
you everybody for the uh for the weight
and for the uh art that you
predicted this outfit with mm-hmm
and feel free to post screenshots with
hashtag Kiara
on the
on Twitter which is I guess changing to
X or something like what the [\h__\h] I
don't [\h__\h] understand uh is it is for
real for is it for real I don't know but
here here one more one more close-up for
good measure
maybe I think this expression fits alter
Kiara better
name
okay got it
thank you thank you thank
you I think now get out of my [\h__\h]
office oh I'm gonna stab you with that
non-existing weapon thank you thank you
see you hopefully tomorrow thank you
guys for watching and enjoying we say
hey please do oh my God what
yeah yeah yeah bye-bye I will rest now
with katos
yes
let's fix that jet lag shall we it's a
good time to sleep now
thanks for watching bye bye
[Music]
foreign