[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
approved stamp i mean
perfect because
uh this stream is indeed
uh approved
by from software not sponsored just
approved
yes
welcome everybody
i'll be nice on kick it again
ring a game that everybody was extremely
excited
for and hyped for for a long long time
and now it's finally here
and
i
don't know much about it i've seen one
trailer
and a few screenshots of characters
classes
um but that's honestly really all i know
[Laughter]
i have not spoilered myself with
anything about it so
i really i really besides me not having
ever played a souls game before
i really don't know what to expect
because i also just don't know
wh
what this game is about mostly i just
the reason i chose to play it
is because i
bought um the creators just simply the
even just by looking at the creators i
was like yo i gotta give that a try and
if you guys are also hyped for it then
there must be a reason for it
um i've heard a lot of people say that
it's really difficult
and that you die a lot uh
so i'll probably do a really bad job
but we start off with a character
creation apparently
so that's good
um some warming up time i guess and also
some time to charge my controller uh
it's currently
on the wire
but yeah and let's i guess start with
that because that's probably gonna take
some time uh do you guys hear the bgm
should i turn it up a little bit
can't die in character creation well i
hope not
i hope so
yeah
yeah i i i am
at the moment still
positive about not being
not failing completely but we'll see
hey
volume up okay okay
um
this might get louder later i am just
guessing that this bgm right now is
supposed to be somewhat quiet but i
turned it up
i turned it up
well can we can oops we can fix it uh
wait what uh
settings uh
is there anything i should change guys
toggle auto log on yeah
all the target on
let's make it easy for me as easy as
possible manual attack aiming should i
turn that on makes does it make it
easier
uh
vibration maybe a bit less yo
and
default is good keep these
off
does it not make it that makes it harder
oh okay interesting
oh
ow okay okay now i get it okay motion
sensor functions performance settings
prioritize framework yeah okay
address brightness until the image on
the right side is barely visible
it is barely visible
camera accents
sure did you guys change something here
on a wall recovery camera speed maybe a
bit faster i don't know
what do you think yeah this is on ps5
i'm playing on ps5
camera speed up okay i opted a little
bit
okay
oh okay okay i heard that
uh
classes are
gender locked no no they're not no wait
that was something else no it's not
generous although they look uh
the girls with all that armor don't look
much like girls anymore but okay wait so
we have vagabond
that looks like
a shield and sword that is warrior with
only a sword is that a double
double-handed sword
no wait she's also holding it with two
hands
but okay and hero damn i should have
like looked at like
how they work
uh
hero
where's the difference between
hero vagabond good for me press triangle
for stats oh oh oh god well that doesn't
really tell me much either
there's a bandit which is i guess like
fast attacking but not much damage
astrologer
is that
like a mage
or
something like that prophet joe why does
he have that thing around his neck is he
gonna lose his head anytime he's like
ready for it he's so ready to be
decapitated at any given time astrologer
is a mage okay
what about a prophet is that a healer
i thought you mostly played this game
alone i heard there's like invasions but
isn't that mostly alone
uh
is that like a cleric so
it's
kind of a healer yeah it wouldn't that
be difficult to play alone like whenever
in any game when you play a healer alone
i feel like it's pretty tough to get
around on your own
a samurai
not a hodos looks someone usually in
other games i've played is always a
difficult one so oh dear what
you
i'm sorry
dear lord
what did they do to you
oh man
why is that when is there naked people
here
is that like hard mode starting out as a
wretch like with no armor and [\h__\h] is
that like their kind of hard mode
and then the confessor sounds really
interesting is that like a paladin
cause i don't know
i don't know what that is yes that is
like hormone oh
hardcore yeah
[Music]
wretch is extremely hard
interesting
oh suffering mode okay
well
wait there's no one with like uh
with a bow really mostly it's closed
combat besides the mage maybe
because i started it looks like close
combat
okay
uh
when you start with different levels
are you why do you start with different
levels
samurai has about ah cool
uh but that's that's okay it's okay
we're probably better off with
um
wait do you have like do you have to
manually block or is the shield just
like
i try to understand the game basics is
the shield like you don't have to
activate it it just gives you extra
defense stats or do you actually have to
manually block
you have to manually vlog yeah
wonderful wonderful
is that difficult
but like he also has a little shield
i think
what's that magic thing intelligence
faith
i don't really know man i i think i'll
go with
uh
[Music]
warrior cause i'm a part-time warrior
a bee
is that the chick yeah oh
okay
should i like
where should i go should i like
where do i go where do i go
should i be here maybe for now
name
ah
okay
ain't nobody got time to
use capital letters
body type
i just see a
it's buff buddies i just see a
difference in the stance of how she's
standing
but i guess it does look a little bit
more slender but
i guess so
okay slam your body body type has no
bearing on the bullet okay then let's go
for slender mmm
uh age
age young
mature and aged oh
they do be aging how do i go up
no i mean with the camera i want to go
up oh
zoom rotate
i'm not sure
okay
uh let's go for young we're pt
super young
and
it's totally where i'm supposed to be on
the battlefield or wherever origin
ah i already chose that keepsake
no keepsake the past has been well and
truly
oh
what is this extra buffs or what a
medallion inlaid of crimson ember
increases
oh
gold of grace shining in the eyes of
your users
to set your interest
oh golden seed
what does that do
washed ashore from not
all available
this doesn't get more detailed okay
voice this
eh
can i listen
i can't listen hold on you listen
ah
simple
she's just suffering
can you talk
she's
suffering
are they just going to be suffering
throughout the whole game
we'll just go with that alter skin color
wow i can be like silver
oh
one like one of those blue people
oh my god sunburn
no
ah
i guess something like that
outer face oh god the the default
doesn't
really look pretty can we actually make
her look pretty
are we gonna
be able to fix her up
yes yes we are look at this
done
beautiful oh it took me only about five
hours to make her look like this
no no no no no unfortunately i think
we'll have a hard time trying to make it
look like me
okay
uh
i just face template bone structure
oh
oh that's decently cute
and that's the cutest out of those basic
ones and then we have form emphasis
wait what's changing
i don't know what's changing
a parent age
this one makes me older i suppose
let's make me younger
[Music]
is it changing
facial aesthetic what is that masculine
oh
what's changing
is it the eyes
it's changing
what's changed
now the eyes get bigger and the lips get
smaller
oh from here yeah it gets much wider oh
okay well we'll do 255 then
uh
okay we saved that face straight
stretching yeah this this oh man i
didn't know there's so many options it's
going to take a while yeah i want to fix
the nose what the hell nose ridge
nose bridge i want to do the bridge not
the ridge what's the ridge
uh
aya oh my god
oh my god
oh my god what are we gonna do with you
that was ridge lengths
uh-huh
um
oh my god
mr classy i mean
just kidding you're beautiful
oh yeah yeah
uh somewhere here
she's she's beautiful right can we do
some fancy hair colors or
is there no orange again
i mean i guess it wouldn't really fit
into the game would be too crazy looking
protrusion what is that concave convex
what is that
the nose tip
um
i'm just trying to make her look
somewhat decent
so that someone will marry her at the
end of the game that's the goal right to
get her
married
get her a good husband that will take
good care of her
that's the goal i think of self games
right
no no
no no no okay
is it getting better i wonder uh let's
do the eyes
eye position
up there
and let's lower them a bit
cute we need to fix her jaw as well
sims edition yeah
dark soul mates
oh you're so much at souls games it's
about finding your soul mate
right that's what i thought oh my god ah
goodnight is gonna have fun with this i
think
that already looks kind of weird but i
believe in it i believe in it i'm
hopeful
oh
spacing spacing
tough one i think that's okay yeah yeah
she's looking better i think that in the
beginning
looks dumb
oh come on
come on how do your characters look like
have you managed to make them look cute
yet nostril slant
oh
she's like
i'm too good for this
i don't care i don't care
i'm better than this
no no that looks too painful we don't we
don't want to put her for that stuff i
mean she's got already gonna suffer
enough oh no
you know what that gives her character i
like that
nostril with
oh
that reminds me of
of other people's noses
[Laughter]
yeah
it's a bit big bro
isn't that kind of cute
it's kind of kind of cute maybe to me a
little bit
yeah
yeah mom
better than before too white nah come on
nobody's perfect nobody's perfect it's
her charm point her nose is her charm
point and from the side it actually
looks pretty good i think this is like a
shadow shadowing thing because like i
think this is her this is her chocolate
side
as we like to say in german
this is her good side
this
is a more interesting side and this is
actually unflattering she looks better
from the side
and we actually didn't do the forehead
forehead
oh
yeah i'll go with that forehead
protrusion
what
do wow
are these kind of
games always like this like do they
always have such a
detailed character
[Music]
creation
wait what's happening what's up oh
yes they do
some do some don't
how many games are in this like souls
games collection that you guys
always talk about how many are there
how cute wait wait wait wait it's
starting to look cute
six seven
six oh you guys are not so sure but okay
this is my first one
but it's an rpg so i honestly i don't
understand why you guys are like yucky
well you're not made for this why are
you playing this i always play rpgs i
mean maybe the cuter ones than these
ones but
but i mean the the base of it is a rpg
so
what won't i be fine
[Laughter]
those bridge wave oh
oh
well that changes a lot
[Music]
interesting
i know i know it's difficult
but but like the the
just the base elements of an rpg
i think i think i'll i like that
wish
uh
now we have wait have we done this
before bro brow red bro rage hate height
you guys can come back later in like
half an hour yeah i'm zooming for this
what's happening what's happening
oh oh
ah
okay i don't quite see it in a bro
[Laughter]
you look troubled
what happened
if i weren't wearing my mask then you
would see my expression better but yeah
try to imitate her
oh
cute
maybe a little bit
maybe a little bit trouble there's some
people who just always look troubled
don't they a little bit
like i don't know michael sarah
sierra sarah out of bro rich
that is too much you can't do that oh my
so true
macy williams oh yeah yeah her too like
she has a thing with her eyebrows too
okay where eyebrow eyebrows so thick we
need to pluck him somebody pluck her the
eyebrows is there really no function for
that
or or how about uh
using an eyebrow pencil um girl
lost trails that we do nostrils living
with it yeah oh no did we
i think we did
okay
cheeks cute cheeks for a cute lady
kissable chicks there's an option for it
oh
in the hair section oh i'm excited for
that okay
okay girl get your cheek game going
oh my god what
[Laughter]
wow oh
oh
wait pretty
before
after i like it
cheekbone depth
i really hate that word it's so hard for
me to say
she's starting to look pretty better
than my sims i think
oh
she has really powdered lips right now
though
you got to call it
cheekbone protrusion
again that word
she looks like she desperately needs
therapy
no way
what is that cheeks
chubby chick she just came from the
dentist
[Music]
cute okay i like it lips so you have
very powdy lips right now which is not
really a bad thing
um
yeah we want to make her smile a bit
more
don't frown so much
smile happy
and then your life will be so much
better
yeah just smile
just smile
don't always frown from the get-go
give her a beak i could but i'm trying
to make it look pretty
oh
okay
lip protrusion
oh
i like
like some there's some people who have
like
these really cute upper lips
um
seen some cute k-pop idols with cute
upper lips there's this one girl i don't
know her name
but it's a really really cute feature
she needs a kfp uniform
no she's not a chicken she can't work
with us
ah next up mouth
uh wait didn't we do this huh
interesting
mouseland
what was that from the side something
ah
occlusion
oh dear
no no
you look funny
sorry i'm i'm not i'm not bullying you
or anything
i think you're beautiful
not as beautiful as me
but you know
all right
can we give her a haircut too
mouth weaver
there we go
either so big
and there you could have made them much
much bigger this is still me holding
back a lot
oh cute
[Music]
chin
uh
see i don't want to waste too much time
on character creation but at least want
to make her look cute
but we want to
want to save a lot of time for all the
deaf
deaths
that we're going to go through
chin length
yeah did you guys also watch my kyle
okay rebroadcast today i was singing
some fun songs i hope you were able to
catch it although depending on your time
zone it could have been impossible so i
don't blame you
yeah thank you
kfc is always there for me
jinder
thank you guys for watching the original
entering broadcast some some of you guys
are just
so so
dedicated thank you
i actually had a recording with the
girls
uh before the stream as you seen on
twitter it ended very last minute so i
had a quick snack
before the stream well i'll be good for
the next couple hours but recording was
fun
recording was fun
uh let me drink some water
with the girls yeah with the girls
whoever the girls are who could they be
the myth girls
yeah kind of a round face
she doesn't honestly with a face like
that i don't know if you can survive but
don't judge by the face right i mean
someone like
i'm not gonna say any names but i guess
probably shouldn't say too many other
franchises
but there's some hot girls out there
kicking ass so
yeah yeah i wanted to shave some of your
jaw off
lower jaw
oh yeah
oh no now her chin actually nah a bit
more
no no no that's her jaw let me fix her
no let me fix her chin i feel like now
it's kind of a bit too much like oh oh
guys don't forget to look from above
i think you tend to forget about that
yeah her chin oh there yeah that's mmm i
think a bit too much
a jaw contour oh
okay but
so so far so good let's just make the
the chin
uh
let's see which part do we have to fix
i did the wrong thing sorry
oh
is this okay
i think that looks fine
check from above whoa
she's naked i didn't even realize until
now
i think it's fine
better better better better better okay
oh face structure done uh
only these two go
uh hair okay okay we'll be oh
cute not bad not bad this hairstyle is
also her hair looks like really really
fresh
out of the shower
gosh her shoulders are so
white though oh cute that's like a
hairstyle you would wear to uh to
be wearing with a dirndl cute i like
these kind of hairstyles
i tried to do these on myself a few
times but
i was never able to
successfully do it
well i think a warrior
will um
not be able to keep their hair
that nicely tied up let's be real it's
it should be this it's pretty
oh heckles what there's there's pink
but where's orange like that's that's
not really orange it's blonde
what really you're gonna let me do that
oh but i i feel like it doesn't
nah we don't want it to be too weirdly
said oh do we do we want it to fit in
more or
i'll go go crazy like not you that's
disgusting
more orange be weird okay but not like
in in a good way
like this maybe
can i do like a second layer
let's see
okay
luster what is that
ah
the shiny part
uh-huh rude darkness
oh yeah that that
makes it look a bit more realistic maybe
white hairs oh i can make myself look
old no thank you right young
pgpt piano face you're scaring me this
no what do you mean this is me this is
me the one that's moving this is me
that's my face reveal
eyebrows finally
oh
oh my very fuzzy eyebrows like
caterpillars
oh wait huh
oh ew
ew
wait they still look so uh
i think i might have
lowered the sides too much she always
looks like really there
but that's okay no we want that i like
that i think it's cute
brown color bro brow brow color uh let's
make it a bit darker oops oh
i feel like bro
i'm so confused brow
brow colors
i generally oopsie
uh
like a little bit darker
uh last
match here my chair okay
uh
broke
facial hair
no
elbow
oh that's so cute
oh my god
that is so cute it reminds me of ahmed
and of a certain dog like some dogs have
a have a mustache like that it's so cute
i kind of want to give her that monster
no but i will never be able to change it
again right
no not quite
i would never be able to change it would
i
are you ever able to change your looks
in the game later on
you can
really but then why don't we try so hard
to make it look so pretty and then we
just smack a mustache
okay if you can't change it i'll do it
for now
way later
oh man who cares we'll be most looking
at her back anyway right
you can't oh man
yes yes usually usually inna is the one
who [\h__\h] around in character creations
like this uh
and i usually always try to make it
really pretty maybe i should for once
say
[\h__\h] being pretty
oh god
chat is lying
yeah you probably aren't even that far
in the game that you could tell
the cut scenes oh there's gonna be
cutscenes oh they're just gonna make us
laugh all the time
with a mustache
well who knows if there'll even be more
than one episode anyway so okay
okay
um
i think for now i'm okay with it
uh
what is it changing
oh you have a lot of mascara on dear
lord
eyelash color
okay that's fine with me
paul should i do a poll i feel like most
people want to troll right now though
irish color
i'm a scholar i was iris color iris
uh people say i have pink eyes but
like i saw i think i saw like a reddit
uh post the other day putting every
member
and
uh in a category of their colors and
there there was violet and there was
pink but they put me in pink a lot of
people but i personally feel like it's
more purple than pink
but it's tough it's like an
in-between thing
what would you say are my eyes purple or
pink
magenta
um
right eye clouding
oh
[Music]
i can make myself go blind oh
or oh wait what wait what if i do like
this and then
oh yeah
no no no that's good we don't need that
but that's interesting that you can do
that
basically get rid of your iris
um
wait ah
didn't change that
even though the signs of her eyes are
like really red oh my god
oh no oh no let's make them big and cute
[Laughter]
this will be me by the end of the stream
probably
pores
wow she has maximum pores
i mean who looks that closely after
character creation
that's what i always think
what what is that doing skinless
lustrous lustrous is that making it ah
it's making it more shiny
oh hell yeah dark circles
well i look like this okay maybe not
that
whoa
no oh my god that looks
funny i would love to make a dark
character dark character like that
but maybe not maybe not maybe not
maybe not
maybe not today
eyeliner
[Laughter]
i can't believe this i can't
okay you know what i'll give her a
little bit of an eyeliner
i'll do that
the the darkness is starting to consume
her
what no honestly
she wouldn't wear [\h__\h] makeup she's a
warrior but i'll keep the eyeliner
lower eyeshadow
oh
damn cute now she's starting to look
like a k-pop idol
except for the mustache
[Music]
[Laughter]
i can't even see it properly the shadow
of the mustache is too strong
wait one second let me
[Music]
okay
let me put myself here for now
oh
she looks cute
i think she's rocking the mustache
uh tattoo mark eye patch tattoo
oh
that looks like cat ears but only in the
icon
should we do something fancy
i i have yet to quite grasp the
atmosphere of the games i don't know if
it's really fitting probably is so
oh and i my third eye
oh god it looks like she has some kind
of skin disease
[Laughter]
can always get one later really
if anything catches my fancy
maybe this
oh the color oh
[Music]
you know that's fine
tweak tattoo
all the positions
[Laughter]
i don't know why i find that so funny
why is that so funny to me
but you know i guess you know we could
do something cool there
oh
that's starting to look like a trident
to me or like one of those uh
another trident something similar
that looks maybe it looks cool i don't
know
[Music]
yeah
looks cool kind of doesn't it but the
[\h__\h] mustache is starting to bother
me now
oh okay it's okay okay
eye patch
nah don't like eye patches
yeah now now
now it's just too much going on with the
tattoo and the mustache
santa claus
[Music]
okay a lot of people are saying no beard
now i think we've had enough of it i
think we've had enough of it
with a similar face
is that gonna change everything
select face similar to prison face
what
that's okay i think this is done we're
done we're done
we're done
well her face looks cute from far away
even
out her body i'm sorry that stash has to
go shaved it off
but it would probably grow back quickly
uh chest
[Music]
oh dear that not only changes her
boobies it always also
changes like everything around it
yeah
abdomen
oh oh my god
i mean all this will be mostly covered
up by an armor now
yeah yeah fuzz squish and with your
thighs
i mean realistically she probably has
some bloody hair
body hair color moscow lecture
oh
those abs yes realistic realistic
definitely also what i look like
underneath my clothes yes yes of course
of course anyone doubting that
come on
ultra body what we're done we're done
save
all the body
i'm done
fresh out of the oven this is what we'll
be working with why was there no butt
slider what the hell
but yeah she's looking cute i think
can't see can't say
she looks strong and cute at the same
time so
she is ready to go oh oh she looks even
cuter when she's wearing that
oh
even though you can only see her cute
little face
i'm i'm scared but i'm ready to go
um
[Music]
what awaits me
i don't know
the fallen leaves
tell a story
the great elden ring
was shattered
i'm getting some
vibes here you home
across the fall too quiet
the lands between
pretty really nice artwork
[Music]
queen of
the whole country the knight of the
black knights
oh [\h__\h] god when the golden
was first to perish
soon
cute
offspring demigods or gods
claimed the shards
of the elden ring
has a huge little the rings fan i'm
getting such huge vibes right now i love
it
of their newfound strength
irrigate the shattering you
the way it's being told
as well
whoa that's a long sword
a war
leader what is god's abandonment those
are demigods right by the greater will
oh
rice now
he tarnished
he dead
who yet live zombie creation oli's debut
the call of long lost grace
speaks to us all
[Music]
the ever
you
i know his ears
[Music]
whom grace would again bless
a tarnished of no renown
wait wasn't that hand big what the [\h__\h]
or the proportions misleading me what's
the fog
crush the flock to the lens between
i stand before the
it rhymes
nice poem become
the elden lord i become the elden lord
wow
bit confused but okay cool
what's up wait i want full screen
give me full screen come on
beautiful
whoa where should i put myself am i fun
here
you guys tell me when i'm in the way
okay
whoa
my jump is powerful
naruto
okay jumping
right right side better okay
okay
i'm trying to make myself as small as
possible whoa
oh i'll be using that a lot won't i
okay that's the interface i guess the
red one is my hp
and the blue one is my
mana maybe i don't know what the green
is hello are you good
oh wait what pillage remains
i don't want your fingers
okay read message
though the path be broken and uncertain
claim your place as the elden lord lord
did you write me that message thank you
what you fight with r2
huh
oh and nr1
oh wait because i have two swords so the
other one is there
oh wow
wow
what was that
oh did i just use a skill
how could i do that
cool yo i got some moves
wow
yeah yeah button smashing
what smashing
show
hey
well
i know you guys are impressed but have
you forgotten ah i'm a part-time warrior
open the door please
okay so i figured out how to fight or at
least
wow
it's pretty bright out here
chapel of anticipation i don't know what
i should be anticipating but oh
big tree
is that uh wait what was that big tree
always called it
drastic
wait what
wait
what was it called again
what's it called oh yeah it was a
drazzle right egg egg egg
egg dressing
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
can i ah
good good good destroy boxes feels good
thank you
but no no loots really is there loot in
these boxes sometimes
i wonder
oh my god okay well the graphics are
pretty
damn
it's running smooth so far by the way
speaking of oh running smooth can i run
faster oh oh that's
that's being sneaky
uh i don't know what if there's a dash
button right now
b
wait where is b what is b i only have a
square triangle circle on x
hold all
ah okay okay okay
okay okay should i like investigate
behind is there like a secret kind
do these games have a lot of secrets i
heard this is open world so
is it worth like looking around
everywhere
yes nothing was there though
yes they do
does this give me fall damage no okay
i love that tree here
oh
big figure is that the goddess the first
one i forgot her name but the one that's
no no yeah do you know the lady the cute
lady
have to fight
what the [\h__\h] no no no no no no
how how do you
how can you help me
i'm ready
wait i heard that i can
i don't i think eno told me that or who
was it someone told me i don't have to
kill the first one how the [\h__\h] would
you assume that i would know what to do
now
i need a tutorial
the [\h__\h]
game will vote what
well that is the end of the stream thank
you everybody
i'm dead but come on i'm a phoenix i'll
give you one of my feathers
come
on that was the tutorial i i couldn't
even
let me try again
very hairy horse you need to
shave your legs girl
wait has horns
wait why do you have horns
are you unicorn don't worry tauren
fortune is on her side nice english
british
we found her here after all
wait for real can i fight a bit more i
need some practice
hello nice to meet you
hello i'm kiwa one of her kind is sure
to seek
the elden ring yeah that's what i'm
looking for i think to become the elden
lord i remember that one even if it does
violate the golden order why
why well i don't want to do anything
wrong
i'm not trying to do anything illegal
here i'll please please please
i'm a good girl
wake up wake up wake up
scripted death yeah i guess was that
could you even kill
that were you able to kill that thing
you can't what happens when you can you
do well flask of crimson crimson tears
those that's my blood
uh free one not a whole doll
oh god
how do i
how do i use it
i don't want to accidentally use it i
just want to know how to use it
oh is it with the
square
why hmm
okay that's way too easy to use
[\h__\h]
i needed that
the cave of knowledge lies below
sounds like a trap
talk
hi ghost
brave tarnish to take the plunge
of learning and remembrance
is that the stretch of uh rhyme recall
the art of war in your warrior's blood
cool
okay
oh god there's another one of those is
that a like one tiny part of the big
tree
if i cut it
can't
oh
no i can't
eh
really
go down
don't lie to me
i swerve that's a lie
eh what about fall damage you have to be
like careful
ow
use item switch
[Laughter]
okay i'm good i'm good
oh what
nice visuals
sights of grace well i can heal myself
here resting on the side of grace will
restore your hp fp and cleanse any
status elements it will also refill your
oh i remember failed my flask that i
just used most of the enemies you've
defeated will be revived oh no i will
have defeated no one so far
you can find sights of grace by going
where light converges
these explanations are acquired in the
form of info items and can be accessed
from the inventory at any time okay
cool
so please fill up my flask
lost grace discovered
didn't i have three
wait did i get it wrong
did i get
didn't i have
you need to rest ah
okay
oh
oh past time flasks
huh what
i'm free again okay cool
i guess we're going then
hello
am i gonna fight that person
okay no problem
reset camera lock on move target okay
oh that's
okay it's an actual tutorial
hallelujah
i thought you're a really good a strong
attack yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
guarding oh no use an arm and mint in
your left hand or both hands to guard
against incoming attacks of l1
guardian consumes stamina oh which one
is to start another green one
that one
that was not
guarding
does it have to be at the right time
is there a sword now oh
so i can't do it anyway
okay
okay i thought i could maybe parry with
the sword instead you can avoid any
attacks of a dodge one or a back step uh
l plus circle dodge roll and back step
back
step
yeah yeah yeah i already figured that
out i guess
roll him to them let's go
um
what
man they turn into like puppets after
they're dead
jump i forgot
jump
oh
he's gonna shoot me he's gonna shoot me
oh whoa hey what what did that say what
did that say [\h__\h] i didn't ring
[Music]
no no no how do i how do i find how did
i get you
perry what what did it say for parrying
why materials
run they just said run is that dash ah
okay okay in every corner of the lens
between you will find fruits and flowers
mushrooms and butterflies and various
other useful materials these materials
can be used for item crafting
item crafting
a berries
fairies
i know the arty's always like glowing a
little bit so it makes it more easier to
see
oh god he's his armor each hand can be
equipped with up to three armaments
while free allowing you to toggle
between them armaments can also be
two-handed making attacks more difficult
to repel shields and boosting effective
strength by 50 percent
switch left and right
wheeled with two hands uh
maybe not for now
ah now i have okay
oh god okay
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait
on let me pack
[\h__\h]
too late
[\h__\h] you
[\h__\h] you can i destroy his shield oh oh
oh yeah baby
okay
well i i need to find her
a good timing you know
i thought i've
activated it at the right time
pairing can be hard to pull off
um yep yeah i've noticed that okay
while locked on change target r
oh
okay
don't walk away are you scared
oh
did you stab me from the back that's not
very nice
we do front battles here
facing each other
oh no on oh
yeah yeah where's down there
oh i'm glad i didn't fall down there
maybe i should fall down there nah
ah this is where he passed through where
he was shooting me from the top and now
i get it
skills l2 armaments have special
abilities called skills skills are
highly varied a range from powerful
attacks to temporary effects using
skills consumes fp exciting exciting
l2
yeah i've been already using those i
think
subconsciously i hold it so this is a
normal attack and the big buttons in the
back are attacking oh sneaky sneak
crouching to make it harder for enemies
to discover you especially effective
intelligence attacking an enemy that
hasn't noticed you will cause more
damage okay
okay
i mean this one is probably extra dumb
so i doubt
nice
yo
beautiful oh hello
that was beautiful
i felt really good
but don't don't don't do this in real
life no backstabbing in real life it
doesn't feel quite as good
uh what critical hit which button
damn can you tell me again game
tell me again please it goes away so
quickly
did you guys see
r1
okay
but from the back
oh whoa
is that what they wanted me to do this
is not that the same thing oh well
ah stance breaking some attacks may
break the enemy stance giving you a
chance to perform a critical hit
okay
charge attacks
and jump attacks make it particularly
easy to break in enemies stance hold r2
charge attack our two while jumping ah
what [\h__\h]
no
i wanna
that button is way too close to all the
other buttons
are you a dummy
stakes of america upon dying you will be
revived at the last sight of chris ah
however if there's a stake of america
near you where you died you can choose
to be revived there and said ah
don't worry i'm not dead right now well
thanks for the offer
ew
is that gonna kill
me
no okay traverse the mist are we done
with the tutorial what oh no oh no
oh
no i'm not ready
okay oh you just assaulted okay okay
uh yeah you can perform a counter-attack
immediately after blocking an enemy
attack uh-huh
rt immediately after blocking this that
guard counter
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay what was blocking again l1 or l2
uh uh
uh
was it blocking again
and one ray i think was l1 yeah i want
power
[Music]
i'm dead
you die
that's okay
oh i should have locked on oh yeah
uh
sake of marika
thank you i know up and down you'll be
right yeah yeah you will drop any runes
if you die again before we claim those
runes did i have any runes i don't think
so
oh no apparently i did
because that indicates where they are
okay do i just walk over it
xp do i just walk over it or do i have
to press something oh god okay
we can do this
oh
i did something
did something
i heard something cool
uh oh yeah
okay why did he attack me what did i do
why is everyone attacking me just a
traveler
just a traveler
oh
that's where i jumped down though
i insulted his mom no
i treated his mom very very kindly and
gently
strength
oh okay
cool do i just go down now
am i really just supposed to go down
here
did i go the wrong way can i hold on to
you
you go i go down okay
wow
oh
i could roll when i'm at the ground okay
so am i supposed to go through here now
okay
yeah i thought the therial done well
that was quick that was fast
but if that's really all the basics okay
touch grace
was chris we should take uh uh
we should rest because we drank one
potion
um
what is memorized spell
if the memorize spells many you can
memorize sources and incantations
you must have a staff eclipse to cast
sorceries or a sacred seal equipped to
cast incantations
oh that doesn't really seem like
something i would be doing now because
i'm a warrior
no
sword i have a chest
with me at all times
oh
okay
until
oh i guess you know why not until
morning
that that was already like a lot for me
to
uh process
i needed a little bit of a nap
what is that
oopsie
pillage remains use tarnished filled
finger to write a gold summon sign
corporative multiple will begin once you
have been summoned by a player from
another world
aha you will take the role of an ally
for old finger and your objective is to
defeat the area boss
hello the compass at the top of the
screen indicates the direction of the
summoner
so it's like
co-op but only for like a boss and then
they leave
optional online stuff
cool
where oh where are we now what
i was just like wondering where do we go
there's no place to go
but the middle was ces
okay nice elevator very modern
didn't know this game already uh knew
how to make an elevator
i don't like walking up all those stairs
i lose my breath after like five stairs
you know
wow
limb grave or
also known as my grave because i'll be
dying here many times
wow
pretty
i like the color of the trees is it
autumn right now
what is that over there
stones or birds
we're humans it's birds huge [\h__\h]
birds
bobs whoa hello wow sneaky
can i like get their meat no don't go
wow
but i assume that you can like
uh kill them and get their meat to cook
maybe oh what's that it's a bunny
what there's like random animals wait no
it's not really a bunny it's a kangaroo
bunny thingy chinchilla i don't know
what the [\h__\h] it is
what
there's so many
let's get some chinchilla meat
it's cute
what wait for me
no don't go
i don't go
oh
are they very shy
don't go
i'll corner you
[\h__\h] yeah
wait you're not giving me any meat well
then it's not worth killing you
then it's just
i'm sorry
hey did that give me an item
no those are not bunnies it looks like
looks like miniature kangaroos
they do sometimes oh that one that one
looks sick they both look sick
[\h__\h]
i want some bird mean i want some fried
chicken
run run run run run run run practice
combat against these [\h__\h]
nice oh i have to pillage them thin
beast bones did they forgot bulging the
other one or was it just not possible
oh no
no dropper no no no we got it from one
of them okay okay okay where was i
supposed to go
maybe there
what was that
nothing
well i like this so far i mean the
combat seems challenging might need some
practice with that but besides that i
like it
swimming pools
in each area you may find effigies of
martyrs these effigies are summoning
pools you'll find it easy to summon
other players at these locations as
co-op and hostile summoning signs
created with small refugees gather at
summoning pools
don't understand that but cool
cool
okay
oh there's a person
that's grace
amen
hallelujah guidance of grace oh does
this tell me when to go crazy says to
grab the tarnished and lead them around
the proper path yo nice thank you
even though some signs of grace retain
that power the golden rays will guide
you along your way
wow
oh that way
who are you oh the map use your map to
check your current position as well as
the terrain and surrounding structures
you can update your map with new
information by finding map fragments at
stellis
along the world you can also use the map
to freely place beacons of light to
service that oh
i don't know but who are you
oh yes
tarnished are we i guess so into the
lands between for the elder ring how do
you know of course you have
no shame in it
unfortunately for you
however
you are maidenless oh i need a girl
without guidance
without the strength of rooms and
without an
is someone there on the horse round
table hold
you are fated
it seems
to die in obscurity
so i need a girlfriend
is that what you're saying
i will say about that
i'll be just fine without a girlfriend
but i mean if we find one
along the way i'm not gonna say no
what about the girl on the horse that we
saw i thought she was like with me
like protecting me from afar
maybe uh
are we gonna fight that dude
he's a huge axe or something
looks very very uh superior
keep talking oh they say more
talk to him more that's a boss oh dear
okay then please don't don't talk
to me don't look at me
you have more to say for you however
there is one shining ray of hope for
even the maidenless oh relay
you may also behold its golden rays
pointing in a particular direction at a
time yeah yeah that one that
is the guidance of grace i have the
hearts
that are tarnished must travel
okay i will try my best to do it indeed
grace's guidance holds the answers
it seems like you have a lot of answers
too to the path you are meant to follow
even if it leads you to your grace i get
that now okay
more
grace's guidance will reveal the path
forward most certainly
to castle stormville
overall thornvale
the home of the decrepit demigod
godric there's a god there they have to
kill it
oh god i don't know if i'm oh god i
don't know if i'm ready to kill god
but okay don't i was wondering if i
could kill
uh
by accident
seems like something the game would make
possible for me okay i i don't i don't
think i'm ready for that dude uh
this is more on my level
i'm sorry i need some food you know
oh man not getting anything from you all
right all right all right
[Music]
are they even going to run away when
they see me
[Music]
right
what
that is adorable
what is that
ruined fragment
and i use that for crafting too where is
my where's my light
i don't see my light anymore i lost my
but it must have been in that direction
and don't be quiet
don't don't don't don't get into a
battle with him it's not worth it
probably
unless you're good at fighting
light is shown on the map wait how do i
open the map
[Music]
gestures
select
wait what is select
map menu while with the map menu you can
check your current position and terrain
and buildings in the surrounding area
you can also freely place beacons of
light and lastly for your map you can
select any side of grace that you've
discovered and traveled there
instantaneously
oh
nice
however there are some dungeons in other
areas where this cannot be done okay
this is where we came from hold on
i think so always
yeah
ah there we go
oh i thought it would show me where to
go wait what is that
it doesn't go any further than that
oh well
well it was kind of that direction oh
i'll be fine
there it is
oh
is there anyone here besides that
church of l.a
there's a santa claus
what
am i looking at
what am i looking at
santa
you're a tarnished
i can see it scented and i can also see
that you're not after my oh you have a
funny uh instrument there purchase a
little something
santa
purveyor of fine goods
oh you would sell me something what do
you have with the shop menu you can
spend runes to purchase various items
you can also sell items for runes
each merchant stocks a different variety
of items
throwing dagger telescope
oh
finger ripped
crackpot
sorry guys oh my god
uh arrow ball missionary cookbook
glorious cookbook oh
should i buy a cookbook or am i am i
gonna learn anything on my own by the
crafting kit you mean the cookbook
white point
crafting kit what crafting kid crafting
kit
on this one
practice of item crafting
uh this one please how many rooms do i
have 620 oh dear
okay
bye bye
nice to do business thank you santa
claus
i i see you're getting greedy you don't
want to give things for free away
anymore if you have a crafting kit you
can make various items from materials
that you find select item crafting from
the menu you can learn to craft more
items by
the screenshot is not really looking
fitting isn't that a combat screenshot
or i guess i can make daggers
is that what you're trying to tell me
you only crack pots or other containers
to craft certain items oh you will not
be able to make more
make more of those einstein than you
have containers
containers will run out with use but
containers themselves will remain ah
container items will run
so i need cracked pots too
banana required for crafting crackpot
items okay
that's all i can uh
nice to do this afford anyway but can i
have your donkey
is that a donkey
looks like a donkey i think
or quite more more something between a
horse and a donkey but
at the smithing table you can spend
runes that's a dog [\h__\h]
no way
you can spend runes and sniffing stones
to strengthen your armaments somewhere
in the lens between you may meet a
blacksmith who can make your armaments
even stronger
wait can i really make something else
strengthen no it doesn't look like it
not not enough runes okay
oh did i activate that do i need to
activate them all
lost grace discovered
for your map you can instantly travel to
any size of grass that you've discovered
however there are some dungeons yeah i
know that
okay should i rest
why not
that's grass what you guys call it touch
grass just because i sit down
wait i forgot
oh well we're fine
we're fine okay nice to meet you santa
hoping to meet more of you somewhere
over the rainbow
and
i hope i'm going the right way i mean it
seems
most logical to go
up there
oops
love you kiara thank you i love you too
oh he was selling an extra flask i
didn't quite realize
it didn't register in my brain what the
[\h__\h] is that
i'm going off course
why the world looks crazy
let me look at the graphics
i want to look at it on a bigger screen
my
i'm looking at it i'm playing with ps5
but i'm obviously looking at it at the
pc screen
i don't want to look at it
what is that
is that like an egg
ew
oh pretty strong
but does it not attack back ew ew i'm
poisoned
i bet it wears off
i think i got poisoned
cool
what's that
what is that up there on the top of the
stone
i i only get poisoned if the bar gets
full aha
well that's nice of them
oh and i just came from there but now
i'm curious can i like climb
will you not hold on to it
man
by the way i want my two swords what is
that
oh it's just decoration or what
oh
that is only slightly creepy
what is it holding like a little piece
of poop
oh god gatekeeper for returning to the
road there's a bird looking at me
there's two birds sharing this beautiful
place with me
are you telling me to go there
and yeah hold up
we'll get better at hunting verbs
eventually
is there
we need to test the fall damage
[Music]
did i get some
no maidens i'm looking for a maiden oh
look there's boats
in the distance that have been destroyed
apparently
the water looks nice oh there's some big
boy down there
come on the water looks nice the cliffs
oh well would you [\h__\h] look at that
it looks like a wallpaper
so again
gosh the
damn
the sky
is that two trees
oh what is that straight
that's the real big boy tree though
but what is that tree then
it's beautiful
those are called earth at trees that's
german elder
it's a
means soil
it's gorgeous
so far i love this oh let's see if we
can get the boobs
i need some
kfp
[Laughter]
no my fried chicken
mommy mommy
mom right
why are you still here
[Music]
cool the rain looks nice
i like i like when it rains when there's
like a
okay this is not a sun but imagine if
this was the sun
i like i like when it rains with the sun
shining
you're so annoyed i'll just collect
berries this would be a great game for
me
oh
i have a chance another chance guys
how do you not notice me i feel like
birds have higher
flight opinion like birds have higher
senses than that
they don't get fooled that
easily oh there's a monster here yes
let's kill him let's kill him well not a
monster but
he turned on his torch just like that
are they are they meant to be killed
they look like they're meant to be
killed
oh there's a lot
there's a lot of them
where do i start
start with you
are you supposed to sneak a lot in these
games or do you guys just
just go for it
oh [\h__\h] i need to learn how to focus
they are weak yeah those are wink
sneaking is new oh really
sorry
sorry about that sorry about that so
don't run away
yo don't run away
let's corpse
at least i don't fight back that much
so let's the corpse they only have
berries man
ruin fragment okay that's that's more
interesting that's how i like it
i kind of don't know where to go anymore
though i've been like did i lose uh
he's scared
sir
i will
i'm a hero
i will not kill you
you're scared
[Music]
oh call my soul
you didn't ask for this what the [\h__\h] is
that
i was a bunny
i thought it was like a fairy light or
something like that
where do i go oh
do i go here
mushrooms
blowing mushrooms
yes i have mercy
i am i'm very kind gentle-hearted
i did not ignore the guiding light i
just felt like
exploring you know can't blame you for
that can you
it's a dungeon
am i oh no i don't think i should be
here
storm foot i hate catacombs
i hate catacombs
uh
touch the light
let's take a look
hello
we don't talk a proper death means
returning to the earth tree hmm
have patience until the time comes and
the roots called to you
unless he has a book with him is that
where is that another book
no no
equal
i'm scared mommy
[Music]
my
love it
road candy
cat comes i'll go there one day not now
i need healing let me let me go back and
get healed at least
you're not like
[Music]
turns out they are waiting for me am i
healed now
i am
well then and my body is there
all good
oh good
[Laughter]
kusa
that was funny
all right
okay back on track where was i supposed
to go
like nothing happened yeah
i'm not supposed to go around this huge
wall of
stone
and then up
is that i seemed like a dead end to me
from there on
where's the lion
well i needed some time to kind of you
know get to know the game first anyway
so some
some running around is
is good maybe
oh
that's cool why is that so randomly here
it's a soccer ball
oh you can play soccer here
with a deadbeats head
why is it glowing that's fascinating to
me
attack it oh oh oh why did i not think
of that wait
wait it doesn't let me
oh there we go
golden rule
what's that is that money
okay well didn't that way to tell me to
go like there where is the light going
that lady i mean that statue of a lady
well i can't really go straight ahead so
i have to go around now
i will
try
this way
check the map uh
oh
it's kind of
kind of that way yeah yeah yeah
hello
he looks a bit more uh
better trained than the others
but he will now be
backstabbed by me
[Music]
i like being stealthy
oh my god they suddenly turn into these
puppets it's terrifying
the game is so important
nice thank you
i'm learning
like that i prefer being stealthy like
that than just going into a big battle
freaks me out i'm too stressed out for
that at the moment there's there's two
people here
will they notice me that one over there
why did that torture suddenly turn on
and off
that's weird what are you doing
are you
is that your dead friend and you're like
trying to is he trying to burn him so
like he goes to heaven or so
i mean i almost feel sorry about killing
you
why why is it going to his butt
cookie
oh
we got some throwing weapons i think
oh maybe he was not trying to burn his
body but trying to loot him okay well
then he got a dessert being killed maybe
i was thinking he was like doing
something good
cookery cookie cookery
throwing anyas
yeah
i heard someone scream i hear someone
scream
really tiny
um so excuse me
to disturb you while you're peeing
oh
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
what is this sound
oh
this is the sound
honey wait what the [\h__\h]
it's a beetle
teardrop scarves there are both crimson
and cerulean teardrop scarabs defeat
them to replenish the floss that match
your time oh cool however you can
replenish more faster than you okay okay
okay okay yeah
okay
so that's one way to do it huh
oh
[Music]
cool that's new you guys didn't know who
here is playing while i'm playing while
watching me
you guys had enough time to get ahead of
me
i gave you a head start so
i am mimi oh my god so many
thank you for watching i know a lot of
people just decide to not watch and just
play it on their cell on their own time
that's okay oh my god what
you want to fight
that dad is calling it
before you want to give me some nice
meat for tonight's dinner you just give
me your poop butt gold
gold colored poop
oh
gold tinged again
they poop gold literally
my mom always said in german
happy name gold shot
where did you say that engage i suck
have you thank you choice out of us
do i look like i have a uh do do i look
like a [\h__\h] money or what
well these
boys definitely do seem to [\h__\h] money
oh my mom used to say that
whenever i i don't know i would ask for
some extra pocket money or so maybe
yup yup yup
i like this game you know to be honest
like i uh you guys were like um
doubting that i would like it i think so
i kind of doubted it too
a little bit but
so far i like it but we haven't had any
like that many yabai battles so i don't
know
but if i like it i might want to
continue playing it i was gonna decide
today
if i
want to play
more of this and make a serious out of
this but i know a lot of you have been
looking forward to me
starting a certain series yakuza
um
you're gonna fight me
is this friendly
is this
you don't you look like the other is so
okay i see
you want to talk no okay no talking
[Music]
um but i was thinking maybe i can do
both at the same time i don't want to
keep you guys waiting any longer on
on on yakuza because i know you've been
waiting for it maybe maybe maybe we can
start it too i don't know yeah but
because like this one is new and now now
if i really like it i want to play a
while it's fresh and hot
i don't mind waiting a bit longer
alternate weekly
we can do that too i guess
maybe i'm not sure we'll figure it out
we'll figure out a way to do it
let's infiltrate this little camp
charlene
they're they are so stupid that they're
not
uh
bringing any alarms
did someone notice me
someone noticed me
hello
welcome to come here
did i do something good nice i blocked
him
and i got bolts i got bolts
[Music]
it's butterflies
over the fire
smoldering butterfly oh no
there's some fire
herba
cool yeah i'm getting the hang of it i
want to block el to the parrot
what
oh and here we go
[Music]
it i'm already dead i'm already dead
yeah okay um you were supposed to be
stealthy here apparently i i thought
that we're not gonna ring any alarms
okay
there we go
[\h__\h] uh i think i gotta go pretty far
no not wait wrong one
but i can teleport no
i feel like the last
thingy thingy
uh where the [\h__\h] am i
huh
oh wait no that's pretty close it i
didn't realize i activated something
here
isn't that pretty close no
that's the same thing
okay
well let's get my body back
give me my body back body back body bag
but not in a body bag body bag body bag
a chamber lies under the ruins oh is
that soul
why did i not see this before
give me my body back back body back body
back but not in the body but he's
looking at me
do not all of them have a
oh
[\h__\h] that was fascinating
do not all of them have a turret
oh
i pressed the shield button
i did
you mean my body bag don't you think
what do you think
oh don't worry i won't get really far
today
get behind them how do i get behind them
while i'm
it sounds really difficult
while fighting
yay
smash it
we need to do something about the guy
with the horn
no he's just sitting there
but the horn guy is coming i think
oh oh
oh
guy
let's let him pass because he'll notice
if i kill that dude
stealth he'll
he's just chilling there with a nice
uh fire did he know this did he notice
me did he notice me did he notice me
i mean he should be wondering when he
comes back whether his friend is dead
now
okay um this is the is that the horde
yeah that's the horn guy can we like
stab him from behind that would be nice
oh god don't kill me again don't kill me
again
are there any more i love horns
stealth mission
a map
we found the map woof
oh
there's someone on the right side i
think
how do you not notice me
these npcs are kind of dumb
oh
that feels nice to stab you
um the blood tastes so good
this is what i like oh hello
i feel like he kind of yes he did see me
but he does not have a horn
relax relax
[Music]
i tried
i'm still i'm still learning guys i'm
still learning
it take free
take free
but does that mean i lost what i had the
first time uh what i lost the first time
i'm still learning
can i read
okay
i got uh to his side at least
okay maybe you stop going right in the
middle maybe i should go
from this side
i'll go from here what what is that
what
he's gonna attack me too isn't it right
that's [\h__\h] terrifying am i do i even
need to clear this camp
uh oh rose you're stabbing oh i didn't
realize [\h__\h]
damn
a puppy
i don't have to
ever now i'm so motivated
i'm so motivated i feel challenged you
know
and where's the horn guy
huh oh there he is
let him let him go let him go let him go
let him walk a little bit
estoy
[Music]
too many are too many
in your ass
how far does he go again
okay i was too much of a chicken
it goes pretty far oh call the helm
i got a helm
oh wait the map was saved the one that i
found
i didn't want to go there
equipment
with you with the equipment you can
equip armaments ball blah blah blah blah
you can equip up to three elements yeah
yeah when you told me that is this is
helmet i have been better
mostly better but it's a bit heavy
lighting
oh but much better let's take this one
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
there's no
pause to get my body give me my body
back buddy where's my helmet where's my
[\h__\h] helmet
why did it not
okay why did i not equip it
oh my god
it's nope it's okay
how would i know
are they back on their position
soon
yeah come here come in come here
come here let's fight somewhere else
here
come here
ah
oh my god
was it light
was that light did i mock that by
accident
what what is that like
[\h__\h]
my body bag
i marked it oh
no no no
no we move we move we move
move that
[Music]
[Laughter]
not the one that i lost first but one of
my many bodies
[Music]
that's okay
esta is
yes yes
at least the scenery is nice
okay you [\h__\h] bastard
you [\h__\h] bastard
come here
yeah yeah
oh god
oh lord here you coming
[Music]
i couldn't get on his side
you guys you guys you guys say roll
rolling when they're wrong wrong you say
don't roll over
guys guys i'm trying to learn here
things don't just automatically
immediately bloop
work you know
huh
[\h__\h]
and now i could stab him from the back
like he deserves
now he's going to fall
and there's one over here too [\h__\h] i
should just give up on this [\h__\h] camp
[Laughter]
where do i even go this
way i'm over here wait what
am i supposed to go for that big big uh
gate
check the wagons
huh okay
um
once uh
okay
all right i'll kill him i want to kill
him i want to kill him but no don't
don't
what do you mean check the wagons
oh my god
oh god oh
oh look at that there's a light
stop following me
[Laughter]
touch
wow
[Music]
oh
let's see
go
hello
greetings greetings to you traveler
from beyond the fog
i am melanoma
oh
i
offer you an accord you lose your eye
it's pretty cute pretty cute
an accord of the finger maiden
tell me the two fingers
offering guidance
and aid
to the tarnish
that's all
i am afraid
are maidenless
play the role of maiden oh i'm sure you
can
turning runes into strength um
to aid you in your search for the elden
ring
what do you get out of this this guy's
certainly only take me with
you i'm sure you're evil
tree you're evil aren't you
it
is this like a temporary fit
why would i refuse
now you can level
of course i guess we're accepting it
then it's settled huh
summon me by grace
to turn runes into strength
okay ah
another matter hmm
i bequeath to use this ring
uh-huh elder ring
[\h__\h] that [\h__\h] i want the elden ring
what the [\h__\h] are those
to brains
great distances great distances
it will summon a spectral steed
named torrent
got married
tyrant has chosen yes
what a name what and i am a torrent
dream of respect of course i will
thank you
uh
level up can i really level up after all
the mistakes i've made
let my hand rest upon you yes
for about a moment
share them with me wow
thoughts
your ambitions she keeps on talking the
principles you would follow
okay
uh with the level up menu you can spend
runes to increase your attributes yeah
with each attribute increase your level
rises by one
as your level rises so does the amount
of runes required for your next
attribute increase
it's not the other way around
my level arises for each attribute i
increased
runes held 128.
but i need
to raise anything
oh
well then never mind
thanks for holding my hand anyway it
felt nice
for as long as it lasted
uh let's uh pass time until morning
damn i don't like night time
oh she's gone
where's horse how do i get horse
and uh
where the [\h__\h] do i even go
horseback riding use the spectral steed
whistle to summon and ride your spectral
steed wall if your spectral seat dies
you can summon it again but it will cost
one flask of crimson tears to do so
you can dismount by using a whistle
again or by pressing l free will just
stop and stand there will it like go
away
um
so oh from pouch in the main menu
you can equip six items to your pouches
okay
uh
there is no pause but i think i'm safe
here
with the inventory you're
dropping on the ground and further away
you can also use tools from the
inventory menu
show large image and explanation
alcohol character data
okay wait so
and that what how did i put it on my
short thingy
[Music]
but how do i put it on my shortcut
back
what
what's a pouch
hmm
[Laughter]
okay
look at my noble steed it's kind of
small cute
oh i can acquire materials while i'm
riding nice
um i wonder how much damage they can
take
i hope they can at least take a few hits
um
now the question is
doco
because this still tells me to go that
low i feel like
did we miss one here
double jump while riding through the
gate with a big gate okay
oh wait oh oh oh
there we go
oh
even faster
today the weather is really really
cloudy man
not the best weather
what was that
quieter materials earthly flower
a nice pretty flower
okay we're riding around the camp
because i'm too stupid to do
anything there at all
oh
all the signs lead to this point
uh l three l three l three l three
patch
grace
i can fight on horseback noise
okay
go there
[Music]
there's a lot of notes there
i suggest speed should i just ride
through
look up
oh
um
right through they say
can i yeah
but you said double jump wait a second
let me test
oh this is like parkour
they want me to do some kind of parkour
but this will jump down though
hello
i don't want to look what's behind me
oh it's that easy
can i have a back mirror
am i safe
starmail let me see
really that's it that's it that was so
intimidating oh
okay they still follow me they still
follow me
thank you
[Music]
[\h__\h] man um am i going the right
direction
touch grace can i touch grace are they
following me
am i safe
i'm not safe i'm not safe i'm not safe
i'm not safe
i'm not safe i'm not safe i'm not
safe two
two i think i can handle maybe
no
okay um this is their territory
oh they're leaving i'm leaving i think
they're leaving
hi
go home go home
go home
you're going they're leaving
[Music]
i want to touch grace but they were in
the way
okay
okay hallelujah
oh thank god
let's touch that grass
oh man
yeah i felt like like good players like
if you like uh experienced those game
players player
then you would probably have
easily destroyed all the enemies i've
been so far passing by right or do you
do you guys also
also
just pass by these or do you kill them
thank you thank you
not all of them
am i missing like a lot of exp or one
though
it's hard still
i try to kill everything
you pick your fights oh okay
i'm ground
what is what is these
[Music]
ah
they crossed the sea for me they fought
for me very nice of them
only to have their arms taken oh [\h__\h]
their legs taste that's not good in
their heads
taken decapitated
taken and stuck
to the spider the spider
if you're grafted by the spider
you become a chrysalid which that's
quite a lot when you think about it
where's your lark speak english with me
sitting sideways oh thank you for
teaching me how to sideways
that's very important for me to continue
this game
oh thank you like eh
be careful now
you're willing to make me a chrysalid oh
no i was trying to destroy the box
behind you
oh don't worry some mysterious wall is
protecting your runaway
shut up already i'll change my mind
yeah i know
so
invisible paywall or something
don't worry about it
okay
oh guys so stormy can i get some better
weather oh my god there's there's
there's there is there there's soldiers
coming
four
i want to kill them but they're too
like groupie
i want them one by one
they're going they're going back
how
wow careful you can kill npcs i've heard
but apparently not her
wait let me look at the map
ah wait that way so one time around like
this i suppose
because i can't go up there
uh okay so do i also just ride past him
i want to ride past everything with a
kill oh talk to her
okay
you think she still wants to talk to me
you're sure i think she's scared of me
you're all on your own are you yeah and
heading to stormville castle yeah i have
a horse though the one in the right mask
i suppose what
oh you've come to be one with the spider
know what i hate spiders
two peas in a pod
no
it's scary you know having your arms cut
off
or legs
or your head
i want to be like everyone else but i'm
just too scared oh you want to be like
everyone else as in you want to have
something cut off
[\h__\h] freak oh i know ah can you take
this little one along with you is this
like a side quest
spirit jellyfish ashes
what
the poor thing deserves someone braver
than myself
and
the spirits look rather fondly upon you
it will be glad of your company i think
i'm confused
oh with a spirit calling bell you can
use ashes to summon various spirits
summoning typically consumes fp well
wait a fight for me you can only summon
one type of spirit at the time you can
cannot summon spirits doing multiplayer
they'll they'll fight with me
oh
jellyfish wait can i only do it one time
and then they'll they'll be like used up
this is like a throwaway item
how do i how do
i play
here
permanent
reusable
and just summon whatever cross mana
i get the belly oh i cannot use it yet
what's the bell for
so
what if i call them now will they follow
me
return to the church for the bell you
need to find a girl uh-huh
church with church
go back should i go now
balance for the clerics
okay
to use in a fight
fast travel oh
oh i guess i could do that
taco bell
ah
okay
got it wait a second
ah
uh my mom is asking me to continue and
make this into a series
if my mom says so then no
i think i have to
yeah hi mom
mommy i want to play elder the
wonder if her pc can even handle alden
ring
yeah
uh okay we've never done fast traveling
before the church is um
here
cave no
the first step church this is the is
that the church i need to go to
church of
l.a church of illinois yeah
oh but oh you mean from the guy you have
to buy it
but
i don't think i have the money for it
it's way tarnished okay i have a word um
no
i did not come for you i came for this
guy he's slipping though huh can't trade
with him
oh
yeah okay well what's up
a pleasure to meet you tarnish you're
pretty i am the witch well your four
to call forth a spectral steed named
torrent yes
uh i can indeed do that
ah
as i had hoped
i was entrusted this for thee
by torrent's former master
ow you give it to me just like that oh
thank you
oh wolves
nice calling forth spirit piss a bell
summon them with it
ash and return to the urgery
the spirits will obey thine command but
briefly
as they recall battles past
now it is dying
to do with as thou
well thank you i'm very kind of you
forgive my intrusion tarnished
i doubt we shall again meet
never still the same
learn well the lands between
how long will it be i wonder
before the tarnished tire of a basins to
the two fingers
they all speak in riddles to me
but now i have whoops
and uh
wait
wolves and jellyfish
ah the jellyfish are cheaper though why
is it so noisy here
i shall sleep until
daytime
i think
yeah wasn't she i've seen her face
before she was in that opening video
until morning hopefully the weather is
better this time
nope doesn't look like it but but oh
[\h__\h] no no did i do what did i do
ah okay oh it's another morning we
wasted some time
all right
hi dude by the way
and
weren't
yes i'm back
but yeah just checking just checking
bye-bye
[Music]
er get toys
horse or i guess i could uh teleport
teleport here
yes
hopefully no big surprises
jumps instead of talking
yeah i i
i'm trying to think
logically
okay how about
where are they
i want to kill them
what what do we have to lose we could
try to
i've never really done combat in on the
horse is this i heard it's easier
okay
[Music]
okay okay interesting
yeah
i'm too bad they can't catch me
nice
wait maybe i shouldn't do this
oh
okay i got two down two down two down
[Applause]
yeah
i'm getting dizzy
this actually
gives me at least
one kind of a chance
upgrade my flask uh-huh
how
horse riding my new favorite hobby
vanquishing an enemy group will
represent oh
nice the number of type of plasma
[Music]
cool
they're dead
yeah
[Music]
good job me
smoldering blah
[Music]
where the weather is [\h__\h] gold
why is the weather so [\h__\h]
i'm more confident now
muy muy confident though
does that make any sense what i just
said
heel
oh
all right
i'm going off track i think yeah
or am i
yeah i think i am
good luck fighting him who
fighting who
is there something coming
here
uh
wait a second l3 to get off the horse
him wait don't go away
is there something up there
oh god i'm so scared the music is so
threatening
someone's shooting me
someone saw me
oh two people
oh
oh god
oh my god
uh
first one let's get on the horse let's
get on the horse
i don't know if i can if i'm ready for
this
oh no
[Music]
i'll come back after everyone calms the
[\h__\h] down oh no
how many how many how many oh what the
[\h__\h] is that
oh okay okay now we're good i thought
the train was a monster
you also like it oh handle number one
number one number one free well free is
still okay
yeah
one down one down
[Music]
they hit hard
[\h__\h] hard
wait do i have to kill that group again
it seems like it
there's my body
alright
overconfident yeah
that is my name
okay
be efficient here shall we
why are you still alive
okay okay okay okay
yeah yeah yeah it is balls go
whoa
group once again
eliminate it we got some bolts
anything else you would like to give me
no okay
cool
i don't want to waste my flasks
so i'll heal down here
again
uh
i don't have to get off
on my own
past time morning time again
oh wait one day ah [\h__\h] don't they
revive oh [\h__\h] i forgot
i forgot
why is it so dark
hear man now i have to fight them again
it's practice it's practicing exp guys
wow
i like the aoe damage there yo
[Music]
my finger i can't pull the trigger
anymore
oh wait my stamina right uh-huh
i see i see you're much faster when you
still have the stamina
put silver gauntlets we're getting
better atoms this time
let me let me use what you giving oopsie
what are you giving to me uh nope no
what what what what no no no no what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] no i want to get out
of here
getting dizzy here yeah sorry me too me
too
uh equipment
so i have
these now
that i think are better but besides that
oh no
bolts bolts i'm not even using the bolts
oh wait i can use that shield no
ah my
oh i can't use it efficiently but i can
actually use it anyway
interesting
oh
i can use that stuff i don't know how
like why how why how do they work
um level up
what i leveled up or are you telling me
to level up or are you telling me to use
it when i level up press right stick
stats
can't level up without that lady
use jellyfish okay okay okay okay okay
we're wherever we're going now
we're probably gonna need some help
anyway
ah let's go from
the side
let's try to kill some friends
before they see us shall we
where is he there he is
did you see me already
no i don't think so
oh [\h__\h] now he did
oh did he think he saw something but
then he changed his mind
turn around buddy
you will lose it
i would lose my rooms if i don't level
up
don't i have to call the lady to level
me up
must have been the wind it's definitely
the wind everything you see is the wind
uh
what's it any grace level cam okay wait
a second
amy what you got
adding skills with a wet stone knife you
can use ashes of war to grant your
animated new skills at size of grace and
iron man can only have one skill any
skill it previously had will be removed
an armament type determines what skills
it can have some special armaments have
unique skills and cannot be granted new
ones
okay with a white stone knife you can
use ashes of war to grant affinities to
your armaments and sides of
did i not just read that
this way you can alter your elements
attack affinity boost attribute scaling
and more and hours after
[Music]
a lot of information
sh what shield war what
okay you want me to
go to
one of the
grace thingies
and level up there
upgrade crazy
how do i do that i don't think the game
told me how to upgrade flasks
anyway
well for rest won't they be revived
again can i
level up without resting
okay
oh we have enough now uh what what do we
do uh dexterity strength endurance
dexterity
maybe for now bigger
yeah
got them
confirmed
how much more weight how much more
how much more did i get i didn't look
that closely
did i get in a significant amount back
and not back but did i get a good amount
of health now
more health yes please
check flasks flasks flasks
okay okay okay okay
um
which one add charge to flask increase
amount replenished by flasks
uh
allocate flask charges
add charge
use one golden seat to increase your
number a flat yes
wait how did i choose which one ah
because okay okay because it was a red
one oh and now i have a blue one
two golden
why does it cost more sale seeds every
time
there's a number of flask uses allocate
do allocate
okay
well in this menu you can allocate the
number of users in each of your flasks
you have a set total of maximum flask
uses you can decide how many of those
users are for the hp
and
i guess this is okay because i'm not
using the blue ones much now
allocate
should i do even more
not enough okay okay okay crease i'm not
finished by flash i don't know i don't
understand what that means
a sacred tier to increase them
ah
no
i don't think i have one
go full healing
okay
six
but you know me i'll be too slow uh to
use them anyway
all right
i'm so scared
why are those [\h__\h] there again
i'm gonna do it again
he killed my horse
oh [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] man
uh wait oh wait i'm trying to fake i'm
trying to fake
i wanted to call my friends in [\h__\h]
bastion
but at least i did the thing before
dying
i was trying to think
how this is wig
too stupid to hit from that side
ow
don't kill my horse
my steep
my beautiful speed
oh
okay now i killed them for the fifth
time i think
what do we have oh we keep on getting
new items from them
okay can i not uh uh bring in the these
weird spirits that i have when i'm on a
horse
because i tried
or do i have to
put the bell there or what
hell wanted oh from the left oh but i i
was carrying my shield on l1
uh
uh only summon them in certain places
oh i thought i could summon them
anywhere what the hell
oh
and there's a door sign on the left aha
okay
well um
uh
anyway
oh yeah okay
i feel like
death is near
uh should i just run through
ah here i can summon them
but like you guys said only when i'm
like in battle right
she's someone
should i should i just should i just run
through
will they fight for me are you gonna
fight
oh you're gonna fight everything that
attacks me
the [\h__\h] was that
kill it are you attacking it
whoa wow
i don't know if this is really effective
are you just shooting like randomly
oh
too far
can you come with me
my sparrow come with me
yes and then
oh that was by accident
no no okay no that was fun
and then call it again
[\h__\h] now i can't
i can't call them
yeah the thing is gone
uses oh i don't have enough ah
guys i'm scared
i'm gonna die
what the hell
hi hi sorry just passing by
oh
okay okay okay okay okay um
you guys should tell me what to do like
what the [\h__\h]
you guys are just gonna go through this
[\h__\h] all on my own
you just want to see me die no
i have to kill those [\h__\h] again
[Music]
oh wait i don't have to kill him again
maybe
is that my body
oh
cool
cool sorry bro
what the actual [\h__\h]
i can't call it now but like is it is it
even worth it what about these boys girl
kill some people
you're following me
okay let's go kill some people
am i supposed to fight
i'm fighting guys
uh can i go friends
friendly fired
yes they can
i was just gonna ask if it could hit the
enemies instead of me it can't it can't
it can
but that was
an improvement
um
at least i have my mana back we can call
the wolves again
wolf is better here i think
and
okay
don't get hit by the fire thingies
am
just kill me
no not my wolves
no no no
no no my wolves
come with me wolf guys well friends
come with me
really
this isn't even what you mean guys with
uh
him right
there's something is there something
worse waiting for me
never give up
never gonna give
this up never gonna let myself down
all right
another try
get the snipers
oh
did i just kill my
horse or did i unmount
oh or your snipers
ah
[Music]
[\h__\h] give me a break give me a [\h__\h]
break give me a [\h__\h] break give me a
[\h__\h] break give me a [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] break
am i really just gonna what is going on
here
[\h__\h] you
how am i still even alive
at this point
[Music]
oh it's getting better
not really making much progress huh
not really making any progress
where's my body
up here
oh
excuse [\h__\h] may yeah
attack wolves attack them attack those
bastards
okay called them again what if i just
walk through
it
are they able to come through
um okay
well this is a
good place to be
um
interesting
well at least i'm not fighting all alone
anymore don't i don't don't you [\h__\h]
guys
well where where am i getting revolved
am i am i getting revived at that door
no
there's a grayson tunnel should i just
should i just run through or should i
i'm not sure what to do
like it seemed kind of possible
you just run
oh [\h__\h] you
you deserve that you deserve that
i want to
kill you
oh wait where am i where my dog goes
what am i talking why can't i not call
my daughters
i wanna come no no no no no no no no no
give me my dog what the [\h__\h]
there
it's not fair
[\h__\h]
huh i can't leave i'll get it
wait you don't have to go go scale it
hell i'm suffering
i have no clues where did i get the dogs
i'm from the lady who gave me the bell
right
okay [\h__\h] this i'm taking a different
route
i
i've been wasting too much time here
why am i getting off my horsey oh [\h__\h]
oh no
okay i guess my horse is not an option
in here anymore okay
my dogs will protect me
touch grass
he's coming who's coming
who's coming
knuckles
[\h__\h] come over here [\h__\h]
are they gonna attack me once they're
done with my dogs
it's not good it's not good it's not
good it's not good it's not good where's
clothes coming are they following me are
you fooling me
no
what if i go back
oh they're there
who's coming
wait what if i uh
i get the hang of it i don't know about
that
i thought it's me please give me up
give me a break
i'm gonna rest for a moment
i can't i can't do that okay
okay
what i'm not ready for a boss
this one is not optional i guess
okay
yeah
what is this
touch
oh is this like a
another player
who could help me
is this a real player or an npc
it's an npc
they're better than nothing no he'll
actually know what to do
unlike me
summon i mean is there any any bad thing
about it
i don't think so summoning culprit
summoning
npc please help me
hello
hallelujah okay should i be on my horse
no
huh
[Music]
you look cool
can i like
kiss your ass and you'll be nice to me
[Applause]
nothing beats the ground pounds
there is no way
that i'll do this first right
now phoenix
i forgot
how do i switch to tear thingies again
how do i go to the other tiers isn't
that the wrong tears yeah kill my
friends kill my friend that's good
[Music]
on the wrong on the wrong thingy but hey
hey hey hey hey we can do this i was
just wondering about my flask if once
now that i know what my flask is i'll be
fine
here's my flask
oh why is it like this now
you could unequip the oh why do i even
have a as empty though isn't
it why does it take so long to summon an
npc
some of the wolves oh i can
makes it even easier
okay yeah
let's go travis
travis
he's already here
[Music]
um
oh he does so much damage
i'm not even fighting
i'm just scared to get so close to him
get out of here get out of here
yeah yeah
okay
look they're outside they're dying i
need to
okay okay
no
i'm alone
well we got almost to half we got i'm
almost halfway for
hmm
maybe i should keep the doggos until
the sorcerer is dead so that i used to
have something to
order jellyfish should i do jellyfish
why are you here
forgive me
i've been
testing are you were trolling me whether
or not grace truly does gonna give me
easy mode now
whether you were fit to face the
challenge maybe i should do two swords
it seems my worries were unfounded
torrent had your measure from the very
start
whereas i merely pretended
there is but one other thing i can do to
offer you guidance or i can take you to
the round table hole i'm kind of busy
right now girls
of tarnished champions
guided
by grace
what now
what
is
she giving me like for real
is it is this what she means as she's
gonna help me
or is she just going somewhere else with
me
oh okay
what does that very well
let my hand rest upon you
for about a moment what's happening
what's happening
why are we not why why now
that's so random what
why are we going somewhere else
huh
the round table hold is a place where
tarnished together guided by grace
combat is prohibited on the premises due
to the to a pact of non-aggression this
rule is an effect when the roundtable
icon is displayed the round table hold
is a little is located outside of this
world it can only be reached through
sights of grace uh-huh
oh no what is this
what's it for
oh this is a rare occasion homebase
can't remember the last time in utah
very well
as your senior why now
i bet you welcome
it is safe here
you may let down your guard
no no i want to go back to the fight
but i guess should i talk to all of them
first oh i see you've just arrived
welcome to the fancy neck warmer that
you that have there
a man of the cloth
teach incantations
strength granted us by the two fingers
and explore the secrets of the golden
order
so that one day
if a tarnished of the round table hold
should become elden lord i might cancel
them
ensuring order regains its proper form
writing rule over men
do you still see it
the guidance of grace i'm not sure
i see it you do i think
most tarnished are blind to it these
days oh you said so you are something of
a rare breed
i'm a phoenix what do you say care to
learn an incantation of the two fingers
i suppose so
can i really do that no no i cannot
i can apparently not
thank you i'll be back someday
who is you ah hello
nice armor
i'm
well
just call me diana you want to borrow me
not alma one's house holds little import
in these lands
by the way
have you met a young woman named lanya
on your travel lanyard she's my servant
no but fickle is the winner
take your eyes off her for put a moment
and she's good as gone
if you find her
please be sure to tell me okay side
quest or what sounds like a side quest
okay well i'm kind of like in the middle
of something so can i just uh come back
here later another time
um i kind of kind of wanna
do
this big boy now
here
yes
eh you can use the map to go yeah yeah
yeah talk to them again
ah what will suddenly give me like the
absolute insane power that i need to
kill this
[\h__\h] god
because i doubt it i doubt anything
will save me
at this point
[Music]
let me
maybe
do this
okay
let's
go because no [\h__\h] way i can block
off anything that he does with a shield
oh
there we go
what if he just falls down wouldn't that
be funny
okay
yeah source me some magic dude yes
it was some dangery damage
yes that looks beautiful yes let's go we
have a chance now
oh no be careful
he got blasted
me too me too i'm i'm coming deaf
my sweet sweet is released
oh
i didn't mean it that literal
didn't get as far as before but we also
didn't have so much damage as before
uh we'll do it we'll do it next time
we'll do it next time
we'll do it next time trust me
come on come on come on
jump attacks
okay uh and what are loading r2 i'll try
i'll try
he here you here buddy ready
here goes uh
yeah focus on me
ow
where's my body
touch my body
does this help me
okay okay
oh [\h__\h]
no don't kill him don't hurt him
warrior blood must
i'll never be able to kill him never and
i tried to i tried to jump attack and
but no it doesn't look like it did more
damage maybe wasn't it a more fancy
attack
oh yeah i was only using my i got so
used to only using my right weapon [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
i can never kill them
i'm trying
i might have to grind
ain't nobody got time for that i'm
already here
yeah
but everything so far was so tough to
so tough to tackle
okay
you see we get really good at this after
trying a million times
where's my body
okay
did some good damage there though
she's getting wrecked
it's going pretty well
let's go
time for some help
no no no no no
oh my wolves they die so fast oh no i
can't live without them
[Music]
i can do it i can do it [\h__\h] did i drink
two
forever
this will take an hour
oh man i'm trying to tie my [\h__\h]
rules stop telling me to tap my rules
don't i look like i'm turning my rules
i'm trying okay
uh anyway
[\h__\h] trying
my first souls game okay
yeah we we're doing progress
progress come online always takes so
much time
oh
while he's occupied
with my friend i really need to trap
higher
do some damage
oh [\h__\h] i drank it by accident [\h__\h]
want the wrong button
ah [\h__\h] this is a wrong bra a bad bad
bad turn
back turn bathroom bathroom
maybe just experiment in this turn
oh yeah
[Music]
oh he's still alive
friend is still alive you should have
used resurrection on me
do you guys think jellyfish is better
in this in this fight
what do you think guys
yeah the wrong direction i tend to
always roll to the to one side somehow
no yes
jelly yes we can try i guess
but do i want to have it out immediately
in the beginning won't it target my
jellyfish and kill it immediately i
don't know if i should wait
with it let's see
that's it
right now it's focusing on he's focusing
on me right now
oh not anymore
oh
oh my body forgot my body
i think it's going well
i haven't gotten any damage yet
oh
damage damage incoming
damage incoming
okay we're still alive i wish i could
like
heal him
i want to keep him alive
no don't kill my jellyfish
oh wow wow
no
and he's dead now it's me it's all on me
unless you want to kill my jellyfish
yeah he wants to
he very much wants to
[\h__\h] you so [\h__\h] you
i'm like so [\h__\h] i need a tank
i need a tank
i got too close to him and then
that end part
i got too close
how many tries do we want to give this
huh
you think it's better with the jellyfish
i feel like it's actually it's good it's
good
it's good because because the wolf's
like they come too close to him and then
he just does an aoe move and they all
get like immediately wrecked
a hundred tries
hmm
shield my [\h__\h] tiny shield that's as
big as my head you think that will
protect me
i feel like i do much more damage now
with the two swords and uh i want to
count on that right now
you're in the way
hi
[Music]
where's my body
don't worry i didn't have that much
there anyway
i think
well that was the first
that was the first gotta be careful
there
yeah i tried to grab the body first but
i didn't expect that to happen
man
but can the bus fall down too
hey
hey hey hey
let me let me first like you know
out
you standing on my body on my course
[Laughter]
no
maybe i should look at that tutorial
i know i know i know i know i know i
know come on
why does he take so much time
[Music]
this is so unfair
like i don't even have time to summon
oh
yeah okay okay
no not my jelly boy
wait my body did i spread my body no
it doesn't matter
at this point is there not actually
nothing
inside
oh well
that was uh i feel like wasted
a lot of potential there whoa
the trees
it doesn't matter right
don't have to bother picking it up
anymore
[Music]
eventually eventually we we will get a
lucky run guys i have i'll feel it i
believe it
i have leveled up once
one time
let's go let's go roger
don't hit me again don't no it's a
little [\h__\h]
you little [\h__\h]
oh god don't they don't get away get
away
oh maybe too early
he almost jumped down
[\h__\h] yeah
he's coming for me
oh
[Music]
oh my sorcerer is still alive
still alive not much longer
so surrounded
i don't know how the [\h__\h] i can fight
you without my friend
[Music]
last flask it's impossible but but we're
lower than before on his health and i'm
dead
i'm dead i'm so [\h__\h] dead
i'm so [\h__\h]
i have leveled up once kelly you
probably understand how bad that is i i
have like
no upgraded [\h__\h] no experience
neither in the game nor in real life
with this um i mean like my character
has no experience and i have no
experience with the game so
wonderful combination
oh on the phone
but we're getting better we're getting
better we're gonna scuff this we're
gonna scuff the hell out of this
let's go kelly can you be my co-operator
please
i'm gonna let you hit me again right
from the get-go no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no
now
[Music]
i'm gonna kill you
i like how my sorcerer is every now and
then just trying to beat a tank
he's so sweet he knows it's not what
he's meant to be doing but he doesn't
for me
because i'm just
not meant to be the tank
stop
not my destiny
oh what did you do there
what you gonna do
it's gonna kill my sorcerer
go art of passing skills
no
[Music]
no no no no no no no
no no no no oh wow oh god gave me some
big advice here huh the only general
advice i can give is grinding on the
experience good try baiting enemies out
one by one i've been i mean yeah trying
to go stealth him
you're both thinking behind
here
sneaking here you mean
what do you mean in general not not not
in this boss fight right i don't see how
i can sneak
here well but you know i'm kind of like
i don't want to go back anymore now that
i'm already here
i'll give it maybe
15 more tries and if i still don't
manage do it i'll go grind my ass off
well
for buzz you want to take advantage of
the npc dating him oh callie
call you kelly
see i i really appreciate you trying to
help here
hit him behind him yeah unless you want
to make sure his attacks just barely
miss
and punish him just barely um
now yo kelly that sounds like something
an experienced
player would do but
i'm i'm um i i get the i get the
the thought of it
no it's not this back seating is always
very welcome in my stream
wow
[Music]
we didn't like that he didn't like me
touching him from that point
i was ticklish for him
it feels a little ticklish you know
did i punish him good you like that kind
of punishment
you like it feels good huh
yeah
oh no
that looks like it hurts
okay
um
[Music]
okay
it's my chance it's my chance
it's my [\h__\h] chance tonight
no no no no no
no
oh
chubby shall we wait
oh lord he's coming
jelly's still
alive no no no
shelley dead chill you're dead jelly's
[\h__\h] dead
no i can't do this
no
i'm gonna mess up i'm gonna mess up
[Music]
ah
what
wait what
[Laughter]
oh i didn't realize
what what what what
what what
oh my god the standoff the [\h__\h]
standoff the [\h__\h] standoff man and my
jellyfish he survived for so long i i
felt like that was the run it really
felt like it and it almost was it almost
was
it almost was
it almost [\h__\h] was
[Music]
man
ah
all too close together
he's in the shitty position in my
opinion
we're all in the shitty position right
now
don't is can my sorcerer fall down i
hope not dear lord
warrior blood
get rekt
how dare you hurt him
how dare you
oh [\h__\h] that would be the time i was too
slow i was too far away
sorry sorry sorry sorry next next one
next one this one last one
believe believe believer
i'm gonna be so proud of myself if i
manage to do this
i'm gonna be so proud
you ready to go
okay come on boy
starting to get some cramps in my hands
man
i'm starting to get like a
what do you call it um a routine here
what
i'm getting so [\h__\h]
no that's a very dangerous game i'm
playing
can someone revise me
can someone revive me
hello resurrection
i have to revive my stuff all the time
what's your hp oh too late
combat combine
now that we got him
so far
so close
i do
indeed believe
ow
not fair no don't attack my jellyfish i
need this for as long as possible
and i couldn't do my sick move i don't
honestly i don't even know how i did
that in the first place
sometimes it works sometimes it doesn't
no i need
gotta attack the front
yep but i was i was slicing his
he's a
butt crack
that's the move that i mean
that was from behind the filling
front stab
well the one where i slice up his uh
ass
ass crack
to make it bigger
i feel like cow carrot is gonna make a
compilation
[Laughter]
oh this is this is something good for
cow carrot
okay i am
hello you're not gonna do your thing
well
he didn't want to apparently
oh
nice
[\h__\h]
physics
warrior blood
muscles okay so surrendered
now it's time for screeching chicken
noises
okay jelly you and me
we're gonna rock this
but
hello i would like to stop missing
don't die don't you dare die no no i
can't live without you
i can't
okay
he's poisoned though isn't he
oh no god oh god my hands my hands my
hands
no no no my hands my hands my hands my
hands my [\h__\h] hands
ah look that was so unnecessary
this is not the run
although if i start long enough he keeps
on getting the poison damage
so that's good
oh
[Music]
i don't know when to attack
oh no no
but like
my movement is so slow
i'm never going to attack him again i'm
never going to attack him again because
then i'm dead because then i'm [\h__\h]
dead
[Music]
you're stinky you stink you stink you
stink you stinky
yeah i did some i think those were some
good dodges
there were some good dodges but like
it's so hard to like get back into
attacking when like i'm
trying to roll
away from his attacks like he doesn't
give me time to do it
that was a good try if only a jellyfish
would have survived a bit longer or or
my sorcerer like someone
man how did i go
so close to killing him that one time
i was so close
[Music]
all right
i want to try to be a bit more
aggressive though
when he attacks the others
i gotta use
just
while the others are still alive
sorry sarah why aren't you dodging
why is he not dodging huh you guys tell
me to dodge all the time tell him tell
him
how about you tell him oh [\h__\h] no
what
oh yeah
now he's thinking he's thinking he's
like damn this chick gets better every
time
unbelievable who would have thought
[Music]
that was too much damage
oh man
i can summon what
you can summon jelly twice
does that have enough mana for that what
and
for phase two what do you mean i can
what's with phase two me summoning
jellyfish
reflects ten percent damage jellyfish
are tanks oh really sorcery is the
dealer let's keep the sorcerer alive for
as long as possible sold on a yes yes
[Music]
the best way to touch you so you can
wind up up
forward bros roll into him can i like
roll through him well dodge roll towards
him so in position to attack
so i should actually not like go behind
i should
go right in front of his crotch
if you aim
a bit to the side
i will try
okay
yo yo yo chill chill uh
oh i do have enough mana to call him
twice
can we get out of that corner
suddenly turns around in the sides nope
now now i want to fight you
oh get out of here
is going pretty well
i maybe shouldn't have drunk that now
thank you for your hard work
i'm so scared to go to him
oh but he's focusing on jelly
yay
well one time i'm brave enough to roll
towards him
i think we're doing it
it's not as dangerous as i thought it
would be
please please give me a chance
okay drink drink drink
i am drinking the right timing sorry
sorry sorry sorry but okay okay okay
okay okay okay
i didn't drink it in the right timing
but that that look that felt um like we
did
it more efficiently
[Music]
although sorcerer still dies very fast
that's not my fault
that's not my fault if he pulls aggro
and then is so so sensitive
is that really my fault it's not like i
can i can really take i mean i can't i
can take aggro away from him but if you
guys are right and jellyfish is the real
tank here
then
jellyfish should be pulling the aggro
not me
[Music]
reflect that [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] that starts kind of a bad
start
i want to practice dodging like into him
oh boy sorry i was like what the [\h__\h] is
going on
i thought my game was lagging but it's
just slow motion
kind of
sorry i'm not dodging i'm so sorry i'm
so sorry i'm so sorry i'm so sorry i'm
desiring desires i'm sorry i'm sorry
sorry
i know when he goes down like that this
is when i need to hit him i know it
feels like
that's the right moment
my friend
my friend how many times are we gonna
meet
feels like a [\h__\h] deja vu
i'm stuck in this stuck in this dream
it's never ending but you know what
it's kind of fun
only a little bit
always dangerous always very dangerous
dangerous dangerous
oh
[Applause]
this is this is
impossible it's possible it's possible
it didn't count
wow my hands are feeling not as good as
i did half an hour ago
i wanna
i wanna do this
thank you kelly your spirit being here
it's
motivating i am motivated
i can do it
at least i'm not so hopeless anymore as
i was in the beginning i saw the goal i
saw it in front of my eyes
it was at my fingertips
kelly did you see that one time when did
you look away that one time when i got
him to like
like
one one percent down
one percent was like one percent left
girl girl
you you want to start it differently
okay wait i should i'm getting my jelly
you get my down get my tail get myself
get my tail and get me jelly
[Music]
wasted
for what
well you should if you fall down that
[\h__\h] cliff you would deserve it
stop
[Music]
no that was such a moment that was such
a moment
oh okay we're in that face oh oh no
oh no oh no
oh no no i feel like getting worse i
feel like i'm getting worse
no friends friends no
please stay a little bit longer
find me instead hit me
yes yes hit me
do some damage
dead
he's been
he's dead he's dead
no no no no
oh wow
my fingers
single moments
he has no chill
he has no chill guys
no
no never gonna give up
wait whoa
whoa
i'm gonna make it
and it's gonna be legendary
i believe
i believe i can die
i believe i can touch the grave
first wait wait wait wait give me a
break oh
friends
too careless
ow
oh too careless
that was a good start well and that was
a good end
that was uh
one way of ending it
oh
man
[Music]
can someone build a [\h__\h] fence there
this is dangerous
man
i'm so stupid
i'm too low level i know but we got him
once we got him once
is he there okay
oh yeah okay
can you give me a moment yes thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you
that's exactly
the ideal way to do it
uh
oh
yes the damage
shooting all at once
stop it
want to survive i want to survive i want
to survive
oh [\h__\h] sorcerers
that move i i i i kind of recognize the
pattern now i'm still too slow to
react to it though
yeah this is it again this is it again
[\h__\h]
ah that move when he turns around
move that move though
it's like i feel it but i'm never 100
sure and like i'm like 90 sure
and then i'm not sure which way to
which way to roll when he does that
i have to anticipate it yeah like once
like when he's focused on the other one
and i attack him from behind he like
after a few hits he does it he's like
sick of being beaten from the back and
then he's like [\h__\h] you
no
all right all right
all right
oh [\h__\h] dude chill chill take a chill
pill man or snickers
whoa
did we just like get him on his back for
the first time ever
i feel like we never did that before
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh
[\h__\h]
i'm trying to
like
be more active you know
like slicing his throat there man now
now now he's a
he was about to do it but sorcerer died
now he's like okay girl
[Music]
no no please let me drink
let's give me a chance
[Music]
i didn't anticipate that
oh
wait why are we not in phase two
[Music]
why was i able to call my jellyfish
again i said you said i can get him
again a second time
wow
thank you colleen
kelly can you come over and
play for me
uh
someone asked just once per passport
somewhere a lot
feel like a bunch of people said i can
summon him twice
i was i was kind of like
counting on that
i am using both of my weapons
if you mean both of my swords
i'm using them all the time
thank you kelly
i
i don't know how long this journey will
be
but
oh dear lord
that's not the start that i like to see
it
it's a very bad sight
cornered him
that's good or bad
oh
i landed a few good hits there
no
no no
no that was so good
that was so
good
at least i'm not the only one suffering
i'm dragging you guys into the suffering
surprised my cats haven't come by to
check if i'm okay and why am i screaming
so much
it had such a
bad start
uh-oh
i tried instead of dodging backwards
to come okay
ah can i restart i
i was i was i wanted to call this boy
accidentally use the potion
can i restart
oh can i reach that is a bad run bad run
bad run bad run
oh
we're still gonna try and make the most
of it does everyone is a oh oh wait i
thought i thought he was going to turn
around i thought he was going to turn
around no
no
everyone is a practice a a way to
practice i was going to stay
[Music]
go
oh oh
i can turn around and for once i dodged
it but i was so far away anyway
yeah i just wanted i was too uh
impatient there i wanted to attack
but this was a [\h__\h] run anyways
dodged too much dodged a little too
aggressive so coward
yeah then i
[Music]
have noticed
that's what i was thinking
ah
[Music]
you guys
i i have i've read about a million
comments about me
stop
needing to stop rolling so much
and if i have yet to
adapt
that trick then you can probably guess
that it's not happening
at least not today not now
i'm trying to
dodge you know
it's not like i'm just doing it for fun
there's a
purpose there's a purpose
ah
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] slap oh oh we found him
and i'm busy drinking some [\h__\h]
energy drinks
all sorts so we're not gonna survive
very long and this run is
[Music]
oh
sorcerer i did
oh sorry sorry very bad moves today
this time not good
got my jellyfish i needed i need my
jellyfish
is
you know i i actually
have um kind of like a a time frame like
um
i can i can probably go a bit longer but
i'm supposed to like not play longer
than five hours
max maybe like five and a half
so
get a few more levels
but like huh
but these [\h__\h] there's too many of
those two so sorry gonna are you gonna
help me fight those
i can't
maybe with the experience i have now
and my wolves
let's go
if we get him down wait a sec if we kill
him
then there will be no more shooting
shoot right
oh
man i feel i feel like i leveled up like
not necessarily in the game but i feel
like my hands leveled up a million times
like my my gaming skills by trying that
boss a million times
i'm
kind of stuck here
like i
i wasn't able to do this before
okay but i also have a sorcerer with me
still
well we'll just take them all on from
behind but wait wait a second
one way to do it
did i forget something here no okay
we'll just take them all from behind
get me those exp
oh god
no they weren't supposed to see us
okay we're too strong am i even getting
hp when the sorcerer kills them
wait wait wait tilt the lid
it's in the socker
yeah i guess the numbers are rising i
think they were on zero before so where
are uh yeah i was looking for you buddy
i was looking for you i came with my
wolf pack and my sorcerer and i'm gonna
obliterate everything that's here oh you
little [\h__\h] you killed me a bunch of
times
you think that was the right choice to
do the right team to join
oh who's the [\h__\h] with the horn
i'm invincible right now i'm [\h__\h]
invincible
i'm confident and motivated
[\h__\h] no ain't happening
no no no no
ain't nobody gonna stop me who are you
guys fighting let me help let me help
let me help
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah we're talking
oh
anyone left no beautiful okay come with
me guys
i'm gonna kill some more people if i'm
if i teleport i assume they're gonna
leave me
right
we don't we don't wanna
have to leave us i want them with me for
as long as possible
oh i thought you were an enemy
never mind they reset i think my wolves
are leaving
what about my sorcerer how far is he
gonna follow me
ah my best friends
hey i can handle you without my horse
now i think maybe
maybe maybe
maybe maybe maybe
maybe maybe maybe i'll try it
i'm a sorcerer
that's all it takes
ow
don't die no don't die no
well my sorcerer is like overpowered
whoa
it's so strong
[Music]
[Laughter]
where those angels are oh
my brothers are angels swords
and i'm feeling good
[Music]
should we go to the cab guys with my
sorcerer
i'm scared to lose him if i save here
will he disappear
where is he
i see his
uh hp bar
i don't see him
but he must still be somewhere
i can't live without you
or maybe he's trying to show me that
i'm strong without him too
i forgot how to use this okay
what
wasn't it just triangle
no wait what
i'll do it
x
i forgot how to use this i can't use it
i have to dismiss him
oh bug
can't use my horse right now either
too far away
can't go with him do i have to save up
there
where i was before
fingers can dismiss you have to dismiss
him
he's gone like how
do i do that
finish him in the multiplayer menu uh
oops
i always do this wrong i always do this
wrong
multiple
you set up a group password you'll be
more likely to see messages some of the
signs blood stains phantoms and so on
for all of you the same password
if you set a multiplayer place you're
only revised with other players using
the same password for most multiple
features
i'm wondering okay i don't understand
but cool i'm totally i'm gonna let him
go
this one
finger severa sevira
a seventh player
is this it
ah
oh no what do i do about him
okay
should play this game go on his empire
sorry
i'll see you again at the boss fight
i'll see you there
okay now
i think we can level up
what do we need bigger
what do you think guys something bigger
one more bigger
bigger
goal
maybe this one bigger and the next one
dicks
okay and then what else was i supposed
to do
let's just wait until morning
next
yeah we're going to do another level up
how do you you guys said like upgrade
stuff but like how do i upgrade stuff
the cat comes
okay
uh
[\h__\h] catacombs really
[Music]
is it very big here
kind of comes so harder
i ghost friend i know that right there
something will spook me we've seen it
before
got a [\h__\h] heart attack
no heart attack now
it's coming it's coming this coming's
coming
what was it again
what the [\h__\h] is that
looks like a murloc
[Music]
okay
what is that what is that bloody thing
what is killing me
[Music]
was it really a good idea coming here
some kind of weird [\h__\h] goblin goblin
gremlin
goblin
gob cumberland grappling yeah yeah
that's it
okay
[Music]
what was that
no don't have to go so far to get my
body
what
i guess i'll change to
[Music]
[\h__\h] okay chill chill chill
you little [\h__\h]
insane
the little tipsy noises of your feet you
think you're cute
okay
oh my god
that was actually
a little bit challenging
root resin
what's happening with my blood what's
happening with my lug is it supposed to
go down or up
okay i think i'm good
damn
the sound sound the sound sounds weird i
mean sounds crispy sometimes the
capture card does some weird things
i'm gonna
i'm gonna kill that boss
today no matter what nothing here
grave
flower thingy
summoning pool is now functional almost
like again i forgot
which way do we go
are those alive is that alive
don't i have like some kind of shooting
item
i have some dagger thingies i for co-op
ah
is that thing alive
oh my heavens another statue
like it could come to life yeah okay uh
are you gonna shoot at me from up there
it's not very nice should i go for the
door
maybe the door is better
oh okay i guess that's where you come
back
run below
okay
sometimes
sometimes that is the only option
oh they come down
hmm
okay okay okay okay
yeah this might be a good place to level
here
so far so good some nice flowers here
cute pretty
did i pick up the other ones
yeah okay
next
oh
so narrow
what is that
what the [\h__\h]
oh my god oh my god sorry i i didn't
i couldn't i couldn't oh
it's like oh horror game
are there enemies back
oh they are i want my
i'm just gonna
ignore them
maybe oh man xp nah
get my body get my body get my body get
my body
this place was safe
and then
kind of just
run through
don't die now before getting your body
don't you dare qualify
you have a goal
come down now
where are you where is you
oh there come on you're gonna come down
here right like you did before
no
i don't have that much patience
okay
okay don't don't be surprised
there's something coming here
okay where is it where is it where is it
where is it where is it where did it
come from
why why why why do they come like out of
[\h__\h] nowhere
[\h__\h]
will you [\h__\h]
stop very aggressive
oh my god
what do we do here gonna be fast run to
the right side i suppose
what
what what what
wait
no wait should wait wait
did
i can turn them off
where
jesus
okay [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
if i hit the pillars they will stop
another body are gonna pick up
another body
another day
that was man burned alive
burnt a life man
focus
[\h__\h] goblins
stop you [\h__\h] creepy
she was so creepy
[Music]
no no
okay this is not a good place to be i
don't want to be here anymore
cause like
they are really dangerous i gotta go so
far to uh to get my [\h__\h] when i die
yeah i think the i'm better off with the
soldiers
uh unfortunately
uh
yeah with the sorcerer's help yeah that
that was pretty
pretty good
how much does this give only 19.
yeah those lowlifes
there's good stuff i believe that i'm
i'm sure i'm gonna like come back here
eventually
um but
[Music]
at the moment it's kind of dangerous i
feel like i'll continue to lose uh only
xp that i'm making
i don't know if
it's really that efficient and worth it
you know
i think it was that way
some soldiers here
what are those dragon thingies over
there
okay
attack
sneaky attack
mission impossible
ah
you thought you'd never see me again huh
you were wrong
i'm your worst
nightmare
yeah sorry about that
just uh
kind of
need to survive myself you know
ah that was just the wind
he needs to be more careful if he wants
to be on patrol
gotta be more careful than that horse
boss i you think i can take that one on
now there was indeed a guy somewhere
[Music]
somewhere in this area
a big boy
yeah that's always the question who is
really
the bad side you know yeah
maybe maybe we're the bad ones
never killed that thing there
it's flying hello
the hell are you
can i sneak up on you or do you notice
oh
the [\h__\h] it was that was like
huh
they were like nesting there
in [\h__\h] state oh my god oh my god oh
my god oh my god
three at once but no problem no problem
where's the last one oh
there it is
and they don't give that much uh exp
either
but it's better than nothing golden rune
get older
where's that big dude
i don't know we should
go to that uh this was
was this it was that the the the
uh
the camp
what
oh go away
i wanna go
here
try that first camp yeah that that that
one that's the one you mean right
yeah this
this place
we have died many times here
and
wait we can't level up anyway right now
right
okay
how do we do this this time i think from
the left side wasn't bad
oh no this side seems
quite difficult
but with more
experience it's just a wind or just the
wind
you're coming towards me
oh oh [\h__\h] he is
as long as you have no horn
come on here can we stand to uh
uh
seduce them out of their camp
i'll gladly do that
let's see let's see how much i have
learned
not much
he's pretty tough though he's pretty
defensive
his armor is strong
ow
[Music]
what is the matter with him
let me kill you let me kill you
oh
sorry
[Music]
whoa
he wants to appeal to the audience
he was trying to do some
some cool poses for you i hope you took
a photo of him
he wanted to be on youtube he wanted to
be on the telly oh we're here now
don't like that should i just raid it
with my horse
you could
try that maybe after taking one or two
people down i'm gonna do some groundwork
my body my body
eh use golden rune
items to get runes for level up
uh what do i
sell them or
just activate them
how how usable usable
uh sorry i always wish why did i always
use
um
inventory
uh
what was that again
cracked pond no
uh
where is that
[Music]
ah this one
you use how much
where's my current amount of runes
ah 288
oh
oh nice
i want to stab him
in his
stupid back
this is good really see me you can't see
me yet
but this dude will see me
i have two more oh
okay
oh that's where it turns around
some wolves
my friends oh
do you see my wolves
you saw my wolves
oh they're so pretty
oh that's fun
let's see when the horns
uh the alarm will be ringing
bring the alarm bring your alarm oh
don't die don't die
no what
get me strong
my walls
oh i kill you back
nice
quiet materials
now who wants to fight isn't that the
horn guy he didn't notice any of this
is that the guy
got him
that's him
let's follow him
yummy yummy
you're next you're next
you're next door
kill him eat him a lot
it's dinner time baby
that's what i'm talking about
clearing this [\h__\h] camp once and for
all
although then we'll probably save and
then restart
now these two but they have a wolf
they have uh oh my sleeping wolf too oh
ah
[Music]
treasure in the carriage
what the [\h__\h] are you doing
be quiet no
no they killed another
oh
oh he's looking at me
wait wolves you forgot your mommy
which carriage are we even talking about
uh
oh i killed it oh they don't have much
hp at all i thought they were like super
strong what cameras are you talking
about i wanna see a carriage oh that one
that one
okay okay
wait a second
[Music]
took me a while oh there is one guarding
them
oh is it because i didn't
uh focus on him ah i think i
understand now
oh
i didn't lock on nada hold up
oh hi
hi
at least you don't have that big [\h__\h]
shield
ah finally
finally justice is being served yes
how do i get that uh treasure
oh
what is it what is it what is it
a
flail oh
is that a good weapon for me
[Music]
you could say his flame went out mm-hmm
um
i want more one more to clear
[Music]
give it a try
and i have to uh
got the equipment and
oh
and i want to use it effectively i
wonder how
how
um serious that is that statement
so small
check weapon stats
uh
dicks i'm missing some decks
uh two two to be exact
i don't know is it smart to not use it
then at the moment
well i wanna
clear this
now let's see let's kill
one from behind but um wait there's only
a dog left and him
will the dog notice me
[Music]
okay i did it i kind of failed oh he's
got like a sledgehammer or some [\h__\h]
oh no wait there's one here in the front
mystic it tells me when i clear the
whole camp right because when i killed
that one group
i feel like it told me
that i killed the whole group
uh
where is that other thing you talked
about the other carriage
carriage ah that one up there
healing items left
but there's only isn't it only him left
i kill him from behind and everything's
cool
level up to use the flip
yeah
yeah yeah
i hear you
cool
backstab
okay i'm gonna go
i have to do the leveling always always
on that
safe point right
uh where did it go oh there it is
have you killed a dragon yet what dragon
is that like a spoiler
i have yet to kill a single boss so no
it i know wait wait wait wait
huh
don't rest yeah
how do i level without resting
i don't wanna i don't wanna i don't
wanna
i don't wanna
what
what they already respawned
i want to heal but like
well i don't understand
i'm clear to cam for nothing well i need
more exp anyway
but i didn't rest i didn't really rest
you sat down for a moment okay that's
enough
man okay we'll level up
so now we want some decks
uh
i still have quite a lot left over oh
wait i can do two because i have
apparently i still have um
the these ones the golden runes
yeah
and another one
number one
how many levels do you guys think i need
extra until i can manage that boss you
think free levels make such a big
difference
that's never another dex i guess
no
yes yes
at least all 25 no
no no no no no
it boils down to skill yeah
i just wonder if this makes such a big
difference
i'll wait
uh what about my
[Music]
what about
my flasks can i do something there
no
i was 15.
you were level 15 okay
yeah we'll try to play oh i guess
uh
maybe maybe with that dude but does the
treasure reset as well i i'm guessing no
just the enemies
can i do that backstab with the blaze
no
feels kind of weak but okay
treasure
no it's already opened
[Music]
my death counter is immeasurable
trust me you don't even want to know
smash his head
instead of
mashed potatoes we're getting smashed
brain rots
who's up for that who's hungry
oh my god it's already 11 p.m what the
[\h__\h]
by the way uh minecraft tomorrow is not
happening because i said i was gonna
replace uh you know uh
um
minecraft with this
today because otherwise i wasn't
supposed to stream besides the
rebroadcast today but maybe just maybe
just a small maybe i might do like a
little gorilla short stream maybe
but i can't say for sure yet
okay
how do you like the game so far oh i
like it a lot i'm just like wondering if
it's not too frustrating for you guys to
watch and if
um
i don't know it's a serious maybe with
like playing
a little bit privately
uh maybe it could work well like that i
don't know how much
[Music]
yeah maybe playing
off stream a little bit would be uh
to my advantage especially as a beginner
but i generally i like to
think that seeing
a beginner in any genre like fps or
whatever seeing them improve on stream
from zero to whatever 100
seeing an improvement is
isn't that kind of
beautiful and and
inspiring
but maybe a little bit of
private
game time can't hurt
yeah your friend is dead what do you say
what do you say
thank you thank you is what you're
supposed to say oh wait i forgot about
my dogs
help me
that was a good time to help me
damn this dude is so strong i can
compliment comprehended
wait i can do sword and flail
interesting
i was like who the [\h__\h] are you hi
how are you doing
i'm gonna backstab that sucker one more
time
did you hear that guys
he stood up for me in order to backstab
him so nice of him now wolves don't ruin
this for me
that's such an easy kill i already got
the carriages there were two no
thanks for waiting so polite of you guys
so polite
ah the tip about something being under
this room yeah yeah what how how how how
do i only get that if i clear everything
[Music]
there's a treasure on the ground what
how do i
do i go and i wear that i remember a
little
there was a
some stairs to go down over there
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah okay
good
[Music]
way smarter than that i think i think i
think they were would notice
when i'm walking
exactly next to them
isn't that why you have guard dogs at
home
to protect you
wouldn't they immediately bark like i
wha
[\h__\h] man
i from my own experience i may not be a
dog owner but
for example when i walk out of my
apartment um
there's like
dog owners living on the same floor
and the moment i step out of my
apartment
even though they're inside
and actually pretty far away from my
door
i immediately hear loud barking just
because i left my
uh
my apartment they hear that they
immediately hear it and they go like
that it's [\h__\h] crazy
[\h__\h] crazy
there's a treasure here right here
is there enemies too we're just uh
gonna be scared
oh just a treasure
yeah that's how i like it
what is it
i shall wore a storm stump
and a wet stone knife
what is that like a like a
super special move
new skill
skills why do i
[Music]
why do i use where do i apply skills
skill i'm the weapon
i do i do that at the camp uh-huh
not a whole goal
i wonder if that could help us
in our boss fight it's almost five hours
so we should
uh
i can do one more level up we should go
back
to the boss and give it a few more tries
oh there's the
horse dude
i'm gonna try to kill him quickly
because
um
oh they left i don't want to go
too much over time
should i even use the flail with the
boss
i know
where's dude too strong oh okay
and what do we go for now
wait i don't have enough
huh
oh i do i do i do
endurance sticks
stamina
bigger bigger yeah
helps me survive a bit longer
bigger for now
yes
so that was four levels
four levels
if that is not
enough
then it's just a bad skill
bigger bigger bigger
and yeah we're gonna go now we're gonna
do it
we're gonna do it
ash of war what check out ash's software
what was that
is this the
huh with the ashes of war menu you can
use ashes of war to grant skills and
effort
i don't want to scale any skill
processing will be lost by adding an
affinity you can is that like a
throwaway item the the
the skill like if it gets lost will it
go back into my inventory and i can use
it on another one or
is it like one time only
not reusable okay
so
uh
wait so this is what it is currently
and that's on both of them
on all of them is that the main basic
one
okay
what
it's reusable oh
okay okay
then i'll go what standard quality
quality
i don't understand that more strength
for this one
less decks should i go standing okay
oh i can put them on all of them if i
want to hmm
[Music]
hmm
is that it
what is that
that's the that's such a boring skill
man this is the new skill right damn
it's pretty good shouldn't i put it on
both of them
now two-handed how do you do that again
how do you do that again two-hand press
l2
what no i always had that
i don't know what's happening whole
triangle push r1
oh
it's two-handed now
but is this not the skill
you guys say i always had that
why why do i wanna
i don't know which sword i put it
wait how do i do that again i forgot how
i did it
[Music]
oh
that's how i did it
[Music]
oh that's it oh it only works when it's
two-handed
whoa
but i'm so used to
fighting with the two swords
that i don't know if i trust me fighting
the boss
with a one-handed sword now
so i will
pass some time
i do use the other sword i do
i'm gonna go to the tunnel give it a few
more tries
uh let's say half an hour i'll give it
half an hour
so
let's give it half an hour oh wait a
second wait a second let me just just
see if
every little
okay i think it's fine
although maybe maybe before that i'll go
take an idle meeting for one minute
just to increase chances
brb
so
[Music]
okay
i am back
i feel like we might need around
to um
get back into the groove
we'll see i mean i've had times like
this before where in games i take a
break from something and then suddenly
so easily
i manage it first try or second try
use the flail how about i use
both the sword and the flame
um
what's that is that your special move
no that's mine
we'll use it both
maybe
maybe maybe
is it a good idea i don't know
we'll try it out
sick flail drink it's a cute little
trick
wait that uses mana manga doesn't
recover
does it
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] wait wait don't waste it
it doesn't recover does it
i don't want to do that
although it's still enough for me to
[\h__\h] no i can't it's still enough for me
to summon my jelly whatever
whatever
okay
traversing getting back into the game
hello you thought i would never
come here again huh well you're wrong
i'm here
i'm a fan of you you know
i can't help it
oh i keep on coming back
i don't remember how to fight
we'll see how it goes
so much time loading up that
let me go let me i need to drink some
[\h__\h]
okay we're stuck
what is that spell that you do
okay for
warming up again it's not so bad
i think
oh he's got his hammer out oh
he's got his hammer ready and my
sorcerer's still alive
oh
it's going so well
but now sorcerer is dead so don't get
your hopes up guys
this is not even a good run
already made mistakes
like this one
no no no no no oh okay
hmm
no
no you're not allowed to do that you're
not allowed to do that
i command you to be a good boy
no
warming up warming up
[Music]
just just just
give it a few tries
it was a good try
but it was just warming up
i feel like
the level ups helped a little bit
they gave me a bit more room to play
around with maybe 100 hp more or
something like that
because
come on shoot your shooting thing no no
you want to do the other thing this time
the side
you make the first move
okay if that's your move
keep with me
whoa whoa whoa
he has a problem with trees i think
i don't know what it is
maybe a tree has hurt him before
maybe he wanted to date one of those
trees that have
yo
but sorcerer has been sliced into sushi
[Music]
oh and he even just does some more
damage to him just just to stick it to
him
just to stick it to him
what do we do what do we do
scares me
wait my sorcerer died way too early
way too earlier
last time he had his hammer and then he
died
oh then suddenly changes his mind
interesting
now he has his hammer
[Music]
am i a little bit unlucky here with my
companions
in this round
jelly about to die already
okay i'm all alone
oh
oh wait my body i forgot my body and
totally forgot my body but it's just
like a little bit
just like 150 or something like that
oh
190.
what are we gonna do about you huh
i wanted to go behind
he's healing
what
he was healing what do you mean
yeah it was poison
said he was healing or i i would
rage quit the game if he suddenly
started healing himself back up in some
phase
yeah
okay okay okay okay last round was kind
of unlucky
[Music]
suddenly
yo
um
up
not this time
no
not this time either
i
oh man oh man i feel like it's going
well
but
there's still a pain in the ass
oh
no please soldier stay alive a little
longer will you yes okay at least at
least you stayed
there he goes there he goes
what
oh jelly don't die
don't leave me alone in this hellhole
don't leave me alone in this hell hole
breathe
so wasted again
just stop stop
focus
focus stall
stall
oh
i'm too scared to attack
i can't i can't
oh [\h__\h] no no
no
sorry
i'm sorry
got close got close got close got close
i got close
and the next one that's the one
no i cannot summon the jelly twice we've
tried
i've tried before
man
that was some good moves that i had
there in the middle
i think
these these ones i got myself get hit by
that too often
it was so unnecessary
okay let's help our friend out shall we
damn i'm so slow like i see it and i i
pushed
the dodge quite early
but it's just
oh well not early enough
oh
i didn't see that coming
don't use heavy attacks for flail
eh
e
two hands to flail
you wanna see me do that one sir
uh
two hands the flail
two had to flail
you sure about two handing the flail
should i
to have a sword
bleed oh i got bleed from like he gets a
bleed thingy from that
okay interesting
okay
wait is he with me
yeah
oh
okay
am i allowed to do heavy attacks then
is it like
like the ones in a dungeon where uh
i have to apply it like
several times and only then it will
eventually get blood
oh [\h__\h] hell yeah okay
oh wow sorry this is a bad run this is a
bad run
will i see it
when he got it
like i see when he's poisoned
why is dodge sorcerer
friend
let's not give up let's not give up so
sora
he has given up
i suppose he would
just oh bleed out
any harder william
i think it's bleeding
i'm bleeding too
that was close
i don't know
hey he's bleeding huh i don't know i
don't know what it looks like
oh
yeah it's not good not good
we'll see it [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
oh that that move never know where to go
it's a single huge hit oh okay
they will take a huge ah ah okay yeah
yeah that's how i like suddenly
died in those catacombs um
it's not a small dot damage it's just
like one big one i see it
they got that so quickly though the ones
in the catacombs
how did they do that
hikaru
[Music]
heard you lack some jelly i mean
personally that's really not really not
my taste
well you do you
pretty pretty dodge you've broken down
the clutch please
do me the favor
oh let me go there
this run is good this one is good
this one is pretty good
[Music]
hmm the tail flip
out
ow
ow [\h__\h] out
[Music]
how's my jelly already
how is my jelly already gone
[Music]
oh
oh i want to try that l2 thing that you
guys told me
am i battle with two swords
they took too much aggro
you
wear off all
ah
players are gonna let you focus more
mm-hmm
so which might make him really happy
originally
always when he summons point but what
you could just play just need to hit it
more
i wish there was like a
bar that i can see
to measure how close i am
nice
welcome to the party everybody
i
am your host today and what you see here
is a big fail compilation
wow yours truly
ow
of course
we have this really aggressive big
friend here with a scorpion tail oh [\h__\h]
i feel blessed well this is a fail run
he doesn't quite know what he wants to
be he says he's a god but i don't trust
his face him like
i don't know
got some parasites eating him up
what you already got what
oh wow we did that fast
oh my sorceress
mind you
you're allowed to stay a little bit
longer unless i die [\h__\h] sorry sorry
sorry
i got out of the ribbon there
eat them up eat them open them up
yeah
why didn't we how what hmm
how did we
even get to that point
just now with everyone still alive
oh
eating my feet i'm are my feet
i'll give you a few more tries buddy
[Music]
how did you not see that coming huh
sorcerer
hmm
what do you mean why i roll away right
after summoning because
it takes time to summon and at that time
he usually always likes to charge up an
attack against me
sometimes it still hits me while i'm
summoning
don't let don't do three to four hit
combos too long what do you mean do just
one hit instead
or two
wait i pushed the wrong button i swear
to god
i thought it was triangle for a moment
also i just like rolling okay in other
games they really want you to roll a lot
i can't help it
yeah i saw that coming
this is not it this is definitely not it
it kind of needs to start off on the
right foot
does that even do damage that stupid
little trick that he does
because it doesn't
look like it
what what
and he got his hammer and he's attacking
me with it of course
of course
endless ground pounding he just can't
get enough of it
oh my
lord so this is not it either
come to me
yeah you [\h__\h]
oh
how's my jellyfish still alive i have no
healing items and i'm dead
[Music]
there's like every every run there's
something that's better than the other
everyone has like some lucky moments and
improvements but also then other moments
that are worse
but i don't know i want that i want that
bleeding that you guys promised me
so
in the end let's be honest i'm just
smashing buttons i know you don't want
me to smash buttons but i'm smashing
buttons and then it doesn't really even
matter what weapon i use
makes
barely a difference i think
what are you doing what are you doing
out
go back go back
and his magic is so pretty
looks like christmas
no no no no no no no
he's on a rampage
oh man
this might be it though this might be
the one
where you going
making me nervous making me [\h__\h]
nervous
why are you changing your mind so
suddenly
it takes me years to get over there and
it's [\h__\h] dangerous
until the point
why would i try without the sorcerer how
would that be
any better
he's so strong i need him
don't use the summon
why why not why not
it doubles his hp
you guys said it would be easier
i don't know we're like uh in sync team
at this point
like we've been for so much [\h__\h]
together we gotta do this together now
it has to in some way be easier no
otherwise it makes no sense
okay you know what i'll try it once
without him but then he'll just go for
me in the jellyfish and i'll have way
way way less opportunities to
attack him from behind
for me he's like
sorcery is a distraction for me
but if it doesn't really double the hp
hmm
if it's really double then maybe
wait sorry that was a reflex
that was a reflex
oh it's actually reflex
i've done this so many times now
oh
[Music]
no
staying out of that one
my [\h__\h] head
you died
how many deaths i thought we don't think
we stopped counting
i think we stopped counting at this
point so don't don't summon don't summon
us
are you sure guys that this is the right
idea
will attack me don't attack me
let's see
both got the timing for both of those
wrong
oh
he's wild
he's on his tippy toes
always waiting for me
oh man oh man oh man
but
maybe try that but not with the
jesus the backseating is insane normally
i welcome back seating but with this
game with this game even i
get annoyed by it you know what i'll try
it with two swords
this time
like absolutely actually obnoxious level
today
i i usually i'm like yo please help me
but hearing the same thing about a
million times
not necessarily helpful
are you so
stop running i'll roll even more
y'all
could you have been just one meter
closer
hey
the
i feel like train getting less uh
careful you killed my jellyfish
we're not getting anywhere now
i know that's
this is pointless
a little bit too early there
i'm gonna give it a three more tries
three more
free only free only free
only free
but
with with a way about my boy
we can drive
without him
it doesn't really
make much difference
i need to hunt
some
no
[Music]
should have summoned right in the
beginning
it like
leaves me more
opportunity
there
[Music]
i feel like
when callie was watching
if we would have tried a few more times
we might have gotten it
i feel like i was so
immersed in it so
i mean i might have been exhausted but
i was like so practiced you know
so warmed up
no caliber yeah without kelly of being
here
i'm a i'm a worthless little
aunt
and he's just stomping on me he doesn't
care about ants he doesn't give a [\h__\h]
nobody gives a [\h__\h] about ants that's
the sad thing
[Music]
hiding behind my jellyfish
but one day there was enough
oh
wait kill yourself that was a good start
i don't want to ruin this run
oh wait sorry my honestly at this point
i think my focus is gone um like my
concentration
too reckless i feel like my skill level
is there but my focus is gone
nice
it's gone it's gone
the magical
magic that i had
that feeling of being invincible
but this is pretty good so far he's been
focusing on me
and now he's poisoned
and i've been handling
him focusing on me quite well i would
say
oh pretty pretty
good this one always takes so much time
to
charge last healing item
jellyfish by a miracle still alive
bye bye
i don't think i jinxed that that was
about that was bound to happen
finally i dodged that [\h__\h]
no no no no no no i'm ruining it i
ruined it i ruined i [\h__\h] ruined it
i can't stall for that long with so
little hp
this is a good good distance
take your time
a good run
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay if this one is super [\h__\h] and ends
too fast then i'll give it another one
but let's if it's a good one then this
is the last one or so i don't know
oh yeah
i don't like that start
i did not like it
i hate that move
it takes so long to charge for him
[Music]
that was a cursed
uh run it was always bound to
immediately end
badly
that was cursed from the beginning
i told you if it's a [\h__\h] run that ends
too fast then we're doing it again
you'll never
get rid of me marget
or margaret
never
oh
oh it's also bad
i was also bad
yo i'm just gonna
peace out bro
uh
concentrate
i want that one [\h__\h] success i don't
want to end this like this because then
it means i failed and
i'm not supposed to play these games
we don't want that to be the conclusion
of today
oh [\h__\h]
leave her alone
okay
yes you're far away from my baby
nope
who are you trying to attack huh
no no no
no
i'll sacrifice myself for
last
last one
i swear
i swear still it's the last one
it's the last one
all those experienced souls players are
even laughing at me or like screaming at
me
they're like how the [\h__\h] are you after
almost six hours
still here oopsie
[\h__\h]
are you like
she's so stupid kusa
yeah this is not good
uh
it just sometimes you just no this is
not it and that was not it so
last one for real
oreo
for real
it had a bad start you know
you saw it you saw it it was really bad
okay
are you going for him
finally i dodged that
[\h__\h]
we at least get to the hammer part again
please
i'm i'm not improving i'm deproving
i'm deep proving
you guys made me give up on my summoner
i don't know if that was for good or for
bad
[Music]
no i hate this
can i lower the difficulty somewhere
i feel like you guys would have already
offered that to me huh
oh hey quinoa
we're dancing in here
did you learn those dance moves
where did you learn to miss like that
man
[Music]
oh
okay
[Music]
this is depressing at this point um
yeah
i
don't know
i like the game it's just the combat is
a bit too difficult if it were like a
little little bit easier i would have i
think a much better
time oh i don't know i like i don't want
to give up on it i like exploring and i
like the graphics i like the the vibes
the atmosphere
the story so far even though i've barely
barely seen any of it story i like too
and uh i like rpgs it seems like a
little cool game
[Music]
um i
yeah maybe i'll play a bit off stream
and see if i can get better i get good
uh um
yeah
i'm gonna
i feel a bit broken i was loaded more
motivated before
game broke me
the game broke my
on the first [\h__\h] boss
no establish
but i like it this is the problem i'm
like i'm like torn i like the game
but it's a bit too difficult for me
but i don't wanna i don't wanna
i don't wanna give up you know
yeah maybe if i get a few levels behind
the scenes i guess i'm just really
pushing
something that's
too difficult for a beginner
thank you guys for the members messages
thank you
[Music]
uh uh my throat is a bit
in pain
[Music]
yeah um
takes a bit time to schedule
uh eleanor ring anyway so we'll see
maybe at the end of next week of the
coming week maybe
uh we'll see another one of those
in the
yeah
thank you guys for watching hope you
enjoyed it please continue playing ellen
ring yourself have fun with it you guys
are probably doing much better than i
did
um but it was nice diving into it um and
i want to see more of the world i want
to learn about the story you know
i don't want such things as combat to
hold me back from
enjoying a great game
yeah
thank you
tonight
[Music]
never give up yeah
yeah
um
gotta do something about that
obnoxious backstage though
maybe you ban the word
roll
or stop rolling
man
[Laughter]
i appreciate the sentiment but after a
million times man no
nah
no more
okay guys uh
i only need to think about what to eat
for dinner now
and i wish you all a lovely
day evening whatever
i'll maybe see you tomorrow but it will
be decided spontaneously
so in that case just look forward to my
tweets
or
my schedule going up
hope you enjoyed this guys
and in german we say
auf wiedersehen thank you
for
uh hanging out with me while i'm
experiencing
some
major
gaming
issues
thank you thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
i'll think about how to continue with
this
bye-bye thank you
great game though great game
bye-bye
[Music]
do
you