​​​ ​From the cat lovers,​ ​​
​​​ ​on account of cat lovers everywhere,​ ​​
​​​ ​and for all you cat lovers,​ ​​
​​​ ​we bring you​ ​​
​​​ ​today's program:​ ​​
​​​ ​hololive Staff​ ​​
​​ ​Harusaki Nodoka​ ​​
​​​ ​A Showdown Between Cat Lovers!​ ​​
​​​ ​The Queen of Cats!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay then!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hello, cat lovers of hololive!​ ​​
​​​ ​Meow! Meow!​ ​​
​​​ ​Everyone here today​ ​​
​​ ​happens to be living with cats!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's start off with introductions​ ​​
​​​ ​for everyone and their cats!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sure!​ ​​
​​​ ​hololive 1st Gen/GAMERS​ ​​
​​ ​Shirakami Fubuki​ ​​
​​​ ​A fox who found herself a cat one day,​ ​​
​​ ​I'm Shirakami Fubuki!​ ​​
​​​ ​The brown cat on the left is Leo-kun!​ ​​
​​​ ​Leo-kun​ ​​
​​ ​3 y/o​ ​​
​​​ ​Azu-kun​ ​​
​​ ​2 y/o​ ​​
​​​ ​And the greyish cat on the right is Azu-kun!​ ​​
​​​ ​They're so cute!​ ​​
​​​ ​Om, nom, Okayu!​ ​​
​​​ ​hololive GAMERS​ ​​
​​ ​Nekomata Okayu​ ​​
​​​ ​Official shows are​ ​​
​​ ​always done in the mornings,​ ​​
​​​ ​so my voice is kinda hoarse,​ ​​
​​ ​but I'm glad to be here!​ ​​
​​​ ​The one on the right is the older sister, Temari,​ ​​
​​ ​and the little brother on the left is Kojirou.​ ​​
​​​ ​Temari-chan​ ​​
​​ ​3 y/o​ ​​
​​​ ​Kojirou-kun​ ​​
​​ ​0 y/o​ ​​
​​​ ​They're cute!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm Iofi and I'm always thinking about cats, so​ ​​
​​ ​I'm excited for today! And I'm from hololive ID.​ ​​
​​​ ​hololive Indonesia​ ​​
​​ ​Airani Iofifteen​ ​​
​​​ ​Here's my cat!​ ​​
​​​ ​Cimoy-chan​ ​​
​​​ ​My absolutely adorable,​ ​​
​​ ​super cute daughter!​ ​​
​​​ ​She's so small!​ ​​
​​​ ​She used to be a stray.​ ​​
​​​ ​A stray?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah! I just happened to find her in our garage​ ​​
​​ ​one day and I figured I'd just take her in.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah!​ ​​
​​​ ​There's a cat!​ ​​
​​​ ​Guess I'll take her in.​ ​​
​​​ ​Attention please!​ ​​
​​ ​I'm the hero of hololive ID!​ ​​
​​​ ​hololive Indonesia​ ​​
​​ ​Pavolia Reine​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll be in cat mode today,​ ​​
​​ ​so let's have a catful time!​ ​​
​​​ ​This cat's name is Cimol!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's the name of an Indonesian snack!​ ​​
​​​ ​Cimol-chan​ ​​
​​ ​1-2 y/o​ ​​
​​​ ​A snack?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, it's a doughy snack.​ ​​
​​​ ​Cimol is very lively.​ ​​
​​​ ​Also, she's a girl.​ ​​
​​​ ​A girl!​ ​​
​​​ ​From hololive English -Myth-,​ ​​
​​ ​I'm Takanashi Kiara! I'm actually a phoenix,​ ​​
​​​ ​hololive English -Myth-​ ​​
​​ ​Takanashi Kiara​ ​​
​​​ ​but perhaps I look like a cat today?​ ​​
​​​ ​So, about my cats...​ ​​
​​​ ​Smoothie​ ​​
​​ ​?? y/o​ ​​
​​​ ​Chonkers​ ​​
​​​ ​They actually do have these colors.​ ​​
​​​ ​One of them has this​ ​​
​​ ​slightly greenish color.​ ​​
​​​ ​She's really naughty​ ​​
​​​ ​Smoothie​ ​​
​​ ​?? y/o​ ​​
​​​ ​and lately has been giving me a lot of grief.​ ​​
​​​ ​Chonkers​ ​​
​​ ​?? y/o​ ​​
​​​ ​The other one who's orange​ ​​
​​ ​is called Chonkers.​ ​​
​​​ ​She's really nice and shy,​ ​​
​​ ​and she always comes to my side​ ​​
​​​ ​even when I'm sick. She's a darling.​ ​​
​​​ ​What's in store for you girls today​ ​​
​​​ ​is a quiz about cats!​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoever answers correctly gets a chance​ ​​
​​​ ​to tell us a tale of their beloved cat!​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanna show my cats off!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let me show off my cats!​ ​​
​​​ ​The person who gives us the​ ​​
​​ ​most stories about their beloved cats​ ​​
​​​ ​will be awarded with the​ ​​
​​ ​Queen of Cats title in hololive!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's the programme for today.​ ​​
​​​ ​Meow! (Leave it to me!)​ ​​
​​​ ​Meow! (OK!)​ ​​
​​​ ​Meow meow! (I'm in it to win it!)​ ​​
​​​ ​Meow! (I have so much to say!)​ ​​
​​​ ​Meow! (Ready to show off!)​ ​​
​​​ ​I love cats!​ ​​
​​​ ​Question #1​ ​​
​​​ ​Here's the first Cat Quiz question!​ ​​
​​​ ​When a cat blinks slowly,​ ​​
​​ ​what does it indicate?​ ​​
​​​ ​1) Trust​ ​​
​​ ​2) Intruder​ ​​
​​​ ​3) Indifference​ ​​
​​ ​4) Annoyance​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh? You all know this, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​So for this question, we'll use​ ​​
​​​ ​the hand-raising format.​ ​​
​​ ​Who knows the answer?​ ​​
​​​ ​What's your answer, Fubuki-chan?​ ​​
​​​ ​I pick #1!​ ​​
​​​ ​1) Indicating trust!​ ​​
​​​ ​Surely.​ ​​
​​​ ​Fubuki-chan is correct, it's #1!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Cat-and-Tell​ ​​
​​ ​acquired!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, is this common knowledge?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, it's common!​ ​​
​​​ ​It is!​ ​​
​​​ ​Everyone knows this.​ ​​
​​​ ​O-Oh...​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's hear a story from​ ​​
​​ ​our fastest answerer, Fubuki-san​ ​​
​​​ ​Shirakami Fubuki's Cat-and-Tell!​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, the cats who live under my roof​ ​​
​​​ ​are both Somali cat breeds.​ ​​
​​​ ​They were really vicious with​ ​​
​​ ​each other when they first met.​ ​​
​​​ ​Leo-kun took the initiative​ ​​
​​ ​and got close to Azu-kun​ ​​
​​​ ​and started licking her fur!​ ​​
​​​ ​And then! Azu-kun returned the favor​ ​​
​​ ​and started licking him back, too!​ ​​
​​​ ​I got to witness a miracle!​ ​​
​​​ ​Once foes, now friends​ ​​
​​​ ​How nice!​ ​​
​​​ ​And now they live endearingly together.​ ​​
​​​ ​So, I also have two cats.​ ​​
​​ ​For a cat owner,​ ​​
​​​ ​the moment that they both start​ ​​
​​ ​getting close to each other​ ​​
​​​ ​is one that's hard to beat.​ ​​
​​ ​I certainly know how you feel.​ ​​
​​​ ​Nothing beats it!​ ​​
​​​ ​I love cats!​ ​​
​​​ ​Question #2​ ​​
​​​ ​Here's the second question!​ ​​
​​​ ​Similar to fingerprints in humans, cats have an area that differs between every cat. Where?​ ​​
​​​ ​1. Nose​ ​​
​​​ ​2. Eyes​ ​​
​​​ ​3. Claws​ ​​
​​​ ​4. Paws​ ​​
​​​ ​For this question, you'll all answer​ ​​
​​ ​with your whiteboards.​ ​​
​​​ ​Please write down your answers!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's take a look at everyone's answers!​ ​​
​​​ ​Fubuki-san picked paws. Okayu-san also picked paws. Iofi-san, too, picked paws!​ ​​
​​​ ​There's so much to unpack!​ ​​
​​​ ​Rowdy Whiteboards​ ​​
​​​ ​My screen is all over the place.​ ​​
​​ ​Reine-san picked the nose!​ ​​
​​​ ​And Kiara-san also picked the nose.​ ​​
​​ ​It looks like we have a two group split!​ ​​
​​​ ​A cat sweats through their paws,​ ​​
​​​ ​and I was thinking that maybe​ ​​
​​ ​the amount they sweat differs,​ ​​
​​​ ​or that the shape of their paws​ ​​
​​ ​often differs, so I picked paws.​ ​​
​​​ ​Their nose's, uh... texture?​ ​​
​​​ ​They have those bumps, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​I thought that maybe​ ​​
​​ ​they differed like fingerprints.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Whichever side could be correct, I wonder?​ ​​
​​​ ​And the correct answer is...​ ​​
​​​ ​Please! Pretty pawlease!​ ​​
​​​ ​Pretty pawlease!​ ​​
​​​ ​This one!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes!​ ​​
​​​ ​The nose!​ ​​
​​​ ​It was #1, huh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Only primates, like humans​ ​​
​​ ​and monkeys, have fingerprints.​ ​​
​​​ ​As for the equivalent in cats—​ ​​
​​ ​like we just heard, the bumps on the nose​ ​​
​​​ ​differ in count between each cat, it seems!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Since Reine-san and Kiara-san were correct,​ ​​
​​​ ​Reine / Kiara: Correct​ ​​
​​​ ​let's have the both of them​ ​​
​​ ​tell us a story about their cats!​ ​​
​​​ ​Cat-and-Tell​ ​​
​​ ​acquired!​ ​​
​​​ ​So! I have a story about Cimol!​ ​​
​​​ ​Reine's Cat-and-Tell​ ​​
​​​ ​She always picks up my drawing​ ​​
​​ ​tablet's pen with her mouth. Like a dog.​ ​​
​​​ ​Walking while gnawing​ ​​
​​ ​on a pen like a dog​ ​​
​​​ ​That's so cute!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, a video!​ ​​
​​​ ​She really likes rolling around.​ ​​
​​​ ​Cute!​ ​​
​​​ ​And I'm always left wondering​ ​​
​​ ​where my pen's gone.​ ​​
​​​ ​So she steals your pen!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​Cuuute!​ ​​
​​​ ​She steals it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Does your cat like rolling around?​ ​​
​​​ ​Absolutely loves rolling around​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah! She really loves to!​ ​​
​​​ ​I have no idea what she's trying to do,​ ​​
​​​ ​but she'll just start rolling and rolling...​ ​​
​​​ ​I bet it feels super nice.​ ​​
​​​ ​Next up, Kiara-san!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara's Cat-and-Tell​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay!​ ​​
​​​ ​So whenever I bring this up,​ ​​
​​​ ​everyone else starts freaking out​ ​​
​​​ ​and saying stuff like,​ ​​
​​ ​"That's scary" or "That's creepy."​ ​​
​​​ ​So, up until recently,​ ​​
​​​ ​I was living in Japan a bit, right?​ ​​
​​ ​For about a year.​ ​​
​​​ ​Having to leave my cats back home​ ​​
​​ ​got me feeling down in the dumps,​ ​​
​​​ ​so I, um, decided to​ ​​
​​​ ​cut off quite a bit of fur off my cats...​ ​​
​​​ ​What?!​ ​​
​​​ ​And then,​ ​​
​​​ ​using some tape, I attached the fur​ ​​
​​​ ​to the backs of some​ ​​
​​ ​cute photographs of my cats.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hesitant to leave her cats behind, decided to bring​ ​​
​​ ​some photos of her cats with her cats' fur attached​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh I see! So they'd always "be" with you!​ ​​
​​​ ​But that's kinda cute!​ ​​
​​​ ​Whenever I felt down while in Japan,​ ​​
​​ ​I'd take out those photos​ ​​
​​​ ​to look at them and​ ​​
​​ ​"pet" the fur with my fingers,​ ​​
​​​ ​and I'd feel a little happy​ ​​
​​ ​from that. That's how much​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't live without being with my cats!​ ​​
​​​ ​So uh, thoughts?​ ​​
​​​ ​Everyone else I've told this to​ ​​
​​ ​says it's creepy...​ ​​
​​​ ​But I know how you feel!​ ​​
​​​ ​CAT​ ​​
​​​ ​Speaking as a cat,​ ​​
​​ ​I feel the adrenaline rush coming up.​ ​​
​​​ ​Really?​ ​​
​​​ ​I love cats!​ ​​
​​​ ​Question #3​ ​​
​​​ ​Here's the third question!​ ​​
​​​ ​1. Saltiness​ ​​
​​​ ​2. Sourness​ ​​
​​​ ​3. Sweetness​ ​​
​​​ ​4. Spiciness​ ​​
​​​ ​Which of the following​ ​​
​​ ​do cats lack taste buds for?​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh!​ ​​
​​​ ​We'll use the hand-raising format for this one.​ ​​
​​ ​Meow when you think you've got it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Meow!​ ​​
​​​ ​Nearly Simultaneous!​ ​​
​​​ ​I know this one!​ ​​
​​​ ​Iofi-san, you know this?!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's #3, sweetness.​ ​​
​​​ ​Sweetness!​ ​​
​​​ ​What about you, Iofi?​ ​​
​​​ ​Same answer.​ ​​
​​​ ​Iofi-san picks sweetness, too?​ ​​
​​​ ​Are Reine-san and Iofi-san correct?​ ​​
​​​ ​The correct answer is...​ ​​
​​​ ​Sweetness! Sweetness!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sweetness is correct!​ ​​
​​​ ​Reine and Iofi: Correct​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow! You two sure were quick!​ ​​
​​​ ​Now then! Let's get to hearing​ ​​
​​ ​about both of your cats!​ ​​
​​​ ​Cat-and-Tell​ ​​
​​ ​acquired!​ ​​
​​​ ​Iofi-san first!​ ​​
​​​ ​My umm, it—this—er...​ ​​
​​​ ​She's sleeping on my lap here.​ ​​
​​​ ​At first, since she's a stray and all,​ ​​
​​ ​I thought she'd be afraid of people.​ ​​
​​​ ​But nope. She sleeps​ ​​
​​ ​on my lap, even right now.​ ​​
​​​ ​My daughter is absolutely adorable.​ ​​
​​​ ​Your daughter!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's hear some more stories,​ ​​
​​ ​this time from Reine-san!​ ​​
​​​ ​Reine's Cat-and-Tell​ ​​
​​​ ​So I take care of two cats,​ ​​
​​​ ​and, let's see...​ ​​
​​​ ​The other cat is fine,​ ​​
​​​ ​it's just this one who's really noisy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Cimol's the noisy one​ ​​
​​​ ​Noisy!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah! She'll always start meowing​ ​​
​​ ​outside my room!​ ​​
​​​ ​The talkative type, huh!​ ​​
​​​ ​And when I let her in,​ ​​
​​​ ​she'll be here for one or two minutes​ ​​
​​​ ​and start meowing again to​ ​​
​​ ​let her outside. It's an unending loop.​ ​​
​​​ ​I really wish she'd decide​ ​​
​​ ​whether she wants to be inside or outside!​ ​​
​​​ ​Still loves​ ​​
​​ ​that always noisy side of her​ ​​
​​​ ​I'd love to come over​ ​​
​​ ​to your place, Reine-chan!​ ​​
​​​ ​That would be nice, but...!​ ​​
​​​ ​Question #4​ ​​
​​​ ​I love cats!​ ​​
​​​ ​And now for the next question!​ ​​
​​​ ​How many months after birth​ ​​
​​ ​do cats establish food preferences?​ ​​
​​​ ​1. 1 month​ ​​
​​​ ​2. 3 months​ ​​
​​​ ​3. 6 months​ ​​
​​​ ​4. 12 months​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, what? Uh-oh...​ ​​
​​​ ​Please write your answers​ ​​
​​ ​on your whiteboards.​ ​​
​​​ ​Sure!​ ​​
​​​ ​Which month, do you think?​ ​​
​​​ ​Nekomata Okayu​ ​​
​​ ​0 Questions Correct​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm still not on the board yet,​ ​​
​​​ ​so I really want to nail this one.​ ​​
​​​ ​I hope you do!​ ​​
​​​ ​Me too!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​All of the answers are in,​ ​​
​​ ​so please show us your boards!​ ​​
​​​ ​Reveal the Answers!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's a lot to take in...!​ ​​
​​​ ​Fubuki-san: 6 months.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okayu-san: 3 months.​ ​​
​​​ ​Iofi-san: 6 months.​ ​​
​​​ ​Reine-san: 3 months.​ ​​
​​​ ​And Kiara-san: 6 months.​ ​​
​​​ ​Everyone is split between two answers!​ ​​
​​​ ​Correct Answer​ ​​
​​​ ​And the correct answer is...!​ ​​
​​​ ​(3) 6 months!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes!​ ​​
​​​ ​You did it, Kiara!​ ​​
​​​ ​Cat-and-Tell​ ​​
​​ ​acquired!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hooray!​ ​​
​​​ ​Why don't we hear more​ ​​
​​ ​about Fubuki-san's cats?​ ​​
​​​ ​Shirakami Fubuki's Cat-and-Tell​ ​​
​​​ ​I mean, as much as I would like to,​ ​​
​​​ ​I also want to hear something from Okayun!​ ​​
​​​ ​Me, too!​ ​​
​​​ ​So, I pass my privilege to her!​ ​​
​​​ ​Meow!​ ​​
​​​ ​Time for​ ​​
​​ ​Nekomata Okayu's​ ​​
​​ ​Cat-and-Tell​ ​​
​​​ ​Here is a picture of my cats,​ ​​
​​ ​Temari and Kojirou.​ ​​
​​​ ​I bought one of those round​ ​​
​​ ​donut beds for them a while back,​ ​​
​​​ ​which they have come to adore.​ ​​
​​​ ​Heartfelt Present -​ ​​
​​ ​Round Donut Bed Adoration​ ​​
​​​ ​Unfortunately, I only bought one to try out.​ ​​
​​​ ​Two cats with one bed.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's rather big, and I assumed​ ​​
​​ ​they would take turns using it.​ ​​
​​​ ​They ended up squeezing in together​ ​​
​​​ ​and sleeping like a thick, hearty cat pot,​ ​​
​​​ ​nestled up tightly until morning.​ ​​
​​​ ​Packed nice and tight.​ ​​
​​​ ​How cute!​ ​​
​​​ ​What a cutie!​ ​​
​​​ ​So cute!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's your turn, Iofi-san.​ ​​
​​​ ​Iofi's Cat-and-Tell​ ​​
​​​ ​Mine has a cute voice.​ ​​
​​​ ​Cat Impersonation​ ​​
​​​ ​Like that.​ ​​
​​​ ​How cute!​ ​​
​​​ ​The end!​ ​​
​​​ ​Your turn, Kiara-san!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara's Cat-and-Tell​ ​​
​​​ ​Sometime last summer,​ ​​
​​​ ​I bought a robot litter box for my cats.​ ​​
​​​ ​Robot Litter Box for Cat Companions​ ​​
​​​ ​Robot litter box?​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, the kind that recycles it?​ ​​
​​​ ​And I w-was worried that​ ​​
​​ ​they wouldn't want to use it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Automated A.I. Cleaning Unit​ ​​
​​​ ​Right, it might freak them out.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, exactly.​ ​​
​​​ ​Some cats refuse to use them.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh my.​ ​​
​​​ ​But...!​ ​​
​​​ ​Mine took to it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Without a second thought!​ ​​
​​​ ​No, seriously!​ ​​
​​​ ​You'd swear they were geniuses!​ ​​
​​​ ​Consider me interested.​ ​​
​​​ ​We'll need to commission​ ​​
​​ ​a larger size for Okayu-senpai.​ ​​
​​​ ​...For me to use?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Although I wish we could continue​ ​​
​​ ​hearing your wonderful stories,​ ​​
​​​ ​our time...​ ​​
​​​ ​Cat Quiz: Complete!​ ​​
​​​ ​No!​ ​​
​​​ ​...is up.​ ​​
​​​ ​Keep going, keep going!​ ​​
​​​ ​And now...​ ​​
​​​ ​to crown the Queen of Cats!​ ​​
​​​ ​With the most correctly answered questions,​ ​​
​​​ ​your winners are...​ ​​
​​​ ​Queen of Cats - 1st Generation​ ​​
​​​ ​Fubuki-san, Iofi-san,​ ​​
​​ ​Reine-san, and Kiara-san!​ ​​
​​​ ​Subscribe to the hololive official​ ​​
​​ ​& our guests' channels!​ ​​
​​​ ​But she's the real cat here!​ ​​
​​ ​The only real cat!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm the only actual cat among us...​ ​​