[Music]
n
w
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
w
[Applause]
[Music]
n
hi you Darlings this is Hell live
English Advent devilish Diva the one and
only narissa Raven coft and today I have
the most amazing of coaches most amazing
of senpai the one and only beloved
Phoenix of Hol live English takanashi
K yay
Kiki I'm I'm I'm her teacher today M we
are sorry we tried the remote thing but
on my side it was like one frame per 5
minutes yeah not great but this is fine
you just you never finished a solo run
so I'm going to guide you through it and
be there for you like you were there for
me when I played Holo cure yeah
exactly it's going to be okay you were
good you were good at holoc cure you can
be good at this yeah right right totally
doable also um H I'm suffering from
blood loss blood loss that is because of
the pain in my head do you have I don't
know what helps with blood lust um can
you give me your blood maybe oh sure I I
like I like vampires you can go ahead
and suck some go
[Music]
on thank
you all right so kiata said I have to
play na
well I mean I don't want to force you
but it's it should I know you said you
didn't play well aser but it should
still be the best and easiest way of
getting through the game alone okay but
there's now a saving feature which might
make things
easier but yeah you should watch her
whip you should watch her na
ne
yes
or she has a lot of in her song well
she's n she better mhm all right I
finished with n before okay um but I I
only I it was like pretty much first try
like every boss wow
okay but I not I don't know if I'll
actually be good at like oh God okay
well I don't remember how to play
so do Dodge is this button attack is
this button and how to use my special
attacks is
why yeah okay you don't need that the
Power Attack we don't care about the
Power
Attack okay just uh keep an eye on your
health
yeah and uh I'll I'll just do my best
relaying uh tips from the chat to you
because I think I'm better at reading
the chat than you are
wow
unbelievable it's okay I I just have a
lot of
experience yeah I mean the beginning
you're probably going to be fine in the
beginning yeah I I can probably get
through this
level all right we'll have to find you
like some decent equipment and
stuff and act accordingly and upgrade
the equipment uh properly yeah whenever
it we can so pick up all the
money and no no money left
behind yeah good good good good
AO
M
other your other
oi yes Japanese oi JP oi it's okay I'm
not mad you can't be mad cuz you don't
love me as much as you love
pekora which makes sense cuz I'm not
your oi
but no I I don't know I I would say it's
a very very different kind of love um
because I mean I didn't know you before
you came into my world that's true I I
knew peka before I came into her world
I've known you for a long time well yeah
exactly so it's like a different kind of
POV dream POV and
um but but no no for real like I I love
you yeah no I love you too I have a way
deeper connection with you than with P
Empire that's for sure so yeah well for
something yeah I have a deeper
connection with you than I do moding H
for
now I don't speak Japanese
so it's okay like i' I've seen her make
some pretty deep connections with GAA
for example really I mean I mean they
don't really have deep conversations but
they like each other a lot
oh it's fine it's fine language is a
barrier but it must not be a
wall did that sound deep so deep
apparently YouTube is lagging really
bad I think it's YouTube I can see it
because mine still says I have a pretty
solid
connection yeah it's the original thing
my stream runs for you
properly uh okay so we have a
minion uh just don't don't kill the
minion seems for whatever reason it
can't handle me
playing oh and it'll it's it keeps
crashing the
OBS with me probably screen sharing
it oh oops oh cuz when I pause
it oh never your upload is so [\h__\h]
girl
no
is it lagging for me I don't really see
the here let me TR maybe it's maybe it's
like jumping around a little bit let me
let me see if I can change the
quality at all no but maybe it's just a
temporary thing maybe maybe let me just
just see real quick um on the actual the
cuz I am streaming it in two different
places oh true so let me just turn it
down here
Oh you mean in Discord yeah that's fine
lower it lower lower okay let's go back
it says my connection is good now so
okay
hopefully oh okay okay it wasn't lagging
then apparently okay yeah well when I
pause it it stops
lagging what was happening it's been a
while since uh I played so I don't
really remember anything but I think I
remember like what items I likeed well
as
what generally what um armor I like in
the end in the end you just got to get
good oh my
God Kata Senpai telling me to get
good I actually loved the the the balls
that you just picked up because you
could just Spam them there's certain
items that I would keep for the bosses
and certain it that I would like to spam
at the like small suckers yeah so yeah
maybe for example your like sound Fork
it's so strong yeah I loved spamming it
at the boss because once I spam it they
usually just stay in the same line so
you just throw them all out usually you
can get up to 20 I think yeah so if we
find those we want to bring them to the
boss I think they're pretty easy to
throw at the bosses usually
agreed you haven't equipped the
equipment yet oh you apparently you got
equipment but you didn't I'll put it on
in a minute I didn't need it yet we're
on the first level yeah we're fine we're
who needs equipment on the first
level not
us okay
yeah H promise Ministry Host Club wa ooh
we should go a host
club okay I guess once in a
lifetime
ah the kimono I think I was wearing the
kimono until
the was maybe was I
wearing
I yeah yeah for the first boss it would
be nice to have some equipment okay I
put it on I put it on yeah yeah yeah
we've got we are equipped with the
equipment
mhm how you guys doing in the chat so
early in the morning or L for you it's
it's not 8:00 p.m. perfect time it
should be a good time right now it's EU
prime time yeah I'm an EU streamer now
yay making the the stream in EU prime
time let's
go it's it's I um asked you to do the
stream with me yeah but now it's I'm not
even partaking and it's on your channel
I know I'm so sad ah there's a coach
there you got to pick it up I don't know
if that was useful but I think I can
just sell it for money that was just a
normal coat
yeah Casino have you ever been to a
casino yes not to gamble though to eat
at one of the
buffets oh I've been to a casino to
gamble before oh yeah for whatever
reason a lot of casinos have like really
fancy
restaurants
so I don't know why um you know that you
can heal your minions right yeah heal
that one please
[Music]
um oh get them all together and then
heal them yeah we don't want to let them
die die okay we need them
okay
uh one of them is still pretty low do
wait wait for another one yeah yeah yeah
okay wait pick up the rest of the money
yeah pick up the money real quick you
don't you never when you were there to
eat you didn't use it any of the
gambling appliances no um It's actually
kind of funny I technically wasn't
supposed to be allowed in because I was
under the age of um oh CME ding dong
ding police police no no they let me in
because I was just going to eat but
technically speaking they're like well
we're not supposed to let kids into the
casino uh I am yeah okay well I had a
case like that I think where I was was I
too young though but I was just there
for dinner and then every my all my
colleagues they went in for you know
having some fun but I left and I went
home the food I would have left too but
another time I did go properly and I
think back then I didn't know how to
play Blackjack yet so the only thing I
could really play Blackjack was uh no
now I would love to play that cuz
Blackjack is easy but now I think I was
only able to play like rouette or so
maybe but oh wow only no I was only
playing on not on a real roulette table
I was only playing on like a
machine yeah help him help did ntii only
get these minions in the beginning
yeah one of the Nickles coming in I
guess these are the first ones SLS I I
was not playing with
slots I can't believe you would
gamble yeah I don't really I didn't
really you know do it like I was just
dragged along and I left likely
story no for real for real I wasn't B it
anyway that was like that was that was
once like in six or seven years ago okay
well even more see I like to gamble at
the um the round one oh they're all full
heal the round one so round one is a you
mean ah okay I thought you meant with
round one like I know roulette table no
the round one I I like to I like to
there's a these like Pinko type games
that round one has and you can get a lot
of tickets on them and I really like one
of
them one of them in P yeah it's like a
pearl game where it drops
pearls yeah wait so it's Pinko yeah oh
I've never tried Pinko because in Japan
like Pinko places they're all over but
like they kind of like intimidate me
there's like really loud music music
coming out of it and it's just uh scary
somehow this is more scary to me than
even though it's more like Anime stuff
visuals all around but like it's scarier
to me than a casino for some
reason it's just it's just for
fun and I mean for you it's part of the
round one right so I imagine it's kind
of different atmosphere yeah cuz I mean
some people are there gambling for like
limited stuff but like most people are
just there to like I don't know play
midnight and
stuff
yeah Senai
water not zai do you have a problem
where you call certain kohai zai all the
time no I have this problem certainly I
don't think I
do oh but is coyote coyote is your Kai
or Senai Senpai Senpai we Senai okay so
you don't okay you don't really have
this problem because you you your only
kohai is uh reglass yeah okay and you
call them not Senai no I don't call them
Kai either mhm yeah I feel like calling
them kohai is yeah we at least English
language over kill
mhm no worries no worries okay wait I'm
going to heal them where are we I think
we're getting
close can you open the the pause
screen we're on stage four uhhuh was it
six usually with the I think there's
only five no five look it's me I
know okay
we you can only see my butt though but
that's perfect yeah my butt has been on
display a lot these
days don't I know
it God did you press
four no but I didn't need to
yeah so apparently with my music video
he
and you yeah just press four on your
keyboard while the MV is open and then
you know what we're talking about yeah I
I already knew I was like I don't even I
don't even need to do it cuz so many
people twittered it that I just it was
smagic to me I was like how does this
work it turns out it was exactly at 40%
of the video so there I think that's
crazy yeah oh not 40 yeah 40% yeah oh
wait you had coil oh [\h__\h] uh G uh what
am I supposed to say how do I train her
how do I coach her just uh oh yeah
you've killed her before I'm not very
good at dodging her attacks but it's
fine make sure to throw those balls at
her
to spam them in the right
direction I forgot how to throw them
you're doing fine uh do we have any
healing items we should have probably
locked them into one of
the yeah there we go
nice it's okay we can lock him in later
a yeah just keep on yeah run run
yeah oh she's already past 50% yeah if
now we can also manage to not lose any
of our Minions that would be dope but
they're doing well oh [\h__\h] oh yeah at
least you dodg it woo oh yeah prepare a
little healing field maybe they'll run
into it oh my God wo man quick take her
down kill her smack her
slapper yeah beautiful Oh I thought I
died
beautiful you did
it amazing easy clab yeah get rich Let's
Go will they follow me to the next round
no right they will follow you oh really
no no mind they won't I forgot no they
won't oh will they no they won't no they
won't oh nope
okay H don't don't buy the consumables
uh don't buy the equipment for now we'll
see what you have let's look look at in
detail no look in detail at what we have
what are we wearing um wait so your
kimono is
already uh yellow that's oh [\h__\h] wait
you actually got a good one yeah we
might keep that for a while mhm M and
then you're wearing the yeah let me look
at the gold up increase all healing but
ah also Reviving other players oh well
the the apple is good for now I don't
know if I would keep it for that long
what about the shark thing what does
that do the shark
hat ah okay we don't need that hood once
we get a better hat we'll switch it out
because you don't need power
attacks um that's fine you don't need to
ow ow ow ow ow
ow you want to check if they have
something good oh they got money Sen's
hat but we don't oh okay yeah yeah sell
it sell stuff Let's uh it's not so no
don't buy it don't buy it I'm not buying
anything I'm just looking good we'll
hope to find a better head item in the
next round it's not so urgent yet that
we have the best equipment right now so
we'll find something good and then we'll
switch it out but we can probably we
could
uh no we're not buying stickers we can
maybe
upgrade the the K Maybe
uh
yeah yeah twice just once what
level should we should we upgrade it to
like as much as we can guys what do you
think F the gcha we don't need the gacha
where some money we need to get Nissa
frutus okay you already did it nice why
does it say x what does doing X here
do uh it's just sitting down it doesn't
even heal you from my experience
what's the point just being cute but
they should let it heal you at least we
have our own healing
yeah okay ah also yeah now you have uh
the beetle so remember to bring out the
beetle every once in a while I also kept
on forgetting it uh at least in the boss
fights you should always have the beetle
out how do I use the beetle I hold down
the um yeah down B down a yeah yeah oh
new outfit but ours is better for
now yeah whenever you feel like you're
in trouble I'll or when I feel like
you're in trouble maybe I'll remember to
scream Beetle and then you you let the
beetle beat him and then I just got to
figure out how to
Beetle nice Dodge on the poison there
girl I'm trying I'm trying to make you
proud pretty darn good get those
balls maybe throw them at them if you're
in
trouble doing good I'm just fine good
good good good I'm not I'm not quite in
trouble yet it's a stag beetle a stag
beetle oh we got a ring oh my
God just a random
ring are you sure it's random and not I
don't know the one ring are they going
to play together sorry no our last was
like one frame per 5 minutes so it was
not not yeah not doable sadly yeah but
trust me guys I wanted it more than you
guys
did once the real like a builtin online
feature comes in we're going to try that
out yeah
promise promise okay you save us play
together I'll make you play we got get
team a what we got to get a four team oh
you're right I guess that will be
possible huh yeah oh I only thought
about playing like with one more person
but yeah now we got to get a full
stack yeah that's that sounds amazing
yeah right I feel like this game would
be fun there it is you
fck
you're yeah yeah the pit what do we get
rid of maybe
[Music]
these
uh uh the super chat right now you don't
need Super Chat but before you throw it
away you can throw it at your minion in
Fury yeah
um yeah just a tiny bit oh two two sets
of
them well let's keep them for the boss
maybe see if we get even more get them
get a full stack of them
that would be
nice oh Pebbles but yeah you don't yeah
we're
full what else do we
have
um we have healing
baseballs tokino soda I ever used the
soda how does that is that a normal heal
how does it gain an additional 25%
damage I don't use it
either you could got the Pebbles
instead I love I love using the Pebbles
okay I like using them
too or wait get them
no wait you picked it up again I
know yeah uh wait what's the button
again to drop it yeah you got you got it
you got it I just wanted to take one I
want to drink it smort
let's hope we can use it on some enemies
there we
go beat them up beat them up beat them
up beat them up get
kicked eat my paw ooh your
sword oh oh yeah it is my sword mhm but
we don't have my sword we don't have any
room left yeah don't force yourself I
also usually had full inventory just
yeah but we'll bring the claw to cell
probably
yeah it's the wow sword it's my C you
know I had the
craziest the finding out that it's a
part of your sword oh my God not part of
my shield yeah like I
mean you saw that yeah it was really
funny but did you also know
yes I mean I was aware of the button on
my top where when I uh put the weapons
away it's like kind of combined and when
I have the weapons out the badge is like
smaller and it doesn't have the weapons
on it anymore but I just I didn't see it
that way I just thought when it was
combined because it was so small like a
tiny badge I just thought that was like
its own little design like cute bad just
it's just a separate thing and I didn't
see it as a hint that my Shield can
actually do that yeah but now it makes
so much more sense because now I realize
oh maybe mm maybe that's why my sword is
so small so that it can fit into the
shield
yeah he's got to keep you
shielded I like everybody
knew everybody knew bring it up because
the the the the fascinating thing how
this finally came up is because my
figure can do it
yeah I I don't even blame myself not
knowing that this is possible when like
for example we could have made that a
thing in my 3D deut or so or in other
figures or in other merch like anything
really we could have official badges
where that is possible or whatever like
they my my somehow I could have been
made aware of this earlier but uh I
didn't know yeah I wouldn't have thought
about it too I didn't know that they
would add this feature to my figure
either it's pretty cool I learn so much
afterwards yeah it's awesome it's so
cool I'm excited for your figma it makes
me want to get it cuz I've never had a
figma before me
neither yeah people are bringing up that
like it was in my reference sheet but it
was just it was a tiny like black and
white scribble
yeah it wasn't even like it didn't stand
out much A lot of people who looked at
my reference sheet they admited that
that they didn't notice this part either
on the reference sheet so there's
nothing wrong with not noticing no I
didn't see it in my life to do because
it's not possible except on my chest but
whatever anyway nice surprise maybe
there's certain things that you will
realize about yourself three years later
as well I'm sure there
is still learning new things it's kind
of
refreshing yeah it keeps it fun it keeps
it interesting yeah
maybe maybe you will realize three years
later that your shirt is able to open I
don't know God I hope so maybe there is
a
future are there are there visible
buttons under your ribon thing no right
no well if I'd have to zoom in I think
there are but they're really tiny yeah
see yeah they're small was oh there are
buttons yeah there are okay someone
quickly unbutton my shirt to see if
they're
[Laughter]
functional they can make a functional
buttons are supposed to be functioning
mhm although although head cloves that
have like buttons or Pockets that are
not functional me too pants I'm like why
what's what was the reason mhm mhm but
then I learned uh for some like quates
or so that I had I learned like years
later that the fake Pockets that my code
has you can open them up they're just
like SE soon sewn together oh yeah that
is the case sometimes where they come
yeah mhm but that's crazy mhm that's
crazy oh no I really like these the
bombs or the punching
things yeah the poab bombs they're
pretty nice yeah
but no maybe no no don't at least don't
throw away your balls and your fork
because yeah but I don't I don't care
about these
ofk okay good oh might as well get this
to sell it later oh yeah yeah yeah nice
yeah just dropped a tea I don't what the
that what did the Tea even
do God Only Knows some some kind of
healing yeah we didn't need it yeah I
don't need that DLC Pockets
yeah I guess it just makes
production does it make production
easier for them when they keep those
Pockets
closed uh I don't
know I don't admittedly I don't know
what the purpose of to close them is
though but it's the same with like men's
waste coats on suits sometimes I think
or like the uh suit jackets I feel like
sometimes there will be like the bottom
part that splits but it'll come together
and you have to actually separate it
yourself mhm I don't know why but but
it's a thing somebody said yeah the the
balls the the balls are weak yeah but
look at how many we have they are able
to like uh I'm able to spam them they're
able to stack so high because they're so
weak that's why the fork for example Max
is out at like 20 but the balls are you
know we're at 44 so you can just Spam
them you know need you know that's why
they're good they're not weak I want to
say they're
weak low damage but fast damage and
muchos muchos
quantity sometimes maybe quantity over
quality you know but then other times
quality over a quantity ah
depends are you screaming because uh
you're in trouble bring out the beetle
oh you're doing it she's doing
it get him Beetle yeah Beetle him up be
them up easy easy
easy yeah oh whose's feather is that uh
sh is it's her writing quill oh oh yeah
blue feather I thought it was yours no
alas I guess your are mostly black I
mean I guess I did give that feather to
shiori if we're talking lore if you want
to get into the lore oh is that lore not
officially but in my in my dulu lore
yeah if you two decide that's how that
feather came to sh then honestly it
makes sense she got it from me in the
cell okay we're coming up to the boss
soon maybe she was like yeah I want to
ride to like whoever my family and then
you were like okay here take this
feather of mine and she that's when she
was like oh my God you're such a Chad
yeah exactly she gave me her feather so
I can write and and yeah you know an
archiv needs to write a little bit so
yeah it was very thoughtful of me to
pluck a feather off of my off of my
wings is bful you know how painful that
is it's like ripping out a lot of your
hairs I don't think it's that painful oh
oops I need to wait for that to birds
lose a lot of feathers yeah when they
fall it's like hair if you rip out your
hair it hurts but if it falls out
naturally it doesn't you know guess I
guess are you saying you'd be fine if I
came and ripped out a chunk of your hair
um I will [\h__\h] kill you exactly
okay okay I think their health is full
do you um you know I also was hesitant
when people were telling me to put an
item into the like slots there but I
think you should do it because once you
ah learn how to use them then it's going
to be easy like for example putting
healing items on there is reallyy okay
oh well let's go we rolling we're
beating bring out the beetle right away
I guess that might be good
then you can charge for the next time
you might be able to use it twice in the
battle Beetle battle battle
Beetle before yeah oh it's okay it's
okay yeah bring out the healing yeah
good stuff spam those
balls uh if she hits you so often just
stay a little bit far further away and
spam spam yeah
stagger
nice oh uh maybe lead it away from your
minions I try to do that a little
bit as much as possible CU those minions
are very important point five brain
cells
oh they don't understand that they will
get hit if they stand
there maybe put a healing field again
yeah or the peep yeah
nice nice nice nice coaching
really oh get out of there
yeah bro where is she oh your special is
ready I don't how do I use my special um
both of the left side like the bottom
and the left button at the same time I
think I think right
uh yeah
yeah yeah
let's go your minions will not
[Applause]
die woohoo wo except I might die no no
no no you're you're pretty she's almost
dead okay bye
bye if only the minions followed you
from round to round I get why they can't
but it would be nice if they didn't no
it's it's fine it's fine it's fine you
don't need them okay you don't need them
they need a bre
yeah it's fine it's fine good job good
job good okay freaking job yeah let's
get rid of some stuff everything you
have extra let's look at the kfp Hat
what was that
again I guess we could see
here okay um so we have an another Apple
mhm here which we should probably equip
in the meantime mhm we have the novit
pen which increases exp gain by 20% like
when you get that in the very beginning
it's awesome I don't know about now kfp
hat what does that do changes the power
attacks to be able to cause burn need no
need okay uh the what does the cobal
clothing
[Music]
do
H yeah that one will not
flinch nah but buy outfit taking damage
there's a 20% CH uh chance the attacker
is burned that's pretty cool but like
for now we can continue with the kimono
you can sell uh if we get those outfits
like already upgraded in like yellow or
whatever with free stats then we can
think about it but for now I think we're
fine continuing with the kimon yeah uh
so we can sell pretty much everything
well what about the pr bre press plate
press blade breast plate the and super
armor while charging power taxs are
ability too we don't use power attx get
rid of all the Power Attack stuff inre
oh oh you switch to Apple yeah ability
too yeah right yeah yeah oh why not mhm
yeah okay let's uh uh sell and then
upgrade some stuff okay
equipment Buy
app
[Music]
byee
I don't think you said for every item
you owe us
some and then do we want to upgrade our
our outfit
[Music]
again uh wait upgrade maybe the claws a
little bit thank you thank you okay what
about uh do we want to keep the Hat are
we wearing it yeah yeah uh ah ah no no
no why are we even wearing that did we
have nothing but I guess not the kfb
head was also about power attacks [\h__\h]
well then I just don't upgrade it okay
yeah
um yeah just upgrade the kimono a little
bit this one how
about no okay at this point we might use
it forever I might as well use my
share spare
thousand why would you do that without
getting my permission all it's it's
okay no it's not okay every set counts
we
have you ain't got the money take your
broke ass hole C
L I love that whole album why you
surprised fgy was so she was iconic she
was
spicious delicious definition make them
Bo go
logo
I love those too yeah I listen to the
album on i s a bunch of those
before it's just good good
[Music]
music right
ah okay beach beach episode get
undressed okay clothes are
off takes clothes off in asterisk uh
shows body to you in
asterisk uh asks you how you feel with a
a red
face how what do you
think I know these are pretty good too
but I don't know if we should oh yeah I
like them what else do we have um let go
through them we've got the healing we
probably don't need the I mean it's to
hold on to
it um I would we only have
19 of the the
bombs but you know no we can we can use
them you can go a little bit forward
throw the bombs at the enemies and we're
at least making use of them then run
back and get the stone
star that boys love book yeah I like
that one too but you know most of the
items are pretty dope so yeah there we
go you have to you don't have to run
back now though yeah after this round is
over this round of enemies
huh huh huh H yeah she's
cute cute oh we got a nickel
now
they they die pretty easily
yeah are you yeah be Beetle it's fine
it's okay okay let's run back for the
start to
yeah it's her song song about having
lunch with her so cute I would like to
have
lunch I already ate
yeah lunch what did you eat uh I had
eggs for breakfast and then for lunch I
had Jersey mics I had a club what's
Jersey Mike uh it's like do you know
Subway yeah it's it's like better than
Subway it's it's a similar concept
though where they have sandwich Subs do
they use actual bread
yeah youy mik bread bread it's
uh who's that what else is it then it's
not bread what is it I don't know but I
don't particularly want to
know
I mean it's still bread but it's it's I
mean a lot of American bread is just
sugar you know yeah right by those
standards probably a lot of American
bread is not bread yeah
exactly like I once had a friend from
Germany and she was like this bread
tastes like
cake M mhm I can imagine
now yeah there's some there's some bread
uh like like milk bread soft milk bread
that we have that's uh also I guess
cake yeah ours is just our everyday
bread
though
oh yeah we we we in Europe still do
bread best yeah the bread there was so
good did you like the shield pun the
salt bread yeah I did like the shield
pun oh oh I uh if if you bring her to
the next uh stage how do I pick her up
uh just how you pick up the other item
to and throw
her yeah o body mhm don't break her
now what was I going to say ah yeah so
in Japanese bakeries i' I've had sh pun
salt bread and Japanese bakeries all
over and they're always bomb what the
hell why are they so
good why why is salt bread why is that
oh my God like normally when I go to a
bakery I I usually go for something
where it has a filling like Quon just
every once in a while I would get an
empty Quon they are awesome too but
preferably always with a filling like
some bread stuff but Shan it doesn't
salt bread it doesn't have a filling
except for a [\h__\h] ton of butter that's
invisible to your eyes so mhm but it's
so good the Crunch and the salt and the
tasty
yum okay Thro that Hur
how do I throw
uh how do I throw again I think uh uh I
didn't need to throw it I can just drop
it perfect money Ali waiu
[Music]
yay I think you can generally use your
items more at least the ones that you
don't value as much like the pebbles for
example I value all of them what do you
mean yeah of course like yeah you don't
have to keep all of them for the boss
they throw so many items at us so we can
make our life easier by using
more my life's pretty easy we're not
having a hard time we're doing really
well risk it just make life life quality
[Music]
improvement
yeah
yeah well you know you never know even
in many like smaller fights you might
get in trouble sometimes
so it happens happens happen to me
happens to
the wow you placed the anchor perfectly
on top of the
tree I'm just that good I
guess are chilling nice
comfortable it's been getting warmer
over here what about over there yeah
it's getting warm here too like it legit
feels like early summer even though it's
still spring yeah it makes me sad
because none of the summer stuff or
spring stuff is going to
last ah yeah made me happy cuz I noticed
like winter depressions leaving my body
that's good yeah that's really
good oh you feel like winter depression
affects you not so
much that's good
yeah I think it really hits me hard this
year well I'm glad it's clearing then
not the winter
depression even though I like winter
man sometimes it's just hard when it's
cold you you know it's it's
scientifically proven though like the
sun gives you a vitamin
but here in Europe we don't even when
it's quite sunny in summer we still
don't even in summer we don't get enough
of that vitamin here I don't know how it
is in America but really Europe is no
one gets enough vitamin D here either oh
okay so I I was trying to take
supplements but then I keep on like
giving it up and forgetting about it I
really should have taken it n you just
keep taking them they're good for
you I just wish it was like like one
pill that like combines everything I
need right that' be nice oh more Pebbles
thank
goodness let's go going to heal them
rocks at people all I guess I'll move
over first oh oh oh nice two minions at
once nice yooo and the yukim Min is the
Healer but she's also the weakest yeah
weakest minion it's okay she's cute so
she gets a
pass Aqua sire doing her job and
back she's working
hard or hardly
working oh apparently you picked up a
golden hat I wonder know what exactly
that one was we can look at it after
yeah level up Double D it's doing so
well girl I know this is going way
smoother than the last time I playing
nice
yay oh ah ah that's the
maze no need to force ourselves to pick
it up but it's a pretty good weapon too
yeah yeah let's look at the inventory
while you're
healing uh what's that hat we
got aquaa speaking of aquaa oh whenever
getting up after knockdown
invulnerability time is doubled and also
gain 25% that that sounds amazing yeah
and it's already it already has the free
stats so I think use that one got to
take
it she was right there we just took it
from her we ripped it off her head
violently said mine
now
nice take him down take that fluffy
bastard down fluffy
bastard hug him hug him so hard that he
jokes it's over for him so
over ripped it off some
[Music]
on again the shieldy feather she just
loves
me she loves you so much that she needs
to get S all her pens from you mhm cuz
those are the only ones that right well
yeah thr those
Pebbles you need to use your items for
no you can't especially when you when
you see them coming in like a wall of
you can't you can't make me I
will the saving feature guys uh I
haven't played since the save feature
came out but is it automatic now like if
we were to die here do we just go back
automatically to
the last checkpoint every Camp yeah tell
us guys would we revive in the
camp it's Auto
nice h when you quit so if I die if she
dies we just die would we have to start
from zero again
or I don't think
so cuz yeah there's there's
checkpoints
ah if you die you start from last
checkpoint okay and it's automatic so we
don't have to like push a button to
save
no ni
dying you can checkpoint at third screen
if you die early you started first
aha
[Applause]
interesting so many minions y we got a
full party up here of little
guys
yeah
oh
oh bro what am I doing you switched it
out by accident no I just want to pick
it up yeah um I was just I forgot I I
forgot how to use buttons same sometimes
same okay it's time already oh my God
we're like swooshing swooping through
this uh make sure to send the beetle out
right
away oh I used my
Al that's not what I meant to do and my
charge back Mo yeah it's fine surely
it'll be okay use it that's
okay if we lose some minions it's okay
yeah shoot another yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
don't I love the dks
right oh this is super awesome oh doing
well yeah almost 50%
easy easy peasy lemon
squeezy oh yeah good placement H yeah a
good placement though
ah yeah good stuff good stuff you can
set the Beetle
again get beetles good awesome yeah spam
some
balls spend those balls yeah those balls
in her face you're absolutely
obliterating
her she's almost dead oh that's fine
also my little guys might not survive
it's okay she's almost
dead but you're so nice for healing
them now give her the last few punches
in her
gut K get over here maybe switch to
another use an item if you if you feel
like a there we go you failed at Chloe
before now swosh through it yeah look
you're carrying
me oh Callie's cloak but uh
uh what
actually it's you it's
me I think I
got let's go cute cute cute it's like
they're sending you a sign
yeah okay let's check anything the
reaper code Dodge rolls can damage
targets N I don't think we need we'll
sell it okay I think our current lineup
of items is pretty damn good
already it's already upgraded so we
don't have to waste money and
stuff
yeah oh you can get rid of pretty much
everything the shark hat
too
yeah
stinky it was stanking up our
inventory yeah a shieldy feather you are
you keeping one just for oh sentimental
wait h no gotcha good to see you again
go upgrade now we can upgrade our hat
this which one thank you this one how
about this thank you how about keep like
the claws also at a higher level like
everything like
[Music]
Bal yeah a kimono can get upgrade too I
don't have any more money broke see see
that's why don't gotcha it's fine it's
fine it's fine I was worried I was going
to die
why we're so far girl oh we're going to
do it we're going to freaking do it girl
hopefully easy oh you have the you have
the F
sword make sure to use it in front of a
crowd of
people it's kind of AOE I'll try I don't
know what AOE
means area of effect I don't know what
that means though
it's like an attack that's not single
Target but like yeah you use it on
several targets because it's affecting
an area
a damn I can't believe you didn't know
that word I know it but I just I can't
comprehend it no matter how many times I
have it explained to me you know what is
not that difficult to comprehend don't
don't worry about it what that's amazing
I don't know even now I still I still
don't understand and you just explained
it to me so oh my
God so okay for
example the ball the the base balls
balls they they pretty much just hit one
target but the Phoenix sword as far as I
remember it gives like a big swoosh like
a half like a crescent shape of attack
so whoever's in that area gets hit your
heal this is also AOE your AOE healing
Super Chat uh item which is like single
Target
healing okay I see yeah I think it's not
that
difficult it's a gamer special I'm not a
gamer though it's your job to game
you're a gamer
girl oh my
God that other sword whose sword was
that
again
sword item that was lying around let's
go look what that again um it keeps on
reminding me of my own sword but it's
not the m one is it is it yeah yeah M
yeah that one is pretty good too but
it's okay we we have enough
stuff I'm finally going to get to fight
Tak you
will people were saying that Lou is more
difficult than laas depending on maybe
depending on your play style mhm I think
I think yeah I think I was mostly fine
with Lou uh laas was also fine but
there's just it's just her um special
attack that's really stressful cuz she
brings out all
her uh uh gen mates attack one after
another at least not all at once that's
a good thing I
see it's fine it's fine you're just
going to be like y
y and scream
unless maybe you won't maybe you're less
panicky than me I don't know is she is
she is she more panicky than
me does narissa freak out when there's a
stressful situation no no of course
not she not really oh really does she
stay more calm depends on the
genre tends to keep her cool oh wow do I
jail bir wow they they're ging they're
gassing me up wow you're you're chill
your level arur says you're
levelheaded I
see that sounds like quite the
compliment well I mean if they're saying
so now you got to prove your
level-headedness oh
okay yeah as far as I'm concerned I I'm
pretty good I don't usually get like uh
tilted at games either I can I can get
like a little M play this game you rage
quitted it that's because I wanted to
play
everyone and I didn't have time to sit
at it all day and when you restart at
the checkpoint you lose all your little
guys and it starts you at like uh it
doesn't start you at like the beginning
of the round so it makes the boss fight
harder than if you had just survived you
also lose all your coins so I was like I
can't do this right now I had that
during my run I had that happen to me
only in the very very very beginning
like around the first boss and then
after that I had everything first try
wow lucky
you yeah the only person I've seen Panic
scream while on the offensive oh yeah I
just scream all the time she just likes
to scream a war scream
mhm anyway you're doing good so far yeah
I don't know where we
are on stage we have besides the Phoenix
sword uh Dango katas Pebbles 81 Pebbles
you go and use those freaking Pebbles
now no they're for
emergencies 81 pebbles for emergencies
you never know easier use them you never
know my God
they stack that high yeah maybe they
stack up to 100 I guess we're here to
tested the soci yeah we're going to find
out y the way you play we're going to
find
out well before you die just make sure
to spam them okay if you're in TR
yeah they go up to 100 yeah okay so we
don't need to test the science because
they have uh proven it to us
they they already tested the science for
us
yeah oh Nissa yeah you struggle with the
r
yeah okay you're
European did did you hear me saying the
old to Joy No recently like people were
fascinated I don't know why but I rolled
my RS on purpose because I was sing it
in in it in German I rolled my RS on
purpose cuz biten was German yeah yeah
um so I was like singing it in beautiful
German I wonder if you could try it too
to sing it in
German I've sung in German before many
times yeah yeah wait there's potential
yeah I'm not like have you ever heard
how it sounds with singing or to Joy To
Joy I've never I've never heard it in
German I've only ever heard the
English oh how does the English one go I
don't remember you
know I'm pretty sure there's an
English unless I'm insane Joy
English
a it's
like did you hear my sneeze yeah very
cute bless you Kaz bless me yeah Kaz
time I'm sorry I'm a demon so we don't
really do that
here oh my it goes against my uh all
Ru
oh daughter of elium we enter drun with
fire Heavenly s
Sanctuary it's pretty much directly
translated yeah
okay repeat after me
okay the German R is very difficult for
me honestly don't even have to say it so
clearly in everyday life we don't
clearer something funin g g funin
yeah
to
houseum wow you sound just like
[Laughter]
Elizabeth something
something
for Tren
mhm well you can pronounce it quite well
though oh
really thank
youen that's also in the
song I see no it's not I see you're just
making [\h__\h] up recognize the word no no
say it one more time what word hard no
say
iten
hard but but did your cat come
over no no no damn
99 oh damn German always works
normally it's a meme oh it's like it's a
meme from one of the few of these like
Tik tocky memes that I know although I
don't know if it originated in Tik Tok
but it's like a dude who who is like a
compilation of videos of a dude who goes
up to cats and he tries to get them to
react to him so he'll be like in all
kind of languages He he'll be like push
push push
push cat doesn't react and he does do
that like I don't know Japanese and
English and Russian and whatever and
then he's like okay nothing works and
then he says St how back which is a
supposedly made of German
word uh but it sounds like German so he
just claims it's German and then cat
looks over and he's like ah German
always
works that's that's the way oh
nooo
put so you try that on your cat if your
cat ignores you my cats always ignore me
that's just because they're
[\h__\h] a love them though no heal your
minions if you want yeah I'm waiting NE
is NE is looking sad
yeah wait what I oh yeah smooy has
recently been kind of
weirding oh no that's not good I wonder
if it's just my imagination or yeah if
it's a coincidence also she'll be like
constantly up on the top of my kitchen I
cannot reach her oh
no yeah the on the top of the top of the
top like what are you doing girl get get
down here this
instant she doesn't want to she doesn't
want to
listen hopefully she's all good she's a
baby she's a
baby I think uh we're probably fine you
can oh oh you got another one no okay
okay okay
just cleaning my shelves from dust or
maybe
wa you didn't open the last
chest happens to the best of us I did
that once
maybe it's my it's my superum
talent okay we're we're not oh you're
finally using the
Pebbles I did what you wanted me to
do yeah help your minions
they've been working so hard they're
such hard
workers you don't like chests anymore
huh no my chest is the only chest is it
some type of um Rebellion
Rebellion here she is you can't open
your buttons what already oh my oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
uh
Beetle ni
has
SP you're got to be fine yeah you're got
to be so fine it's okay sorry Lou Lou
Senpai you brought so many rocks in
there those tornadoes sucks let's try
suck let's try to dodge them they always
throw you away and they're like pretty
easy to
see oh maybe a bit early but sure why
not she's over
halfway wa what do you mean he's moving
fast it's moving
fast okay who girl she's doing
it everything's going so fast oh she's
[Music]
doing
oh oh you NE died but it's okay they'll
all die
eventually yeah I mean after we beat her
it'll be over oh God
nice nice nice yeah this is a little bit
tough but just keep on
running that's okay she's pretty much
dead you can't lose
now
bye-bye
woohoo you did so
well thank you you are swooping
fuest sweet sweeping I keep on saying
sweeping I guess I mean
sweeping it's okay good job English
English does not comprehend itself
English is difficult
yet yeah let's throw it all out we are
pretty committed to our equipment as you
can see it's working well so which
one you have a second fell that you
didn't sell but okay how about this yeah
let keep everything around the
yeah confusing it's okay okay money we
can we can settle see you later you just
want me to get rid of my feathers at
least
one I still don't think we have money to
uh upgrade anymore true okay we'll keep
it though don't go to the okay okay Mom
oh yeah cuz we get one more chance to
upgrade before the boss really yeah
isn't she next or is there another
boss no no she'll like have like one
more like so to say Camp before the boss
oh yeah yeah
yeah Kyla will be there you'll see okay
yeah it's okay one more upgrade time yo
okay Stars nice we have stars so right
so we can stack them
yeah
okay so seems like currently the the BL
you know what the BL uh book does in
this case yeah I love it it's like the
same as in Holo pretty
much owie um yeah this stage get is a
little bit difficult there's a lot of
strong uh
enemies so you might want to use more
items in general to save your butt
especially right now when you're
alone it's
fine they're dead
I'm only alone cuz you wouldn't play
with me there's some really tough boys
for real though yeah I'm sure there are
I'm
scared was there again there was some
enemy that when I saw him I would first
go to him to take him down because he
was really really a troublemaker what
was that again I got to let you
know when he's
around
[Applause]
[Music]
when are you going to plan the uh book
club my book club yeah well I haven't
really uh I want to read The Hobbit now
okay well okay yeah I'll have to like
ask again who wants to be part of this
time because there was an original group
um so I'll just ask again who wants to a
hit with us but I've been uh just like
asking around what like how long how
fast you can actually read it because
originally the plan was to read a longer
book and then like separate it in
chapters like one week we'll read
chapter one two whatever and then we'll
gather and then we'll continue reading
but The Hobbit seems like you can read
it in one day or at least like yeah in
preparation to for one stream we don't
have to like separate it yeah so oh it
will be maybe like a simple oh your
yukim man will die thank you I know
that's why I was trying to get to her
dump yukim me yukim me how could you
you're so squishy yeah so we'll just
read it and then maybe in the future if
they're going to if there will be
another book club we can do like a
longer book and separate it in several
episodes okay yeah oh oops oh
that's okay let's pick it up and then
quickly go to the next
one okay
okay show show I'm so happy that you
girls have been enjoying Lord of the
Rings so far cuz like Lord of the Rings
man I I've did several watchong in my
lifetime in in Hol and I I really love
it and you know I went to that musical
yeah it's coming to America it's coming
to America so what do you think you're
going to go or what I don't know Love
musical I I I don't go to that that
place that place where it's happening
Chicago
yeah I've I've heard Chicago is the
build of Susy yeah I'm scared of Chicago
I don't have any friends there so I'd be
I'd have to go there alone and I don't
really I I don't I I can't travel by
myself on which side of of the continent
is
Chicago I'm pretty sure it's
C no c
c I just I would like to see it again
but I don't think I would travel all the
way to America for it
so I didn't travel all the way to
England just to see the musical but use
the same actors probably not right yeah
probably definitely not stay in England
yeah
squishy minions first stage enemies are
so
strong is there did you see it it no I
missed the
window
wow I need to go back she's spying see I
see her PE p
[Music]
p do I sound like P up
but today it's not coming out no peka
[Music]
today thats good I
think oh my
God I missed that
P the short lived
yeah tried to throw
oh yeah you're so scattered why are you
all me
too I'm scared by all of them I don't
know what they're
doing ah it's good it's good it's good
it's
fine it's fine we'll just take our time
did you see did you see p mama I did oh
no you threw the oh I did on purpose
there's some on the floor
oh P
Mama maybe your mama can talk with Mama
wouldn't that be
cute imagine get along probably they're
both
Ms I think P mama can probably speak
even less English than
oh I mean probably it's okay they'll
communicate in mom yes
in maybe mothers just have a certain
brain wave that they can communicate
through they do they get they they just
understand being being mothers it's just
it it happens I don't make the rules
yeah exactly they're mothering so hard
explain mothering to me I don't know how
to explain mothering so I'm not going to
I think I get the vibe so I I know like
when to use it but I guess it's
like mother energy is maybe like a
mature female energy it doesn't have to
be no someone who seems you're
mothering you're
slaying I would I would I
[Music]
um I guess like similar to when
somebody's a green
mhm narissa was very fertile yesterday
with m i was uh I've seen a clip of you
guys messing around peing on each other
and uh awaiting each other to procreate
aren't you lucky what is this game I you
you play as wol and it was made by like
people who actually care about wolves so
like it's accurate to like real wolf
life or something
oh so you have to consider that um it's
to show how hard it is to be a wolf in
real life was it hard was it hard to be
a wolf yeah it it was so hard don't
forget them
chest no now just because you brought it
up I'm going to forget it on purpose
no y you're this like wolf and Twilight
Squad is a really special one isn't it
yeah it seems like it oh you want the
bomb or
oh oh I see I see I guess all health is
full H oh you you have you don't have to
use the sword oh no I dropped it so I
could pick those up ah okay okay throw
them yeah um you're ah the [\h__\h] bird
uh
the your your minions are like at this
point constantly like close to dying so
we want
to help out with like AOE attacks Etc as
much as we can try to try to keep them
alive now right now it's fine but oh
there's more coming so throw some items
at
them oh yeah oh the star is maybe a
little bit little bit much inappropriate
it's yeah cuz it stays there and they'll
probably move away
oh probably healed there can you not yet
huh guys
please it's okay actually I remember um
I was also really struggling at this
point and I had like two of free minions
left by the time of the
boss and then they soon all died and it
was a solo fight for quite some time I
had to really focus oh my
God yeah I don't want that to be me
mhm it's going to be rough oh that oh
that nickel almost died oh my God it's
okay because he didn't he's still
alive y it's fine we wait we heal
everybody
up I lose all my minions in the stage to
I had no minions at the BS to yeah it
seems pretty common it's really really
tough and they give you mostly squishy
minions that's the thing it's on purpose
mhm oh yeah oh yeah there we go now
they're all
full okay uh shiny ring let's
go oh another squishy boy thank you Game
thanks
B so it's normal though to lose them no
do be like
that that good good Beetle use good that
you remember oh [\h__\h] that's a lot of
that's a lot of enemies oh but they seem
gone quickly yeah good that was a okay
wave they're
gone how you feeling right now good good
we're doing good everything's good
everything's fine no for real though
for now yeah aren't really squish they
just have super armor so they never get
post hit invulnerability
uhhuh
huh it seems squishy to me squishier
than like the the P one for
example oh my God who are
you he's strong but you are stronger
yeah we I should go help them hm
and physically yes of course oh the bomb
guy is here okay so there's the the bird
I think is the one who froze the bombs
and then there's a icy Guy where did the
bum guy go already dead
okay uh the or cars y they're all all of
all of those are yabby so throw some
throw some
stuff want to get rid of them ASAP no
that's good that's good keep up yep
Bros
ah oh we got some space good good yeah R
those pitchforks
pitchforks it's a pitforks is not the
right word right no it's a tuning fork
but Pitchfork is the one that like like
for farming for example you use it right
but then it's actually pitch to tune a
pitch so not that
unsuitable it sounds right because you
tune a pitch
yeah a pitchfork is just the the Trident
of the land yeah it's the people's
weapon
yes even though yukim is still alive but
for how long probably not much longer
Target that bird Target
it oh those freaking tornadoes
man well doing so good I'm so proud of
you Melissa I'm doing my
best I feel like when I asked you uh to
play this with me just because last time
when you played it you rage quitted and
maybe you didn't have the best
experience you probably not planning on
playing it again oh no I was going to
play it again you really okay because I
feel like now with I was going to
wait yeah increases your curbs Your
Enthusiasm oh increases your fun with it
so now you feel like I have more
confidence with it oh that's fine yeah
you can use that here they killed
everything what that's fine that's fine
we were struggling and then everything
was suddenly
dead do we have time to go back home oh
honestly I even just waited when that
when I needed it for the boss fight
don't you need well we're on stage five
now so yeah we'll just take it slow take
it easy we we go to Kyla anyway so we
have some time to
chill oh you just let it happen I just
killed
them it looked like you were just
standing there yeah but I killed them
with my boy love book
they said is that yoi oh God and I said
Read It and
Weep their eyes are burning they don't
like it well we will force you to like
it yeah you will like
BL is that what BL stands for boys
love no it stands for um uh beautiful
lady be Beetle love Beetle love uh n
should we wait because I think next is
going to be her no like what what
happens next uh no no there must be at
least KY before uh
so where is she it's it's still
okay bi boo love bi boo love bio
chat birds love Bird that's what's
between us yeah birdie love bird love
between two birds have you ever watched
scrubs no oh why it's such a good show
no uh you heal yourself if you
can um you have
something yeah yeah okay oh wa oh it was
already over and you leveled up
okay
okay there she is okay pick up
everything um the thing is I think you
can't sell anything to her so it's like
whatever okay but we'll upgrade whatever
we can okay I'll heal for now mhm my
little
guys okay hey and I mean we're at the
end now and you still didn't pick up how
to like lock some items in the other
slots so we'll just go without because
even if I you now you're probably not
going to like remember how yeah thank
you I know how it is thank
you well you've been you've been doing
quite Welling through them okay there uh
all right what items do we have P 20
Pebbles 15 books eight okay a lot o
you'll probably end up needing more
healing items
um it's a balance and also uh I noticed
when I I I ran out of all my items a
because I really needed them just but
the good thing is she drops items when
you I think it's only when you really
are out of all items then she will start
dropping some pick up whatever you can
you'll need every support cuz you'll
also lose your minions good luck
okay just
chill oh she ran into
that and the Beet is out
nice nice and the Beet is absolutely
bullying
her yeah that one comes a
lot a lot
yeah oh good damage output wow
wow yeah tho stay as long as you have
the the Pitchfork yeah stay in the
distance throw
it she brought out a little minions it's
F get tuned you
50% oh this is going to be
easy oh oh she I think yeah she she's
doing a special okay don't just just
keep on dodging don't even focus on
attacking just dodge
everything cuz yeah you don't have time
to
attack
uh can you drop a heal somewhere or is
that too much to do right
now oh okay
yeah was more like for the minions but
die it's fine it's fine I'll just
uh oh oh it's over already the oh wait
what the what wait up what you
already
ah Senpai that's
mean oh what you feel like
done you even have minions left over and
that was so kind of
easy oh oh oh that's not how my
experience was I'm a good teacher yeah
such a good a good teacher indeed oh you
didn't struggle at
all that's uh even antil
climatic because it was so
easy so confused you were supposed to
scream and
struggle nice yay wow is it done it's
done with the defeat of of holl's leader
their plans were stopped seeing the good
within the members of hollock nepo
extended a friendly offer the girls of
hollox can join their vtuber group and
take over the world in a different way
thus hollock instead became a group of
idols and took the world through the
stage
instead back in the office the members
of nepo and hollock received a message
they were called to help save some fans
somewhere
else and so nepo and holl joined forces
and head off to their duties as
Idols but aren't we forgetting something
eh
Nah Nah The End dot dot dot get out of
here get out of
here
what what what can't believe it yeah I'm
going to dislike it too why what was too
easy you should have suffered more too
easy
you got Holo XG
now
hu you can play huso now you got a
rooster rooster oh wow now when we play
together we'll have all these options
yes so many
options oh my God
cute I'm still
flabbergasted
why I don't know why it was so easy I
guess we chose the right equipment and
the right items and you just were you
were just vibing you're just the best
coach in the whole world my teacher I
thought we'd be here struggling for a
while but it's only been an hour and 30
minutes and you were the best uh
student you were I know you but before
we started I told her we have to use
vanity and you were like no I
can't but I said we have you get good
it's it's really the easiest way and you
were not struggling at all yeah no that
went well you need to understand that
when something seems like you can't do
it it's just your mind putting a wall
there uh-huh you're very capable of it
as you saw mhm we just D we can destroy
and devour yeah oh you got the lava
stand some of them I just need two more
oh oh yeah well now you have some money
left over I think wait can can no you
can't use the money now huh no oh man
there should be a left like a way to use
your leftover money at the end I
know Dad oh well that's fine well now
what I don't know do you want to read
your super chats or so I don't I don't
really do that you don't do that no I
I'll usually read them live but if I'm
collabing with someone I don't read them
oh yeah that's fine just like you know
cuz that was so short yeah I I I don't
know man should I read the super chats
for
you see AR thank you for the pinky as
well as Kashi 145 thank you for the
akasuba tax money for the best swooping
teacher student Duo there there is your
collabs are the
best you should give him a
kiss there go
I'm back seating your Super Chat wow I
can't believe you I'm going to give him
a thumbs up wa W the
[Music]
backseater well I don't know how much
longer they'll take to implement the
real multiplayer but once that is there
we're going to try again right mhm we're
going to get a we're going to get a full
four team and we're going to go in
interested in playing uh well obviously
since I already have tried I I think I
think I did get to try everyone from
nepo so I want to try everyone from here
but I guess
whoever
H I guess I'd be interested in coyote
and Louie and chlo people told me
they're all good I bet they're all good
great yeah but there's no other healing
character besides n so if we do a group
game it would probably be helpful if one
person is deny yeah but I'll I'll I'll
gladly I used to when I used to play mm
RPGs back in the day I always was the
Healer me too I actually like I really
like to be the healer actually wait what
MMO you not not in MMOs but in like
league for example I was I would always
when I played I I just like to do
support because I tried I tried
everything else I tried top I was like a
Riven M for a while and then I tried
jungle and I was by for a while and then
I tried mid lane as AI but I saw you
saying some weird words you tried top
and you were by for a while I'm like so
confused no no no no those are character
names so I tried top and played as ribon
and I tried jungle and played as vi
vi vi I I think I don't remember how her
name it actually and then I played
middle as Ari the girl who's in KDA
who's all sexy with the fox taals know
okay but I just I just really like I
tried ADC as Jinx when they released her
and I was really good but then they
nerfed her oh so I just realized support
is the place for
me I see well we can experiment and find
a right fit for healing people is just
nice yeah but nowadays I feel like back
then I liked to be the healing character
but nowadays I also like to be more on
the offensive and be the one in control
the damage dealer the only thing I don't
like to do is tanking mhm
tanking is rough yeah tanking I don't
[\h__\h] like tanking
either tanking tanking tanking thank you
thanking thank you well like okay well I
guess this is so weird for me my streams
are never this short well yeah what do
we do now do we just do we just end do
we talk I mean I mean like we could Fe
we do another round but I'm not going to
like push this on to you I I don't want
to do another round unless we're playing
together cuz it's it's unexpected
already that we won so fast yeah my luck
won't be good again zatu yeah weu we
zatu for like for yeah 20 give me give
me one sec let me uh switch over to my
show together
again we could shower together you'd
like that wouldn't you we we might get a
chance to shower together in the future
yeah must we yes must of course it's
required okay we're on my chatting
screen oh oh you so getting so big hi
giant giantes
narissa hi there takanashi Kiara you
look so pretty when you're so big thank
you I'm going to eat you now no no no
let me go no just no I don't taste good
right now no no no I guess I taste like
chicken still but no tasty where did I
go help help me help me help me oh I'm
out of her tummy oh my God now I'm
huge beat them up beat them up bro they
don't even got to edit this way excuse
me what her mic is dying yeah I was
hugging my microphone sorry wow there's
so much green on here yeah why are you
so
green oh sorry
sorry excuse my greenness yeah stop
being so green what are you a
frog yes I'm
FR do you know how to do that can you no
oh my God that sounded not
good oh go
stop that is not good I don't know if
you guys heard that on stream but mama
Mama Mia Mama Mia I will teach you the
right way of Fring someday
okay what do we have to talk about
narissa how much we miss each other
a I do miss you I miss you too don't you
guys Wish You Were
Me probably some of them some of them
not all some some might the jail Birds
might wish they were for me yeah
probably kfp and jailbirds now kiss
[Music]
yeah time passes fast don't worry we'll
meet again soon yeah there's always
other opportunities to do things who's
your favorite in Lord of the
Rings that's actually a really hard
question for me um so I feel like I
really like legalis in the movies but
but he also that's also because he's
played by Orlando Bloom you know and he
just he's great but I feel like even in
the books he's not really like the
deepest character you know what I mean
like there's so many more details in the
books but at the same time I still feel
like the the main characters of course
are like the hobbits you know not not
not that crew so you get a lot of
Aragorn and then you get like little
other things but like Legas is just kind
of a pretty boy but I still love him
yeah yeah but I think Aragorn is
probably and Sam wise gamji y Sam is my
favorite Frodo in the books though he
just so cute I thought Frodo couldn't
get any better with Elijah Wood being
him but then when I read the books I was
like holy [\h__\h] somehow like his
character makes so much more sense to me
froto like yeah and like faramir also I
I didn't like in the movies at all
especially in the first movie in the
books I love
him fa or my oi what about billur you
like billur I show up much yeah I
haven't gotten read The Hobbit yet but
bbo is fine I've seen the Hobbit movies
and I like them just fine I mean they're
they're okay you've seen the Hobbit
movies oh okay so you I I had already
seen Lord of the Rings before this
wasn't my first rodeo I just read it for
the first
time oh oh yeah I just wanted to join
because it was shiori's first time
Oh I thought y'all were first time
Watchers I'm I'm an experienced
fan well have you have you have you sat
in the theater when the third harbit
movie came out to a marathon all three
movies in a row no I've done that you're
crazy that was fun that was really good
mhm it's been a while since I've done
something like that it just doesn't
happen two movies that uh I I watch
these days there's just no no second
third and so on where
you like I feel like the last I mean cuz
they do that kind of with The Hunger
Games kind of yeah yeah but like like
Hunger Games Twilight the Harry Potter
movies cuz he watch the new Hunger Games
movie with me
late you were getting the popcorn I was
so lost it's I so bad cuz I was like
when she's going to I kept on like
continuously looking behind me and the
people behind me must have been thinking
can she stop looking behind but I kept
on looking because I needed to see if
you're coming in uh because then I was
going to turn on my phone light really
quickly to show you where I'm sitting
cuz it was so pitch dark you wouldn't
have found me probably and then you were
wear you were carrying like two popcorns
right and like two drinks like how how
is she going to you're going to I was
like so word you're going to fall and
you're going to drop everything
you Balan so perfectly juggling well I
used to I used to be a server you
know I me too oh no wonder we're so
talented then tell me your craziest
server
story um you have one not so crazy but
there was one time this was more
irritating than
anything um some kids had come in to eat
and while we were not looking they drew
on the table with ketchup and mustard
and left oh at least that's removable
yeah but it's still pain to clean up you
know cuz like you you can't just use one
rag you got to like continuously go back
and rinse it out in the kitchen and then
and I really am grossed out by ketchup
so it was getting to
me a I also have a story you want to
hear it yes so I was
[Music]
serving see you no uh I was I was Ser no
I actually have a story yeah yeah yeah
yeah but that was that would have been a
good opening um so I I was working in a
hotel so uh I I Would S like be a
waitress so to say for breakfast buffet
but also sometimes for lunch and dinner
but mostly breakfast and lunch and then
for breakfast we often had like big
travel groups uh from all over the world
and so there was this one Travel Group
where uh it was already summertime so we
C we were able to have the people sit
outside on on the tables outside okay so
but you have to go inside to get
something from the buffet and we had
like uh floor to ceiling windows and
doors and the door was however open you
know wide open but this one guest he
takes a bowl of cereal and stuff and
then walks
towards the outside and just walks
straight into the wall that
is glass window and I saw it move my
eyes because you fought that like I
guess the windows were just so clean but
the door was literally right next to him
it was open like normally you should be
able to see a difference between where
there is no window and where there is a
window but he walked right into it and
he was really perplexed and all the
other guests saw it too he must have
been really embarrassed so I tried not
to laugh but some people were giggling
and the cereals and the milk were all
over the window and the
floor yeah but I feel bad because like
this can happen to anyone like these
kind of accidents are so embarrassing
you were just hoping nobody was looking
and you just act normal and all that
like oh not a big deal yeah my head is
really really hurting right now but not
a big deal hey but you know the upside
you said that was when you were working
in a hotel right mhm upside is at least
you're in a hotel you're staying there
so even if you get covered in milk and
cereal you can just go up and wash and
change your clothes you know like at
least it didn't happen at an actual
restaurant cuz then you don't have the
option to leave you know like well I
mean you can but then you have to drive
home in your car cover you have probably
a change of clothes in the same building
so yeah was good
yeah yeah that made me think like cuz a
part of me was kind of annoyed by uh
these travel groups sometimes because
they often left a huge mess on the
tables uh some of them didn't even take
plates they just ate on the um like
tablecloth I'm like what the
[\h__\h] so a part of me had really real
shot and F oh when that happen yeah I do
German word is is this one of the words
who has no uh English translation we use
sh fora right because it has no English
translation mhm yeah it's amazing it's
actually a German word for my language I
love I love shouen fora makes me feel
glad that I'm not that person over there
who fell on their ass exactly ha you are
hurt and I laugh at you
ha pleasure and Misfortune of others
exactly we have some good words in the
German language such good words oh yes I
can sound very German this is uh not a
good German accent actually I'm not I
don't know what I'm doing it's not
working out it was a good a good one
yeah you had an intonation of maybe like
a little bit of a Bavarian or a ination
there well you know my favorite
historical figure is from Bavaria
so oh oh yeah right yeah yeah so if you
talk like this this has a little bit of
a Bavarian accent
oh no no no and sometimes Scottish
accent reminds me of a like German
accent I need to learn I need to hire a
language coach and learn how to do a
Scottish accent cuz recently I found out
I'm 69% Celtic which is [\h__\h]
hilarious
69% C isn't that so funny oh of course
so you're more European than American of
course but wait I guess that's that's
just a that's just like isn't I all have
European Roots right yeah yeah yeah
pretty much everyone here but yeah I'm I
I can remember back in my family when
when the Celtic Celtic Ravens immigrated
to hell so we we remember when that
happened why would they do that from
Celtic lands to hell why they were tired
of potatoes I guess I don't
know what's better about hell um
honestly I I couldn't tell you but yeah
so now sadly I don't get a cool accent
or and I can't speak what's the rest um
it's just other
European uh any Austrian I actually I
don't know give me a sec I can I can
find it it'll take me a minute though I
can tell you what I am Scottish Irish or
GIC they're asking uh it's it's mostly
Scottish and thenot and then the second
it's like it's it's a lot of Scottish
it's mostly Scottish but then it's
mostly Irish
did you do a test yeah you do the DNA
thing you go and you get your DNA tested
I want to do that too do it I should do
it because I found out um through my
mama uh I have some American Roots
because yeah uh the the father of the
grandmother I think grandmother it was
from America probably I can't believe
you're American
I can't believe it either like I don't I
don't want to be H just
kidding hey I I look if I could if I
could go to Europe and like live there
successfully like and not have any issue
and not have to pay European taxes I
would also do that I think the problem
is more like not the European taxes but
that you would maybe have to pay double
like American and yeah that that too so
you know it's not great then what if you
if you were to marry me do you still
have to pay American taxes uh probably
you you are you trying to marry me no
I'm just trying to I don't know give you
a better quality of life I
don't I I want to go back to my roots I
want to go to Ireland and Scotland cuz
that's predominantly where I'm from yo I
have land in Scotland I own land I I
bought that same thing
too okay move into my one square meter
of
Scotland same us in our one square meter
of Scotland wait I found it and then I
clicked off of it isn't that just just
like you'll show him your certificate of
69% almost mostly Scottish and I'll show
him my certificate of land Ownage and
then they let us be there yeah okay so
I'm 42 oh it was three Square sorry
three Square it's small I'm 42% Scottish
I'm 15% Irish and then I'm 12% uh Wales
and then Wales 12% Germanic Europe oh
and then 10% England and Northwestern
Europe and then Norway
9% oh yeah
wow wow well you looked apart honestly
yeah I look I look I look
Scottish yes with my raven black hair
and my beautiful red eyes yeah the the
red eyes are very Scottish mhm
I've seen many Scots with red eyes
yes
yeah wait
so that's that's the 69% yeah this no
the 69% is uh the Celtic origin which is
oh combined Scotland Ireland and Wales
ah is it not why are people saying
what's Wales what do you
mean yeah it's say it's like a I don't
know I'm not saying it wrong am I oh no
you said it wrong
why are they clowning on me then ah I
guess it's Welsh ah yeah but it's you're
not whales and it's written as the area
that's why I didn't say I'm Scottish I
said
Scotland or did I I don't know it
doesn't matter did you I don't know it
doesn't
matter you know she knows it's whatever
don't worry about it it's fine you guys
understood W you turning me on right now
you're so hot oh thank you you know
that's what I
do I love that that sounds so
good you know I actually really struggle
when I try to do a German accent of
English because my English normally is
pretty decent I don't have such a
strong accent now that I'm saying these
words I feel like they're coming to me
the accent uh but but normally I don't
have this so when I try to force it I
have to really think really hard and
focus on speaking worse English than
usual yeah no you you I feel like a lot
of German people tend to have a really
good accent already but you you have a
particular like as a German speaker you
just did you just say lots of German
people have really good English already
I mean when they when they learned to
speak English but I was saying yours I
think even that is particularly good
which Germans did you talk to I have met
at least five or six German speakers and
all of them speak a phenomenal English
I'm not talking about Germans in Germany
or Austria I don't know about that yeah
you me met them elsewhere okay then yeah
they might yeah have different they're
they're internet people like you I would
say for both Germany and Austria uh it's
yeah I mean I don't I think we have
really good education so a pretty pretty
good most people have pretty good
vocabulary but a lot of people struggle
to get rid of their accent yeah I mean I
struggle too when I speak any language
that isn't English m I'm like
come and everyone's like what the [\h__\h]
did you just say and I'm like I said
thank you in
Korean that's very recognizable don't
wor about it it's fine plus it's
cute it's
[Music]
cute no I think you have a good ear for
picking up uh the accents and stuff and
intonations you're very nice you're very
polite
well I am a teacher I have to be nice
and you know
motivating that's my queen thank you I
I you know people serve their Queen
right
yes
serve serve what what are you going to
serve to me [\h__\h] I guess oh [\h__\h] she
said it oh my
God you you dared to say it oh
wow I didn't think I'd actually get you
to say
it I I don't I'll admit I actually don't
like that word so I prefer not to use it
I I have to say to my defense also like
I feel very very very very uncomfortable
to say it in German the same word the
equivalent is it different it's
embarrassing well no it's like there's
an equivalent to it like just because
when I say it in my mother tongue it's
just it makes me very uncomfortable it's
just because it's English that I have
this this like this distanced feeling to
it and also because I just like heard it
even before people were saying it to me
I already like heard of it before from
slang and all that so it's like I just
it's just I feel like yeah for the
people who are accommodated to the slang
they just don't feel the same way when
they hear it mhm it hits differently
yeah no for me there's there's few
English words that I actually consider
to be like cuss like swear words like
for example I don't think [\h__\h] is that
bad I'm sorry I know some people are
like it's so intense it's so bad and I'm
like no it's not it's my favorite word
in the English language it's so funny to
me because like I think most of
everybody besides you in Advent I think
kind of uh stays away from curing a lot
right yeah I think only me and Sh sh oh
really yeah does I don't think she
swears as much as I do but I'm pretty
sure she still
swears but yeah most it's it makes me
feel very connected and comfortable with
you that the one Advent member that
joined who has me as an Oshi and likes
me really much who interact with a lot
is the one who feels very comfortable
with swearing so it's nice we're vibing
mhm but the the c word is actually what
I call that word I I actually don't like
it also same with there's there's the
other c word that is like cocka doodle
doo but if you get rid of the a doodle
doo doodle doo yeah the doodle doo yeah
I mean I don't like you don't really
call people that do you yeah no like
I'll be like someone's being a dick you
know but like I don't like I don't like
to use that just sounds weird I never
heard someone say you're being a c c k
instead of a the other one there's some
there's some potty mouth words that I'm
just like these are two potty mouth for
me I get it I get it I get you but I
also feel I feel like I don't it's funny
because people were pointing out and I I
indeed find it funny I don't want to say
the V word v
v the v v v a g i n a for example oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah I don't want to say
that or like any other like similar word
I I even feel a little bit uncomfortable
even though I sometimes do bring it out
the the P U SS y word yeah I don't like
that word either
yeah but sometimes I say it when I want
to say you're a little
po sometimes sometimes but generally I
feel uncomfortable with it yet I say I
said the CU word several times yeah I've
realized I've realized that my my jail
birds make me I actually really don't
like the word tits at all I I it's not
that I think it's a bad word I just
don't like it titties no I just think
breasts are such a wonderful thing and I
think there is so many more eloquent
ways to refer to them but now like I
can't help myself sometimes when we're
all talking I'll say it without thinking
about it I'll be like I can't believe I
just used the worst word ever
breasticles and just say boobies or
boobas yeah booby
booba
breasts look at my breasts bosom oh I'm
looking respectfully Mor oress thank
you they look they look good thank you
you clothed or
unclo it's okay I have X-ray vision
remember when remember when like I guess
this is when phones were becoming more
and more common and apps were becoming a
thing or like I don't know if it was
even an app but people were putting out
these like x-ray vision things that
supposedly when you use it you're you
can they were advertising it as such
that you could see through but of course
it was all a scam yeah never used it
though but like I don't know how you
would even get your hands on it was it
an app or was it a what was that anyway
I have no idea but I I remember what
you're talking about but I feel like I
like missed out on
that I hope they give everybody a virus
who got themselves that app probably you
deserve it you want to see through
people what do you even it's not even
erotic to see someone's bone big it was
it was that kind of X-ray that where you
don't with the magical x-ray that I
don't think even exists where you don't
see the bones no no you just see the
clothes yeah yeah that's not possible
alas no no no it doesn't like that
you're going to see their bones and tell
me tell me how that's going to work for
you is that does that turn you on yeah
damn that's you're like damn look at
that skeleton in that
body sexy yeah sexy skeleton oh my God I
got to get that skeleton out my little
Skelly
Welly just play Minecraft if you want to
look at a skeleton so
bad or go into Callie's chat yeah become
a dead
beat it's funny it shows how I think it
was mostly teenagers kids who fell for
that they were so ni yeah that makes
sense kids are kids are curious so
they're like oh my God yeah it's cute it
can be cute and then and then they suck
when they're teen little beasts yeah
fing teenagers freak me out God even
when I was a teenager I was like [\h__\h]
teenagers man yeah they scared me I was
always getting bullied and even nowadays
I feel like if I'm around teenagers they
bully me
too God I I just can't stand teens man
they're they're on something good for
them but also like grow up
please yeah when I'm like on out in on
on the pathway
outside PA is when I see a group of
teenagers coming towards me
or get really scared yeah oh my God same
I was I was walking in the city and a
ton of teenage boys were walking and I'm
pretty tall and imposing right but I was
like not teenagers it's like that one
MCR song teenagers scare the living [\h__\h]
out of me that's literally me that's the
lyrics yeah whenever I see a
teenager I get it yeah are you you guys
scared chat people yeah are y'all scared
scar me cuz I'm scared they just like
maybe they maybe I'm not necessarily
scared but I really have this feeling
that they think they're like cooler and
better than me they just don't have
respect for adults and I that adult to
them I think so they're like what is
this like in between teenager and adult
looking person looks lame and just
uncool what what gives them the the goal
to act like that that's all I want to
know I'm like you're still in school you
should be doing your homework little one
why you why you talking to me what leave
me
alone I'm cool I'm cool I'm cooler than
you look at how many steps I have in my
passport look at uh I don't know what
else makes me cool uh what makes me cool
mhm am am I cool to you of
course what makes me cool to you um I
think that you're so comfortable with
yourself I also really like how
straightforward you are about how you're
feeling I think I think it's you're just
giving me random compliments is that
really what makes me cool
yeah I mean they're not random
compliments that's what I like about
you thank
you I guess I don't need to be cool yeah
I mean you are cool self protection from
the teenagers who want to harm
me the teenagers who are looking at us
funny how dare
they hate them I hate them let make them
grow up yeah hurry up and grow well no
they shouldn't wish away their youth but
I think I the one thing I think I regret
the most for my childhood that I wish
more kids knew is I was in such a rush
to grow up and not be a kid anymore but
you know now that I'm an adult obviously
things are pretty good for me right now
but like there was a a period of time
when I was in jail you know when I was
like damn I wish I was just a kid again
outside playing Pokemon like having a
good time were you jail 9,000 years oh
[\h__\h]
yeah that's so long it's a long time man
what a long time I was only 1,000 when I
was locked away are you
like uh do you not die um I can but us
demons have a pretty long
lifespan oh yeah okay
yeah uh is there how do you you know
there's ways of killing a vampire how do
you kill a demon um you know
exorcisms ah that doesn't really kill us
but it can weaken us potentially yeah
you can you can send us back to
hell you know but like a different part
it won't send us night to like the nice
the nice hell that like we live in we'll
get like trapped for a little
bit oh in the nice part of hell you get
sent to Nice Part no we get trapped in
the bad part of hell for a little bit
and then we have to get out so we can go
home walk the walk the path of
Shame well I I wonder how weird the
differences are of nice and bad part of
Hell different levels of Hell well bad
hell is for the bad demons and and the
good part of Hell is for the good demons
someone said
Detroit to Detroit you get sent to
Detroit what what that like a game thing
does that happen in a game or I didn't I
don't know I think there is a game
called Detroit something something
become human or something I don't know
but I don't I don't know I think I think
they're making a joke about something
that I don't understand with Detroit
yeah uh they're saying n Detroit is just
awful no not Detroit anything but
Detroit no please spare me wait is
Detroit in
Chicago don't ask
me got to look up you you don't know I
don't know Detroit I don't I live in
hell why would I know about
America it's in Michigan Michigan where
is
Michigan Michigan is by the Great Lakes
wo yeah the first picture it shows water
a body of water and it looks so nice wo
oh Michigan as Chicago is really close
to Michigan but Chicago is not in
Chicago is
Illinois yeah is it is that Illinois
yeah read it read it as if you didn't
know how that was
said
Illinois Illinois have you ever been to
Illinois no I know how to say it
Illinois there was one one thing that's
really uh difficult to say ah Pittsburgh
is pittsb or no what was it was that the
one it's Pittsburgh okay well I I can I
can name all 50 states for you in
alphabetical
order guys say Alabama Alaska Arizona
Arkansas California Colorado Connecticut
Delaware Florida Georgia Hawaii Idaho
Illinois Indiana Iowa Kansas Kentucky
Louisiana Maine Maryland Massachusetts
Michigan Minnesota Mississippi Missouri
Montana Nebraska Nevada New Hampshire
New Jersey New Mexico New York North
Carolina North Dakota Ohio Oklahoma
Oregon Pennsylvania Rhode Island South
Carolina South Dakota Tennessee Texas
Utah Vermont Virginia Washington West
Virginia Wisconsin
Wyoming nice I think it was Arkansas
yeah
Aransas America explain right yeah it's
Arkansas but it looks like Aransas our
cancers our cancers not just my cancer
it's our
cancers that's or like our like a pirate
Aras AR canas
Aras
canas
[Laughter]
ksas yeah I wonder why why you can't do
it I don't know it's not a tongue thing
cuz I have a short tongue
too I can do that but it's like when I
try to
like the
horing it just doesn't
work it's okay you don't need it you
don't need it it's fine I'm cute enough
without it all right shall we there a
different wait just one thing there's a
different art that I struggle with oh
yeah yeah yeah it's the Japanese like
like the pcka uses it when she say is
like
yeah I can't I can't yeah the German R
is different from that like just saying
a
or I'll never get it I don't know how
that works it's
hard yeah I I can't do that either I
really wish I could but I even my
Japanese R right now is like fake it's
like a
D ah it it does kind of honestly that's
not so far off it does go into that
direction ction mhm yeah I just can't
correct it you know one day I'll get it
maybe it's like that for real it's
supposed to be like
that that's my best I say I let you go
even though it's your channel yes I'll
let you do you have anything to announce
kiava Senai no no just stream Kima
please stream chimera
[Music]
kedie
yeah hey you should sing it in your K
sometime give me the
instrumental okay okay when are you
going to do a k I don't know I just did
one so probably uh actually I don't know
tomorrow you
wish but um I if I can say
something do it do it I'm trying to hit
669k subscribers by the end of the month
oh yeah I heard I heard I'm so silly
please consider subscribing if you're
not already should be possible yeah
right I'm only like that's not so far
15K away maybe it's doable I don't know
oh but didn't you want to reach it not
by the end of the month but by the like
at on four on 20 of
April don't worry about
it they they'll under they'll understand
later for now we're just for now wait
yeah by 420 would be fun too because
that would just be really funny but I
don't think that's going to happen
uh cuz we have n days for
that confused
okay no no you didn't you're beautiful I
love you I don't I don't even know if
you know yet actually I'll tell I'll
tell you after I don't know if I know
I'll tell I'll tell you after okay
anyways thank you guys so much for
watching there's no one to rate into so
go and take a break eat some lunch if
you're going to watch more Hol streams
tonight or if you're EU have a good
night sleep tight
and K thank you for yeah oh yesi thank
you for leading me through hello break
you're welcome it was fun even though I
was just like
there I'm glad okay and uh in in nissa's
streams we say by
Darlings I'll Fe Us by bye m
m
[Music]