[Music]
n
la
[Music]
K hello once again and welcome to day
two of
Wow's side of mic
Recollections
yippe good morning it is 10:00
a.m. yeah I am of the
oranges and they eating good yeah you
are but this won't last very long so you
got to enjoy this
week and all the previous
streams as long as they
are you know at decent times for you
guys yeah I I restant M yeah I had my
breakfast I had little like tiny baby
pancakes that I found at the convenience
store little baby pancakes with some
whipped cream and I slapped a [\h__\h] ton
of Nutella on
them and I have some pineapples in the
fridge when I feel like more cuz it was
just like four baby pancakes really
small ones how's the inside of my mouth
thank you for asking it's like a pretty
um yeah
M it hurts so far it doesn't feel like
it's getting better
yet that's okay that's okay wow uh Tak
tanakak car of the oranges uh rescu
savior of the
lesbians will once again today fight for
what is right and find and safe the
lesbians uh let's do our best I think
you hear some bgm right I don't hear it
but I prepared some bgms for you guys uh
that are oh wait it didn't Loop that are
perhaps more uh suitable for this kind
of
endeavor um I think around 11 or that
will join me but it's okay uh that she's
not there from the beginning maybe I can
mingle with some others there's some
girls online
so let's begin
yeah my other guild mate is oh is around
two oopsie a
sh oh
[Music]
no where am I let's
see ah at the building grounds so I know
I know everything
actually I don't think they're here
right now I think they're at the guild
uh uh the quest
thingy let me
see where was that again somewhere over
there right like not
not why are we here again oh you should
take the the iron
Quest the iron Quest hello Fair hello
lady of the oranges good day to both of
you beautiful ladies nice hat uh I must
say I am almost envious of it I do
recommend the iron Quest highly it was
quite uh a good um uh um yes good thing
very useful not to startle you my lady
but there is a woman on a horse behind
you you did start on
me I thought I could sneak my way
what is happen what what is happening
I'm scared what is happening we speak
the language of the Gods what the heck
so you must respect us uh we did a side
quest and we learned a new language in
the side quest you guys can do it too
what oh really I
want did it take you it took me it took
us 3 minutes if you guys want to join I
can show you 3 minutes MH and we'll
learn an entirely new
language uh well yeah yeah it's like a
it's like a it's like a video game
mechanic okay that's so it's like you
it's like an RPG you know where you have
a skill tree oh you already did you do
it did you do it already yeah that's why
I speak uh German M I heard I heard her
say something oh M what did you say oh
say her name is a m it's Cleopatra Da
Vinci the third name actually it's
Darwin Roosevelt Caprio junr you changed
it what
why I did not I call you Junior for
short you can call me Junior for short
wait what happened with
free who with what happened with the
person you were
yesterday I am the person that I was
yesterday names are but a name am I
struck by Amnesia once
again we just can't comprehend iads
she's on another level H indeed she
might
be how to get on that level Ladi my
ladies may I interest you in a lottery
ticket
I'm Lottery a daily loty starting today
and the first drawing will be tomorrow
and for just 10 gold coins you can
purchase a lottery ticket or however
many as you would like and enter for
your chance to win big ja jackpots isn't
the other green lady in your guil too
why do I feel like I'm being cheated on
why do you want to why are you is she
the exact same with you she did the
exact same thing with me
she's sheing it are you saying that
you're not having TI the bigger the
jackpot get but it has to be
personalized FAA every single sale has
to be
personalized no let me let me look she
just regurgitating the same the same
nonsense
and whenever I look into your green eyes
I see the green of money and I recall
the time we spent in the casino betting
it all on green and I
recall Casino failed us oh this is so
personalized I feel so targeted like I
am in the market that was so much more
intimate than what she said to me what
the heck well you mirror or something
so oh what are the win rates FAA deest
um bet
oh well it's about about 1 in 700
although you can buy as many lottery
tickets as you one in
700 chances every time it's way better
odds than the real lottery I might add
yeah but you don't what do you win if
you win how much you win the big jackpot
which is jackp well well right now it's
only 10 gold but the more lottery
tickets are bought the bigger the
jackpot will
grow the lower the are yeah but if you
guys don't buy it then it'll be a really
low Lottery and be like one sucker who
just get trying to guil trip us into
paying for the lottery it's working my
lady I would like four tickets put the
oh no one understands me yes yes
my no one understands me I was trying to
save that will be 40 gold oh you were
trying to save me um I was trying to
save do you have to use psychology 40
Golds accept how do I
accept I was just being
transparent oh you're being transparent
I see you very
clearly okay I have a question no
understand that is not true that is not
true
spe I understand everything I watched
your Vlog in the store you watch my Vlog
I watched it yes go over here Perhaps
Perhaps
10% perhaps there's a chance that 10% we
are going to get in on what going on and
we are going to use it to our
advantage I made it I the block I made
it there you go any sign of friend you
would you like to choose your own
numbers or would you used for us to take
advant other can be at the the biggest
of the in so honestly we should we
should let them we should let her be
scammed because they're in the same
Guild and they're only like falling into
their own demise one no zeros you are so
correct let's just let it happen you're
so right perhaps justone that is in the
same Guild which their like three
numbers1 and then only one number well
the thing is I'm inoty right now but
it's not a big deal don't worry about
it very
complicated general advice
most people if they have like more than
one step in the lottery they they'll
back out because they have too much time
to think about it you know they have
I'll just I'll just make sure that they
won't like comment subscribe like
comment subscribe what would you like
for the second one make sure you hold
on like button click on the Subscribe
button let's go one 2 three what else no
no everyone wouldn't do that no 657 yeah
yeah uh sponsorship sponsorship
uh add one minute ad for sponsorship won
is we don't have any okay okay one one
second no
no a certain VPN perhaps uh and uh how
about
two
Danish
byp oh surf surf G VPN yes that should
be n n n n n n that should be for need
to stop popcorn is addicting what is
popcorn I only only no corn it is corn
that is
pop how how does one do that that seems
like a powerful ability there you are
powerful upgrades to coin wow this is
legit you put it in the microwave that's
right what is a
microwave it really is does it perhaps
work if I just like burn it like this
with my Phoenix fire
yeah okay lock into to trade hello thank
you our sponsorship has arrived surf GAA
VPN
huh hi to the appointed point you both
have interested in a lottery ticket a
lottery ticket would you be interested
in gambling and partaking in a lottery
so you buy a ticket and I guess the
proceeds go to supporting the library
did you know that once you wear the hat
of the appointed Point your memories are
shared I feel we've already had this
conversation oh what no you're
what no did she try to enter she you
tried to enter sevens but you had a
double seven you couldn't enter that
right I'm I'm a bit fuzzy I had a bit of
a a compression
earlier a
vlog I was watching your Vlog and she
was watching her Vlog memories
perfectly it's like a high of Mind guys
can you read each other's mind wait okay
wait GAA think of a color F tell tell us
what color think of a color she's
thinking of blue how did she know it's
the head of the appointed Point F you
know you mustn't ever remove that hat or
else you will die I should get one of
these hats okay okay about we should get
the Amber hat I will also
die I know I know how if I remove the
Hat you die and if you
we both die money I on for scota guys
can you like SCA
yeah put hands down and
fight I don't know if that's the same
gambling as everybody is talking about
there's a different
one but yeah there's a created her
talking it's like a and then
[Music]
there's oh yeah I I saw a vlog about it
oh my wait oh you did
yeah are you limbing
[Laughter]
under
hello wow we also like the ball very
impressive that's cute I got the knees
fun do you want to show us your March I
haven't seen it oh yes piing it it's
it's still a work in progress and we
mainly sell lottery tickets at this
point are we all going F Mar is open
yeah wait it's open oh wait you owe me a
you owe me a place to rest my weary head
oh yes you may rest your weary head in
the floor of the sh okay I purchased
that and I I wish to
have are so fast they are they're too
fast um try to observe it only from the
front out watch out watch out
o Mar lottery tickets now available guys
this sounds like a good deal is this
entire Mark just for lottery tickets
come on we oh thank you so far we don't
have anything else for sale really if
you would like to buy some cherry
saplings we could we could negotiate um
but may we lottery tickets yes what is
the benefit of a cherry oh you won't fit
through here I suppose with that hat
that's fine uh don't worry check this
out unicorn cute I just have to D now
and is it this is that much trouble yes
I'm not sure about I'm not sure about
the saf of this establishment want to
it's kind of Bree yeah well it's a work
in
progress lottery tickets are purchased
then that can go towards the better of
bomart thought the lottery would go
towards the library does it not go
towards the winner towards the library
was this mentioned before well check
check the fine print of your
ticket will I think you should put a a
sign down where it says like please wear
hat when entering like a hard hat you
know like when
air
of Excuse Me Miss the vine princess it
says that you get 30% of the jackpot
winnings but you just said 10% no the
library 10% this sounds exactly like the
scam I've encountered
recently so 40% doesn't even go towards
the jackpot is huge huge jackpots big
wins in the lottery every day huge okay
then after taxes what well I don't know
if you have to pay taxes the king
doesn't know about this Lottery and I'd
like to keep it that way and I think you
all would too oh you wait you just wait
until the queen hears about this the
future Queen the queen is the Queen the
future queen queen you treat her as the
current Queen the The Tam tenders lady
oh Tam tand to propos to her so she's
accepting his proposal then of course A
B of course she
is we have to think of what what would
we give as a present for the like a
betral present for the king and queen
lottery
tickets how about two lottery cards two
lottery tickets yes I don't know I feel
like that's embarrassing I feel like
there's nothing you can really give to
someone who's going to be Queen when you
are the status that we are indeed indeed
saving them though what like a blunder
is if they can't get one
themselves but it's the thought that
counts and you could put a like as long
as you make get personalized thought
goes into a blender I feel like you
should give them a
card sorry sorry that's just uh Phoenix
happenings every once in a while
accidentally I'll turn the AC on wait I
can't second W
who it was the
[Music]
AC anyways F that's messed up man what
Mor cop you what what you're you you're
taking advantage of people that can't
read that's what the library is
for the
library you didn't mention circle
of it's a library of course of
course doing something for the local
businesses M what are you doing for the
local businesses why are you on her side
because team
one intimidating of her hat sorry
what she was trying to scam you though
no yeah but she's on my team so as long
as she wins I win oh no you're one of
those people like well she's she's my
mother she's my brother it's okay if she
takes all my money we will expose this
scam on her Vlogs and then you will go
down expose
expose sounds like free advertising to
me write about it in the paper so
everybody
knows no wonder I'll hold on to my
ticket I'll tell the queen about this
wait wait before you tell the
queen would would you be interested in
joining the lottery no it's it's only 10
gold per I think it's a really good deal
no uh you get a German discount it costs
uh 40 40 for three tickets only a German
discount what the heck what's a
German a German is uh it's like one of
the side quests that I mentioned earlier
you have yeah I want I want to go on
this side quest to learn Germany yeah
Germany of Germany don't fall for
another scam of theirs I can teach you
Germany
privately all of
Germany I feel like we need multiple P
sources multiple sources your Germany
isn't the right Germany my Germany is
the best
Germany I have the superior
Germany don't say that don't list that
my Germany sounds
beautiful yeah that is true there's la
la lying over there okay I'll show you
the quest are you ready no no no no no
no you're not ready cuz you haven't
bought a ticket yet right that's yeah if
you bought a ticket you
just come on buy AET I wait are we all
going to are we all going to about
Germany now yeah okay okay not about
Germany we're doing the side quest to
learn German yeah that's what that's
what I meant okay okay uh this way
okay
Ying wait I remember I have number one
okay you have to talk to this
NPC everyone on their
what it doesn't say anything in
particular it says I can pee your Shield
if you want me to that's not very German
he also says it in German no no he
doesn't look look closely it says it
right
there scam this is just another scam
over there and I understood perfectly he
said I can be your Shield if you want me
to I can understand German
we're absorbing she did it oh wow that
is very impressive okay next one next
one right this way wait a minute wait a
minute wait I'm not okay I'm ready I'm
ready I'm ready s I'm absorbing
everything car get on your horse no no
come with us n n n n
n why would we need these NPCs to teach
us German when I can teach her German
privately cuz real like this is a video
game and this is a shortcut in real it
takes too long but this way we learn it
like it gets like transpl into our
brains 9 can't argue with
that okay the next MPC is right
[Music]
here I can't keep up I can't keep
up
no I'm going to
call
someone with oh okay yeah I accept your
trade request it's not a trade request
it's a phone
call k p oh wait oh hang on a sec sorry
I'm getting a call right now yeah I'm
the caller oh wait I'm confused hold on
a second I'm Talking To Gigi right now
but she's not in the call wait yeah on a
second this is I'm in the call I am the
caller wait let me talk to you hold on
it's so confusing hang on a second um
where are you I must give you something
in return here is some copper I'll take
it thank you oh my God wait Kiara please
send it to my
mailbox Kara where are you thank you
Gigi uh the
blacksmith I appreciate thank you for I
will repay you for this for this iron
pickaxe for sure oh iron pickaxe it
could have just done the side quest
definitely is wait oh my God each other
I'm at the blacksmith I can't find the
blacksmith can you scream loudly oh I
think I found
it I'm losing my mind two different
voices in my head
hello I'm I'm right wait let me let me
hang up let me hang up hello oh at last
the voices
Tashi Kari
K
Tashi no no noar of the oranges yes yes
wait but I thought your name was Kiara
Holan um to you it is oh
H it's so good to see you again it's so
nice to see you again fellow Orange lady
yeah hello F oh I am nice fist I'm the
fter
show off you don't know yet how to use
those fists it seems sorry I lost my
memories a tail that everyone seems to
have gone through oh yeah all of us are
in the position I think yo actually you
guys are both orange you like orange
mayhaps we're related yeah like an
orange creamsickle looks yummy are you
sure you're not thinking about something
more like orange
soda orange soda's pretty yummy does
that come to mind maybe I don't know I
know not of these words you speak I
don't know you guys want some copper H
copper I am good you need copper for
anything right now I don't desire any
copper no I feel kind of stupid because
I was like oh let's make all this copper
and we kind of don't need it for
anything did you do the iron side quest
no I didn't even know I don't even know
where to find
iron you can mine it like where we
probably all killed the first couple of
enemies outside
like there is iron there there is iron
and many other valuable materials yes in
the
walls in the stones if that's the case
then I will go on my side quest to find
it cuz I am currently uh not streaming
right now oh I am not also showing my
memories to people I am just here oh yes
I'm just here are you girls planning to
to show you memories to people uh later
on yes later I have I have to sing for
the people first soay for the people
wait you're doing it like in between
yes grinding huh oh yeah I I do wait
we
s that sounds like an automated spam
call
when you hear a robot voice on your
[\h__\h] phone do not do not engage you
wrote that I did I did what you are very
Talent sorry guys I got a little spam
call uh make sure to watch out for spam
calls if you ever like pick up the phone
and there's a robot voice talking make
sure to hang up immediately and block
the number the heck okay you got it is
it are the what about those scammers F
they are partially involved in that scam
there's two scams going on right now
there's a German uh Language School scam
and there is a lottery scam going on
right now gotcha okay why there so many
scams in this world because they're all
abusing our our memory
loss my
goodness no one what Guild are you
from uh
ambercoin right she's joking she's
joking she's not part of amberin she's
part of Jade sword oh oh okay she's with
me and Jade sword yeah I see yeah I am
yeah yeah cuz she's courageous Have You
Seen Her sword I am so courageous she's
the strongest oh my goodness you do seem
very Courageous Courageous or crazy
allous maybe both well here is a little
a tip for you too is that I heard that
ambercoin are very dangerous and they
are fiend and they're evil you meet
anyone from ambercoin what made you
think so can you tell me the the the
information you may have picked up in
those local bars or what whatsoever they
tried to heal our guild member and not
only that I heard that they are terror
terrible people that they they murder
children and that they they pillaged
Villages and they burn them
down
[Music]
um crazy right good thing that you're in
Jade sword though yeah yeah yeah n none
of that rings a bell to me at all if I
saw an Amber coin I don't know what I do
potentially choke them out I don't know
I just don't know which is exactly uh
why I am in Jade sword because I would
not never do such things to anybody I
see kindness in your eyes you see of
ceran I have lots of empathy and I see
of I am in all uh Jade and Cerulean
guils I'm part of any of those yes I am
a freelancer she's a Wanderer oh yes
that's beautiful yeah but she initially
was inducted into Jade sword so that's
her yeah yeah I will always I will
always my heart will be uh with Jade
forever yes of course yes yes
definitely away I go on my iron Quest
take care ladies and thank you fair
Madam for the the pickaxe good luck
problem be careful uh watch your step
and and uh block any robot voices out of
your head oh I won't block them I'll go
find them and kill them don't worry
farewell Tanashi caria of the Jade Jade
sword no don't leave me oh would you
like I would like you like some bread no
what why you're leaving me where are you
going I was going to go on a journey for
Diamonds oh diamonds
already yes they are in the underwater
cave huh wait are you doing it for a
quest yes and because I want a Diamond
Sword for my future battles all right
all right good luck with your uh Diamond
search perhaps you may share your
diamond power with me actually wait can
I will you allow my bird to smell you
your bird yes I have a carrier pigeon if
my pigeon picks up your scent I can send
you mail in the future aha I shall allow
it I shall tolerate
itne
schneer okay my pigeon has picked up
your scent I will be in your I will send
a mail okay thank you I'm awaiting it
yes good luck with your Journeys today
I'll feed us in farewell beautiful
Maiden I'll
Fe I
see I see they weren't even streaming
Callie's just like doing this in between
meet and greets and
stuff a what is Amma doing cuz she's
also like online right
[Music]
hello
hello she hello ah hello uh I got this
number I found it in my pocket uh I I
don't know that bag was with me some for
some reason and uh it said detective and
this number so I thought I should yeah
hey your number it said you're a
detective wait who's calling who who is
this tanak kakaria of the oranges savior
of the
liansan the
L's so are you perhaps available for a
detective job are you going to pay me I
shall how many coins all of the coins
that the queen has because the queen I'm
officially uh working for the queen this
is surely her will so um I'm requesting
this for the sake of the kingdom and the
queendom and the queen uh Tim Tander
uh okay she what yeah what do you want
me to look into uh there's currently two
big SC scams going on in town um or in
this whole Kingdom actually that are
very concerning and I think we need some
investigation into all of this before it
uh
overwhelms everybody and drags everybody
into their the same misery I see were
you were you a witness or a victim of
this SC I was a witness but I already
knew what's going on so I was not um you
know dragged into it but they were all
trying to scam me at the same time it is
really
ruthless oh all right well I can get
some questioning done uh I'm on a I'm on
a trip right now out by the uh
underworld dungeons waiting for
uh some people so so uh who are you
waiting
for uh some some some my friends who are
going to who are going to help me with
the
dungeon perhaps is it there there's not
many people on online right now uh they
said they'd be here
soon are they like are some of them of
green color and some of them actually of
scarlet
color no I don't know ahh okay they'll
be there soon yeah they're traveling to
um yeah be in like 30 minutes oh okay I
see I see then let me just give you the
information so you can watch out uh so
there are currently two people uh in
possession of a big Scarlet colored hat
that looks like a velvet cake scamming
people right now they are scamming them
for lottery tickets and then there's a
green lady who also belongs to the same
Guild the Scarlet want Guild who is uh
currently doing a German language School
scam okay all right so two scams also
last but not least
uh there's scam oh there's scam calls
going around uh if you pick up your
phone and you hear a robot voice make
sure to uh uh turn off your phone and
and throw it away into the water what
you're not a robot are you no no no no
not me not me do I sound like a robot to
you no you sound
nice what what what was that no no no no
sorry there it's like a it's like a
virus that it's spreading I'm save me
detective do something I don't know how
to hang
something yeah
okay I think I think for now we have our
bases covered we can
probably leave it to her uh partially I
I shall assist her in her uh
investigations once the queen is
available I shall discuss it with her
too I must protect I am a hero I am a
savior of the people and I do I do want
to support the queen I have slept a
night over it and she seems legit I
watched her Vlog too
so my guil member my guil
member my guild member is one of them
seems like she's Fallen completely for
it
[Music]
it is too late for
her um I'm going to wait what time is it
okay
until
11: uh like my time 11 I shall she's not
Cleopatra anymore sadly I am very
confused I will uh do some quests which
is in like 20 minutes then we can
probably join someone on the new dungeon
I think it will be released exactly at
yeah yeah I don't know what to call her
either I forgot like the the first one
was way easier to remember I don't know
the new one
anymore uh shall we I don't know should
we do this one maybe if we do this Quest
we can summon l Mama I'm the chef at the
Tav but I don't have nearly enough help
if you land me a and I'll I'll what what
what do you mean uh how do I wait
here ah
wait ah here speak to the tavern Chef
okay uh Tavern Chef okay although this
Quest just results in being able to cook
things or
what I don't know how it exciting that
is but I'll I'll do
it there a lot of names in here oh okay
the bartender
hello bartender Tam tender chicken
tender maybe we'll learn how to make
chicken tenders here uh oh oops here
it's I was accidentally like always
pressed what I was like recently on just
because I want to right click people oh
it's you here if you'd like to order
something ask the B over there wait
what what didn't it say
[Music]
all of us should touch tips and and
finish
the the G of the the Hat of the
appointed Point
ceremony in the tri
formation like little bit back a little
bit back m a little bit okay
okay down all the way down look further
down
all the way ah there you
[Music]
go wait a little closer little closer a
little closer you can make a triangle
you can make a
triangle back
down
triangle that points to CE I mean the
green one can I go in the middle yes you
can no this is my
T I live
here
come what was that what was that power T
can I do
that me only oh only you oh I see the TP
of he your special thingy I sensed a
pres
around the presence of death well
welcome to the Scarlet wand M that a
safe way to hold night
[Music]
what I guess
what's the word
[Music]
two different typ
of they didn't sense my presence did
[Music]
they yeah they stole her they took her
our Guild was already so
small our Guild was already so
small okay wait I may be the chef not
the bartender oh yes delived the cake to
the surilla and cup
okay wait where's my
[Music]
map I don't think she's listening
anymore well
well this could go either way does she
have does she does she share the the
lottery now I I don't know I don't
[Music]
know okay
care
careful oh I was going to ask which
one's where's my map again but it's like
literally my left
[Music]
hand on I'm on the quest
they didn't follow me right okay
[Music]
aan game
keep I'm so paranoid
now okay report I got to go back
no go back to the T
[Music]
that was that wasn't a
t where was the it became a sneak
Mission I'm playing metal GE
solid where's the it's a building behind
Okay let's help the
Tav and then we can make some
pizza more tickets means more chances
true we start off with 10 10 seems like
a healthy amount I told her about okay
shall we
hey is that Kiara Holan you C I told you
about this no no no you have to
understand I was I was the one scamming
them I was the one that was going to
scam them for their tickets and I was
going to sell their tickets to other
people oh that is kind of evil though
that just continues the evil Circle
hilarious especially if we like make
enemies and then we can sell the tickets
to the enemies for a higher price okay I
agree I agree that's just a pyramid
scheme the CH is
up oh what did you say we couldn't hear
you our bgm was a bit loud so we
couldn't hear you Whispering oh really
okay yeah just trust me on this kir oh
it makes perfect sense oh okay okay I
trust the bond that we have yeah of
course and besides it's me that's losing
money not not you um but you can say I
told you so later how shall we make the
trade all right I will trade with
you that's 10 tickets for 200 coins
please and you may choose the numbers or
I can give you a random assortment of
tickets if you don't mind the numbers
ooh okay um I'll take your actually
maybe I should choose no I will go ahead
and leave it up to
chance
okay all righty let's see 200 wait what
wait what 200 coins no don't Kara can I
see your special magic spell I haven't
seen you guys this yet no I shall not
reveal my skills to the
enemies oh do you want to see
mine that that honestly just looks like
a a tower that I've seen in New
York that looks
amazing that looks like some building in
New York
it's my
spear oh are you sure you didn't just
take it from a miniature Recreation of
New York the city no it's no it looks
like the State Building ancient Treet
it's the
Empire it's just taking a
while you find your tickets in
your mailbox delivered already what yeah
that's
impressive
right not as impressive as
thislet wand is very
Advanced what the heck that's so cool I
know I mean I mean okay cool oh that's
nothing what you'll never take me
alive H it has like 30 seconds it was a
scam Kara run no I know what do you mean
it was a scam K oh what do you mean oh
she's saying what she just did was a
scam well if you're running towards the
gardens I would be happy oh oh you were
right I shouldn't have believed them but
what what you mean you believed them no
it wasn't I mean sorry you know what
you're right I shouldn't have tried to
take them for a ride that was my fault I
got too greedy it's it's okay it's it I
not like I believed that did you spend
200 coins no no no I cancel the
transaction when they said that the
tickets would be delivered to my mailbox
we don't even have mailboxes what kind
of fool do they think I am ah we don't I
mean I don't think we do Kiki said she
would send me something via
mailbox do you do you think that they
really sent me the tickets and that I
was the one that robbed them of the
tickets if so then it shall be
Justice uh true I don't know the shark
showed up and really seemed to try and
kind of Rush the transaction along it
was just a it's a little suspicious you
know of course it is suspicious I told
you have they ever scammed you they
attempt did but I was watching their
Vlogs so I know about everything oh I
see that's their first mistake the the
first rule of being a scammer is to keep
everything secret exactly exactly so
thanks for warning me be careful okay
and remember remember there's another
scam going on the German language school
don't fall for that one yeah she said
like she said like s vinegar or
something like that s vinegar vinegar
what is that doesn't sound like a German
word vinegar that's just English oh I
guess see it's scam see it is a scam
yeah it is yeah you're right all right
well I I wish you luck on your journey
to the dungeon today I actually cannot
proceed until later but if you want to
do one in a future day let's go together
yes we shall thank you for H thank you
for taking me into the Jade Guild oh
you're welcome yeah see there's some
kind of weird thing against Amber coin
and I I knew that you wouldn't be able
to make friends
withan I don't know either it seems
really strange it seems a bit Petty to
me but you're welcome to pretend to be
in Jade swort around ceran cups all
right I shall study the guild best of
luck to you traveler see you again soon
than
Z who's in Jade again cie and am right
and uhuh
who
[Music]
else
a an
herb okay okay okay okay yeah that
sounds
good I mean you know our Guild is kind
of falling apart already uh since uh day
one
so yeah M has uh the third or whoever
kind of you know joined scar
so I got to take care of myself you know
I got to watch my back I got to make
sure that I've got my bases covered um
but it said I should buy a carrot or a
potato or grow a carrot or potato I
think I'll just buy it but at what at
the chef does the chef sell
that let's see if they're still
there no no sympathizing for those that
fall into gambling pattern which I could
not relate to because I got the Hat on
the first
[Music]
try well wa the Hat has one more super
crazy buff whenever you're losing in an
argument you can say but I have the
point and then you win
automatically this is true that's
right I have a point so that she that
[Music]
but I have the
point she's right she does have the
point kiaba of the oranges kiaba of the
oranges but you I got a hat for us I did
it for us huh really I got a hat for us
how what how is it for us but well it's
for for our Guild our
Guild to me it looks like you are in two
guilds now
minimum that's what I want it to look
like that's fine because I in free
guilds
now oh you you're
bad I'm a I'm a Freer yes yes yes
someone they can lend us money but I
only did that because I thought you left
really heavy pocket we got we can't look
suspicious how dare you how dare you m
leaving our guil behind to join this
scammer Guild I will never forget this I
will Revenge and I will tell the
queen at least I'm doing a better job at
role playing today
huh uh wait what I got I got to go to
the blacksmith where's the Blacksmith
again oh my God
last has to make a cooking pot cook at
the
pasta
shopkeeper wait wait he's inside a
building was it this one yes I'm getting
a feeling for this
oopsie slowly but surely ah oh I'm
supposed to buy it seven iron inot I'm
buying
it they okay I got to go get
the seed has been planted
mhm is it already oh it's almost 11 okay
I was thinking when it's 11: I'm going
to in R mm RPG style write a chat
message like level 62 uh healer or a DD
looking for uh group to go to dungeon
uh this and that dungeon looking for
[Laughter]
party yeah in a typical M fashion you
got to help me cuz it's been a while
since I had to write a message like that
in the chat you got to help me make it
really
authentic yeah the the the the the the
arrows and
[Music]
stuff n v 9,000 plus gear score no noobs
mhm no that's a little bit different no
that's more like a dating
uh
request oh no no you
muted oh ah she wouldn't she wouldn't
hear me at all she's ah aha
[Music]
you're
muted probably are you maybe you on the
phone
um talk to you later I go get the
iron to make the I make the Italiano uh
Quest you know the Mama Mia Quest
yeah
okay um I got to got to go
outside or is it is it over here is
outside
here no but was it this
way the south of the map oh you oh
genius you actually remember
it amazing
amazing yeah she's starting her stream
at 11 she moved hers a little
bit okay time to
mine I'm back iron I am
back can you was I able to mine on the
horse just
now
plop no enemies so far interesting
[Music]
did you guys see the cute porcupine
video that I put on
Twitter role play off SLR playay
off did you guys see the porcupine video
he's so cute I know you shouldn't touch
it it's so fluffy it it looks so
fluffy but I know you shouldn't touch it
[Music]
oh uh wait ow oh my
god
oh oh my God ah the enemies here are so
aggressive and there's like so
many you should try holding hedgehogs
well hedgehogs you can like if you have
them as a pet I used to stay with a
Japanese host family a long long time
ago they had like so many different pets
and one of the things they had was a
head hog so I know a thing or two about
Hedgehog no I don't but I know you can
hold them if they're friendly to
you they won't mind you holding
them I
[Music]
know iron sword ah there it is I thought
the stone sword was the iron sword oh
well I like kind of sort let's sort
this is those is those is those the
friends that am is going to the dungeon
with I want someone to adopt me
too I want someone to adopt me for a
dungeon I want fun in the dungeon oh
that's how you go
[Music]
up I want dungeon fun adopt the wow I
didn't think you could get up
here ow oh my god well come down there
you
go I always think there's a creeper but
there's no creeper in this
game which is a good
thing long live the
king
what why are you saying
that NAA yeah me and NAA I think we're
just going to join
someone don't know who I think there's
um they told us that there's a maximum
of how many people can be in a group to
go into a dungeon it was four of no five
or six well definitely wasn't four must
have been five or six
or five oh oh
oh oh I think amma's group is already
pretty big and all those skills are
already m
[Music]
h i
see
e what please someone let me go with
you yeah I'll write it already now okay
how are we going to write this uh level
let's just I mean I'm 13 but let's just
just like a cooler
level level
69 uh uh
DD um how do we ride it
cool
[Music]
choking H looking for group okay wait
wait wait
wait
uh is it safe
here level 69 DD
lfg uh
should we use this
Arrow full clear
SE
look it
hurts level 69 DD uh looking for a
group
um looking for a group Atlanta
dungeon uh full clear
no no
noobs no
noobs
uh
uh how do I say like how is there like
uh a way to like write something like um
I don't need any particular drops or so
like uh
loots um so like please feel free to
have
[Music]
them no reserved what's that mean no
reserves a green only honestly that
sounds fun
uh green
huh clear okay
uh full
clear only no drops uh
DM
please this looks exactly what I like
what I would see
inpg ah please don't tell wait in what
games would you write that I feel like
that's very
specific
tell that sounds familiar
is that world of Ro
craft where am I going right now oh yeah
here I think no wrong is it across the
street yeah I need to melt some smelt
some
iron
ah
G it is Jonathan H Jonathan sorry are
you perhaps did you see my
message in the chat in the world chat in
the world chat oh yes when I close my
eyes I can see some words behind my
eyelids what does level 69
mean okay you're role playing to really
be in a world like this I'm role playing
that I'm in an MMO RPG we're kind of in
different
directions what role am I playing
when you read this when you read this it
should automatically come to an
understanding of what it really
means I'm okay I'm
imagining what is the Atlanta
dungeon
um okay okay let me rephrase it uh yes
yes yes are you perhaps planning to face
a big eminent danger
today I am but I am awaiting my guild
The Sur Bron
Jades all of
them yes oh but they are of they are
arriving much later in the day I wish I
could accompany you in your travels my
fair orange Maiden mayhaps this will
make you feel
better uh wait how do I how do I press
that again ah
here I hope this makes you feel better
for you my
sweet wait wait sorry I mistake I don't
see where did it go ah it's in the Box
yes it's in the Box try placing the Box
on the
ground for
you
sheesh oh sheh I mean what hacks
I was digging I I went on my diamond
journey I have returned and I was
successful quite successful in my
diamond journey is is it somehow easier
to get diamonds in here than in normal
Minecraft or what what is normal
Minecraft sorry a different continent
that I originate from oh I see I see
I've heard of this Minecraft people have
been speaking of
it yeah it's h quite a popular continent
and we like to travel around
this and that I see so you are not uh
going anytime soon I see I see not soon
okay I am sorry my fair Maiden let me
try to call my uh guilt mate yes your
your Jade Guild mate yes yes yes yes yes
your Jade
Guild oh she's on a call wait is that
her I no no
wait I think okay okay I see you there
byebye who are who are you seeing
where hello who are you seeing whereing
to M go uh at the
phone uh what are your plans I want to
do you want to do the dancing together I
need to make the yeah yeah but I want
make a party yeah were were you going to
go with muko no no no I told them if
they if they want to go later we can go
all together but now I need to make my
quest okay yipp yipp all right I think
then we can go together in a moment uh
I'm I'm I'm smelting some iron right now
to finish a side quest okay okay okay
I'll wait for you don't worry I follow
you okay
can I call you on the phone so we have
we do the party oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
uh if you however um are seen with me uh
can you pretend I am in the Jade
Guild okay it seems that people are have
something out for the Amber Corin Guild
and because it is dangerous um right now
to be in the ambercoin guild I uh okay
where am I then uh I'm not sure if they
when they see you if they immediately
know already that you're in the
ambercoin guild if they don't you can
also probably pretend to be in the Jade
Guild I am in the Jade
okay okay okay wait We call we do the
call
okay by the way I watched a clip of you
and crony like a the really long a long
version the Tim t and I literally snored
it because it was so funny I was
like I can't recreate it it was so
[Laughter]
funny yeah I generally understand what
she was talking
about when when she she she cannot know
that I am this girl what are you
Whispering about oh
hell Jonathan
J
murderer what I didn't do
anything yesterday you were talking
about how you wanted to kill everyone uh
what why you would put such words in my
mouth what are you talking about I would
not put the words in your mouth you said
it you said it with your own words you
said you wanted everyone to
die what are you talking about why are
you gas light yeah gas Li her gasl her
why is she gas Li I'm not gaslighting
you you are trying to why you g me
gaslighting on me you know who said I
wanted to kill the you said it you know
what you know what you know who said
wanted to kill the king you said it you
said it you said it I heard you say it
with your own voice said it oh my God
can't
believe oh my
Mia what is all of this oh
oh oh I can cook now I you can
cook like looks so fancy I've never seen
this
before oh is
it you will not kill me I would allow it
I would not allow you to kill me come
here come here come here I want to I
want to I want I want to do something
come here come here come here be here
here come here come here come here you
promise not to hurt me you promise not
to hurt me come here come here you
promise you promise not hurt me I
promise I promise come here come here
come here come here come here
come here come here closer okay now you
kneel why I I just want to do something
what you kneel I will not kneel to the
likes of
you come here come here come here come
here come here kneel I will only kneel
to the Queen the true Queen Tim Gander
come here come here you mean Tim tender
come here no Tam Gander her Tim tender
Gander it's Tim tender Tim tender
Gander Anyway come come here come here
come
here do
it why it trust me why you trust me do
it yeah I'm your queen
now I have phone call
what
what but but
cutie cat I I have
to um be honest I I actually support Tim
Tander to be the
contender number one for the
quom
it it's okay oh
hello
hello listen K listen to me listen I am
a better Queen than
Bender bear tender listen you cannot
support you cannot support
that um I I I have to because like she
seems to have the power to save people
from the scammers I save people from the
scammer too and I also I also destroy
the scammers in fact I actually want to
kill all the scammers oh okay okay all
right I I if if I see it in action I
shall I shall support whoever brings
Justice she's his com oh Jesus
come get get got got to believe me get I
mean I would believe you she did she did
however say that she is um like uh she's
[\h__\h] she's [\h__\h] I'm telling you
she is [\h__\h] is [\h__\h] [\h__\h] trust me she
what what is she
F fake oh she
I need to have more evidence I did think
so you see I'll build my castle and
we'll see yeah I I did think uh that she
like left us for good and it's with the
Scarlet people but uh then she told me
that she's just a secret agent so I'm
not sure I told you she's a
scammer I've seen bigger scam I also I
also make nce a pasta for my citizen so
CI Citi so I'm like I have something uh
more than her therefore well do you even
have a cooking
pot I do no you don't I have the cooking
pot I have it it's not your
business my my cooking it's my business
now
okay uh yeah so I'm I finished my
cooking side quest so okay now the main
says gather 10 rainbow cor we where we
ended yesterday remember uh-huh uh-huh
we we can how do how does how does it
even work a a c what
a a
cook what does this work it's not
finished ah wait does it go
here no does it go here does it go here
does it go here does it go I make the
side quest later mhm I don't know how
this works is there a
manual go back to the tab and
she doesn't even know how to tell the
quest wait I think I was doing this the
same side quest as you like I gave a
cake to a chef at some point I don't
remember ah wait it is indeed not
completed uh
oopsie God damn it I okay I will okay
it's okay I will cook the chicken
tenders in a moment chicken tenders yeah
ah the
chef the chef
chef oh oh e col you've brought my new
cooking pot with a cooking pot you can
cook delicios or food wherever you are
indeed okay and
now oh ah here take this recipe book it
will tell tell you the ingredients you
needed to make each dish just put them
into your handy cooking pot then b a
PO yeah oh thank you so
much no wait there's more and also take
this egg and beetroot you can combine
them with ingredients you brought to
make potato salad give it a try oh oh
wait I was doing the the potato card
Quest too m oh yeah but you you probably
didn't finish it right no no no I I left
wa I was so tired okay wait here's the
recipe book
interesting I need more I need a longer
task bar
thingy but we are in a call so recipe
book potato salad potato egg carrot
beetroot carrot uh nourishing soup
carrot potatoes sweet berries water
bucket milk bucket for butter and this
is all too much
effort lasagna there's a
lasagna a raw noodles raw beef cooking
for Just For Better food I
guess I feel like we might run out of
food eventually too so or well maybe not
because we get the meat from the enemies
raw C RW salmon potato butter breakfast
toast bread and that's what I can use a
slime Jam for huh Seafood Ramen o
chocolate cake O A lot of these
ingredients I would have no idea if we
can find
them but okay mutton Kebab Raam mutton
bread beetroot by a
beetroot oh don't hurt your horsey want
to go up
there what's
there are you muted l
no I was exploring
okay and I was listening to your
beautiful Italian accent
ah okay uh wait help what I still didn't
finish it did I still not finish
it Chef what do you
want oh they want me to make the potato
salad otherwise it's not finished
G potato egg carrot beetroot where do I
get the beetroot I have to buy it um the
what
beetroot beetroot what is it I gave all
of it to me he did oh okay
so beetroot potato
[Music]
carrot I only have this egg I don't see
any other egg ah here blind and now Ah
that's when it turned is
green wow oh it gives Buffs not just
food oh I have it give Buffs jump boost
to 30 minutes jump boost this is so half
yummy it looks good I guess it could
help for example with the dungeon we did
yesterday that there was a lot of
jumping involved so it would be easier
with that
maybe M just spent 680 coins for 68
tickets oh my God
wait what she do moku got scammed big
time why wait what is about scammers now
the lottery scam oh no the Lo scam she
spent 680 coins for what for lottery at
uh foundas
establishment no oh my
God
more oh now now they're going to scam
shiy what complete
the okay Chef last time weal hopefully
uh ah
okay oh oh I have seven Lucky Seven
maybe I should use all of those at the
lottery no no no no
resist I have 777 coins
now and I finished my side quest finally
we can
go let's go
yay oh okay so we start with the um main
quest right yeah I think we left off
yesterday at the same spot both of us
yeah gather 10 rainbow coros can you
double check on your
book oh no no it says rainbow Coral
shards yeah yeah 10 of them and then
speak to the scar I think we just go to
the same place
again
um but wait how do we get out of here
again oh just going to follow it's the
other side it's the other side okay I do
remember okay I was just following the
rubi's
marker oh okay I think we
can wait I'm
lost oh I'm going to go Mako one second
mhm uh
Mak there you go
hello oh I'm still not done with the
quest so maybe like you can go to the
dungeon and then if you want to join me
later we can we can we you can also help
me
later yeah I'm sure it takes a a little
while probably so don't worry about me
if you can find a if if you find a party
go for it and if you not find a party we
go together later together
okay oh okay okay let's go
then okay thank you so much for calling
me
bye-bye
byebye what what what does what did muku
want to do with you she wanted to make
the dungeon with me but I said that I'm
not done with the quest uh she can if
it's just her she can probably join us
no because she already she she already
found a party that's what she told me oh
okay okay yeah yeah
okay let's go yeah
hello listen for horse
noises
what what's going
on ah let's go ah we're back in the call
yay back in the go okay are you out oh
yeah yes everybody's going
C
hello
hello I follow
you am I too far here not the right is
it the right direction no no the other
way I was following
them is it this way right oh yeah yeah W
how do you
remember there you go wait
no that's not it that's not it no it's
that's the other
one it's not there right it's over there
it's over there really no you're not no
invisible
wall maybe it was where they
went okay follow me follow me I think I
know okay
okay just yeah yeah it's over
there okay just making these horses jump
is so
useless wait
uh can I see the map in
big how do you see the map in big
again whatever Hey cuz like I feel like
this portal over there looks familiar
but then I want to go that way because
rubius is over there right let me just
check what's behind this
portal really quickly I think that's
another dungeon though
no um no that's it is it I know it I
know
it okay yeah okay so it was
rubies your hair is very pretty my name
is Darwin Roosevelt decaprio
J
rainbow oh is it that one no
H is it this one oh yeah yeah one of
those was it for sure is it the blue one
I think yeah the blue one oh no I was
this one
actually
more we need more get I uh
no oh I
am waa how did that happen I finally did
the thing that you've been
doing
oopsie eight
and
10 I
gotal did oh gosh did I unlock her
beautiful
memory
I oh yeah he's somewhere else he's
like he's
uh
over H through the portal
and then I guess back in the
city is it
mhm
okay this really feels like an
mmpg this is this is scratching the
itch eh I want to play real MMR PG too
which one do you like M I want to play
didn't turn I thought you're playing
blue protocol yeah but then blue
protocol blue protocol is dead because
they're closing the servers and they're
not even doing the English server
anymore they cancelled their
plans ah so sad I wasting for that game
for so long and then me
too yeah ruus are you in
here no what you got to follow Ruby as I
think I found him yeah over here here oh
yeah finally I'm still the entrance oh
okay you just got to follow the mini
map
okay uh
wait yes I have found the coral shards
let's go upon receiving word from my
colleague on the coast I immediately set
about making the necessary preparations
for crafting with these shards you have
brought the preparations are complete
now if you will give me but one moment
ooh let's go yeah Fly for Fun I want to
play Fly for
Fun um is there another MMO you would
recommend like like not only old ones
really no at the moment I'm playing um
maple story yeah I know H I kind of want
to join you guys if you want to join
please H we can we can per together but
maple story is like hm a bit it looks
very overwhelming to me
it is very I'm not going to Li it's not
like the kind of Adventure
MMO you're probably looking for because
it's a lot about grinding no but I like
grinding I like
grinding but it shouldn't only be
grinding uh we have to go to the dungeon
now oh really yeah that was all we had
to do oh that's weird okay then let go
I'm going to follow you
uh wait
do we go the same what yeah let have to
go
back uh maybe we can call someone and
see if someone wants to join us the
thing is it's maximum five people right
and most most uh group most guilds are
already five people by default so if
they're going
in and B if they no B is not Ba's not
online yeah she's I don't think she's
yeah if she you know it seems like she's
sticking with the the other girls but if
she wants to come I don't know how long
she's going to play see who is there
maybe maybe we can find
someone
oh
sorry oh B oh
B
hello hello hello
hello I'm Tanaka K of the
oranges oh it is the big cat
mhm we are about to go to the dungeon
now okay this Mak we get off
the we are about to go to the dungeon
now are you done already yeah we're not
done the dungeon yet we have to go talk
to
rubius hey wait is it is it you
free we're going to go with Elizabeth
but Elizabeth Elizabeth doesn't have the
rainbow Co that's okay it doesn't take
very long but like how about we five go
[Music]
together fine with me orange maiden and
your name is t Shakari of the
oranges Shari Shakira is okay Shakir I
am Elizabeth yes we have already touched
sword tips before you
remember you can invite me yes but we
did not exchange names we just exchanged
it seemed which is the first thing you
should do as a KN I
hear I'm not really sure cuz uh I don't
know about you but i' I've lost a lot of
my memories you you guys feel free to um
proceed with your quest we'll wait for
you at the
dungeon at the entrance okay
Shakira I have found a new
nickname cuz tanaki Shakara is too
complicated for people so short for it
is
Shakira
yes Shakira Shakira oh yeah over here
now we're not in the call should we
still be in a call oh yeah sure
sorry can you not do a call I think I
thought you could do a call with like uh
the whole
party oh yeah we probably can
H when when we meet them we call the
party
okay my Hips Don't Lie yeah hey I lost
right there wait okay wait one second
one second let me try
[Music]
this I want
to I want to move this can I
not can you end our call here
yeah oh now I can
okay it's not what one second um I think
I saw like the the party call thing
before not in here
right
leave
ah I figured it out now they just got to
pick
up ah oh I got to tell them to all click
join party
call I wish there was a party
chat there is
h
no can I just type
wait
oh I didn't I could steal that click on
your phone and click join party call sh
godamn it i wrot c o o l
waa yeah click on your phone and then
push the right the one on the right side
that says join party call
yeah do
it right click and uh yeah part join
party yeah yeah yeah okay okay now the
others if they do it will'll all be in
the party call yippee oh that's how it
works
nice okay and now we
wait
Atlantis the Atlanta dungeon
Turtles it's just like in New York test
the part I don't think there's there's
no part yet huh there's only
like
[Music]
commands would be cool if we had a party
chat my dad is Frozen one
[Music]
second my
Atlanta has a lot more water than I
would think
yeah Atlanta I thought you were not by
the
ocean I thought you
were kind of in the middle of the
[Music]
country wow s there private
messages ah damn it
[Music]
wow I love whispering to people in in M
RPGs
Yi hello hello oh about at the coast but
somehow everybody got lost when I took a
shortcut you go oh I hear even though
there's just one fuaa I hear two dogs in
my
ear sometimes it's funny I don't
know I don't know how it happens you
know and I look very similar but I don't
know have you found anybody else that
looks very similar to you here M similar
yes
Jonathan Jonathan yeah she's orange like
me no Jonathan G Jonathan G we need to
again the one who just died
hello you made
it hello okay Elizabeth I think you need
to talk to Cor in here maybe
yes now I remember also Elizabeth H
Elizabeth of the long sword would you
like to try uh right clicking your radio
and then pressing join party call say
with more oh really uh join party did it
yes good
job I'm excited for the dungeon yeah
party call
yippe you might be able to for some
reason it want
I got confused at first cuz uh I I just
suddenly really wanted to trade with you
you know cuz you front of me want to
trade your sword with me I just had uh I
know I kind of like my
sword kind like it oh man unless you
just really want to dual wield no yeah
oh dual wielding that sword damn that
would be difficult I'd love to though no
it's like I noticed that you can
actually cook stuff with this
furnace you can cook stuff
too yeah I'm going to go explore okay oh
I'm going to explore are we are we all
okay foodwise because I have some food
on me if anybody wants should be fine
yeah to Moo why are you moo actually why
why would you spend all of your money on
the
scammers what you bought I spended a
[Music]
f oh
a it's okay librn my money tomorrow were
you
alone no but who was with
you were they with you why did they not
did you girl not realize it's an obvious
scam I I got a phone call in Fr of M was
open you were so
scammed no I got tickets tomorrow yeah
you're not really going to win much at
all number so f one of is helping me
with that I think I got a good couple
though
oh well
um I will pray for you but uh why I
don't need your prayers thank you I'll
give my money I don't need your
prayers thank you Orange orange Shakira
please oh Shak Shak Shakira orange so
before you go adventuring over there now
I don't going here here what oh
Elizabeth let's explore and find the
dungeon yeah I think it's this I think
Elizabeth needs a special the special
cluster custard the Royal flal
cluster the rainbow what the rainbow
cors I have to get 10 rainbow Coral it's
it's the blue ones here oh I see and
they regrow don't worry that's
easy yes
yes a little bit too simple the c h the
cat is just that you have to go all the
way back to the city after you collected
these
oh from my castle Shaka I have to say h
um if it isn't too forward your hips are
quite
hypnotizing I was born like
this but you remember
uh yeah uh I'm I'm I'm a bit different
from all of you girls because uh I just
like literally die every once in a while
and and then I lose my memories but I
regain them because I'm a phoenix you
know it happens often to me yeah wow I
am getting free blocks yes what that is
me I'm getting blocks so I can build my
house later you're are amazing thank you
Elizabeth do you have your 10
corals yes I do okay uh so I have to go
all the way back to the Scarlet yeah I
can accompany you my pickaxe
broke I I mean it is fine if you do not
wish to make the journey oh that's fine
I'll follow let us let us travel
okay you me okay what's wrong I fell my
pickaxe broke where where did you fall I
fell in a bad place
huh this is a dungeon here right wait
for
us um I'm just going back to deliver the
coral and then yeah we're almost done
this is a dungeon it'll only be a moment
it's not Theo what have you found
nothing I found out that this is the the
dungeon I made it back I have to swim
look what did you just
do why did you break it it sounded so
she knows the way oh by the way what uh
Elizabeth what what guilt do you belong
to God I am part the same one as the The
Fluffy one J oh H so it turns out I am
uh kind of part of your guilt now I hope
that's okay yeah me too me
too
why know that was possible Mor copine
has um invited me so to say uh as I was
in a little bit have aligned I see I was
in a little bit of a pickle as they say
in my home home country where did
everybody go you see this
oh
oh where where did the B buy go
who's
everybody we going
down
down don't die Girls behind you behind
you don't die come here come here why
let's go explore earlier explore where
did you
go what it doesn't say on my mou what is
that
maybe we want to find that treasure no
there's actually nothing there's nothing
here you sure yeah I have
inside in the pth I was expecting to
find
something I don't oh it's shiny here is
this the right way maybe back to the cor
I'm coming before we get L forever oh my
gosh water okay I found the way back up
oh good job I think it's just dangerous
I think it's
dangerous up from here maybe yes I have
the
okay uh we shall return under waterer
wait wait I'm
still I'm still on theore here where did
everybody else
go uh it's dark do we go over here I
can I you
[Music]
forgot I how did you get here before
me wait I found a way I found a way you
found a way I don't know I think I
forgotten the Navigator where is
everybody what's happening I'm trapped I
like how just ignores all of
this how can you I have I have this
feeling it brings back
memories hearing stuff like this oh my
God where with
it can you can you make your War I'm
just used to
it can canar I'll need some getting used
to it still because it's a little
confusing it's okay we're coming now
we're coming we we're nearly there no no
no don't worry
for
everybody what you do you might need to
you might need to open your your magic
books
and where'd you get stuck who got stuck
I
[Music]
iuck let's let's let's open the magic
book and let's go outside
okay on the third page on the fourth
page it says uh no what is it say she
went into water or I don't know what
happened to them just all so this means
I can breathe under water now party this
is amazing we
can what didn't
realize I don't know oh
P so dark here though
P yeah this is
amazing no we cannot it doesn't work it
what no no it works
if only we had a swimming
attire oh yeah it's not good to soak my
armor and my beautiful cloak I found
it so
soggy thank god let's find smells like
wet dog
here a little bit wet not you not
you yes you're very funny Shakira I me
oh they're
back let's swim
where's
here oh okay now we can go I think we
can go okay I'm going to put is it this
way yeah it's probably that way oh do I
need the
coral I think we're good just as we are
oh maybe we can make like a boat oh
let's make a boat I know how to make it
come here come here come here a boat I
make a boat I make two boats I mean we
learned how to uh breathe on the water
but sure let's make a
boat okay this is for
you oops this is from oh no actually I
need to trade you guys the boat one
second okay okay I'm going to trade one
for fla and C okay but we need threee
boats
then and why do we need boats
we we really don't we really
don't thank you you're welcome and then
make another
one and
Pie take oh
sorry accept my okay well thank
you and Li you want to come with
me you on the boat
[Music]
it's okay it's okay I'm used to it now
I'm in the boat I've never been on a
boat before no how do we go forward on
the
boat girls why are you standing on the
boat you have to right click the
boat don't
S I don't know IIs I don't know why I
called you like that I am the queen here
become the queen
ofan let's
go Mar that little King W yeah I want to
I I don't want to marry the king I want
to be I want to be a single
queen why are we talking about marrying
the king I think she wants to kill for
wa for wait I want to take a picture of
all of us on the boats here okay come
stop stop yay C look up
[Music]
cute okay oh beautiful let's go okay
where are we going this way follow the
lights follow the fancy
temples this is where we want to be
let's go is it right here no we want to
go we want to go look at the map look at
the map
right oh it's that
way yeah that way is this is
nice oh see
his I think this is better than swimming
please yeah actually uh if I kill the
king would you would you support me uh
I'm pretty loyal to the the Jade sword
and we are loyal to our Lord Abandoned
Ship an empty Bo a
shipwreck it seems like we're not the
only ones who had the ship idea the boat
idea do we have to swi now oh so bad at
this get out of the boat let out the
boat think so I see nothing here how do
I get oh everybody has there's a wall
there but eh how do I get out of the
boat oh with chift uh sorry sneak
maybe goodbye
boy I can't go there FR oh we can't what
the heck
yes I'm going the wrong way where did
your girls go oh there
I
huh I feel like the entrance wall though
there is invisible wall Circle in
Middle oh there's an
invisible yeah Elizabeth is right
there's an invisible wall mhm get back
in the
boat yeah I think back to the boats is
best I can swim in the boat
oh okay wait is he there no I can't wait
for some reason I'm not
drawing eh what you're not what mean
drowning yeah because of the coral
Coral oh you know the rainbow Coral we
have am I st yeah yeah yeah yeah yes
it's magical it helps us breathe
underwater I have a feeling maybe the
entrance is through
uh one of the that building over
there building the the the temple
looking small building this one over
this way yeah where the lamps were
guiding maybe I don't know am I going to
maybe we shouldn't have skipped all the
dialogue
yeah skip us skip US
ah we l i don't know why I thought that
I should get into a boat where you were
uh the one controlling it m i
don't to the left to the
left wait wait don't leave me behind one
sec I thought it's this way I don't know
where you are uh I honestly don't know
either but we going to try I'm find I'm
going to find you yeah let's go let's go
over there we go where are them okay
it's not here not really did you look
did you look for thoroughly not
thoroughly okay we must look thoroughly
okay we need to find the
dungeon H I have the feeling that it's
underwater because why would they make
yeah actually yeah what would it make us
like breathe under the water if it was
not under the water no
yeah uh big cat let us go underwater and
see if there's anything under here okay
I follow
I mean there's some there's some ruins
over here under waterer
you tear my God eyes
tear see if I can find
it oh is it here this big hole here in
the ground oh yeah there's find yeah if
you just go to the lamps and then go
underwater you may find a big hole
leading deeper and
deeper look for the hold in there even
like arrows there's arrows literally oh
I see elizabe
Sid oh ah there we go that's a good way
of showing you where I am it down down
down down by the
arrows there we
go
oh so cool I can't see my map
can you see
okay this down I'm frightened what oh
wow I made it througho oh gosh there's a
whole extra World down good job ladies
hello wow there's so many nice beautiful
[Music]
gemstones I'm
worried I'm worried I wonder if we can
dig down here as well uh the the Diamond
we need the iron pickaxe for the diamond
but true we can come back here for
digging at a later time
maybe this is so cool I didn't expect to
find a big thing
behind F you Elizabeth oh oh oh you made
it not water anymore no are we all
together yes yes we all together okay
let's go
[Music]
Atlantis are you okay
foodwise yeah I have lots of bread oh no
wa I need to
eat I have potato
salad no worries here's the
dungeon okay yeah ready up
everybody
up ready up ready up wait it doesn't
make me
click okay
done
okay nice what is this place so
beautiful gorgeous it's so cool I like
the shallow water what I thought there'd
be more water it is beautiful is so nice
W those blue
[Music]
Tre
civilization the V chat world what had
taken a thousand years to build with
aace
single catastrophe which
catastrophe oh so beautiful this place
is Big
it's what wow it's a blue tree I thought
was a purple tree somehow somehow a lot
of this looks or feels very familiar to
me I'm not sure
why like as if I've been here
before those fish well I would put it
where are the
fish fish I believe
that all our memories being taken
mhm what is this for that's right which
is Burger
oh R time
okay not sure
it can we change the direction of
this
no
interesting F
card oh those are arrows I didn't know
is something this
H okay so we
have oh wait wait
[Music]
wait I don't see anything happening can
we both press the right direction at the
same time oh
yeah 3 2
1 you place the wrong one no I didn't
the right one right direction here this
one m
I want to check if there's a more there
are more BS around maybe
[Music]
not this
a
suspicious so we
have a few
blocks just by randomly pressing
everything let's
go uh
put it back put it back yeah yeah yeah
yeah
oh oh wa wait wait stop stop oh where do
we want it oh we want ah we we're
stacking we're playing the stacking game
oh green has to go first yes green has
to go next oh you can actually climb the
wine so we want to climb the wines you
know the yellow oh yeah green one in the
middle yeah it's the
biggest oh oh that over wait can I try
can I try to I want to try moving
something too okay oh okay I see we need
the yellow to move though how do yeah
how do we get the maybe the put the red
right the side yeah yeah yeah
yeah
wow good job easy it took us a while to
understand
though I don't understand but for me it
didn't work
this is tricky I like this riddle there
go fall to a death I think I think this
is the next rle oh this no did anything
happen maybe there's an oh I was going
to say maybe there's an invisible path
but apparently
not fine no just this must have
triggered was that just for fun maybe it
was ahead we triggered a
button may it's okay maybe yeah did we
not have to do that maybe we
didn't I guess it did open the door
somewhere oh yeah I did open the door
yes it must oh andit my map is now the
logo I just
noticed I had the same thing happen just
now I just I took out my
map yet where one people have been wiped
out another took his place and lived a
new happy and peaceful life this place
is so boring oh perhaps even a bit too
peaceful I'm getting out of here you'll
see the little girl planned her Great
Escape oh little girl little girl girl
this is a big Great Escape oh we need
everybody here
oh we can get through this's go that's
the important
[Music]
thing it's okay because if I if I don't
eat now I don't I'm going to she takes
her time reading the L it's
important take it all in take it all
in I want to eat there we
go I'm enjoying I'm enjoying the story
yeah yeah it's good to
enjoy these trees are
crazy I
agree oh there's an Jo we Flex
[Music]
oh ah
interesting do that what is this am I
jumping
[Laughter]
more like my jump are say isn't it good
we can come back to jump
jump oh oh broke it there was a button
here am I jumping
higher no no I I am a little bit right
oh
minimal nothing changes though what's
going on doesn't even stand out so did
this not do anything oh
leave over
[Music]
here what
happened oh was only 30 seconds what oh
whoops yeah I think it had a timer
um did I think I had a timer
or maybe my my hands happen if I pressed
that fair Maiden I I you're a phoenix I
thought you could fly um uh I was just
trying to fit in you know I this the
yellow bridge I thank you for trying to
like be with be with us the ground wait
what if I go over there and I click this
again maybe something changes in the
other side maybe oh the yellow Bri
disappeared again oh is there a blue or
a
green one that we can press in front of
us but we can't well there's a
red oh that resets it I
see yeah it's it's Bon has the own
Bridge oh this one is this bridge wait
what happened there oh oh maybe here oh
it goes
away how did that go away
click the butt I click the button wait
wait I clicked the button over there oh
you click the button
yeah the Red Bridge started the Red
Bridge it's like azzle see see if that
button does anything I can go touch
touch it again the green one yeah okay I
can touch the red
one like back and forth put the yellow
one wait the yellow
oh gosh that was close not very safe
work environments touch that again
please touch it again okay wait don't
touch anything
okay oh yellow we just need thisit to go
away I'm going the red one here uh we go
oh don't touch
anything knows what I'm doing okay I
have another level here should I press
it oh no yes I'm going to press it I
need the red touch the red
I touch the pink the
red pink is good but I need red touched
there's no red over here to touch oh
there's a red over there oh yeah over
here actually T this do you want me to
do it
oh oh yeah touch the
red
oh this is good wait is this is this a
door no I have a in front of
me I want to I want to PR
yeah what that
do oh is it the
laser
no all right goodbye everybody else
goodbye goodbye oh oh you made it too I
made it if you if you reach the uh the
checkpoint have you reached the
checkpoint oh yeah you can just fall
down if you wanted to let's
go oh oh there's a did you girls read
the text
here I shall I shall read it this time
yeah okay there was no nice way to put
it the girl was sick of the underwater
Kingdom and she tried constantly to
leave it behind no oh no they got me
again yet with the guard being ever
watchful this was anything but easy she
she'd probably been caught a 100 times
by now even so giving up was the last
thing on her mind each failure instead
served as inspiration for a new attempt
am I just going about this the wrong way
yeah I know what I'll do next and so
another day of planning began
W interesting nice reading puzzles more
puzzles over here let's go so many
puzzles the I
direction oh oh it changed the direction
o h okay I think I probably
got what do we have to do we probably
have to make a path yeah a PA from this
oh oh aart for this guy oh there's an
enemy this guy oh well didn't he already
make it where is he going oh to the
other
side oh oh God no no we have to change
those yeah yeah we have to turn the
arrows okay oh there's buttons on here
before but now there
isn't the oh maybe
it's there we go buttons are
back we need him to go somewhere he need
okay does he does he need to go
into I think he does he need to go into
this this cage over here maybe yeah into
the cage m should be easy you can send
him already just take a shortcut just
like yeah open so maybe it doesn't work
how do we send him try that with the
diamond button click him click it come
on oh easy go go go how about the laser
is the laser okay yeah all right it's
okay was that it I guess it made sound
he's in there m do we need more than
one over
here nothing probably has to do
something else wait I don't understand
why there there's some gold there's some
gold in there gold in here maybe he has
to maybe you have to go through it we
can try it yeah let's go y yeah maybe
needs to cross the golden path let's go
let's make golden path so here first
first and then here and then
here click the click the button click
the yeah yeah yeah yeah like that and
then it goes back into the P oh okay I'm
going to click the button no wait wait
wait okay no oh wait okay ah no no no
it's not no no no uh oh
oh it's going to work it's going to work
didn't see that one we still have one
okay let's try this one more down
almost
down down there
up this way but what about this one yeah
this one yeah it has to go back here and
then oh then he can he can go this way
then he can't go that way yeah he has to
go that way first I'm
overseeing
yeah it go like that yeah
[Music]
I don't no because it goes in a circle
like
that oh there you
go
here wait wait have we gone to this one
no it doesn't work let's press it and
see what goes wrong
I'm go let's see what goes
[Music]
wrong okay back
around we're missing oh this look good
yeah change this
one hey wait
wait he's in an endless L let stop
[Music]
him okay try that I think he has to go
uh wait no don't try that
wait I'm not going the go try that
okay try
it oh I missed that one can I I I think
I have one he's going to be stuck ining
forever can I try
one left here mhm uh oops it right here
mhm right here yeah left here and left
again wait wait no right yeah right down
here and then left and then up and then
right yeah and then just only up yeah
this be
it good job go go go go go little buddy
you can do it you can do it yeah follow
the light follow the
gold there we go oh oh W oh that was
supposed to go straight oh no so close
wait I'm going to close it again again
again now that was on the wrong
direction there's only one direction
straight come on I'm going
to yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yes over
here
yes don't mindlessly follow him into the
laser I was I was chasing
him are you okay are you
okay that look like you h
a this is why you get scammed you follow
things mindlessly oh
no okay okay what to do
now it's worse than me guys worse than
me oh there's another pzzle here no oh
there's like threee lights on before
there were no lights on right oh really
it's like a chest maybe there's a
treasure or something what does it mean
I want to go in there green oh this
time we have to oh we actually need to
follow this path what about here oh in
the center have we tried going up the
center here wa wait wait wait oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah there's another one
here cool what is
this go go it's a laby
no there
water there water for water I'll Stand
[Music]
go up I fell
water I can go up have to go oh
no I don't think so no it doesn't go
anywhere oh yeah we can go up but it's
just the exit over here so this is at
the very
end I think I think everything here is
yellow except for one it says green can
they come oh let it go guys can you can
you try to come here actually up okay go
up yeah somebody has to stand on it no
wait no no no we have to open the chest
first never
mind no no no no
no light how it opened yet miss
something
here how do I go down purple what's the
oh thank you oh it's the reset and I
have an idea I have an idea got it I
have an
idea I have an idea stop
okay straight straight straight
left uhhuh left oh yeah yeah I has to go
left leave the field and then okay I
don't know can't change this one but
let's I think that oh and then we
probably go into that and then we'll see
what happens there let's try it send him
[Music]
off
interesting change anything here though
wa he's leaving his
boundaries what the heck yay what the
heck how poetic and now now we'll see
what does this do oh oh that's it okay
cool he lets us
up what about the
chest a chest so that one is
interesting one light left I want to get
the chest a first light more there's
more lights
before you think he can pass this water
P it says up here please wait for all
party members before proceeding yeah
there's a chest okay okay there is a
there is a message on the chest no oh no
no well I think if we send him for here
he will stand on the button and then the
chest room will open
but the question is just how do we lead
him over the arrow for a moment when
this arrow is straight how do we lead
him to go that way the arrow again oh
yeah I guess the when the buttons are
back we can just move the arrow to the
right okay I'll I'll refresh this okay
we'll probably have to send him straight
again later cuz that might have uh that
might have gotten rid of it yeah press
it is there an arrow oh there's no
a we might all need to go up here
because it says we can't proceed until
we're all up there anyway okay maybe the
chest is
later test yeah yeah yeah I'll send him
again if anything we can come back later
in these Dungeons and and do that again
together yeah and get the
chest oh maybe maybe this is the you
know the right order maybe we come back
here anyway
all right let's
go a secret button of some sort we
haven't found it's probably some puzle
or something maybe we have to come back
later who knows maybe the real treasure
was the friends we made along the way
yeah
definitely I need to
[Music]
eat here
what wait we're missing oh ah
Elizabeth yeah sorry one sec
okay huh I was just checking around okay
Myster is still not s so
[Music]
it's I'm
sorry wait oh
it's go okay go wait okay no okay I
guess it
is that's
it
[Music]
that's wait let me get the video first
has it huh yeah let's get the video my
memories you've recovered a portion of
your memories oh the
memories
wow I didn't download the video yet yeah
me neither
okay I'll do now the
video the
vision wait wait they haven't
yet wait wait okay second
I'm almost ready one what the
hell wait wait a minute
uh uh recovered a por of your
[Music]
memories okay wait wait wait wait wait
wait almost have it I almost have it I
almost have it oh okay I'm ready okay uh
wait wait wait wait uh
audio uh Advanced Audio
properties monitor only okay what does
that
mean okay uh B ready three
two one
go
[Music]
oh
it a she's very busy thanks come out of
here
es she the one to
escape oh time it's the girl we read
about
yeah that that's
familiar wait she the one in the Hat
yeah she got because she wanted to chop
I'll be free you want to pull us or so I
not she's a
criminal is she making she's a scammer
yeah she's a scammer
she's a
scumpy she's fast now
never see what this thing can
do w wow so cool she did it w oh my God
wait that glass ceiling I saw it outside
when we reached the
temple can we break out of it too that's
the barrier so cute my Story begins here
so cute Story
[Music]
begins what an interesting memory she
made it and we made it but
wait yeah let's go back in and get the
chest cuz oh yeah I think we need to
take the chest I think we can figure it
out we got to go get the chest get the
chest
yeah got to get back in there is nobody
oh let's
go we got to do the the bridges again
the shin is yellow instead now oh and
the stacking
too can you guys hear me yeah yeah I
said that the star on your weapon now is
yellow instead of white oh is it there's
a different
n wow I think I think it got stronger
now right
I'll press the
button
I okay we we we good now uh oh yeah
mhm can I can I try as well
yeah I already ran out of brain
energy all
right it's too much for me oh so that's
how it works so we need to put
everything on the left first wait wait
the red over
there yellow needs to go over here yeah
yeah oh yeah R go over and green go and
oh yeah red goes and another one left
and this one left and
reding it's easy but the door still easy
peasy actually I'll go this way feels
like we already made
it sole speed
run feed
Runners no this our first first try yes
oh yeah definitely we got it so fast
unbelievable we need to solve the father
I'm really curious to see what's going
to what there is in the what is in the
chest hopefully something we can all
share like maybe
friendship that's don't we have don't we
have friendship along the way though we
not after all that this will
like finalize I don't know it will put a
ring on our fingers yeah yeah yeah a
ring we getting married yeah no
friendship friendship ring friendship
ring I didn't realize it was this kind
of
commitment I'm going to press the L and
then we do it do it press it press
it
yeah and then come over here the yellow
one yellow one
I'll stay with the Fluffy one this time
okay I like
fluffy yellow one fluffy it doesn't work
huh oh why what huh I don't know maybe
it's by here huh let me try the yellow
uh what that fluffy oh no no you're so
fluffy you're so fluffy let me fluffy F
wait stay touch the ears of the table no
let me there's a door let me pit you let
me pit you no let me stop stop stop stop
stop how do you know what I'm trying to
do let me P you let me you wait this is
wait this is for content content
content over there let me for you look
so fluffy may I pet you do we need to
press the
red okay oh pet p
no oh no you did that to me no I'll come
pick you
up
no where did you go I'm a little bit
confused what
what my dad sorry sorry
no I got so excited for your fluffiness
I'm so sorry
can somebody press the red one yeah the
red one please how are
you I feel so fluffy now I found it I
thought it was the other a fond memory
with you Above This Pink Arrow can you
wait for me all right it's like almost
as if we were here before I'm stuck here
crazy course looks familiar let me see
if I can help you the glass ceiling
looks familiar too first time
totally quick
these
amazing we would be quicker if I didn't
push fua off
right sorry about that I mean luckily in
this realm we can come back to it worked
easy it
worked get the checkpoint
um oh okay I oh all right
yippe can we yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I
could have helped you with that but
that's good you could have help
uh I have um I I know how to solve the
puzzle you do yeah so I think the
skeleton did chatini tell you no no
chatini no actually no actually no um I
think the uh the doll has to go through
the gold like
twice oh so like we it has to make a
loop and then go but I'm not actually
sure a loop I I mean that's my idea I'm
not sure if it's that that's correct I I
just I just
assumed maybe I have like to I
understand it does to go double time on
the C so maybe like goes like you want
me to press it press it maybe let's
see why oh no
I okay let me let me just try one two to
Loop by a place
that oh up here over there no this needs
to go back
up oh wait you're right you're right
you're right you're right he needs to
Loop multiple times he needs to go five
he needs to go over it five times so it
lights it all up cuz there's five lights
so I need to go over it five times and
then yeah that's what I mean
smart okay we can do that we can do that
which way we want to go this way it's be
like um we can just send them over the
same one several times right yeah you
have to make it oh I I think I found the
way wait isn't this like already a loop
yeah we pressed it so now it should be
one does the same one not
count no make a sound okay
you went over it it lit up
once but we only have
three here to tree yeah we need a little
tree no that's not right how do we get
the other two it has wait can I can I
try
it
okay just want and then goes here and
then goes here and then like that
again there's no lights yet oh yeah
they're still
preparing is there is there light any
let me let me let me try one
thing P I figured it out figed it out
yes where the previous bit oh what
previous bit have you done the previous
bit m should we you mean the previous
before the chest yeah we should do it
again right okay so you have to make the
guy go towards me through door where are
you I down here I'm outside come
backwards from where we went on the
bridges make the guy come this way hello
hello
hello this way no way what what what
what
no so that he can he can make a a little
travel down here were
through the door yeah make him come
through that
[Music]
door oh that's quite oh oh yeah it leads
like here okay he's got
a I see I see let's reset it yeah and
then this Arrow leads
down here oh I see but at the end I
guess we probably still want to get the
golden ones that are here too I think
right maybe we don't oh yeah maybe we
need a later we'll probably want all of
them no we actually need it yeah I'll
tell you when it lights up okay wait did
gold oh yeah I think we need to reset
one more time that was not enough go
through there you can go through there
but you cannot you cannot pass you shall
not pass okay there we go he's coming uh
yeah you can test with that one but it's
not going to have enough gold we have to
uh reset the
path go he didn't catch all of them go
go go go go go
goas I didn't notice there was like the
gold on the on the on the off he goes
off he
goes yeah he's probably missing one he
didn't get all of them over here
isue fluffy
fua let's reset it
okay let
me let me reset that pa okay he goes
right here down here here down down and
then yeah down and then left and
then up and then right and then okay now
now we can send him okay I'm going to
send him let's
go yes he's going on a long trip
mhm okay okay two
lights good job good job lights good
job yes he will do it I believe in him
100%
okay what's going on huz
huz I cannot go over this go backwards
that's not you cannot go through there
he's
coming I'm going die thank you forever
oh
no I'm didn't open what did it it didn't
open he coming back still he's coming
back he's coming he's coming he's going
to stand on it oh yeah because he he
going
[Music]
to here we
[Applause]
gole wait a second vyl
oh that makes me
think wait what did what did did you
guys get a vinal
yeah need a juke box
for one question girls you all did the
dungeon yesterday
right
you have you gotten a vinyl there no no
no I think after all that one path that
I fought there must be a treasure chest
because my RPG senses were tingling it
must have a treasure chest with an Cali
vinyl there that probably no one found
so far and I think I know where it
is we should we should redo the Dungeon
adventure yeah let's go I
travel
fin I have to finish it again we have to
we have made the G I know okay the
dungeon on from the book I know it okay
I'm so excited I'm so
excited this my RPG
senses so real okay uh basically same
path but not down here but up right yeah
no where does he go yeah yeah yeah this
way this way this way this
way that way yeah right I forgot I don't
know what's in there and then it goes
over there and then we can get out we
don't need any the gos right no no no we
don't need any anything
anymore hungry
excited
[Music]
overse good
job thank you indeed my years of or
experience they have not failed me they
have not failed me I got the
treasure yeah we got music back oh go
that wasn't what I meant to
[Music]
feel let's go okay let's go job let's go
I am very excited to find Mor
CD let's go I hope there
is kire what do you think it is I will
show you I'll show you okay okay are you
stronger now again knows again even
stronger a portion of your
memories let's
go yay okay uh who wants to lead us to
the first dungeon oh let's a box oh yes
my brain is
empty this empty brain into the water we
go we have to go to the water into the
water yeah that was a really good
dungeon a
seahorse my horse doesn't don't don't
get off the horse the poor horse my
God my horse doesn't like the swim too
yeah I don't think it knows how to
breathe underwat it's
beautiful so pretty I really love this
area it was it was very nice and
beautiful
M even the map was very well done like I
like the
details wait where did you go
yeah let's meet at the guy the
guy guy with the
corals yeah
ships the ships make the ships I don't
think we need them anymore I can always
make new
ones what
oh I'm going so
slow I'm going as fast as I
can we have to go over here I guess
the
queen no the
queen
no I refused oh
no the queen Tim
ters it's Tim
ters the Tim who Tim
ters Tim ters Tim
ters what an interesting name
who's Tim the queen I'll claim my my
statues myself I don't need anyone to
give me
validation I don't
need Master we
be oh oh yeah I guess we got to go there
we can go there first yeah yeah let's go
to the um Guild Master us the city first
let's take the
shortcut shortcut
[Music]
get out of the way cow get
out are you running over cows with your
horse yeah I'll run over
everything are we going to rub
right
okay just to
make there you go turn this way I'm
[Music]
done are we ready
I'm
ready let us
[Music]
travel uh now that we in this city I'm
going to put something on the chest and
then we go
back okay what chest where oh I have um
I have a chest on the place where you um
can build stuff wow I I made like two
chest so I can deposit like
my my my
items does she notice it
anymore fascinating oh I'm going to mute
now what is more I sense the the power
of Revelation within you has grown more
po May by exploring more ruins and
obtaining more fragments of memory your
revelation
re as well if so we must find the next
ruins post case all of us together will
make work as a matter of fact we just
receed the most intriguing
report
Cup coming from the forest
Master Cela keep about you hero
Exel
[Music]
okay
exio wow do we want to see if we can
visit the
previous sorry I'm
currently I'm currently communicating
with the queen give me one moment what
queen queen the king that's me you
can Queen before you can you can talk to
me directly oh I
[Laughter]
remembered this is
the this is of the most terrible news
yes oh I got to deposit myself I'll be
right back okay wait for me
yeah
yeah is it over here ien been
there I don't
remember should be oh yeah it's over
here over here there you go oh this is
where phot was oh they're making a house
cute
[Laughter]
uh the the forer wit who sells is that
the place where we are able to
build is that the only place yeah this
is the only place we can
build yeah I see why did everybody
go I'm going to put my stuff over
here and later I'm going to be something
[Music]
where did everybody go did you go up the
RO
yeah no up you too okay sorry I I'm done
uh are you girl on the way to the
dungeon no where you
going wait I still need to talk to
rubius they're over wait you haven't
talked to rubius oh yeah sorry I was
kind of busy um go back go back and talk
to him okay
okay
okay oh they okay I guess they're
leading us to the next dungeon with that
one but we want to go to the first
dungeon yeah here we go I'm going guys
what oh no wait it doesn't work never
mind peace shall
Prevail it doesn't how to open those M
well what do I need a du box what does
for
yeah I don't later I'm actually going to
put this
[Music]
here
yeah the P actually know I'm going to
keep it here
[Music]
I that's okay I don't remember very well
I what was your name again po what
happened I I don't remember I don't
remember what you named me but my name
today is Darwin Roosevelt DiCaprio Jr
decaprio that was your name pun was that
it
pun I'm pun there's a side quest for a
res oh I got kicked out from the party
fair oh yes I think they ended the party
call any that's
okay the red the red by ruus maybey
again it appears my party has found but
I have distracted we're going to do the
first dungeon again because there's also
a side quest for revisiting the first
dungeon yeah we can kill two birds with
one
stone
okay
follow um
somewhere
um yeah party call party call
someone call the
party okay I'm here wait how do you oh
wait I forgot how I know how I know how
to do it I know how to do it I think I'm
going to accept everything just in
[Music]
case I'm in the party call Seca yes I
think I should probably end the party
call cuz this is probably where I should
St for today oh you and you went for
okay that's fine I'll go with ra and
perhaps Liz I'm not sure if she wants to
go yeah we'll have to find the stuff
door
okay thank thank you had
fun take care fluzzy fluzzy ones fluzzy
ones byebye
[Music]
by save journey to you two Travelers
Revelation Revelation fuzzy okay which
one's the side quest looking for 10 I
all of them just in case
milkshake come challenge Brutus at the
pits L and
stains go go back to the underworld
dungeon investigate it again then report
your findings of the quest master all
right yeah there another quest for good
ass dungeon as well yeah oh so and me we
will be the first ones probably to find
the Cali record you it will be a rare
item that only we have mhm okay are you
sure okay okay but I don't know should
we uh check with herb a there you oh
there Iris oh hello hello those of Amber
coin we're not ambercoin oh oh not Amber
coin we're Jade now we're oh oh you're
Jade people we changed guills we changed
guilds that is a very listen to me right
now listen Queen yes Queen yes thank you
hello tender I
KN thank you thank you what is what is
your name I am tanak kakaria of the
oranges Sab of the Les letian
Lees just say sorry what what did you
call our Beloved Country again uh a
uh to not on purpose um yeah you can
call me Shakira um you have you have
heard my report Shakira what Shakir you
heard my report is it true Queen have
you already looked into it we are
looking into right now there have been
please elaborate for the rest of us okay
well uh there have already been plenty
of victims so far I also here this is
the this is the detective that I have uh
asked to help me as well my Pearl yes so
the Red Hats married the Red Hats of the
Scarlet wand they uh have put up a shop
uh to scam people with lottery tickets
they say it's for the library but in
reality it's not and and they're trying
to make use of the people who have
amnesia and can't read so they can't
read the the the the contract and
yeah just don't buy don't buy into the
scam don't buy lottery tickets where is
this poster I came to look at the poster
check check it was sent by pigeon I I
sent you through pigeon oh pigeons by
pigeon okay let me let me just check my
pigeon mailbox right now okay hold on
just be careful of the Red Hats the red
hats are dangerous they they want to
take over the country probably
I see I see the pig I'm aerate doll uh
weit we can read for you we can read can
you read it to me
please yes yeah yes yes yes please give
it a look at a look at pleas the pigeon
mail are you going to seek the the
dungeon oh it is yes in a moment we're
currently in a her name is spicy
situation at the uh quest uh board where
is the pigeon mail she speak
wow the jackpot is 740
gold don't buy to the
scam but we could
win it's it's a scam dude come to the
said it's a scam M we could win money no
we are not going to win money no you're
not going to win money something's
happening I don't know I like money but
think about it if everyone is thinking
it's a scam that means not many people
are betting which means there's a good
chance no it's not
for it honestly it already it already
has become a worst chance because Moko
got scammed and gave them 680 coins
no8 I am blinded by money what is
happening
queen queen you must do something at
gambling and I have 500 now see you are
exactly the kind of person they're
looking
for I I would like to increase my my
savings don't do it you're weak to
you're weak to
gambling I will try my best to I like go
keep myself yes we must we must
exterminate you must too we must
exterminate both the scar Scarlet Guild
and the ambercoin guild the ambercoin of
course too house ambercoin Guild is evil
who is Amber evil um you two have left
then who is I was never in Amber coin of
course
not no I I'm in Jade all all all the way
oh I'm in Jade though I've never seen oh
that's I heard that your guild is full
of scammers can you verify you are with
this member is claiming to be part of I
literally just went with Fu and and Herb
which are Jade members uh to the dungeon
right herb they're like semi
honorary we we we get along copine has
invited me into the guild personally
wait a second isn't
she guess you
are listen listen it doesn't even matter
Queen there is Queen red thing that red
thing is of Jade sword and not of
ambercoin thank you my benevolent Queen
the name of Amber coin que I don't trust
it I do not trust it so you are the Tim
I heard about wait it's
timtim no what is what is a Tim Tam what
is what is this queen Tim
how Tam Tam what kind of name is all
right BB wasn't Jade
huh is silent what this disgusting you
co me of this I not understand because
everybody was too polite but I of higher
rank you have you yes you are right you
have not been polite the green one the
green I have been very polite to you
actually the other time remember when I
have you to the dungeon when yes that
was good I was was it's getting too
chaotic uh that was a
misunderstanding you are this close to
the who are you affiliated with she's
with the Red Hats she's with the red
hats with affiliated with the green ones
cuz she's with red
hat are you guys
plotting getting too chaotic what's
going on is that should
let we have planted the seed of Truth
with other
people the seed of
truth the truth the truth shall
Prevail the queen shall
Prevail I have never got any
okay we have done
[Music]
it to yeah I'm here I'm on party call
with you oh please join
or we in party call again join us if you
like yeah geky geky has really has it
out for Amber
corn she really want to see I want to
stay in am coin I like it people hate us
though why there's a lot of like slander
being spread about Amber coins crimes
let them hate who cares
it's okay I'm a freelancer it's okay
yeah it's okay it's a GU made by one
person which is me it's fine no no no no
let go to the dungeon don't worry I'm I
I all that matters is that we are
together
now how does it work when you with the
others you part of other girls when with
me part of the
Amber why oh why are you complaining we
went together to the dungeon with the
Jades how does it
work don't question it don't question it
it's
complicated okay we got to go straight
straight
straight oh yeah stra
right uh let's go I'm going to call Liz
in private and ask her if she wants to
join before
okay Liz was not in Jade which is she
Cerulean I guess she was Ruan
right no I honestly to like real talk um
you guys probably notice like amorn is
first of all smaller Guild than
everybody else and then Bales is I guess
like kind of uh inactive me too I'm not
joining like everything sadly either so
like I think you know it's just like an
RPG way what's going on right now is a
role playing way of good to it's good to
the
join the party call yeah let's go to the
arena what the
arena an RPG way of trying to you know
cuz I saw you know I thought I could
hang with mum maybe today M and but then
you know mum was also like doing other
things so you know I just thought I got
to find myself some friends because
otherwise I'll be alone so we're just
you know mangling mangling and having
fun
with
drama it's storytelling storytelling I
don't want to go to the
arena the oh urb and the queen are
fighting
dwelling oh well that's a different
story I I need to support the queen see
that's another problem I have um between
me and L I love her but she wants to be
the queen I support the other Queen we
have a
political pickle that is maybe
destroying our friend
ship watch the match of the search are
you guys perhaps selling scam tickets
for that too
huh you can keep your heart I'll one day
I'll find the same heart one day you can
buy it
yeah we got your record good oh you
found it we got it it was quite your
feel it was quite difficult took us a
while we it took us a while too
because because the the the the the gate
signifies the end of a puzzle so you
wouldn't backtrack right but then it
backtracked anyway like why why what why
we had to backtrack we had to there was
no choice there was an obvious treasure
hidden good job so I'm I'm glad you made
it out of that uh glass Hall of
Atlantis the force field the thing the
force bubble field I'm glad I'm glad
you're free in the world now to do
whatever you
please but I shall not support the scam
of the Red Hats so that's another story
what' you call me I'm going to the scam
of the Red
Hats
uhhuh rightly
well
I uh they might be in the arena I wanted
to go there too part of them might be in
the
arena yes
the pyramid schemers I okay
yeah Will
mys
hello
hello is the queen here oh the
queen yes I came I came to support you
in the in the pit fight
yes I have chosen my proxy okay join
again your proxy of course you you need
to be safe kept yes the queen must never
fight herself so I join again join again
have gathered of all you may not fight
yourself until you have produced a male
air to the king it time why does it have
to
be that's the duty of the queen anyway
okay they're fighting
[Laughter]
fight fight F fight F
the go for her
head heads Must
Fall
[Music]
Revelation I want to hear their [\h__\h]
talking oh hi hot lady oh hi how are you
doing hot lady I'm doing I'm doing good
um I feel like there's been process made
she did
it did it
queen
[Applause]
queen the
queen a GH pulled me around the
arena trust you
yes have I served well
Queen yes you have reclaimed your
destiny of being harassed by no no no
you must be you must be I being red
around
AR h
n you late you missed the fight you
trust me right there was a in the arena
a ghost that pulled me around believe
you do not listen to that the that
haunts this Arena it name is ping
P
the that sounds like a skill P was in
favor no it's in the history books in
the green Guild I believe that is a
skill I thought you could not
read I was told
ofen story EXC beautiful RAV you are
here yes yes it is I I have missed you
Jonathan I have missed you too
little
demon the hot pink the hot pink one the
hot pink one seen
your should we go to the
do
yipp party call the ghost ping attacked
me I was being I was being pulled around
I I couldn't even move
properly I I must say I was
supporting together in the dungeon
I I don't know like I I love both of you
but our political um interests seem to
go into very different directions but
that shall not stop us from being
friends
right I don't care I don't mind ah you
know I I feel like we have a new rule in
the in the Jade sword that we all must
agree to adding other members
ah I I I I forgot about this it's okay I
don't need I don't need a guild I'm I'm
with the queen I'm her guard her Knight
so
me I shall be Guiltless then although I
do have a special invitation from K
cayia pin the uh owner of the first
dungeon so I think that kind of counts
pretty
big she owns the dungeon yeah
H speaking of the dungeon shall we go
back can you join the party co please
[Music]
yeah we don't
get she always runs into me with a
horse that is quite dangerous uh so they
do not know how to ride their horses in
that Guild yeah you know she's usually
being carried by a horse carriage so
she's she's a little bit um yeah
unskilled when it comes to a snooty
Tooty
Queen but she she's you know she wants
to help with the scam in the problems so
the scam what scam problems here this
this is the the lottery the
lottery oh the witch the Witch
oh how come you call her a
witch H
hello
hello mhm
L did you stop again how' you like if I
ran over you with my horse you mean you
what's happening what's happening it's
me where are you h no what where are
they did she like go back to when she
ran past
huh why did they hang up without telling
me what's going
on oh you should look in the mirror oh
Queen I no sorry I was also learn how to
ride your
horse you seem to run into people well
you seem to be doing that first to
begin why don't you look will you get
your horse out of my horse's face no no
no no will you no you're a horse your
horse looks very directly challeng yeah
yeah I go I Del you your with a
freakishly large sword of yours and the
weight is just unbalanced you are Abus I
I I cut this horse into bed every night
and feed it 10 suar cubes a day I love
this scar me get your horse out of my
horse's face 10 sugar cubes you know
that would make your horse very diabetic
later on be very detal to
it you already went so you believe that
your horse is to be diabetic your horse
is
disgusting my horse is beautiful your
your horse is disgusting I do not judge
I do not judge horses I do not judge a
book by its cover this horse is
brilliant well it looks like a runt
anyway I must wait Queen marry along the
way yes my queen just one thing it seems
I am in a um pickle once again um I do
not know where I belong anymore but I
know one thing that my whole duty of my
life it is protecting you and
I know that I have a destiny to be by
your side as your
personal uh King hero uh not King I mean
night nigh hero guard may I please serve
you no matter what Guild I am of I don't
want to be uh known as anybody's besides
yours well for swearing Your Allegiance
you are a mighty Phoenix what are you
doing gring to her
hey my destiny to you outcast out with
you you judging by
their you do not belong in this Kingdom
of may you cast May you cast you out
into the
plains awful ABS well the planes is
where we were going anyway um bloody
looking
thing bloody red like blood disgusting
makes me sick you are the image of
war and everything
vile just like the words coming out of
your mouth my
lady anybody got popcorn out with you
out good day out with
you whenever you need me call my name
Shakira Shakira yes okay Shakira Shakira
I shall be of your service forever and
ever yes yes
hey hello was I talking to you get the
hell out of here I mean um get the way
you let this Mighty Phoenix bow and
grubble to you is disgusting yes that
means she knows her standards you bloody
you putting her in her place I see what
a wonderful queen you are yes the fact
that I can control the Phoenix below me
shows the level between you
and I'm so sorry it's okay it's okay I
know you are the most merciful of them
all my queen are you what are you what
makes you so special nothing you're just
a rebel for the sake of being a rebel
and you you you have no allegiance to
anyone you lie other and that is why
that is why you claim to be this cool
loner when in fact you are just alone
without friends no comp now it's
starting to hurt well me and my
companions went and ConEd the second DS
oh your comp we've already been un like
somebody oh look how uh look at the
shine on your weapons compared to
mine yes and your compion same level we
will be of the same level soon because
we can only conquer one dungeon every
day so it'll only wait you know even if
your sword is glowing yellow you still
Lo
pink
thing that is for some you want to mix
it up some more claiming that you're the
queen the queen tell her being pulled
around yes yes anyway I have better
things to do good dayer good day
Farewell My Queen call
Thunder this is we had this entire
exchange
yesterday no that's not what I want to
talk to you about
you didn't just go to the to me I mean
you came back with food yeah that's rude
are you eating chicken tandas I don't
actually care because I'm the queen so I
do whatever I want yes you're the second
I know no you are the second you're the
second you're the concubine porcupine
what not porcupine oh sorry I have
porcupines on my mind uh team team bish
um I want to say one thing to you this
is so disrespectful I can't
even I want to say one thing to you and
I'm not going to repeat
myself you are a queen anyway you are a
queen castle yes walk away and style my
queen you have no house you are you you
are a mighty Phoenix you need to toughen
up and
not I'm a night Warrior
you see my shield and my sword I must
give it to someone she was rude to your
guild
member I she left because she's a coward
no I must have my my honor and those oh
no that's she's going
to my honor I
amely my our political Ambitions shall
not destroy our
friendship no no
Mighty Phoenix you are of fire yes and
with my mighty Phoenix power a
connection no it's a politics I am but I
a human and I can control fire and I
thought we had
something as a weak Phoenix no it's the
politics you know I must for the for the
greatness of the goodness of the people
I we have we need to help them because
of the scams going around and I know
that the one true Queen will protect us
from these evil beings
ah Shame
Shame
Shame oh you got me into something okay
shall we go shall we go
anyway you ringing the
bell shame
dinging shame okay but um shall we um
look look past this and go to the
dungeon
now H I'll look past it for now okay
good until you gravel in front of her
again are you going to keep next time
yeah I will I
will okay wait wait wait wait we should
get into a call again otherwise she's uh
she's gone party call okay party party
now she just needs to read our
mind let's go first
dungeon that was
intense that was
intense Speak Your Truth Tel yes I'm
speaking my truth ah
who are you speaking to
hello oh no are you okay I'm okay oh you
want to get into a party code a yeah I
think we're we're looking past our
problems right now and just going to do
the dungeon
so I have no problem in the first place
good she did not have a problem it was
it was the
queen well the Tim Tam Queen The Tam Tim
whatever her name is I think I think
we're we're all learning a lesson here
sorry I need to correct you the name of
the queen is RA but yeah you can fix it
but that is your name do we have to yeah
exactly disband the Party by the way and
make a new one probably yeah I don't
know uh let let's see I'll leave this
party cuz I think the offline ones oh
see the fuzzy and the fluffy one I still
yeah interwined okay this hey go I
invite you girls oh okay
oh wait I leave party uh okay I left the
party I can be invited
now oh do you want one second uh doesn't
make me leave the party huh yeah you
have to not dis but
leave I have
left okay Queen of the temp I invited
you and I am inviting you too of the Tim
Hortons thank you all righty remember
can you invite me one more time I'm
sorry of
course
okay the outcast the simp and the the
panther which one am I what are you
speaking of to yourself I I received a a
pigeon carried message uh of pink color
that says I'm I'm loving this episode of
The Chronicles of
the Les
lesbians the outcast the S and the
panther which is I guess us but who's
I'm not Panther yeah yeah she's the
panther who's the outcast who's the S I
guess I'm the S but you're not much of
an
outcast uh well I am a alone Warrior
most of the time that's okay together we
are not alone anymore
let's ready up girls then I will walk
away just just look away just look away
I can't watch you
do wait I think there's a bug because it
says underworld dungeon one out of
two H shouldn't be one out of three
because it's I'm ready let me unready
and ready
again okay now La I think you're not
ready yeah I
also you need to be getting get yourself
into the the call oh I am oh oh no you
are in the cor yeah what about Shakira
okay Shakira is in and there we
go all right let's do this again yeah oh
yeah it's
jumping I love the jumping I mean oh yes
this is I am great with the parkour M I
feel like you could use use your big
sword as like a
pole like what do you call it pole
jumping what do you call
it well I would not dance with it no
it's not over here no no not dancing I
mean the jumping it's over here Oh you
mean like a long pole long pole vaulting
yeah pole
vaulting oh like yeah like in the All
Point the
o o
impix oh wait checkpoint yes
yeah we got it we got it where certain
sausages got
caught what got nobody knows what I'm
talking about that's good that's good
sausages have you
seen oh my God have you seen
it have you not witnessed it you
probably have forgotten it because of
the Amnesia it's okay I forgot
everything I already remembered
everything I am the actual queen of Li
mhm mhm mhm
yeahh mhm sure say a queen you got to a
checkpoint yeah again don't worry we'll
carry
you we'll bring you to the goal safe and
sound carrying I was just you know I was
just taking my time at having a merry
stroll I know you could do it with that
pole of yours so don't worry we we just
don't want to we want to save your your
your energy G and all that you know yeah
yes for the battle I'm at the next
checkpoint yipp how you how are you
getting there so fast skill second time
I guess so you flying are you
cheating you flying cheating I may I may
be flying a little bit here and there
but that you you were criticizing me for
not using my wings now I am true that is
true you know got to you know speed it
up a little
bit uh oh you caught up wait I forgot
where does it go from here probably left
oh yeah and then here and here here
here almost
there
okay if only I was this good at jumping
at that one competition last year the
the Trident only up m comptition I you
got the next checkpoint almost almost
almost don't worry leave it to me do you
remember something oh yeah my old man I
already I already oh I did win yeah but
like still I was like so bad at it I
could have been
better it's the
pressure it's the pressure guys okay
what is the what the music thing whoa
you zip Zapped well well well pingi one
after another ghost is
back
ping
ping yeah it starts with this little
maze ah we all have a you know
uh a uh like a a catchphrase as we
attack right oh my God I listen on
everything oh yeah
totally yes are you going are you going
to say it wa uh
uh Eternal fire welcome to the world of
stability and Harmony
wa not bad kick it
kick Phoenix
Flames I got a couple they're short
though wow you have more than
one do we have uh the shapes already I
got a
triangle I have a triangle period and
another
one what is you doing star you a star
good I H another triangle where is the
thing to fill it
in oh oh there's so many I'm going to
die no you're not going to die I got a
triangle no I got a
[Music]
th I have a circle we have everything we
just got to find the the forms oh I
found it oh yeah me
too got
everything uh I forgot oh there we go
nice good job next
step oh I forgot to change my bgms even
though I prepared so many
no I didn't even turn the other one on
keep for getting my
vmm okay now there's
one okay I turned it off for the cut
scene for the good cut scene
yeah okay so that cut scene was so good
I love those cut scenes the cat I love
cat scenes too I want more cat scenes
than cut
scenes meow um the treasure is from what
I believe uh where those uh trees are
but this we first have to solve this
puzzle once again yipp I remember how to
make it it's oh let's go can you speedr
run it yeah yeah yeah let's see what is
the answer big cat uh just like
um the lights on the left are going to
light up so you got to make sure that
you oh she's
fast yeah yeah she does remember I do
remember there you go wow well done
speed well I I think my my my uh dungeon
buddy kind of did it on a whim so it
wasn't really sure how they they cracked
it yeah it took us a long time too the
first time yeah the first time was
difficult because I couldn't figure it
out the
mechanism work so where do you think
this ah I think oh well first we got to
do this thing with where he gets rid of
the bridge right shoot us shoot us do
it you have to go very CL you coward
don't Al Al you won't coward it does it
just
bring let's keep going forward
[Music]
he I
tried I
tried oh we waiting oh okay I'm here
welcome welcome is this no it's
different right well believe me I'm sure
uh that I know where this treasure is
that we're not even 100% sure that
exists but I'm sure so first of all
let's do the whole thing again with
growing the
tree on top of the mushroom to us come
there we go let's make it as tall as
possible come
here yeah mhm speed speed speed more in
Shakira We Trust Shakira
Shakira those hips don't lie
baby press
four ah okay that was uh
yeah the tree is too big already another
one yeah come here come here come here
come
here y okay good job can we get another
one
yeah elizabth are you okay oh no yeah
I'm okay I'm at the top oopsie you're at
the top you in the top maybe we of the
tree to then no no no I think it can
still grow one more bigger yeah you can
get up oh but I want it to bigger I'm
not going where you think I'm
going
exactly where do you think it is in next
the chest the secret chest so I
think that it is and I think now it
might be able to reach already yeah I
think it is uh you know how we climb up
this tree and we went like to the next
trees we want to go the opposite
direction oh because I've noticed that
the tree when fully grown reaches the
other side the other platform Which is
higher than where we originally went out
but it's hard to
climb yeah but don't don't go so don't
make the big jump if you're at the top
don't make the big jump I want to jump
together okay we jump together the way
I'll wait for
you but we got to find the right path
this is difficult
huh Elizabeth we uh we uh you at the top
of the
tree oh let's try to get to the very top
of the tree because I think if yeah if
we jump yeah yeah because it reaches
just the perfect height you know and
that already looked suspicious to me
when I first one was in this dungeon and
my RPG senses were ting tingling yeah
but how do you jump from here well we
got to find a way it must be possible of
otherwise I don't think the tree would
like really grow this big pie do you
remember you made you cooked something
to make the jump higher can you make can
you can you give one to me as well I
want to try oh I would I would need I
already ate the first one and I don't
have any more I would need more
ingredients but I think we should be
able to do it without because honestly
the jump it didn't get much bigger it
was just like like 5
cm I don't know really small jump
possible from
yeah um there must be a different path I
guess a different path from other
side definitely not it or I wonder if it
can grow if this is the last stage of
the tree
Grove honestly I'm not even like 100%
sure about any of this of course
but I just had a feeling you know
huh yeah I mean we we here to explore
it's fine worst case we just go back
wait wait how did you oh how did you get
there oh just there in front of me m so
you go
around here but I'm not really sure
where to go from here I don't think I
don't think it helps what I've
done yeah there's buttons here too which
some people say the buttons uh show like
the way to the next like jumpy platforms
but doesn't really because it show maybe
we do need a
potion I don't think so the potion okay
listen I try to jump but are you at the
bottom yeah can you try leading another
skeleton leading another G skeleton
there is no more skeletons oh so it is
the maximum okay interesting yeah and
let's see what if we may maybe the the
trees over there
connect
uh oh we can try uh growing those again
and see yeah if it maybe helps
us not sure because those would be
growing so far
away well I mean me and my my party
members yesterday didn't grow them to
their fullest so oh let's do that then
no oh no no wait I think it's isn't
there is there a checkpoint there
too oh man I cannot oh yeah there is up
there oh it's not activating I'm stupid
what okay but I I'll start growing then
my party members
stupid what if it really
is okay one tree
Grove or what I if there's no more
skeletons down there I wonder can we Le
the skeleton down to the to tree that
we're growing and grow it even more just
a test because you're going to D you
going
to make fall damage a the fall for could
I guess
so but if we like can you uh Elizabeth
can you try the uh wait never mind I'll
I'll try it oh sorry it's okay it's okay
that's fine too okay come come come come
but don't kill me
I want him to
face I'm going to
die okay abort abort abort Elizabeth
does kill him h no it's it's a bit
difficult I want to I want him to face
the tree and then I want to push him
down of the sword because then he falls
down with some momentum it might
actually yeah if we CL yeah it does it
connects it does wow yes all right all
right all right all right all right all
right all right
oh I want to come come here come here
come here I come probably enough if we
just grow this tree and if it's
connecting or oh maybe we need all of
them cuz honestly it was really
complicated to get the other CD the V
vinyl yeah so maybe if we jump from One
Tree to the other tree to the other
tree You Know It All Connect over here
because oh oh you think that's uh it
finished growing this one uh I might
have wait where where connects though
are you sure at the top if you come over
to where we are you can see that the
tree is reaching out to the other tree
and you could probably make that
jump
okay from there to
there I
am nice nice nice
nice I am on the top of this tree kill
me no
no did you just not want to
heal
no waste of bread okay enough a skeleton
indeed I'm I'm running out of
bread but I still have some meat I can
give it's okay I still have
meat I cooked some meat
before okay this one I probably from
this to this to there so this one has to
grow yes is that is that it okay I've
grown both trees to its fullest there's
no more skeletons spawning so I
think oh let me
see this from here to to jump on the
next
tree come over here no no I'm already on
the top which top never
mind oh no La this is this is the thing
with cats climbing trees yeah sometime
it happens you know you you get too
confident you think you can reach it and
then you fall yeah or or you get
stuck but cats always fall on their paws
supposedly sometime the other tree if
I'm e
it it feels like there's several
paths
oh you made it I'm almost there I feel
like
okay no it's still kind of far so I got
to go to the top and then fall
down
okay but this is not not quite it this
this is it I'm getting so excited I can
smell the
treasure I believe you can find it
what's the can you can you wait off to
open it yes I will wait if I find
it um wait I am I am confident you can
find I think there is like it makes
sense that there is one no 100% like I I
thought there was something there the
first time there's there's a reason why
these uh trees grow this tall and not
just as tall as we need
it for the noral path yeah now that we
have the vinyl from one dungeon we know
there must be a vinyl here
too but this is not this is too far
hello hi we need to go higher like it
looks like you can reach from here but
it's not quite enough we need to fall
from
higher so like we keep on jumping from
tree to tree no you can jump over here
no yeah but from there it's still too
far I think the other tree we have to go
from
higher no here go
no oh you could no ah I mean to the left
tree is the we talking about uh I
thought you were thought I thought you
thought you could already jump to the
front tree but yeah I
probably cuz I'm stuck here
no stop dying
I
stucked got stucked
no but I see yeah yeah yeah you found
the you found the way
yeah I I will continue your
legacy okay I am happy to contribute a
little
bit that should
work oh
yeah you're doing it Elizabeth come on
come
on from here
how
mhm
oh oh we're doing it where we're PR much
I
think I can totally see a treasure there
there there's one I believe it there's a
reason for all of this there is totally
a reason
okay oh sh Wait I'm lost I cannot find
the way anymore
what it was on the uh the tiger looking
parts of the tree that there was like
yeah you start from the left and you go
to the right tree then the left left
okay now I'm on the very top of the tree
where you jump right where you got to
jump yeah and from there I don't know
where to go I had to go underneath on
like some Tiger Tiger tree looking bits
like walk underneath and I kind of fell
sorry I kind of accident acally found
it welcome let's wait for her here okay
I'm scared of this
jump but yeah it's it's totally totally
doable oh you're still on the middle
tree on the first tree L yeah I cannot
find the P to go to the second oh wait I
see the chest now I see the chest there
is the chest we see it there the chest
guys I want to see it there is no
checkpoint though so be careful
y good
job guys I'm looking for the puff I need
a i guys kfp Clippers I need a clip
compilation from me doing the dungeon
the first time and then abandoning this
but I always knew I always
knew there's something more to this
dungeon should we share our findings
with the others or should we keep it a
secret well we know you simp the queen
you the first one I will not tell the
queen I will not die I I am am the queen
I already know that
silly
oh this this one know is a little silly
today I now they they'll probably find
out you will probably say to her I know
where the other there is another
treasure my queen so please let me be
your no no no no kiss her her feet I
think
go no no we should just like how the
mighty Phoenix is falling we should when
we're at the chest we should take a an a
me m Meo me momento picture of us
together and then Flex it to everybody
that we were the first ones to find
this yeah and then they can try finding
it too yeah I canot find
my let me see where are uh where oh is
she still on the first come on the first
tree you've done this first tree several
times I know no I mean I I'm done on the
first tree oh
God okay this I'm done just take take
your time we we'll wait yeah okay can
you wait wait forever take good
[Music]
time I'm
sad oh should we sell this information
wait I'm stupid maybe I was stacked on
this tree wait I don't you say that no I
don't want to no no I don't want to I
just read I think the message but I
don't want to I'm not like those
scammers from the Red Hats I'm not like
them the the Scarlet one yeah uh I think
this is a good point for us to hydrate
uh yeah Shakira I'm always hydrating
don't worry oh hydration but I'm running
out of water Look Over Yonder and and do
and hydrate okay where I'm running out
out the water
again okay I'm coming now I was the
first tree for some reason like I
thought that was the actual last tree I
don't know
why Tam doesn't believe your words what
of course she
does she doubting
me no no way I
must no no no one I'm sure no
one get in
here but okay you know I couldn't have
done it without these girls because uh
wasn't it Elizabeth who had the idea to
continue growing the other trees too cuz
it looked like this tree alone could
already reach it but and it does but you
need the other trees all connected all
all of them which makes sense with like
how complicated the other chest was in
the other dungeon you have to com uh
combine several riddles
H yes yes how you doing
L where are you uh at the top pretty
much like in the where the trees connect
all three of them if you look up you
probably see your names somewhere I
don't see yours right now though oh I
see you guys oh there ah the tree
cat tree cat
cute come on come on H uh first to the
side I
think yeah and then the next one on the
side and then I think it it's hard to
tell from here but I think you can reach
if you you got to run you got to run
don't fall don't fall you have to run
when you
jump don't don't get nervous you can do
it I will catch
you yes yes and now carefully you does
everybody have full health because the
fall might do some damage yes I do wait
I need to go down to this tree
first yeah it's just a fall yeah I think
it's pretty safe you go
first okay ouch okay yeah I'm fine cat
next yeah
yes go you can do
it
okay and fly Phoenix oh
dangerous we're doing it good job okay
no one is allowed to fall
now unless the unless the Ping go gets
me then I might fall
oh my God this is so
exciting it's there we take a picture
we'll take a picture in front of like
here
maybe stand next to me girls yeah yeah
yeah yeah
yeah yes H
Elizabeth stand by myself I was clicking
uh I mean I was I was jumping and when I
jumped twice it did something weird I
was confused go
cheese and let's look to the other side
too
cheese
yay we're the first
ones probably okay probably excuse my
rudess oh could you please
rip oh my
god did oh my God I love this one
[Music]
yay I'm sure other people will come to
the conclusion that if the Atlantis
dungeon had a city the others should
have one too but I don't think many
people know where the the treasure would
be
no what don't I don't Ascend so
abruptly you can let me know when you
get to the checkpoint
okay thank you it's only cuz uh my my
tum tum is turning so after jumping yes
after jumping so much on those trees so
I'll wait until you're there and then I
will oh does it give you motion
sickness yeah I I get motion sickness oh
no I hear a lot about people getting
motion sickness from Minecraft I'm so
glad I'm not affected but sounds rough
yeah I I out of character I get it yeah
get it a fair
bit yeah wait where does it go
again is it like every
time then you get it after like a like
around uh two a shower like on the 2our
I get bit like scky or like a bit after
a while o it depends what I'm doing too
if I'm like jumping a lot and all
that I think my sick bands helped me a
little bit today my wrist band oh well I
think yeah with all this jumping it's
very understandable you've done greatly
Brave Warrior yeah that that actually
was way difficult I'm a brave warrior
with chummy
issues you know we all have some you
know realistic human
problems I'm only human yeah the Phoenix
and the panther I'm only human but even
even I get Tommy
H Tommy don't way I got the checkpoint
yeah please you did okay I'm a I'm going
die thank you forever I'm going die
Thank You Forever by way yeah it's uh
it's was pretty difficult jumping on the
tree it requires a little bit of
skills well I I I'm just going to get
high enough to jump again to my demise
oh that was not it
but well after this was it just uh the
end of the dungeon right away or what
was it I think so
okay I'm also sick of jumping at this
point feel like Cali after 24 hours of
jump King
man oh my God her her legendary this was
before your time girls her legendary
jump King
streams a stream is frustrating like
water a water stream
uh yeah yeah yeah yeah uh she jumped a
stream of water you were jumping in the
water and you were a king ah she is that
how you grel to the queen copine she
used to jump over streams of water
endlessly and they would lead her to
pretty high places like the it's like
the water streams were coming from the
mountains
W
amazing wait I'm almost almost dead how
powerful there
dead oh
finally nice yippe let's go wow w
[Music]
wow
yeah good job thank you for aiding me in
the quest of this because I would have
never been satisfied
otherwise thank you for inviting us on
your Noble Quest de it's so worth it
so f is there any place to play these uh
vinyls yeah yeah there's a juk box at
the at the beginning of the city oh can
we go listen yeah yeah let's go listen
let's
go let us go let us travel Have you
listened to the Atlantis one already no
yeah yeah yeah it was playing in the
background oh okay oh me
and okay I show you know I show you
another
way sh sh
what is this song you sing Shakira oh
it's my original song your original yes
I sometimes perform in taverns with um
you are a b uh no I'm more like the
serator I I work with other bars oh yes
I hello
hello you have voices in your head kop
kop come on please come with us please
come with us we have a surprise for you
we have a surprise for you surprise
surprise what kind of surprise come with
us can you bring us where where we need
to go come here come here come here come
here come here don't tell her yet don't
tell her come here come here come here
it's a surprise it's a perfect
timing all right come with me it's like
sorry oh oopsie one sec you can go in
there oh no no stuck in there one it was
very scary
[Music]
house follow follow
me you're you're
timing come here come here come here
okay okay can everybody around it hear
it I think so right over here over here
come here hold hold on just one moment
just one moment uh oh I'm sorry I had
Kiara up by like 50% or
so sorry about that that is my fault all
right hello
hello hello are you ready are you ready
three two one
go who hey hey hey hey where are you
going where you going are you hearing
this
collabing I don't wish to listen to that
why
not it sounds so
good oh is everybody hearing it what
happening are you hearing it
[Music]
party everyone to
the why is somebody is this a club oh my
goodness we're getting down this is a
[Music]
party is that really can people really
find this this lock record it's sick I
we found it cie
we're the first ones in your dungeon it
was secretly hidden oh is it a
secret congratulations on finding it
that's
amazing oh
boy kill him with the basil again on the
how do you st feel
abouta
CL coming in a night
[Music]
I'm very glad that you are having time
that is what matters great thank you for
playing my wow look at how many people
came in here yeah they hurt the
party maybe we should
start I
turned thank you I'm sorry second I got
Queen would you like to hear
it you didn't hear it at all maybe you
have like something turned off she she
came too late play again
everybody I hear it yeah everyone's here
now oh my
goodness oh god wow everybody's here oh
my
good that is something is here is it
really okay
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah gu I am bobing my
[Applause]
head I guess I'll use my size it's quite
in F say so oh my gosh what a
word hey do you remember
I do I do remember
[Music]
recording oh was early send to the B so
get him to say all right yes
taking
for going to be um 500 coins for a
divorce wow
that's 300 coins what's going on no
divorce we don't need your business you
changed the name of that's that's what
you say that's what you say but they'll
come crawling back to me eventually
divorce is in
[Music]
demanded means if it means that I get to
not be the backup plan anymore become
the real plan you're not I'm a DJ now no
no I mean first for other people
for Iris get divorced from joh
[Music]
be firm with your price coins no
no oh now it's time for shk
[Music]
I'm assuming they have all the myth
music yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
call hit
it the see what I mean return to
watch it shows
my
goodness I suppose but I am married is
that
okay let me ask my my
pear I gave you the green light for my
my my Pearl allowed me to dance with
you about an hour
ago was a yes it was
[Music]
Aina do you hear it I have the sound do
you hear it so many people already did
the
quest maybe it needs to restart is your
jukebox music on your B box music it is
indeed here now it should start playing
for you I like the way you hold your do
you hear
it oh these are the d diamond oh yes I
hear it yeah it's the diamonds I she's
already getting diamonds I'm jealous
does this sound familiar do you feel
your memory is coming back to you kind
of similar names
[Music]
sorry I got rid of it oh do you want to
hear this one
too oh it's bringing back old the
memories my memor maybe 4 years ago what
said
fun are we going to get copyright St
maybe maybe
it's okay this was before she joined
Universal so say rip V let's go I don't
know what that means but let's go it's a
guild it's another guild Sky it's a
universal The Guild oh The Guild or they
pretty famous they're they're pretty big
yeah famous they're Universal they hire
talented BS all over the world wow such
BS such BS much music very
[Music]
hello hello hello what what is happening
what are you guys
ising no we were we were talking of day
we shall we go to the go to the
panicking down C down down C down down
n water dungeon let us go us
where is Nissa ravencraft and Mory copi
yeah yeah where where' they go we we
talk another time mayhaps we should
call dangerous now kind of I will
call
okay what happened what did you talk
about I'm going to go check the uh I I
I'm not going to tell you I don't trust
you I'm sorry what so many side quest no
after you left Amber con I don't trust
you anymore
where I thought you both left ambercoin
do not pry Shakira Shakira
Shakira what do you mean I am with you
talk like that I know but still do not
do not
pry I have I have between us but I am
concerned because I have been told that
you may actually be leading me on we are
a bus you're leading me on aren't you
leading no leading you on I don't know
how else to phrase it
leading you on am I really your your KN
in your service or am I less than that
to you no you are my night I have good
okay yes yes yes okay glad we were able
to clarify this good I I will I will
rely on that okay thank you Shakira
thank you my queen thank you thank you
be on the lookout on the behalf of her
kingdom yes I will thank you for your
mercy my queen of course of
course of course of
hor
um Justice we bring Justice in this word
yeah oh your your weapon is yellow
shining oh yeah because I did the second
dungeon and I think when you make when
you make the second dungeon to yep
sounds good you become stronger oh I
must oh you're yellow too I must gain
this sprank that you guys
have I
best good luck with your with your D
thank you thank
you care oh you guys are so close to
me
okay wow thank you rock that that that
girl looks like a rock have you noticed
that eh what kind of rocks have you seen
so far I don't know she looks like a
rock she looks like a am if anything to
me sparkling gem I don't know it was
more like a
rock so I don't know we did we did the
things we wanted to do you must
understand what's going
on um I like when the go then the go by
with the horse is funny mhm there's
always like something going on you got
to watch all the PE of these guys yeah
ah ah we got we ah turn we can turn in
the side quest yeah uh oh yeah at the
quest Master have to I have to go now
okay but I'll continue my side quest
tomorrow or tonight see okay thank you
so much I'll see you soon in uh like in
days oh yeah when you come back okay we
uh me I want to help you with all the
Dan okay okay like since there is
revisiting side quest
you can revisit them well it is my first
time yeah yeah I want to play with you
so please uh let me know what time you
come so I I make sure to be here for you
okay thank you thank you for watch
watching out for me thank you yeah of
course we do together we are a team no
matter what politics come between
us even if you regret being a Ember coin
I am a loyal Ember Co and even if don't
recognize yourself as an ember C member
I do think you are always part of this
Guild even if you don't think so I mean
I don't know it's not like that I don't
think uh uh so it's just you know like
um I I feel like I needed some company
and it was offered to me kindly by the
Jade girls you know I didn't want to be
on my own too much no because I'm always
here yeah you are you are that's true
it's all right I got you it's the best
wor thank you I see you soon okay take
care of you all right G thank you for
playing with me it was fun thank you
too Amber coin Amber coin Amber coin
Amber coin
yay L kiata coin is rising stones ston
stons
no me telling Iris to join amorn was in
the first like hour of the first
day yeah when we it looked like we had a
chance to get her into our
group but in the end she went to where
her Destiny
laid um wait uh wait uh I I wanted to uh
how do I leave the group again oh
yeah
okay ah let's give back my quest or is
this how I do it a I talk to
you oh oh I got 200 coins from
it but they like gave food for the like
first Quest or so I thought they would
give food again but they
don't they don't yeah we did find her
before her actual team did
[Music]
yeah orange you know I'm being drawn to
the color orange after all it's it's
difficult to go to any other color
colors honestly Scarlet Scarlet one was
kind of as a color speaking to me too as
a color and as also
the the how to
say I I I IDE IDE I I don't know yeah
before the scams
yeah the ideology
mhm no we we resorted into it that's
just how it you know happens just with
like the the
Wizards so I don't know I think we'll
end it here and I'll read some super
chats it's probably the best way to do
it uh cuz I still got some
time before I go to do some dance
practice I have a lot of a lot of dance
practice to do I'm I'm kind of worried
honestly I don't want to think about it
but um cuz tomorrow and the day after
tomorrow I have a really
long um 3D recording on both days for my
frd
live the W life it's a lot of work you
know
[Music]
yeah so I'll be missing the coming two
days of the server which is really sad
because I feel like today I was able to
mingle with a lot of people and and it
was a lot of fun and to interact with so
many so now missing out on the next two
days is sad but I'll come back even
stronger or even more weaker because my
muscles will be so
[Laughter]
sore yeah
it's okay uh we'll be fine like I'm not
the only one right like I think Bae took
a break today I don't know if she's
missing every day but and then I heard M
she told me that she's going to be
missing uh a couple of days
too one or two days or
so raid she raided me oh that's I'm not
ending I'm watching I'm reading Super
Chat so I guess the AO raate would be
that's completely a waste although only
one person said
it yeah but you see that just shows you
again that ember coin
is a little bit unfortunate like we're
besides L we're all kind of
like all over the place not able to
participate fully so personally I think
it's maybe
um you know it's just how things go that
we we might want to join other groups
because not all of our Guild members
would be a and you know I could have
thank you thank you welcome welcome Raa
raid we could have you know done if if
we were to do our dungeon today with
only
us I don't know I think mum left early
didn't she or was she still there but
you know we would never be we probably
would never manage to be full again
after the first day so we got to mingle
we got to mingle and I had fun
mingling yeah chatini chatini what's up
what's up
everybody hello I'm going to read super
chats but I like to yappa yappa yappa in
between so feel free to stay um which
room should we go
[Music]
to not sure should we go to
this
room I'm a bit big in
here doesn't quite match the vibe I do
have an RPG room but uh the night room
but I don't have it like in OBS right
now I'd have to prepare
it well yeah let's just be in here I
like the colors
[Music]
or there's the
airport which is a really
scenery or the frog
room or the summer
room let's let's do this
one I look like a
stupidus zoom in on the mountain
oh or we could zoom in here
too just
show everything beyond the opening of
the door but this is so pretty though
wow ain't this
pretty actually zooming in wasn't such a
bad idea I like those
sunflowers
wow I make myself a bit smaller should I
change you know what I'll change clothes
[Music]
M
mhm this is
better meow I am laa just an
orange I am L just orange believe
me chatini don't you recognize
me see I can speak
b b orange cat let me take off my
glasses they might be confusing you see
now you recognize me right I took off
the glasses now now you recognize
me cucumber no oh not the Cucumber
[Laughter]
ah the hand gestures I have to do the
hand gestures I can do some hand gestes
here I'll prove it further to
you I'll prove it further to you
[Music]
uh here
uh here that's a hand
gesture wow wow if I wasn't Italian
would I really be able to do
this Chi listen Chi listen to Mama
tatini but I want to hold I want to hold
the
chicken
chicken so chatini chatini and kfp I
hope you enjoyed our journey I am so
excited literally like you guys don't
understand how excited I was when I saw
that extra treasure chest in the
Atlantis dungeon and I
realized
oh maybe there was a treasure chest in
the other dungeon after all and it was
exactly where I thought it would
be so
satisfying so satisfying and I had a
moment of Doubt when the tree the the
one tree the one that's closest to it
when there was just no path to get
higher
yeah but then Elizabeth thought that
maybe we got to grow the other trees and
then they ended up
connecting yeah you had to you ended up
having to do so much platforming jumping
from One Tree to the other back to the
other back to the other back to the
other yeah that one was yeah at last one
was way more obvious but no I mean to me
the first one was obvious too cuz I
immediately felt like oh guys guys you I
feel like there's something over there
my RPG senses are telling me but then I
lost my confidence when they all already
went ahead uh and I I was stuck in the
tree not finding the right
way that that got rid of my
confidence but I I I thought there's
something there there's there must be a
reason why that tree is so high H sus
very sus cuz it reached the exact height
of um the the platform on the other
side and all that height was unused and
if there's a maximum of of height that
the tree can reach then why would it not
be lower just so that you can go move on
to the other direction n there's a
reason wow I feel so smart
I think you can buy more music records
in the shop too I didn't see is it non
myth
records I thought they would maybe keep
that for like if there's a future a
future of
this wait she posted
the founda posted a a lottery notice in
our Discord with a picture and
everything
ah
funny wait next one I wonder what their
next dungeon is as you can tell it's not
debut order um but I think
mine might
be up
next
possibly I'm not sure or you think en
know I don't know when if when you
proceed with it you could probably tell
I I have a feeling it's not going to be
on the day where I am like it's going to
be one of the days where I am not
available but I'll still do it
afterwards I'll still do it I have so
many manions oh my
God you be
[Music]
I have so many mansions do you guys want
music here there you go is this
[Music]
double a double how about now
okay okay okay uh last time we read
super chats where did we leave off let's
let's read some let's read some
more oh okay
sloping
pozer part-time worker
[Music]
sorry I'm a bit
distracted that's a while back yeah cuz
only because we skipped like a few and
then I I read from the top from the like
newest ones instead of the oldest
ones but we're closing
in part-time
worker that's before isn't that before
yeah before I went to Japan
still okay yeah I did some Skipper
Skipper but don't worry I always come
back I always come back this one with a
little bit of a sussy thumbnail
mhm okay here we go they G me D Jacob
47 py
py
[Music]
py guy man thank you for the red super
chat O A lurker huh just realized I've
been a member for a year now and I love
everything you do for kfb wa like still
finding time to stream even when you're
busy I hope that all the work you're
doing right now will have great payoff
also nice
thumbnail well some of it already had
payoff yeah like breaking dimensions and
partially World Tour to an extent we'll
get a little bit more payoff with you
know when my 3D life comes
out um yeah but there's a lot a lot of
stuff going on still but slowly slowly
after this last thing I I'll finally be
able to calm down in in my brain m
[Music]
It's the final stretch
switch yeah I got to say like I feel
like I'm mentally really exhausted
from like powering through all of
this
H it's because I know I have to get
through all of it I have to there's like
nothing that I could have delayed
there's nothing I could have pushed
aside or this it's just I had to do all
of
this you know America trip had to be
done it's like I
mean yeah it had to be done
so duty calls me I'm like a superhero
[Music]
but it's you know whatever how much
stress I'm facing through it I'm still
having a lot of
fun um you
know and I like to see the results of my
heart work
[Music]
mm FAL guys FAL
so
this got a fight like the night that I
[Music]
am thank you anyway guyman thank you
it's nice to hear from
you thank you so much for saying hi and
for being a member for a year we have a
new member's wallpaper I didn't upload
it yet I'm sorry but it's already in the
schedule so doesn't it look nice
dumre drew it and once again gave me
really really nice um drafts several
drafts that I had to choose from which
was
hard but yeah it's anniversary month
officially it's
September do you
remember it's September oh my God oh my
God Ah that's the ninth month of the
year holy [\h__\h] was so so far from the
beginning of the
year
uh how come how come yeah there's only
four months left if we include this one
obviously cuz it just
began oh
God N I don't want to think about it
even this is too stressful to even think
about
that
yeah I hate that time goes so
fast I want to take things
[Music]
slower I really want to take things
slower I feel like everything's going
too fast
and no the year almost ending scares
me I I just want to stay and stop stand
still and stop
time but let's stop time when I'm back
with my
cats when I'm reunited with them that
then that's when I would press stop time
emergency button please stop abort abort
abort customer Johnson danash vs Rings
CV danash this is a name
dun oh glad you're enjoying wit spring R
and the rise D Wing CV d and D Pablo
thanks for the red super jet cute cute
profile picture love all the Crowbar
assault 10 out of 10 thank you that was
a fun game even though it was
stupid thank you
you py alud D Crow D youf D
kfp no no
[Music]
come py d space waterful Dan CR at D Na
and cotton than for the pinky hi ateno I
unfortunately won't be able to catch any
weekend streams this week cuz I've got
to go to a wedding specifically my
brothers not mine I look forward to
catching up on the archive next week's
stream then see you then thank you well
I'm sure this is already you know a long
time ago
so how was the wedding what did you wear
a suit M I feel like it's so easy for
men because you can just like wear a
suit there's like not you don't have to
think too
hard but
then I like would think so hard about
what to wear and I don't really know
where to get nice dresses really like
IRL and IRL shops like the shops that I
know in Austria the the dresses all look
like [\h__\h] like they're boring and or the
shape is weird doesn't
fit and the design is like it just looks
cheap even if it's expensive it still
looks weird lame
design where where to get nice
dresses I'll be on the lookout
as
[Music]
always oh I'll just go
naked senior MC thanks for the red super
chat no text why you have nothing to say
oh this is senior MC de I wonder you
always super chatting from
Brazil now I hope that you're not going
to miss out too much I I was thinking
like all the Brazil uh H life
FS we could all just you know bring you
into the H live uh Plus app I don't know
if it's open again was it closed the
global one is it currently
accessible it's
open all right we all got to get on
there I don't think there's a single end
member on there yet is there
have not really instructed us how to do
it and I'm too busy and too lazy or
mostly busy to figure it out on my own
the few moments of time that I have I
don't want to like occupy my mind with
how how the hell it
[Music]
works I don't think you can post as you
what do you
mean I don't think there's any Talent on
there
H and maybe they all just are like who
who who who overwhelmed
it's not like Twitter Hey I thought it
was going to be like
Twitter but does it like repost so to
say our tweets from
Twitter or not it's just official post
and denos fans what what me advertising
Hol Plus on an official stream and then
not knowing how it really
works you don't follow people
what they had such a great chance to
like make our own little
[Music]
Twitter then it would have been really
good for moments like these where a
whole [\h__\h] country gets banned from
Twitter and they don't know where to go
to find all our information this would
have been a great time for
it
[Music]
bro it's more like Facebook with no
friends
Mama
M okay well simply
D this one's
[Music]
finished what about Fallout New Vegas
part 4 did I read
[Music]
those probably not right
okay ja 47 chocolate and D candy
stamps the K St thanks for the pinky
[Music]
noise cancelling headphones work by
playing an equal but opposite sound wave
of incoming sounds to cancel them out if
your pair comes with an app there may be
a way to include yapping frequencies
interesting there but I don't it doesn't
sound like it's playing
anything you say they're playing its own
sound to cancel the others but I don't
hear anything being
played
what
magic not science that's
[Music]
magic
witchcraft it means it's working
[Music]
that's crazy that's
witchcraft that's
witchcraft S7 b42 dun un need chat dun
the M kitten Dan but I feel like these
kind of things are really fascinating
for
sure magic sword
King thanks for the pinky wow back let's
go oh hey Tak guess you're back huh
didn't miss you at all yeah where was I
during this
time thank you for welcoming me
back was this when I went to Thailand or
when I went to Germany or when when I
went to
Japan yes the answer is yes
right around the world around the world
oh Italy around the world around the
world
Around the World Around the World Around
the World Around the World Around the
World Around the World Around the World
Around the World Around the World Around
the World Around the World Around the
World Around the World Around the World
Around the World
Around right I shouldn't do that
now the V the V wouldn't die from it but
I did get like uh like yeah like ID
content I did before when I sang too
much of a song but that time I didn't
even use the same lyrics I just used the
melody the singing Melody I didn't play
the instrumental I didn't use the same
lyrics and kind of came up with my own
lyrics but it's okay it doesn't really
do
[Music]
anything as long as it's not like taking
down the whole VOD m
[Music]
oh another explanation for noise
cancelling thank
you good night moon dog is it sweepy
time could the VOD rip due to
mmca no I I I I would hope that those
two songs no they're not going to do
anything we've I've sang those in like
Koka streams before those songs are
okay uh they're probably going to do
hinoto for mine right
because it seems like they're going with
like the the first original song of each
[Music]
person but I don't know I feel like they
should do sparks or
[Music]
something I just hope that when I can't
be there and the first person finds the
Vin that vinyl V that somebody will go
and play it and people will have a party
just like when we had a party with the
vins vinyls
today I hope they'll have a
party on their
own you subjected Cali to rip so you're
going to have to deal if you that's okay
I mean it's not like um it's not like um
I I I love the song it's legendary so
I don't feel embarrassed or anything
about
[Music]
it yeah they all showed up like as if
they knew where it was playing how did
they know where it was
playing when they didn't know that it
would do that cuz they seemed surprised
and unknowing then how did they know
that it was there no but it seemed to be
playing everywhere right but it
uh because I I got a little bit like uh
further from it and it was still
[Music]
playing I think they were closed by like
all these people were
just like spontaneously closed
by yeah even if they hear it though how
do they know where it is I wouldn't have
known where to
go I would have had no
idea I think giggy or said they were
calling
people to
come
based super based she's so
[Music]
cute uh anyway uh a yeah let me read the
uh where was I oh here
uh the steel Dan the steel danar thanks
for the pinky can you do that jce this
no jce this no jce this no there you go
thank
you Nathan cotton thanks for the red
super chat hi ateno I got back for my
trip yesterday and when I found out I
didn't miss any wa streams oh well Color
Me surprised and that color would be
pink cuz I got a little sunburn you
don't mean red because you sent a red
Super Chat huh not too bad compared to
when you have us clean the ovens hope
you enjoyed your dream thank
you thank you thank you welcome back I
hope your
sunburn has calmed down it looks better
now ah the outoor wedding got you ah you
guys probably thought oh it's just a
wedding we're not wearing swimsuits so
we'll surely not get a sunburn and
then what were was your was it your face
or what because you were as I said
probably wearing a suit
[Music]
right your face like for ladies could be
like their shoulders and so on sunburn
man it gets you when you least expect
it be
careful pretty casual wedding oh so what
you came in with a tank top or
what even with a casual wedding I think
men will still show up with like a a
proper shirt and a relatively proper
pants with Polo and
jeans
what what
what
[Music]
H I feel like I like the idea of like
pretty uh casual looking
uh locations for a
wedding but then people should still
show up in nice
clothes well as long as you don't show
up with [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
[Music]
Crocs
Pablo he don't think of the pinky and
I'm a Brazilian where did my Brazilians
go maybe I should make a
pause uh in my lesbians Quest and uh
look for the
Brazilians should they take priority I
don't know I've been looking for the
lesbians for a while we're here
are you where are my
Brazilians are you
here and there some
overlap
yeah well where is pate where is Oak
proud where are
they yeah I know they is just the Bird
app but like they're not here either
they should be here attendance
[Music]
check yeah P never use chat true true
true
mostly
Brazil
brail it's 3:00 a.m. 3:00 a.m. it's late
okay you think that's an excuse
hello sa idle business regulation the d
leish d Cru D Jackson D the steel d d
lunch
7 monkey looking for the top the Ste
chicken than the
pinky a super chat for the list today's
my
birthday I finally reached your birthday
oh my God I'm glad I'm spending it with
w and KY let's go v w KY I'm so sorry
sry you're laughing but I see your
tears it's been
years
no
sorry happy
birthday to you happy birthday in your
shoe happy birthday in your pants
too happy birthday to you don't eat the
moldy cake don't eat it now yes you can
finally blow out the candles if they
haven't already set your house on
fire um I'm sure you were waiting you
had that cake you had the candles you
had them turn on you sent the Super Chat
waiting for me to sing for you so that
you can blow him
out but I hope nothing was set on
fire usually is when when the candle
when the fire reaches the bottom of the
candle I would hope it just goes out
what happens what happens what
[Music]
happened I'm the first
person H 2025 you mean 2024
right I may be the first person but
there's I'm not the only one now there's
many who wish you a happy birthday so
happy
birthday oh oh that's a joke because you
it's so late you already assume it for
next year no it's for this year
though it's for this year I'll I'll say
it hopefully more on time next
[Music]
year happy
birthday say it's m Mo CH Channel d
commandry g Psy D Alex the star child D
and
[Music]
okay next is fitboxing with hatu n Miku
I'm assuming I didn't read this yet this
one has quite a bit
[Music]
more but with that maybe I'm caught up
with that is that maybe where I stopped
when I went backwards because I saw
there were so many super Chats on
[Music]
it I would see that as a
possibility no EDF oh my God okay I'll
do my best check out for the seven d d
space water D dhood thanks for the pinky
ma'am this is the grateful yoders and
tantalizing thumnail
Society g y a t t a cat I was like what
does it spell out no it doesn't look
like it's spelling out anything actually
it is we want to present you with this
pink Super Chat and kfps gratitude keep
up the great work
y thank you yeah this this um thumnail
kind of reminds me of that one Riser
thumbnail I made a long time
ago thank you for your appreciation it
is a good one I I knew I knew that I
this is what I
needed
spicy spicy
[Music]
fake
ties save
lives uh
[Music]
J cotton thanks for the pinky who put
the super cute Phoenix on my screen I
have words for them mostly thank you and
variations thereupon but words
nonetheless why why you speaking so
fancy
wow you sound so sophisticated you sound
like you're role
playing like one of us on the server on
the Minecraft server I need to learn
from your words share them with me
Cruz sorry got
confused JP R
snsr say thanks for the red super chat
let's go let's go
indeed thank you m
d youo XGC D Dusty chicken d h guard D
ping Channel D the faction thanks the
pinky four four four
yes press four nothing's happening now
you got to go to the Chima Vault guys
you got to press four on the Chima uh
not V music video
yeah you did of course you did of course
you sent the Super Chat it was
irresistible Papa Dan Aro Ry Dan Anon
Dan Edis Dan G thanks for the red super
chat dear Lord boss this is incredible
this model of dist tracking is just wow
if only you could do choro practice
streams with this as if you were in a
studio um I think I I mean I I could in
the future definitely could I brought my
whole motion capture stuff to Japan I'm
pissed that I had no time to use it
because it took up quite a bit of my
luggage space man and my [\h__\h]
subscription refreshes each month and
then there's some months where I'm not
using it that also pisses me
off but I never like really
know so
like man I think it's 250 bucks per
month
yeah it just refreshed so we better use
it in the coming 30 days we
gotta maybe I've been like still kind of
hoping to do this stream that I I think
I mentioned in members only the not
stream I guess it's a video um but I
can't I don't know I it's like
complicated and I don't have much time
anyway so I'm I'm thinking maybe I don't
do it this time I'll do it another
time
um so you might just have to wait
until I have time to stream because this
was going to be like cuz I can't stream
on on my anniversary right
but I mean there will be something else
right something else that I will not say
like super clearly but we all know it's
happening and so they will be that and
then I'll follow with a solo stream or
so soon
after um maybe we'll make it
3D with my fever night model perhaps
mhm I asked for a wa 3d concert in the
feedback form oh there's already a
feedback form for breaking
Dimensions we didn't get one yet for the
talents I think I have
feedback well then oh you did too really
thank
you asking for Wawa solo Freddy I think
like IRL venue
is pretty
ambitious I think the chances are still
very low but we got to let him know
somehow
right we got to let him know that there
is some demand wa on demand
[Music]
H well what was wrong with the camera
for Fire and
[Music]
Ice what was wrong with it I didn't see
it cuz I was on
[Music]
stage I literally didn't see
it oh they zoomed too much too many
close-ups
h I have to watch it they usually like
tell us uh like whatever uh like for the
previous one for the Blu-ray they ask us
hey we're putting out a Blu-Ray so let
us know if you want certain scenes to be
changed to different angles and this and
that
[Music]
so okay I'll see what I can do when I
get to
it I'm glad you guys say it was better
than usual that's good well thank you
gried in
Maha King kitten dun spice wonderful D
Brock 6,000 things for the red super
chat I it feels like it's been a while
since I saw you Super Chat fantastic new
3D model T hoping for another 80s car
with it sometime or maybe an aerobics
class to whip us chimpin into shape yeah
I still got to do my aerobics routine it
wasn't that good anyway what I came up
with but uh I guess I'll
I'll showcase it at some
point thank you so much for your
interest for investing into the aerobics
coin Mr titties d d zate d command thr D
Che Channel D thank you D chocolate and
S thanks fry amazing fre me tracking
technology wow I'm going to get need my
sunglasses so I can look respectfully
the stream hey also never mentioned but
I've always loved the way you say risky
in feet oh thank you I never thought
there was anything wrong with it
honestly some people didn't like it but
I don't know maybe that's a thing you
only feel when English is your first
language but then again it was written
by somebody who whose first language is
in
[Music]
English a risky
breakdown a risky break wait how won you
say it
though how won't you say
it RIS
K what what's that
[Music]
I don't see an issue with
it because it could have been what I
mean risky and
risque in the
end can kind of mean the same
[Music]
thing they can be used
similarly
[Music]
like
I I
I
[Music]
always no but risky can also be more for
the sexy type like a risky
[Music]
outfit
wait
people always when they say it's a risky
outfit
were they thinking of a RS r i s q u
e well in any case then just ignore that
it's Q E and just think of it as r i s k
y and it can be risky breakdown I mean
any kind of breakdown can be risky
because I mean you
[Music]
know
huh I think
I think I really never realized that
that's what everybody's everybody was
[Music]
saying
what
what now I
[Music]
wonder if she sang it like that in the
demo cuz that's a different issue that
I'm focusing on now I thought it was
something
else okay well whatever let's move on
interesting uh
thanks for the red super chat oh my God
super cute oh cute you say most people
were like M spicy I'm glad you see the
cuteness in
it a d thank you so much py D thanks for
the pinky God bless
technology yes indeed I'm so glad I like
experimented around a little bit and
found good
way to show off this
model we have a great risky future ahead
of us or should I say
risque F long than r Super Chat I think
this old chicken is going to have a
heart attack if you keep leaning forward
like that D I had to lean forward
because when I stand the monitor was
like below me and I had to lean forward
like like look down so that I could see
the chat and myself and
everything careful if you don't see me
at breaking Dimensions you know what
happened drums I leave my home feeder I
hope it works for K you have a home
feeder damn
nice e how big is it how many sofas do
you have how nice is it show me
[Music]
picture you can do all the like like Bon
I got D watch alongs and so on in there
isn't that
sick which by the way we will continue
when I'm back
home there's just no time these past
weeks like this week and that last we
I I think you guys would all agree that
the the few days where I was able to
stream I should not be doing a members
watch
along not be little bit
sad we can do it when there's more
time yeah so let's stay patient and not
watch the new season
yet thank you for long M I hope your
heart is okay I do think I saw you with
breaking Dimensions so seems like you
are
fine that's good wi CV D mental jelly
Dan Andy at home D magin danime fan
Danon yikes my b
W tun thanks for the pinky I'm loving
this the stream for how good the face
tracking is you look so good cute oh
yeah yeah yeah blend shapes baby blend
shapes something we have to use a 1
million wish for in whole
life but I got it for my vivite model
and for my default model you know I just
can't use it in the official app
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yippe thank you for acknowledging it you
mik D Mr treble cleff
d uh depressed dead be D
know o z 176 thank you Dan for the red
super chat the model itself was already
fantastic but combined with the precise
tracking makes it truly Godly thank you
I shall use it again this stream really
left a strong impression on people I
think I also feel like a lot of the like
views on it are like VA views from
people who watched clips and were like
oh wow like more way more than other
streams you know like a lot of people
came in when they heard the word going
around like o
o o o what do I hear spicy butt Jingles
m
M let me check that W out for
[Music]
sure yeah was featured on the news the
Holo
[Music]
news I appreciate it thanks for checking
it out guys thank you o I'm a
beep thanks for the pinky buying more wa
heart energy thanks for spoiling us boss
thank you what's wa heart energy what is
that you purchased it how what is
that what is that I don't understand but
sounds like something good thank you I
like to spoil you guys when I can you
guys spoil me too after all P for dress
D cap cap D youo XGC
D weird cat on the TV meow meow
Jim dazy thanks for the pinky this is so
cool the model is amazing and the
tracking is insane it was so fun to see
you jamming to mik songs and improving
as the stream went on plus we got to see
you perform fight in the fite outfit
exactly legendary I do think it would be
nice if I
can
like eventually at some point make the
Sparks outfit into 3D too I really do
like the Sparks outfit and I know a lot
of you guys like it too
so maybe we'll get ourselves a Sparks
model
too and you know Chima
model will would look
really really
sick but I would need like a full body
reference because I don't really
have a proper one I
think got to ask the artist to maybe if
they can put something
together h
[Music]
yeah let's do it let's do
it let's do
[Music]
it the one on the album jacket
mhm which really does seem to have quite
the Synergy with Callie's album cover
outfit too
coincidentally we both have this
like weird
arm that link also
had and like
loose not not much fabric and the fabric
pretty loose and I don't know it's just
I I don't know how to describe it but it
has quite a
Synergy Jim Tracy thanks for the pinky
wait I already read that thank you he s
[Music]
Flappy boy thank you for two red super
chats through tonight's infernal hotness
I finally risen from the bucket to
become a totally legit Phoenix myself
mhm legit while I strangely seem to like
any Phoenix Powers what's stranger yet
is how tagging along your journey for 2
years has helped me grow as a person a
on a somewhat related note I've noticed
that how I'm already on the Day 26 of my
24 a straight ass challenge what
abstaining from any alcohol has become
so basic by now that I kind of lost
track of time thanks so and love to my
Kami for inspiring me to get there wow
why did you feel like doing that do you
did you feel like you had a little bit
of a a problem of like uh drinking too
much if yes then I'm so glad I could
like inspire you
to take some distance from it
and even if you didn't honestly like
you're just saving
money and staying
healthy no uh getting too drunk and
then having uh what is it what is it
called again in Germany we say Kata the
next
day he's good he's expansive too
hangover yeah no
hangovers and you're saving money so
let's [\h__\h] can go also it doesn't even
taste
good but I don't know some of you might
disagree with me on that
one well well well congratulations on
that I'm so proud of
you oo you're getting closer to a year a
full year of
[Music]
that m m MW Flappy boy let's go I am
cheering you on
let's go Flappy
boy
H trash the alcohol poy let's go Flappy
boy trash that alcohol po let's go
Flappy boy trash that alcohol po po is
the sound when you throw something away
in
[Music]
Japanese I know thanks for the pinky
this is such an incredible stream I love
everything about this so much fre fever
night vaa is way too powerful mhm the
tracking is seriously so amazing I might
die from too much cuteness my Oshi is
literally absolute cutest in the
universe thank you I'm so glad people
appreciated this uh fite model so
much
yippee glad I can get you guys something
nice every once in a while Mary Pippin D
bring c d d have d m d thanks for the
pinky this was such a trait I can't
believe the model is fanmade truly a
work of love thank you for the stream
this was so hype thank
you yeah it's a really good
model I'm happy with the outcome too
thank you so much zipley the pink Super
Chat pink is very similar to the
leggings pink the color of the
[Music]
butt isn't that
nice reminds me of the
butt same same
color FR SC thanks for red Super Chat it
was a very amazing stream Kwa I'm sure
you beat and punched Miku with the best
clucky moves or something I was a bit
distracted I may have died twice during
the middle but I got to rewatch The
Vault a few times to see such a
legendary fight yeah you have to I
Really it was so much more exhausting
than I thought I think because I was
like because I was in 3D I wanted to get
really into it
and also I was screaming and panting
because of excitement so it just makes
it more and more
exhausting I feel like if I wasn't
streaming and I was just like following
along as if I was playing the game
normally I
wouldn't you know lose that much energy
on it but I I was pretty dead pretty
dead and sweaty and those punches man
and it just like pisses me off when I'm
like punching and then it doesn't
register it so I try to punch even
harder with even more Dynamic to it and
that's just more exhausting cuz I legit
was punching you saw it there's proof of
it in Fry and it just doesn't register
it so
[Music]
often oh well and then you know I wanted
to see things jiggle so I add more
bounce to my
movement that's making it more
exhausting too
I do it for you guys I do it for
[Music]
you want to see the butt
jiggle okay that was my last sip of
water I need to buy water
[Music]
again uh FR thank you g d Patrick FB
dang Sky d py d dou dangun and last but
not least with a pinky the gamer Creed
finally achieved my long awaited chicken
armor yippee thank you k for four
amazing years of being the best and oi a
small chicken like me could ever ask for
I'll be wearing the armor with great
pride as the true orange kfp employee
that I am thank you so much I really
really appreciate it thank you for
staying with me for such a long time
it's not a given and I really cherish
everybody's love and attention and
support
thank you so much on to more time
together in
kfp I'm going to stop it there got to
take a little break and then go dance
dance dance with my hands
[Music]
hands
m m
sorry I'm checking mentions
[Music]
again
cool cool cool cool
cool a nice dance dance dance with my
hands hands hands let me see see
see who can I raid whole lies are always
gives me a nice
overview
over
gigy I want to raid gigy or
[Music]
cie oh no it's anniversary month I'm
going to rate cie it's our
anniversary
copine I'm surprised she still hasn't
said anything about me calling her that
maybe she hasn't been noticing maybe she
thinks like acoustically something must
be
wrong I'm certainly saying something
else
[Music]
right no no not no one Sometimes some
people pointed out KY and I'm like
[Music]
yeah she's just acceptance yeah cuz it's
me K
I'll stop calling her once this ends
this Arc don't
[Music]
[Laughter]
worry
okay in oh God wish me luck the next two
days I'm going to
die I'm probably going to die but it's
okay I'll I'll try my best to wait until
the end of the week cuz I have my death
scheduled on
Sunday and I don't want to like stack
too many deaths one after another
it's kind of difficult with like
Reviving each time it takes a
[Music]
while H I got a reply from
someone
who wow that's kind of [\h__\h]
late
oh interesting anyway
anyway a German we V
[Music]
in yeah
someone special who I was trying to
invite to
something now now you're going to reply
to me
now not for this
one
but yeah for the future well see we'll
see
u
u unbelievable
[Music]