[Music]
[Applause]
T
[Music]
[Applause]
OG
[
Music] T [Music]
DET
[Music]
In a certain country, there was a
donkey girl.
She
seemed blessed, but her heart was never full.She
lived like a doll, wondering who she really was.When she
looked around, she saw all the small, beloved dogs.  I'm
the only one with a big figure and a loud
voice. Don't be afraid, let's play together.
There was a cat who wanted to be really cool, but
everyone was lying to him.
In reality, he just wanted to entertain everyone,
but he just loved it.
[Music]  ] I'm
jealous that I have to work every day, right?
It's a fun and enjoyable farm. But every day I do the same thing
over and over again. There's a place where I can shine even more.
[Music]
Or the world's greatest thief.  I don't
have an eye for gold and silver,
but I don't want to do anything bad.I
just want to make the poor people
smile.But how much better would it be if I could smile too
?Donkeys with big worries, your
story
begins now.
This is the [music] of the adventures of animals who believe in the power of music.It is the mysterious magic that gives color, courage, and dreams to our lives.This is the [music] of the adventures of animals who believe in the power of music.
StoryGood morning, good morning, good
morning.Good morning, what a beautiful
morning.Good morning.Good morning.You
have a beautiful tail.Good morning.Good
morning.A greeting that I hear as I walk.If my stomach
clears, I've finished my ceremony in a beautiful dress.It's time to come out.
Good morning, father, as the day begins.Good
morning.Have you finished eating?
By the way, if you have a recent problem, hurry up and change your clothes.I
understand, father, that you will be busy today.  I
walk through my life with a smile on my face. I don't even know what's me and what's
not. If I sing a song with my hands,
I'll become the real me.
[Music] I can
go anywhere in the forest.  But if you're
in the world of songs that you can live in, then we're holding a music festival for all of you in oil-rich countries.Find
your favorite music of songs with accents from all over the world.This is
what I've decided to do.
Let's find it, find my own song that will change the world
[Applause]
By the way, where should I go, Breme, here?
That way?
Oh, I surprised you again. Actually, I just
wanted to play.
[Music] That's all I heard.
Time is strong,
and you're a no-good guy who always annoys others just because you're different from others.You have a really
nice
voice, right?It's so loud.  You'll
surprise everyone. Let's hear it again.
Then, this time, bark twice to the music. You're the
enemy. If we overlap, we'll
find a place and start resonating.
[Music]
Wan Wan
[Music]  I'm sure
there are things you can do with this voice, so let's go together.  In the
morning of my departure, I
will open my throne to the Initiate and hand it over to him. What does that mean? That means I
gave up my seat to an elderly person in the morning.
It's beautiful,
but it's still a strange melody. A song that opens in a foreign country. It's a
new and
interesting adventure.
[Music]
Let's dedicate ourselves
to each other, so that we can shine even more as we go. That's music, so let's do our best together.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] Let's do
what makes us saddest than anyone else.
Even at the end of a square sea, people can change.  In a
world where everyone forgets that they're playing a
part, everyone will slip out someday.When I
hold it in my hand, I'll send it to the sky.I'll
give you a mysterious name and
reassure
you.
Mystery
[Music]
Even if I hit the constellations and run away from the sky, I still
feel nostalgic in my body, don't you think? In a timeless country,
in this town that doesn't need anyone, I picture the
blue sun falling hot snow without windows, doors, or walls.
Freedom, with no mistakes or answers, my
dear, the one who
protects me with my abandoned wings is
Yokoshima Kiyoshi, who hugged me and flew away
[Music]
I sink into white death, but it's hard.  I
gave up on the fluttering companion who was wandering, and I cast a curse on him with the strong darkness of the feathers.I made a wish
without praying.I made a mistake in the behavior of a baby.Whether I am
friends with God
or not, I am
mysterious.I am
your friend.
[Music]
Let's play the best role in a mystery
Ah
[Music] The
elements of throwing and rolling that you know in your head  I
laughed. I threw him away, a person who doesn't know what loneliness and love are. I
can't get out of this small box with words that I can't hold in front of me. I was
playing the role of someone who ran away, but I was
heading towards the end credits.  Everyone is
acting so desperately that no one is impressed by
it. I'm not a nobody. I'm sure I
can't be anything. So,
I'm going to do it now and extend it, and no
one can do anything about the development of the drama.  You too  I
was crying and crawling, but my
heart was melting, and I pulled the tama. Don't
move to my eyes.
In the meantime, I've become a monster.
If I don't acknowledge everything, I can't move forward. It's probably not
possible for you, so it's definitely not possible for you. Before you know it, we've
been doing this. We're all desperate.  I
'm trying to protect myself and wait for a way to save me.I've been holding on to it all the time, but I
can't become anything.And that's why you've
been saying those words in such a dramatic way just now.
Yes, we promised each other at the tournament, and we only had one shot. I
felt like I was going to climax for a moment, but the truth that I was hiding was nowhere to be found. There's no place for the people who laughed at me. I remember and threw away, but I have no feelings.  The reason for the tears  I
can't even feel the warmth of your tenderness.
All I can do is sing in my outstretched hands. I want to give you sweet love.
This is a book about me, who is
about to give up. You're the one who's about to give up, and you're always
singing to me.  What does it look like?
Take a breath, I'll never be anything,
and
I'll fight a long battle, and I'll
put aside the dramatic development of my love, and you'll be
there, too, even though it's cold there.  Take your heart
out and just look at me,
Reba.  What I
see is a donkey, a cat, and a cat who set out for Brehme, and as they walk in search of a place where they can shine, there is a wind of anxiety and expectation, but at the same time, I am filled with a feeling of autumn leaves and freedom that I have never felt before.
Let's move
forward To those who can hear a happy voice It's
fun, it's
fun,
women are just having fun,
women are fun,
women are
warm and fun, and they're having fun.  It
's a very big and beautiful song.It's a
waste of words,
but
that's what I really think.It's not like
this, it's the music that sticks out
in this place.If
you want to test yourself more, you
can't stop when it comes to more free music.  Do
you like that song?Actually, I'm
glad there's going to be a festival at Buremen from now on, so let's go
together and
have a taste of it.Do you understand this sound
?Let's do it together.
[Music] Let's
go to Senkyure and get used to the world we want to be. The world has the same aim.
[Music]
Hey, everyone, don't go into this store. Once we have a break, we'll
have a strategy meeting.
[Music]
Let's do this. This is the perfect place to howl.
Ah, finally the main dish, the
recipe for capturing the smile of an angel that shines in pitch black darkness.
Well then, who are you, a pervert? It
's not the first time I've seen a pervert. I'm a
righteous delinquent who discourages the bullish and helps the weak. I'll
take the darkness and aim for all the treasures. You rich people,
that's the only thing I
wish you knew.  Hurry up and
leave. Even if someone says something like that to me, I'm
like, oh, that sounds like a lie.
No, I won't be fooled. There's no way a poor person can laugh so happily.
When I was young and poor, I went hungry and
fell into the depths of despair.That's
why I wanted to make those people smile.But
why is that all I do?My
heart hurts so much.Why is this the only way I
know?  No, it's a
question of how to make people smile. I
might have figured it out, but I can't do it alone. Let's
go eat some noodles with us. We're not the only ones. I'm sure we can sing a song to make people smile.
[applause]
Yuko
[Music] Seka Mogi I
passed by once as usual.
You're a convinced criminal who doesn't even know what to do. After you cried during dinner, you laughed. I said, "
I feel the same way, too." Then we both fell
silent.  I stayed silent for a long time,
no matter what, I
didn't have the right to say goodbye to my husband,
so I fell into a trap and struggled inside the God Bee,
but I didn't break down, I couldn't stop, I knew the truth.  I'm going to
move on without it, but I just
want to forget it.Even
if I don't say I'm sorry, I don't need words that don't have a form.
Even if I don't come out, even if it's not for me,
you'll protect me.
[Music] My
thighs are
so blocked up that it's meaningless. I can't move.
Don't find me, I'll leave you alone. I'm looking somewhere.  No
matter where I look, I crawl into a room that won't open, and I
pound both of them inside the ham, but it won't break. They won't
stop. If I keep acting like this, I want to
take it away, hide it, and forget it.  I
don't need scary words
[Music] The
crows scream, I don't invite you, I laugh, I fall,
I'm pathetic, I want to blame someone for something that's no one's fault.I
know the truth, but
even if you abandon me, believe me.  I'll put it away
[Music] I want to
take it away, hide it, and forget
it. I want to take it away, hide it, and forget
it. I want to talk about it. I do
n't have a single thing, but I'm sorry. Don't do it. Why can't you save me, who only doubts me?  There's
no need for lies,
so it's sunny
[Music] A
beautiful full moon glitters on the strong priest,
shining happily on the world,
but I'm a failure, and I can't help it, so I
weakly dream and fall to earth.  I'm
spinning around, but I still want someone to follow me,
and I'm screaming.I want to run
away.I can't see the point in not letting you run away.But I
want you to find me, so desperately.I'm
soaring like a star that's hard to see.
[Music] A
beautiful full moon sways in Miki
Koimochi, sleeping in someone's arms.Who am
I to be crushed by the night alone?  I ca
n't even see it, I
'm slipping up, but I still don't want to lose to anyone, and I'm
also portraying the sins of the universe.It's a
world that I look at because I want to catch up, or overtake.Still, if I compare myself to someone else and
look at those around me, I'm a winner.  I searched for shadows and
objects in the distance
[Music]
But still, I want to see the same scenery as you again.Even if I want to start
crying, even if I want to throw it away, I
can't give up.Even so, the
rabbit is strong and stretches out so that you can find me.  of  I'm
holding on to what I've given up and releasing my wishes.
Still, I want someone to find me, and I'm
screaming. I want to cry, but I
can't let it out. There's no turning back. Still, I
want you to find me, so like a butterfly, I
'm going to soar and fly away.  The devouring star's
water shines
[Music]
Mizuki
Even when the carp is not feeling well, the beautiful full moon
shines, laughing and saying that next time it will be your bread
[Music]  We
're finally having fun at the welcome to remix festival.Next, we'll
be joined by a special Sado unit.The
miracle voice that shakes Daiichi Roa, the princess of the land of oil.
[Music]The music of
the dog, the explorer of the fantasy world,
the cat.
[Music]  [Music]
Listen to the
Kindness List The
Bremen Animal Team that uses the power of thief music to create miracles
Many encounters
have taught me The days of choosing for myself have made me who I am I'm sure
someone will notice this voice that stands up
That's why I'm fearless
[Music] A
picture of being shunned
There's a place that can be called a dream Someday, the wind stirred by free leaves I'll
turn it into someone's small and show it to you Music of a song Let's
echo the sound and send it to the world  We
believe in the power of this magic and sing our
[music] loudly. We've
finally found a way to bring a smile to your face. It's
not always easy, but if we
join our voices together, we
can definitely do it. Let's try it and he'll be
with us.  The
music pod echoes this song to the world,
burns this magic into your eyes, and
sings.No one is the king of music alone.With
this voice, our hearts pass through the ages.
[Music]
Sing
[Applause]  The
overlapping waves of warm sounds that tell us what we mean, always give us dreams.
That's
music, so let's all come together and
bleed.
[Music] Let's
go
[Music]
[Applause]
Thank you to everyone who is watching Arouna Autumn Birth 2024. It's
not over yet, so I'll leave the channel as it is until the end.This
year, I finally
got my favorite Auster Project to create an original musical.How do you like
it?  I'd be
happy to hear everyone's impressions, so please post a
lot with the hash tag Aze Raw Exploration 2024. I'll
go find it with my ego. I'll
be waiting.
And subscribe to the channel. Members participating this time.
Thank you to
everyone who hasn't done so yet. Thank you to everyone who has registered for membership.Actually,
I was
going to say there will be an after-live event for members only after this,
but I've invested everything into the main story, so there
won't be a live show.  However, we
are planning to release unreleased off-shots, so please
register as a member and wait for us.
Tomorrow, we will tell you
about the production costs, behind-the-scenes stories, and other impressions of this musical.  I
thought it would be great if we could talk as much as possible, so please look forward to the broadcast.It
's time to announce the goods you've all been waiting for.We've been working hard to make birthday commemorative goods.This is
Don Autumn Rosenthal's Birthday
Commemoration 2024 goods.  I created this with the image of the Bremen Town Musicians, which is
also the theme of this musical.
First up is the Fantasia of
Bremen Reversible Tote. The back
illustration was drawn by Mr. Caro.  I
received a drawing of Ze and the mascot that pops out from the world of the Bremen Town Musicians.This time, it
has a reversible design so that it can be used for everyday use, so
even when you want to show off
with lots of fun, you can still look stylish.  I would be
happy if you could use it as much as you want.It's
super
cute, and then there's the Fantasia of Bremen
Accessories
Stand Bremen is
known for its silhouette, so I
made some goods with a silhouette design.  It looks
really cute, and I
think it would be cute not only as an accessory, but also on a variety of things, around the desk, or around the entrance.It would also be cute to
hang it on the Fantasia of Breme pin badge, the bag I mentioned earlier, or an accessory stand.
And now the marching version of the Ate stuffed animal
is finally here.The marching costume was designed by Mr. Orco, which is the jacket illustration
for the original song The Fateful Circumstances Related to You, which was released at the Aloz Anniversary Live.
Dondo
Puff Puff has been turned into a stuffed animal.It's cute enough to be attached to a tote bag,
so please enjoy it as much as possible and
pet it.Furthermore, it will have a voice
again this time.I'm a
little curious about how it sounds in your ears after a birthday party.  I
think it's in the title,
but this time I drew it myself myself,
so it
might be a little more exciting.In
order for you to enjoy the ASMR voice to the fullest, I had K100 record it.
Please look forward to it! Are there
any of you who are planning to purchase the full set of goods this time? There is a
bonus! It comes with a postcard with an original illustration written by Mr. Caro. What's more, if you purchase the limited edition version, you will receive a postcard with an illustration written by Mr. Caro.  There
will also be a direct-release version.If the quantity
exceeds the limited quantity, it will become a white-printed copy,
so it tends to be quick.Distribution will end after this, and
sales will start from 10pm, so be sure to purchase now.
Check
it out Check it out Once again, thank you for supporting Aze Birth 2024.
During the end credits, I talked a lot with everyone who appeared this time,
so please stay tuned until the end.
Look forward to unreleased off-shots exclusive to members.  I'm also
waiting for you to register as a member. I'll tell you
more about the production costs and behind-the-scenes stories tomorrow, so
please look forward to that too. Well then, everyone, today, come to see Zeseitan-san's 2024 3D live. Thank you for coming, and I'll continue to support you a lot.
[Music]
Well then, let's introduce the guests who appeared this time.
Let's start with Coro, who played the role of a big dog
.
[Music]
Ha, it was fun, it was fun, it was fun. Yeah,
Gema, the dog from Polo Live's Polo Live.  I
'm Ko Inugami, and I look forward to working with you.Yes, this was a role that only I could have played, and I'm sure this is a role that only I could play.Speaking of a
dog, it's actually a dog.
That's right, it's a dog, it's a dog itself, so it's like it
's already shown me its mother.It's
back to the wild.Today, I felt like I was back to the wild.What was it like
doing a musical on Echi?Well, I
feel like this is the first time I've ever been able to do it.
But yeah, Aki-chan
taught me a lot of things and did things with me, and
somehow I managed to do it,
somehow I wanted to do it. She was so cute and the
best.  I'm
happy, but it was fun. There are some
favorite points about Corone, and points to look at here. My
favorite is that I
met Chan first, yeah,
yeah, and when I was worried about that connection, I
saw Aki-chan.  There's a scene like that,
but yeah, it's
not the buds of friendship, but I
really like the interaction with Neaki-chan there.See you guys.  I
want you to look at it. Oh, I
'm so happy. I love how it barks.
Look at me, but it's there too. Is it
the body? Is it the bottom? Isn't it the bottom? No, it's so
cute, I love it too.
That's the point. I'm really happy. It
was fun. It was fun. Okay.
Well then, thank you for this, Nee Aki-chan. Happy birthday, Aki-chan.
Thank you. Bye-
bye again
. Next, I'll play the role of a cat for 12 seconds.  The
porridge you gave me is porridge. Hello, the cat
is porridge again. Okayu Aki-chan No, I
wanted to do a musical with porridge.
Well, me too. Every year I watch Aki-chan
do musicals and
I want to participate someday.  That's what I was thinking, so I was
really happy to be approached like this this time. I like it, too.
I
like it too. Hey, let's try this today.
I was
trying to play it cool so much that
when Aki-chan called my name at the end, she said something like a chuunibyou cat and I
was like, ``I like this role.''  But
if you look closely at the lyrics in the middle of the song, ``Aki-chan stays still for a while'', it has a very middle school
feel to it.That's
really cool.I thought it was a nice cat.  I
didn't tell Kayu Oka that it was a sick cat, but
now that I know it for the first time, I don't like it, but the
rating made me feel cool after all, so I guess it was
just the right thing.
Well, no, it's just the two of us. I
love it when we sing and harmonize. I
know. It felt so good to sing, too.
That's
what I want everyone to hear as much as possible. Please
listen to it as much as you can.  I want you to say
thank you for working with me today. It was fun. I'm here for you. It was
so much fun, Aki-chan.
Happy birthday to you today. I love you.
Bye-bye-bye.
Bye-yes. Next up, Chiara, who played the role of a chicken.
[Music]  ]
Elive English's Takahara played the role of a chicken,
but that doesn't mean it was a chicken.This is
still bad.It's bad.It
's a chicken.
That's okay, it was a lot of fun.
Thank you for working with Kia.
Of course, I tried doing a musical.
What was it like? I
thought it was great that there was a story that was connected, and the
performance was very moving.  I thought it was good, and
I
tried to visualize it in my head, so it was really fun.I
think Chiara's part is the most interesting part in the song.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it was interesting, it had a lot of character, right, yeah, yeah,
right, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, I was playing the guitar, and of course, I'm going to play the guitar, oh, it's perfect, thank you,
lie,
lie, I don't care if it's a lie, but I'm really glad you did it together.Thank
you, thank you.
A genius, a genius, you're a genius. Even if you praise me like that,
nothing will come out of it. Well then,
let's do something together again.
Yeah, let's do it. Thank you.
Please call me. Happy birthday.
Thank you. Bye-
bye.  I'm so
excited.Next up is Marin-chan who played the role of a thief.Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa  I
noticed this for the first time,
but I think I really like this kind of thing.I
can't believe it.It
was a really good experience.Thank you very much, Tartare.Actually, you
call me Enetaru Daru.  I'm so
happy, I'll read it carefully.Of
course, I
don't have any experience in musicals,
but I'm so happy to have been given such a great role.It's
so much fun to be able to say the lines.
Yeah, yeah, the song is amazing too. What kind of
type of thing does the captain like
? I guess he's a bit of an aha type, right?
Yes, yes, that's right. Let me know.  I
was so moved when we all came together to welcome Odae. It was really fun. It's a
good thing, but actually, I was
thinking about doing a musical this time, and I was thinking about a lot of things and coming up with a lot of stories from the beginning.  I
thought there was only Marin-chan, but thank you very much. That
's right. I'm a pirate, so I
feel like I've finally lived my life. There's no one else but Mari. It's
impossible not to be a pirate, but a thief.
Yes, there can be no other than Mari.  Really?  I
made the choreography and all that kind of thing, so
there were some movements that were a bit like ribbing, and I noticed that element as well.Isn't it obvious
?It's like something you've done a million times before.  That's right, I stopped. It
was fun. Thank you. It was really fun. Oh
yeah, Tartare,
happy birthday. Thank you. I'm feeling like a water cooler, but
thank you for the congratulations. Yes, I'll call you again.
Please, yeah, let's do it again. Bye-bye. Bye-
bye. That's it for the story this time. Hello, I look
tired.
Thank you Pol-por.
Pol-por. I don't
even know what that's about anymore. I think you've brought something amazing this time.
You're right.  Okay, I brought a new one.
Mr. Polka, you don't like it.
To be honest, Polka is in this standing position.
Thank you for the delicious food. I'm going to
focus on myself first.
But thank you very much.I
like reading aloud,
and I've seen you do it quite a bit, so I think it's a good fit.I don't think
it's something I think or say for myself, but I
think I'm the only one who can do it.  As I was
thinking about it, I could only say "Porpor" and "
Thank you very much".
in  In fact, it
seems like there are parts that liven things up. It's
so much fun even though I can't talk about it,
but I wonder why it's a little bit like watching everyone as a cat. It's
really
amazing in terms of role, too. It's delicious.
No, I really love that place.It
's at Marine's place, or rather, the big thief's
place.It's so funny when the sound changes and it comes.When I
look at it, I
get excited, not to mention excited.
Well, I guess everyone is thinking the same way,
so I'm sure it's a mess. Ah, I really like how things change completely and it's the thief's
turn.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, of course it
's the best, I feel like it's over from here,
but by the way, Ze's worst point is,
but it's the setter this time,
but I'm sure he's going to come with a polka.First
of all, it's me, happy birthday.  That looks
like a ball  Well,
that was surprising and
interesting. I think so. That
's right, everyone. That's right. I'm sorry. That's right. No,
no, thank you for the wonderful gift.
No, I'm happy to congratulate you.
Thank you, Palpal Ami.
Thank you, and thank you. Bye-bye
.  Music]
Bye
[Music]
[Applause]
P
[Music]
H
A
I