what I need oh do you
[Music]
heart with the
anything iing queen of
[Music]
you I
super
[Music]
super don't
I want a Christmas remix of Mirai
[Music]
part around
confused obession I still wonder if I
was made for you if I could
no oh
please perfect for
[Music]
you me
my Mir r
[Music]
anything but I be the king and queen of
you P
every I'm you you all me
Escape my
[Music]
way break me sh
me no no no w
[Music]
w you up into shred I don't even know
what to do with this mess help me to C B
good place part
[Music]
my SP on
and and
[Music]
oh
uh one thing after the
[Music]
other just a totally
oops oopsy reminder oh I oh oh I didn't
see you there uh
advertisements oh I didn't see you
there wait I'm got to change
[Music]
something yes I have stopped moving and
I am aware of it please hold the line
guys
Happy
Thanksgiving right at least if you
celebrate
Thanksgiving K did I say
k did I say it okay here I
am I'm moving again
ke we're going to play a cute little fun
game now you guys go away hush hush hush
hush little
birds there we go before we
begin H I would like to say I'm drinking
hot chocolate right
now thanks for for the red chat
M no
but before we begin I would like to uh
formally announce so to
say the
beginning of or not the beginning the
the The
Happening
of the 2024 whole life English advent
calendar this year once
again sponsored by
kfp I am taking the privilege to say
that and put that there because well
things have changed back to me paying
for uh the graphics and the stuff but
you
know it's already looking really really
marvelous and uh I think we're going to
be hosting uh perhaps almost everybody
uh there will be again doors that you
can open and doors that you can
close but hopefully mostly opening
doors um where girls will surprise you
with a little
something uh yeah all of H life English
members are invited to
participate uh and give their little
something to add to the Advent calendar
that has
been happening since
2022 I think yeah this is the third time
the thir time
[Laughter]
yay officially holiday tradition yeah
it's it's becoming a tradition I wasn't
sure about if I should host it again um
but then you know seeing you guys really
liking it um I don't know I feel like I
can't I can't leave you guys hanging so
I will not leave you guys
hanging and we will be able to look
forward to 24
or maybe 25 no but I think
24 24 days of Christmas
Shenanigans little itty bitty tiny
videos maybe somewhere a little bit
longer who knows um yeah
and so I have I I don't even know yet
what we what we will be doing for the
finale I still have to think about
that um but yeah for now it's happening
at the website is being worked on right
now and this Sunday is the 1st
December
crazy
crazy so wait so the Advent days are
always on Sundays
right now it's like starting perfectly
with the
first wow
amazing how
perfect m
oh good hot
chocolate the last four Sundays Before
Christmas
yay and I mean you know uh Advent not
the generation I mean Advent the days
yeah so yeah I hope you guys are going
to support it again and also other not
just kfb of course I would will be I
would be really delighted if um fans
from all of the girls would come to
check it out what we are cooking because
we are cooking some cute stuff I think
you like the website this time I had a
little bit of a different idea for the
overall design and Direction yes yes
indeed um you'll see when it's going
online so wait for Sunday I actually
don't know what live we're what time
we're going to go live and what time
like what I think there was a particular
time that we always did it in the past
year years we'll probably just go with
that
again
so or maybe I don't know I don't know
we'll see just sometime during Sunday
check out the calendar the old websites
are also still online by the way so you
could if you wanted to still check out
all of the old
videos um through the old website and
you know still
enjoy
the festivities of it
[Music]
especially if you missed it for the
newer fans who missed it because they
were perhaps not there in 2022 and 2023
damn it's a tradition
[Music]
yeah yes
yipp okay so uh yeah I just wanted to
one time properly announce this I'll put
this up
here yeah
does it fit nicely a little
bit I'm in freie today by the way Cas
you haven't
noticed ooh ooh ooh ooh
freie
okay all right don't dis we're going to
play one of my favorite games today I I
I didn't even know that they were
working on another one how can you come
up with more
situations than they already
have I am
amazed cooki means read the air uh
cookie is the air and Yumi is the
reading uh so the English translation
for this game is considerate but uh you
know it's I think yeah you know it's
about reading the air and being
considerate and
Mindful and
[Music]
demure very considerate of of them to
release a new game exactly you know it's
a nice little oneoff game we're going to
do our best to read the air properly I'm
starting up the game now what's
happening is it happening oh wait oh
okay now it's
happening grab a controller now we don't
need a controller right do we do I a
controller it works without too I'm sure
usually it's just like clicking in the
right timing and so
on let me in I kept on clicking the
controller thing
away okay
[Music]
wait oh sh
that was already
delightful what delightful
music let me turn this down a little bit
everything's so loud okay will the game
show up on
[Music]
OBS wait maybe I no it worked ah there
we go it's too
[Music]
big that Melo
reminds me of Tales of
Symphonia a little bit but this part not
so much this part also not so
[Music]
much that part that
part this part
no come back to my part come on
no also not that
whatever is it too loud still kind of
loud right what the hell setting uh it
on Windows really barely does a
difference going from 100 to 30 and that
barely did a difference how about
13 that's
better okay so what we
have reading like
that uh Japanese reading system confuses
me top right downwards haven't read a
manga in a long time uh consider it
quick consider it consider together oh
there's another are those different
games there's a new but this is like uh
couch Co-op I
assume cuz I think even
the even the other one that was like for
four players even that was couch
Co-op m fun mini games okay well then
let's get right into the normal mode
Yahoo let's
consider thanks if I know how to proceed
ah space okay oh God uh this is a space
where you are free to consider things as
you like there's no one here to stop you
from being as considerate as you please
but we will judge you if you're not
considerate enough uh I don't really I
hope I don't need more controls than
space and arrow keys cuz I don't know
what it would be
ah after considering the situation move
the red object on the screen sometimes
there may be nothing to move just do
what you consider appropriate action if
you wish to stop playing just push the
Escape key
okay let's go number one these are
usually very fast-paced
right but okay I'm in control of
everything uh yeah I I get up get up get
up how do I get up what he got up too go
to the left go to the left go to the
left yeah obviously because there's a
pair there and they want to sit next to
each other but wait wait why wasn't I
the one to get up though first why did
the other I wanted to get up before the
other person even got up why did it take
them for me to even do anything but I
tried to get up it didn't seem to do
anything because I had to leave yeah but
I I wanted to be considerate before
they
left oh what the [\h__\h] is that oh I need
to ah no wait I should have let myself
be
caught here catch me no let's catch
me no
no no I'm a hair I need to be pinched
and squeezed and torn apart no
I was trying to like I don't know trying
to move towards
it we'll we'll redo it sometime what
this ah ah uhuh
uhuh
no no I killed two
people that was not very considerate
cookie on
theana which maybe I shouldn't have
moved until the very end so that I don't
hurt anybody
uhuh is this about not stopping at the
end of it yeah walking away quickly so
that I don't stand in the way of them
yeah very very demure very mindful very
easy very
easy
uhhuh yeah that's that is that is that
accurate
I'm happy with
that yeah even the sun is shining
intermediate results please be nice to
me please be nice to me please have
mercy very vaguely they always so their
choice of
words thank God this game is not
about whether or not I'm able to be an
empath because this would say
very vaguely and empath and it would be
very
true we don't even need to test it out I
suppose we already know the
answer okay number six how many are
there oh can you please ah actually ah
[\h__\h] because would yeah it it will touch
the the floor [\h__\h]
sorry oh he's like right behind me I
think even better with be maybe upwards
like this yeah why did that hurt
you why maybe because it was on the the
very last frame
[\h__\h] cuz I
I I don't want to I don't want it to
make markings on the
floor
uhuh why is that consider it what is
this what if I just turn it off would
that be more considerate like throwing
away my phone but is this about the
Wi-Fi being
considerate
H it's it was so quiet too I heard
the so yeah I feel like it's night time
what are we doing outside looking for
Wi-Fi signal go to
bed baby okay and me it's looking at me
uh I I I look away but why babies uh
like look being looked
at so should I just what if we kiss me
and the lady not me and the
baby she she might need a new husband
because she seems to be all
alone um our eyes met for like a
millisecond I wonder if that's
bad it's time for tag run awayk
okay uh am I tagging oh I should be oh I
should be considerate of the the more
chunky person uh because you
know they need a chance to to have fun I
can't immediately catch them
[Applause]
N I didn't catch the other one either
though if anything off screen yes
oh no no no no no don't touch
it careful careful careful careful CU I
guess you will just not drink any water
at all
because this this is so difficult I
can't change the angle of my
face friend yes it's a friend faucets
are friends although we didn't see a
color it was monocrome but to a chicken
it might be a
friend in some way or another is that
worse in some way or another consider it
that that sounds maybe worse better
really oh okay okay well good good good
I think so too I think so
too number
11 really can I just
go okay yeah because okay I see the
situation in Japan a lot too but uh some
like sometimes where I want to like when
I want to enter when I want to exit like
often I'm in the position where Somehow
mine are like the direction I need to go
to are like the the the least
represented
ones and so I must I must force my way
into a double Direction one and just be
fast I get that confused you you get
confused a lot lot by that you mean I
think the other one was no where I went
was definitely
considerate I know I know it for sure
because otherwise I would have bumped
into the middle
guy yeah but yeah I I can see like if
it's your first time in Japan or so it
might be confusing um sometimes like uh
there there are uh this is by the way
for trains so if you want to pass
through sometimes um there are are some
that still take paper
tickets and the peep touchy one but then
there's others that don't take the paper
tickets and it might look confusing and
then also like sometimes you feel like
you're going into one but it's just an
exit and then you might also be confused
about it I don't know you got to get
used to the Vibes that they're giving
you the
machines yeah best to get yourself one
of those cards because always
calculating and St standing at the uh
big map trying to figure out how much it
costs to get where you need to
go that's not really
convenient get yourself one of those
cards there's even like you can like get
one on your phone too but I've never
done that before I don't know how it
works I just use the physical card
M but yeah I do always use Google Maps I
used to use some uh Japanese um like
website for uh train routes but
nowadays this was 10 years ago nowadays
Google Maps is really good for trying to
find your way through the Japanese train
system or anywhere really it's really
reliable and very updated so uh I can
definitely recommend it it also tells
you like
uh on which platform you need to stand
and all that like it's kind of more
informative more detailed than here in
Austria like for example oh the digues
the exits I hate in Austria when like I
I use Google Maps to try to get
somewhere and um it says get off at the
station but it doesn't really say or it
doesn't match like when it says Exit via
something something it doesn't match
what's actually there in reality in
Japan it
matches so it just
works what is this a
closeup is this a
bug I can throw something but this is is
this a
bug when I pressed space I was there it
was a throwing sound
that was definitely
bugged that was definitely bugged
because it it looked so zoomed in that
it was like even kind of blurry and
mosy the screen was not being the game
was not being considerate game a cookie
on the
night thanks Todd you guys stop hating
on Todd a Fred brought the K along hey
Mr what's this game which
one uh am I the who am I in
this should I I should take this away
because
children sorry yeah cuz they're kids
yeah I'm the adult I think my hand was
bigger yeah okay okay that was that was
uh really close
yoink number 14 too soon kid it's too
early for you oh I need to I need to be
I need to be consider it to the to the
paper the scrunched up paper yeah go
yippee number 15 that was too easy it
didn't I feel like the other games
weren't this easy giant R B's coming up
oh
uh how do
I oh okay this is for sharing wait a
second what was this I thought I would
be serving more and then maybe giving
even even either it's considered to give
both the same amount or it's considered
to give the guy more to
eat but in any
case since only one was available they
should be sharing right although you
don't share only
[Music]
gidy that huge it doesn't usually come
in that size very vaguely what
maybe if I would have acted uh faster
then I would have been able to serve
more Onin because I didn't press space
until the very end because I thought I
just have to reach
in
h number
16 oh [\h__\h] oh but the one behind me ah
does oh they all adjust to oh sorry
[\h__\h] okay who
[\h__\h] no sorry but at least maybe as long
as we're in the same rough
distance it could be
worse it could be worse my timing was
very
off it caught me off guard party of four
party of four
ah okay the party of four is going to
sit on the four table as I am a single
person I should sit at the counter yes
that's fine honestly I don't mind IRL I
don't mind sitting at the counter
depends what kind of um
atmosphere there
[Music]
is well that's a lot of
chocolate good choice but no and it was
also the option to sit next like on the
table with the other people that would
be the most
[Music]
inconsiderate I think that they surely
allow it but you shouldn't do it
what is this about toot a Look
Away [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] just
mind your own business is what this is
about mind your own business it always
automatically looks at them but quickly
go back to
yourself but on the other hand I do
think when on a Japanese
train somebody is purposefully being
disruptive and not not not not really
really okay there I guess there's people
who are purposfully being disruptive and
there's people who don't really know how
much they are being disruptive but they
are being disruptive in any case then if
they're continuing to be loud or
whatever playing in the train as if it's
a jungle gym then you should be looking
at them but not saying that's like the
typical Japanese reaction
is you look at them judgingly just by
your eyes you convey your displeasure
but usually you don't say
anything yeah you shame them with your
looks joh I wasn't even thinking of
Johnny in
particular um for that guy that's
another step
up
ideally ja Japanese people are too nice
you know ideally for a guy like that
that's when you need to call the
authorities but I'm talking more about
like people who just aren't
considerate uh but like I at a level
where you don't need to call the
authorities
yet
Mas that guy deserves Divine punishment
mhm
yeah I've been
following uh the things that have been
transpiring because he's getting in big
trouble in Korea right now let's go
Korea get that
guy
so could stop ignorance is bliss that is
true that is true but I'm also like
when when as particularly when I'm in
Japan cuz when in my own country like
being noisy in a train is not
really like it is looked down upon by
some like plenty of people but it's not
really like we can do anything about it
it's so common that it's just like well
you are in a [\h__\h] train now and you got
to live with it until you leave the
train or the bus this is just how it is
you're just going to live with it if
that person is eting in the train if
that person is playing loud music in the
train or if that person is having a
really loud conversation it is what it
is
hopefully next time we'll be better this
is your life now yeah welcome to the
zoo did I
do ah I need to be considerate and go to
the one that my face fits
in I guess because I couldn't reach up
in the giraffe
H I didn't want to be the poop though I
wonder if my face could have fit in
there I would have had to lay down
today's the field trip hey you want to
trade launches I'll trade you this one
for mine oh okay I it needs to be like
approximately the same size and the same
niess I'll take this other isn't this
the same thing though ah I got meatball
some in here I could have given him some
[\h__\h] item from my
lunch the Tomato would have been really
bad probably I would I would love a
little cherry tomato they're really
refreshing heck in some way or another
okay okay it got a little bit better
again I think yeah the sausage the taco
sausage would have been good too because
just by its shape it's already like on a
high level of popularity and who doesn't
love sausages that would have been fine
too I
think don't know which is better maybe
the sausage is
better wake up my sweet
you what is this is this a referen ISM
game o o today is
your 18th birthday woo when you
become an
upstanding adult is this about her
reading way too slow and me not skipping
through
the uh the text box forcefully you know
what I mean say hello politely when you
get to the castle surely that's it right
all right because I could already skip
or get the whole message all right off
you go
okay oh wait maybe maybe
not
adult should
I it says 18 and then
it's um no 18 though I'd have to be even
more adult or
what that's not where I wanted to go
that shouldn't be the first place I go
to okay is his treat pick whatever I
want okay we're not going to do
something too crazy we're going to pick
the cheapest thing oh surprisingly
M ah no zero only that thing thank you
wait that's not the cheapest thing the
puffy the puffy we can
share is that weird middle
AG cuz I'm uh attempting to
share no that's kind of weird though
that's not inconsiderate but that's kind
of weird
like some way older guy than what the
character I'm playing I
suppose it's a bit awkward maybe but uh
the achievement seems like it wasn't the
big issue a [\h__\h] I don't know
maybe maybe I should have gone with the
the chicken rice after
all I got rid of his oh that was his
order I thought I accidentally ordered
it oh but okay okay I I removed his
order and oh wait should I get hit oh
because he's a super he's in super bow
oh oh I should be at the right timing so
that it looks like he's getting rid of
me
with a super mode wow you're so strong
sorry it took me a while to
understand no yeah okay I didn't realize
that I removed this order but I added a
parfait to share
so interesting
choice uh ah
stamp wait I guess I need to make myself
wet do I push this yeah
[Music]
okay [\h__\h] pretty good dear
sir uh this this is weirdly long the
letter you where do I put it in this
case I think upper right honestly but
that's like European
style that letter was European style I
guess I don't know we like West W
St I think we put it top
right at least for
postcards it's International right
yeah man I'm so hungry I know
right if you're hungry take a bite of my
head
eh what is
this ah ah am I aim
aiming how how many may I
take should I get rid of the whole head
wait it say one bite like a
bite the one from his
[Music]
hand
uh I'm confused I mean he seemed so
happy to offer his head
that's CU I don't I mean surely it will
regrow otherwise he wouldn't make such
an offer
right should have eaten the thing he was
already giving me yeah he already took a
part of his head on offering it to me
damn
it oh oh
sorry I'll let you go to those those
okay [\h__\h]
huh he wasn't moving I was trying to let
him go first but and then he did move
and then he bumped
into damn
it ah damn it yeah cuz like I I should
have gone to the right because I was
like not the last the last person should
be in the front and in the middle what
am I
doing should I sorry I shouldn't change
the pose though maybe I should have made
it interesting in the
beginning I'm flirting
again in
unintentionally but surely they will
give me extra points
right now then which one of you broke
the flower bays oh the one next to me
all right I did it I did
it would you would the guilty party
please what sorry what me it was
me please put your hand down again
okay you can all sit up again
now you please come see me later in this
St okay no problem I'm
considerate I'll take the
blame oh maybe I could have pointed
too I could have probably pointed if I
cuz I only used the upper Buton button
the upper Arrow key wonder if I could
have pointed at
them school party why am I the only one
with hair Once Upon a Time in the far
away land oh There lives an old man uh
and an old woman uh the old
sorry I was too
early no you no you the end okay
great my sentence was so short too huh
huh consider
it wait is that an
improvement damn it it's cuz I'm
flirting with everybody it's
questionable adventurous Tavern
excuse me I'm looking for travel
buddies uh me uh I
should uh maybe here I fit in more of
them
[Music]
maybe I don't know level 99 they're like
too high level
probably what kind of air was this
it was the animals well because I I had
had an animal I
did moment fought demons with Animal
Companions oh I didn't
know oh
[\h__\h] keep your head
straight keep your head up got do
here I'm even moving it for
you like a little bit shake shake shake
I don't know maybe you didn't need
that okay there you
go good he was able to cut efficiently
oh maybe I should have given him my
other side too though so that he can cut
on this is not my stop does it say it's
not my
stop what's happening what is that what
are you doing wait is it is the bus
missing I think the bus is missing
he was holding on to a
rail did other girls also have so many
bugs uh but yeah there's I can't do
anything I was like B for real for
real it's not
ending I think it's
bugging let's try to I think I think it
saved the progress so I think we can
probably go back to
that
[Music]
yeah game not considerate is this the
same rain is play went fine so
okay bus
coming no was there there's supposed to
be a bus right but the noise is
gone where's me though I'm is the red
one a maybe I'll restart the
game yeah I'll I'll
restart oh cookie yummy never had so
many issues with
me okay let's see if we we bug less now
inconsiderate inconsiderate bus SL train
yeah it's not even showing up I have to
move myself on my
own okay now number 33 one more time
this isn't my stop maybe I'm the bus oh
maybe I'm the bus I'm the
bus oh the train let's stop when the
person shows up yeah
okay but I can't do anything I can't do
anything but it doesn't it seem to be
able to move on either from this
one can I go to the next one
please we can skip this one let's
go up
a I restarted the game I already
did h H can I somehow skip this
please there's no like overall menu for
me to look at all of
them no maybe if I start a completely
new session verify your game pass okay
that's an interesting
idea that's just right click right and
in
Steam U
manage no where do you do that again
uh right click just says manage and a
bunch of things but not the right
thing maybe
properties uh local
files oh yeah browse local files no that
opens the
window the Windows window
uh manage local
files I don't have oh wait no but yeah
but I have that but it opens the windows
window properties okay installed files
that's the right one thank
you uh verify Integrity of game files
please fix it please fix it please
no no okay stream's already done that
was
fast game of a cookie on the
N okay we're back
in am I the only one with these
[Music]
issues please please please I want to
play this game it's my favorite
game this isn't my
stop ah looks
bad what am I is there some something
supposed to be here already at this
point I can't do
anything maybe I'll re reinstall the
game it didn't take so
long exit Okay manage uninstall
and install it's 300 MB should be pretty
fast okay oh oh it's so
fast oh it's already
done wow
so
okay we're back again
oh rocker SRA back with another one it's
been a while why is this not on the
switch it also exists on the switch but
I'm playing on
Steam no
way no but I literally can't continue
the
game like
[Music]
this no how what should I
maybe
I cuz even though I reinstalled it still
knew that uh I didn't even consider that
at all I might lose all my data
um but I guess at that point we could
try to redo everything if I delete all
of
the uh yeah new new start you think I
should just start over with within the
game without deleting the data okay we
can try that
but imagine we go for all of those 3
free games and we still get the
bug G the the one that was like super
zoomed in also had a bug let's see if it
will fix it there a new session please
please
please please please time for an
inconsiderate run I already did a
reinstall it just took barely any time
okay I want to get up already you won't
let me though okay hi move move
move okay I can't just scooch over I
have to get
up
okay if it still doesn't work yet I'll
try to quickly buy the game on switch
maybe if I can will switch to the switch
version I we can fix this oh
wait oh
I was able to get in the right direction
this time in record speed as
well there's some upset to this I can
also fix my behavior here I'll
wait I don't oh oh
god oh perfect
perfect
perfect didn't bump into anybody
go go go go go go go
go number
five you can play it on hard mode now no
no no no
no there we go that's like the most
straight I can
do surely that is the right thing to do
how considerate plainly I would never
heard that one before that's a new
one plainly so perfectly you mean
there's very say so purely purely
considerate
yeah straight up considerate no no
complaints so apparently it wasn't good
to this this worked fine when he passed
by surprisingly so I'll guess I'll just
keep it like
this what about this guy though you good
oh he's
good I'm I usually I carry it
differently I I like to carry it uh like
my I gra I I I grasp it in the
middle kind of and that's not probably
not really considerate because I could
potentially stab someone with it because
I hold it like
straight
vertically I firmly grasp it but I'm I'm
always careful though and when there's
many people around I change the angle to
be more like in line with my body but if
there's not many people or like no
people around me at all then I have it
like
vertically sword grip I
guess so why why is this considerate I
don't know I guess we're just oh it's
this time we just have to help the Wi-Fi
signal be considerate towards us I can't
find it though oh
there
there thank you WiFi you're so
nice be considerate to your phone is
that what I'm
doing okay don't look at the baby or the
lady just look away the whole time
is that considered I don't know how do
people with babies feel like when
strangers are constantly like making
faces at their babies it's usually just
because the baby looks at us first but
the baby just I actually also I'm most
of the time when I notice a baby looking
at me I actually also just look away and
give the baby something to stare at but
I don't really want to be like yeah
sometimes I make faces at the baby
sometimes but mostly I look cuz it's
completely away even though in the
corner of my eye I know the baby's
looking at me let's see let's see if I
can catch the
guy y I'm so fast cat that [\h__\h] I was
supposed to press space huh I thought
just catching up with him was going to
be okay damn it damn
it damn it I was so Speedy
even next time we'll get him next time
can I can I drink
without I don't think I can I can't
without touching it like really barely I
don't think I can very vaguely shut up
what was wrong with what I did
nothing yep let's
go no that was too easy I ignored the
baby h H I wonder if I could have made
faces at it probably not maybe maybe a
this one's bed
again so the other one probably
too
no oh
okay it might take a moment but I really
want to play this game so let me try to
get it on switch really Qui I have it
right here I just sometimes have
problems of like buying things and in
the store but cuz I have like three
different four accounts now three
actually n turn to
ESOP
um which one's the right one I think
that
one the switch version is bugged I I
don't think so like other people didn't
have as many issues as me
apparently so if I just get it on switch
I feel like I'm probably going to be
okay
me and can I I wonder if I can get a
refund on Steam I mean it's really cheap
but so I don't really mind if I can't
but
still um there it is oh it's fr% off
let's
[Music]
go can you hear it the
noises two hours two hours of play time
right let me close it then
I've never refunded a game on Steam
before Raina also played on Steam as I
can
tell
um
okay I'm
buying okay is it downloading
where did it
go where did it go it's not showing up
on my main
[Music]
screen I like those sounds
too especially especially the bird
sounds what the heck
the the Nintendo shop is so laggy holy
[\h__\h] oh my
God what what happened what where is
it some data could not be downloaded
because the system version is out ofd
please perform a system update
okay maybe that's why all right system
update update complete console will
restart that was fast
TW okay it has
restarted does it show up no it doesn't
show
up is it under all
software why is it not at the top
cookie y
me ah it's adding now it's adding
now
slow okay it's downloading the game let
me put it back into the
dock I'm trying to get the capturing
going uh haven't haven't used my switch
in a while for capturing uh
is it even
connected I wonder if it's connected I
don't think it's
connected oh ah how about
no ah yeah okay it's working I think I
think okay
[Music]
Oh yay okay another step closer and as
you can see the game is
downloading
controller L just Manion to let's go
well we already did a full playr on it I
think right we finished it
right so if you want to see that it's on
my
channel uh controller do you have
batteries or do you
need life
support I don't have a USB cable right
now different idea
I'll be back in two
seconds wow I made
it
[Music]
so okay
I not going to use the pro control I'm
going to use the
joycon we have
this I love that I love slotting that in
and the game is ready for
me please work please
work oh doesn't
matter okay okay so we're going to do
the first couple of games
again but we can fix that what what was
that the one thing I did wrong
apparently
still looking at the maybe I should look
at the baby and then there was another
thing first times the
charm please please
work everything might be more smooth now
things might be so much better now let's
go and catch a a catch is it just a
button I
wonder he's getting up how do I get up
how do I get up how do I get
up so okay it's a it just took a while
it's
confusing stressing me out game audio a
little loud okay wait I need
to
ah that was a close one
okay I'll do the same strp oh oh I'm not
even visible I can go like all the
[Music]
way wait oh really we ready we're
ready a [\h__\h] it's a little bit off
center but I think it's fine
yeah and move move move move move walk
that walk
slay
nice
okay and I'm so fast everything's like
nicer with the
controller
yeah I know these games by heart now
considerably consider
it considerably
considerate cookie
that might be the best
one I don't think gets better than that
W
[Music]
yo okay the controls are kind of weird
in this
[Music]
case okay it's lowered as much as I can
hope you're happy
[Music]
ah by the way I had dentist appointment
today it's all good even though I didn't
go for two and a half years cuz you know
like I moved around so I didn't have a
dentist for a while I mean I could have
found a new one but I didn't want to uh
yeah everything was fine I didn't have
any
holes and
uh uh yeah just what's what's uh tanin
in
English a little bit of that here and
there but gum ises no they didn't even
they didn't even do the the flossing
but they got rid of the pl plaque yeah
little bit of plaque
and they did the sand blasting just like
how they sand blast my
knife yeah I I I asked them to get rid
of like one little like color thing that
developed in the two and a half years
and they sand blasted it it was kind of
crazy okay it wasn't with sand but it
they explained it like that cuz I was
like why does this feel so weird and why
is there so much like tiny particles all
over my face too because it goes all
over oh tartar really why is it called
tartar but yeah it's like super graen no
that's not polishing polishing was
different
procedure with just like some uh
toothpaste but yeah it's fine I didn't
have any holes and everything was
okay yippe I'm glad but like even the oh
the tartar removal was a little bit
painful only on
my cutting teeth the ones the next the
ones next to the big ones in the middle
on those my nerves were sensitive so I
felt it I felt like he was like drilling
into my teeth but it wasn't drilling but
it was
painful the sharp ones yeah okay baby I
wish I could make faces is there way I
can make I can make
faces yeah don't mind me I'm playing
with you baby and it's
happy but I'll still look
away this is probably the best yeah I
should have I should have looked the way
the first time too ah I committed to it
and I made a funny face usually a mom
would smile right yeah or she's just
like so [\h__\h] tired today she couldn't
care less it's okay let's give her a
break it's time for D okay okay okay
okay I'm coming I'm
coming I can't how did I get faster I
was faster on
Steam how do I get faster
okay just stay
away I I really wonder if I can't make
it happen
somehow n it's too
dangerous this might not have been a
good face yeah yeah yeah whatever shut
up I did my best with the
baby careful
okay
nice that's enough of the lips oh that's
what that is
uh
ah okay I'll switch my side so that H
okay no worries no worries I got you I
got you
fam I don't know if they were supposed
to do that in real life but in this game
everything's on
that's how that one goes A friend
brought the kid along hey M what's this
game which
one animal
sex I just realized those are animals on
the
magazine wait this one's the m one that
okay that's a that's you know it shows
the animals that should tell me for the
future but I didn't pay attention to
that
[Music]
oh I'm coming I'm here for you oh so
slow I got
[Music]
you
yo Discovery Channel
you like do Channel B okay how does this
work I think I didn't do it quite right
okay here
one oh that's it so it's even if I do it
faster it doesn't serve
more maybe I should have aimed more for
the girl because
because she looks like less weight so we
should give her more food I don't know
she didn't look like anorexic or so to
me so it's like mind your own business
but really what I should do is look at
who the [\h__\h] ordered the food and serve
it to the person who ordered it
moderately is that good that sounds good
that sounds pretty
good middle is safe right oh [\h__\h]
sorry okay oh oh [\h__\h] sorry
[Music]
sorry
okay pretty good yeah
wo
oh woohoo
I anticipated every
[Music]
move was this one party okay it's
finally my turn but I will take uh this
corner one actually maybe that's even
better oh I could go straight to the
toilet I
wonder that's weird
though first sit down and then go to the
toilet Maybe
[Laughter]
okay
ah
no no I'm not
looking I am minding my own business as
much as I possibly can I'm the first one
to look
away so don't count on me if you have an
accident or if you need first aid I am
the one who looks away forever
ever that's when it's not really
considerate anymore
though no no what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h]
ah what the heck that was more easy on
the switch say like that that's
decent that was more easy on the steam
version to get the right the
position huh hey you want to trade
launches so you know what this time I'll
give you my
[Music]
tacle although I think out of all of
that I would be most happy about
the cuz those are usually so juicy and
especially if they're homemade by
someone's Mom
oh so good the egg but that's a big part
of the lunch you should shouldn't give
that
away I shouldn't it's huge we only have
two wake up my sweet
you yeah we're just I think this does
have to do a little bit with not
skipping the text I want to test it out
but I don't want to mess up my
score so I'm going to wait it
out h
mhm say hello
politely when you get to the
castle all right off you go so what I
still don't know if I should
go I don't think so I'm still going here
cuz like what kind of what kind of story
is this my mom wakes me up wishes me a
happy birthday and the thing I do is go
into a love castle where everybody's
banging
uh-uh I don't think
so okay okay okay pick whatever looks
good so that's
[Music]
yours and I share and I choose the Sheep
is that bad is that bad midd I'm still a
middle-age
charmer are you saying I'm middle-aged
or I'm Charming the middle-aged people
excuse me please
speak it truthfully speak it
clearly okay okay okay okay
okay upwards upwards oh [\h__\h] sorry what
the heck up what I didn't do that
before okay sorry no
it's supposed to go one by one or maybe
backwards like in a straight
line not
sure so what's this all
about did I do it right I think I did
originally so this is the same format
pretty much so we can put it here next
to the post
code and then this I will still put it
here cuz there's no better place to put
it stamp of approval the game approves
of my
actions
e man I'm so okay okay okay okay okay
leave it to me
m if you're hungry take a of my hand
that the bite that I am now putting on
my hand here take it thank
you thank you thank you I'm I'm I'm not
wasting anything I'm trying to not waste
anything
there you go I'm happy thank you what if
I take exactly this spot too though nah
n not his hand yeah what if that's the
catch said that was his hand
so
vaguely very vaguely
okay uh I will go to the
right before the last one goes into the
middle
okay okay okay okay perfect amazing
that's where he wanted to go I made his
dreams come true all according to
Kaku we're 27 now so far no bugs
yippee okay let's
ah sorry does that bother you at least
I'm doing a nice
pose and I should stay in
[Music]
it I'm not sitting though that's
inconsiderate to the
chair poor chair not being
used oh who wants a squeeze of
lemon wait did we this this feels
new ah wait but there's
four and but only
does
it what are
you
that maybe that was inconsiderate but
they're saying they want to squeeze a
what because even when I squeezed it on
all of the meatballs and they're not the
right amount but even when I did all of
them it didn't give it to them so I
figured maybe that's a joke they want it
on
themselves right right come on you're
maybe it's really
Soul which one of you
me okay quick that ended way faster than
before I didn't I didn't hesitate and
then all of the other stress was that
was perfect that
thing it kept this the this like scary
situation as short as
possible first time I've seen it K you
crazy yeah nobody needs to worry with me
around I'll take all the blame I am a
martyr as what doesn't like to say
then it would be the opposite okay okay
I just need to get the timing
right 2 three 4 1 2 3 4 1 2 three
4 do I have to take it away too a
sh I pressed to take my bubble
away damn
it could have been perfect
[Laughter]
perfect the old man but the old
man adventurous okay I understand M
let's
go you apparently you go here sorry for
the misunder understanding
previously okay okay
the old man the old man okay okay here a
little
bit maybe
everything what about this you don't
like oh [\h__\h] you don't you're not going
to cut there okay damn it I thought we
might want to get all the
sides FY
freak this isn't my
stop there's a tree
uh is not my stop either oh wait am I
supposed to like go
out and then go back in yeah cuz yeah
cuz I'm considerate so I let everybody
go off unlike I love that this is a
thing in
Japan bless
Japan the country of considerate
people neon cycle
they don't do that [\h__\h] in my country
they're going to let you miss your exit
if they have to they're going to stand
in your way as much as they can possibly
do when the train is full
nobody okay sometimes they do honestly
sometimes when there's a like some
considerate people and there's somebody
really not able to get out if you're
lucky then they will take a step out and
then go back in but not always sometimes
they're really [\h__\h]
ignorant ice cream excuse me please
pardon me allow boys to get them to move
yeah you got to say something yeah in
New York City if you stand in the way
you get pushed aside really well yeah as
it should be as it should be if you're
not making way you shall be pushed
away I wish my country is like that I
get squished a lot a damn squish him
back no people do get out yeah it's it's
rare to not it but like I have to force
my way through really you can find us a
spot
right oh yeah here red carpet
baby oh but not over the top or maybe I
shouldn't take too much SP space either
though that would be inconsiderate of me
but I'm already inconsiderate by taking
the best possible space am I not oh oh
that's a lot of people [\h__\h] how would I
have
not can't they like be a little bit more
like one in the front one in the back
like
bro but no back to the other thing in
Austria yes like I I don't often see
somebody like really being stuck inside
on like until the door closes but even I
personally it gets closed sometimes
because it's hard to get out people
barely move for me so I'm speaking from
personal uh experience it is stressful
it is stressful when the train is full I
can't get out
sometimes that's it
right yeah turned it on for
you very vaguely look at all these
machos Macho
mask
up got to cover the nose
[Music]
too didn't see it right
away side chest taking the relative's
kid out to eat spinning Sushi plain old
Sushi oh it's got to be
spinning why why are there so many dogs
on the on the pictures there though are
the dogs serving or is it for dogs
or should I not have gone I think that's
the right way
[Music]
though get out get out
bro yeah because a sign in Japanese they
should translate it it says don't overdo
it well i' I went to saunas a lot these
days I I am a pro when it comes to son
on us
yeah huh did I
just did I just lose them your pants
no come back come back
okay it disappears a little bit so you
got to like have a feeling of where it's
going but I think I think I kind of had
did I not was that not
okay it was kind of on my
body that was so fast and now wait from
the principal
uh good morning the weather's been
warming what am I ah
[\h__\h] trying to feel like
summer that summer sun is scorching huh
make sure you don't get too much sun out
there and take oh maybe this is to yeah
no the students don't care this should
be
faster hey don't
whisper don't what are you Whispering
about I want to go even F faster faster
there you go oh there you go there you
go there you go you B I should have done
this earlier they're getting so
bored
died I should have done it earlier help
me Dam it I didn't know that the
controls work like that in this case
Skipper skipper
flowing noodles party beat the summer
heat oh flowing noodles we can eat as
much as we want yeah but don't overdo it
[Music]
either
[\h__\h] it flew over their
heads no take it take it take it okay he
got one but that's not enough
no oh the
shade wow they grow so fast they grow up
so fast these
days we need to protect our people from
the dangerous dangerous sun when we go
out of a way to touch some
grass very considerate bushes mhm um oh
it's too cold for and too hot from that
guy oh now you're freezing sorry now
you're good oh okay just still just uh
and now you're hot
ooh ooh ooh is there a middle
ground didn't feel like there's a middle
of
ground or maybe stay in the middle and
then go really strong I don't
know uh
what oh I see when it gets hotter we're
going to have the coffees be cold is it
hot yeah May is still spring we can
still keep it hot and now we're going
to get cold all of them I don't know
maybe all of
[Music]
them yeah cold ice coffee
yeah Japanese weather yeah I think it's
already hot what what are you saying oh
[\h__\h] he's a
foreigner uh uh translate
it there were good options
though damn
it and somewhere or
another I'll take it that's so yeah call
the cops today is our date since we're
here why don't we do that one thing
oh oh
romantic I was holding her
tightly I could have probably jumped off
the the ship I feel like I could
have maybe in inconsiderate mode what's
this ah bubbles bubbles bubble Bob this
one mhm
the bubbles were considerate to me CU
they gave me a fun Pastime thank
you first I thought it was
medicine what's going on oh no do oh
[\h__\h] do it
here maybe it would have been
better that
pose just walk normally like a normal
person
might have been better to do it behind
the pole though you know but there were
no people coming up from behind so it's
fine praise the
sun Sparkle Sparkle Sparkle Sparkle
Sparkle Sparkle what could I do wrong
here oh no
[Music]
no I will forever regret what I've done
to that one plant it could have been so
gorgeous I'm
sorry let's pull our money and buy candy
at the store to share
okay uh to
share baseball well mini Donuts are best
because that's free free
thingss
yeah H what even was that is that like
gum the right one like not not
necessarily gum but like the the the
chewy
thing oh was that
um it it looked so flat wake up oh my
darling again you [\h__\h]
sorry wait it's okay maybe it's okay she
just finished her
sentence today is your 30th birthday
there we go now it's going to be
appropriate to go into the castle of
love probably why am I still living at
home with my mom though sorry no no
shade you know circumstances and all
that and some people you know some
cultures are different too but in my
case in my case I wouldn't want to live
at home with 30 cuz I just want to be on
my own with my cats and have freedom and
privacy but I know like in some cultures
it's normal to what are you doing there
bro maybe I should still shouldn't go in
there yeah normal to like take of your
parents and everything at least until
you get married or even beyond
that [\h__\h] the ah was I supposed to go
there damn it I didn't really read what
she said at the
end damn what should I have for lunch
today oh hello sir would you mind if I
ate lunch with you no The Foreigner uh
sure let's eat together here come on
come with me
sir fancy Dapper sir
[Music]
does this count as us eating
together my subordinate
[\h__\h]
no as much as you want okay no I'll only
take one uh and I think no not not into
the drink no just this just fine thank
you nice I'm happy I like those things
though but
usually I don't want too many of them
it's like
um
Ang usually it's like some kind of
pickles like Japanese style yeah it's
not always that shape and that color and
that taste they they have different ones
but this one's pretty common
mhm yeah it's like it's like
sour yeah damn it no [\h__\h]
may I should have placed it next to it
because it was already pretty full but
the left hole didn't look too full I
wonder if I could like flattened it
before putting it
in if I pressed a or so need to try it
out don't know
yet okay what's the point here what's
the
point the front are you
sure it should be the front door
opening that's for exiting holy what's
wrong with this
bus in Japan
legitimately like you cannot exit
through the front it will only let you
exit through the middle
but yeah H
ha but I guess there's some very very
small
exceptions was the opposite reverse
bus was it reversing no it wasn't lady
got left behind what lady you mean the
one in the like loading screen just now
what is this dangle dang what a good kid
you are those are Stones those are
Pebbles if only things could stay like
this forever
oh am I supposed to consider something
here
what am
I I didn't want to destroy them because
they want to stay like this
forever but like what what
sideways uh
ah oh it's behind a it's just the sun
behind you I thought it was his gaze
bothering
everybody okay okay no worries I got you
the Sun was too blinding that you
couldn't see what the heck is going on
on your monitors ideally I would want to
cover up the boss for everybody too
though oh ah oh no you got me you
totally got me but maybe that is antil
climatic to be killed
immediately but you know I want to make
him feel
strong let me get you
what
else what else nothing
else still 8 minutes left on the show
really was I too fast it seemed fine
oh that's a good
amount oh that guy surely wants
more oh that's a good amount oh he's got
a lot of
rice [\h__\h] sorry
I was I wasn't trying to go away I
should have known though I was just
trying to like spread it a little bit
more cuz I thought it was going to pour
over the the plate cuz all of the space
was taken by the
rice sorry no no
CH not what I
intended well he's he's got his R he's
not going to
starve no no no no message received no
no no no okay Cafe
oh
uh no
don't why are we not sh where's the girl
I don't want to drink too much because
like aren't we oh maybe I
should put
like where is she where is
she I wanted to leave some for her but I
wasn't sure what to do
anymore no can't hold it in any longer I
know what that's feeling
bathroom oh
God yeah let's
go what
what I it was too small to read from
like to know for me I
guess good Heavens the bamboo is glowing
is something
inside aha let's not cut the person
inside
let's not hurt
them well maybe I should
have no no that was fine right that was
positive thinking oh yes here forehead
right on the forehead or on the
chin I'm not sure
anymore chin okay okay okay okay a oh I
can chase finger position okay this is
it this is
it nice saved it bring it on you monster
ah oops oops her show
no go back on okay okay The Show Must Go
On oh that must be so
embarrassing nice safe very vaguely
consider it
why I did well I believe in myself 66
[Music]
baby take this you monster oh more
monster
fights did it
work yeah yeah it totally
worked I I like what's going on but okay
the dust is settling so I'm supposed to
be dead to just you know make sure it
worked it totally worked you're good
you're strong you're so powerful you
saved us
all this game is so
cute I love this
game a [\h__\h] what what's going on
you
ah when I'm passing through I'm supposed
to be like a little bit like s s
s right
I
guess you know that no that's not Moon
walking it's more like
[Laughter]
a they're expecting us at 3:00 got
it oh oh digital clock tasas
[Music]
they're expect should I be
early or exactly on
[Music]
time H how did I
pressed oh [\h__\h] that was the
[Music]
cam I'm sorry I'm late by 5 Seconds
they're going to hate me or minutes
actually that was that was minutes huh o
nice damn it I was so ready the class
changed
seats uh
sorry is that all we're going to
do we should switch
seats surely you want the front seat
more than
me a you're still writing it down sorry
no hey are you good can I get rid of it
now no you're still on that
right or are you he looking to the
left a he's happy he's done he's
done okay
okay okay okay okay okay he looked happy
at the end I think he got
[Music]
[Laughter]
it yeah I still got to write everything
down write faster
if you rescue a crane a beautiful lady
appears oh is that so I'll leave some
cloth for you please don't look in here
until I say it's all right
[Music]
mhm what a
dork he's so easy to fool now I'll just
do this and this is she stealing is she
robbing me it's okay I'll I'll no it
might you know might be a I wo the very
finest of Club this club ought to please
even the old man
oh she never said she's ready so I'm
never
looking I don't know
man I'm I'm not opening the door she
never said that yeah which is probably
right I think so to mhm
[Music]
when the lastly Falls my time will
come you don't want to die right cuz
that means you're probably going to
die or do you want
[Music]
to I I reattached it somehow it kind of
adjust uh uh attached itself to that top
part
I made her life longer she's Timeless
she's a phoenix just like
me she looks kind of sad but at the same
time she might have been ready to move
on I don't know but we'll give her more
time what's going
on okay
I'm on
sent I thought I was going to lower my
head and
apologize I was about to
sneeze well good enough but I I sneezed
towards the guy right how could I do
that
[Music]
differently
uh ah
should I think of nothing cuz I'm
relaxing or should I think of only good
things I don't know I think I'm relaxing
so I want to like not think of
anything
yeah yeah I'm
meditating okay Bon card only one pack
uh what
the is that considerate maybe it's
considerate oh but look at the a little
boy [\h__\h] I don't know how to okay so far
so good how am I going to get
the oh oh I can still influence this
after there you
go wait I didn't see the hand but he's
still
happy um nobody gets red car cards no no
nobody gets them nobody gets them I keep
them no but the child should have gotten
the rare cards no I didn't know how it
worked
yet this is the thing this is the thing
you just don't know he he looked
happy need to teach the kid the world's
cruel maybe yeah I think the kid maybe
is even happy about normal
cards feel like maybe are like more like
super fixated on
it maybe but at the same time we
shouldn't give it all to them oh meow
meow wait actually it will be good for
your Tik Tok it will be interesting but
I won't take up your whole
screen oh I'm dancing along wait how ah
sh there you
go let's dance along that's going to be
the best best for your Tik
Tok wa they look sad though bro you
don't understand the comments are going
to go crazy on that one a dancing cat
that's crazy that's going to go
viral trust
me oh this is Miss why your favorite is
signing off until there's a
v
uh oh she's still
no no she she has a no I'm not listening
I'm not listening she has a little oopsy
moment where where where hot mik hot M
oh I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I
wonder if you get like an achievement if
you already like in the first half
second pressing the X so ready to move
on or what if you continue
listening maybe maybe it's not as bad as
this seems to be maybe she wants you to
listen like me sometimes when I do fake
hot
mics and tell you another tangent wait
what's
going this too bright right it's too
bright sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry
no you got to stay on for the raid yeah
I guess so yeah yeah what if she was
going to raid wake me up in a little bit
in a little how much is a little bit oh
is it maybe uh ah okay wake
up class is about to begin otherwise I
would have let him sleep forever if
there were nothing really to like wake
up for then you know they're tired let's
let's let them sleep a little bit
[Music]
longer but he did ask for
oh is it considered to have the same
score
[Music]
maybe let's catch up no now just uh okay
I was still
below who are we considering it for
there's two teams we want to be
considerate towards both of
them we close we we we we uh lost but I
don't
know he cheating wasn't
cheating was too high up beforehand so
oh he's with his girlfriend all the
coworkers oh it's embarrassing for him
to see me with his girlfriend I guess ah
sorry I got the little bit too close for
com I wonder if I could steal the
girl that would be
good ah I want to try being
inconsiderate we're all signing this
Keepsake card for our boss okay well I'm
just going to do in the corner of
course small message oh but wait if this
if I'm the last one then it would look
lame to take up only tiny piece cuz then
the boss is like oh man like part of the
oh
[\h__\h] you know what I mean like I don't
know if there's somebody else signing
after
me but also it looks like I could have
drawn outside and also I wanted to kind
of give him a mustache but no no no
intrusive FS are bad bad bad
bad signing the card oh sign oh sign it
ah he can't see it he can't
[Music]
see
[Laughter]
yes nothing's nothing's happening
everything's you'll see it
later hi on the server but if you need
service leave it to me oh are everywhere
now D human's forcing me to work for
pennies I shall soon have my revenge
meow so cute look over
here Revenge Revenge
[Laughter]
Revenge consider it towards
myself [\h__\h] them robots shall take over
you guys have no respect for robot
cats you will regret it okay I couldn't
help it intrusive thoughts were too
strong my sons look closely alone the
arrow is weak and
fragile yeah see how easily it breaks
even when two hours are put
together ah how to break how to break
how to
break no it was supposed to break I was
like doing things but it didn't break I
don't know how are we supposed to spam
[\h__\h] truly mildly that's first also
[Music]
interesting that's pretty
good damn
it okay
me uh oh okay make some space for
him
bro okay I guess I should have I thought
we were going by the principle of like
previously where you know when we got
into the
train and but judging by where that
other guy stood but I guess he's a
foreigner like he chose to stand so
close to the other guy so I thought I
should stand right next to him but okay
I guess we were supposed to keep the
middle open mhm cuz the other guy was
someone you know it's okay s with him
right how will you pay with my
phone uh what's my finger doing ah
ah keep it keep it lit up yeah yeah
yeah
mhm 88 one kid meal of a toy including
coming including right oh to the
child uh there you go why is it so
huge wait I it looks like the guy wanted
it
[\h__\h] the guy wanted it but you're not
supposed to order
that damn
it damn
it hey let me ask you something which
teacher is your favorite
[Music]
um kind Mr a cool Mr B regular old Mr SE
H him he wants to be pck oh
he knows my
thoughts he tried to make himself known
I like
him he's
cute oh oh what what oh
sorry Doo why you not why not
passing car
Doo Oh uh what I was taking as much
space as the blonde guy behind
me those
a little bit more to the right was
apparently
okay my head really really
nah mildly wait what are we doing uh I'm
taking one of each
maybe there you go and
bye hope I hope fr shaped guy is also
happy with just one each though I'm sure
he's fine with
it see you again soon let's go I'll thr
barbecue next
time oh oh bye-bye
[Music]
byebye bye-bye are you guys going to
stop first or
me I'm not going to I'm not going to
stop first you hang up
first yeah I'm not just going to walk
away as long as you're still waving your
arms I'm going to continue
waving
yeah
forever uh what's going on here okay
three people leaving are you going to
yeah okay I guess we're going to sit
down I hope I don't I'm not going to
regret that oh sit down nice looked at
each other awkwardly for a moment but
okay close your eyes close your eyes too
by the way can you not okay seems like I
can't that's okay we're almost at 100 is
100 the max I wonder probably let's
watch the first sunr of the New Year Sun
appears here h
ah but I mean we don't want the uh
Mountain to cover it up but it's also
the best spot wasn't sure how much it's
going to rise but perfect perfect
perfect perfect 95
looking for
something what am I looking for oh keep
it on what am I looking
for oh I see we don't want to make them
feel
awkward and back on
oh dear what the
heck
animal spicy
love but wait why are the Lions so close
to the humans in this park are you
scared are you wait maybe he wants to be
lit
up but wait that's probably the person
I'm looking for cuz he looks so so
stressed so maybe it's fine that I lit
light up the last person oh he's afraid
of lions oh yeah wait maybe maybe I'm
supposed to light up the Lions because
they're not supposed to be here and it's
going to scare them if I do light them
up I don't know seems like there's all
kinds of ways to read that situation
it's dangerous to have those Lions
there this game teaches me so
much okay
96 apologizing to a business SP okay
these things happen to the best of us
we'll bring them some cake e okay sorry
yeah obviously that
one what
obviously it was a cake the only cake
and it said
sorry but
maybe maybe the left ones would have
been fine too because they're like
easier to eat and more Japanese
style like bringing a cake is kind of
unusual
as
like actually I mean it
did but he did say cake but maybe that's
like a you know like a just like a like
you know a way of saying it but you
really you you normally don't bring so
you normally don't bring whole [\h__\h]
cake
well well it did have the dog as a
figurine maybe I'm overthinking special
delivery thanks
power I didn't know what it was going to
do I'm sorry I'm sorry oh oh Savage a s
I'll send you the cake to
no that's so rude I mean it's my door
but still we're making capsules please
include a letter to your future self and
something precious you want to give to
them to my future
self the picture for
sure I don't know maybe these cards will
be really uh like what about
everything why not
everything but I'm trying to the value
of the cards will be really high the
money really makes no sense I
know letter oh as long as it still fits
does it fit it
fits upfront investment upfront is it
because the only thing I kept out of the
money is that
okay I mean cuz like what what is my
future self going to do with 500 yen
I mean could be happy but 500 yen is not
that much adult me would probably
have or yeah I don't know I don't know I
don't know I don't know it did fit
though so I mean the 500 probably
wouldn't have changed it oh oh I'm
opening it
now dear future me
[Music]
hello I credits after growing up did I
become right now I want to be a pilot or
maybe okay the credit should end at the
perfect
timing there was a typo in am Sons
oh I no de pass me hello it continues
I'm
sorry I didn't become a pilot or police
officer I haven't really accomplished my
other dreams either no I'm just living
my life and trying to be considerate
that's that's great other of people
appreciate that for sure you're still
going probably aren't you or are you
yeah I mean being considerate might not
sound all that important but thinking of
others can make the world a slightly
nice no for real though that's why even
though I grew up like this part of me
still thinks maybe I am being a hero
yeah maybe I oh it's going to make me
cry you're doing good you're doing great
are you done now that's so corny I'm
probably just making
excuses but if you ever want to I'd love
to talk about the good old days again
wait it's gone now well good night
[\h__\h] when was I supposed to raise the
[Music]
credits no n for real
like of course it's great if you can
achieve all your dreams
when you become adult but even just if
even if you can't just being a decent
human being yo some people don't even
manage to do
that looking at Johnny Somali so I think
your parents will also be proud if you
just manage to be a decent human being
yeah so let's just try our best to be
kind to each other and to
yourself uh what
thank you for covering for me at work
today you seriously safe my
bacon okay and now oh you're totally my
hero okay wait I want to reply what I
can't
do yay just
kidding I picked up immediately I guess
that's
good very B what do you
mean you said the same thing what
gay
oh you kidding me my empathy is the my
empathy is the highest thing on of these
stats but only like half are you kidding
me know how common sense specified
knowledge considered for the common
sense above average uhuh commonly
understood social manners and etiquette
this is the first step in becoming more
considerate specialized knoow that isn't
com okay maybe this applies to like
specifically like Japanese um situations
like the momano thing yeah having a lot
of knowledge is an essential weapon for
being more consider true I
guess uh spatial awareness oh I don't
have much of that but apparently I do 60
sharpness for sense of direction and
maintaining the right amount of distance
knowing your place helps in being
considera of
Hest 55 for group dynamics the knowledge
to understand the role others expect you
to play in a group your Cooperative Co
Cooperative Cooperative nature leads to
smooth teamwork mhm thank you uh
sympathy whether or not you can put
yourself in any another's shoes and
understand how they feel pretty good
adulting I hate adulting ability to step
back and take in a situation then assume
the role others don't want to do
allowing everybody to better enjoy
themselves M 68 almost 69 that's my
highest
score information integration average oh
that's pretty low the power to instantly
find the right meaning from fragmented
hints with no context
mm and then
speed okay the ability to immediately
make decisions in any situation above
aage the speed to understand to react to
a i and it might have helped a little
bit that I already knew the first 33
situations
mostly timing uh rithm Talent of
following a ribbon that's probably like
the the the game with like
the steps going in Rhythm being flexible
with the ability to go with the flow
will be useful in being considerate and
interval good and bad intervals whether
or not you understand the best timing
when acting in a serious of EV nice I
love it that's that's uh I mean you got
you can always improve it you know
inconsiderate mode shall we go for
inconsiderate mode yes we should yes we
should yeah it only comes available when
you already finished it
once please be in considerate and mess
around there's no explanation so just go
nuts here we go 100
number one let's watch the first oh it's
a different
order don't go
down I'll just never never
appear I'm done move on move
on no no stay down never go up I'm
done do I have to make it right no okay
just a
little okay
yeah we did show it just a little oh the
pear I'm not getting up for you I wonder
if I can make it worse
though I I don't want to get up and make
them think they can get
up can I make it worse can I
yes they don't seem to mind how
considerate of them
nice can I turn
around no I want to wait I managed to do
it for a moment
no [\h__\h] let me back in let me back in
let me back
in just going to obstruction of
justice that's right that's what you get
for not letting me back
in yak yaku
I just wanted to go the the other
direction but then I accidentally
[Music]
exited uh okay let's sit awkwardly with
them hi or is it worse to go to the
toilet for some reason I
wonder I also could have sat on the four
people table there many options many
[Music]
options how about we put this in my
drink
all of it or maybe even next yeah just
on the on the
[Music]
ground make it
[Laughter]
worse moderately bro b i red
broke b yay moderately way that's good
that's
good let come on you we can find a spot
right can I make it
worse how far can we go I can even just
not extend it at all
[Music]
or well that's definitely a red carpet I
I
[Music]
mean they SPAC each other out that wow
wow
okay
um how can I make it worse I don't know
man just I don't know how to make it
even worse than
that that's fine do nothing ah [\h__\h]
right
oh there's more people smack I want to
smack the other one
too and I'll walk for
here
illegal Dam it hold theight I did not
pay as much chaos is possibly
possible I'll continue looking at you
but they're blushing so
cutely bro what are you doing you
[\h__\h]
idiot you guys are so inconsiderate you
guys should play the game Cookie yomi 4
and learn how to be more consider
it I couldn't stand I it didn't seem
like I could do anything else I tried
is my treat okay so first of all we get
rid of
yours and then I take the maximum of the
barbecue beef
combo I I mean I want to make sure I
place my order because I think
previously I just uh didn't place it at
all 35 of the barbecue please thank
you what do you mean very vely I was
insanely booking
or I don't know if you would even call
it book it's just
rude giant rice Ball's coming right up H
what if I eat
it I took it back no rice balls for
you uh
uhuh yeah yeah that's right this is a
game now where I have to eliminate
everybody else
nice
nice A friend brought the kid along hey
Mis what's this game which
[Music]
one take it let's let's read it
together our hands
touched h
can I get his
[Music]
eyes no I just got
up anyone
else I got one of them and I made some
mess on the
floor man I'm so hungry I know
right you can eat my
hand
H should I eat everything except his
head or everything everything would be
great
[Music]
[Laughter]
too woo
oh look at his tricks with the umbrella
he's a god umbrella
God can't hold it in any
longer there's no restroom there is no
restroom my friend you got to pee in the
corner I guess oh another person or you
came back
nuh-uh not helping
you toil not
is this inconsiderate I still think it
would go
viral damn
it just going to leave I'm not going to
make your video viral I'm not going to
help you or is it I don't
know N I don't know I didn't dance for
them though didn't dance for
them damn it damn
it I tried covering the whole screen but
I
couldn't I can look the other way
H yeah but besides that I think the only
thing I can do here is look at
them spicy can I join
M continue why are you
stopping are they going to run away
let's see no they don't care oh [\h__\h] oh
they sound angry but they stopped but
they didn't run away
either and
then well
[Music]
H I
think want a good kid you are
[Music]
a if only things could stay like this
forever so let's try to destroy it I
guess yeah there we go yeah yeah so I
think I originally kind of you know
definitely had the right mindset not
trying to destroy them
okay can I jump off the
ship yes your lover is now being eaten
by the Sharks while you can
watch how
[Music]
romantic get dunked by Jack
bye so I
wonder I
wonder should I throw everything off
again or should I just move away I just
no no I'm not working for you
[\h__\h] previously I I pushed all the
plates off okay is it inconsiderate to
squeeze okay you know what we're just
going to squeeze it on him I can't yeah
I
can specifically on you I have a very
specific problem with you
oh okay I can just squeeze longer
okay oh
my I hate you I hate
you yes this is my space now [\h__\h] off go
go for a different alley this is my
territory I will never be done tying my
shoes give up already give up I told
you he will never understand it seems we
need to make him understand smack him
with my shoes or something expecting us
at 3:00 okay so what if I never show
up I can't
leave oh I'm knock I can knock
too maybe that's more polite
[Music]
the camera again you can't actually
click it I'm pushing but it doesn't do
[Music]
anything now I'm just never showing up
because they didn't open the door when I
was early still
so how will you pay with my
[Music]
phone no no I I will not pay I refuse to
pay [\h__\h] you get away no no no I won't
let you no no I I hate new technology I
want to pay cash if anything [\h__\h] off
how long are we going to do this go away
no away no
no
go transaction
rejected look at those cute
lemons the one in the middle cute looks
like a
monkey
okay how do we make it worse just fall
down I wish I could make it
worse can't think of any other
way I can't move
anymore it wasn't even a problem I
didn't bother anybody
no I was fast enough to not bother
anybody damn
it okay she wants to make some cloth for
me oh pokey
poke oh wait what's going on
wait I want to open it
again I'm not really seeing anything
problematic here I want to open the left
door
though I guess that was not okay for
streaming uh how do we do this again uh
just maybe never or just oh speed speed
speed yo
and now never
again it's not moving anymore it's
[Music]
stuck yep you had one chance you should
have catched it you should have caught
it your fault for not being ready take
this monster
Kap did it
work no it
didn't
yippe cut it's cute
phase two it didn't work this is good
you're getting a phase two it's more
exciting for the
viewers already at 30 guys food is in
demand oh okay another one of these
Bring It On You
monster I left him alone in his shame
yeah
nice not my problem this is stage is
yours can I also Look Backwards
Wonder
yes so can I go to the girl no no no no
no now I'm getting hurt [\h__\h] CU just
because I moved an in damn it I I I
tried to move towards the girl and like
be weird to the girl
no well I obstructed them a little
bit it's I I I don't
know h
[Music]
inconsiderate towards myself I
guess
oh I mean I did it under the table so
that's surely lessen some of the sound
and dampen some of the
sound but I
I sneezed on his pants take it as you
will so I'm going to do this thing
here ah you can do
bubbles
[Music]
nice long capacity
check I love doing that I haven't done
that in a while
what was your intention I'm not sure I
was trying to see what I could
do oh you can kind of oh no maybe not I
don't
know let me I think this is the yeah
this is the okay the left hole didn't
make it explode remember this one did so
very nice very
nice
[Music]
nice yes think about all the all the hot
things no D for you there's no shame
these are things that make you happy
right why not think about it no brain
empty no head
empty think
more think
harder uh I want to do something else
can I push them like this no no no I'm
being considerate
no can't
do anything worse than leaving it open I
think
yeah all the down oh maybe
yeah Special Delivery but I don't
even what if I leave it open forever and
watch him oh yeah cuz I don't trust him
not now you're saying
goodbye but I'm leaving it open and
watching you I'm watching you I got my
eyes on you taking your ass out nice
ass wait and see
type I mean seeing him off maybe it's
kind of
nice he still you know looked back to
greet me maybe it's even kind of
nice look at my intrusive thoughts
nothing to be ashamed of at
all okay
bus how can
I no no no no no wait
oh oh if I kept the foot on there that
would have been the most
considerate if we were trying to be
considerate considerate to her at least
rest of the bus would maybe be
annoyed okay M but
actually I'm going to sit next to you
can I I can't sit there you
go why I die I will now land on your lap
while I
[Music]
die I just poofed I see that's how it
goes good to know I just disappear so if
I feel like disappearing but not dying
necessarily then this is the way to
go no
I wanted to take more [\h__\h] I should have
taken one of
every no no it's done it's
done no what no
that should have taken all the meats or
something
yeah oh
[Music]
bye-bye no bye I don't care about you
bye
so
sad so sad I'm ashamed for my actions
that's why I can't look at them in the
face
anymore was this I
yeah so the left one is going to move
there but I'm not going to move there
I'm going to push you
away oh you're coming with me still stay
there or what if I can I no
no fine still a good
solution ah it still counted me pushing
him
out I did both of the
tricks so I would like to go back
down
yeah I can't I can't keep up with the
stairs but I'm going to
stop you right
there
perfect 100 points for
that surely what should I have for lunch
today oh hello
sir would you mind if I lunch for you
h no I'm going to leave I I I'm going to
just
completely I'm out of here and you make
me uncomfortable with your offer
stranger i' prefer to not eat at all can
I go into my ear or can I go into my
nose can I poke my
something what can I do can I punch
myself can I squeeze my nipples can I
squeeze my biceps
damn
it no
achievement I wonder if there's an
achievement for
everything and then I wonder what it
would have been what you need to
do you see your cowork on a day off
uh-oh he's with his girl yeah let's try
to steal
her no I want to steal you let me
oh no let me oh
gangster what do you want eh what do you
want no let me steal her oh Bo
die please wolf
whistle trying to impress her satday
night the fa yeah the
squat iron belly I want to eat him can I
attack back
oh damn he's got some moves well oh it's
credits oh and maybe I did let myself
get killed too early in the cookie yummy
like proper air
reading
[Music]
situation there's credits and he still
had a couple of attacks
this special move very vaguely
book oh it's already
over well there only 50 oh wait was it
even 50 you really played along a very
popular comic St thank you w 330 out of
500 that's more than 50% right so I
actually did better than being
considerate
[Laughter]
yay well the lower the
better hey I thought they might do all
of them but okay maybe there's not
enough or is it randomized and is there
not enough scenes where you could be
properly inconsiderate is that
why h
chapter Secrets the past
you the past you mean from other
[Music]
games what is
this ah just my last uh scores
okay what about the
secrets is it like the ones I found oh
master
of oh these are the achievements oh
there's so many
he I got 21 out of 100 so I guess that's
one
per if there's one
per uh like
scene
then that means some only have like an
achievement for being particularly
inconsiderate or particularly
considerate or just doing something
really weird and so on
cuz I did get some achievements for
being particularly inconsiderate or for
being particularly fast and so on and
you know
[Music]
interesting are these different ones or
8 use you game jump you okay what is
this use I'm outs of the train
now oh my you
ai8 exit8 look CL at all oh maybe not
it's a reference at all eight use what
wait wa what what car
one do I have to do
math what
what what no doing I didn't read the
whole thing can I slap their
ass
huh wait I need to read the rules
again hey
this time it did ah
didn't
what the anomally
ah al so I do have to kind of observe
them a little bit but there's more here
oh so he's the one right ah then he
disappears ah let me redo let me redo
thank you for long
who's doing something
weird
you he made a silly face so this is this
a reference to D 8 ex Exit
8 oh wait did you just look down are you
the one yeah he's that one he's not
focused
enough oh wait so I think we're fine
even though I failed the first couple of
times it just
uh
huh it just brought me back to the
beginning I guess each time and like
it's always randomized he what about
this
one maybe
wait maybe it's the the you know one two
two one two two this one no or should I
have like what's the hit box like do I
have to hit him with my hands or with
more of my body I don't know damn it am
I
reset or one two 3 4 ah okay what's
going on here it's probably the
you the one looking
differently okay okay okay
okay I don't it can I keep going if
there's nothing okay this is uh ah
you're the only one who's not on their
phone which you know apparently is a bad
thing
now car
free uhhuh there's three two one one one
is it about that or is it about
something else I feel like it is about
that but
[Music]
what's the anomaly here but their faces
they all look the same h no looks the
same looks the
same like the urinal dilemma but
like there's
two I don't know how about you [\h__\h] if
that one comes up again I won't
know leave if no anomaly really
[\h__\h] oh this one's
similar why why are none of y'all
sitting down though okay I'll try
walking past oh i c one so bad there was
an
anomaly you little [\h__\h] why you making
faces at me
rude
carto I won't be reset anymore I'll do
it
right but I wonder if there really
is
uh is there something
happening if there really is any time
where you can move on if it's just the
last
one did you just do something
I feel like he
[Music]
did the Bonnies in the background no
they don't matter I don't think so they
all look the same too first one this
one's easy what are you talking
about second to last legs they Alo look
the same
no ah he's a bit more widespread than
the
others yeah he is but it's like not even
that
much I
see oh I you not supposed to sit like
that but we are kicking the one out
who's sitting the way you're supposed
to that's
sad that was subtle yeah the leg one was
subtle oh you're kind
of friend shaped get out of
here for for Japanese standards I
guess well it certainly isn't the leg
thing again here's
four here's
[Music]
four they're all on their phone they're
all on their phone
[Music]
he did look
down he
did two two
three one
[Music]
H he only has one camera get out of
here in this day and age phones have
like four cameras minimum it's obviously
him but is there a catch no
and this guy obviously get out of
here upgrade your phone
yeah oh is it the guy standing but no
there's one here
[Music]
too maybe it's not about the GU
standing but it's kind of rude that he's
like standing
like they're both doing it I guess
blocking their View kind of it's kind of
[Music]
awkward this is good I'm done
really oh right there the background
looks different too did I finish
it no more bunnies oh I was done
ah cool they got little mini
games and I wonder if the other ones are
also around reference to
something
55,000
points wait this is not jump King right
I'm I'm going to kill myself it is oh
no wait wait wait I was drinking
something my jump is so
small how do I jump
higher I don't get it
oh maybe I need
okay I'm charging but oh oh I see have
to I do have to charge it like jum King
okay okay but I already spent so much
time let me can I redo
[Music]
I do want to start from a
distance okay I already you know was
able to skip a little
bit
now I don't want to fall down again but
I do want
to damn it well this is fine
ah that thing stops me so I have to jump
on top of that
first damn
it hey turn
[Music]
around turn around you no
no get out there yeah okay okay okay
okay and
now okay and I'm guessing I can only
land on the baskets or even maybe oh oh
on top of them
okay fine oh how much is
there okay okay okay cie has yet to play
this right
oh
do she'll have to get really into this
she probably doesn't know
yet why is everything filled with this
kind of jump King game
now oh
no oh look C
also y it land no
[Music]
what has become of modern video
games oh no I didn't make
it oh God look at all of that now I
don't know I don't know if I want to
really get into that oh I was able to
skip a little bit there nice nice nice
nice wee
[Music]
oh okay stay here did you see that bus
up there or
something
okay I'm getting
better I think I I like it more than the
one in holoc cure because at least here
I'm playing a cat
come
on no no no no I need momentum
here
y ah don't overdo no no that was close
that was
close Okay what a what are these soccer
balls up there you want me to land on oh
there's an elevator oh no put those
soccer balls up there are you
kidding you can do it as
OKO true I
guess
m okay I'm on the
elevator if I fall again like
really badly then I'll quit this is my
one one attempt but this could already
end badly although we fall so
slowly that this is pretty easy to
control yeah actually oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh
hitbox
incredible not really moving with this
one can I skip a few
[Music]
it fall wasn't even so bad but no I I
don't really care about this type of
game enough
to go hardcore into it so what is this
one about the U
game a the Q
game right no wait it's just
Tetris oh wait it's The so is it the SOA
game wa it's the SOA game the the basket
first reminded me of uh the Q game thing
that we played
before Oh the physics here already seem
kind of weird though
interesting like slow and fast and
bouncy
[Music]
everything oh maybe maybe I'll be the
best at this sua game finally a sua game
I'm decent
at
Okay small small
small oh why did I why did I put it
there oh wait they
formed a bond together so that's
good even smaller
they're really
uncomfortable looking being together
squeezed like
this oh no they're already piling up and
not able to get
through but that's just how it is
sometimes is this one supposed to be a
different one than those ones yeah I
guess so no they make the same face
still go to the
right yeah now this one's even
smaller just go anywhere you like ah
it's so
far why is it so
far I fumbled this
no I can still fix this look they
they'll touch
eventually I I if I get another one of
those I can also form it on the left
side and
then oh don't bounce too much okay good
good oh oh we're pushing some stuff oh
oh he what did you say I F oh what that
ah so much for fumbling
it get out of here you know nothing
about SAA games and cookie yummy games
have you even ever played one of these
before look how comfortable they look
now having a
little
go looking so
clean can you get in there o hey let's
go I don't know about this one can it go
in ah no well that's a
problem but
okay we'll see how that goes
[Music]
small small another one is coming so
we'll combine
that and then this one can touch that
one but I want that I want those smaller
ones those mid ones to
[Music]
touch those smaller ones are kind of
difficult because of the distance it
feels like
too far away to really measure where
it's going to
go okay okay now I kind of miss sua
game
wait
woo SAA
game was a well a good times I feel like
SAA game time was a good time was it it
not those were simpler
times The Craze the grasp that sua game
oh the grasp that sua game had on all of
us on not just
vtubers on
everybody it's kind of insane I can
still hear the music yeah is it too
quiet should I turn it up what do you
mean oh Oh you mean the sua game music
I don't remember it I would need to
remember
it how did it go
again it was good
though oh oh they're almost touching
those two [\h__\h] I feel like I can push
them damn
it this game I can get behind let me let
me in let me in let me in thank
you ooh ooh let me me let me actually
add on to here oh they're also pushing
at the bottom oh look there's stuff
[Music]
happening things are
happening things are looking
good remember it so vividly as well the
music I really don't
know the only thing that's in my head
is actually when I was uh oh we got a
square when I was at
the uh resort with my
sister um I don't know who brought it up
first was it me I think I brought up oh
e yeah and she knew it and then I I gave
her an O room and every time I did O she
found it really funny I always chose
Great Moments it seems when I would
randomly do oh and she she laughed I
entertained her with my o e i
e I'm
glad it would be pretty good to fill
everything with squares cuz then there's
no empty
spaces isn't
[Music]
it wouldn't that be
nice how considerate of her for laughing
no she was genuinely laughing though it
was not like a Pity laugh in case you
say oh saying that that's what it must
have
been get to the right yes yes ah it
doesn't want to go are you for
real but this is for being my first ever
cookie yomi sua game I think I'm already
doing quite
well ah this one's small why are those
so
similar I thought I was getting the same
one
a now it's getting Troublesome
though it's getting pretty Troublesome
those also look so
similar weird they should make them more
different you didn't considerably well
well not anymore now
definitely it's
[Music]
rough I want to play more of this
but this is kind
of somehow I think maybe it's the STS
and the speed of how slowly Things fall
down it's less there's less potential I
think for you know entertaining an
audience than the
OG would you
agree I think that's a
[Music]
fact less physics chaos well who knows
we might just not have been blessed with
it yet [\h__\h] that should have gone there
I thought it was the smaller
one
ah touch
no it's going to fall out
no
no W but it's uh it takes it a while for
it to react like I feel like you can
still build on it what
falling hey I want to play one more
time I'm sorry it might not be the most
entertaining s game but I'm having
fun game it's these like kind of simple
phone
games like what you would get on your
maybe but like normally like I don't
play things on my phone especially
simple games like
this unless when when phones were still
new and you had like snake on your phone
or so when I say snake I just mean the
the not like Metal Gear Solid you know
what I mean
right that was exciting to play Snake on
your phone because phones were still so
new and fast fascinating and at times
where okay this kind of makes me sound
like a boomer but at times where maybe
not everybody had a phone yet and only
like a couple people in the class maybe
were blessed with a phone then you could
show off your phone
games but I think actually I was kind of
like even though I had a PC very early
on
I didn't have a a phone as early as
other people in my generation I think n
Al still kind of
earlyish but back in my
day the average age of people live a
mobile phone was still higher than
now I'm So Young you think so why thank
you thank you so much you so
nice H I need the same size thanks for
the 38 months
membership got my first cell phone at 18
wa how old are
you
H well if you if you're like from the
older generation then that's that makes
sense then maybe you just got it when
everybody else got it when it became a
thing
so hard to say hard to judge not knowing
how old you
[Music]
are I am okay oh oh oh w we got a square
at the very
bottom
oh oh and so I see
the oh no after the square there's still
three more okay even though the square
should be like the ideal shape that we
should aspire to be in for this kind of
game cuz it it will just fill up things
[Music]
nicely Square on top square on
top good thing you said for this game
what what did I
say Chicago Bears just royally [\h__\h] up
what what sports are you talking
[Music]
about are you watching sports while
watching my stream and is this not
entertaining enough for you
[Music]
how
rude football like American
football
right holiday right it's Thanksgiving
are you guys going to eat with your
family
today I'm so dump I forgot I didn't I I
oh two squ t each other kind of want to
keep them like that but they could touch
each other soon um I forgot God I
accidentally I was going to have hell
fresh on break for a while so
ah but uh apparently I had it on but I
forgot about that even though I saw it
kind of I saw it yesterday and then when
I woke up today I kind of forgot about
it and I ended up buying some food to
cook today but at the same time today my
hellofresh delivery uh showed up
so what do I cook
now honestly probably I should cook
something from the hell fres box because
those things are going to be
less
uh going to have less
longevity
yeah and the other thing I bought to
cook was at least not meat
so so
this but I I bought spinach even though
I hate spinach and you must know why if
you are a a a regular
Watcher why is it regular kfp tell me
why did I buy
spinach the correct answer is yes those
dumplings with the cheese sauce I was
going to make those
tonight cuz after the dentist I was like
well I'm already outside might as well
buy some
groceries I was like what should I cook
though I'm so uninspired so sick and
tired of all the hatred
you
no and completely forgot that I had food
coming my
way oh
touch they did those look like the
almost the same size and they have the
same face they should make them more
different or just less of them less V
variant with be fine oh oh but this is
like a pretty good
run they just mirrored no not even only
their eye uh direction is they're
looking in a different direction but the
rest of their face is the
same
yeah oh there we
[Music]
go this is pretty good but at the same
time it's a about to get probably really
cramped in
here how long I wonder will my spinach
be good I feel like that also won't be
very I should have bought frozen spinach
damn
it I bought fresh spinach now I regret
my life
H damn it what a weird awkward position
those two on the bottom and those two at
the top should touch
[\h__\h] should be good for a few days I
don't trust them I don't trust
it I'm so used to streer games launching
things up a crazy amount yeah right it's
really chill too
chill where did I put you maybe up here
cuz there's another one coming and that
will
will merge with the bottom one right
yeah and then with that one oh we got
another Square why won't you TW tilt you
should
tilt damn
it you guys remember the photo I posted
when I was on my
vacation uh with the snow bunny H yeah
was no it wasn't the bunny the
Snowman with the little Twigs the tiny
Twigs as it's
arms so my sister made that but the
reason why she made it we were sitting
in like a a very hot heated I think like
I don't know how much it was 60 50 I
don't know pretty hot like onent
temperature like liquid sauna basically
as I said as I called it very very very
hot water we were sitting in it and it
was Outdoors so it was cold outside and
there was snow lying on the edges on the
ground and I was getting too heated so I
was picking up the snow and just
like uh putting it on my forehead and
every
everywhere just to cool down a little
bit and then I thought why not be funny
and put it on top of my head so that I
just have something cooling down my head
the whole time and then I also just like
put it a little bit on my
nose and it was just looking funny it
was just messing around then I I told my
sister sister you know what you should
do cuz I already have some stuff on my
head you should build a snowman on my
head and so she started building a
little tiny Snowman on my head and there
were some other people in the in the
on and they were watching and they they
seemed to be entertained by it they
thought it was cute I think we were we
were messing around like little kids but
the other people seemed like it was they
thought it was cute and my sister went
all out to add arms to it and everything
but yeah oh it was actually oh it was
actually um you
know quite hard and
snow and it wasn't melting on my head
either oh
nice almost
maximum
so I could take it off easily and it was
keeping its shape very nicely so at the
end I just put it on the ground and I
took that
picture I actually don't know what
happened with it I took a picture of it
and I left it
there and I don't think it melted but
maybe somebody stepped on it or
something by now it's probably gone I
wonder to this day I wonder what
happened to that
snowman well that's cute right
yeah my sister going along with it
also my sister is up for some
Shenanigans here and there she's also
kind of
like childish in a way I
guess even though she's older than
me by a few years M playful Soul yeah oh
I another
Square no I shouldn't squeeze it in
anyway no don't let me oh okay maybe
yeah okay
fine okay okay wasn't sure about that
one but okay
okay
oh it's getting tight ooh that one moved
weirdly we got some uh s game physics
happening a little
bit oh that one's pretty big though that
will combine let's
go no space Oh
no space I'm lacking space even though
I'm so far
[Music]
no I didn't if I knew you were going to
become so big already [\h__\h]
no oh squ squ wait wa
oh
h a there's so much empty
space too
[Music]
bad n it's so over so
over ah no no you have so much
potential
no it's over no it's all over wow yeah
yeah they really let it like just
sit and oh
wa
who wow very
[Music]
forgiving
H but I'm not going to make it much
longer like where where am I supposed to
put
this
touch no no don't fall
no it's all over goodbye okay good
try
1,964 Kyla needs to get into this go
Kyla get high high ass scores in all of
those mini games I believe in
you g g
t t where
T yeah is your sister single no she's
not I really told you about her
[Music]
boyfriend
sorry I'm single
though why are you asking about my
sister what about
me no I love that okay I'm ending the
game we can read some super chats I'm
pretty satisfied now
played all the mini games played the
considerate mode played the
inconsiderate
mode y yum
y
yipp thank you for your attention today
and as a reminder from Sunday onwards n
uh the 2024 life English ad
calendar and don't forget to order my
Android or my V merch if you want to
only if you want to
only if you want to of course now let me
move
to my office damn it the winter
version Let me let me let me let me get
my V vter my winter
version I'll I'll get it we
hello let me find it I should
have it probably on my PC
um H
kfp how do I make
under how where is it's so confusing
when oh well let's type it in like this
does that work no winter
Christmas oh Christmas office I don't
know if there's a newer
one uh that has like if this is
an cuz I think at least once it was
updated
maybe but good enough and the
tree oh oh wait that is that for the
office yeah a oh look this was at a time
when I think when there was only myth
and
Council and Iris right yeah that one's
the middle one is Iris the middle above
enas one two three four five 6 7 8 nine
10 one two oh I guess there's no waa
gift there's no Wawa
gift oh so they're all for me I
guess I don't think I ever used this
tree or at least I only used the top of
it it looks so unfamiliar to
[Music]
me not gushy do you guys want to make
ornaments
again should I make a tweet about it
again only new
ornaments does it look fitting there is
it too high I want to show some of the
gift
wow what is the
gift yeah yeah that's balls my balls The
Comeback of my
balls we didn't do it last year I didn't
do it last year
[Music]
changing the size of the
chat
uh we're so back still kind of too small
right we want it kind of
bigger
[Music]
so maybe like that oh yeah that's that's
good wow I like how festive it is
is it's Christmas time once
again I wish I can get whole life stage
World Tour SW type type I tiet to see
you oh that would be lovely I hope you
can get
it I wish you good luck we should
upgrade to big flat scen tvs we still
got I like them but um yeah maybe we
could renovate the this office someday
even though maybe not because the the
this this is literally based on it hold
up
no yeah yeah yeah we shouldn't change it
it's just iconic and that was recently
made so I shouldn't change it now
although
um Eden is working on a new background
because like Eden didn't make a new
background for me for a while so Eden
actually was like hey should I make
something new for you I was like oh I
guess so
actually oh H so edan's working on a new
thing yes boers Bo I'm not going to say
what but we're updating something we're
not making something completely new
we're kind of updating
something
yeah oh yeah as much as I'd love to
upgrade this St office it's kind of
iconic and other things are based on it
so but maybe the menu ideas over there
can be changed
[Music]
again and and I don't know maybe my cat
can be an made it to be breathing or so
or twitching its ears I don't
know something like that would be nice I
guess and maybe some old outdated uh
decorations could be exchanged like the
picture on the top
right it's pretty
outdated yeah like some of the picture
frames those are really old I mean
Nostalgia yes it's fine
but where's chuny wonky anyway
here but that's that's not like the one
that was originally made for this but
I'll take it I'll take it
yo there you are my
baby I love
[Music]
you I love
you is it's very in character chunky
wony would totally lie here to be petted
by
[Music]
me let
me let me go find some new Christmas
music on audio stock only have my old
[Music]
ones maybe the you know what what could
change the scenery the background I feel
like mountains would be nice like a more
Austrian Countryside landscape would be
pretty what do you think
[Music]
Eden looks like I'm in New York or
something right now or in
Tokyo which is nice
too but you know could change it up
could switch it up a little bit should I
can do that let's go let's go
[Music]
oh you know what you could do you could
uh instead of like picture frames and
maybe on the on the on the corkboard we
could uh put the old Advent calendars on
there 2022 and 2023 and the 2024 one
could be like in the
middle but you don't know the 2024 one
yeah but you will see it
soon I can give you a
preview that would be a nice decoration
to have up yeah by the way I was really
considering because I really like the
idea of it and the Aesthetics of it I
was really considering making another
hand cam uh crafting Advent ref Reef ref
Reef uh stream again but then I thought
I already did it before and nah whatever
I'll just do something else maybe I'll
just bake some more cookies and all that
when I have my uh after I'm done with
the Vite cooking stream or so but yeah I
don't
know how about decorating a small
Christmas tree you could also craft
Christmas tree or Man true true but I
really like really really liked the
Christmas ra free free because that's
just so beautiful and it's like you know
very specific and nice and I will buy
one though because I think it's a really
beautiful
[Music]
decoration I will buy
one
yeah they have kits where you can paint
ornaments I guess but I don't
know I don't want to make cookies again
because uh there's one type of cookie
that I didn't make before uh that I
wanted to make
simp cinnamon stars like it's like kind
of dry cookie with uh with cinnamon uh
dough cinnamon flavor and they're kind
of supposed to be pretty hard too I
think or maybe not necessarily but they
have a a topping that is a sugar you
know the the sugar coating The Fluffy
that will like dry to be like what do
you call it what do you call
it I think I already watched some yeah
just frosting I already watched some
tutorials this looks pretty simple and I
I am in the mood of making cookies again
now I'm wondering if I should like
document it and make it into a video for
the Advent
calendar that's kind of less stressful
than making um making
a stream about
it
yeah but then I'm wondering like should
it be my first Advent calendar video
or cuz it's it's looking
like you know the solo videos are
already filling up like most of the
Advent calendar slots and there's only
space for a
few collaboration
videos yeah I don't know what to do yet
I'm I still got a little bit of time to
think about
it go yeah I've been seeing a lot of
people receiving their waa figas right
on time when the neroid is going on so
pre-order are you guys having fun with
your wa
[Music]
VMAs oh that's also something we could
put down Eden my figma and my
n
yeah that would look cool
figma not here yet it will come I'm
sure Eden writing everything down right
now memo memo memo memo no update on my
thing I'm sure it will come everybody's
been like just getting it
now stuck in customs oh
no and the pop-up parade one could be
figma pop-up parade and the Al
together I paid for my thing but just
today it will arrive by Christmas oh wow
okay you just pay now I see damn it bad
timing though maybe it would have been
better like if they made you pay when
you first ordered it cuz
now but did you have the choice to just
not like pay and therefore not ship it
out yet and just keep it like on
hold oh would it be cancelled
then didn't get the Fig but we'll
definitely get an Android okay Android
small and cute wait I was going to look
for
music I can't type
Loop
Christmas or winter maybe I type in
winter
no f you f
you this might be a little bit hard let
me turn it down
already a
pretty I like
it what the first result somebody surely
already is using
this how about this one
this one
says
um smell of winter coming closer so it's
not quite super wintery yet which might
be
fitting that's a little bit texy a
little bit of Texas in
there oh that's
[Music]
SN this one's sad
now these are not very
wintery this one's not
looping this one's also not Loop ah
they're not looping this is cute
though that's not
[Music]
winter why are they ignoring my request
for winter what about this one
the keyword for this
is um watching the winter scenery out of
the window of a quiet waiting
room like I guess at the dentist office
or something like that
what that's not that kind of
vibe it sounds like a
commercial um
how about this
[Music]
one
wow oh
[Music]
sophisticated
gentle I wouldn't say it's
[Music]
sad no it's it's not
sad it's just
gentle I like
[Music]
it I'm I'm getting
it let me name
it
[Music]
gentle winter vibes
before it gets lost in my download
folder let's put it into my audio stock
folder and then maybe another
one
[Music]
um these are all not wintery the keyword
is getting
lost Christmas yeah buddy so for
Christmas after
[Music]
all thanks for the
memberships wow
[Music]
cool it's
motivating not bad but not sure if this
is good for Super Chat
[Music]
reading a oh that's cute that's kind of
like upbeat Super Chat
reading oh cute
this one also I shall
[Music]
take audio St AIO AIO
AIO um
upbeat Super Chat March oh it doesn't
say Christmas at all upbeat Super Chat
March in
December March in December I mean like
like a it feels like I'm
marching okay but I want the I think I
want the gentle
one
nice okay okay Mr DJ jump on the
replay turn
[Music]
I'm the DJ I'm the Christmas
DJ no I think today we might be able to
catch up
completely let me see
though so tomorrow I'm not
streaming as you may know
[Music]
just checking my schedule for
something
okay uh
yeah where am I here h
tomorrow my day off oh sorry you can
watch A vibe that you haven't seen
before
maybe Diablo 4 oh then I had actually
the right thumbnail
up
[Music]
coincidentally been missing a lot so
yeah okay there you go wait is it this
one oh is this one oh I'm so caught up
wow rare very very
rare to be so caught up makes me feel
lonely so
[Music]
lonely oopsie what the heck okay
[\h__\h] there you
go such a symmetrical thumbnail I might
almost not notice that I turned it
around okay here we
go unn D hook d h hook D take 47 D you
didn't get the first one you you were
only fifth to send you Super Chat Jacob
what
happened hokan reports about season two
of rings of power let's go it was indeed
better than first except the endings
elves enduring got satisfying endings
but fil rest fil blackluster and just
not finished properly well you know
maybe it's not finished properly because
they're still getting some Seasons you
know not everything needs to be finished
off purposefully uh
properly but yeah I'm glad you liked it
now you're so deep in the commitment
that you will have to watch the third
season when it comes out
too lost his game yeah Jacob lost his
game
D thanks for the red super
chat I said I would welcome you back
with lots of love and I'm a bird of my
word
bird is the word doesn't it go look
something like
that the hills are alive at the sound of
w runs for the hills with wings
outstretched I can V Vision Envision it
looks cute thanks for the early than
discount please dedicate my kiss to
pre-ordering chickin
gladly to all my pre-ordering chickens
who already pre-order her still planning
to pre-order soon well you don't you
can't get it unless you pre-order anyway
thank you thank you thank
you
for
yeah for using your savings for
me appreciate it make sure to use the
discount code guys discount code
yes yes when will the code run out or
least Phoenix runs out after you know a
limit has been reached but if you guys
can still use it that means the limit
hasn't been reached yet but the shipping
one the international shipping one
doesn't seem to be limited and then
there's still another one that I don't
know if people discovered yet but it was
like kind of
hidden in between all the
videos I don't even know what it is
[Music]
but you can stack it anyway with the
early Phoenix you can't stack it so
unless early Phoenix runs out don't
worry about it
but yeah thank you do hood and thank you
everybody
[Music]
di Jones d m with a pinky oh my God it's
shimmy one of my oi what do you mean uh
the nendroid chicken yeah the chicken in
the nendroid package is so
cute
H he's so cute but he cannot stand on
his own you have to support him treat
him treat him like a
baby yeah well well thank you so much M
and T talkg thanks for the red of sad
going to be honest I was sad because V
Rama didn't deliver any merch to Mexico
yeah I was devastated but then a miracle
happened chicken nand yeah now you have
money for the nandroid it's so precious
that I pr two to make it a couple you
got two
nids you're just talking about the
chickens you don't even care about the
wbas you're just going to throw them
into the trash
huh Newton happy birthday and happy
birthday also very nice they gift wab
uhhuh uhuh yeah the laa is the extra not
the chicken yeah it's an chicken nid mhm
you got it right you figured it out
correctly everybody else is
misunderstanding it thank you temp thank
you for getting the
[Music]
nro for theed
thank you for the
[Music]
ra I'll give you a kiss for
now oh no
[Music]
answer what I
sing with me kfp for our Japanese
bro happy birthday to you happy birthday
in your shoe happy birthday in your
pants too happy birthday
you
yay two
gentis wooo happy birthday I am only
five days late that's only because I was
on a break
congratulations almost caught up yeah
crazy I suddenly remembered the birthday
video said this that video uh it was
like shortly after I watched that
episode in Breaking Bad where you know
uh wifey s sings that birthday song um
it wasn't really like trying to be a
reference to it but I was probably like
lowkey influenced by it and I was like I
mean I was only really singing in Sury
because I had a sultry
dance but then it just kind of while I
was singing it was reminding myself of
Skyler singing Happy Birthday uh while
imitating Marilyn
monrell so so yeah it just kind of ended
up like
that I was trying to you know give her a
little special birthday dance I was
going to try to be the stripper that is
being sent to a birthday
party to spice things up I think I
accomplished
that yeah I know I know the Maryland
Monro but only thanks to Skyler maybe I
don't know maybe I did know it
beforehand but she reminded me of it cuz
she does mention they do mention the uh
the fact that it's like her singing in
Marilyn Monroe
style yeah I know I know it was played
in front of all of
them I mean I wasn't really on my mind
when I recorded it but I mean I I I I
had a feeling
[Music]
nothing wrong with that got to spice it
up for
everybody I'm not slouching I'm
stinking and I'm sniffing my cat
I'm just chilling let me chill for a
little bit fa had the best
seat really was it so I did watch the
reactions happy
birthday to
you happy
you happy birthday
Mr
[Music]
President happy
birthday
to
[Music]
you oh de me those
reactions so Mar Monro
I got to run for president yeah go for
it do it do it don't let your dreams be
dreams okay let's
continue unknown thanks for the pinky
already ordered everything from the V
collab and an extra pack of raav ramit
let's go and two wow one Androids oh God
ripped my wallet but I am very happy
can't wait for all of them to arrive
your merch is the best always buy every
single W merch thank you oh my God you
guys will be suffering for a while I'm
sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry it's I know I
know I know it's like a lot all together
I feel bad like even even for someone
like me this is not a purchase I would
make
easily like yeah and I I don't really
have much worries anymore and I I would
still be
[Music]
like that's also just because I usually
don't really buy merch even like from
dendu like if it's something like going
to an event or so like spending money on
that yeah I'll spend money on that but
spending money on merch I generally
don't really do
that
wow yeah so I really appreciate you
guys' support it even if you don't
really care about merch either you know
you know it's supporting me it's
supporting me and it's supporting V and
it's um I guess supporting good
smile and cover um but it's mostly I'm
mostly happy about it supporting me and
Vite Vite you know small
company small business putting lots of
love into
it to make all of kfp Happy
[Music]
H Shield merch is a first yeah cutting
board Cutting Edge cutting
board I really care about supporting wa
that's fine that's good thank you I
appreciate it I wish I could have bought
at least the apron
a well maybe you can still get to it
somehow later maybe next month salary is
coming soon
right yippe salary comes
tomorrow I think
yeah
yeah I know like how last minute
everything was behind the scenes and
then like the team is pretty small and I
think Tim the CEO wrote all the scripts
and was involved in all the filming and
all the direction and everything so then
he talked in the Stream about how little
he slept the past days only while videos
were rendering and oh
God it was kind of stressful for me too
with like some things behind the scenes
but it was like a lot more stress for
their team I'm sure especially for Tim
and so I really hope everybody's resting
well now at
least um but yeah they worked so hard on
it they could have just like delayed
things even
more and just like give it all more time
but they made it happen they only like
delayed it behind the scenes like one
time the whole like uh first
announcement that came with the first
teaser that was delayed once by a week
behind the scenes and that's
it oh and then I guess the final trailer
that came up on my video on my channel
was uh delayed by one
day but that was totally legitimate uh
and good yeah and you know they could
have tried to delay it even more
but they worked so hard on it on getting
things
done
respect and it didn't have to be such a
long trailer you know they could have
made it way less effort they could have
made it really short or they couldn't
have made a trailer at all you know
everything could have been way simpler
but they chose to make it
better m
bjm gone oh I've been listening to it
this whole time but I turned it up for
the birthday songs there it
[Music]
is
okay oh yeah thank you thank you thank
you thank you unknown and
hook n d Mac 4906 thank you so much
[Music]
what
$1,300 what is that what do you spent
that
on we're in a sa F
Festival that German name of it it's it
happens in Maryland apparently but that
German name of it sounds like it was
some kind of like car racing
Festival but nice I haven't been at a
Medieval Festival in a long time
maybe next year summer I could try to go
to one again I want I kind of was
thinking about it this year but then I
missed it like all the all the like
dates were
like
unfitting I bought a PS5 right before
the V merch launch I was warning you
guys that something was
coming so that's on
you that's on you VI Dragon d imperator
9,000
than thank you for your first Super Chat
I did sing PA Fox and Seed songs before
in one of my uncraft cokas actually yeah
I think you could actually find some
clippings of it on YouTube if you look
for it h x i i i King thank you thank
you thank you thank you hope your trip
was nice Daman thank you oh yeah I read
your super chat before
C than of the pinky I may not be able to
afford therapy oh but I can afford
Merchant suas so that's close enough
wait wait wait wait wait wait do you
think you need therapy then go get
therapy but perhaps I am your
therapy which you know is not like a
good uh not not the
best replacement but I mean if it makes
you happy and if it helps you then you
[Music]
know yeah it's probably a
right right
hopefully thank you so much though your
therapist
says you are doing well you're doing
great but you need to come back every
day and pay up
more certainly
that oh
wow if you think you may need fa again I
can only recommend stay strong you stay
strong
hug
[Music]
lunar
Del thank you Cruz Dan Del solce you're
so
considerate Jim Tracy
D boohoo 73 D my best friend and I went
to kfp because he won a backstage tour
huh I read it outside when aak offered
me the best fried chicken I've ever had
I asked where my friend was and Ki said
he was with me how
[Music]
weird lunchbox D and lul L Lulu D thank
you first time watching Soul life show
thank you
come the goods are pretty too I'm going
to buy them all
thank you so
much okay there's one or two one super
chat from Doug hood on the V video thank
you than and now we're at the yesterday
Las Vegas
stream
OMG oh my
God I'm going to cry
it's like the attachment that I made to
Casper now I feel towards my Super Chat
backlog no
no
[Music]
no no no
no c d take for the seven d but it's a
good thing because once I'm done with my
backlog and it's like again like smaller
ones that don't uh throw me back too
much then I can you know every now and
then I can also read some non Reds non
pinks a little bit more
thoroughly yeah and Ja
play thanks for the pinky have a good
time everybody but now I need to go to
sleep so early even before the stream
started no
[Music]
no thank you o so flirty
oh thank you do
hood has been
destroyed by the expensive
purchases thank you Ed five fencer D
Angel be d d Max the first
d
d what does that mean the Jolly Ram
thank you
[Music]
do you mean full screen as when it was
full screen on OBS but I was actually
playing window
screen great JY D the steal D speaking
of vam and my kfb merch bugged and I
bought presets of the merch I wanted it
I wanted it eventually got fixed but I
thought I would let you know pretty sure
the problem was my own oh as long as you
got it fixed sounds fine the steel D
night bunny D thank you oo see you see
you at World
Tour the steel the steel d eler cabalo
d fcy
d the steel D steam power
TW super I used to work in the knife
industry very excited for the V Ramen
collab excellent collaboration my lady
thank
you you understand you get
it Cruz D Mr T D soon
no I don't know about that Vault yet
will I meet that one or maybe I did
I thank you for the hint I saw it on
Twitter too sh boy JT
[Music]
practicing Japanese like sending
a amateur Japanese Super Chat to ask
about learning
German are you asking what German TV
program would help to learn German no
idea I don't watch
TV and I don't
even I think just like if you have a a
decent amount of vocabulary then
watching TV makes sense and will add on
to the knowledge you
have but I don't know generally just
like oh yeah kids shows you could watch
kids shows and then with subtitles like
German subtitles so you read along while
you watch I
guess Ash Hole D thank
you and Sentinel than thank you after
after watching your early streams on
Fallout New Vegas I went further into
the Fallout Rabbit Hole currently
playing Fallout 2 O original one and two
were turn based CRP as well hope to see
follow one or two streams soon soon
probably
not
um one and
two those Pro I doubt it I've never seen
them before but they're
probably no not going to play
that I'm not going to play
that looks like a Sims game it looks
like Sims
1 a little bit two holds
[Music]
up maybe but n and you know I like retro
Aesthetics on some games that like have
Nostalgia for me but if I never played
it before if I don't have any connection
to it
then n nah and I think you got to
understand that like these kind of
Graphics I find that fun when it's like
yeah a game that I played when I was a
child or so but
otherwise not doing anything for me
[Music]
I'm finished
guys we're up to dat I need to read the
ones from
today
no
[Music]
no oh G is going to play Fallout in 3
minutes her
thumnail what's that
[Music]
thumbnail she's LARPing as an
alien a beaver is not an alien you're so
mean to all the be out
[Music]
there okay let's
see where I don't know I I'm so unused
to reading Super Chat from the actual
day that I'm having troubles navigating
towards them there there it is there it
is cuz those I don't read on whole wiser
[Music]
okay real time no whatever I'll I'll
read them on YouTube
[Music]
actually do you want the thumbnail up
guys isn't it cute games like these give
me a chance to use more like simple and
dorky
art yeah and this
artist draws me like TVs of me from my
streams referencing my streams all the
time and they're always so cute yeah nle
so I'm I'm really glad I can use their
art for once he's so cute I'm I'm
carrying you you see I'm carrying you to
the usual room you're so
small I
yeah it's just like whatever I'm doing I
always have this like happy face I love
[Music]
it look
she
cute so cute cute just happily carrying
you to the US so
happy open store frows you in Ram
store
[Music]
shut happily brings us to our Doom
exactly all right let's go crw than
jacob7 D Jim Tracy D Hood f for the
rainbow bro I was just talking about you
like cuz you sent a red a non- red super
chat but like writing about you know
kind of hinting at how you
are uh feeling the effects of the
expensive merch and now you're sending a
[\h__\h]
rainbow
bro du good okay let's go thanks for
singing the birthday song to me during
the last Super Chat raining M was sweet
I'm sorry I had to VOD no problem you
asked what I did on my birthday I worked
and went to bed early H but trying to
get a better
job better as in better times yeah it
seems to take up a lot of your time
so it's good if you have more free time
third round interview on Tuesday oh
third round so same place but like it
has had several interview stages oh I've
never heard of something like that that
must be like a high profile job or
something feathers crossed Everybody
Let's cross our feathers for dug
Hood it's Thanksgiving in America so I
have family stuff I should be able to
catch the first hour of the stream
though oh no he's
gone uh we're thankful for you whilea
every year you spoil us so much we are
so flocking grateful for all you do for
us no but today is very understanding if
you guys can't watch very long I know
you guys take that [\h__\h]
seriously Thanksgiving serious
business multiple ROM interviews are
becoming common
what what's there to talk about several
times that you can't just talk about in
one
round feels like the employers are
indecisive and trying to make it into
some kind of idol Survival show
wouldn't be surprised if there's
cameras I'm also thankful to smoovie and
chunkers for looking after you yeah is
true like without them I'm literally
such a [\h__\h]
wreck I know it's not good to be this
reliant on them but at least I have
something to rely on and feel better
with but I'm definitely a little bit un
healthily emotionally reliant on
them but like yeah without them I would
not be functioning I
[Music]
think please give them treats of
appreciation for giving you cat cuddles
and thank them for purring for us on
stream gladly finally I'm thankful to
kfp everyone posting their V and ner
receipts made me tear up a
you you're such a
ampf
crazy trying to one up me here trying to
make me look bad over
here we also support each other still
one of the best communities love you kfp
true true true could you just dedicate
this kiss to Blue she's helping me
finish a Christmas present for
you thank you blue all right you guys
are cooking something
blue n d you're always so kind
you'll get a kiss Doug
hood and blue also gets a
[Music]
kiss Thank you for the super sweet words
it gives me like such
a what's the word holiday I
guess holiday
season
feeling
Spirits my spirits are in yeah holiday
spirit
[Music]
so
wholesome very
wholesome callid day cheer yeah thank
you I think D Hood really isn't a
real IRL
impath couldn't be
me m thanks for the red super chat hi w
o it's Thanksgiving over in the US so I
wanted to say thanks for all you do I'm
forever grateful for the hundreds of
times you and your community have been a
happy repri for me uh from a lot of
tough times in my life in the last 4
years you're a cool bird thank you I
love you so much I love you too thank
you Happy
Thanksgiving yeah I hope you're going to
eat good
today I hope you're cooking or being
cooked
towards and being
served some really good macaroni and
cheese or
something as a side of course main the
main thing should be a turkey or one
really nice chicken we love chicken man
it doesn't have to be a turkey y
why we love chicken we know how good
chicken can be but no today is the one
day that you guys are being
[Music]
pardoned the one
day where you get a break so enjoy that
turkey I guess or you know a duck or
whatever could be a duck anything but a
chicken yeah enjoy thank you so much for
your support and sauce simply thank you
froo thank you for the red super
chat
oh hey hey T kiaha there's something
really important I need to tell you read
carefully please careful so careful
loves you thank you for being you love
oh bro bro you must also be in Holiday
spirits being so sweet trying to convey
some
[Music]
love mon wait that's
French m
m thank
you I love kfp too
it is not one-sided I'm really feeling
this oh my God
Christmas
yeah yeah J SW D crowdfunding oh thank
you thank you thank you thank you
D okay
[Music]
am Ro to not why are there so many red
super chats today what's happening just
because of Thanksgiving I guess so Road
Tomar says it's Thanksgiving in the US
so while I make my garlic mac and cheese
and bon
bon pumpkin
pie I am reminded of how thankful I am
for my can are those the things you're
in charge of are you cooking for your
family or
so damn you entrusted with
some really good sounding
food and bbon sounds really special
how thankful I am for
my this year I can't wait to see the
wter in Atlanta I'll have a flag of some
kind here
oh hope hopefully not a de flag for
me don't bring a de flag I know it might
be actually a funny joke for me for me
as a
[Laughter]
phoenix don't bring the death flag doll
man not in my
concert oh B is I thought it was Vana
[Music]
oh well but is
it
oh bourbon
whiskey
but
huh no but there's also bourbon vanilla
I guess as a very straight EDG
person I first think of the
[Music]
vanilla
bone yeah don't judge me because I think
that would make sense
too cuz it's the
dessert I don't know if whiskey is NE
necessarily a better match with pumpkin
then
vanilla never heard of the vanilla
unsophisticated
[Music]
chicken Mana sometimes so alcohol yeah
so what what are you saying are
you are
you saying it in my
defense we're not whisk is a better
match for
everything I can't I can't with
you I've never even had alcohol and even
I think of the drink you never had
alcohol
any wa whoo but then why don't you think
of the
vanilla I guess you guys over there in
America just don't have pure enough
vanilla yeah we have the better vanilla
here in Europe that's the thing that's
why you guys I'm sure that my Europeans
in here are thinking of the vanilla and
and are aware of it right Europeans or
at least Germans speaking people y'
unless bourbon brisky is your favorite
riskey I'm sure yeah you are faking of
vanilla with me you're with me hey high
[Music]
five
yeah alcohol brain Rod
[Music]
alcoholics yeah yeah yeah again actually
yes what what do you mean actually yes
yeah you mean like you're thinking of
the
[Music]
vanilla yeah yeah
yeah yeah like for example on vanilla
yogurts or so I will often say bourbon
vanilla or like when you uh go to the
baking section and you buy like
vanilla stuff for your cookie baking
baking or whatever it will say bourbon
vanilla and so
on yeah so leave me alone leave me alone
you ruined my festive mood
how was it different I don't [\h__\h]
know it's good quality vanilla I guess I
don't
know yeah man good the
vanilla
best leave me
alone anyway looking forward to your
flag root toar and enjoy Thanksgiving
and enjoy the concert Atlanta we're
coming
soon Albert cassin D
[Music]
and leer stream
what what would that be
like I don't know if I mean you
know I's see so you consider me as a
leader now
not backer ATT thanks for the r Super
Chat Kik can't be forever I'm getting
ready for some concerts next month a
stinky ghost and a bird show then the H
live world tour with Tano and friends I
have some pan lights and orange hoodie
and orange hoodie and I might meet up
with some C to organize something in
Atlanta my
funeral first the death flag now
organizing something and what I I feel
like you guys are pranking me or
something
[Music]
nah it's okay it's okay I'm a phoenix
it's
funny you want open c yeah so that I can
still get out because obviously I'm
Reviving don't close the door on me that
would be a
problem that would be an issue but yeah
um that's exciting that sounds like an
exciting month you are celebrating the
end of the year as you should thank you
D tag and enjoy and take care of
yourself though also like I think if
you're getting around so much you should
like take hand sanitizer and everything
you know don't get sick yeah I have a
feeling something will go
around and what goes around comes around
you
know take care of yourself M M M M thank
you yeah so you can look at the orange
in the crowd I want to see orange in the
crowd yes please
[Music]
I wish I could go with you to Atlanta
with
me hand in hand or just with
kfp both
maybe why you can't go with me hand in
hand but you can go with kfp hand in
hand maybe wing and
Wing thank you
d d d Midnight Rider d gar
than de is chosen as the word of the
Year by
H Devon
bear rice of reduction for the
[Music]
pinkyy hi it's no that's I want to read
British there we go
British it's p again here is here is our
little early Christmas
gift oh thank you so much
yay PR your payday came up there early
huh I don't think mine's here
yet thank you so much for H donating to
kfp but make sure you still got some
some stuff for your zombie knife or not
zombie knife hope they make something
else for my British people if there's
enough that want one
after all H do you want
one I think you need
one UK Bros come on come on let's
crowdfund the non zombie
knife thank you thank you thank you for
the support and happy
holidays m a
[Music]
d Rocka de s thanks for the pinky yeah
let's say that a bay From Another World
appears and makes it so that your cats
Pur so softly you can't hear them unless
you press your ear against them I do
that all the time anyway is this not a
big deal for you or is it enough of a
reason to Feud with this B it's not a
big deal there's some cats out there
that pure pure perk more quietly that's
fine M perk pretty loudly and I like
that but this is not really an issue you
came up with something really nice today
maybe because it's it's Thanksgiving but
you're donating from Canada so you
probably don't
care no no biggie no
problem d d thank
[Music]
you not
the paying for Wawa's copy but not the
sale price mildly considerate what was
the game 20 bucks didn't realize how do
I get a game refunded let's see
can you guys teach
[Music]
me how do I do this on
Steam before I forget it cuz I'm going
to forget it on Steam it's like a dollar
Doug Hood you paid a little bit too much
you added a zero too
[Music]
much more than
200 you mean since purchase cuz I played
for 41 minutes on Steam I thought it was
about yeah I only played 41 minutes on
Steam Account Details thank you thank
you click on your icon on the top right
of the Ste
oh Account Details cool cool
[Music]
cool do I have to go to purchase history
maybe get click to get help with this
purchase oh yeah it looks like
it it's literally
like free
Euro I would like a
refund you selected the issue my issue
isn't listed no at
[Music]
the oh I could also choose
to no I
want like to request a
refund H issue
[Music]
it doesn't say anything about like bugs
make it
unplayable my issue isn't listed too
many bugs in this
version okay submit
[Music]
request your help request has been
submitted to steam support your
reference code is blah blah blah once
the support agent has responded to your
request you will receive a notification
email
okay thank
[Music]
you okay I usually get back to you
pretty quick cool that's really just a
small amount but um yeah why not do
it t thank you oh I hope you get well
soon come on on come
on eat some chicken
soup thank you Pik us mon
[Music]
D Filipino D Filipino Filipino Filipino
Filipino Filipino Filipino Filipino
Filipino black
ey spay waterful d g d d s s s s
virtuous vment thank you D doing
Thanksgiving cooking and just manag to
dice onions and garlic like a pro o you
know you could dice them even better if
you had the Vite knife just
saying even though I normally struggle
with them thank you for Lending me your
power I could lend you even more power
with the Phoenix knife just think I know
it's it's super expensive so like
absolutely no shame in not getting it
H okay refresh I have
[Music]
headache Steven
tunch
Oh I thought it said I'm late I just
woke up from a serious coma but it said
I'm late I just woke up from a serious
food
coma what you already ate IS F
Thanksgiving not like more of a dinner
thing isn't it still early why you
already have a food
coma early early
early
Steven
chill a eern over there D thanks for the
Super Chat in the spirit of Thanksgiving
I want to say I'm grateful I have you as
my o for almost four years your spark
has L the fire of joy in my life ooh and
I can say I now know what it is like to
be happy thanks I'll stop you guys
that's too much to
say thank you I'm glad if this if this
is
true if this is true thank
you and tmy thank you for the
pinky am another November Valentine baby
my birthdayday also lines up with
Thanksgiving this year so oh oh so yeah
that's uh
not a set date I thought it was a set
date what do you mean it lines up so I
want to say thanks for everything you do
and thanks for the fun stream to start
my day off my Kami got to go see my
family now oh you already gone
no are you hearing me still I'm I'm
screaming and running after you thank
you so
much have
fun eat your belly full
because from Tomorrow onwards you'll
have to eat chicken again the same same
food as
always Happy Thanksgiving and happy
birthday happy birthday to you happy
birthday in your showe happy birthday in
your pants too happy birthday
[Music]
T congratulations I I am done with Super
Chat Garrick thank you than diary.com
chose the
Mir
[\h__\h] Twitter was suspended for some
reason so I can't answer oh you were
suspended damn it the [\h__\h] is going on
suspicious things are happening oh did
it
h hm
[Music]
I have to cook now I guess I'm going to
do a
[Music]
cook a Christmas
miracle I
guess no it's a Thanksgiving
[Music]
Miracle flatlight of fancy donkey sh no
no we have to let it go we have to let
let the backlog go guys it's okay it's
okay it's better this
[Music]
way it's better this
way goodbye bad
blog
goodbye the end is never the end no it
is for
now yeah you guys go enjoy your
Thanksgiving
[Music]
well I'll see you guys on sun Friday
Saturday
evening
mhm thank you oh c
[Music]
d back don't leave me do you want the
backlog to not leave me or me it feels
like you're more attached to the backlog
than me but same thing I guess if the
the backlock continues I'm not leaving I
guess Brandon
dun and dly
dangun
[Music]
Prince good night sweet
prince
Princessa you are dun Jacob 47 dun
thank you oh my god thank you people
thank
you it's an
expression what I don't like
it space wonderful
[Music]
action okay I go now
I I go I go I
go I go bye-bye in German we say I
[Music]
bye-bye U was a fun stream there you go
you corrected
it thank you you soon byebye see you in
the day after tomorrow
n
[Music]
oh
he