King Candy
welcome everybody
to a stream yes this is a definitely a
stream hello hello
um today we are playing a game that
maybe looks familiar to some of you guys
right now well what could this be I'm in
a very
iconic screen with an iconic
uh music in the background I would say
well
Sims one I've always been a big fan of
Sims games and I grew up with Sims one
and yeah since then I've played every
Sims so far and I've been waiting to
play Sims one uh on my channel for a
while and they has come it is today
let's go so what are we gonna do
um since one is known to be very very
much more difficult
uh Denton Sims two three and four
because I mean especially if you have
more than one sim in your household and
more than two is already woohoo
quite something
um so we maybe starts somewhat simple
maybe
um
but yeah we're gonna play uh as a whole
life English member I've been thinking
what we're gonna do this time is we're
gonna have Nino Maya illness start out
alone and work her way up to earn
hopefully a lot a lot a lot a lot of
money with our art but she's gonna start
out with no art skill but you know yeah
you know art is supposedly a really good
way to make money so surely this will be
an easy start to ease us into Sims one
so without further Ado uh let's create
in
England is her last name
who knows oh this music ah who knows
maybe eventually she will get roommates
also uh yeah her first name
this this is where the apostrophe goes
right okay and then well first of all
where's my mouse here
we're gonna make her a lady of course
and we're gonna make her
[Music]
not very neat no I don't know how
outgoing is outgoing that's basically an
extrovert right
she's not an extrovert but
she's
oh gosh she can handle people quite well
people situations well mostly we don't
have many points that is the problem you
have to like try to get it in there yeah
active oh active no playful playful yeah
we can give her some points for playful
uh her puns and all that
she do be playful and she do be very
nice yeah we can give her those points
um
okay then let's add some to outgoing
maybe one to active and want to need
and one more to play for I think
Aquarius well I don't know if Ina is in
Aquarius or not but I think this is a
pretty good
yeah line up okay and now let's see what
we can do with her visually I don't see
my mouse for some reason
uh in most Fields so this is gonna be
like a maze hello
oh it was on there
oh there it is okay uh there is not much
choice in terms of hair
as I recall
especially long hair was not really a
thing I mean still to this day it isn't
in Sims
I don't see any purple hair I think we
probably gotta go with black or so wait
that's kind of purple looking but it's
so short it's more gray maybe actually
on purple
damn this is also
[Music]
nostalgic looking oh there it is
um closer there's some funky clothes in
this game
maybe even maybe something that looks
like her casual clothes is also okay
oh I don't know oh that's like a
scientist what we just saw we could give
her a scientist outfit
this one
how about this one move your arms I want
to see it properly
move your eyes
there we go
what do you say guys what do you think
maybe that's a bit sad
it's a bit so flashy maybe for someone
like Ina
no no no no
no no
this one I'll go with this one I don't
know man okay
are you sure you finished
I think we'll go with this for now yeah
oh here's like the original family the
OG families yeah that you could play but
no we will play with Inya let's move her
in somewhere there's my mouse
whoa what the [\h__\h]
what is that Loch Ness monster one
second guys let me move myself a little
bit
I think that's better okay
well we need a starter house
uh
where are the Stars this is the start of
the house
if you buy the panel will have 7 797 to
spend well the catches oh this is the
croissant family was uh yeah something I
tested out the game with you know but
can we kick her out
we have the bulldoze or epic epic
[Music]
you have to leave
uh but we don't pull those
but we're gonna start with
zero money
yes I don't know how exactly to do that
yet but we're going to do it
okay
is going to live in this because I think
it's the smallest starter house
and the cheapest yeah seven seven
thousand five hundred
[Music]
a lot of them are occupied too okay
purchase this house we are now a
homeowner congratulations wait this
comes without furniture
the first time I bought it it came with
furniture
anyway let me adjust my screen a little
bit
um
okay
okay so just to the screen a little bit
and now we can get started who are you
wait first of all
um I said I said zero money but let's at
least start with buying the most basic
of basic Furniture because I don't know
why it didn't come with basic but I
swear we're going with the cheapest [\h__\h]
like here free handed for the cheapest
bed that looks like we are in a hospital
very sad but it doesn't matter because
enable probably sleep on the floor
anyway uh we'll probably need a dining
table
is it by order of press yeah the
cheapest one is actually pretty big and
I've used I remember using this one very
often at least you can there's like
basically four spaces on this table that
you can use it you can put something on
which will be helpful we need we need
some space to put things on a chair one
should be enough
uh how about the toilet the toilet is
easy we need
the cheapest toilet will actually
doesn't look cheap at all
the cheapest shower
good old shower I'm a shower person I
don't know
[Music]
look at these hot tubs we we need a hot
tub right oh that's so cute but no no no
we're not getting a hot tub Ina is
supposed to be poor
I'm sorry I cannot give you the
wonderful things that you're supposed to
have
[Music]
um
it's fun even though it's not the
cheapest because I I want to put it on
the wall please please forgive me
and the tiniest TV for entertainment now
the question is where do we go to put it
can she watch it
sitting on the
bed I don't think that was a thing yet
back in during these times these trying
times of Sims
actually if we can go for TV to place on
the table that would be nice too but
those get really expensive so I guess
we'll do this
and we'll get one more chair like a
lounging chair this well really old
almost antique looking one I think it's
got to be uh one space in between empty
and then wait do we have everything that
we need for now I mean we could get a
sink
standing sink
it's it's it's it's it's it's it's the
cheapest standing sink okay I'm not
giving her luxury now appliances
um
we'll need something to cook with but I
hope she doesn't try cook too early we
will we should not let her cook because
what is that is that supposed to be a
fridge
never called food hold for the truly
green Sim this pantry
at the storehouse no this is not really
a fridge this is a fridge
um let me turn this around a little bit
there we go back in the day oh wait I
just realized I wasn't moving how far
how long not moving come on this is
almost this is like a live stream huh
There's real technical issues I think my
application was just updating don't
worry I'll be back in the moment
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] is this
this must also be from some kind of
expansion
scratch resistant urine repellent Paul
this is from uh like cat uh pets
Expansion or whatever but can I go with
this one because it matches my
table
t
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] I love jamming too
Sims Music best OST ever what is this an
elephant table awesome
[Music]
sink okay and then one space for
workspace this way she can cook she can
watch TV she can eat dinner she can
sleep she can shower she can go to the
toilet like yeah yeah she she must
[Music]
she's not an idol in this game oh do we
need lamps oh yeah we'll need we'll need
some lamps I think well this space is
kind of unusable so let me put one here
um although hanging lamps probably
better
I'm gonna sell this we need a hanging
lamp cheapest hanging lamp oh it's red
so retro
for the bathroom I'll use this
is this supposed to be a light you use
outside I think we'll need to because
it's gonna be dark in there although
maybe not in Sims one maybe not so bad
in Sims one oh
artist of course we need
[Music]
um
this we'll put it outside for now
because soft question will have lots of
inspiration right and maybe you know
you're not a little bit
of company maybe is that okay can we
give her some company we could give her
a bird
a turtle
[Music]
um
a goldfish
I don't know if those smaller
um animals oh no it says turtleneck
included what birds on include what
and go buy them okay we'll see iguana we
can get
in Canada
wait this one's included
this is a parrot you can get a pet we
can
we can do it
have you talked to a parrot I think
that's that's very convenient that would
be very convenient wouldn't it Mr ball
or speaky Scarlet
I feel like I want to give her one of
these birds
do they need a cage
Hugo cries almost constant attention and
will let you know if he's not getting
enough if you feed him and spend a lot
of time with him the reward is a
lifelong buddy will keep you company for
you to come I think this is the key to
not like dying
from like being alone don't you think
but will he fly
damn he looks incredible
he looks really good I can't zoom in any
further but it looks really good
beautiful okay I will give her that
luxury okay anything else that we like
need for living for just
simple
life that I place lamps everywhere yeah
ideally we should get a alarm
am I allowed to give her an alarm
because there's so
[Music]
in this game
you you don't even you don't even
understand the menu is too small holy
[\h__\h] you don't even real you don't get
it guys if you haven't played this game
ever before
uh fight you know what we will not give
her a smoke detector if she [\h__\h] up her
cooking that is her fault
but what about this
maybe maybe
not until the first burglary Welsh where
she will learn her lesson
and then we'll we'll give her one
although there's really nothing worth
stealing is there but that's small what
if somebody
's going to cry
okay but I think for now we got
everything on otherwise we can still buy
it oh he's dropping up the the magic
stuff
thank you we can already unpack that
talking already he said cry he can't
speak our language oh one thing with
Sims one is that outside your home no
matter how pretty you make it in your
home outside once you leave your home
your room like thingy will go all the
way down and
really ruin your mood if you go to work
uh it's actually influential and the
problem is that it's somehow always
dirty first of all there's always
newspapers lying around you she's just
it's so hard to like catch up or throw
them away and it takes so much time to
do it and then even if you have all of
that cleaned up then still uh there will
be something you can't even see like
bugs and [\h__\h] and and it's always it's
always somehow not appealing yeah anyway
I would get this stuff let me place it
in a somewhere more like not in the way
way I think this one can throw away
so we have a whole uh to the underworld
no to the
we can put this here oh it comes with a
table
let's come over the table
and no to the magical world in case we
need some entertainment that is actually
really good oh wait
magic coins
magic wand can you guys even read those
butter I'll read everything out to you
guys don't worry toadstools and what
wait
how many can I wait it costs money
does it cost money
tub
no no but how much is there ah maybe two
of each scrib okay all right there we go
okay we got some free stuff let's say hi
to our birthday
how are you I wanted to win I wanna stay
here Beauty yeah
reminds me of that bird from
Starship Titanic I think was that I
played on my stream
is this Charisma that we're building
can fall
currently we have of course zero skills
but creativity is what we want
you no he's not he's he's not
quite repeating it properly yet but
let's see let's get this one Charisma I
mean why not yeah
it's got one Christmas skill points
oh oh we have some famous people Bella
and Mortimer goth keep visiting us let's
say hello we might need some friends
besides a bird but it's so hard to make
friends in this game and and keep them
as friends
it's so difficult and you guys didn't
even bring fruit cake
maybe they'll get along
usually like whatever I try it's like
minus minus minus minus relationship
like it's so hard to please people maybe
I should just let them do their own
thing because it's going pretty well I
might just ruin it let's let's let's say
let's admire Mortimer golf
oh
it was nice
I'm sorry I
oh [\h__\h] that oh minus 10.
I wasn't flirting with you
she's all very displeased oh well where
all this please oh what [\h__\h] you guys
and [\h__\h] off
[\h__\h] off they all hate me now well
I thought it was going well but we have
officially
ruined our relationship with these
people also wait I forgot to to get rid
of my money but let's get rid of this
lady here first
oh she wants to talk to me
she wants some makeup she's talking
about music
no bye bye bye bye
okay I've done some research and I'm
pretty sure there is not actually any
such cheat so what we're gonna do
is oh God
make a secret room that will have some
expensive things but she will not be
able to access it
all right what's like expensive stuff
maybe some real expensive oh yeah oh
yeah
some statues some sculptures I mean
oh
I can't even afford this wait how much
six fans we're supposed to get rid here
a big [\h__\h] clown
and one one thousand one hundred more
bucks
um
you know if you earn enough money you
can have this clown and this music
statue
and
here
this oh perfect I mean that seems kind
of like on theme because what is that
the Kraken of the midnight sea will be
yours
just as all these other things and now
we're done to free Simoleons which I
think is is is is acceptable it's
acceptable right
all right okay
indeed oh you want to look at it but you
no you're not supposed to be oh wait
wait I didn't
uh
wait can she walk around okay never mind
I have to make more wall
ah now I don't have the funds for it how
ironic okay
now I don't have the funds for it one
second um I guess I need more wall
maybe here
oh really
walls are this expensive
sorry you're only getting the clown I've
I've clowned you
okay this we can do
oh
she does want to paint the paint on her
own wow I am impressed she's actually
doing it on her own well well what will
she paint this is we have to do this
anyway
well that was fast
what
how come we've received it so fast well
we begged by these pets apparently but
stray animals I think see stop his
lasers pee on your lot
great thank you
but yeah eventually if humans are really
too hard to be free befriended then
we must
just
have animals as our companions forever
once it already has two creativity
points dance is going fast
and okay let's see how much our first
painting was just by the way assumingly
a wedding portrait uh will be
how have we already gained oh sorry we I
guess
what
how much did we get I just saw 59 how
much did we not earn any money I didn't
see it go up I think I still had some
money from adjusting the walls and all
that but still basically no money guys
it's still basically basically no money
no no food you have to continue painting
I'll get another creative disc skill
point we might just get the full today
oh she wants to sit well how are you how
are you doing where's your here oh [\h__\h]
okay I've I've overestimated her
mood
oh okay okay let's get everything up
shall we how about we sir no we have a
quick dinner because I think that does
not include cooking
oh [\h__\h]
oh
I'm nervous but
it worked out it worked out but she I
don't think she even like trained her
cooking skills that
okay and then
uh she has plenty of fun I guess or
still then let's sleep
our comfort is terrible oh my God she
needs more food what why you're not even
that hungry what are you doing
I didn't do this today
please be careful just be careful lady
it's a risk every time and I already
hear flies
we're out of lies are they down here no
why what what is there to be flown at
wait the Flies are at the parrot
why
why how do I even get rid of them
[Music]
I said I'm cursed I'll forever be cursed
with these lies or where
what
are they inside or outside I think
they're
inside
then you have to
click on the floor no well guys get used
to it
get used to the fly sound
it'll be there all the time why did you
get up anywhere I don't know
found
nothing
it does terrible sounds why won't she
sleep
[Music]
because you're too uncomfortable wait
to I don't understand
it could be too uncomfortable to sleep
but the the chair probably provides as
much comfort as the bed how how are we
gonna how are we gonna deal with that
oh
I said oh okay
well that makes a lot of sense oh and I
think that's a raccoon
I think the raccoon was the sound oh
sorry it took me so long to realize I'm
so sorry I'm so sorry let's sleep now
I want that for cool one
oh the raccoon
made a mess
I'll have to clean that up
yeah yeah wow good morning sunshine it
is a wonderful day
oh she's cleaning up several things very
smart
you might as well
before it gets too messy here recycle
these things as well
with this the Flies followed the parrots
didn't they I have to clean it oh
oh he pooped around there
ah
let's fill this food
yum yum let's talk to him a little bit
gotta do we got a relationship like for
this no
[Music]
how are we gonna become best friends
and said something about friends for
life right oh well okay enough talking
maybe some dancing maybe that will raise
our friendship no
oh did you dance really it didn't look
like much of a dance to me let's have a
let's have a lunch
please please do not set a fire please
do not set a fire
okay
we're cooking we're letting her cook I
didn't want to let her cook but
this is this is where we are now
okay she once again maybe she has a
talent for it but look at our money in
29 if you can read it we already went
down from 59 to 29 so it's time to make
money girl you're not in the motor paint
but it's your job okay but you should
pee and you should probably take a
shower [\h__\h] [\h__\h] okay Her Needs Her
Needs Her Needs are really bad uh you do
oh you made a mess okay cool you do need
some fun now
can we learn how to cook for the snow
okay then cartoons
[Music]
watch are you watching yeah
our furnace is indeed going up
very good okay that's enough
turn it off we gotta we we have to be
careful with electricity bills now it's
time to paint
make me some money Ina
it's painting something pretty
nice looking again in in other Sims
games I think when you first start out
painting your paintings actually look
really really bad oh that was five bucks
wow
wow five bucks guys
it's gonna be a little bit rough
can we pet the dog off
I was sleeping oh
but I think we got some
social from that doing
yes we do okay thank God that there is
Strays what are you doing
have a quick dinner
okay
[Music]
fine I guess and it's already time to
sleep see days go by so fast this even
worse
will work oh
please uh the fly flies are back oh yeah
you can really see
the white poop
um
yeah chill I'll I'll clean it soon
oh she's already awake well that was
fast
feed him a cracker or stance
I'm dancing more
cue up those actions
have to be efficient let's clean this up
there Sims and Sims one really don't
like it when it's dirty
wait how long are you dancing
oh no she's dancing much longer okay
then we don't need to dance again
you're too depressed to talk to birds
right now
you have to be thankful and grateful for
that you know
are you also too depressed to clean up
the mess in front of your home
to clean all that up one by one she
walks over to the trash can good job uh
hunger she's very hungry
let's have lunch
please don't burn please don't burn
wow we're so lucky we have a lucky
streak but it could happen anytime and
then we need money to buy a new uh
cooking stove
which is difficult but okay a shower
my social and my fun and my comfort is
looking terrible can you paint them no
[\h__\h]
okay I need friends
it's time guys we have to go somewhere
unless I can call is someone here
I mean we could probably also get like a
TV
but now we have to let's go somewhere a
hole in the ground so actually this
wouldn't lead us to the Magic World and
there's always people there and it
actually apparently it doesn't move time
on your own lot so I don't know if
that's good or bad but yeah we'll leave
the house and we'll see you in Magic
Town or something like that
alrighty we have just arrived in this
very spooky spooky place I've never I
don't remember ever going here but this
world
[Music]
can buy food here too I think
it's called a bit closer hi you you you
you talk to me I need I need I need
contact with humans Randy oh she wants
fun okay then let's ride 20 I don't have
that money
oh can I can I do two dollars for golf
I can afford that at least hopefully
that's a lot of fun do it do it do it do
it
[\h__\h] twenty dollars for roller coaster
sir
how much fun can we get out of this oh
yeah pretty final one it's pretty good
let's do some more
okay did you finish oh she she cancel it
why won't you cancel that that's
man
okay let's let's watch can we watch this
one sitting he'll bring up our comfort
hey girl it ended already what the [\h__\h]
and we'll just sit I don't think this is
very comfortable how
ah
maybe maybe but maybe maybe maybe we can
talk to people now oh they're talking
they're talking
it's like bragging and balance
about oh wait they're doing something
now
watch that
mummies blue
YouTuber stop talking right in front of
the stage it's really rude now she
already stopped again
you missed your chance but they're
getting along quite well
Randy Wade it's rare that I get along
with people
let's talk some more yeah we could play
chess with her that should be fun
second one second what Checkers might be
a simple game oh it's not chess but my
emotions are complex and I'm too
depressed to play
you know I'm trying my best here can we
get some food
what this is not some place where I can
get food really
um
redeem magic coins oh no I don't think I
can eat any of that
yeah
I have 10 bucks
and she is not happy
is there no food I can buy here
I don't see any proper food how come you
guys
probably couldn't afford much of it
anyway
um
[Music]
can we at least talk some more guys what
was Randy I want to talk with brandy
fun oh Randy is that Randy no apparently
not it's a different Randy it's a
different Randy it's a female Randy
maybe this Randy will like me too
oh my God there's a skeleton made
wait wait Randy Randy
everybody leave me I know you want to
sit down
oh there's at least three toilets
Bona Bona Hilda
Hilda
okay our social is looking incredible
can I make a wish for free
no
no oh I guess that's kind of a given
a thousand nine dollars okay it's time
to go home and make money I don't I
don't care I don't care girl you've got
enough social
I have to go hi we're back
what the [\h__\h]
um comfort comfort
and energy okay uh sleep
that's all I can think of but [\h__\h] we
need to come for your bed
how can I survive
I've got a strong Elizabeth when I run
out of money
to even make food
you know what will happen to this bird
right
I know it you know it there's no need to
yes okay there's no need to
act as if that's not what's gonna happen
this is a reality are we honestly not
able to buy normal food
[\h__\h] was that five bucks for
was that
Inna is going to die let's paint girl
girl you have to you have to oh she peed
on the floor
no money no food in the fridge get some
money in the refrigerator no matter
actually refill on your Sims can stuff
your face
um
we didn't even start with zero bucks
we didn't even
a skunk has decides to make you a lot
his new home but they call it fun fun
maybe we can even be friends I don't
know what to do I can't I can't
I can't even okay
can I eat your crackers
[\h__\h]
paint is this game over
could you call this game over
feels like can I visit someone wait wait
can I visit someone
yeah we all know
we all know oh my God wait wait wait
wait my mouse is gone again
okay cancel that
um
wait what
what can I
[\h__\h] stop checking maybe we can sell
something oh
um
Sally's flowers I don't have time to
take care of them anyway oh they don't
bring me money
can I sell this
I say that
Switzer's for free because it's part of
an expansion pack I say that's legit
I don't need this magic stuff right now
anyway
girl
have breakfast do better
oh my God she was going to die from
Hunger
like legit that would have happened oh
my God
I have no money
he's not doing well let's help him out
let's villains Boone okay paint paint
can you paint please no
okay okay with this little money that I
have it might end up killing us again
more or less but we need oh [\h__\h] I don't
have money it's not enough
maybe maybe at least a better chair
because this one has uh two comfort
two two two three
[Music]
all of my money
for a free from one up like one point
upgrade
that no that's not even that's not even
worth it
it's not worth it
that's not [\h__\h]
um okay fun let's bring on the fun
let's yeah she's watching comedy that I
think that's the most fun and because
she's playful too
she probably likes that okay please
please please please talk to me
we cannot talk
okay fine
I can invite though I think I can invite
some people okay wait can we talk can we
talk
Betty
please be my friend sorry TV is noisy
oh thank God I need some social
interactions
please like me please please like me
let's Gossip Girls like to gossip right
oh [\h__\h] no they don't let's talk about
magic we don't like magic don't we no
okay cool I'm more interest she likes
she likes fish in the sea she likes
Gouda me too me too
hello please stop more oh my God I'm
getting a phone call please give me free
money or so
what's this what's this
[Music]
what
that is
that is Peak Sims sometimes you get
prank calls sometimes you have to pay an
ass load of bills and [\h__\h] but sometimes
you get free money a blessing from the
heavens Hallelujah
what's so stinky again oh my god oh is
she coming in
oh welcome welcome
shall I paint a
your face so I do a portrayal portrait
of you never mind I don't have time for
that can you not use my electricity and
my water
girl
maybe I'll visit you sometime and get
all of that back she really wants to
talk to me
in Sims 2 and after any of those games I
think
you could always multitask like that and
just talk
it you want to talk to me and you talk
[\h__\h] to me
can we talk only positive things please
my socials are pretty decent right now
let's talk one more time and then I
gotta do my business you know
okay very good
um I am almost dying because I need to
sleep
is she embarrassed about that hopefully
not and not as soon as games you get
embarrassed by that kind of stuff okay
we can finally paint
we painted for a second are you for real
she's done with painting guys
[Music]
what's happening
okay she's leaving we sleep with the TV
oh that's a bad idea actually
what's the stock doing inside Luna are
you my dog now don't need the bird okay
okay and that's enough sleep
I need to get
I need the paint
that was three seconds of painting and
now she's cleaning something okay fine
um
look at this
let's have breakfast this is so
stressful
can she do it can she do it
we don't have a fire alarm I hope we
don't die here
uh
that's a huge pie CE Fire Man
enough
come on
you can do it
it's working it's getting less
we did it and it's actually
it looks usable
but we can't
wait I know when I think I think wait it
doesn't break up yo
what is it only in Sims 2 and onwards
that after it burns it doesn't break
also her mood is not even really
affected by what just happened
what what sometimes it makes it sounds
and I don't know what's going on but
it's also the sound when like somebody
um
burglars you
well well well seems like we're fine
it's probably just our raccoon or
whatever we have
can we paint no
it's your
job I think
I think the one thing that is like
generally you would think that painting
in Sims is an easy way to make money but
the problem is I think even with a bad
mood you can go to work
but with a bad mood you can't paint but
if you have a normal job you can still
go to work with a bad mood that's what
I'm saying um
so a normal job would kind of be better
but she would come back
with less of uh a good mood anyway oh it
seems like we have built by the lamb
let's let's get the mood up a little bit
before we look at the builds because
it's very depressing
wait we have a decent mood now can we
can we paint can we paint
what do you think she's painting
she's painting
something she painted before hopefully
we got more than five bucks why don't
you need to sleep
understandable understandable
yeah we didn't even let her rest the
full night so
so can you you can have this one nap uh
until now and now we have to go to the
toilet and we turn off the TV
and we have a dinner
[Music]
I think we're absolutely cursed out
oh man
maybe we should have just died before
already
it's okay we extinguish it once we can
extinguish it enough
it's spread
please don't make a fireplace on start a
fire today don't stop don't know please
stop please stop just just make a
[\h__\h] salad
even I have the option here all right I
think only having a snack doesn't use it
I wonder
can you not even have dinner if you
don't have a stove another Sims games
you just do you can use you can make
food that doesn't use the stove
I guess not here can we paint yes thank
god oh really short-lived
let's get the hygiene up that's pretty
simple
and now we can paint let's go let's go
what are you doing
why are you always is finished no it's
not okay okay okay
if this is what's bothering you let's
take care of it then
quickly
I guess because the room yeah because
it's outside oh you know what let's move
it inside
the room inside is a bit better I guess
because otherwise she's gonna be in a
bad what and now she's not looking for
painting again
God damn it Inna
let's sleep
then we gotta work on our socials and
our fun
I cannot I can either deny or confirm oh
my God we have cockroaches I can even
denial confirm that Ina uh makes these
sounds when she sleeps
yeah
[\h__\h] hell
every single time yeah can we paint we
can paint for one second amazing are you
[\h__\h] kidding me
yeah okay priorities
don't don't okay
let's go let's go
finish this finish it please it's taking
you like five days
oh at least we got another good one okay
we can sell it from 254 to
we got six bucks I got six bucks
believe it
that is nothing what
in other Sims games you would get so
much more we already have five I think
that's five five creativity points
oh my God what you're not happy me never
you need comfort no
sit there
yeah and just at least instead of just
sitting there at least let's sit and
watch TV in
I think that would be more
efficient
[Music]
okay
but what we really need is social it's
looking pretty bad again
and this bird doesn't
[Music]
he no
flipping top I'll call over a friend or
I'll go to a friend
I think
but it's so time
consuming I should just talk to the
animals
get up get up get one of the pets no she
left
give me something
she's having a mental breakdown
let's wait maybe
something no
okay okay I must have dinner
nothing nothing is passing by
to take care of me
I'm dying all alone okay you know
call neighbor I'll make it work even if
I don't see my mouse
yeah
oh
Betty or the Randy's I got really uh
well along with the Randy's that's
called
um invite over
no thanks I've got to feed my llama no
please
is it too late she's crying she's crying
is it is it am12 does that mean it's
midnight or is it
it's midnight is it oh that could be
also a reason
why
let's try the other Randy
do you wanna if they don't want to come
over then we'll talk
Randy's at work this time
someone
please
Randy
um okay how about we just call this
Randy and talk to her
oh thank God oh that's helping can we do
it again please
how about Betty
Betty's fine too I think oh God you are
socially challenged [\h__\h] do you know
what time it
okay right you're right now
enough thought that other people are
also awake at this time but I guess not
you know call me I'm awake at this time
I don't know I know what to do this is
so this is so meaningless it leads to
nothing no painting
your attitude lady
you have quite the attitude
I do not like it what was what were you
gonna do were you going to paint oh she
was gonna paint on her own okay perfect
we do be painting
this looks good this could sound well
another skill point I think I sell it
already that was fast 240 goes up to
eight bucks well it's increasing it's
increasing are you telling me painting
is not the way to go in this game by any
chance
[Music]
you let yourself in and have you got the
key or what it's good this is good we
can have fun and social with the dog I
think
to the dog
my God
just think think of it as Bubba
Ina likes Bubba
okay good I don't think it's actually
helping with fun but we don't need fun
I I wish she could paint while having a
comfort go up
I guess we just gotta sit
enough of that sit let's just sit
oh she got distracted by the dog I
thought you need to sit girl
keep some
well I can't help you with this girl you
got that just where you
what are you doing
why do you want to see your bills
87 dollar bills wonderful recycle this
[\h__\h]
can we talk no
ain't that bad I I just I just I just
wanna paint
she's just sitting what are you doing
now oh we got more Bells
oh what is this
yeah cause the other ones were late I
was late paying those
more bills I can afford it right now but
we're going down to
65 bucks because those were 86 bucks
bills and her Comfort is not going up
let's sleep
I think Inna is
going to die guys
I I
yeah no painting is
[\h__\h] the skunk painting is just not not
doing it for me
but we got a little bit of comfort from
sleeping thank God
don't start a fire today
and take a shower
and maybe we can paint
yes
yes baby
[Music]
ah
she really doesn't even look the
slightest bit like Ina I'm so sorry guys
this is this is the most I could do
but just think of her as Ina okay do it
for me
[Music]
let's have a snack
wonderful yeah we don't have a trash can
I just realized
paint
no okay
um
since she just will not uh sit still on
a chair I'm forcing her to sleep which
at least is multitasking
at least she stays in the bed
[Music]
not for long
it seems
ah
it's like an endless
cycle and it just leads nowhere
oh
[Music]
oh the bird can die
father was I thought it was
quiet uh
the bird well you know what I think
she wants to learn I think we're better
off without the bird it was just [\h__\h]
noisy and I had to clean it all the time
don't cry it's okay we should eat it
honestly but I can't
oh my God
um oh
oh wait oh I thought cleaning meant
well then let's just leave the dead bird
out there
it's it shows how badly things are going
um
I know I know it's sad I know
I would be sad too that I thought this
bird was gonna help us go through this
it seems like it was a waste of money
how cold how cold for me to put it like
that I'm sorry
spell painting 30 bucks goes up to
what what
box we've never gotten so much before
oh I hope
this will continue like that because
then we have an actual chance of not
dying
what did you just did you leave poop on
my lot or did you make a hole
I do not know but okay
[Music]
all right
looking better now guys
I'm gonna sleep for the night and
hopefully paint some more
wait we're already full energy but I
guess oh she can she can sleep quite a
bit longer okay
we're looking okay so I will take that
yeah yeah
maybe get up now okay
um ladder
food
okay okay
and painting time look how good we are
doing right now our socials are
getting close to kill us again
but we can we can hold on we can keep on
fighting
you know sell this painting for good
money please
and
so we have
almost full we're lacking freeze time
uh you leaked something there
let's call someone to visit us maybe
it's actually
a decent time of the day
uh
there it was there okay
and I would like him to come over to be
honest that would be the easiest because
he'll stay longer no thanks my spiritual
advisor has forbidden me to leave the
house today
okay okay we'll just we'll just kind of
do it with with phone calls whatever
nobody wants to visit me oh Betty didn't
want to talk to me
please
let's just talk oh thank God
okay that was helpful I'll do it one
more time it's pretty fast at least
does the other Randy want to talk to me
by any chance
maybe Ryan's at work duh [\h__\h]
wait who's wait who's that
mama mama my mama what I have a mama
like for real my mommy
or is it like a like someone who tells
you the future kind of Mama
wait I've never I don't remember meeting
this Sim before
maybe do we kind of long because we're
related are we related
is this a thing
a phone calls are way more efficient
holy [\h__\h]
okay okay fine though fine with me
um
I'll have a quick dinner
oh my God there's so many there's so
many people here just leave
a cat cafe bye bye bye
what
what what what what
scare me like that please
uh let's use and oh
clean they didn't flash when they used
my mama didn't Flash
flash I didn't flush either it seems
what are you doing flush it
oh what the [\h__\h] that was clogged
because they used my [\h__\h] toilet
toilet fine now it's fun
time to paint
I honestly thought this
uh that I would have a game over
but
we might actually have a chance now
uh
sleeping sleeping again I guess but we
need to comfort any I feel like we just
got up
I feel like we just woke up
look at those newspapers piling up I
don't have time for this I'm not going
outside anyway so [\h__\h] it
painting painting maybe do you even make
more
um like out of your paintings
if you do it in a good mood I don't know
we'll see because she's not in the best
mood now but let's sell
okay all right all right we're cooking
we're cooking we're at 178 bucks we're
still kind of far from buying like
better furniture and all that
but we at least have a somewhat reliable
not really reliable because it only
works when I'm in a good mood but we
have some sort of income
[\h__\h] console okay
168. everything was so expensive I can't
really buy anything
um get mail no you don't want to trust
me
there for you
you want to talk to a cat
um I say call someone
oh we can call Mama doesn't have the
same name as me so I guess I guess we're
really not friends
can we talk to her now is she at work
now no okay thank God
nice and sleep
foreign
like you don't even need a challenge for
this game the game itself is a challenge
so making a zero money challenge
it's not even necessary if you ask me
but are we doing it
for the sake of entertainment
let's clean the toilet before we use it
oh wait move this moon is looking good
right now we just gotta do speed eating
inhale it's consume it
let's go let's go let's go
paint
[\h__\h] oh she's going back to this one
there's like three different paintings
you can do it seems
I might even finish this one in one go
yeah last one was over 100 bucks this
one's 100 free again okay okay okay I
think it's very much tied to your
um
to your skill points oh same painting
okay but seems like we're not in the
mood to finish this one that's okay uh
take a shower
hot dog
who's the cute Bubba
oh you good bubble
I don't think you can
um adopt these which is kind of sad
I'll sleep more
okay holy [\h__\h] look at that [\h__\h] oh
my God there's like trash everywhere
I need to hire like a maid or something
[Music]
but even the maze like sometimes they
leave before cleaning everything because
you just made such a huge [\h__\h] mess
and even they can't
you know do anything about it the dog is
just
I hope we don't get like a John Wick
moment out of this
bye bye Dogo yeah go somewhere safe
please
okay
um looking pretty good maybe we can
paint no
okay I love that I love the
all the sounds The Sims make
finish that's cool one free well we
started painting that before we got the
skill points so
said you want to sit wait we have 275
can we maybe upgrade our bed especially
if we sell the current one because this
one was pretty um
it's kind of unrealistic how much is it
so far it sounds for 2025. Oh I thought
it would be less
let me see 500 bucks
and it had
it's Comfort actually not so bad uh with
500 bucks
we can get
this is the best bet that we can get
Comfort 7 energy 8.
oh but this one has the same and it's
cheaper
I'll put seven energy eight
it just takes up more space well then
I mean why the hell not Ryan wait how do
we turn this there we go
[Music]
yeah what an upgrade wait how much
comfort
grade it was six
now it's okay it's just one point
but but energy also end up from
also one point well it's it's it's it's
an upgrade it's it's definitely an
upgrade right that was that was worth it
sleep sleep some more how about that
test out the new lovely bed that I got
you in a sponsored by kfp
you're welcome get as much comfort as
you can out of this place
I wonder if at some point the homeowners
association will kick us out for all
this [\h__\h] trash
oh I've learned I've learned a thing or
two about homeowners associations in
America they would totally do that
well that's fine to me the newspaper
won't be delivered since you already
have too many that is that is 100 fine
with me I don't want the stupid
newspapers I'm not looking for a job I'm
not looking to read anything no thank
you
I don't want it
keep on painting girl why
okay I wish there was like a
a way of quickly getting my comfort up
besides this but
still got more sleep oh we got
cockroaches again
what are you doing oh they're outside
too okay
dinner time
dinner time the next step I think would
be getting a better dinner chair because
that is also multitasking I can sit on
it while
um doing other things at least
paint please paint
okay
what are you doing lady you just want to
sit okay
what are you doing
I'm just letting her run on autopilot
now but she's not doing a good job at
getting her Comfort up here I'll help
you trust me believe in this weird voice
in your head that's telling you to do
things
squeaky key voice
seems familiar don't you think this
place okay now we can paint we can paint
we can paint
finished and
135 that's what I'm talking about we are
almost there
you can do it become the artist that you
are
fall
yay creativity full do I get something
special for that no
that's so sad what did I do I'm doing it
for the money
okay
um
[Music]
how can you forget flashing enough
I don't get it
um
nope
ah okay social
it's time to get our socials up
well actually you know what I just
remembered I wanted to stop when we have
the uh when even when we die or when we
get full creativity at least for now for
this first episode let me just finish
this painting
and then we'll see what we end up with
we just got a
be able to paint but she's so
I'm so done with you
now
please comply with me I'm just trying to
help you
come on yes yes yes
you're a machine you're my machine full
points Honda 66 per painting okay that's
what what you get for full creativity
points
166 we have 300 bucks and with that I
think maybe I can afford
a better chair this one's too
[Music]
um well we can we can we can go up quite
a bit
we have 368 we just don't want to spend
so much that we can't afford food
okay but the the highest we can go is
Comfort free let's say the cheapest
Comfort free
which is already pretty much all the way
down there
okay it doesn't look so comfortable
but it's this one
Comfort free that's one point
but the things you do
the things you dilemma right well well
well that has been a little bit of Sims
Shenanigans guys I hope you enjoyed that
and yeah if you liked it we'll play more
maybe also with other Holo and members
do different challenges uh and hopefully
my Sims will not die
thanks for watching the German we say
I've been
bye bye bye