foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
chicken linking
oh
I'm sick
ah
ically
before we start
now shut up smoothie
oh but shut up
um
let me show you
my schedule let's go okay
really empty set schedule I'm sorry but
uh you know what uh it'll be worth it
because I'm filming some fun things that
will be fun fun things are fun
no worries thank you guys uh of course
I am filming content tomorrow
I am quite nervous about the one
tomorrow uh so what I'm filming for is
for anniversary stuff that anniversary
is next week and I thought yeah I have
to do something special so I thought
um of some things and tomorrow is I have
not even told the members what exactly
I'm doing but it has to do with flying
and it's not bungee jumping because I
don't think I I first of all yes I'm too
much of a chicken to do bungee jumping
but also I've there's something I I
think would be more way more enjoyable
and so I'm doing that tomorrow and I'm
I'm I'm
uh going on a little journey I'm not
doing it um anywhere close by just
because I chose like a location that
speaks to me that is maybe a little bit
familiar to I don't know
um yeah I would not say yet what it is
so you can stop uh guessing but I'm
nervous about it
I'm nervous but
um I I talked to the staff and they're
really nice
um and they have they have GoPros so
um I can use their GoPros which is
really cool yeah
um
hey
[Laughter]
and then on Friday Saturday I'm also
filming something which I also purchased
a lot of equipment for
so
um that one
also should be fun should be interesting
my mom is helping me with that one uh
that one includes a sleepover so I'm
gone for a bit I have to also go and
travel quite far for that one that's why
it's taking up like
full days unfortunately
um but yeah I'll get some cool footage
and then you guys will get to see it on
my anniversary
yeah but today it says The Ballad of Gay
Tony unfortunately I've been told you
know I just chose that one because
people keep on saying that one's so
funny huh so good huh but then I was
told
the other one you need the other one
first because of references
I guess okay
yeah but I heard it's kind of difficult
so we'll see we'll see we'll see I guess
um do you guys think I could do it in
one stream
I'm curious
I can't it's like Fast oh that would be
amazing
five hours okay six hours okay okay
six hours for normal people what does
that mean
gamer gaming is my job so I should have
even less than right
you mean normal people like non-gamers
you guys often overestimated my GTA
Adventures uh necessary time remember
remember
the only thing is with the ending of
last time that you know well the game
was
teasing me so you know but besides that
I was doing really well okay you
underestimated me a lot so maybe I can
do it in five hours we'll see
but even six hours is fun okay
so
let's play uh what's it called uh uh
something something I keep on forgetting
that one the other one just has more
punch to it I don't know why but The
Ballad of Gay Tony just has more punch
to it doesn't it the other one I keep on
forgetting
the last of them yeah yeah okay
[Music]
um
will it show up also should I put the
chat a bit more to this oh what is this
we make bigger
is it not 16 to nine
can I
why is it not 16-9
oh I can still change but I think
doesn't it go back to its
I don't think it stayed the way I
stretched it yeah I can stretch it on
the side like Minecraft but I don't
think
oh wait is it getting smaller
yeah
it's just a launcher okay let's see
[Music]
um yeah
the lost and dance
let's go for that one
people say the DLCs are really good in
this game
well I think I I think it adjusts itself
but I need to move it anyway sorry for
sure
who is this
I have a Coca-Cola zero that has too
much bubbles in it it's so uncomfortable
to drink I hate it drinking it out of a
bottle
should have bought um the can I feel
like camera in the can it's not so bad I
just gotta keep it open
then the bubbles go away
come on guys come on let's go
Dad we talked about that before
all right everybody come on break it up
let's go biker gang oh no it's still
like weird
uh
the bottom one is better no I don't know
at least the battle one you can close
I hate buying canned drinks because of
that oh they think they're so cool on
their bikes biker guns are so funny
they think they're so cool but honestly
they just look like children to me a lot
of the time
[Laughter]
real talk
and they're just so noisy like nobody
thinks they're cool they just people
just think you're like so [\h__\h] noisy
and childish
get out of here vice presidents Johnny
clevitz or what
yeah wow you're so cool
you wouldn't mess with them the
treasurer Jimmy Fitzgerald what a name
[Music]
the music is cool though
what the [\h__\h] [\h__\h] man
got that out
oh is it illegal is it illegal to bike
in the group this group biking illegal
Brian Terry
[Music]
nice ass crack
[Laughter]
uh is that a muscle bike
I miss Nico white Nicos there
there's no Nico here
dodgy stuff
it's just like men in their midlife
crisis look at them
for you that little bike they look like
toddlers
uh yes sir it means that if you continue
down that same path
you'll be locked up and calling some
cell-made daddy within a month yes sir
if I had it my way we wouldn't waste our
time you'd be inside already Mr Gray has
made great progress his share the gray
has made a great progress it's one of
the most powerful things I've ever heard
I believe in this man I saw so many
people got their Wawa bottle let's hope
you don't live to regret that faith I
want mine too where's mine works in
mysterious ways
indeed in this case seems God is
downright perverse but I'll leave the
Salvation to you gentlemen you stay out
of trouble yes daddy excuse me
yes sir
that's it
it's not weird
I know Chad I know it's a disease Chad
meetings every day
call you if I feel any views pray I pray
in fact I'm praying right now you're
very willful was very willful Chad was
very willful she's like a nice dude
you know what Chad
you changed me gentlemen shall we get
the [\h__\h] out of here this seems nice
stay in touch oh is he part of the bike
again
nice here you go is that a Ouija board
yeah what is that a T-shirt oh for some
reason it looked like a Ouija board to
me
oh getting naked
they have better facial expression than
Starfield
Sweet Home the Lost MC president oh the
president just got out of prison
president president
right it did look like it thank you okay
Luigi board let me stretch it a little
bit more because apparently the game
doesn't do it for me clean and Serene is
that enough
Michelle oh
wait my game um is crashing
I tab back in and it all turned like
gray you know what I mean and the
there's a loading loading Circle I may
have crashed it
well at least it happened in the
beginning man it's not responding should
I wait normally this never responds when
you wait
oh it responded
I think I did oh
oh yeah yeah I got a loading Circle
again but it went out of the grave
grayness
and back into the void
[Music]
roast my 4080 it can't be my fault
um
clean and Serene
something happened look I'm not gonna
click into it okay I'm Gonna Leave it oh
oh no but it came back with a loading
loading Mouse
should I should I reopen
you remember how you mess with the
settings at the end of the campaign
uh
no
I'll restart
[\h__\h] that
attack
I'm walking by uh also I uh somebody
instructed me on Twitter to do it
through and video of uh
control panel whatever
but it doesn't even show the game on
that list and even on the bigger list
that includes
every game they can think of
it doesn't show GTA 4 so I couldn't set
it for GTA for
eh I have that I don't know how to do
that
I can't read though
the graphic settings it will have to do
[Music]
we love to hear it
mm-hmm
today hello one more time okay well wait
before
we do anything we change
window size
okay
[Music]
sad twerking intensifies
full screen and I'll tab are just crash
where okay I'm not gonna all tap during
loading okay
Brown
let's see how it goes
can we skip this scoop yes starting a
new game
so far we only had cutscenes so
does your book clean and soaring oh are
we oh are we skipping the cutscene
already
didn't recognize
uh yeah oh no no skip scoop
Simple and Clean
okay stop clean and Serene is the way
all right better be making me fail
tonight
it's hot did they add I wonder if they
added new radio stations for the DLC
Let It Go
hold me
um
let's let's not get in trouble right
away
so [\h__\h] loud okay ride to the Lost
Clubhouse
how are things in there you know John
Boy stay close to this is
in that place okay whether it's train
gangs in the shower grown men crying
stay behind I'm the leader
of homosexuality in this mind country
keep getting caught there Billy
stay away from it
let's be clear I keep getting caught
because [\h__\h] like you ain't watching
out for me
okay I'll save my questions until I see
the chapter and you
you after my baby
what baby yeah a car or a bike or
are we getting his own bike are we
picking it up
oh is that what that what I was looking
at I wasn't even that nice
[Music]
still so [\h__\h] [\h__\h] loud I guess
it's just realistic we're just sitting
almost there
ah
so nice there
look at my Maneuvers whoa
amazing real Italian pizza I saw it on
the on the rosary clip
close to me
finished the GTA game
A4 recently to
I was watching her play it a little bit
what what you are fired
yeah I wonder if she's gonna play the
DLCs too
[Music]
children
not much Bill usual stuff we Mr Bill
so
come on how long was the ends up
early yummy
alcohol's disgusting where's my bike
you know where it is let me rephrase the
question where the [\h__\h] is my bike and
where the [\h__\h] have you got it back for
me because you know where it is
give me that whiskey
are you [\h__\h] is it like no then
answer the goddamn questions
brother one word in business like I told
you when you were in there or were you
so busy playing holier than thou you
started believing your old [\h__\h]
forgive me
Only Imagine
it's kind of hard I think I acquired
this touch of Amnesia I could believe
that business is more important Mr 1980s
Yuppie Big Shot than your best friend's
bike when he's close to getting 15-year
stretch the business That Pays His
lawyers fees the business that puts food
on all of our tables the business that
we are all in while you're out
pretending to be saved get my bike what
am I a [\h__\h] dog I thought you should
have got the bike you told me he told me
you don't tell me [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h]
listen Billy they were pissed and they
had a reason
your bike chopped that girl's leg off oh
but Joe John's nephew in a coma what the
deadbeats kept the bike
[\h__\h] heart
what how did he chop it oh did he drive
over it but then and I can't believe I'm
hearing this can it go that badly
anything we did for you paid your rehab
paid your lawyers fees pager red paid
everything [\h__\h] we set stuff up for you
damn we do well man but it's time to be
smart no just some good right you're
right no you're right good get uh gang
buddies I'm gonna run right out and buy
a condo get a mortgage 401k and then
fold that over into an IRA and a CD
what the [\h__\h] man be smart you be smart
you [\h__\h] jump you're ridiculous
care plan come on Johnny let's just get
his bike come on
babies
meetings
on your [\h__\h] means a lot man come on
babies
Johnny
wait come here
listen man
I'm a little pin up right now you saw
that [\h__\h] I had to go through right
what it's really frustrating [\h__\h] up
[\h__\h] craziness right what okay someone
pissed off and I've been a bit of a
prick lately
come on man
you and Angus built that bike for me oh
that's got us beef steak yeah you're
right brother I'm gonna go get it and
you know what peace and prosperity be
damned peace and prosperity be damned my
brother he what you are my brother
Johnny
isn't peace and prosperity like uh like
uh let's go like a Godly thing that they
say in Catholic Church Brothers I
couldn't let you run this errand without
me you might [\h__\h] it up
I'm the monkey on your back
[Music]
statement I'm trying to remember where I
heard those terms before
[Music]
oh my God I literally you guys are so
loud I can't but if I turn down the sfx
does that also turn down the the voices
in my head
because there's nothing for voices
specifically go back to clubhouse I'm
happy about it all right John Boy look
after that therapy [\h__\h] they're drinking
the roads all I need good to know
sharing and caring and Rehab let's get
your bike and save your motions for
later you know what Johnny you put some
of the trust the sizes they got in there
I'm gonna blindfold you when we get back
all you got to do is fall over and trust
that your brothers are gonna catch you
can you do that you boys would be too
drunk to catch VD let alone 230 pounds
of rapidly approaching middle age
230 pounds of Jewish biker John Boy your
fate is first
[\h__\h] Billy
Billy religion I gave up with faith
Johnny the Jew limits
ain't good to [\h__\h] beer
[Music]
I'm the leader leader of the chapter
again Johnny and you're just another
brother can you handle it
as long as you run the chapter right we
can
we can run it the way it needs to be run
same as the three guys before me did
same as I'm doing now really feels kind
of different before all we cared about
was having fun Brothers
cheat kicked in
you for Jerry and now what's it feel
like to you Jonathan
job and maybe if we stop doing it for a
minute we look around and realize that
the fun ended a long time ago
well I signed up to be a brother for
life you're a grateful [\h__\h] if you're in
the law for the good times only fair
weather weekends in the caraways then
you ain't in the lost you get me chill
out man I just
I just take a break
still an option on the table
okay
but he really wants to see the map so
I'm uh for you just for you
risking
my gamer life
tap alt alt Tab out of here
I'm the one driving though right
you don't need to see the map as long as
I can see it we're good okay here you go
[Music]
oh Johnny
song oh Johnny
[Music]
now
everybody know it oh yeah oh
Johnny
oh Johnny I don't know how we go
[Music]
now we can see the name of the area when
you enter
oh come on
what you're saying basically
is
because I can't cover the phone I can't
cover the the subtitles so you're saying
do this right this is what you're saying
right right
yeah no [\h__\h] it
I hate game
[Music]
game you still see it you what do you
think you're bad you can still see the
the place we just reached this is the
perfect position okay
there's no other position as good as
this one where are we anyway okay I want
to see the oh that was I'm not was am
not the map
I guess it's just
escaped so we're just driving over all
the islands okay
oh my God these idiots
Don't You Buck the police otherwise the
police is gonna bunk you
it's so bad they both crashed yeah what
is wrong with their what do you call it
the AI
what is what's what's wrong with their
programming
oh [\h__\h]
biker gang middle-aged man with their
midlife crisis incoming playing cool
people
they think they're still cool and so
intimidating and so threatening and they
got the power yeah yeah everybody must
kneel before them
mm-hmm I'm so impressed by what they're
doing
I don't know so
bikers really get gets me apparently
oh gets to me what the bike is doing
pretty boy nothing actually where's the
bike oh it's good to see you too tough
guys
um
you know what we're talking about
Billy's bike Billy's bike
Jesus man it's been a long time I
thought he was dead
why would you think he was dead a self a
crack right hey shut up listen not to
drive it you know how it is things past
hands Parts been changed up hard to say
if that job is even around anymore sorry
yeah I honestly I understand the
Bulldogs
good to see you Bill man I I thought you
was dead Tim start up the bike whoa hold
on
[\h__\h]
yeah
where is my voice
an opportunity
thank you [\h__\h] babies
what
[Music]
what's that for what the [\h__\h]
what come on let's get this over with
[\h__\h] I know they're not good people
but they're also babies like look at
that behavior my God I need to they
probably don't have to do that really
nice
so we should call their mommies and tell
them what they just did you could do
stretching The Joint My Heart
[Music]
making that guy pay for a whole mouth
get off with that [\h__\h] we got more
things to
do affecting stupid kids stuff
this is what it's about this but that
money [\h__\h] we're in it they're sticking
to all those yuppies and hippies and
[\h__\h] deadlines give me a
different boy
maybe an occasional bit of a hole
wouldn't be a man if I didn't need that
now would I how's Ashley by the way she
everything I do about a lot I don't
exist without my brothers without you if
you don't get that then you don't get
nothing John Boy it's that State of
Affairs yeah well get some tough love
you're showing them
you
dress was that a drift oh
can't stand people who act like these
guys who can
this is why U.S Healthcare is so
expensive we got bikers running around
breaking everyone's faces on a whim
do you really
man
but with a hammer that must have broken
his whole jaw don't you think
[\h__\h] man that's like so [\h__\h] up that's
like what the [\h__\h] man [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] makes me so mad
it's a joke
I would believe you man oh no this place
looks familiar
knock off
um
school buses come on let's get your
[\h__\h] bike
I don't I didn't realize we're gonna get
it right into it here
do I stay on the bike
should I get off I think it's cooler to
stay on the bike
but it's a little bit more difficult to
aim I think they got off oh I'll stay
cause I'm the Prince
come on
not I'm not so good here though
wait my shotgun aim is so cool
low range short range
it feels like I'm I'm using one of those
like confetti
gun thingies
what the [\h__\h]
even
what
was that
on
camera
are you dead now you're dead
he's not picking up any of these things
oh no now he picked something up
oh God this looks like it's gonna
explode
there
oh was that a gas thingy a gas container
back me up Brothers we're heading for a
drink she is at the double tab what
double tap what's a double tap that's
awful aim huh you mean me I don't mean
me right I bet you might get back on the
bike
pick up the pistol I tried to pick up
things but
did I not pick up anything I walked over
them though
hey I'm Bailey you guys are supposed to
follow me why am I the one following you
hey I'm Billy though right oh no I'm not
Billy
welcome home
Johnny this is Johnny right from up here
behind Billy when cruising in the Gang
oh what's that
I'm playing Johnny oh what is that enter
and stay on the bed to hold the gang
formation like exactly on the on the
badge exactly on the badge okay that is
so specific for me
now it's gone that's a president's job
same with the motorcycle club or a whole
country wait I'm so slow I can't go
faster
what does this [\h__\h] bike man
I was reading hold caps up to focus the
camera only cats caps lock okay oh okay
I'm here but now that now that you faded
my wait wait wait my wait my weird
keyboard
[Music]
oh my God this camera is weird do I have
to do that
I don't want to do it
what is is this like a mini game
this feels like a mini game it'll be
cool now
no need to fix it though
my bike isn't so
easily breakable
or so I would think uh
gets a psycho daddy real bad
it gives you trouble
start worrying about the whole
then we'll see how psycho is what
chapter you mean baby babies baby making
oh my God how terrifying you're
threatening them with a baby
okay
[Music]
oh
are we done okay
that's the guy I murdered the Jason guy
got your bike
take what you gotta take drink what you
gotta drink [\h__\h] what you gotta [\h__\h] I
don't care kill who you gotta kill but
get it out of your system and what do
you do give me a call and we'll get back
to business you're not my PO brother
remember who the head of this chapter is
I do trust me
this is mean in this context you still
have Ashley's phone number gang
why don't you give her a call for me
tell her I'm inside yeah all sorts of
[\h__\h] up and then I would really like I
mean we
meaning all of us
love some old
um
oh what
what a hole
they want a hole
uh what hole
uh
um
a woman's haul yes oh okay they're too
scared to say vagina
see babies [\h__\h] babies
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
you should be saving your strength for
your arm bro lower man
the ultimate mental medal Mayhem
Joe the last campaigns pay respects to
Fallen comrades
he looks like he's weighed he looks like
he's from um like a Sonic game or so uh
sleep on the bed we'll save the game in
advance time at six hours okay
well even the pillows have studs
that's the latest shows on TV no thank
you
man hi
you can use the last level's computer
okay
it's the only one of its kind in Liberty
City what a Johnny Test
okay do I care do I care
Johnny will need the bike to ride in
Convoy but the other lost bikers or he
has to use this one
you can save any vehicle in the parking
space outside your safe house okay but
obviously we're gonna use our bike this
whole play through
is a good bike if you lose your ride a
phone call to Clay will get you an
alternative bike
I see it do you have a pink one with
like tassels
Terry will deliver guns to your location
wow so nice
that looks like a like a logo for like
whole low life Advent or Holo live x x
six
really edgy wow we have a choice
did you just show how fight hardened
your lost gang members are
gang members get it harder each time
they complete a job with you they will
become more effective in God but gang
battles if they die of a job they will
be replaced by a new lost King oh really
okay we keep on recording I guess okay
telling me to go there
you can now phone Jim to get a fully
loaded weapon left in the clubhouse arm
wrestling room clay to bring your bike
or Terry for cheap armors or ammo okay
dorky gas stations
[\h__\h] yeah dude how's my bike
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
but they're also [\h__\h] up absolutely
and if I get tested I have a bag of 12
year olds piss right here I am
real nice oh [\h__\h] you Johnny you don't
judge me whoa calm down man have another
drink or something but calm the [\h__\h]
down okay watch your mouth
guys guys Billy Johnny we got a couple
of [\h__\h] deadbeats outside
[Laughter]
gentlemen gentlemen
questions
might I tempt you in a swift libation
my most trusted and honored guest
I thought we had a truce going on did
you
funny thing I wasn't aware but let me
tell you it's a strange kind of truce
that makes you think that it's okay to
Gate Crash My Party deadbeat
[\h__\h] wow he's so scary Billy
you're so scared you enjoy your little
boy
especially that little skull on top of
your over your over your eyebrows makes
you so scary
crash
come on yeah come on yeah wow sugoi I'm
so impressed [\h__\h]
bang bang he shot me down bang bang I
hit the ground bang bang
My Baby Shot Me Down
all right I'll be doing this on the bike
right
oh
look at me
[Music]
that's cool okay those are skills what
did he just drive over the car let me
get this single one
but my reach is really short right
that's why I'm
that's it
[Laughter]
we don't need more Brothers dying over
this sorry sorry I need to gather myself
sorry sorry I got a little bit too much
into that oh my God okay
[Laughter]
okay
I did your Dirty Work once again where
were you
[Music]
silly belly
such a cute name isn't it
[Music]
I didn't drink Red Bull I drank like uh
100 milliliter of Coca-Cola zero
and I had my my happy nap which makes me
happy because I really needed it this
time today I really needed it I I
already told this in pre-chat but I was
about to have six hours of sleep maybe
um I tried to sleep earlier I did sleep
earlier than usual but I had to also get
up earlier than usual so
um but yeah
it's moving woke me up like 30 minutes
after I fell asleep and I didn't stop
for six hours and after an hour though
hour after of her meowing I locked her
in the living room
but she still was Audible and it was
yeah she she only would maybe stop a
little bit for like 10 minutes then I
would fall asleep then I would wake up
again because she would get noisy again
eventually at 9 30
an hour before I had to get up I
gave her some breakfast I gave and I
should have done it earlier but I did
actually so half an hour after I fell
asleep she woke me up right that's when
I gave her food like in the night
basically
I like what was it maybe 5 30 or so I
don't know
and then she didn't stop though like it
was one of those times where she
immediately after getting food somehow
she wanted a second serving I don't know
what was wrong with her and I was like
no girl you just ate like what is your
issue
um yeah that was that was one of the
worst nights so I really didn't close my
eyes for too long
yeah but the nap helped it is the
recently she was being quite good just
this night she was I I did I do have
um pretty high quality noise canceling
headphones but
um they're not comfortable to sleep in
because they're like you know those
those
uh uh pillowed big things on my ears I
can't sleep with those bulky yeah really
bulky and it's okay it's okay normally
recently she wasn't like that so it
should be okay
um
[\h__\h] airpods
that's perverted brother yeah I'm not
gonna buy another pair of expenses or
even inexpensive
earphones
that's good
I'm on a Highway to Hell
High where the hell where are we going
huh
are we going to be
yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah
why is there no
why is there no routing
yo yo
[Music]
Sweet Emotions okay
over an actor all right brother I'll be
there
running on the highway
[Music]
da da da
no no no no no no no no
[Music]
wow I'm on the highway
why do I know the song I told you guys
before you don't remember the Wawa lore
I told you before I once performed
English rock songs for some old Rich
dudes birthday party
[Laughter]
I told you
ah that was the two different songs oh
[\h__\h] they matched up in my head
and stop them yeah we're gonna wait is
that the is that the chorus
and you forgot the story
the man okay for some people who don't
know the story at all
yeah
um I work for company
[Music]
where the CEO she was
um
a lady Maybe
an interesting and interesting what do
you call eccentric lady
we had I guess eccentric friends and one
of her eccentric friends was this Rich
dude
who's gonna give a birthday party and he
wanted I think he
partially it was part of this band but
yeah he put together this band and then
it seemed like they wanted another uh or
they could use because they heard of me
they could use another backup singer
um
and the the main singer was some some
American dude who was actually good at
singing uh wasn't his main thing wasn't
what he was normally doing in Japan but
just a side thing I guess
um any other he was he he was so
eccentric not the singer the the
birthday guy so eccentric like his
clothes oh my God he was probably like
50 years old or so but he was wearing
these like
lever clo black leather clothes all the
time and I don't know
it was studs and [\h__\h]
really really interesting
yeah and so I learned a couple of rock
songs I don't even know what what they
all were uh just for this one little
concert like they rented out this
venue that was pretty big and then
invited like hundreds of friends
or acquaintances
yeah but I was just you know just a
random
like backup singer not me
I love nothing more than anything right
now man but I'm kind of busy okay I love
that Rocky but I just reached my
destination I thought this call was
going to be important
oh man
[Music]
did you sing knock on Heaven's Door no I
don't think so that's isn't that a
ballad
we're sang wait what is this the ones I
just sang and other than that I don't
know give me some examples that we could
have said sang uh I don't remember
is it not knock knock knocking on
heaven's door isn't that
uh yeah we've definitely sang T-N-T I
think so or did we
go down down
TNT I think we send that
um
what I'm Dynam
is that what they say I'm Dynamite PNG
what does this then say watch me ignite
ignite Rhymes better than watch me
explode
[Music]
Paradise City now that doesn't sound
familiar to me none of those sound
familiar to me
oh well
maybe I can remember some of them
they was mad but see there was only two
of them
were mad Dave word that was you should
know that no you'd have been okay
because you because I am a lawyer yes
and during the week you cover up those
nice gnarly tattoos with a gray flannel
suit and make a nice steady income oh
man Tom Stubbs would love hanging out
with you boys he may be a politician he
may be a politician but he's an earring
smoke day oh hell yeah
hell yeah
Guns and Roses Road roses song
I would have to listen to it to remember
it
ACDC we couldn't do that in with the
weed Dave we can sing that careful if I
were you
now baby gonna make it happen we're
gonna do that one for days
what the [\h__\h] is
that make you more masculine because you
really need it look at this guy this is
Dave Dave Grossman by day top lawyer
excitement by Night a night
[Music]
say Dave are you a bisexual
cactus juice very funny I didn't think
so I guessed you just like [\h__\h]
Jonathan bung it I meant Billy by the
way
would you [\h__\h] off for a second I gotta
talk to Billy please Dave huh up Dave
you're cool there's no problem with with
yours man
sexuality team in here you gonna write
your autobiography or something he's
cool
he's a lawyer you're using it comes with
[\h__\h]
you're just using him [\h__\h] right now
I think he's tripping his face
look dude you and me
the voices
he's not
he's not have I offended you in some way
no
then what do you say we put all this
[\h__\h] behind us and have some fun
because life is pain brother and through
this life through this Brotherhood we
can give the pain the finger yeah
[\h__\h] yeah
are you [\h__\h] kidding me what where
babies all right all you let's go let's
go
[Laughter]
[Music]
the deadbeats are [\h__\h] kicking the
brother stick with me oh no not the
[\h__\h] deadbeats again
let's show them who's boss go with Billy
okay
position
Camille house battle hardens no I don't
care about how hard they are are you
sure you want to be here I mean
Johnny don't
you know see man
it's time
[Music]
oh did I oh there it is
pfk versus deadbeat
but I don't want to be these people
could that beat seem
cool
nice safe
cooler than the skin
you can call this again
I don't like pfk but it's a Jerk It's
jerk because they called us pfk
now we are
not poutine pool pool
something like poutine
fried Kentucky
oh and ages of them okay uh what I don't
see them what I'm blind
oh okay I'll be getting off again it
seems like it
can I use other guns or a bikers only
allowed to use
guns
[Music]
can I shoot this
[\h__\h] you
is it never gonna blow up
[\h__\h]
and you are me
this is lost impossible right okay we
need something else
can I
stop okay something exploded what the
[\h__\h] was that
drove away though didn't they that's not
good is that
no I guess no they're so maybe still
there
didn't I kill you
maybe you should just stay in the
clubhouse
[Music]
it only gives me a shotguns
I have about to just use the shotguns I
guess you're gonna pay for it yeah they
all just use shotguns
I gotta get different weapon if I'm
allowed to use them or is this like you
know again
better man [\h__\h] off Aoki [\h__\h]
you better hope you kill me is this just
like the safest gun they could get oh
that's my friends okay sorry
I am gonna punish you a gas tank is
covered oh wait
okay I should take actual coverage
I tried to judge my brothers You're
gonna pay for it
oh
hold on oh
okay reload baby
[Applause]
where is he is he dead oh he's dead
the Lost emcee is that his title I am
gonna punish you
oh I'm gonna get you I got the pistol so
I got the reach
nice
[Music]
[Laughter]
which one is mine you lost her lost
is it
I guess so
the one that the funky Stripes
subscribers
rest in fire
hey Romanian oh there's some of the
police
ah they will never know it was me
oh two people died is that a problem
learn a lot from
Africa I'm grateful excuse me
it doesn't give me armor right
they're expandable it's fine okay cool
and I want the healing
to him okay cool well then I don't mind
playing this little game oh
oh more
oh okay
Now give me this cover
no I didn't tell you to get on the bike
have you
I'll just do this
thank you
Brian I can't
oh
yeah
okay my brothers
oh is he here
did you just say that to me you're so
rude
okay let me pick some ammo up this is
pistol Emerald yeah bye I'm gonna die
be careful
uh
oh Mama Mia yeah
Mama Mia let me go
there's something here too you're racist
pricks
[Music]
nah this is not good let me get the
pistol Red Dot behind me
yeah I
done take it like a man dude
thank you I was like was something still
there but I can't see it okay
[Music]
I have it in my head because
but I want to shoot this one
are they okay
[\h__\h]
who needs cover
more people
just need to be precise
I've got this one Brothers oh this is a
shitty cover like what
what am I supposed to do with this
we spoil your party bricks maybe here
your time is [\h__\h] up
uh I need better guns man
do we already have enough money to buy
something oh
sure
it's so dark and gray like I can hardly
tell people from environment but yeah
I'm trying my best
Saltine cover no I mean something else
[Music]
he screamed like a black up
this one's foreign
okay
what
I'm Gonna Get You
see I thought he was behind the car it's
so hard to see are you guys seeing
anything at least on my middle screen
it's really hard to see like a comments
[Music]
and he dies from the fall
oh he's falling so hard oh what is that
new car
huh okay he is behind the car no no
[Music]
no [\h__\h]
that's also shotgun
oh wow
[Music]
ah can we just make a fist fight man oh
you're gonna have to catch I can't
believe I did it oh I got his leg and
then he fell down
ah [\h__\h] come on
yeah yeah
we need a kfp versus Deadbeats
it's just role play
ERS
[Music]
well this one's playing cats with me
I'm too okay
all right the reach is just impossible
where is the other one up there this
one's for my brothers
are there I think there yeah
ah got him got him got him got him
this is [\h__\h]
down
now I literally that was the headshot I
literally just can't reach man I need to
get closer
time to [\h__\h] die what you guys up to
here
finally
get on your bike
sure man
have you learned something you better
have learned something
oh
yeah did he drop it or was it there
before
already
wow wow wow oh that's my bike oh
didn't even let me on my bike
Brothers I missed it yeah
I survived I didn't need the med kit
is that beer Brothers yes
Jason's been killed have been broken
it's a Russian broadner heavy duty
father didn't much like it that's the
thing right that happens in GTA 4. Ryan
[\h__\h] slouch gone back all the [\h__\h]
shut the [\h__\h] up
Brothers we will find a way to get
payback against this will you I don't
really give a [\h__\h]
I'm trying to remember if I fought a
bikers gang I feel like I may have and
all the other men who've given the
finger to this shitty little thing we're
just playing the other POV from POV now
Jason whoops he's just a kid
but he hit the throttle harder than most
of us just the guy did we not have the
payback fight
Troublemaker Beer Drinker and Hellraiser
uh he didn't suffer wow Beer Drinker
what a title got any pizza
oh is that time for a brother in need
and he was scared of precisely jack [\h__\h]
in short the kind of man I'd want to be
Jason Michaels
lost but not forgotten Amen to that
movie Jason
okay boys
we are brothers for life the guy I'm
playing now in these perilous times is
more important than ever that you follow
the villains maybe he ends up dead
Remember by the end of this
DLC
oh that yeah at the beginning I remember
that I just can't make the connection
that sir you know now it feels more easy
to make the connection because now I'm
I'm looking at
the guy I'm playing him now I have this
connection you know
um where's my bike again what the [\h__\h] I
need healing you [\h__\h] leaving me
alone to die
I'll go like here I could go to the safe
house
I could go to buy some ammo stuff they
said to call but there's also a store
here
um
[Music]
I definitely need those bullets
in Canada
[Music]
and get a discount for the person I call
your friends because then cheaper
okay so I'll try calling them then will
they bring it to where I am or would it
automatically
update in my inventory
yes
I made
uh
a bridge in my head
[Music]
we need more
legs foreign
[Music]
I just want to say so in case I
um
get heavily injured or die tomorrow
well
thanks guys for everything we've done so
far for me well you know from a little
contact I have really want you to cut me
out of the loop I mean what kind of [\h__\h]
is out there Billy all you gotta do is
grab
and that makes you what a uh [\h__\h]
Grabber crabber wow now see I like how
you did that it was very good very
clever almost like a joke you know Panic
ensues Johnny you met Ray I will tweet
after it was over
hey after I survived Johnny the Jew
Johnny the Jew how the hell are you do
me a favor help keep this degenerate out
of jail I'd probably be fine I won't be
alone I'll do my best yeah later
what's he selling you toys my boy toys
should be fine no come on let's go man
where we're going bill pay somebody a
visit Billy man please don't be a dick
Johnny you seem a little tense
I'm a phoenix guys high colonic colonic
cool
Godspeed
at least I can take someone with me
that's not what I meant wait I'm not
[\h__\h] ready
oh okay this is going fast
I was gonna buy ammo
oh man
[Music]
um
Philly without knowing what's going on
I'd be nothing
kissing my ass all day Brian
what's here man
what are we getting uh
ear piercing
wait wait
my [\h__\h] yeah loading up
guys
[Music]
so you guys watch it for me okay she
will become a tomato no more potatoes
she will now be a tomato
[Music]
how about we drop the hammer on this run
Billy
twenty two outfits
race the last crew to the aod clubhouse
okay Angels up there
all right all right grab a handful bro
it's 3 A.M for me and some others hmm
I should be sleeping ideally by that
time
my feeling
yeah then only gouda will be left
only back
you'll be awake I shouldn't though I
shouldn't be awake
I will definitely I might still be awake
because maybe at 3am am I start falling
asleep but I I shouldn't even start
watching it
it's okay I I know what it will look
like so I'm not missing anything did he
just tell me to go back
yeah okay
she's got some issues
oh
the race
way but
but not against him
right yeah oh is it
oh wait oh
wait do I actually have to win this
no
no man you [\h__\h] ing dropped it [\h__\h] I
was leading
I got a toy for you yeah but it's okay
right what is this what it doesn't
matter man what are you talking about
these deadbeats are the ones who killed
Jason and broker thought it was a pole
or a Serb or something we got some bad
information brother these are the guys
misunderstandings look at you you're
acting like you don't even you distract
it's okay you're sick or something man
these deadbeats killed Jason yes they
did
after killing Jason Huh the almighty
forgives because there's a
misunderstanding
the Lost don't yeah amen Johnny Boy
you're making
they're making me do it alone
Fire Grenade for the upstairs window
when using the aim slightly above your
target to compensate for Gravity okay
genius
[Music]
gravity
uh okay uh do I have another weapon yeah
okay
I hate how the thing always moves
and I lost my
balls
it's so hard to aim when it always moves
because of him moving
I don't care if I die
did I use the grenade launcher again
okay
oh thank God
another one if you guys are giving this
beautiful grenade launcher to me I guess
I could use it right they're gonna
probably take it away again
nope and the plugs
oh hi
[Music]
grenade it is
oh that was a boom not a plop
okay okay do we have it now do we have
it
oh no there's some here oh they just
slept I'm running out of them
so he's got recruited
you are recruited officially
congratulations
dude I'm
dude I'm shooting when you keep on
moving
[Music]
come on
so much easier okay
um go with Billy wait what if I want to
pick up some things you can't tell me
what to do
okay
go with Billy what where is Billy
which one is Billy the one up here
did it say go a bill
is this Billy
you want me to go
to go to burning house
you're insane this [\h__\h] is burning
oh I should have kept some grenades well
I still have uh four okay
is this gonna work
all right
before I'm done
you better hope you kill me
okay
[Music]
come show your face show your face
too unfortunate
Billy I literally killed everybody you
didn't do [\h__\h] Billy maybe I should be
the president he was a brother of mine
wait now it says below
let's just go below from there don't
mind me [\h__\h] stay
I guess so oh yeah here
in the cellar
hit the weights
nah cover I don't need cover
I can do this [\h__\h] on my own
okay we're done Billy are you happy now
what you lurking down here for me
I work for cover hello there [\h__\h] am
I looking for Diamond are they or are
they waiting for me huh Billy what are
you waiting for
I don't see any more red
true gentlemen but we got a little
business matter up it doesn't show
anything on the map but okay up is
burning though I ain't never been in an
aod Clubhouse
um you know who I am what the [\h__\h]
sisters
bugs guys because if they were still
enemies it would show me don't mind me
[\h__\h] stay down
yeah it was on fire
Fire Burning Man hello there [\h__\h]
yeah man this must be
but there was a person just right there
I'm not imagining things right
Okay okay something was glitching oh the
deadbeats have got themselves one shot
back it up Johnny wait I don't
understand what I thought this was
payback for Jason man what the [\h__\h] is
this
2 million in knob candies gonna pay back
as I can think of come on brother hold
your [\h__\h] horses man now we're gonna
steal their smack Slow Down slow down
huh Hold Up Wait
centrifugal inertia training the quicker
your wheels go the more stable you are
the faster we go the harder we hit it
the more us Brothers pull together
that's why we do what we do it okay why
how they're the same [\h__\h] thing we go
faster longer and harder and that's how
we stay together
Daft Punk was a biker gang we lift this
[\h__\h] right now and every deadbeat
Soldier
God
Brian grab the [\h__\h]
you know the the song I was trying to
reference the other day was
Seven Days Seven Seven Nation Army
couldn't hold me down
[Music]
Seven Nation Army yeah I was trying to
reference that when I was like thinking
of soldiers
[Music]
da da
yeah
where's my bike
why is it here who the [\h__\h] parked
in
no Gaslight me
we should say that in karaoke next time
I don't think I sang it before I don't
like the song
mm-hmm
I guess we're going back to Jay
and I guess we're fine without buying
weapons I'll just take what I get
actually shut up
shut up oh I guess I did because I
rammed into okay I remember now yeah I
rammed into it do I go to E
Elizabeth
let's go to Elizabeth
uh why not call Terry now
I know kind of lazy
[Music]
Elizabeth
let's go to the bed
[Music]
together
that's is that where this is going
[Music]
on
okay
[Music]
well guys I started watching One Piece
Netflix
uh adoption thingy
yesterday was it yesterday
or the day before yesterday I think the
night before yesterday
and then yesterday I watched a bit more
we gotta finish watching the rest on my
train ride tomorrow
it's so good and yeah I know I don't
know anything about the story which is
actually kind of cool um experiencing it
like this I think it works actually so
well
uh it's like uh it gives me
youth
um dorky and Game of Thrones Vibes like
a dorky Game of Thrones
um
so cute it's so well made the casting is
so good the actors they casted all suit
their role so well and I looked up the
girl
um I looked up her Instagram and like uh
if she she was a waved before she got
casted and she posted something about oh
Nami just like me for real like two
years or so before she got casted for
NAMI so like oh my God like it was meant
to be
um
and and yeah she's so cute oh my God
she's so cute but all the other like
casting choices I think are marvelous
and I looked up some comparisons because
definitely a lot of the characters
looked familiar to me just by having
seen them somewhere before
especially like cosplayers I guess like
I've seen a million Zorro
cosplayers and and apparently it's Luffy
not laughy okay you guys are laughing at
me for saying love P the other day
buggy is crazy yeah
um
laughing
could I cast it for him like he fits it
so well he has this like uh really
Charming
Charming uh something sparked This
Charming spark Network
yeah it's so cute oh my God I really
love the story so far
um
I didn't know that one piece was about
finding a treasure that is hidden in one
piece I wonder because there's like over
a thousand episodes or chapters I don't
know what's the episodes of chapters
maybe both
um out there
just one question or is this two
spoilers does he ever find it in like
that's what's been what's what's been
shown so far
oh no
not you
what how many things can get in the way
of finding the one piece currently in
the Netflix show it looks like he's
going on a pretty good Pace like he's on
a good path to finding it maybe the one
piece is actually not real because
everybody makes jokes about it right I
was thinking so like if if it's case
that he has still not found it after a
thousand chapters and episodes then the
catch must be the twist must be that it
doesn't exist of course yeah that's
probably it now uh I don't know but yeah
that's probably it that's why he can't
find it I mean
yeah
and then he will like question himself
like why did I look for it and oh my God
I thought my whole life I built on the
big I'm trying to find the one piece
I'm coming sweetie [\h__\h] I'd let you kiss
me but I'm afraid you stick a knife in
my back while I was doing
the first man I tried that trick on
sweetie oh hey I think I know the lady
listen I also heard you got somebody for
that I know this Laney maybe there's an
apartment on Cassidy Street at shoulder
the officer said one piece is real dirty
when isn't there it's real in my heart
it's going along with toys from me stop
some ways
if the Heat's coming from Charlie
is him
you know what you got to do well either
way it ain't coming back to you Liz
hey you know Playboy he's going along
too hey Playboy yo chill for a second
show Hi how are you really
don't you want to dance
yeah I know it's a Jacob lady
it's a physical object too not something
named like friendship
I see yeah it could have been that too
who is your favorite character so far
wait let's talk about it a bit more when
I'm driving again
yeah I Don't Go Near this stuff
professionally but I found him a buyer
we're nervous when you oversee again
sure
thank you wake up I gotta go pick up the
stuff
it was like zoned out right now
[\h__\h] okay uh
collect the package from boy okay
same Mission different perspective oh my
God exciting
that's so cool I like that so uh
so so you know let me talk a bit more
about what I like so I made amaz episode
I think I just finished episode four
maybe nah nah
now I'm at episode the episodes are so
long it's like I'm watching a movie it's
so cool and and and
um I I love how they chose also Japanese
actor for Zorro but apparently he was
born and raised in La I looked him up I
was curious like what is he actually in
Japanese you know
and
um
um um
I just finished watching the one with
the with
um Kaya and the
uh the vampire that was
shocking I didn't know there would be
even vampire Pirates I guess there's
like a like an everything pirate a
pirate for everything
oh do I have to pay here too yeah Kudo
it's so cool I like how they introduced
each pirate each time like with this
wanted poster and oh the one that
um Zora was having that fight off uh in
the restaurant
that one is really cool oh they're cats
but Kudo is a vampire right maybe the
other one they're cats
I thought they were vampires
what
yeah mihawk is so cool and I think I
noticed you know this is maybe just by
me specifically noticing these things
but
um I've seen before in shows that use uh
like either uh after post editing
um for editing eye colors uh those are
usually like Too Fake uh and too
saturated and so on
um and then there's shows that use uh
colored contact lenses but you can also
clearly see the
um you know where it goes from their
real eyes to the colored contact lenses
for mihawk I think what they did is they
gave them yellow contact lenses but they
also uh did post editing by edit by
adding also a yellow color layer on top
of it for the part where you would see
his real eye color and that way it
really Blends in really nicely
um it doesn't look unnatural it it
doesn't like look too crazy it looks
really good so I really appreciate how
they handled that not only the eyes from
mihawk I can tell you 100 that's how
they did that I've looked at the eyes
really closely and I know what they're
doing
um but not only those eyes I think like
generally
you know how they handled like all those
hair colors and so on I think they they
did a great job at finding a good
balance between making it look natural
but still staying in character and not
making it look like a straight up
cosplayer on a convention but you know
giving it like a good natural feeling so
that they blend in nicely oh my God I'm
fangirling like oh my God like I love
the [\h__\h] visuals like oh my gosh
I guess your semites are good at
slipping on a deal is that right Johnny
I didn't get you because Liz Taurus and
any other two-bit Hustler on the street
would take you for the little [\h__\h] that
you are we'll rob you blind but give me
that [\h__\h]
big guy give me the package yes my
package that was easy [\h__\h] that was so
easy is the building close yeah
um one I I thought someone in the
comments saying you you like how they
built all the ships yeah yeah the fact
that they did that is I respect that at
least at least the one from the straw
hats crew whatever uh that one they
built right a lot of the others look
more like CG that one they built though
I can tell but I must say the ship looks
kind of low budget like
um
the sheet Parts oh wait ship sheep wait
a second
the Sheep part I can like see looks a
little bit low budget
um the fish the first boat the smaller
one that
um Nami brings in I really like the
smaller one the bigger one though is you
know that's a hot take no because like
it just looks like yeah the whole sheep
head you can see where they glued things
together more or less like the cuts and
and it just looks kind of cheap you know
the material looks cheap
um sheep sheep is that on purpose no
right
you will you will learn to love the
going Mary I think it's cute
but you know no no it is so cute yeah
and somebody said the the whole like
restaurant Chip the thingy is real is it
the restaurant things go oh I like to
cook I like the cook character I forgot
his name um I guess he will be one of
the crew it's it's so cute it's so like
ah I love I love it when you know
there's like uh characters in anime that
are like you know just chefs they're so
so into cooking and into food and all
that Sandia he's a really great
character too so far everybody is so
lovable I love them all okay I love them
who's my favorite oh my God I don't know
who's my favorite well Nami I love Nami
I
she's cute but also because I I thought
you know because I always only looked at
her um superficially like I only saw
like her visuals before I never knew
what kind of person she was I want you
to tell me yes she is
I want you to tell me
if she in the anime and in the manga is
she also like the same kind of
personality because I thought she would
be you know not so confident not so
badass girl
oh I love that I love that she's so cute
I love her oh my God I love her
um um but besides her because obviously
bias because cute girl um besides her
from the guys
I think
a Luffy just makes me smile so much he's
he's just ah it makes me happy I need to
get Sanji a little I need to get to know
him a bit a little bit more
um
yeah I don't know I I and I'll tell you
at the end maybe after the six episodes
YouTube I like Yusuf too yes and also
really liked the father of not the
father he's not the the shank crew I
like the red-haired guy
I guess he's not the father but he he's
like his father figure for him right
shank yeah shank he's really nice Nola
pudor no no no no I like him
but
um you know he's a very cold type but
but he's cool I like that I like his his
story and I like
um
his actions like especially in the
beginning
um oh my God I can't even
[Music]
buggy buggy gave me a little bit of
Joker Vibes which I felt was
um too bad like
um you know everybody has a right to
make some character that's kind of
joker-like but
um I would have hoped for like the first
big pirate that they introduced for them
to be more like something else original
um
you wouldn't get it
but he's he's funny too and
um I was thinking you know the best way
to fight him because they were like what
the [\h__\h] do we do we can't cut him up uh
what do we do so I thought why not just
okay there's many options you could
choke him uh like or just you know
cut off his airflow or you could drown
him you could put all his pieces in the
into that tank if it wasn't broken
already and just ground him you know
there's so many ways to kill someone not
just by slicing them up I was actually
beginning right they they execute the
the old pirate king I guess
um
[Laughter]
and and we
and they killed him with those like
poking him in the back a little bit uh
with those Chopsticks it just seemed
really like
the calm like a calm way of killing
something like a really um like not so
brutal way right so I thought oh is that
how is that how they're gonna do yeah
only the tips of those Chopsticks had
blood on it it just didn't seem really
brutal so I thought okay I see well one
piece I guess is like
um you know kind of family friendly
maybe so I guess that's how it's gonna
be like not too brutal but then soon
after like people like Zorro will like
slice people up through the middle of
their body right like that number seven
I think that's how he died he just
slices his body in two pieces yeah and
I'm like oh okay wait never mind they
are actually really brutal so far
holy [\h__\h] I was shocked at that I didn't
expect them to be brutal after all
um God damn it sorry I'm like fangirling
so much right now it was really good
show is really good what's this dude
doing
what is he doing
well I shouldn't go here huh
what else what else what else
um
man I hope they're already working on a
oh
what's that oh I'm live hope they're
already working on uh season two I would
think they would be already working on
it
maybe or they started working on it now
because they see it's a big success with
so many people are surprised about right
because normally adaptions like that are
they don't do so well especially from
Netflix
so people really should have but
I think
it's amazing I can't even compare but
from what I'm seeing like it feels like
it just works
just work yeah press YouTube is it
better than what I have
for sure
yeah I heard bad things about Cowboy
Bebop I never watched that though so
no idea I never even knew there was a
Cowboy Bebop adoption
but one piece like one piece is so
mainstream right A lot of people know it
I would say more people than the amount
of people that know Cowboy Bebop so and
there's so much potential people will
love the [\h__\h] out of it even I love it
man I don't know it even made me think
about if only
like in the Vietnam just like the movies
money if only it wasn't such a long
series I wouldn't I would even consider
picking it up hi
was it supposed to hide I would even
consider picking it up and watching it
but let's do this too long so I'm just
gonna wait for the
Netflix Seasons all right come on
they're not gonna have so many fillers
right what's going on not much let's do
this you got the Heron right right come
on let's do this
what's wrong with you you're being
[\h__\h] weird well that's what drugs do
to you I just want to know if you care
doing the stuff right you ain't right
friend no come on let's get out of here
LCPD freeze [\h__\h] I said freeze
was he really oh he's [\h__\h] out of here
what [\h__\h] do this you [\h__\h]
am I alone
am I alone in there
fight me you expect me to fight all
these Pockets along
[Music]
and I don't stop coming and I don't stop
coming and they don't stop coming
I'm gonna cover me
yeah just go to sleep buddy just just go
to sleep
[\h__\h] there's so many look at the mini
map
what do I do
foreign
[Music]
thanks camera for nothing
okay okay wait no that's not where I
wanted to go
[Music]
okay this is better maybe
nice gift oh thank you for membership
[Music]
do I kill everyone
or do I just need to escape
shotgun oh I guess it's braised like oh
wait I got this one though I got an SMG
love matcha immediately
does he even know how to use a gun like
this he seems like the type of person
who's only ever handled the shotgun
until now what where did that come from
wait wait what
from there oh my god
oh you [\h__\h] do I still I don't have I
would like a grenade launcher right now
no grenades
leaving that building will be rough
because there were a lot out there
okay
anymore
okay he suddenly decided it's time to go
down here
we have three nates oh is it is it this
is
was that window open
what is this gun is a shotgun the other
one
this looks open right okay
it feels like it's coming from above but
it's not right it's just like pew
bopping off
okay let me try
would you stop please
and I went too far
okay bye bye
yeah that might have not helped so much
it's okay
um this one's for extra
cops well grades three stars
great thank you where did I put my bike
I need my bike right yeah wait wait wait
wait wait wait I I think I know where on
this on the corner of the street
foreign
[Music]
where is the end of the circle this
circle is really [\h__\h] big ah wait I
[\h__\h] I see the end of the circle
we can do this we can do this
follow the road oh easy easy shouldn't
be so bad
okay
um should we try staying here yeah it's
disappearing is disappearing is
disappearing and free two one yeah
[Music]
different kind of bike not the cool bike
yeah Billy Billy you have no idea what
just happened to me
fishing by some kind of LCPD drugs task
force the fire was a pig
that's not kosher
there's a congressman need your help Tom
stubs to third I told you keeping that
lawyer around excuses this guy's at one
of the dumbass gentlemen's clubs in
Algonquin the kind without tits
what are we becoming man next thing
you're gonna tell me we're doing some
[\h__\h] kicking for the LCPD
it's just opposite the libertarian go
pay him a visit if you're
if yours and not just your own ego that
is
well well
if it isn't the consequences of our own
actions
should I go to one of these stumps or
stops is the third right
let's go to Stubs
I fit in I
under the sensor well
you think it's gonna be
getting me in trouble
I've been warned about the peepee
the
homo
pain Puff
purple paintball
ah Elizabeth
Liz Taurus
yeah only problem was your friend the UC
he nearly blew my ass off
[Laughter]
how's your fancy European friend working
out okay okay he was like maybe he's the
only guy in the city not working for
this thing I am in the Lost MC me and
the brothers are tight
she sounds so nice man
she's so chill
down to earth more or less
relatively
a match made in heaven I'm glad you like
it
hey
side worship shot play Oh I I'm already
completely deleting that from my memory
you know I I to me that didn't happen
I delete all memories that I'm not fond
of you know
oh Unknown Caller
[Music]
mistake what who the [\h__\h] is this agent
Jones
[Music]
[\h__\h] you fed this conversation's over we
got any evidence on me get a warrant
y well well well seems like Nico wasn't
the only one getting in trouble after
all in the city
even though it certainly felt like it
like it's always me
always going after me I need healing I
need I haven't been with my with my bike
again for a while where is my healing
that I'm being promised as a perk of
being part of the gang eh
what is this one I'm
it looked like a like a brush or like a
flashlight to me well
um
well maybe we find some food but I would
like a
vest as well
Burger Shot need her damn you know you
know New York so well huh
Burger Shot did I pass it already
what is this Hospital Pharmacy no
I guess not
I'm misleading
oh wait the park is usually yeah uh I
think that was usually hot dog people at
the park right
now I gotta go there but oh yeah I see
someone
what do you got from me
nuts as well but we're gonna go for the
hot dog that's that just seems more
nutritious to me
thank you that's what I was looking for
yeah do you guys think I can do it
without an armor
and armor
because it's far but I guess wait if I
buy you know over the phone you said
they bring it to me
could I also buy
um
the best
which one is uh
what do I do
Terry
thank you
um
gun ban
does he come by with a gun van
guns can you get here leave it with me
don't forget the vests I need some vests
that's all I really need let me tell you
the tea icon
not house
you see station there was he coming any
closer
might be stationed there okay
I'm on my way
[Music]
wow
it's not even that close what the hell
[Music]
okay there he is
well I guess can't be selling this stuff
in the middle of Central Park
hi but your car is
um
it stands out quite a bit maybe maybe
you should just go with a normal van I
reckon I'm better equipped here than our
boys over
[Music]
okay oh
cute
you know what these red things look like
down here
they look like
for sewing machines and like also just
uh so so so so so long on its own they
look like those little you know Fred
thingies it looks like red Fred to me
you know
thank you
um what should I buy I I have the SMG
now right and I have a normal gun
[Music]
right should I get in this oh that's
really expensive I can't really afford
that oh
I could get a normal grenade but even
that is 700 you call that sheep dude
I think I'm fine as long as I just have
the vest so
assault I mean I could afford it but
that's all my money gone
normal gunsters judge double well
no
yeah I'll be fine I'll find it I think
so too
uh exit thank you though Johnny man I
hope that SOB your after deserves it
sob
shoes
what could that means
ah son of the Peace
[Music]
will I find the place again without
setting my navigation
oh yes
all right I remember being here before
but not
as Johnny
you'll have an appointment uh no I
thought I'd inquire about a membership
excuse me
lies the heart of a reactionary prick so
I thought I'd fit right in here I think
you should leave sir before I call the
police
already
well maybe where will it be
[Music]
um
uh the whole screen oh are they doing a
close-up on what
um
ah
good idea
hi
ah no something happened I kind of
skipped it when I tapped back in
now
uh can I re-watch it
what's happened
yeah but maybe it's fine right
Moon's better that one what what what
what what's the context though explain
to me
got that pineapple you've got that pee
pee out
I'm going one two one two three you can
reload the game
it's okay
what's the context of the Peeping
[Music]
the rest of the song right now because
everything after one two one two three
when in context of a peepee just no
[Music]
let's not sing pineapple now
but you guys go ahead and stream
pineapple
on your own you can redo if you retry No
Need No need no need
so
pineapple ruined
oh what the hell happened
[\h__\h] guys what is wrong with you
traffic
[Music]
[Applause]
it's fun to drive on the bike hit me I
like it
oh in a sauna
Asana setting well how would I know
that's what I'm literally asking for
nine Blades of Glory
I'm going one two one two three
there will be no pee pee
no not on my stream
uh
yeah unfortunate
[Music]
you wanna see one
you know where to find one probably
not all of you but
probably most of you
all right hold on all right treats you
free well yeah you can check in Baldur's
Gate but I thought there was a simpler
option than that well
Google
[Music]
um
it's different well
it's just it may be different but
[Music]
um
aren't we all the same in the end I
don't know
it's not you want it to be the same
wow be happy with your own come on
oh Chopper's Landing find a way to take
a find a way to
where where where where where
here in here can I I'm trying to protect
people over here man oh that's not good
uh find a way they say
yeah
uh well I'm I'm [\h__\h] now
the target AKA who's inside it's you or
me
can you shoot the blaze
well now it's probably too late
[Music]
The Big Red One
I'm so Dynamic with my bike okay I'm on
my way I'll fix this situation I promise
get out of here when he he went down
wait how do I get to him is he in the
tunnel there's no ways is he in it I
hope I didn't make a mistake
[Music]
20. oh I think I took the right one yep
yep yep yep what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
can they stop feeding you don't even
look like police what do you want from
me
what's with these cars
oh okay what are we looking for uh
nice I got really close
explosion
foreign
[Music]
so is this not how I was supposed to go
down and it felt like a way to do it
not according to keikaku Nanda Emmanuel
oh wait this is already passed
by 10 30.
okay
is this past the cutscene already man
now we gotta wait forever I guess I
could tangent a bit more about one piece
it's already Landing okay
okay
um
could I take it out without can I climb
on a tree or something oh wait I usually
profile like a terror
start treating you like one no no don't
mind me
why am I already red
one choice do I have then
[Music]
is this scripted oh no he's dead don't
you think yeah he looks dead to me
nobody's shooting at me for some reason
all you need is
[Music]
can I jump over these
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay there was another exit okay
ah this is so funny
oh
why would my bike crush me we're
supposed to be buddies
[\h__\h] I'm so disappointed
too cool for helmets not my phones I
only wear a helmet
it's just you know trying to look cool
it's too cool for your helmet although
helmets can look cool
you know
plenty of heroes or anti-heroes or
whatever manage to look cool
why was the gate not close the first
time but now it was close
okay
I didn't do anything yet and now they
want to give me four stars
is that normal and now they start
shooting what okay
um
[Music]
okay I think I got him oh now
is that what I had before
okay okay
I was trying to be creative last time
okay
[Music]
be realistic guys
cops should be on bikes too like look at
how smooth I'm sailing
[Applause]
all right please let me throw a bag you
oh so nice
so Cooperative oh I'm down to two stars
what happened what made them
what made them let me
go back down to two stars oh God don't
don't [\h__\h] this up
all because I left the airport
well I mean but I was in there that
doesn't change that I was in there
and gave them trouble
well apparently just being in there
makes it a lot worse okay
there's one right there it's gonna
extend my circle oh
yeah we'll just keep on going a little
while where are we
drunk daddy and the door get ready to
[\h__\h] I don't know what that said
I wanted to know what to get ready for
[\h__\h] I should have taken that exit
um kind of easier to
Escape
uh well okay
huh
I guess I wasn't in the circle anymore
[Music]
I'm not gonna be able to disappoint you
you're
from my conscience's sake I hope your
lack of humanity is a genetic quality
okay they're not rip people the pp is
very much alive
okay Mike disturbs you might say sleep
easy and drop it to the club sometime
soon because I'm talking to him right
now
yeah kind of confirm he had a PP if he
was a guy
stops
I I hope we can see him again and this
time hopefully clothed
oh hey well I guess we're going to him
right now
[Music]
I wonder if there's anything else I want
to talk about
um with one piece
[Music]
actually never mind no one piece Johnny
Boy John I need some help Johnny got a
handout for you sorry uh
Johnny Boy
it's bad
you sound [\h__\h] entitled where are you
from project on Ward ice come quick baby
I'll try
I don't wanna
okay
I guess I have to the [\h__\h] who's gonna
go to stops get to know him better
sounds like a personal promise sounds
like a your problem
huh all right
the new brands oh yeah I don't know I
have yet
I have yet to really pay much attention
to it but they were debuting on the
weekend so then we'll see
what kind of girls they are but yeah I
think this is important to note I'm not
sure if it's really gonna make much of a
difference
um but apparently they're like a branch
like
um whole life Japan whole life ID whole
life em
PTY where am I going they're like their
own Brands you know because I guess
they're
focusing on
music activities
[Music]
I I do wonder if it's gonna make a
difference
we'll see we'll see
but within hollow life but they're all
they're doing their own brands
they all look cute though
um
I need to find out if that penguin Emoji
is for her mascot or for herself
but I mean if they're doing you know
their own music thing then then there is
no need right to even think about
horotoni right so I think no need to get
stressed out over it
uh
because they're they're gonna do their
own thing in terms of music right they
they don't need
um
good good good
portal 27 groups
well well well
Tony
hey hey
I'm first also somebody broke the pole
no you have a nice day can I even pay
there we go
paid and fall hola has two penguins now
yeah
the quiz
she like really a penguin or just the
sort of penguin soil
in soil
just like Kyla
people called Kyla a penguin but she's
not really but you know we could still
you know treat her the same way like
like we treat Subaru
you may not really be
what we claim that you are but we will
make you
what we think you are whether you want
it or not
just because you're not something
doesn't mean that we can't force you to
become that thing
very very cult-like
so so excuse me for saying it in a
German Way
[Music]
Health kind of low oh [\h__\h] oh but we're
back to
this place so I'm gonna grab a hot dog I
I
oh wait where was it
wasn't this the hot dog place is it over
here
it really doesn't like does she really
you know don't worry don't worry
we did not forced her into polotomy
so no problem there ah there is one
why did you fall down
I bonked the corner of the wall not you
no no
sorry mistake
it betrays the Lord which is personal
okay okay well I got no problem with
that you know
I have absolutely no problem with that I
think I'm gonna buy another vest
oh yeah
yeah but they look cute they all look
cute your services are required bro can
we meet up no problem Johnny I'll be
over soon and they got like cute
matching outfits
that are not very individual but they're
like you know already performing
stage outfits I would say
so
um it looks really nice
[Music]
I like red orange girl you seem to have
uh
special taste for orange girls don't you
dare leave me behind for another orange
woman
but yeah she kind of gives me piano
vibes from the design
which is cute
visually she might be my favorite too
and apparently she can speak a little
bit of English
[Music]
it's just interesting I want to hear her
speak English
oh hi greetings
get off
[Music]
I reckon I'm better equipped here than
our boys overseas [\h__\h] disgrace
[Music]
okay we man you're cool
rock and roll baby don't you know that
we're all alone now I need something to
sing about rock and roll baby don't you
know that we're all alone now and if
something to say about
nothing compares to a quiet evening
alone just go on too
that never happened
[Music]
this
one
boom boom boom
[Music]
okay
where am I going
okay almost there
nice Paramore I by the way I had a
interview today it was fairly long like
over an hour but it went quite well I
talked a lot it was in Japanese but
they're gonna translate it to English as
well
so I don't know when that is coming out
but
I will let you guys know
it was about the album basically
so I talked about the songs and musical
aspects of my career and this and that
so yeah keep an eye out for that I gave
them my point of view
yeah
of my album
explain explained everything
that I think a bad point of view
but I noticed you know because I was
doing it in Japanese
like damn
my Japanese used to be a little bit
better uh I'm getting really like
um
uh
what's the word
Rusty yeah
I was gonna say rotten I'm like that's
not it it wasn't again not rotten Rusty
foreign
but also because well all the topics
were
basically always asking for the same
words as well
Ashley are you in here
crazy apartment is kind of interesting
chill out
we want to get do you wanna do you wanna
okay
you want some you want some
I was just looking for someone okay [\h__\h]
you I'm here Ashley don't worry
oh okay all right stop it now
get down stay down
gonna regret it
chill the [\h__\h] out I'll show you dirty
fool
dirty I like I like Dirty by Christina
Aguilera is that what you're referencing
no
you don't like Christina Aguilera what's
your problem man she's hot
who else who else wants to fight me
about Christina Aguilera huh
[Music]
all right no one to fight
is that cat cat food or dog food oh no I
guess it's just normal food
doesn't look very appetizing
makes me so much stronger thanks for
making me a fighter
a [\h__\h] else so hard to walk in this
game in the narrow environments
sure know how to get yourself into
trouble don't you baby
how to get me out
come here oh
[Music]
she just needs get needs to get off of
drugs then she would be nice I want to
hang out here
can we go
I don't want to hang here neither
then again
I'm not the one messing up my head on a
week-long ice binge I remember when you
used to mess around at my place
it don't happen anymore either
take me home man
crashing hard yeah you seem [\h__\h]
um
take Ashley
Home Country Roads
Florida Play
Ed
two times three who's counting away from
the truck
[Music]
maybe if you answered your calls
tell me or something teach me every time
I sing a song people I thought you hated
this song baby
you're making yourself hurt already
[\h__\h] idiot hand me give me a break
sweetheart I used to [\h__\h] love you I
don't hate the song so sweet for Words
Johnny boy you think I'm sweet I just
didn't like our cover of it
I think I think that was the issue I
spent so long Actually I don't even
remember anything about it
yeah I just don't like the cover
[Music]
not the best memories with it I guess I
but I really I deleted that memory I
needed more storage in my brain
well but come on I wasn't the only one
the other myth members also always felt
uncomfortable about that
um song cover
and they also were not hiding it that
well
every time somebody brings up
country uh what road what what's it
called huh what what what's it called
everybody's like
um yeah okay it's country roads
let's not talk about it
Johnny it's a nice song on its own
the OG is nice
yeah I just always say everything very
clearly
I don't hide my feelings which often I
should probably hide a bit more but well
I can't redo the things I've said so far
like this
I'm just European man
and I I don't think
in German we say
uh Raiden um
I don't like that
um
I don't like talking around the hot the
the hot porridge
feeling so good
I thought you said you stopped smoking
that stuff I did Johnny boy I did I
promise I never lied to you come on baby
that's crap you know it I never liked it
beating about the bus okay
talking around the hot porridge in
German
sorry
I know I ain't much
but I'm all yours you do know that baby
don't you say so I love you Johnny
thanks for saving me again yeah yeah hey
[Music]
better than this we can we can live
better than this yeah well let's hope so
can we take that bike we'll ride off
into the sunset you and me you me and
she wouldn't if she's already so nice
and bearable on drugs imagine how nice
and bearable she's she's without drugs
I can't fix her really
whenever we bring her to
[Music]
um
what do you call it a a
thing uh
rehab yeah
let's check her into rehab
she really needs it
I will try to fix you I don't even need
the radio to give me copyright strikes
I'm My Own radio
but I saw Rosemary when she was playing
it she kept on playing the music
I was thinking maybe I could too because
every time I play the radio even for two
seconds just to immediately switch away
from it I still got um not copyright
strikes but like you know
it was immediately like recognized
but since it's since the videos were
already unmonetized anyway
I think it's actually fine like it's not
a big deal
yeah they're just claimed but I I could
have probably played it what's going on
Jim hey but I don't want to risk it know
the deal he said don't play the music on
the radio coming close to really losing
my [\h__\h] here
let's dance can I do that too
we gotta go steal some bikes from the
angels of death are we out of the bikes
are we a little too old for stealing
bikes and Clubhouse Flags it don't help
nothing I'm gonna play that yeah
but spikes on
the bridge now I gotta go what on our
craft alone
over Japan
apparently they're gonna go crazy for
these bikes in particular
Angels they're the Angels Oh you mean
the music she played it for one episode
okay okay
prank like this
together my boss got blocked
just never played it again a long time
ago yeah I don't even remember her
playing GTA 5.
but
me and gouda and amen should go on
online GTA
[Music]
I know I kept on bringing up over the
past two years or so
to play it with
but I think it would also be fun to play
because then we can actually communicate
freely
and I think
good as just as much as a little Savage
[Music]
uh capable of going on crazy Rampages
so that would be fun
just you and me
when we played Amazon Tony what the [\h__\h]
man what the [\h__\h]
um
no paranormal cleanup I'm sorry for me
screaming a little bit I was angry uh
yeah that that made me really happy when
gouda invited me and I thought our uh
our triple team even though the game was
kind of lame
you know we still had fun with it so
there's potential for even more fun if
it's a good game you know
oh sure
with our bikes on Club term friends are
parked up yeah
but the diner okay
the game was so buggy
yeah I mean yeah it was so fun though
like yeah it wasn't that scary as like
but we turned into some kind of I'm glad
I survived it very funny [\h__\h] this
[\h__\h] belongs to my contact if I wanted
to take a bike of mine somewhere I'd
drive it myself yeah having an old lady
and kid hasn't made you scared of
getting dirty I was riding right before
your mama rode your daddy Jonathan oh
[\h__\h] baby yeah it's nice and all and
[\h__\h] I mean I love them and stuff but
I'm still a brother Lost MC man forever
so it really ask you to do something
that meant oh yeah maybe after the DLCs
sometime or maybe not ever yeah Johnny I
take your point and how many people can
get together I think long and hard about
whatever yeah online
[Music]
could I do it with all five members in
theory
a lot for for our highest uh
I mean I've seen more than four before
in like mikko's online playthroughs but
four four highs hmm okay why is
everything for why yeah
why yeah
all right I'm here for the bikes
let's pick them up let's pick them up
it's time to stick it to him Johnny
let's do this I guess it makes sense
because for console games it makes sense
because they usually also only have
like four
yeah
for uh controllers a lot of time or like
ability to use for controllers
dead [\h__\h]
oh are we already getting in trouble
wait you do the shooting right phone
Terry or clay for backup
let's do it while I'm
bringing this bike up here how many do
we need Jim's hide from some angry
deadbeats we need your help now only a
chapter head like Billy can ask for that
kind of
helping to you oh okay
sweet and at the same time concerning
that they wouldn't help me
normally because of Billy's now take
cover your little [\h__\h]
[Music]
be careful there don't run into my fire
so recklessly
what exactly are we doing
we're feeling by Skies don't you want a
new bike who's left
you're also not on my map I only see
blue dots how interesting
Cali is watching me no no she's not
right
you want the blue bike uh it's so hard
to see colors in this game I'm sorry we
may have to do a paint job I don't know
if I can find the blue bike
going on here
that's what I'm talking about let's go
oh I told Cali by the way okay
I'll see you soon bye-bye because I got
really excited about the show so and I
thought she would like uh to hear my
opinion about it so I wrote to her oh my
God
I can't charming and cute oh my God
yeah and then she was like I know right
I I uh she she was like I'm hoping for a
season two and I'm like I'm sure they're
all ready
on it
hmm
cannot pay attention
ah what am I already done look at this
blue bag somebody requested the blue
bike here it is
it's okay I guess we're done
yeah yeah let's get this truck back I
never understood one piece and thanks to
this show I finally at least am getting
introduced to like the basics of the
story
foreign
[Music]
not me cute
I give my enemies then I can drive over
them right
you can go [\h__\h] themselves
here
not getting your bikes
[Music]
we should have stolen even more bikes
oh I hear police
not for me right not for me
we should unload a couple of these bikes
Prospect can handle the truck already
then Amigo you shouldn't Carry On from
where it left off as a fair amount
changed what does that mean
let me gets hot later in the show later
as in that first season still always
this easy
cool man you think so this is normal
you feel like a couple of mops with some
Stolen Bikes
these bikes are ours officers
stolen so give us a break wow looks like
these boats about smiling us don't it
unbelievable like a rednecks get smarter
every year your parents must have been
[\h__\h] brilliant siblings yeah funny
think you're smart how smart you're
gonna feel when you drag your old lady
downtown turn the cameras off and
interrogate her real hard man I bet
she'll love it excuse me for another
[\h__\h] interrogation and no [\h__\h]
time oh
[\h__\h] Birds that's right we saw the whole
thing you [\h__\h] jerk offs case clogs
now you're gonna [\h__\h] pass just like
your daddy paid your mama
oh no give her own brother a freebie
yeah
now think of a number [\h__\h] and it
better be a big one while you're at it
we're going to be watching so you better
behave yourselves boys oh you sound
scary oh oh I'm so scared
blow him up
[\h__\h] pricks like those who have maybe
join the loss in the first place I'm
gonna go back to the clubhouse see who's
around
later man later
hmm
I'm priest one piece is crazy like
everyone who watches live action only
got a little piece of the cake yeah I
can imagine
[Music]
you know after shooting apparently like
they uh until the release of the show it
took one year after ending the
the filming
so damn it's probably still gonna take a
while
they're gonna do more
but I'm happy to have given it a try oh
hey what do you mean a redeemable
wait does she already show up I know who
you mean I've seen her design before so
she's this boy Hancock show up in the in
the Netflix show already
she's hot
damn one piece has so many interesting
characters right
I am curious no
okay
eh the I'm not quite done with all the
six episodes yet but for anybody who is
done and knows one piece well how much
of the story does the Netflix show cover
and it's six episodes
how far like in percentage
one percent
uh okay maybe the one percent people are
exaggerating or like
under at uh look exaggerating
60 episodes
they covered quite a good amount
five percent ten percent five to ten it
has something to do with those cops that
pulled one over on us I mean I figured
the way I see it we got two choices if
we ignore all the fillers
the rest of our lives or or we head over
to the clubhouse close to where I happen
to know they got themselves set up and
we show them that we're not quite the
[\h__\h] that they think we are there is
no fillers well what tempted As I Am by
your first option I'm gonna have to go
with a second
really I figured you'd say there's not
much filling in one piece wow okay so
unlike Naruto
that's good
now I really wonder what's what's fully
automatic Kelly was singing about
still got it all right
they do it made me think you know of the
dream Islands when when everybody in the
Netflix show was always talking about
dreams greens and dreams and dreams and
he's like oh you have it Luffy is like
oh you have it
you have a dream all right and you're in
all you need is a dream I respect you
for having a dream and this and that so
probably are you good dude are you gonna
catch up
I'm thinking yeah that's the current Arc
right I'm thinking maybe
dream Islands
is
I actually I don't know Jim you should
think about retiring with moves like
that
but
I should watch that
and McCormick's fat as a present oh I
forgot how stupid looking don't I need
previous knowledge about one piece for
the movie Friends what do you got
no spoilers
a little bit
lots of spoilers
[Music]
lower the bent cops to the ambush
bent
big real mature man
we don't want to piss him off too
uh this is really I can't drive like
that you think I can drive like that I
can
when you want me to not go too far away
or ah okay
you can drive like that man
I can't even look at my back mirror in
games like this
where is he
[Music]
makes me so confused
thing
ah okay well as long as he can shoot me
I'm in range again
balls the size of mangoes talk more
I want to hear this conversation
true
let's keep the siren around the same
volume twice
[Music]
hey
what the hell
okay we got him time
take out the band cups uh okay
well thank you great uh where do I even
where do I even where do I even oh my
God this is not good oh man
[Applause]
is that
my friend oh
I may have been my friend
so sorry oh I killed him I may have
killed him
for you I'm gonna make it up
why is this gun make so funny noises is
this gas
I can't reach that one
oh they're positioned so nicely
how are you alive man
resilient as [\h__\h]
you better hope you kill me
this gun needs constant reloading
oh my God what is this gun
I'm dying
think I have to redo this mission
I'm gonna die
[Music]
[\h__\h] on and that's okay
then I won't kill my friend at least
I'm so sorry about that I was confused I
was visibly confused
um
but we almost cleared it
[Music]
but it's incredible how much
these these missions screw you we got
lucky because I had a vest too right I
had a vest I had full HP and these
missions are pretty hot man I'll see you
soon
all right let me pick up some things
leave the area way
[Music]
way it's better than
I'll pick it up
I got it pick it up
how did you live good question Ryan I am
confused too
I wouldn't have minded redoing it
no get the gun oh well well now I need
to get out of here I'm sorry
[Music]
I need to get out of here
out of here oh my God
man
[Music]
I got heated
ah oh what that scared me
scary bushes
so the one piece movie Red
if I watch the Netflix show
you don't think it covers me enough for
the for the net for the one piece movie
ran
I want to see that cute pink haired girl
though definitely not
oh man
what if I have Kelly give me a synopsis
could not recommend it not even close oh
man then I'll then
[Music]
I'll just have to go until Netflix
releases more
to the point of the movie
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm not gonna get into such a long
series per manga no I generally don't
read much do you really think
I'm gonna go through millions of mangas
like that be realistic guys
be happy that I'm even getting into this
at all
you might
erase too [\h__\h] right I'm in man I'll
be there as soon as I can sounds good
brother all right see you soon
is that a game oh do I have to
wrestle in the races you will battle
with other bikers for first position it
will be very smooth
I have to I don't want to do that
side mission okay do I cancel it
doesn't look like I need to cancel it
okay okay
um
the S is up there but before maybe we
can go to Safe House
to heal or so
if I find the way out of this place
there it is
blading
I'm bleeding out
[Music]
um
you should just ask Kylie her opinion
whether no I believe you guys oh
it makes sense to me
spine is fine it's fine I don't need to
watch it
urgently
I'll wait for when Netflix catches up I
I am very certain that they're gonna
make another season I spoke to the
director personally just kidding just
kidding
but you know it makes me feel very happy
to see the actors also being really into
it
[Music]
um
I can say for certain that the Nami girl
was a weep before I don't know about the
others but
they seem to be really passionate about
it and really like you know into their
character Johnny it's Jim you want to
roll on some deadbeats they're big fans
that's great I wonder if they
casted fans on purpose
like if I were to make a movie or so
about something that I created meeting
for Gang words I don't have to go to
that either huh
I'm low on XP guys
um I would I would like to you know
have people
acted out who actually appreciate and
have an existing love for the for the
um
cycling for the original
yeah
that would be not only because they
already go in there with pre-existing
knowledge but also just you know as a
thank you like
just because
I think as the author it's
it's just so much more satisfying to
give the role to someone who actually
really likes what you created right
hmm
that Nami girl that actress she's gonna
she's gonna get
really I think this is really gonna kick
off her career like apparently she has
already did some cool stuff before but I
think this is this must be her biggest
thing
so far I'm sure she is
gonna get a great career after this
she's so cute too man
I don't know that Fear Street movie but
it looked I looked through her Instagram
and it looked pretty legit I don't know
what that is though but looks pretty
legit
[Music]
Lord of the Rings best performances were
from fans too
who was a fan
oh yeah yeah also the I uh she only had
a short world but I liked the first
pirate
um the lady
and
um
what was I gonna say yeah yeah alvida
oh hello Jim
hello there James how you doing
through it brother
my whole shopping list of bikes he wants
you interested in procuring them for
them as long as it ain't gonna get us
into [\h__\h] with any more dirty cops
on The Wire when you're ready to roll
yeah cause that killed them
uh okay what
am I waiting for the details then
what was I gonna say
don't worry she comes back later really
yeah so far to use
don't really kill off the Pirates
properly because like the the guy the
rule what's his name Bobby
guppy uh what
buggy
he also and the bunny dies but then
Seven Up
whoever that was
do they just not kill the Pirates
of course they're gonna come back for
more trouble later
seven up seven who the number seven with
the tattoo on his face
that one's definitely dead right they
only kill Side characters oh okay
I'm gonna get rid of all those annoying
Pirates trying to
steal your spot is the biggest pirate
like that but okay I can see you know
Luffy wants to be a different kind of
pirate right he's a he's a good a good
one but yeah somebody asked and I wanted
to talk about this too anyway
um about the Marines uh you know one
thing I thought was really funny the the
guy who apparently is dead now uh with
the the Ivan chin cover the jaw the Iron
Jaw cover weird weird design but
interesting
I noticed that on his on the iron thing
and there's like some German words on it
for Seagull the German for Seagull
I found that interesting
but seems Seems typically Japanese to
implement some German somewhere
mm-hmm
[Music]
Colby first of all I think again great
active Choice he looks cute he looks
like you know the character is supposed
to look like the big round glasses are
so cute too this time they didn't give
him the right hair color but I think it
still suits him and then gives him still
the right
image like you can definitely recognize
him but he's supposed to have light pink
hair right
it's not that what you think then
huh because he got replaced too by the
Vice President oh well okay he's opened
up there then okay
hmm
is that a spoiler
not yet at least okay vice admiral
whatever but cool I know Colby is alive
of course well Colby
it's really
unfortunate and so far I think as a
character development I understand that
you know he looked up the Marines and
said so therefore wanted to become a
Marine then he sees how
they are though and they excuse it
because oh but you're gonna be one of
the good ones but I mean he's still
partaking in everything bad that they're
doing
and now I guess he's just getting more
and more
like eaten up and becoming part of the
problem so
no that's unfortunate
he has a huge part in the future that's
great for him I hope he one day realizes
that the Marines are bad and that he
should leave them although I was
thinking a little bit while watching
that this might be a case of where we
are watching the supposed bad ones
being portrayed as the good ones and the
good ones are being portrayed as the bad
ones just because we're looking at it
from a different point of view but it
does make the good ones the supposed
good ones look really bad though
but this maybe this is just you know a
POV kind of situation
extreme POV
he gets more development here than in
the anime oh really
yeah because in the end of the day
they're the Pirates and the Marines are
not wrong for trying to stop something
like that they just have a really a
really brutal and scary kind of way of
dealing with it but are they really
pissed
about it from a neutral point of view
are the Marines
it's really evil people in the show but
are they really bad you know are they
really to blame
they're they're [\h__\h] up some of them
are really [\h__\h] up characters you know
but in the end in the end I guess
they're just doing their job so hmm
[Music]
we just see the story from the side of
yeah yeah
and I I was thinking about that it was
quite interesting
but even then
Luffy the way Luffy wants to be a pirate
is definitely a better way because he
doesn't really want to harm anyone and
and he's just being naive innocent cute
so
yeah he's trying to find like a neutral
Middle Ground he just wants to be a
pirate so he doesn't want to hurt
anymore
how are you doing I'm fine good hey let
me ask you something do you really enjoy
life I don't really know what you mean
sir
I mean to serving all these rich morons
you know
smell of money and all that stuff you
know does that make you happy
yes sir something like that now tell me
sir are you happy I mean has giving the
man the finger really satisfies I'm
inner urge within user
there's always a man dude
he just wears a different uniform
as you say so Mr stats is in the steam
room I won't be less confused if I
watched the previous cut scene but I'm
also grateful I didn't see it
are we so annoying again how are you
doing sports is he wearing clothes this
time
you guys are not warning me this time
murdering politician okay
[\h__\h] it I'm all right okay you better be
right oh I've doubled up on the therapy
change a therapist no but I've been
seeing Dr White since I was seven man's
a genius
yes well
that if it happens
I mean
a PP games have mistakenly been very
clear PPS all over so this shouldn't be
a problem
well there's something you could do
about that yourself man pull some
strings
one sport way too far down the line for
that too much red tape yada yada
now all you need to know is that these
gentlemen are in a prison transport bus
and you my friend need to liberate them
station
get them out of there and we will make
it worth your while
okay okay I got it
don't sweat it clevitz
how sad
yeah when there was a side POV I could
see his butt was like looking kind of
spiky what a cute car over there where's
my bike on
oh
yeah
okay uh oh you know what I should do
while I'm here uh called Terry
for the gunman to get another vest why
not have to keep on stuck it up just
give me Snapper your services are
required bro can we meet up I got you
covered
give me more than one man
I need one after every [\h__\h] mission
foreign
muscle car that was not a muscle car but
it was still great
oh cute
anyway I enjoyed all of the one-piece
discussions with you I will continue my
discussion after I finished
all six episodes
I'll be back with more opinions
what
you're not
no I I pressed E I have a right
will he pick it up right now
[\h__\h] L Terry is it because I pushed
him it was an accident
um
Come Back to Me Now
come back please Jerry leave a message
no come back how how long will it take
man Terry I thought we were besties oh
okay are we like almost done with this
because the the letters are disappearing
we already like we're we're only at
three hours guys
halfway
[Music]
gone Shopper I don't see one close by
there's no guns guns that goes by
don't [\h__\h] lie to me
I know this city like my best Natasha
my West pockets
[Music]
eight oh it was eight huh
uh who's eight
where am I whatever I just finished the
the one where Zorro is like
on the floor dying
yes West pocket
the German saying yeah that's every Arc
but then why so
awesome but you watch normal one piece
didn't you come on please say yes
I feel like everybody here knows what
I'm talking about
this episode is so good I can imagine
but I stopped myself I had to go to
sleep and also I thought I'll just watch
the rest on on the train
um
yeah after he bought me Hawk yes yes
who is again so cool I really like him
like out of the villains I might like
mihawk the most
like character design but also
personality wise he's really cool Chad
look it was a victimless crime my taxes
pay your salary
long way from The Exchange now aren't
you you Yuppie bricks still think you're
better than guys like me huh
should be put down I saw what you did to
that orderly
come on even though he's supposedly evil
he's also got his like
very honorable
principles take control of the prison
transport bus
um over there
it's approaching the Station House today
how else am I supposed to approach sir
I would like to approach oh [\h__\h] that
was a nice day
[Music]
oh
oh thank you for the cussing if it
wasn't for cutscene I may have died
whoa if I would have had to get a
normally that takes so much time
I can't believe that works either
got a new destiny Nation people
yay American school buses this is still
a problem though they could still uh I'm
not I don't know how to get out of here
I might die yep
no worries we're gonna try it again
so guys okay
it's okay no worries
huh
yes try again
that's a prison Buzz why do prison buses
look like school buses in America guys
you have to explain that one to me
that's really not my problem
but it seems like a problem
I think that has like mental influence
oh no they're not okay
no you can't get me [\h__\h] you
what why cut scene
doll was I too early
huh
sakinawa
why are you just running because oh
because Leroy Jenkins yeah
well
at least up until this point I can enter
normally I wish I could climb the
building
would be nice
what was I too early no we need to enter
the bus okay maybe I just have to press
F and then immediately it triggers the
cutscene
this is maybe not the best way to do it
either
no okay yeah I gotta press F I thought
it was happening automatically before
but you have to press f
yeah
okay you're the best tasting thing
what spicy
yikes I can still very much die because
of my HP
also this bus is slow as [\h__\h] and I have
three stars
this is not good
five
this is so not good
now
this was your commute to school
oh my God this is terrible myself
Pro Donuts to bait cups
we're going for a ride
oh my gosh
How's my driving should have shot it
[Music]
I tried to
try to Shimmer this time
get us out of here where's everybody
screaming so much
should be celebrating are they
celebrating maybe they're celebrating
and I'm misinterpreting
they sound like they're panicking oh my
God
no you look happy right
just plowing through
we love to see it oh end of the circle
there about another cup is there too
yeah too bad I will go down
here oh and of course there's one here
too
terrible drivers these crops
oh my God
okay so much background noise in my head
oh [\h__\h] I'll go back up
the bag
[\h__\h] off
man can they shut up like Mamma Mia
silence
beautiful
wasn't that [\h__\h] annoying to you guys
too the amount of noise I feel so Serene
right now
serenity
Colleen and Serene
wow silent GTA play through isn't this
wonderful
wow oh my God this is so quiet I feel
like I'm in the void
should I go left
what's going on left I go up
yeah maybe we'll go up
oh they're not gonna catch us
I think this is a good path
at least they're they also seem to be
pretty slow actually the police
oh
they're catching up though
we'll see how they do with the Curve
the heli well if I stay down here then
the hilly can't see where I am
okay go go go go go go go yes this is
good this is good this is good this
could be good
potentially very good
no cop inside
out of the circle stay away from Helly
ooh stay here stay here people people
people ah
fire
almost had it
they're everywhere wait I'm still losing
them no not anymore
it was kind of oh [\h__\h]
you guys not [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
hi
close one though
try number two
you got me flanked
can't bring this big ass bus into a
spray job either I think not that that
ever worked oh [\h__\h] I'm no I'm well now
I'm [\h__\h] because this game doesn't
really turn the cards around like GTA 5
does does it
yeah now I'm kind of [\h__\h] like pretty
much [\h__\h]
I can't go back I can't go oh
yeah
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
Sumi massarium
now take your time getting the buzz
but that wasn't the end of getting a
boss isn't so much to problem
escaping with free stars in a slow ass
bus that's the problem
how am I supposed to do this maybe from
here
well then I can't really
um
I could shoot a couple of them from here
but
will be difficult to get in
yes I like dessert yes
should I try from here
kill me already
[Music]
so far they got nothing on me is this a
shotgun
uh all I got left oh no I still got the
pistols pistol
[Music]
beautiful I had I didn't get any damage
yet I think
foreign
[Music]
let's go
going in
excuse me
I'm just passing through you better want
to stay out of trouble trust me
[Applause]
[Music]
so I'm still down so much
whatever whatever
at least we're not in the Reds
let's go
at least not so many can follow me from
here
but of course they got a crazy amount of
backup
oh I will not do I not dedicated to you
look at me
look at what I just went through you
really think I'm gonna pull over that
easily um
boys
I watched some funny police body cam
footage the other day
one
was a police chase
in America we're on the highway where in
the end the the car does stop
and a lady comes out naked
completely naked
runs kind of towards the police car
and they tackle her with their rifles
naked
she had nothing on
except maybe a jacket but it was open
and you could see you have boba
everything
well that is to me sounds like the land
of Freedom can you
me
unbearable
I've never witnessed something so
disturbingly noisy before
wow
oh God
also this car is terrible wow
wow people taking photos of me can you
turn off the flash please God
stop taking pictures of me God
at least turn off the flash man
going left
trying to go left
[\h__\h]
ah Freestar Chase like this is the worst
can't go
like that and what am I doing I'm trying
to do a turn
okay
nice turn
it was a maneuver
oh according to my kikaku get out of
here get out of here
I'm dissing your standard ambience
uh this mission is ass
is this is this one of the missions
people were thinking of I wonder
when they told me
it's rough
and my circle just expanded once again
but now it'll expand again
they're like every freestars is
how
I literally have no choice but to go
with three stars man
um
how are you supposed to do this I'm
gonna go that way
thanks for the membership welcome
there's a tunnel last time I took a
tunnel on this game
didn't go very well
I don't even know where the tunnel would
be
just I'm just driving could I could I
get a spray paint I I could try but then
they're gonna see it someone's like
right on my ass
[\h__\h] off
could I could I
um does it work
please speak so they don't let you oh
it's a school bus what are you talking
about
[\h__\h] man if it was at least like if it
had like a like a
location to drop him off and the chase
would end right there
no no you're gonna lose wait this is a
chance unless they [\h__\h] scam me again
this is a chance I'm out
five four three two please please please
yes
[Music]
I was so close they were about to
go around the corner
wait ah
we did it let's go don't underestimate
the Wawa they're so nice there's a boat
waiting behind the glow oil plant and
actor Industrial
no okay now they're not so noisy get the
bus to the drop
okay only if you all will behave my
little
oranges
oh should I get some am I allowed to get
off to get some food
maybe not what you folks in for for
these fellas it's white collar
Shenanigans caught with their hand in
the cookie jar my greed was of uh more
corporeal nature
let's not discuss it as you wish dear
boy I'm guessing it wasn't paid to bail
out anyway I doubt those who remember me
think it a great idea that I am about to
be romantic terrified
[Music]
let's see
is he a cannibalist or
really in no way
no way
that's so weird
that's so [\h__\h] weird
oh my God
wow sorry sorry sorry what do I do what
do I do
[Music]
come on
okay
oh
[Music]
physics
oh
be careful careful
just like in real life
yeah
all right
good luck to these cute oranges I hope
one day somebody will peel you
and suck the orange juice out of you
just like you're uh
supposed to
bye bye thank you sir my fellow
prisoners and I are most grateful well
you've got a boat to catch
[Applause]
why does he sound like a group out of an
RPG game
medieval RPG group
[Music]
um
one one one one seven
we got some good money
your friends are out to see Mr
good luck to them I think they'll need
it oh don't you worry those boys don't
need luck you should have seen them in
73. believe me a short recession and a
trip to Panama isn't going to finish
those boys off all traders buy blood
great genes I was thinking the problem
might lie with one of the other
passengers on their little Cruise later
on oh
um
um is that why he seemed to be in such a
good mood
anyway no bikes are you really forcing
me to get on a [\h__\h] car I can hire a
bring in a bike too right
so
what to call for a bike
was there someone I could call to bring
me a bank
because Terry is for the weapons clay
bikes and bring me the hexer I guess why
not
hey dude can you find a hex or four
meter right on okay man
I love you clay that's so sweet that
you're bringing it to me uh indicate it
is it moving
oh
that's pretty close
all right ah sneeze
oh hi
are you the one
oh
I'll try to kill somebody
yo man I got to go friendship is magical
thank you
really you want me to come here or else
I don't know
um
let's call Terry too for the gun van
thank you guys
hey it's Johnny I need some of your
merchandise how soon can you get here
sorry Johnny tied up right now it should
be free later on how
tied up
are you doing some kinky stuff right now
I'll go to bed and Billy
[Music]
maybe he doesn't want to come to this
location
always a possibility
Polly married Marissa
what the [\h__\h]
okay fine not like
I like that I can't really it's not like
she's like my wife or anything or not
like I wanted her to be
no
[\h__\h] loud
oh God can't have a [\h__\h] conversation
it's not like that anyway
just you know
surprised like
they don't even know each other that
well
the taxpayers picking up the bills of
this goal so I'm going to make it
breathe
estimate
the algorithm you can
you can tell you what I need more than
that what side glasses
is that like side quests stuff that he's
offering to me okay okay yeah yeah she
did say it I don't know they'll
apparently only be married for what half
a month
and and she can even shorten it uh in
case I ask for it
uh
they share the same Papa well me too me
too though I'm also a cafe daughter
[Music]
if you think about it
yeah but uh funny I'm glad only only is
getting some love back
Billy I just don't see how we have a
choice man I have a choice I'm free I'm
not a slave I have a choice Jim I love
you man but since you've hit middle-aged
you've really lost something yeah and
since you've [\h__\h] been strung out on
this [\h__\h] you've lost something you
[\h__\h] mind what the [\h__\h] you're
speaking to huh hey what's up I'm just
trying to explain to our friend here
that possession is nine tenths of the
law we should make the slopes pay us
back right
yeah
John you think a guy like you should be
pleased yeah but Jim says there's some
problem there is that is it belong to
the Chinese the deadbeats told him we
got it they want it back so [\h__\h] them
finally Billy yeah about the meeting
look normally I'd be down for that I'm
not done straining this movie [\h__\h] them
too there's some heavily armed pissed
off [\h__\h] who killed a couple of
angels when they found out this [\h__\h] was
gone
now I'm thinking maybe we could strike
up a deal with them
okay okay yeah I want you to suck them
off while you're at it and tell Chad I'm
Cerberus can be over here look I just
think that given this war we're back
into with the angels of death and given
the fact that one or possibly two
government agencies are looking into our
[\h__\h] that offloading the heroin would be
a good idea all right don't be so
reasonable Johnny is the wrong thing to
do don't hit us with the logic I can't
even stop fighting amongst ourselves
yeah you're right we should probably all
get in a circle hold hands praising
Kumbaya
uh whatever to say no joke and matter
either end up dead
in the lockup with you I ain't going
back there I'd rather be dead damn
straight well you don't have to do
either man I just think that get rid of
that stuff now is the right thing to do
okay
I was taking the opportunity
to try to finish the last few bites of
my sandwich that I was eating before the
Stream
[Music]
I need that healing I should have gone
before starting the mystery man
I've already problem
my authority problem yes I may have one
and it's called Billy I have a problem
with his authority
because he doesn't really seem to
deserve it
don't go
hey Brian yeah
an interesting character
he stands out
yeah but I hope for the problems I'm not
in charge but maybe that's what he meant
anyway but just in a way like
I can't handle not being in charge
goodbye King we cruising I like that
we're using only bikes in this whole PLC
I appreciate that I barely used bikes in
the actual game hey hey hey hey hey hey
hey thank you
[Music]
a little bit more please
a bit more please one more place I need
some armor
Sean is more resistant to getting
knocked off of life
Oh you mean compared to Nico
you think they
fix some Physics there
what did I read about some games DLC
being
on its way or so
what did I what was that
what hey
that seemed familiar I didn't feel
anything
no it's not the ring maybe
or Final Fantasy
maybe Final Fantasy
um I might be thinking of Final Fantasy
15 race the Lost crew okay okay this
time
well if only I wouldn't have started so
far behind uh okay but this time I know
we're really racing okay
[Music]
foreign
oh we're going left okay
I cut that one a little bit shorter than
them and here we go nice nice nice stay
behind sucker look at my cute butt on
this bike
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah now we're
talking
getting that distance from them
and slowly a little bit slow down and
thanks
wow 20. thank you
you blank the Chad
[Music]
all right gin Johnny sent you two were
both so vocal in your support of this
deal you two are going to be the ones to
hand over the brown to the slopes wow
you and your boy here gonna be doing we
are gonna watch your backs because
unlike this Batman here I don't trust
those little yellow bastards
good luck hey they don't need luck we're
looking out for them
those two [\h__\h] ma'am
small PP energy staying behind like that
okay we're gonna be cool and do this
thing so let me get these straight you
are here to sell us back our heroine the
heroin my cousin sweat it over in order
to bring to this country only to have it
stolen look man we can do business or go
to war it's your call in this country
they seem to be the same thing you'll
speak in pieces of [\h__\h] off you
they were dressed nicely though I like
their quotes
man should have jumped onto her bikes
and mounted them immediately
yeah and wait wait wait okay
[Music]
how you take no damage
the way out way out what are you doing
what is he doing
okay that was a good start
good good that they were all bundled up
over there special bundle
shotguns are [\h__\h]
oh hi
come on you open
can I race this one
oh
yeah [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you
shotgun for a close I know I've noticed
but do I have anything else yes
yes I do okay okay
we're not doing so well in the gun
Department generally in this game
unfortunately
is that better should I switch that out
it doesn't really look better
yes
okay
oh looks like a revolver is that a
revolver is this what you call it is
over
hey it's telling the Clippers to clip it
there's not much to clip though right
now but um you know what stream POV uh
I guess
and
um what else could I do that's clippable
um um
[Music]
I can't think of anything clappable
wait this is not a revolver this is
again this uh I've had this weapon
before
who's left
ah I don't like this one because it
needs so much reloading
[\h__\h] fat Clippers just put some kind
of clickbait there or so to help me out
because I can't think of anything
capable right now
oh nice shot wow
wow should I switch this one now or is
this going back again
you're killing us thank you
well you're a good Clipper though
I said enough on his stuff today I think
I already covered all my bases yeah
nice ow who the [\h__\h]
yeah yeah the fun is over
yeah oh okay a little time to like this
gun if only it didn't have to reload so
much
that's not let's not jump down
let's not try to jump cat down
is that a med kid that I see and I don't
need it I'm full now
what about this thing
yeah it doesn't look good
where am I going
on here
oh oh the way he rolled in
am I hearing police
getting warm
EST we're having a discussion okay back
in the day when I was still living with
my mom
you know what I wonder if you guys can
relate every time my mom had like a
fight with with
[Music]
um
you know her relationship partner
I it would always like freak me out
because they would fight really loudly
um yeah and I was always like doing fine
and they're like it's not a fight it's
we're just having ah
oh I survived
yeah but they would be like ah they're
just having a discussion but it doesn't
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] like a discussion you
guys up there
yeah
um
is that relatable to somebody
but yeah I guess as a parent you're just
trying to I mean I was already a
teenager I don't know but I guess he was
just trying to uh
you know
have your kids not freak out and uh yeah
in the end you don't you don't want your
kids to be concerned with that stuff
oh you little [\h__\h] get out of here
[\h__\h] dead man
how dare you shoot me around the corner
honest I don't like this position
um
okay gotta be risky sometimes
my sister would protect me some anytime
my parents thoughts oh
run over there
you little [\h__\h]
someone so left there I can't see ah
foreign
give me some ammo guys nobody got the
SMG so they can't give me ammo oh wait
are we picking any of this up
doesn't look like what I picked up
before
nice good teamwork oh he's got an SMG
thanks for reloading timing
I can't shoot from here for some reason
wow
record speed
I can't shoot like that
screw you sometimes
do it the Bold way I think this time
I'll take the med kit even if it's just
a little bit
oh are we on the shotgun now oof okay
okay now I need the medkit
[Music]
it's not always as easy as it looks
I'm coming
do I want some of those stuff
um
sorry I was reading chat
I don't have much ever on this one left
either man
[Music]
switch to your pistol yeah
where is it there oh hey it is the
upgraded one
wow and what do you call this thing
that's not a pistol is it
it's like a hybrid oh it's slippery is
up
[Music]
I got caught in a good position though
Hallelujah
laughs
a muscle pistol machine pistol oh really
I haven't had the pleasure
of getting acquainted to this gun in GTA
4 much I think okay how do we go down
normally again
not like I just pressed F and then he
went on to jump down there automatically
wow
wow the audacity
oh
only for this you can see uh-huh
[Applause]
[Music]
Johnny you're dead shut your goddamn
mouth shut your mouth
[Laughter]
all right man shit's [\h__\h] Billy's been
taken down
let's go
mm-hmm
may have been the other way around if it
was the other way around haha logic
how's she going
it's like saying people die when they
get killed
did I leave my bike somewhere
we've got no leader you're gonna have to
take charge of the chapter man let's go
let's see what Brian's got to say for
himself
hmm
didn't Brian get caught too
[Music]
um
oh
clay my brother oh wow he escaped okay
at a certain time that has to pass until
you can get another one
oh wait is that my bike
the blue one
I'm sorry
oh is it because my bike is closed
um
the [\h__\h] Brian what happened back there
[Music]
[Applause]
follow me [\h__\h] Hey where's the other
guy
you're not in any hurry are you huh
he does not care
oh
the ground
[Music]
so
who was this who said something to me
about me having like Authority issues
hmm
you want to say that again to me now
to know what the [\h__\h] went down as well
I know exactly what went down though
I am the authority
but now that I'm a leader I can't like
issue that healing thingy for myself can
I
that's kind of sad I like that feature
[Music]
exactly
I even had to redo the mission once
because I died and you weren't there to
help me
in that bad bad timeline where your new
leader dies
they turn at the same exact time
yeah okay I'm trying to look at you guys
because I actually kind of cute how
you're
copying me like little duckies look
so now that we're the leader
are we like halfway through the DLC
I'm hoping a bit more that have for
halfway through half through halfway
through
eh Mommy
okay
very good
11 out of 22 missions okay ah [\h__\h] I
missed it again no
[Music]
it thinks I'm above
um
well go around I'll go around
and then down there it wants me to go
down
now I got it well sometimes it's not
even my fault sometimes it's the
navigation fault okay
three to four more hours damn it's
already 9 P.M
I guess we could now in this case we
can't even take a taxi because we have
to leave the Gang
hmm
well I don't know how we could speed it
up maybe in other cases we can take the
taxi dough
that's
or we cut it off a little bit early and
then we combine it with Gay Tony
because I still kind of eat dinner and I
need to sleep early
I was actually thinking I could even
read super chats
sorry we're doing a turn
is that better okay
is the Gay Tony one also about the same
length
what is this not the red left
[Music]
a bit longer longer
okay
that's fine
just want to get a rough idea
yeah
and I'm getting nervous about tomorrow
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm scared but I feel like I would be
more scared of something like bungee
jumping I feel like bungee jumping is
like
the mentality it's like you're jumping
into
like okay you know you're safe you you
think you know you're safe but it's kind
of like you're jumping into death
hmm
so that just doesn't seem
like a very like smart thing to do
you two want us to end up all dead man
really was right about you I knew you
were a rat now he's gone man
he's gone to prison he's not dead back
to prison he was barely out he really
got me [\h__\h] killed you set us up you
always wanted to be the one the man
you're a [\h__\h] John you're going to be
okay
yeah I think what I'm doing is more like
calm at least once I'm in the air it
will be calm
s and they've been calling him I know
because they did the same to me and they
told me you ratted us out you keep
talking like that you are dead my little
friend [\h__\h] you man what you sent Billy
to jail huh show us your phone yeah yeah
people won't be insuring my safety [\h__\h]
to you and I didn't I'll be I'll be tied
to come on a professional
hear about Billy going down there's
going to be more pressure on us than
ever
we got to get through it brother but it
just sounds difficult to like run
together with when you're tight how do
you
how do you run when you tie to someone
like that
arrested I get [\h__\h] Billy
they'll teach you everything yeah yeah
who knows maybe it'll be so much fun and
I'll do it like
more often afterwards
can we get armor again please
sorry really is your name I'm sorry you
know I mean the Billy in the game
what if I sleep uh in the safe house
for a night for six hours maybe then you
can help me
I'm missing what's with Amy's new outfit
I told you about it
you think uh no I'm not staying up for
it sadly I'll watch the archive though
I'm curious like if she is
coming up with something
original again an original way to reveal
it like she
always did
Emma finally she just went
yeah I already saw like two days ago
like a screenshot from her stream show
up on my tweets timeline
that's how I found out
that she's
having finally her new outfit reveal I'm
like girl
is this the way
the only way people are gonna know about
it for now
she could have like tweeted out two days
ago but I guess she's waiting she was
waiting for the graphic it was late for
her too
I didn't get my graphic at all I had to
commission someone
fusa okay how about now Terry
the colors are really nice right now
such an ammo way so true I need some of
your merchandise how soon can you get
here
finally yeah
yeah but immediately after I tweeted the
Japanese whole life Twitter also tweeted
it like one minute after me I'm like
okay now you're tweeting
no you're twinning
[Music]
ah Terry
but still still but I helped I helped
some people only saw it when I tweeted
it
just I'm away
yeah she's
she should promote her stuff more she's
got lots of things to be proud of and to
show off
things that she worked hard on I mean
she didn't work on the outfit but I mean
she gave instructions but I mean not
being Mama worked on it so but still
still just in general speaking in
general okay
by ammo for sale
[Music]
for some SMG ammo
uh how do I buy a
um SMG runs here
are they good they're cheap
good
Rocket 3 500 but now we could actually
um actually we could afford a rifle
really really easily now
be my balcony tomato I don't think so
I don't think I did they weren't ready
um carbine or
assault rifle
M4 is better M4
yep guys you gotta tell me what the [\h__\h]
is an M4
huh
the car but guys don't speak in riddles
to me
what the [\h__\h]
I don't understand yo
you of your professional Gun Talk
like where we just don't we it's like
we're speaking different languages
okay we're down here
not cool
we got a cool rifle we got lots of ammo
we got the armoire we're ready to go
what is happening next tsukiwa the J
for Jim Jim
good supplies yeah
let's go to gym I don't know whose gym
maybe I've been told before but I
already forgot
memory like a thief
can I tell you guys something
[Music]
in the thing that I'm doing with my
mommy I'm still speaking in riddles
chickens will be involved
[Music]
this will be involved
I'll be you guys
yes yes you you
you you'll see what I do with them
I will gain their trust and then we'll
see what happens with that trust
are you going to wear until I don't
think I can prepare little kfp uniforms
in time if only I had the plushie the
kfp plushie already at hand I could try
putting the uniform on the chickens but
I don't think they would really
agree with that I don't know how easy it
is to put clothes on a chicken
it would be cute though
maybe at least a name tag clip on one of
their feathers that would be so cute but
no
ah
I don't know if these chickens will even
like me
[Music]
okay if uniforms and post edit oh
it sounds like a lot of work
[Music]
I'm sure they will love me
I think that will be the closest I've
ever gotten to some chickens
I wonder if I can pet them
I'm gonna wash my hands very very very
thoroughly though after I pet them
don't want any of the chicken's diseases
how about using virtual virtual
wall between us it's a date Rod some
older mature [\h__\h]
hey ew who that milk you're not sick I
believe you you're taking good care of
yourself are you what's up Max
the rash got better I swear
okay don't worry about it
can't see the rash anyway because of the
fluffy feathers
write death out of business
RPG
you gotta remember this you're getting
any trouble
got that [\h__\h] man but one thing's for
sure we will have fun all right play
nice later
wow
I must have picked that up from the
Deadbeats
all right use the pipe bombs to blow up
the angel of the fans pipe bombs you
could throw a Piper from the Middleburg
okay
okay am I like already on them
I'm gonna assume yes
so the longer you hold on I'll be the
shorter the fuse AKA what like the time
it will take to
[Music]
um
for it to explode
[Music]
okay
all right where are these let me create
oh they're far
let me create a room maybe it might be
this one first I guess
okay
what are pipe bombs
this is pipes and gun powder
oh
sounds very self-made
ah
did you guys see that because I'm
watching so much like police related
videos right now did you guys see that
[\h__\h]
going on with like there's there was
this like
news report about some guy uh some some
family living in an apartment and I
noticed like
their help was the Terrio rating good
English
um
be and they didn't know they didn't know
why and they kept on checking everything
in their apartment and then later
because of a camera
they figured out it was their neighbor
poisoning them their neighbor who was
doing something sciencey yeah in
University and from there kind of
learned
how to you know do stuff with chemicals
that's so [\h__\h] up and the only reason
he did it apparently I guess oh do I
shoot oh
was because
um
how does this work
I'll do it should I go on the side of
them
[Music]
uh I understand now how it works
he only throws it to the side huh I
would have hoped he would throw it to
the front
uh wow
so yeah anyway everyone was really
[\h__\h] up that
um where's my bike no bike
your bike
that uh
basically
like eh just buy it
doing something like that studying
something like that in University you're
capable of doing something like that and
oh no no yeah he was just doing it
because of the family's baby they had a
toddler or so and
and yeah he was annoyed by the crying or
whatever I guess
yeah [\h__\h] psychopath too
if if that's what he does just by being
pissed off at the sound
of a baby crying then honestly we should
be happy that he got caught with like a
somewhat smaller crime early on of his
crime career that was surely upcoming
[\h__\h] psychopath would have probably
murdered somebody straight up at some
point
so um
but what was his end goal was he trying
to kill them slowly or was he trying to
get them to move out probably if he was
trying to get them to move out in his
own way
um
yeah
he's not attempted murder I
think he could with a lawyer he could
get out of that
assumption easily
maybe I don't know I don't know was
there an ending to it like how what he
is getting charged or so
[Music]
um
he got charged for Crime for what crime
though
oh I see the car
is now here
well he definitely got caught
question is just
for what exactly
oh yeah that's so scary like
people
just capable of doing such things
man
[Music]
uh where am I going
[\h__\h] I almost got him
[Music]
there he is okay now I go on the right
side of the car
[Music]
no
did it stick
S no it didn't stick oh
[\h__\h] it didn't stick again
but
[Music]
oh
he put back on
in the end in its own way okay okay it's
another sticky one though
okay so it wouldn't stick to the van
anyway
one down let's go to the next one
nice actually went quite well because I
got him stuck in traffic
hey hey
oh [\h__\h] my bike
uh
oh hey this place again
get off how many times do I have to
press F man
can I get a new one clay please
[Music]
are you gonna turn me down again
I'm the boss now too so
so your priorities straight or else
yeah I lost a wheel
there they are
you being so fast makes me very happy so
good job
good job good job
and take the other bike and just fix the
the wheel I guess
yeah
three kinds of battery possession of
controlled substance and aggravated
stalking
oh how much does that give you
[Music]
the time zone is low here
Maybe 10.
oh it's Typhon here
this is a good
a good topic
ah you are here depends on the specifics
of the counts okay okay
[Music]
but damn they're like so smart for
setting up a camera there
I'm catching him come on must have been
like such a shocking experience all
right hello
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
perfectly calculated all according to
cake
okay
this is already cleaned up
oh no there it is how you guys doing
that's what you get for being on the
wrong side
join the last
and the Damned now
or die
in vain
with
Nothing Left Behind
[Music]
joining all right hi you guys I already
consider you guys joined
already
let's make a new one oh cool cool cool
cool cool
he doesn't know
what's gonna happen to him
it's gonna be a nice surprise
oh is that him no
looks like one of the Vans but he's
still like where
um oh oh still there
[Music]
over here oh
to the left to the left
there it is that one's found the target
so
um not [\h__\h]
wasted
are we going left or
yeah
let me go in front of him
[Applause]
perfectly timed and everything and they
don't care anymore either huh
they're like oh that's not [\h__\h] with
this one he's he's like messed up in the
head job done what man those deadbeats
ain't a problem and you introduced me to
your new friends
oh campy biker leather jackets
that sounds cool
give Terry a clay a call if you ever
need some help on Club business
might even do them 's good to get off
their ass later on
let's have hot dog what's your guys's
favorite hot dog topping
give me one
give me let me buy it won't let me buy
because of the prompts at the top
corn chili sauerkraut
also German relish
Mayo green mate what the [\h__\h] video
only Manuel
I understand like a combo of mayo with
something else just you
okay man I'll take one
simple one with chili sauce only mustard
bacon
adding more meat on top of the meat I
see mashed potatoes ketchup eggs and
corn that sounds like it's some kind of
like uh some cities
specialty specialty hot dog
because that sounds so specific
um
blah blah blah I want to go
sorry
I
want the gunman
extra mayo onions
Style Korean style hot dog the corn uh
yeah are you talking about the Korean
dogs
because those have potatoes and stuff
maybe not I'm confused but I love the
Korean
corn dogs
um
[Music]
my hot dogs have some crunch
wait where's uh Terry going to
uh
yeah so far what the [\h__\h] ing
problem
[Music]
oh well fine I guess
corn dogs I like mustard and mayo
mixture for so like like Rissa oh
Oh I thought it was a I thought it was a
pigeon
I was wrong
[Music]
I you know my first corn dog ever I ate
in Japan because they have them in the
convenience stores at the warm counter
and they're really yummy there I love
them
apparently they're a little bit
different
from the real deal
in America
warm not worm
they don't have a worm counter
but yeah I really like them I never
tried one in America no
you know there's still so many things
that I haven't tried yet
in America
still much potential for
new foodie experiences
[Music]
sorry you you decided to park really far
away
[Music]
sorry just the usual thanks just ship it
to me at this point
daily delivery please
yeah yeah shut up
um
Mexican food
I feel like I dreamed of Mexican food
huh whoa what was that
[\h__\h]
[Music]
I would not mind eating more the one the
few Mexican foods I had so far were
quite good I mean the
that weird brown stuff I had was
unnecessary but at least I tried
something new
that's no no that was before summer yeah
that was
maybe not necessary let's go to the gym
no maybe that'll be my last mission and
then I'll try to read a few super chats
[Music]
um
they're based on corn yeah yeah yeah
I've noticed
oh I've been here before too
oh yeah I remember this
ah it's like a nostalgic ride through
the city again
[Music]
mm-hmm
oh that that is um scenery in the
background looks nice
I said sorry I missed my
turn I was fascinated
New York looking a little bit better
right now than usual
wow no yeah
[Music]
oh by the way for the Minecraft collab
we've never saw
um
I'm gonna give her an En server too yeah
private es server tour because I asked
them what are you girls planning on
doing if you're checking out the en
server then maybe it's not worth it but
if you're just checking out the the new
server thingy
then maybe
I could do what foreign
they are not sure about what they're
doing anyway
but they might be building like a house
together
so there's room for showing nerissa
around separately of course afterwards
in our own stream
so that's what we'll be doing I'll show
her the history
in person
man gentlemen Johnny yeah hey what's
your plan I'll show her Phoenix welcome
to that fat [\h__\h] Brian he wants to sit
down I'll tell her I can only use
Phoenix then nothing else
[\h__\h] that let's go get us what I thought
you'd say let's do it
aren't we better off without Billy I
feel like it's way less toxic about him
the atmosphere oh wait I'm leading yeah
true
I'm leading let's go
now we just gotta get rid of Brian
[Music]
show her the legendary hole yes
yes kind of whole I don't know
not the whole that these guys keep on
talking about
Minecraft oh
the mysterious hole sorry guys that was
me going
a little too wild
do you remember where it was I will
never forget
where the hole is
at least roughly
[Music]
tough none of us do James don't worry
about that thank you
thank you
I remember fondly
I don't remember fondly but I remember
angrily aggressively
remember aggressively
just like how I like to sleep
aggressively
ah where is Brian
[Music]
yeah you think Billy would stick his
neck out for you you're dumber than I
thought
I knew you'd say that you're so pathetic
foreign
what a baby and your babysitter Billy's
on the inside now they're with me I'm
also calling them baby all the time now
they're with me
oh [\h__\h] it's going down
we're breaking up our own gang
yummy
also have little to no Minecraft
exposure oh really did they say that
you guys should be driving in circles
it's very predictable
well I gotta reload though all right
don't be in my way
nice job
on you Brian
oh man
ooh Mommy
and does Chihuahua said [\h__\h] it and when
it went right into it
the physics were just like that one game
wow kiwaba as vague as ever wow it's
gone is there another one oh that might
have hurt my own
you good
oh okay
nice
yeah that one game
that's one game
let's go
[Music]
what a fun gang outing uh what wow
oh
I'm running around so freely and I still
lost barely anything in terms of HP yo
I don't want to hit my my bodies can we
be more careful about that
again
was this big you guys
don't know
I love that in this game it gives me so
many opportunities to blow up gas tanks
bricks get away inside they wear a
tongue oh really
inside where the gang house I was in
there were sometimes
they're getting smaller by the section
you know oh there's even more Ryan's
faction yeah
[Music]
well I'll be dancing goodbye
damn
go to gym okay
yippee
this is I guess the disadvantage with a
bike when you get shot you're just like
immediately taking taking down from the
bike way less safe than where's Jim wait
then a car
where you when the car protects you a
little bit and you just generally
not as easy to
not not as easy and a Target wow
but look at me
not being shot down a single time
[Music]
yeah a car is a kind of armor
this time baby this time baby I will be
[Music]
oh he's like going even he doesn't want
to see me it seems like it
come baby
[Music]
car more wow
what don't say anything like it's only
us two
and that's what we got left there's
still some right
[Music]
one two three four five
oh [\h__\h] I wish we pinned down Brian can
we even call that a gang still
so many of them turned against us what
how was Brian so popular
oh well so
I'm still the leader
this is my place y'all better have
respect for me
you do right
bikers are shady they follow the Monies
ridiculous especially since Brian is
terrible yeah like
[Music]
what did he do to make them all
follow his
idea
how's the DLC so far so good like I've
been having fun
um
I think I've also I've been able to
follow
the story quite well a little bit better
than the main game honestly
I don't know why
[Music]
um
but yeah we'll end here unfortunately
because
um we could in theory if I didn't have
something to do tomorrow where I had to
get up early we could finish it but
I am
I want to be somewhat energetic tomorrow
so we'll don't we won't go too long I
will read a little bit of super chattos
so
the other
thanks for streaming thank you for
watching
for watch it's fun yeah DLC d-o-c-d-o-c
I'll see more DLC soon soon
and Gay Tony as well one when next time
we're probably gonna have both in one
stream somehow my things aren't not
working like something's wrong here
once I close the game
I can't click on anything in my bottom
Windows bar
I I can't
um this is weird I can't
I can't open
my uh chat Windows plus what I only see
you in obs
Windows plus one went faster way I'm
pressing it it doesn't help
I can't click on anything down there
I broke it
maybe I'll try task manager to open some
stuff yeah now it works
and GTA once again trying to manipulate
my fun
in my
experience
sassy
okay let's go
I should use this a bit more before
summer ends
[Music]
hello ah it's not working
huh I what the [\h__\h]
hey my keyboard
my number three wasn't working anymore
what's going on I'm being haunted
I was joking out now maybe now
it fits
[Music]
welcome to the membership thank you
okay
if it fits chicken sits
[Music]
blah
bam
[Music]
that's what I had to think of when I
read the title that I gave to this track
they called it
[Music]
looks cute
okay I'm gonna quickly read the like six
Super chats that came in during the
album teaser reveal
uh Studio wrap thanks for the pinky
is
[Music]
Papa
it's so cute
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] Patsy duncast
for the pinky
congrats on the new album
and today is my one year since the
beginning
I thought you were in here longer it's
an honor to know you and you know be
happy and healthy and thank you for your
stream as always
but I forgot the thumbnail yeah okay
okay uh which one is this Sports okay
thank you renad for being a member for
one year feels like you're here for
longer down thank you for the support
and you better stay healthy and happy
too
thank you so much for celebrating all
the accomplishments recently thank you
Jake's the best album thank you for the
recipe wow
I feel bad for asking but my dream
is to hear death metal
what does that mean from you can I hear
it before the album realigns thank you
love you
what is the bellag is that um
is that just the scream
what am I supposed to understand from
this
I don't know how am I supposed to should
I do it to this song
[Music]
foreign
just want me to suffer what the [\h__\h]
weaker than the average gaming kiosk
well I'm trying to follow a melody
screamo when you can have just cute
[Music]
this is so much better
another Pinky
I had three days before I left Austria I
visited Vienna and tried some desserts
and Brad mentioned in Tangent stream oh
which ones basically I didn't enjoy
dessert so much but it was a good
experience excuse me
by the way I didn't go to Innsbruck so
don't worry well thank God
at least one good thing
we didn't enjoy the desserts
but did you eat them in the right places
don't write them off completely yet
please
because maybe you ate it in the wrong
place it could be better elsewhere
[Music]
no I would be much happier if you
enjoyed them because I'm quite proud of
our desserts okay we don't have much to
show off
[Music]
um
don't say that Lord ever give little
[\h__\h]
foreign
[Music]
you think you were the best chefs in all
of Europe man
[Music]
freaking Italians with their huge huge
cooking egos
man
we at least do good desserts okay and a
good schnitzel okay
um
what happened
well a lot okay emotional damage
emotional damage
if he doesn't like desserts in general I
don't care I don't accept that excuse
thank you renat for two pinkies
I'm glad you uh hopefully at least
enjoyed your stay in general
ah man
we love them over here what
Austrian desserts you mean
huh so on whose side
[Music]
it's okay tciano I was just joking but I
mean it might be partially true
I can imagine a lot of Italians maybe
thinking their food is the best in
Europe or in the world having quite some
pride on their culinary
expertise and influence on the world
with their I mean you know they
definitely had
you know they you know you know they
have a good a good what's the word a
good reputation in terms of food
yeah yeah I believe that
which Austin desserts do I recommend
noodle with poison
um
foreign
[Music]
you know
vanilla sauce
[Music]
with vanilla so we have so many desserts
that you're supposed to eat with hot
vanilla sauce
[Music]
oh yes
spelled those before for you you should
know by now don't make me type it out
again
um
[Music]
good morning to you how early is it
must be really early like 5 a.m or so
did you see the news about cover hiring
people for Korea yeah but I feel like
they did that for other countries before
too and it didn't really mean much I
don't know
who knows what that means
um 8 AM oh I guess wait because they're
even further behind than for the far for
ahead than Japan so uh
yeah okay okay I was thinking backwards
for some reason
yeah it could be even marketing related
you know because we do quite a few
collabs like with Korean cafes and stuff
[Music]
so it could just be to help out with
that part
but who knows who knows
[Music]
swings of the pinky
congratulations on the album Kiana
pre-ordered it and looking forward to
your MV thank you I hope everybody here
pre-ordered it did you guys pre-order my
album because
it's only a limited time available and
it's gonna be a very special thing yes
yes yes thank you I love you guys I will
soon okay okay try to do it before the
the time is up um yeah I saw some of you
ordered more than one thank you so much
honestly uh you might
hmm I think that's a good choice because
maybe in the future somebody will you
know join kfb and they're like oh I
missed I'm So Into Kiana now but I
missed her album physical release oh no
that's too bad and then you can be like
hey I got like five of them do you want
one I can sell you one at the same price
of when I bought it
you know
no not five times depressed no same
price same price
hmm
not the Green Market no no also not
Black Market nothing just orange market
just sell those oranges
to people who just joined the fandom a
new
[Music]
don't scalp my scalp wants to stay the
way it is right now my scalp feels very
very
hydrated and
admired and cherished and treasured
let's keep my scalp safe and everybody
else's scalp I don't want to be sculpt
okay
[Music]
doused in gravy yes
gravy gravy feeling good
[Music]
I did want to take a shower though I
think after this
endless love you thank you Judy Duncan
vlk.com
Jake's the best ever again thank you for
the red super chat you deserve this oh
is this uh
did I oh I must have given did I in this
stream give you guys the Sparks preview
the Sparks remix review
because then I think I understand why
you sent this
question for the support mwah
oh that was at the karaoke not this one
okay
well well well then at this point you
were happy about just
General
the album upcoming
or the idea of a Sparks metal remix
[Music]
thank you for the pinky Emma wake album
is
that thank you I'm happy Tim Keen so
proud of you Kiana and I'm so excited
for the album your honesty humor and
passion are what stuck me in this whole
life rabbit hole and I'm forever
thankful for you and all the hard work
you do
you wow me
it was me
wow thank you that's so weird like three
years ago we just joined
and I was saying that about like pequoda
senpai
but now there's honestly people who say
it about me which I totally understand
when people say it about Cali for
example because uh you know she did get
a lot of people in through the
Trash Talk podcast for example and gura
just generally you know picks up a lot
of people from outside
um I don't think I have that much reach
to bring in new people but yeah whenever
it does happen I'm very glad very proud
and what did I say they're not trash
talk
just
[Music]
I got it wrong well they're talking and
trash was in there
so maybe sometimes they are trash
talking
close enough
oopsie sorry brain horns
ah
foreign
I'm seeing them this Saturday oh
at some convention
enjoy have fun
you deserve to feel that I'm proud thank
you
[Music]
they Trash Talk each other that's fun I
like when friends are able to Trash Talk
each other that means you're really good
friends
[Music]
you made me fall into the room
thank you
hey
I'm glad I could seal the deal with you
[Music]
could have said you and AMA the only one
she can Trash Talk seriously with really
oh oh I appreciate that we should ah
there then there is potential for us to
do like a roast
oh
oh maybe that's what we should oh
oh wait
we are currently I don't know if anybody
said anything about I think Cali said
this we're all doing our individual
um anniversary streams I think
but we're also doing
um perhaps uh five collapse
um together uh on each Channel
um and I was like thinking what what
what do I do for mine what if I organize
a roast for our collab on my channel
hahaha
yeah five full mythical Labs basically
like a marathon mm-hmm
[Music]
back to back
that doesn't sound like fun what I love
roasts but just gotta be careful that
nobody gets really hurt
um
I'll keep it as one idea
[Music]
five collabs sounds Overkill well and
you sound like a buzz kill man
celebrating
[Music]
it's not like it's uh like every collab
five hours they're short ones
[Music]
roast him too yeah I'm already starting
the roast I didn't plan on having you
guys be the roasted ones but here we are
[Music]
I'm still thinking but uh
yeah cause the problem is like so many
collab games are four people and we're
trying to do like five different things
you know
um
and for garlic phone for example I think
we're too few like five is kind of yeah
for garlic food
I don't know ah chicken run too I didn't
see the trailer yet but I saw that it's
coming out in December let's go and even
on Netflix right
[Music]
it will be our Christmas movie guys
it will be on the 15th December I think
[Music]
let's watch it together as a Christmas
movie yeah Family Feud
[Music]
I don't know if we can play that one is
it oh
only some Ninja sounds you play that one
two versus two of you as a host
it's a try
[Music]
but try
um
was that Ubisoft family huge
will be soft
[Music]
it is
okay I'll look into it
um
yeah I did my own version with Cali for
the Advent calendar
um
but it's kind of fun with that game like
when I watched him play it
the the scuffedness of it was fun to
look at
[Music]
it it's it's
more interesting with those
models
and when they both stand at the at the
buzzer and all that the visuals are just
fun
[Music]
making your own questions and asking
whole life talents as the hundred people
would be fun would be fun or I ask you
know the audience maybe I could set up
like a
like a form for you guys
some polls some Google Google polls or
whatever
uh yeah
I I could I'll see if I can play the
game first
[Music]
um
life during the game that I don't know
about that maybe better to do beforehand
uh
thanks for pre-ordering
[Music]
oh the pineapple MB teaser has like two
Vivica and Patsy
uh let's do pineapple MV quickly
[Music]
um
thanks
for the album pinky Super Chat thank you
Sir
with a pinky so many pineapples
pineapples go it was skipping in for now
thank you Studio Rob thank you
thanks for Pinky this is the best
birthday present ever Viva La Canada oh
oh good timing for me to bring out the
Envy huh
happy belated birthday
hope you had a lovely birthday please
take care of yourself and thank you so
much for supporting me all the time I
wish you all the best much love
from me to you happy birthday I'm a team
Reuben or Raven thank you thank you
Tracy dungeon and Evans out thanks for
the pinky keep up the hard work
thank you I saw that tweet from you and
the others on my timeline that was funny
about
saying how much you love me freely
my chickens are so cute
[Music]
okay I'll do you one more
one
[Music]
that art is cool right this is
see not really in this outfit she I knew
she liked it a lot the first time she
saw it she already like was so into it
yeah
and then and then she drew me and I
didn't think like I was watching the
beginning I did not expect her to finish
it in one go
but she used her the technique where she
doesn't have to do outlines when she
just draws on top of her sketch so she
finished it in one go it looks so good
do you guys want to see anybody who
hasn't seen it I can show you you can
even go to her Twitter or
[Music]
it's so sweet it's been a while since
she drew me like so seriously so I was
really excited I was so pumped oh look
at this
even the gray background which is just
like some messy Strokes even that looks
so good
the hair looks good
the Flop the the side flaps they look
like elf ears to me from a distance
the blue line is so pretty look at this
look at this look at my Claymore
[Music]
wow so looks like this it's the perfect
size for my phone as a phone screen
thingy image but
you guys you guys use it I don't want to
use it because you know I don't want
people to look at my phone and then be
like
so
it's good chance
[Music]
sword could be a bit bigger still
but so cool like damn I like the setting
that she put me into as well
[Music]
really like
mystical Magical
fantasy-ish World
well I love the light that's coming from
below that's perfectly lighting up my
panties that you can't see
it's so cool down
every time I watch her draw I feel like
I want to draw two
um I think you call that inspiration
[Music]
yeah
chicken with the blue flashlight
underneath
yeah I watched her draw it I watched
like I was watching One Piece in like in
between
when I was gone for like 20 minutes or
so from her chat and then I looked back
and then oh my God she made so much
progress and then I go away for 20
minutes and I look back and oh my gosh
it was done
[Music]
thank you so much always for the big
support and that code sends two pinkies
that gives you a PC unless you're giving
it to someone else no not this time it
seems
cases for you then that could love your
album boss tgw and pineapple on my face
pineapple Justice for pineapple but
they're all great songs you should have
called the album bangers yeah maybe next
time I will
if you're going to turn this into
another POV kind of looking boss I
insist on paying for the ticket
oh no not this one I guess why
why why
maybe another time and I want to sing my
songs more
[Music]
now you know remember when I told you I
had like everything like my order of
songs I had like a set list for my
birthday uh 3D if it was gonna be in
summer and I had like guests that I
wanted to call
this and that and
it was gonna be before my album now that
it's so much after my album I feel like
it's it's messing with my plans
completely because in one way I feel
obligated and also I want to
perform all my new songs
um
but
I also don't want to throw a board on my
plans that I had well maybe maybe maybe
if I get the like an anniversary 3D life
like soon after then I could like
you know split it up like that but who
knows if I'm even getting that I would
like to know
about it
[Music]
oh there's a cat walking into my room
s
[Music]
let me ask
um
[Music]
you've delayed by 3D life let's just do
it solo live next year instead of a 3D
and we'll call it even
I want it all I don't wanna like give up
on anything I want everything that I'm
supposed to be getting
um
I don't want to sacrifice anything
I want at all
[Music]
I want some you sound well I'm supposed
to be getting hmm
can you blame me I'm like I'm I really
want to perform
I really want to perform that's my
problem I have so many songs I want to
show off I have so many collabs like in
like copy songs that I want to collab
and show off with others this and that
you know
[Music]
um
you know get me what I want
hopefully they got enough staff to be up
and running at full capacity soon I hope
so too I mean
oh I'm very worried with
you know five new members that are
focused on music apparently joining uh
um but yeah
[Music]
foreign
wasn't so nice but the day was fine
wow wow wow uh try my regular hours
[Music]
foreign
I can't speak English but I like your
voice so I uh subscribe do your best
must be a drug
must must be a joke
must be a jerk
great back thank you thank you soon
shoes
[Music]
um
don't feel insulted but I'm not paying
full attention to the gameplay
[Music]
ah you want to play it too so you're
being willful healing or ignorant okay
no problem
I'm taking my time with everything
though so
I think my streams are still not a big
spoiler
I'm just doing Side Stories
[Music]
I have one Joke Man thank you
in retrospect ah this one in
retrospective love brushing down that
Chasm was a real heart challenger but
now the great one the Chihuahua is sleep
talking to some demons like a fever
Night Dream
[Music]
about
need a
still drink after all this
is this like actually referencing
something I did or
oh yeah you are indeed missing hinotori
what's up with that
but nice implementation
you jump down the hole and maybe the
mushrooms
um
Maybe
good try
did you forget you know Tony
[Music]
maybe just adding kiwawa to it is enough
to say Hino Tony because I am the
hinotori after all and Kim is a synonym
for a hinotori maybe
wow big brain oh I'm helping you out
here
don't yawn then I have to yawn again
makes sense right
palette five
thank you for the pinky Hello Kitty
foreign
[Music]
um
thank you for the red super chat always
a great time hanging out watching with
my kitties the Pro Gamer of hollow Ian
and her kitties voice acting another 10.
thank you oh wait we're starting in
Baldur's game was I voice acting
because like the characters were
actually all voiced on their own
[Music]
ah reading the books oh
yeah I've been having surprisingly much
fun
reading the books yeah
[Music]
no no thank you thanking him glad you're
enjoying it
second time did you see Pepito on
Twitter I recommend follow Pepito
recently I I found the cat Twitter
that has like a security cam yeah happy
birthday Pepito
and they have of this 16 I was surprised
so old 16 year old black cat and all
they do on their Twitter is update about
him coming home through this little cat
door that's like quite up high uh on the
shelf and and coming home and leaving
home
yeah I might have been liking them all
the time when I see them recently so you
guys may have seen them
and and that's all that they do and then
everybody in the comment section of
those tweets is always like oh my God
and when he's gone for too long they're
like oh my God
I love the commons
um
and they they post all those memes when
whenever Pepito comes home they all post
those memes like you know like like
those like those fangirling memes like
you know all those kind of pictures like
oh my God
oh
and it's so cute everybody's memeing and
exaggerating their reactions to a random
black cat coming home and leaving home
[Music]
and somehow I felt like I needed to
follow Pepito
he's just like such a normal cat but
somehow
[Music]
the name is so funny too Pepito
and sometimes he's gone for quite long
honestly surprising as a cat that goes
outside like every day
um that was 16 years
he's like still a limo alive like I feel
like with outside cats
I'm so worried that something will
happen to them because I hear so often
about cats leaving and not coming back
because something happened to them
yeah especially for an outdoor cat wow
survived for so long is that's impressed
if Pepito is built different
gotta be careful Pepito
16 years holy [\h__\h] that's even for an
indoor cat a long life
what you know hey one of your cats was
outdoor cat
[\h__\h]
some cats just
just don't want to die damn I hope mine
live long
25 years is crazy
[Music]
I did oh mine made it to 21. wow
that keeps me hold
[Music]
the cat that's 13 and never to live past
18 years
17. yeah but they're definitely already
considered old by that age I think
they're already like Grandpa Grandpa
Grandma age right when they're around
that age
oh
yeah
I I want to keep my cats healthy as long
as possible
oh thank you spanking him what that cool
thanks for the recipe chant hey boss
it's our devoted chefs General's
birthday today oh can you sing the
birthday song again in his shoe maybe in
his pants too thank you love you
all right all right all right wait wait
wait is he here to witness it
[Music]
what should I say can I think of any
rhymes
I'll do my best don't get your hopes up
happy
birthday
happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you happy birthday
happy birthday in your shoe happy
birthday happy birthday in your pants
too happy
[Music]
you used to be cold
a completely different name
what was it I can't remember was it
General yeah holy totally happy birthday
to you happy birthday happy birthday in
your shoe have a birthday
friend so I remember I know what it was
I'm just acting
you to be cooking
while you do be looking
[Music]
happy birthday to you
happy birthday in your shoe happy
birthday in your pants to have it both
birthday General wow extinct and every
day
you think of the wild one
what is she cooking today
I hope she's doing well thank you
[Music]
shine happy birthday happy birthday
yeah you're always paying so much
attention to what I'm cooking
I think like every every day like oh oh
will she upload Wawa wama's kitchen
what is she cooking what is she cooking
let her cook
yeah our passionate chef
sous chef
you're welcome congratulations on your
birthday that was when
when was this
how many days ago is this
I don't know
[Music]
a couple days ago not too late am I not
too late
and by the week ago
oh so what did you eat on your birthday
did you cook something for yourself or
did you treat yourself to someone else's
cooking
I think sometimes even if you love
cooking it's nice to treat yourself to
someone else's cooking right
sometimes nice to just let someone else
do it
went to a Barcade what the [\h__\h] is that
a Bar Arcade Maybe
a mix a hybrid of a bar and an arcade
gotta take off early no oh no
no oh that sounds fun home yeah I would
I will take the arcade solo please thank
you
anyway congratulations
[Music]
already that little [\h__\h]
okay I'll be quick
foreign
oh well that's kind of late you look
great you look like a character in a
tails off game hahaha what a coincidence
would it be called House of kfb tells of
chicken oh I remember the super chat now
because of the usual room we love to
play a game like that
I I don't want the game to be about me
but I would be super happy if I could
like voice act through character no
trolls of game in English or so maybe
one day that would be cool I don't know
maybe I got a poke band dynamical a bit
more about it I'll say I'll do it for
five bucks
can't offer myself a free I'll just say
it I'll do it for about it for five
bucks that's it
Queens
won't be so cool
I'm actually surprised that we don't get
like more like real voice acting offers
because so many all live English even
only even only considering home life
English talents have great voices for
voice acting and I don't know
I don't know why we don't get considered
for it
I think it would be good because we also
have a good fan base that promises
exposure
um
I honestly thought we would get like you
know jobs like that like
quite simply but no
yeah yeah I'm guessing they're just like
really uh includes exclusive exclusive
including exclusive Maybe
your company very hard to contact yeah
but like all these gaming companies are
able to contact us for sponsorships and
I don't think that anime companies would
have such troubles
um maybe I'll I'll
just got a appeal to them somehow I
don't know
I don't know I don't even know if I
would do it be would if I would be able
to do it well uh probably not because I
mean a certain amount of training is
probably helpful
still I would do my best if I could do
one
gave rules for joining the big strike
strike going on right now uh-huh okay
so if I don't strike
can I get a job
[Music]
what is that what you call a scab
okay I'm not getting into it anyway I'm
not getting any drums on your mind like
anyone's considering me
[Music]
this is
if you're not joining people's strike
you're like
automatically a bad person
is
that's right I mean okay
oh Hot Topic oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
okay
wait so what if I start a strike then
everybody has to join me if I started
striking whole life and they don't throw
me their their scabs
foreign
[Music]
oh only if I get the majority
with me
um
well I'm too lazy
[Music]
all these chickens yeah I don't want you
guys to get some crazy idea about your
rights either so
yeah let's move on
everybody is happy with how things are
aren't we aren't we
yes we are
um
super snake Mario
again thank you oh thank you
oh oh it's not a person playing with
words how can I wanted to tell you how
amazing you are and I love hearing your
point of view on subjects as I often
find I agree with you on things
fossil person who is sweeter than
pineapple
I feel a love rush for me when I seen
you before finding you I also felt alone
and as the great wonder that I am I
would jump from place to place but
eventually I found a home here with you
with kfp as I make a retrospective of
what I've seen you do I feel so proud
knowing how far you've come and I'm glad
you'll be I could be here to see you
girls I admit I haven't always been
around to do streams happening while
what
what a stretch this one's a stretch
because there's a period in between I
admit I haven't always been around to do
streams to do two streams happening
while I sleep period talking with you is
always a pleasure
and I'm happy when I can be here also
stream point of view I love you
[Music]
yeah you were doing so well what
happened
I only have a song called sleep and a
song called talking I have a song called
sleep talking
uh you could have written something
about like you love me so much that you
think about me even when you're dreaming
and you think you're probably sleep
talking in the night about me
or something like that
or that watching my streams while you
fall asleep makes you start sleep
talking to me
[Music]
not enough word counts
sleep twerking sleep twerking
sleep twerking
anyway thank you
message I like everything you came up
with except for sleep talking
no good one thank you
dominique.com
a wax eagle eyes
[Music]
tiny Chef had appreciated Cruise that's
you oh what happened
thank you
okay
I will go
you guys are free shift is over for
today earlier than um so be happy
you're lucky
you're lucky lucky chickens don't get
used to it
[Music]
um
thank you for watching today have a
blast
[Music]
quite vengeful and violent something
good aim
good kills
good Tony store
good good roasts
oh
oh you're still at your real work oh man
that's like
depressing fighter
you can do it
good morning also and good night
thank you for the memberships oh thank
you thank you
all right
I'll be back for the Minecraft collab
with noisa
and the day after tomorrow I'll keep you
updated if I
um
survived what I'm doing tomorrow
okay
[Music]
I am going to make lasagna
Young
[Music]
you know what we'll go to we'll go to
um
first album
point of view
[Music]
do me a favor and stream pineapple after
three minutes okay just go through the
Envy
once maybe don't tap out while you're
watching it thank you love you
down
to me
one one of the usual room you are being
such a little [\h__\h] these days
love Rush
[Music]
such a brat you're a brat I'm telling
you
you're so lucky that I am like
accepting you as the bratty bread you
are
and letting it go so many times
[Music]
the great Wanderer
just be truthful about your love to me
don't hide it be honest to yourself
[Music]
[Applause]
talking breath
[Music]
Ori
no you tell me
[Music]
to sing retrospective in the shower man
thank you
[Music]
Sparks
baby baby
[Music]
good night guys