foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
server because I was spawned there from
the last time I was there I spawned in
the in the New Year's fireworks area
which means the last time I logged in
here properly was for New Year's which
is almost a year ago
a little bit and then I I had my lighter
so I was trying to fly towards the the
you know the gate to go back to the
answer but I couldn't find it and um and
finally was trying to help me find it
through watching my screen but then my
highlights were um broke it broke for
the goal and crashed yeah like crashed
you crashed into the bamboo Thicket and
I just died right there was a too high
fall I guess and yeah now now fana
picked it up right yes I got all your
stuff except for a melon slice I can't
carry it so I'm no problem you have to
say goodbye to a melon slice
it's not the problem that I still can't
find you because I don't know where now
I am and I need food oh my god there
must be food here right
um
do you know your coordinates I'm at uh
the like a festival place right now wait
isn't this a fireworks place it's uh
five
I swear
huh sorry what was the what are the
coordinates uh 85 and 85 x uh and uh Zed
is 189 so 200.
positive positive positive okay
ah there must be food there is food
some food I take this is all abandoned
anyway
no no no no no no no no no
no no no good Adventure is starting off
strong
we've had our first step and we haven't
even gone to another yet
well there will be no more devs after
that okay I'm at the festival ground
where are you hello
here let me give you oh yeah I even had
a totem with me and stuff oh I had a
toilet with me but I didn't have it in
my hand I'm glad I didn't waste it
what do you mean waste
wouldn't want to waste it for a stupid
death on the Japan server by breaking my
Electro
well they wouldn't have done there's
like we can have infinite
[Music]
oh did you make a farm or something yeah
you'll have to check
I'm like nobody who logs in I had the
same problem like last year still
um I last year also people were already
stopping to play really
um
[Music]
yeah thank you thank you thank you I had
always stuck with me wow wow did I
really have all this stuff with me I
don't know I'm
did I have the oh well thank you for the
diamonds I surely had those with me
you might have are you good at gambling
are you lucky
no but also I've never seen hot wings uh
my my lights were broken before oh yeah
well I have a farm that you can use to
fix it I can show you ah can you show me
the world oh that actually I think that
unenchanted shovel was mine if I could
have that one back
shovel and I thank you so much so
fireworks from me oh yes
I'm also low on fireworks but we won't
be able to fly back anyway no this is
yours too I think one of your I think
your lovely members
all right so oh yeah what we're gonna do
today is prepare for the litter we're
gonna shoot some skeletons right yeah
get some heads yes but but not the ones
on my thumbnail apparently I thought
that you have to get three normal
skeleton heads and then put some coal on
them and then they become black with
their heads no black or skeleton heads
that would be clever it's just because I
was Googling
um like skeleton heads on Google for a
PNG and then I saw one which was like a
recipe like they were making it uh
probably someone's custom yeah maybe
that's perfect I guess that was fake I
guess you don't know that I thought
because of that I thought you put one
skeleton and you need four coal and then
it turns in Black
I feel like it's it's hard to get a
skeleton skull though isn't it
apparently I don't have to like kill it
with a Charged Creeper explosion or
something what
I thought you just have a regular
skeleton
a wreck the regular
[Music]
yeah I think it's actually easier to get
the Wither skulls oh really oh was that
when we went with the regular River
skulls we can just shoot or or punch or
whatever yeah do you have a a good sword
oh
really you just need looting three
little thing free oh I have to check in
my chest at home
maybe if you don't have it though I can
I can get you set up
for free right of course of course
oh there's an Enderman stuff up there
how did they do that
enclosed in glass
it's like a zoo yeah have you seen oh we
were talking earlier about the ID server
Kiara hasn't been yet I have no videos I
guess I was kind of waiting for an
opportunity for a tour
um and then back then when people were
doing that mostly
happen you know I didn't go yet but I I
know it's very very very very stunning
I'm sure anyone would love to give you a
tour Kobo has a zoo in the ID server
mm-hmm it's probably much better than
the zoo that we have I think it might
have been taking us the wrong direction
this wait is it this way
[Music]
why is there so many chests
the stuff is done
damn all the treasure on here
[Music]
I left all my fish at home
I mean in the real game right
in the real life that is Minecraft
okay I have some fish here but I'm not
gonna give it to them
[Music]
I'll give some wait I shouldn't should I
these ones are already pets so these are
someone's someone's pet cats
tormenting like this
it might be hungry
where are you going
I fell
are you looking at the coordinates
um
yes
I think it's this way
okay
it's your dream to make the en server
look like this no
[Music]
I was hoping for it to at least like be
a smaller version of this in the
beginning
and then you know one by one the most
girls didn't play so much anymore then
cancel drawing with a new console yeah
also also didn't play for so long I feel
like yeah and then Ross came along
everyone was playing runs
playing a little bit though on the Ian
server
some members crony and Bae mume and me
have been playing
Minecraft
when when
she played last week
oh gosh I'm
streaming yeah
what
I completely missed that
what you got a whole group together
yes if you ever want to play just let me
know I can always make time for
Minecraft we could play earlier too at
least I can wait and I forgot to write
my starting tweet oh okay I'll protect
you in case there's any monsters
I think we have begun already a long
time ago why are you not here yet
question mark
um you already missed the best part no
no not the best part is yes get to
happen
hi yo coin action
what are you were asking me
for the Stream
you want what are you what were you
eating what were you eating
the reason why I didn't want to tell you
is because I wanted to say it out loud
here I was eating
basically a chicken salad
oh what is the chicken salad to you
um in this case it was a in Austria we
say but candles a lot
which is
um potato salad
with of basically like a baked fried
chicken
fillet oh
um it's very special and then they also
make it with uh they add like sunflower
uh sunflower pumpkin pumpkin
sweet pumpkin seed oil pumpkin seed oil
what am I saying
and uh I just wanted to say that because
I've heard people call us um chicken
salad before Oh
you were actually eating
eating it eating the chicken salad for
the occasion yeah
all I see
[Music]
oh I think you're welcome oh yes yes
then I smile when this is the bamboo you
died in I think this one over there
that's so you were so close to the
portal and then you died it all closed
down
I was curious because then
in America chicken salad is something
weird
oh I guess like like wrecked chicken
made into a salad it's like do you know
tuna salad like tuna salad sandwich oh
that was the Portland I was like why did
she go yeah yeah
it's been a while yeah it's like that
but it's like chicken with mayo
We're stopped into a paste and then put
on bread
ew ew that's weird like a sandwich like
a chicken salad sandwich but definitely
very different from what I was thinking
I mean there's also like a chicken salad
like a salad with chicken on it but like
I feel like when people say chicken
salad a lot of the times they're
referring to like a chicken salad
sandwich
well we need to try the Austrian one
someday
with the soy chicken
will you make it at kfp
you can I guess you can have the chicken
salad about the chicken
[Music]
fun
no oh
anyway we are on here
yes
if you want to do you have um a sword
on my my home and see what swords I have
it already then I just take it from you
um I don't okay okay what you could
borrow but it's probably better if you
have one you can keep right
[Music]
oh
okay so okay so
do you why is this what what what what
the what what where are you going
to have the same problem but it's been
like this for like a year I feel like
what is this
oh thank God I stopped I think
okay uh you'll want to go the other way
if you want to go to your house bring us
asleep
it was extended
it's a whole Loop there was construction
and everything look to like
yeah connects from Council to myth to
PPP and all the way back
what when did that happen
um
last year
oh last year
there's so many freaking carts oh no are
in there yeah I'll give you a push
okay I broke one
I think this might have been movements
doing
on the other side there were also a
bunch of cards that's why I stopped I
was able to stop thanks to them
apparently it was like six months ago it
feels like a year ago
that's just half a year ago
well well I was surprised by that
see I don't know I don't think the
answer needs to become like the JP
server I think the en server can be its
own thing with its own charms
okay we can always improve though
oops
okay
[Music]
here I'm just gonna oh wait was there an
actual
one for the cards a little box for the
form it's probably this okay there's all
kinds of other stuff in here too
yeah okay
um would you like to
you know have some tea at my place
yes all right well there might be
something waiting for you there
you broke into my home like wow inside
let's say your cats let me in
them with some treats hmm
wait is this why I left your
oh oh do you have their house you mean
probably the other house oh my my new
house that I don't use that's not new
anymore either on the bottom floor
oh
[\h__\h] you Mama thanks for everything what
is what's everything what did I do for
you
Kara you've done so much for me
as my Senpai you've helped me out you've
inspired me yes
with whatever inspired you yeah
well for one when I got to watch you I
will dance for like 14 hours in one day
oh that was really inspiring I think
that was more like torture but good for
you
oh oh wow
are you flick this is just a flex you're
just flexing on me
oh this is my bride for everyone to try
to get everyone to play more Minecraft
wow and the enchanted book is efficiency
damn girl
yeah I mean about the totems though
don't you shouldn't you should use them
wait so how easy can you get them now uh
quite easy for my Farm's broken right
now because I need to fix it but
okay but when it's working it's very
easy
oh you said you need we need what on the
on the on the uh looting three
I don't think I have that right now do
you have a diamond sword
yes I have diamond swords well we can
put to looting three on on your sword
wait wasn't there a maximum on things
you can put on there
um there is are your swords
did you enchant them a lot
yeah one of them has four things but
another one only has three things so we
might be able to put it on there did you
add the enchantments with books or did
it come with the enchantments oh these
are with books okay those might be too
expensive but oh
oh should I take one where nothing else
is on
um
let me see
oh you can do this um
thinking about that one yeah that should
be good that one has good enchantments
on it too yeah yeah I know I know
although I'm kind of scared I got for
working for a second and really not
doing much though okay she never told
him if it's too sentimental though we
can make you a new sword because there's
a chance that we'll die in the nether
I guess we don't we also don't have to
mend my hot wings because we're not
needing them in the Never
show you how to mend it though I can
show you my farm because it's very
efficient
anything else I need
um
we could bring fire resistance potions
but I don't know
do you know where the nether fortress is
I think I've been there before but it's
been so long
yeah I also don't know
with the help of Chad we will definitely
find it yeah I I will just have to
remember are you bringing your totems
like one or so yeah probably
okay because if we fall in lava it's
like it might not do that much well we
could
just have to be like somewhere inside
all right I'll bring like two photos and
I shall be the show me the hot wings
place
yes we can pick the rail there too oh
okay
we could probably make fire resistance
potions at Ina's house
that way if we fall in lava we can like
drink one really fast and then
hopefully we'll be okay
you think it will be so dangerous
I have a bad time in another
yeah me too I don't like the never
that's why when I was looking up the
pictures you know of the pngs I thought
oh oh we'd only have to fight skeletons
okay all good thank God we don't have to
fight in the never oh no
but I guess we do have to fight in
another
we do unfortunately
Kyla spends like all her time in the
nether she loves the nether
maybe she likes Dark Places maybe
um spooky
oh speaking of oh my goodness
is that just I guess that could be just
normal for her right yes I think so
she didn't possibly join because she
knew that we were here streaming
[Music]
um I think we can take some of these
potions you know said before that it's
okay
so if you want to take maybe two fire
resistant potions
okay I took two
okay I'll probably
um
be too slow to react to use them in time
but well if you have your totem you'll
have extra time
oh and your armor might help
okay
all right mending station
yes let's go on the rail
laughs
are we going in the underground now
um you know the opposite direction where
I went yeah yeah go the other direction
oh
wait did I go the wrong way are we
actually
kind of I might take some of this though
damn me and my mom built this I remember
all right baby you make a really big one
didn't you make a really big one and it
was too big and it lagged the server and
you had to make it smaller
what no no did I dream that
no I don't at least that was the paper
Farm I don't think so oh
look I heard that maybe it was someone
else's Farm different Farm
Chad do you know what she's talking
about
like that happened
oh
that was around like the very very
beginning I bought I I built I I have I
still have that Coop the chicken coop
and uh
I guess it lacked my game a bit when
being close to it
but that might also not be what you
meant I think that was it
hmm oh
I'm confused I don't remember anything
well it was related to me through like
three layers of chat so no one ever that
happens it's like who knows what the
truth is
we're going so deep
it's a roller coaster
I think this is it though
laughs
[Music]
okay whatever oh
this is it starts yeah it's disobeying
me okay
that I know
wait
the PPP right
uh no you want to go okay we have to go
further then oh
oh
[Music]
I wish you could write one card
that's just kind of perfect
like a little dog oh
wait this is this is not well builted
the CPM yeah if it's not
it needs repairs okay I got Leanna one
back there are plenty of projects to
work on in Minecraft as always
do
when I replace the torch
maybe one more hair
okay
um How do you
how do you get direction I'll just place
it here
all right
let's just um
uh float flow flew I wasn't your lights
are broken though oh yeah right that's
why we go there yes
they're right we could not have look
flowers you've seen them the rail though
get to show off all the new stuff yeah
um but in reality we're not taking the
New Path right now
where are you from now oh this this
isn't new right is it all well maybe not
it's all connected though this is old
this is nostalgic for me
very old is this the tunnel this is
did you all dug together
yes we did I mean I feel like there was
one member who didn't take as much
because she was carrying a camera and uh
it was her idea
she may have not been digging this much
foreign
[Music]
but then I I went uh straight because
you pushed me thank you what about you
though I'll be fine maybe just continue
a few steps further ahead
yeah I don't really ride the car this
way
usually I go in the other direction
it's long this is a long tunnel
yeah it is we kind of needs PPP closer
but
so you built uh
something like PPP or are we just going
to PPP well it's near PPP
I've been building my farms at PPP so
it's like Farm Central now
you are a farmer's daughter
picking up the farming job that's right
picking up the pickaxe trying to
reinvigorate everything parents dream
come true take over the farm so that it
doesn't get destroyed by history and
time yes yes yes some big corporations
knocking on the door yeah trying to shut
it down to build a Costco
but no
who's going here
yeah do you have something similar no oh
something where you can buy a big box of
a chicken
big big box of like one thing several
things no like a huge Supermarket like
that no
not really no no no really no no no no I
I don't and maybe we don't I just don't
know about it because like for for
Costco
you need a membership right to get
something
and maybe that's the same thing in
Austria and that's why I don't know
about it because I don't have a
membership it's secret of Secrets
yeah it's like a secret Club
oh
like the Mean Girls oh it's night time
okay so we're not going up there but
maybe there's something yeah not up
there
are there two beds anywhere
ah
there's beds up at the top
two beds
oh I've never been inside the fishing
house oh yeah maybe upstairs
you go upstairs out here
oh there are no
sleepy up here not quite our colors but
no
but it's fine pretty cozy
here
on the en server
oh she she is oh no she left she'll come
back
don't go where's the fish where's the
fish no fish no one's been fishing
oh she's back
[Music]
oh
okay we'll have to swim
but I need I think I need some food
first otherwise a little bit too slow oh
okay
I have some oh
please
oh
no what's your favorite sweets
oh I don't know I like every sweet
maybe cinnamon rolls or french toast oh
I can make the French toast oh I've made
it in a while though can you make it
yourself I do make my own French toast
oh
oh where are you oh just going straight
I think I see something very tall yes
this is where we're going yeah you have
your elytra
uh yes okay
what's your favorite sweet
you oh
what do you think
no
um I have so many but uh oh man I have
so many like I should send you one of my
Austrian snack boxes oh I probably can't
eat a bunch of it though
um are they do they have to be vegan the
snacks well yes I don't eat naughty
things
well then the milk chocolate probably is
a No-No right
what about dark chocolate do you eat
dark chocolate
um if it doesn't have milk in it
sometimes even dark chocolate has milk
in it
normal it shouldn't yeah I agree it
shouldn't but you never know
not really my thing a butt really I love
dark chocolate
I'm sure there's some snacks that I
could give to you that are vegan
especially like I feel like over the
past
five ten years
companies have been making more and more
like vegan snacks as well yeah I know
you're not German but I know that
Germany is really vegan friendly
we're dead yeah so it might be similar
I would love to
I recommend
Munich just because you have to jump and
then
you'll have to jump and then push this
down
oh
um
so jump and click on the yeah yeah okay
and now this is the sword in this chest
this belongs to the farm so you can
borrow this Farm
you don't like them the fishies are
weird as hell they're weird
it's the funny fish farm
yeah
and it's laughing here
just stand down here it's safer if you
stand here
okay okay
um and put on put on your armor yeah
does your armor have mending on it
um the armor no just the just the hot
wings that I want to mend okay well
you'll want to get mending on your armor
eventually because the farm it does hurt
you a little bit
so it's best to use it it does hurt you
a bit but it's okay
we can get mending for your armor too if
you want but why do I hit
um so you stand did you get the sword
out of here
what
yeah
no heard it inside the baby has already
died
um how could you like
like it's a torture device for the poor
Dolphins this is the Dark Side of nature
this fish are an invasive species
they're ruining the natural ecosystem of
Minecraft so it must be done okay so
stand over here where I'm standing
are they eating the Dolphins probably
they're evil these are evil fish Kiara
and you must kill them okay
yeah and it hurts a little bit but
you'll be okay you can eat the fish
oh no that hurt my soul and my body you
can put on a chest plate if you want
you'll take less damage and you can hold
your elytra oh they're probably going in
The Hoppers aren't they do I have to
hold it in my right hand I'll hold it in
my right hand
[Music]
this is so scary oh is it healed though
follow
[Music]
I think that took me way longer in PPP
do you see the power of this Farm
power of destroying nature yes no
they're invasive species they're they're
the ones destroying nature
well good job on on building this is
pretty good
ah
I didn't even take damage although it
felt like I took damage yeah it's best
to use it with mending armor otherwise
you will
start to destroy your armor but oh you
can put the sword back in here
yes I want to hear this one
don't worry about the fish don't worry
it shouldn't be sure it's FFF it
shouldn't be funny fish Falcon it should
be freaky fish falcon
I'm freaking it's just a nicer word for
it
but you're right there are freaky fish
the freaky fish farm
all right
do you want to go to the Rain Farm to
see it it's not functional right now but
yeah yeah let's just get away from this
flap flap slimy flaps do you have your
electron
uh yes okay I think it's
I think it's this way
[Music]
if you want to fly this way oh wait it's
this way
oh
it's difficult to follow someone this is
why it's this way
oh you see it have you decided where to
go yes yes this is this
what
I thought you build it somewhere else
another hotel we go to the top oh no no
no you can go to the bottom oh
so this Farm is not working right now
but
um I don't really recommend that people
use it because it's actually pretty
dangerous
to operate so uh ideally I will just run
this farm and then other people can
yeah there's there's not too many in
here because I used a lot of them but
wow wait did you bring any emeralds with
you uh oh yes I did 64 blocks okay
that's that's plenty
you can take more if you want no no no
no no no no no no
no
I don't have many totems right now
either oh but there's gunpowder which is
useful
and glowstone and Redstone and then
these just have emeralds but they're
this gets sent to the bottom
man I dropped a lot of good stuff hmm
yeah
oh oh instant health potion
oh
and swiftness or speed
good job thank you
okay now we can go to
um right yeah I have a trading haul
which is
this way I always get lost I think it's
this way
wait oh yes it's this way
you made a trading Farm I did I did ask
you also if you wanted to
make it in Phoenix 10. but where are you
I lost you
uh you're there
it's this way
this house
what what
I lost you again I lost you again where
are you
where you just saw me a second before
um
buy the cake
yeah just this way
so are you saying that Phoenix Sun is
obsolete
well I don't think it's obsolete
sounds like it to me foreign
I did ask you if you wanted to work on
it my mom's crying right now fauna she
made my mom cry
oh let's see what this is it's not done
yet even so ah
it would be so unfortunate if a fire was
hit the towel
I still ain't removed all my signs and I
didn't put them back up yet but
I made fun I don't know how to get down
there
um hold shift can make sure yeah I was
just doing it weirdly okay so over here
I need to put the signs back up but he
is looting three so this is terrifying
fauna everything will make us terrifying
scary
picture of things look at them asking
for more space because they're going
insane
body left fauna do they even have
something they deserve
they're librarians
[Music]
do you hate books so much you don't hate
books I hate them what did Librarians
never do to you you know how you make a
book
have to chop down a tree
maybe there's vegan books
maybe maybe I guess maybe ebooks are
vegan books
yeah
if maybe if you if you charge it with
solar power you
it's a wood the tree is sacrificed
themselves for me so the grain are good
so you told you it's okay
they did
why don't they talk to me though phone I
guess because I'm not nature yeah
exactly
you you have your own you you know you
talk to your kfp employees
I don't hear your your nature saying any
word
[Laughter]
well this guy is looting three so you
can yeah yeah I need to chop up the
emeralds right oh yeah and you'll you
probably I forgot to get books so you
might need to get buy a bookcase to get
books do they have a bookcase yeah you
can buy the bookshelf and then break it
and it will give you books how do you
break Emma Roblox just in your inventory
in your crafting table
oh
wait this is silk touch nice okay
oh I stole it here oh no no problem not
like I really need that one exact block
okay hello sir
um don't worry I will
save you later
um but for now
uh bookshelf.com
[Music]
yeah you have to place that one
oh
come on here
okay
I just need one right do you need one
too
I don't need one okay oh he's about to
level up
oh nice not that it brings him anything
in this says scary scary
sad world
um and then do you do you want mending
for your armor
oh
I'll have some mendings myself but uh
yes I'll take them this guy has mending
meant my heart
[Music]
oh there's also protection for here
which is also really good for armor
all right can I not get one more sir
oh he might only sell so many for the
day
uh okay
I'll put it on my chest plate and then
actually I can buy some really I don't
have any emeralds though if I could
borrow some emeralds
[Music]
uh on it oh you're out
I'll give you this oh and did you run
out of books actually
I have one more do you need okay no no
no
oh oh
here you go
are you one of them or are you enough
something else
or I don't see any chickens down here
she that's that's because unless he's a
potato no no they're so small they're
like not on the same level height level
let's go ahead of these people he would
be like on the bottom yeah on the ground
how about a trades for you know
um you and me care favors as well what's
your whole thing called huh myself
instructor name
a construction name no I don't have a
construction name yet I've been thinking
of it though
I think I was thinking about it because
I was thinking maybe I should make a map
art maybe that's what we need oh yeah
yeah but then you need also like a
construction logo yeah maybe Kieran Coe
has a nice ring to it
also could I have more emeralds what do
you want did you want more mending
uh yeah yeah I guess so yeah yeah yeah
how many do you have or how many
Landings oh I have one right now
okay
do you want any protection
uh you have protection here too yeah
part four is here
uh wait ah wait I can't I don't think I
can can put bending on them because
they're Unbreaking free right uh you can
oh can I okay some things you can't
combine I don't know what they are oh
yeah there's a few things my diamond
helmet has protection free and I'm
breaking free but my pants have only
Unbreaking free my diamond boots have
depth Strider free and Unbreaking free
and my uh oh my God has also protection
for the Unbreaking for you so
not too bad right
yeah better than mine actually
haven't gotten fixed my armor yet okay
okay
so oh yeah okay okay so now we go to
enchanting top table somewhere Yes
actually it might have to be back at the
at the farm the funny fish farm unless
you have levels but
levels how many levels do you have
24.
[Music]
um
I don't know how many you'll need that
might be enough we can sleep in here the
communal bed
still in their beds I got nothing no
they have everything because of me this
Village was nothing
they owe me everything
that's quite some ego you have built up
there
this I built this big house for them
and it actually like looks really good
thank you it's not done aesthetically
pleasing thank you
the sad thing is that everything's
happened downstairs in the basement
oh I think there's a there's a candle
over here
[Music]
it's not done yet it's not done yet
fake facade
here's an anvil you can put
um ah
um
[Music]
real estate
okay
oh I think I can do everything here nice
[Music]
we need a golden helmet right when we're
down there should I put mending on the
golden helmet oh no I don't think that's
necessary
okay actually I didn't bring any gold
[Music]
uh
long resistance
a pencil already pencil
where should I put that on well why did
you give me that
um that you can put that on anything I
think that was your gift
okay oh yeah oh I still have that okay
okay
um
[Music]
here's some more fireworks oh thank you
oh
but do you have something like um
for fireworks you need paper and
gunpowder right what's up do you get the
gunpowder from you're a big farm over
there nice yeah yeah it also makes
gunpowder noise
all right on the sword I was gonna put
what
a looting three
okay
oh no I need some more levels for that
one okay we can't go back to the farm
okay
oh so colorful
oh this one has loading for too
expensive it says oh yeah and this is
actually the sword for the raid Farm
it's just not there right now because
it's broken and I'm the only one who
uses it right now
but I might take that one to the nether
because I'm
Kyle and gaming
if you want you can stay here huh
you can stay there I'm gonna okay you're
going to the fancy fish farm yes it gets
a new adjective every time
on uh somewhere
this one yes do you have to enter from
uh the the weird stairs no you can fly
there oh
[Music]
do you have your totem equipped no but I
landed in the water safe
you know the totems I would feel
I like the Subways I know you said it's
not a voice
they're infinite
um
but all the all the good treasurable
cherishable items I feel like I can't
use them
because then I don't have them anymore
but you can get more
okay today today I will I mean today I'm
gonna
find skeletons I can't really see us
getting into such a dangerous situation
maybe maybe I think it's quite dangerous
ly oh
I'm trying to help
do we need something do we I don't know
is it good
um I mean I only have one elytra a hit
just kidding
if I lose my life actually no I actually
have a backup elytra never mind dad
because I I went Elijah hunting myself
when we first uh started
out but I didn't think I wanted 200 of
them because I wanted to leave some for
my colleagues
oh encouragement yes
look under this
and this
I wonder if Tyler also plans to
take down the weather she probably
already has
oh really
I mean I don't know if she actually has
but it wouldn't surprise me
[Music]
what did I come here for upper levels
for levels
oh
oh quartz is this healing is this
healing
oh
oh oh
fire rest potion she's offering
oh
is it healing
did you put mending on it are you
wearing it yeah
should be then
I guess I think it's healing
oh scary
and my ah I guess as long as I'm wearing
this the level does go up but let's
let's get the oh
a while but suddenly I had like I don't
know 10 10 at once and that's where
suddenly yeah
once again and all my armor is healed
nice sir
damn now you see the power
I I think I see it FFF
uh uh yeah
uh brain slow this goes
here
[Music]
routine okay
now this sword is incredible don't need
anything anything else ever
ready
okay
I'm trying to get us some food right now
nice
and don't think we need food
I saw that um I saw a compilation
of you struggling with some Nether
Portals because of Amish
yeah actually
just because of our mother
the server was actually broken uh
hmm the server plugins were not working
properly
um yeah something was iffy there yeah we
had to have the server updated ah
I don't know so it was updated yeah I
was really annoying and I made them
update the server just so my farm would
work
I wonder if that affected anything else
too though because
um I don't know how how much that one
era
did but if it affected other things and
we never discovered it we would have
never discovered it without you you know
struggling with all those portals
wait so with the whole portal are we
creating itself over and over again like
that was the bug
I've had that issue too but I don't know
if that was normal or not well it's
actually that can be normal
um
yeah it can be normal there is a problem
there was a bug with the the way the
portals link but I just I like I
researched a lot on how portals work
um they're not actually linked to one
another like if you build a portal it
doesn't necessarily link to a portal on
the other side it just sends you to the
closest portal but the corresponding
coordinates in the Overworld so that's
why you can have a situation where
you could have like three portals that
are linked which is very annoying
yes yes
do be annoying it is very annoying
um I'm at the snowy Village
I have some food
now
is very bad no potatoes
look I got some fancy prismarine from
fighting those dudes oh yeah there's a
bunch if you ever want to build with
prismarine
I think good I might want to yeah
we're trying to bully her into building
oh oh you probably don't want that
that's probably kind of things do you
want to play Minecraft anytime
I don't think she's really like
quit or anything Cali however you know
Kelly doesn't want to play Minecraft
anymore
here's some food in here well
cookies
and bread and carrots if you want golden
carrots
apparently the best food in Minecraft
but there's only 18 yeah
have them we have okay we have infinite
now
that
18 is infinite well it can be you can
buy them from villagers
okay oh there's the ah there's some
outside here they must freeze in the
cold no no they're warm in there
is there either inside yeah I need to
check okay
foreign
he's looking really worn down I do have
I made an iron farm too it's not that
good though
I mean he he is feeling the effects from
your not good iron form
it looks terrible he shouldn't see what
happens in the iron farm
it's not good
let's hope no one tells him so he
doesn't start a rebellion in the
revolution
[Music]
that no one poaches your villagers
telling them that there's a better place
where they can have their own little
houses and sleep inside them and work
with better working conditions let's
hope no one tells them I hope they
didn't hear what I just said oh they
sound very interested in what I just
said they're like but are you very
interested in that
then when you want to when you want to
get any enchantment you have to run
around for 20 minutes clicking on
everyone to see who it belongs to
I know where they are you normally and
then oh yeah for someone who built it
it's no problem
think of everyone else
well you know what I'll just when
there's something that I can get from
Phoenix and I'll just continue going to
rain extend because I built it so if you
if you ever want to finance Services
Kirin code Services in Phoenix 10 just
let me know okay
wait I need looting for you so again
I'll come here because I don't think we
have that hmm
my Villages right
oh these are all born and raised here I
raised them from children
for Mommy Mommy they call you fauna
mommy no no let's not go that far
I wouldn't I wouldn't say anything like
that you must have some weird jeans that
everything you produce they're all boys
it's like how do you know boys are you
Lois is that your second name they're
actually genderless
it well they all reproduce with each
other so
that's Minecraft logic
humans
what are they
they're illagers
now you're making stuff up oh no you can
Google it they're called illagers
without the V
[Music]
that's such a stretch fauna it's real
it's real
ha
anyway Lois are we done
sure you're right Kyla did ask where we
are oh no
oh
sorry I didn't see your message we are
at the snowy Village
she know which snowy Village I think so
she was building with us
oh
she was gather see all these shulker
boxes Muna donated all of these shulkers
of supplies
neat
and Kyla gave us this glass
oh
yeah that's a lot of glass
if you ever want to build here it's the
open collaboration
I want to make it like a cute Christmasy
wintry
Village and build a bunch of houses
yeah hello Ian advent calendar
um
you may be some there in there too right
some days it's possible I might be also
involved in the calendar I may have even
made my video already already
wow wow no way
no way wow so
full maybe sooner rather than later
thank you Father for being so reliable
thank you for organizing it for real
Kiara you do so much no no no no no no
no
[Music]
such a good
idea why don't we have this like
organized by the company why why but
then interestingly I saw that um uh when
like one day after I started planning it
which was like three days ago or so
I said actually the Japanese uh Holo
Stars they have something like that
going on a company organized yeah so I
realized oh I guess because probably if
I would have thought of this earlier it
probably was impossible to yeah yeah
have it go through management and so on
it's not impossible but
in advance
but this way you know it also works I I
bought I bought a domain vonna oh if
you're so you're so techy now so
professional I'm I'm I'm I'm I can go to
Silk Valley or what's it called yes
silicones
Silicon Valley yeah yeah yeah I have my
own website yo I mean but honestly I I
did not obviously not code it but yo the
person uh who coded it is a kfb who's
studying and Harvard I'm just flexible
for the kfp now yeah
[Laughter]
is really cute it turned out really cute
thank you and they sign in has the
second one gone up yet not yet right um
it will go up in uh two and a half hours
I think oh no
it's so cute oh I mean we don't know
totally don't know who the next video is
by but in two and a half hours you guys
should go to hollow Ian uh
Dash advent.com
Okay because I always say minus yeah Oh
I thought minus works too yeah I mean
it's the minus holy and minus admin.com
and then open the second door and the
first one if you haven't yet and yes
it's fun everyone yeah it's cute that
everyone can look forward to a new video
every day yay yay who knows what they're
going to get
yeah and who who knows indeed because I
didn't uh I don't have all the days
um filled up yet with participants but
I'm just gonna have some repeaters
hopefully hopefully every day there will
be something oh she's here oh
hello hello
a penguin in the snow oh her natural
habitat territory yeah
oh she's probably gonna bring like 500
potions right because that's her style
yeah yeah
it's not gonna be you two or five or ten
and Potions gonna be 50 or so did she
did she gone already
oh my goodness the chocolate box is one
sec before tragedy what does that mean
take it drink the potions
foreign
oh yeah right you can't like
um
pot pile them right
so
thank you should we just bring the
shulker box into The Nether oh yeah
probably we can put some other stuff in
there too
oh yeah
do you have
actually
well
the real way to do it is to like bring
um an ender chest and then put your
shulkers inside the Ender Chest
oh yeah that's what Kyle's telling us
too
why do we need chocolate chests all
right Ender Chest
so if you take an ender chest with you
and you put it down and you put your
stuff inside then you won't lose your
stuff if you die yeah I know that but
aren't we just going there to get free
skulls yeah
We're not gonna like need so much uh
space in our backpacks now
that means we keep our stuff if we are
silly die oh yeah but we could just not
die yes actually I don't have a silk
touch pickaxe right now I mean we could
get one that's pickaxe oh you could
bring should I mine this one
yeah you can take this one okay mine is
kind of full of nonsense you can um put
this shulker box inside the Ender Chest
first okay mine it I think
yes because
oh yeah oh god um
[Music]
a lot of stuff in there too yeah mine's
also full oh gold boots in here
oh there you go oh that's gonna throw
away
the iron nuggets I guess I don't need
the iron nuggets don't need the paper
huh
okay well
um I think I'm gonna go
uh to my home once more to like clean
inventory out and then we can go
okay
[Music]
do you want to fly there
I guess ah it's that left yeah it's
pretty close a few times yeah
okay where'd you go
um I'm behind you
okay
yeah it's just like this way
oh
how does she know she's listening
probably
um
maybe one shoulder chest
or two would be cool to have because
right now it's filled with fire
resistance potions that's true
um yeah yeah and I clean out my in the
chest and then no problem because we
just how do I put
I want to put like
I need them pleading emote
please
uh wasn't it like this way oh that Tower
the top of the tower isn't that where me
and Kelly jumped off
present up there
fauna do you know of this present
the
present by the council area
in the sky the red big gift with the
green bow
on the on the way to
um I think I'm getting lost
[Music]
um
I do not know
[Music]
um
secret apparently it's secret you're
lost
um
who's made that
secret and the Christmas present for you
maybe from someone else
yep I am lost
you know the coordinates
uh it's near zero zero
I think that's where council's area is
you probably know the way from there
right so yeah
okay
um
okay this way
really far how did that happen
[Music]
I think if you just travel like um
Northwest
oh I see something I see something oh my
god
let's buy hot tomorrow right I mean only
hatima could have built something like
that what oh yeah keep going if you're a
hatchimal you should I think from hajima
you want to go like
slightly South mostly West
oh
is that her Hogwarts I think she's
building Hogwarts oh maybe it looked
like a castle a church or a school yeah
yeah
she's been working on it
she streams usually like right before I
go to sleep so sometimes I watch her
when I'm about to go to sleep
watch her build
[Music]
do you know how to check which direction
you're going if you push F3
you look at facing this is like a facing
west in the second block okay
thank you
okay
so and then we go through the main level
portal or a specific one I think the
main one like close to Ina's house would
be yeah probably we'll go in there yeah
I'm waiting for Kyla right now okay you
wanted to get stuff at your house right
yeah I'm I'm there right now I'm gonna
clean out the chest and then
I'll wait by another portal for you okay
[Music]
um
all right this can go this can go
this can hold this and More Than This
can go
um
come with me
oh where's that pocket from
oh was that the one that
you had Japanese from the Summer Fest
um
sword or with your bowl or so we need to
use the sword because it has looting
three yeah okay okay because otherwise
the drop rate will be really low
okay okay
makes sense and do you think we'll get
it pretty quickly but I heard the 2.5
um
2.5 percentage of China getting way
higher with looting three I don't know
what it is it's something like 20 I
think maybe we'll get it in 10 minutes
but then at least we spent
um one hour
exactly we even get ready so well this
is also preparing you got armor better
armor right you can use that for the
Wither and I want golden carrot Source
we want that for the Wither
mm-hmm
friend of this
I'm so slow brain is so slow for now
what's so slow brain brain yes brain
slow me too
slow brain I always just throw
everything into a chest and then Chad
gets mad at me
because I don't organize anything you
need crony and kid inko oh man good
combination me and crony have a
different skill sets we have a history
in Minecraft though we're kind of we're
kind of Minecraft enemies oh
I like that that's spicy it is spicy
I would like to Arrow anyway
[Music]
um
I think here and Co is like we used to I
used to work for bunkeroni Co
but I we had a we didn't part ways and
complete so now now I have my own
kirinco
oh but no no hard feelings right
only in Minecraft
to bring my shovel right oh yeah you
don't probably don't need it no ax ever
maybe the pickaxe that's it
yeah
I don't want to lose anything yeah you
could bring like a a worse pickaxe too
you don't have to bring your best
pickaxe
all right uh I'll keep the flint and
steel
um
so slow so slow faster faster Chihuahua
no worries I'm still
we're still waiting for more presents
from Santa Claus
oh it's Christmas it's December
I can't believe it November is already
over yeah when does for you really like
what do you need to feel like the
Christmas season started the first of
December or something else
um I don't know unlike December 10th I
had the desire to put up Christmas
decorations but I didn't because I
thought it was too early but I wish I
would have because now I'm kind of like
oh I don't want to put them up if I'm
going to take them down
so soon anyway
[Music]
so
actually pretty later that you get in
the Christmas mood
yeah I think usually it's when I'm like
when I go see my family
oh
thank you Carla you got it yes not sure
okay and she flies away
I have cleaned out my chests
and uh yeah okay
um I will come to you then
okay
okay I'll give you some sugar boxes
courtesy of Kyla how did you bring huh
what did you bring
quite a few oh we just said like talk
hey it's always overkilled I know
foreign
[Music]
cannot sleep while flying
skill issue
you're right you're right
Pro Minecraft player would have no
problem or a pro flyer
even though I broke my hair yeah
that's because of the hot wings in there
and it's just not optimized standards
anymore okay well there you are
oh my god well
what
did you keep some in your inventory too
yeah I kept them okay I'll put like we
really don't need that many but I'll
keep some they will be useful for
private use
yeah yeah that's what I was thinking for
you I don't know how many you have
oh well now I have a lot more
um
I don't know what to put in my under
chest oh shoot I don't have silk touch
wait can this break it
[Music]
I don't know if this could break it
break it oh
don't we just need one end of chest girl
uh yeah probably I guess so yeah I have
that one already ah you placed one extra
yeah then I can't pick it up because I
don't know
okay the right one
oh
there we go thank you
yeah
yes I think so
um
they probably won't fly right yeah I'm
not bringing bringing anything to fly
okay
[Music]
all right you have your fire potion
you have your totem in one hand oh
um
Marsha's Shield is a good idea yes new
Shield we have any shield and shoot
I don't have anyone
um
[Music]
uh help me chat what's the rest of the
lyrics
[Music]
that was about right
I believe it is sounded right oh wait do
we need milk
do we oh for withering oh
withering me fine just remember to eat
yeah especially your golden carrots do
you have any wood
uh not right now how much you need
um one two three four five
blocks okay five
planks oh got planks okay I should have
some somewhere and
for my shield
oh you're making a shield yes do you
have a shield
um
no not only my own but I got planks
you said five five
yes I think it's five
I'll give you I'll give you six
I got more than that but six six it is
in case we weren't right and you need
actually six
there you go
thank you
with full Enchanted armor and gold
carrots you don't need milk yeah
seems so oh wait is this not how you
make a shield oh my way I do I not know
how to make a shield oh wait it was sick
oh I don't know how you're right
[Music]
I anticipated that
she also need iron too I think you need
iron yeah yeah I had some though chunk
of iron hmm
take more totem no no no no no no no
no where do I where did I put the rest
of my totem stuff
how many totems are you bringing phone
yeah uh three okay
one second my inventory
just throw it all away
throw it away
en Seaver is very ex excellent weight
and trembling fear wait I've read this
before haven't I what was that
almost dead
okay are you ready
all right let's go I don't know
yeah I don't know how to get to the
Fortress
I think it was that way first of all
right chat Maybe
this seems like the right way I think I
took a screenshot at some point
um let me see him
North and then East this is East
and then North
wait let me see this way and left I
think
I feel like I took up
a screenshot of it before but finding
that now might take a while hmm no this
this way
you think so yeah I think it's this way
I think I remember the last time I saw
it I was
um
close to it and and I needed to be
rescued because a pig was on a one block
road a big pig you know and I felt
threatened by it wasn't it like there I
think when someone came to rescue me
because I think I had nothing really to
protect me and then one block
within that big
big pig push you over and fall into the
lava it's just not that'd be very bad
and funny mm-hmm
okay should be
would be somewhere yeah I guess here and
then left
it would be very handy if there's just a
road right there
I just left it up here is that the left
path probably I think I have been here
before I think I got blaze rods here
so spooky
are you not saved me oh yeah that could
have been enough because like
I was like hello can you help me
your Knights and Shining Armor
yes
good old times
see so much can happen in Minecraft
excitement is this the way
I don't remember this path to be honest
I think I'll leave it
oh oh oh I kind of continues weirdly
here
you still behind me yep
okay I'm here
wasn't that far away hmm
they can be pretty far
oh
this pathway oh yeah it's cool
whoa
oh oh there's enemy but I I have gold
um
oh goodness
ashes
wait where not no when you look straight
on to the right
um I can't see because of my settings
oh I think I'm pretty sure that's the
Fortress we have to go down here I think
bye-bye so scary uh so scary oh so scary
oh so scary
we should have brought a boat
do we need to take the other scaffold I
think we need to take the other one I'm
scared
you can take her your potion if you're
worried
how long does it hold on for eight
minutes
oh you have a lot of them so
you might as well wait where are you
going oh yeah come on no no I'm coming
back up
oh this is so scary already
[Music]
okay I drank it yep and then just gently
yeah
first and you can tell me before
I took the potion I'm not dying in any
lava I'm glad that
the one job of leading us to The
Fortress yes yes one thing that I did
besides all the things that you did
you can it was I was planning to
eventually doing it myself like taking
down the weather but uh and then I would
have done my research and all but you
know fauna hears so much into Minecraft
so just leaving it all to you now my my
dear little cool high oh of course
[Music]
wait be careful there's like a
lava block there oh that's dangerous how
it's surviving yeah are they gonna like
immediately greet us and attack us there
um
oh I got nice achievement it seems to
save so far no okay should I oh my walks
I totally forgot to bring blocks
oh there's okay
is they're three blocks tall
so you can like block them so they
cannot go down the hallway because
they're too tall
well tell me when you think there's a
good spot to put down the chest
oh do we need to put it down in the
chest well yeah
I feel like yes
I don't remember these coordinates uh
I'll put it here
there it is
hey sapling so you remember these
coordinates for me
take a screenshot saplings
oh oh yeah I guess torches the Torches
block their spawn
it's just dark in here
okay well everything is
in place
I don't know where exactly this spawn
usually I just like run into them when I
don't want to
then let's run around
people
okay oh wait I have a different PGM for
this I don't know if it will really get
this dramatic but I have dramatic RPG
danger music here there you go do you
hear this chat
I love it it's been a while the last
time I used this I think was when I was
um uh taking over the what's it called
the forest Mansion oh you did that yeah
I did it alone it was fun alone
did you do it before
um I've done it yeah like before
hololive whoa this is dangerous time to
do it again oh my God that is dangerous
scary oh
what's the rest of this portraits do we
need to go up
baby
oh oh there's stairs here oh there's the
boys oh wait I have fire resistance so
oh yeah you're no problem I guess yeah
oh never mind I'll pick up I'll go pick
up the under chest
and bring it why am I bringing it you
don't need to bring it you can just hold
it
okay
um
or I went upstairs
[Music]
I see you hello
um I'm getting rid of torches because I
think maybe they only spawn in the dark
oh okay
I don't know if that's actually true
oh scary scary scary
ah where's my Emerald where's my bowl I
left it somewhere I could have shot that
thing
um it's okay if you're a fire resistance
though because their shots won't hurt
you okay
but they will hurt you if you like touch
them so
oh not so brave
there's a magical suspicious door I just
wanna see the wither skeletons
is there a specific point where they
spawn in the Fortress or just anywhere
I know there's some biomes that are
better than others
um
because I think it's just because other
mobs won't spawn there so
um
do I get a curse when I try to destroy
some of the Fortress
no
what is what is this what is this
oh I guess we just need to keep like
walking around
and we might see them eventually I feel
like I always see them when I don't want
to see them
now that I want to they're nowhere to be
found oh you
are here where are you
I see him he's outside the Fortress
um oh I'm outside
outside uh don't worry about me too much
though you can look for one two I think
oh no there's piggies
don't worry about it
[Music]
where is up
up the stairs I think I saw you
I see you I'm making a staircase for
this guy because I don't want him to
fall off
oh come on come on
little guy come on up let me look so
friendly right now he's not watch out
watch out
food eat some food oh I'm good I'm good
I'm good look he dropped his skull
already
here do you want it a little thing's
sword is insane yeah
oh oh my oh my oh my
[Music]
heroic
it's stupid
potato fry there's three of them now
yeah just make sure to drink another
potion because there's probably going to
run out soon
oh ah one minute does it stack if I
drink it before it runs out no it'll
refresh so you can drink it before it
runs out
[Music]
oh I don't see anybody
um maybe
you look this way I see one oh
[Music]
he's not even looking
nice but no school no school can't get
lucky every time
towards my heart
my heart pitch black
hoard oh there's one over there
how do we go there black heart and soul
it's the emotori inside me
get over here take it down fall down
take him down
a butt
ouch
um
oh he didn't drop a skull did he
too bad the first one was so lucky I
know our expectations got set too high
when we
are lucky the first time now the next
one will be it the next one Shirley
I kind of wanted to get like six though
six one so we'd get them twice so much
yeah because they've been oh there's one
it'd be nice to have more beacons for
the server I think
oh for the beacons
yeah
oh sorry I think I hit you up
normal potato fries
why is there so many they all spawned
before there was only one yeah their
Blaze runs are pretty useful though
fancy fancy
when we'll go up here see if there's
something up here no I will look there's
a normal skeleton
why is there a normal skeleton
wrong Dimension buddy
you good you shot me
[Music]
hey
all right for now I'm going to look for
some of them me too
um
what is that oh there's one no don't die
don't die
okay
the skeleton I thought oh
hello there's a pig and a skeleton
oh
aren't they friendly no
um the pig's trying to flip me out ow
[Music]
he's strong this pig
I normally just kill them with a bucket
of lava
okay
I still haven't gotten another school
oh wait there's one I got one that's
already a good amount
you go to school now they're free no no
oh
no school
but menu
oh let's put it in the chest all right
you're right oh yeah
oh yeah you should put the skull in the
chest at least
it's nice checkpoint
I'm gonna try to break through here
foreign
oh I see one in the distance
from the back what are you guys let's go
let's go
out of nowhere
oh I feel like I always see them lurking
in the distance oh I don't know where he
went though
[Music]
scary scary
I swear there was one over here
[Music]
um
I should go oh there you go
there you are oh
you saw me no sorry I'm talking to the
skeleton oh
a winter one or a normal weather one
still no
I'm sure who nature is that's right
uh I still know skulls badass nature
don't underestimate nature in Phoenix
this should be like your natural habitat
fire everywhere
yeah I'm totally comfortable with this
situation yeah not too hot
It's gotta be hot
but to be honest I like
um cold environments too can you ski or
snowboard no I've never been oh you have
to learn yeah I would like to try it
it's very difficult it looks easier than
it is scary
it is scary I crashed before when I went
skiing with Callie and hope I don't know
your story
yeah it was terrifying he's gonna die
not that that would be a problem because
I'm a phoenix
so yeah but still it was still
terrifying yeah I would be scared that I
would like run into a tree
yeah that's almost what happened to me
yeah
normally if you ski somewhere there's
like a you know a big area of you know a
big road
Snow Road with no trees in the way but
yeah if you lose control hi if you lose
control you might crash and that's
indeed very scary
mm-hmm
so I have to start in a safe place until
you feel like
you have a bunch of skills
oh is there is a pig up there
thought so
can't reach him
well as long as he stays up there we can
be friends
you want the
you want his meat no just picks on me he
was just his friend bullied me earlier
so I'm getting revenge
the thingies now
I've been wandering around up here for a
while I can't find it though
maybe I need to turn my back on them and
then they'll pop up again maybe they
want to play hide and seek mm-hmm
foreign
that's the first time I did that I
didn't know that you know it was so easy
to do I thought you needed a mod or
something yeah it's pretty fun I hope we
can try it again sometime I don't know
if people actually like Among Us I
genuinely had fun playing on my list
among us but of course like too much is
of course not fun like yeah doing it
once per maybe two months or so
it's fine in my opinion
because I wish everyone got a chance to
be the Imposter yeah
apparently I should have oh I should
have um like reopened the lobby a few
times so that helps with the bug is that
really a bug I have heard that before I
don't know if I believe it but I was
like I would have fixed it by now
oh
hi hi
hi hi hi
oh
oh my panicked
oh skulls what the hell the first one
was so lucky I thought we were gonna
easily get them all in the short time I
already opened that up sorry there's
nothing there don't fall don't fall okay
I hate when that happens when
the first try you just get lucky and
then yeah comes back together forever
big expectations
can't follow up with no you're just
suffering
at least it's not so unsafe in here it
is like hard to fall down somewhere
mostly
yeah it's true
oh apparently it's ah
it's five percent
oops probably with looting three
[Music]
okay
I don't know about not being too easy
I wanted to six
but now that seems like that seems
ridiculous
yeah let's not do that
we'll be here until Christmas so I'm
about 1 in 20 then
[Music]
huh but I don't know what how are we
going to split a beacon
amongst everyone
but Beacon was for what speed running
speed
um or like mining I feel like mining is
the most useful
no friend
no skull
and how um how far is the reach of the
beacon
um I don't think it's that far
I can maybe
you know 100 blocks or so honestly I
don't care so much about the beacon for
me it's just the experience of taking
down the Wither oh I really want it oh
where are you guys where are you
I guess like the beacon it could be a
communal Beacon though so that people
can borrow it when they need it when
they have like big projects to use hello
what did you find a skeleton who has no
skull oh no
[Music]
no cause if you ever need to like mine a
bunch of stuff out then the beacon will
help a lot
because it can allow you to like insta
mine things it's ever need to like
flatten something
sounds good oh you have a flattening
area yeah I can see that would be very
helpful there
if we ever do have you like thought
about doing
um en sports festival
it's also quite into Minecraft I think
that would be fun but yeah
I don't know I feel like a lot of Yen
members don't play Minecraft maybe they
would join for the sports Fest so I
don't know I don't think so
I think they weren't no you don't really
have to play Minecraft
you know like yeah
even Steven Kelly would participate but
at least two like to build it
we would probably need out the building
is still the big issue I don't know how
they managed to build all that so fast
with like what three or four members
yeah they're really coordinated though
in ID
oh yeah we can get ID to help
it's true but doesn't that take away a
little bit from having like yes not
doing everything oh my help
yeah you need to do us ID server tour
yes
I'm sure anyone's really happy to show
you around
um it's really incredible
I've seen like screenshots and videos a
little bit I think yeah they don't do it
justice either it's like it's like being
in like Disney World when you're there
I think um Japan servers also very very
incredible but probably like in a
different way Japan's River the stuff
they built is this a bit more chaotic
um cute and chaotic and fun stuff while
ID just built seriously impressing
structures and like everything an idea
is like coordinated too
like I think they planned a lot of it
from the start
I'll open up here oh there's nothing
here
I've seen people say the en server is
like the countryside I think that's I
don't think that's anything to be
ashamed of I think I don't think our
server is bad it's charging especially
we have to consider for the most time it
was just five members and then you know
now even now we're still not that many
we're just ten
it's not that many members
I think it's a cute server oh I see one
in the distance oh how do I get to him
oh
there's a pig oh no that's not a pig
almost kind of scared
Maybe
oh I'm scared I'm scared
do you need help
um no I think
I think that is your bull I'm just gonna
like you got it make some what was this
one
making stairs
are there is he still up here huh
I thought I saw him here he was here
right yeah that kept happening to me too
I would think I see them but no it might
be around somewhere
more did you go oh there he is
scared
what do you need help oh I have the high
gun I have The High Ground that's right
and you have a cool sword
does does he know where I am
oh where did he go maybe he's inside
it might have been me oh no oh no maybe
I feel like he's running away that's so
sad oh no follow me follow me you need
help oh I need your mental support
like I saw him up here what's going on
and then I saw him down here it's not an
illusion I'm pretty sure and then he
went that way
maybe there's two
no school no schools
sad
[Music]
it didn't even spawn in the Fortress
like he was walking on the on the
mushrooms what the hell
since again oh but that's hard to reach
because there's love out there
the fauna do you want to go to this one
sure where
um you know where I went
I'm on the roof
what I I
will try to make myself notice I see you
I'm here down here I'm too scared to
fall down but there's one
um over on that bridge
we need blocks
no I have blocks okay I'll leave this
one to you
or maybe you can start just stop the
lava somehow
I got it I think oh
oh oh he's so scared of you he's running
away he's running don't run go get him
go get him
he's he's been cornered oh now he's got
courage to come back
yeah
[Music]
let's go
no
oh
no there's okay okay okay
pick scary Pink scary
[Music]
don't fall down
I won't fall
I'm very safe
I'm not safe but you're safe you're safe
no
oh this guy he's bothering you yes yes
he likes to flip
oh nice
nice huh
oh no my boots are about to break I
should feel them uh the golden boots
yeah
oh I hear
oh oh big white boy
everyone we're not here except for
skeletons oh there's one
no school
back up in a safe space man
what the hell
I guess this is why they recommend you
find fortresses in a certain biome
because they can increase the spawn
rates because here I think like the pigs
can spawn because we're in like the
forest so
was there more than one Fortress per
never
um yes there's one there's like
confident
oh
well I think we'll we'll find it here
eventually
come on can't be that difficult to find
two more
spawn rate seems so low
[Music]
potato fighting them is no problem
I does he know how to get to me no he
doesn't
I'll get to you maybe
um
oh
oh he's so confused he's so sad
his AI is so confused
okay so I took down the place here let
me make a pop
[Music]
um
don't hit me from over there can you hit
me from over there please don't hit me
from over there
okay
can I oh
this is scary
is this is this enough
you got this
oh he might fall down into lava if I do
this too oh are you gonna give him a
pathway
I've been making one but now I'm too
scared to put the last stop there
okay nice oh was that too tall for him
that's too tall
yeah we can do it like this are you
ready yes I'm ready
hi hi nice
I'm so much cool though I even made it
so rude
rude I he wanted to come to me I helped
him what the hell
I mean it's obvious he has a skull so
why doesn't he just give it to us
we need to we need to help him
hey
I agree on is there a TV show that
you're watching right now anything
oh
the baby is
just run away
um I've been watching or I watched
Breaking Bad and I've been watching
Better Call Saul
what Better Call Saul yeah Better Call
Saul is like a spin-off of Breaking Bad
oh
um
that's the one where the Malcolm and the
Middle dad is in right yeah
a completely different character
yeah really is it really or is it is it
maybe really actually him there I think
it actually did like um amalcum in the
middle
episode where it's like him but he's
like waking up from a dream
and then it's like Breaking Bad was just
his bad dream
I love the Malcolm in the Middle dad
I just recently re-watched the whole
Malcolm in the Middle like from season
one to last season oh I like that show
too
yeah yeah but I guess I need to watch
Breaking but how is it like like what
what genre is that
um more serious right yeah well actually
people say that it's a black comedy
which it kind of is
so really really dark comedy but yeah I
would say mostly it's like drama
Thriller
dark
the friller's that much maybe I don't
even seem Thriller it's not scary but
it's thrilling uh climb
[Music]
yeah I don't know you might not like it
though it depends you're like I might
not like it there's a lot of Gore I know
how you feel about
Gore
yo should we take down the other mobs
that I hear just so we can spawn
something else I don't think so would we
make them too much I think they'll be
too mad and they'll be mad forever
okay I better not touch them
[Music]
the butt of the piggy oh no
have you angered someone no I just
killed the baby and I feel bad
maybe can we is there's some oh really
are you watching anything right now
I'm always watching something but I'm
gonna finally start watching the newest
season of the handmaid's tale oh it kind
of freaks me out but it's it's good and
I hate it at the same time yeah I read
the I read the book but I haven't seen
the
the book oh damn cool
the whole book it's short okay it's only
like 200 Pages or something I think
and he never wants to show though no the
show is terrifying like yeah the book is
terrifying too yeah you have to we have
to watch the show the most season last
the most recent season is season five
they've brought out a lot and it's
really high quality but every episode
like after every episode I need like a
break because mentally I can't freaking
take it it's too much yeah
I understand that yeah I wonder if they
like
I bet it's new material the show right
it wouldn't be just following the book I
don't think
I think it's following the book properly
I think I haven't heard many complaints
about it being like the book is accurate
pretty short though I don't know if they
could make so many oh they're definitely
are dragging it out endless so much out
of it
yeah they're really squeezing that lemon
they really are like for many seasons I
was thinking
um okay are we ever getting out of this
[\h__\h] or what is it just like one does it
fall like one character oh one mainly
but you do definitely hear about the
others yeah
um and some of them have really cool
backstops actually one of the girls that
you learn about
um is being acted by Rory from Gilmore
Girls Alexis Bledel oh you know
everyone's good little girl no
foreign
[Music]
because there's no like laughing tracks
and [\h__\h] but it's funny and and and it's
cute and there's some romance and a
little bit of drama but I don't know
what what how would I describe it why
did you not
I like I like dark stuff I like I don't
really watch comedies or anything
most of the time no but I think you
would like it perhaps perhaps
[Music]
oh
no fauna is getting wrecked by the Peaks
no he's probably gonna oh no my boots
are already gone
oh
um I only have my helmet one in terms of
gold
it's okay
I will survive
one way or another
little [\h__\h] is Gilmore Girls It's like a
comedy what is it
definitely a comedy but it also has like
a lot of sadness and drama and cute and
romance like you know all kinds of stuff
and like splice of life but not anyway
yes yes that's all I wanted to say yeah
Slice of Life kind of
and it has a lot of Seasons so you have
so much to to binge watch if you need
something to binge watch
I have a lot on my list right now
there's a lot of animes coming out that
are really good oh you're still you're
still deep in the anime hole you're not
watch anime anymore I used
a lot of anime let's see laundry also
no anime from like 10 years ago or so
um I know some
no I don't know it
I know it of course but I haven't
actually watched most of it you
too much
the whole series All Seasons you have to
yeah
I mean it's funny but it's not like
mainly comedy I would say it's about
um
about putting as much information in
your head as possible in in one scene
that's yeah that's how I felt when I
watched I watched a couple episodes you
really have to pay attention yes yes yes
yes yes
they just have a lot of dialogue um but
I freaking love Pokemon it's like my
favorite
[Music]
you like it you like Central yeah she's
kind of like
which one is
not because it's a crazy one with with
the snake hair eventually kind of a
spoiler is your glasses
oh oh no oh no that's that's um uh
you're talking about what's your name
the one who turns into a cat
um
that sounds cute
yeah
I like them another real cat what's her
name again the snail girl
ah um you know I'm forgetting all the
names what the hell
um
she's adorable
so cute yes with the big backpack oh
hello it's so cute hello hello hello I
got him about uh no scholar
at least I found one again and by
killing him that means we can we can
spawn a new one maybe yes
some places Maybe
there's a lot of places yeah
come on guys we need you to wither
skeletons
um
[Music]
what kind of shows do you like
sorry sorry
did you watch Umbrella Academy
yeah I like that but the world I don't
know what what did you watch the new
season yeah I did I haven't seen the new
one yet
it was kind of ridiculous
um parts of it it's high quality and all
that but for some reason
I already forgot what my exact words
were when I gave feedback about it but
something about it was just like
please did you feel that way about the
first two seasons as well or just the
third season I think
I may have partially had those feelings
in several episodes also in on the other
Seasons
but the first season I think there were
reasons why I
absolutely
was disappointed oh it's still worth
watching I would say yeah I really liked
the first season
oh
first season was was decent yeah yeah
okay
are you okay
what's up
no skull
why
distance
straight you'll get that one take it
take it I got him pick him take him
rip his head off
ah no no school
how many have we killed killed so far I
don't know have you guys though
there please count for us
look at our stats page
um
is that me dying it's just that's Paige
wait wait wait no shut up just don't die
when you're looking at this dance
where are those stats I don't know how
to uh go to the escape and then
statistics and then mobs
hmm
and then oh
see I never looked at this before wow
I've killed a lot of zombies I've killed
almost 1200 zombies
oh
is it from The Raid Farm is that why
I've killed 8 000 vindicators wow oh my
goodness 20 000 pillagers almost
wow
that
was he upstairs chat
it was upstairs Ryan
oh yeah yeah there's upstairs
[Music]
I feel like yours you like to watch
shows I think you should watch Breaking
Bad just to say you've watched it
because many people say it's like the
greatest show of all time
oh I just fought two at the same time oh
nice
they gave me a stone sword
s
no but that was lucky I guess to have
two at the same time
[Music]
If Only They gave me two skulls
man
I panicked but I think Discord cut out
my Panic so you didn't you go yeah
probably
oh man but I I've seen her spawning a
bit more than before yeah maybe
never give up
[Music]
wait it's almost damn
it's been two hours yeah looking back to
play for like maybe one hour
man
this is everybody
so dark
oh
a new room
a new room and
stairs
I found a new room at least more rooms
to run around and check out yeah I don't
even have like a path I'm following I'm
just running randomly that's a long path
can they spawn in here too chat
so the Fortress I think is looking at
the ground
um
[Music]
probably as long as it's um there's not
torches
oh yeah no no one's ever been here
before it seems but yeah that's uh
that's it hmm I don't I don't feel like
they would spawn here Target acquired
Target quiet take him down
oh
he's coming to me oh
no school
what
it's [\h__\h]
[Music]
in three swords and everything
and come on
come on
what is that looting four and five two
no
four and five two
that's definitely looting two oh no I
forgot I don't have boots anymore this
guy's really angry oh maybe do you want
to go home once to get some I don't know
I don't realize
isn't there I think I just ran by gold
spawns here right yeah you can make it I
saw some gold here let me Farm it for
you but I only have silk touch actually
oh that doesn't work right you can bring
me the book
okay and I can unsilk touch it I saw
some gold oh will he be mad
oh wait do I have one in the under chest
wait I think I do actually I think it's
also almost broken though oh it would be
very smart
I hear I saw some gold
um
it's hard to reach
oh oh sure
oh there you are you hi
maybe you can mine it yourself then
yeah I can I could go mine
what was that one no you're going the
wrong way I don't know if you'll reach
there but I guess you can take some
different gold don't have time same gold
there's just some quartz here though
oh don't need corn I think huh don't
need quartz yeah I don't need quartz
what's it pretty yeah it actually is
pretty useful too for Redstone
but I have some I think they have a
favorite
uh Stone uh gem in real life
I really like uh opal
opal what color does that have like
rainbow rainbow
[Music]
pearlescent kind of like opalescent
oh I see one
what's your favorite do you have a
favorite gemstone I like them well
they're all pretty but of course
Diamonds Are a Girl's Best Friend right
that's true
no skull
didn't burn in the fire
that would be unfortunate oh I see one
well there's a couple ones
oh where oh
um actually just two
oh I feel finding quite a few
yes I think I see one here Target
acquired
let us kill you
don't get too cocky kiwawa
so I I make you stare can you come now
no no
one
oh but no
oh there's one where I just was
hahaha
[Music]
did you get it let's go
about time one more
good one
Chihuahua is going to collect all the
skulls
like the ones that I started attacking
you know you know which ones oh yeah
I've got the feeling I give up
oh where is uh
oh
oh chest
[Music]
and I didn't even touch me this time
because I was attacking them from
above
all right scroll is safely placed in the
chest
Phoenix luck very nice
[Music]
where could this one be oh do I see no
just blazes
um
I'm gonna turn on my hitboxes so I can
definitely not miss anything that drops
um Pro Gamer
oh I dropped that
I'm so shocked Anna that like you never
saw the shows that I shot so far
besides a few more girls like what
what about
wait I think mommy was the one who
didn't see it but what about you did I
ask you before about Lord of the Rings
oh yeah I haven't seen it either oh my
God I have but it was a long time ago
and I don't remember it
baby was it I see was it hurt or mermaid
that I said I want to watch it together
with because it's impossible that they
haven't seen it before
because if it's her animal Maiden yeah
I think it was one way yeah it was money
oh my God
it's probably because you and Mama you
must be Zoomers and I'm just a boomer
but I I don't know is it a Zoomer thing
to not I don't know the Rings maybe I'm
a boomer too I'm just I don't know I
tried to read the books but I oh I don't
know
I I have nothing but respect for Tolkien
but his writing style is not really for
me you know
that's true
uh no skull but call thank you for the
call it's like wait call ah Santa
not Santa but I think isn't it Krampus
[Music]
yeah
and you know the the dude that looks
like Santa he's called Nicolaus and
actually I think it's on the 6th of
December we have the Nicolaus day and
um you know Nicholas here comes with
with the campus the evil evil compass
and if you're not a good if you're a
good child you get like an apple or
something boring like that that's not
even that good oh yeah but if you are
bad and the compost will hit you with uh
whips and pick you up and like are we
around and [\h__\h] it's really scary
they literally raid schools
it's terrifying can you imagine what
they look like have you seen them before
I have I think well have do you know
like The Binding of Isaac
the game I know the game but then no I
don't know what you're talking about
though oh there's krampuses in that game
and he he is like a goat head
he's like big and furry
yeah I have the big fairy day they wear
like big big suits fairy suits and I
mean not not you know those firsts can
we be in the modern era modern Krampus
no no no
no okay this is my first so now for
children and then they come and rate
schools but also like in on the
countryside they go to like they have
the Krampus runs where just a ton of
them will run for the streets and then
there's like always these normal people
who stand around the street like just
because I guess they like the the
adrenaline of maybe being punched in
your face and still stuff and and they
think it's funny so they just wait there
for their Destiny I guess
oh I see too that's amazing
it's so scary doll have you heard about
the the Santa the dress is in White and
the Santa the dress is in Black
what don't
they say
that originally there were two Santas
one dressed in white and one in black
and
the Santa dressed in black was evil
like you say probably who said this
kidnaps kidnaps children and one day the
Santa dressed in white had enough and
murdered the sandton dressed in black
and that's why he has a red coat is
oh I said I'm sorry from a movie or what
um yeah it's from a game
I don't think it's a real story
but it should be
it sounds like it could work with your
with your air Krampus you know
but some some people mistake the Nicolas
for Santa but he's a very slim version
of Santa oh he could be he could be evil
Santa who brings Krampus
ow well he's supposed to be the good one
but maybe maybe that's all just a facade
yeah oh no I'm in trouble Krampus and he
lets him do the evil stuff while he
actually also wants to do it no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no he is a
good boy
but he shouldn't just bring Apples and
those nuts because
um
don't children deserve something more
than just apples and chocolate yeah it's
Christmas you know
yes I mean it's not really Christmas but
it's close enough
Nicholas and apparently it was the fifth
not the sixth
[Music]
I make mistakes so does that mean the
Krampus are coming again soon when I
hear the bells they wear like big
cowbells and stuff so you can hear them
coming normally
what's going on are you getting some
Withers uh my killed some and I have no
schools still
wait I need one
ah well I got I just got one recently
and it has to be paced and balanced you
know I'm still looking for them but no
no luck but that's normal oh God I see
one over there pink
okay okay I can do this
you got it the pigs are dangerous uh she
does help though
okay instead
everyone I keep thinking I see a skull
but then that's just a lump of coal yeah
at six was correct okay
oh thought it was skull but was only
cool
we'll win maybe maybe oh yeah no way the
Wither Skeleton
okay now he's already taking some damage
oh did you see it yeah I see
foreign
[Music]
they're manipulating our work here
this one will drop it no
um I'm starting to think that I might be
unlucky
one of us
went over there
oh yeah we built like some stairs over
there the parallels
um Bridge oh yeah yes yes precarious
Bridge you go there and I need you to go
I'll go
I will watch you but you're the one who
has the good good drops
that I don't like that Pap if you build
a better path I would go
oh
at least I'm watching maybe my presence
will he's going in the lava I'm kind of
scared what if he knocks me off on this
but you have to fire a potion though you
can it doesn't matter that much right
yeah
well is he okay oh wait but I don't want
the skull to die in the lava yes
all right all right
oh and
nothing
but that one over there though I think
there might be another one oh
good looks a pig
the pig
oink oink oink oink oink oink
oh I was feeling so ambitious at the
start of this I was like oh we can get
sick so we can find the winner twice
get two beacons grab that idea quickly I
know I thought we were set with the
Looting
three
oh but as long as the other pigs don't
see it right oh oh no never mind they
don't really seem to be angry at me on
it maybe maybe I hit the weather and
stuff no it wasn't the weather
they sounded angry for a second but
maybe you're okay
hello
see that one I I thought I hit him but I
guess he doesn't care are you Skelly
here
oh
my gosh you're right
well there's our three skulls don't die
don't die if you have a fireplace is
free skulls uh I I just turned off um
but we're done now
[Music]
I'll come back sometime okay okay you
know the way now yeah it's not too bad
that's all we needed right the skulls
what else is there
to make the wither we do need like Soul
Sand I think but I have some okay it's
not hard to find
all right yeah other than that um I did
want to get like Smite enchantments
come on drop drop it I didn't drop it oh
look is pretty good but not that good
for the other one yeah actually I just
realized this is your karma your luck
Karma because well you you I'm sorry you
lost your shiny in Pokemon
yeah I saw it you post on Twitter I
walked by it on stream and then you know
I fought one and then I walked by
another one and I was thinking while I
was walking I didn't say it out loud but
I was thinking oh that looks a little
bit different but I didn't think
anything about it because they're both
very bright you know
after that like a while after that while
I was fighting the next mob already a
few meters away uh and Chad was saying
oh that was a shiny but it seemed like
they missed the one I was fighting they
didn't even mean the one I walked by but
the one I was fighting before that was
not of shiny
when I checked I checked the archive and
it was of course too late anyway even if
I'd gone back by the time they told me
it was too late but I'm so sad because
it was the The Ice moth and I think that
yeah it's really pretty
nice yeah I'll go pick up the Ender
Chest okay
actually do you want to put it since you
have the other ones okay
and actually you know what time wise
it's yeah
it's almost midnight here it's pretty
good I like it the balance time balance
all right the the stone swords I'll
throw them away
I find it interesting to use the stone
swords they're so weak but I guess they
match their look
yeah their arms are strong
wow
what oh wait so this one oh we still
have so many portions you know what I'll
drink one I'll drink one because if I
fall and then die that would be terrible
on the way back
that goes in here
wasn't there I think I placed one more
uh of those chests in the other entrance
oh yeah I think I saw shulker
around there somewhere oh my golden
helmet is gone oh damn mine broke too oh
so we're both without going
oh
we'll be okay though I think
we just have to get back
yes
okay I think is it here
yep
oh scary scary scary scary scary scary
scary scary scary scary scary scary
scary scary scary scary scary oh you
watch out the Strider
it's all good oh wait there's a lot of
pigs
[Music]
I don't know what do we do I'll fight
them don't worry bam I'll be your backup
yes
on top of each other it's so cute
oh Pig
ah oh that pink
I think it's this is safe though
let's go quickly
I think the the pigs don't know how to
use the scaffolding my God
they would break if they tried to go up
on them
cannot support them
oh
when will we fight the Wither
um
maybe before Christmas yeah
I think we can manage to do it before
Christmas oh my goodness oh watch out
here watch out watch out watch watch out
okay
oh God
there's a pig at the top there's a pig
at the top
pancake
place where your stuff doesn't drop
it don't die I shot at and there's
everything is here
oh no oh holy moly where are you now I'm
on the scaffolding
did you go all the way to the top is
there still a pig there
um yes
[Music]
there's still a picture
are you even higher than me right now no
I'm below you now what that is so scary
I fell I fell to the bottom
what and I died but my totem saved me oh
oh
do you have to hold it uh but you know
what I'll put it that actually scares me
see I've learned learned my lesson
and
[Music]
can I build here to though they're
scaffold but how do I build from a
scaffold I'm really bad at building from
scaffold I don't want to fall off okay
it's too far
[Music]
somehow he pushed me off I think I went
too high up oh okay okay was it this way
I think it was that way oh yeah it was
this way um
good work Kiara you got all these skulls
wasn't useless you did most of the prep
for the prep but in the actual action I
think I was not useless thank God you
got all the skulls
I got the Lucky Sword the lucky hit me
if you ever need more you can always ask
me I can accompany you I know I have to
take you along
I'll come with you I'm your lucky charm
you are
finally my Phoenix lock came back to me
I know yeah this is this is your karma
you had bad luck and now you'll have
good luck yeah have you found any other
shinies in Pokemon no I don't think so
have you tried shiny hunting with the
the mass outbreaks yet
not really no I mean I've watched some
videos to see how people do it so I
might do it maybe or maybe I'll try next
week but I don't want to do it after I'm
already done with the game because I
don't see any meaning in getting or
shining when they're not using it you
know so yeah if anything there's like
any tournaments though left or right ah
that way because we said left right yes
so now it's right
um
there's we'll find another thing there's
also you can get a shiny charm at the
end of the game I think it makes it
easier but honestly like people
encounter so many shinies even without
so I think inferior is totally like yeah
shiny hunting when I had a mass outbreak
and I found one after like 40 minutes or
so 40 minutes or an hour of which one
which one it was uh Fido
yeah you should be using them yeah
they're also cute it is really cute the
shiny color doesn't make him look that
different no it doesn't actually because
I evolved him and then he really doesn't
look that differently
just a caramelized dog mm-hmm
a rat or safely
[Music]
where should I put the sculpture I'll
just keep them in my under chest for now
yeah that should be fine they're safe
and cozy in there yes
uh the do you want some of those potions
or should I also keep them in the River
the river attacks with fire too doesn't
he I don't think so no I thought it was
like shooting fire it does I think he
shoots like withering blasts wow
's explosions but I don't know if it's
fire
[Music]
not just the weathering effect he
attacks with explosions so that doesn't
count as firearm okay so I guess like
blast protection would be good
we took like what how many two two
potions from or four from Ina oh yeah
yeah we could return them yeah
okay I'll put this here
one four was it
we have visitors
hi we've been sleeping when we were in
the weather you want to go to sleep
yeah all right won't they shoot us when
we made me sleep out of the office it'll
be okay I think quick quick
terrifying Awakening they're still here
but they're burning
in the sky
okay
gonna put them back where they were
before and she will never have known
that something was missing and we've
been here
[Music]
I love her house I love the glass Taco I
know it's because her house caught on
fire but it's like so good
yeah it's been for some stage and some
history do you see you look looking
literally at his story honestly this
area where all the myth houses are is so
nostalgic too see that's why I like the
Ian server the way it is you know yeah
angry
I will play some more Minecraft now that
you know we have the weather thing going
on I don't know what to do after that
but at least now we have something to do
I just need
really like building farms and stuff
that much
um I find that a little bit boring
um as a stream at least for me because
like I don't know like I need to think
so hard and plan just place blocks don't
want so if it's adventuring I'm always
in
yeah
I want to Adventure I think yeah I think
Bay also wants to go on adventures hmm
[Music]
I actually I should check out how my
frogs are doing though before I leave
um
I must be still alive right maybe they
multiplied by 50 or so but do they
think I guess they don't
slime slimeballs but I do like one cream
right I remember they were going to make
them eat fireflies but then like they
had to take it out of the game because
apparently in real life there's like
poisonous fireflies yes yes yes yes
that is true I know that from froggy
Wawa
she likes them anyway but yeah it's like
eating like Fugu
actually if you guys want to know what
frogs can eat
I made a frog
um food or food for frog snack fly to
your list
uh or a froggy Mama made it on my
channel
a while ago if I remember it was quite
afford it because I was literally like
froggy about was giving really really
informative information yeah about like
normal flies and all kinds of flies what
flies are there I don't know
you're so cute flip and flop oh
they don't like quack quack oh wow that
was a big jump wow nice jump flip my
flip door Flip Flip cute
whoa whoa he's having fun oh he's living
his best life
he is living trapped in a tiny glass
cube but
have you ever thought about getting like
a reptile pet like you know
it's considered the reptile it is right
they're amphibians amphibians that's
what I mean that's what I mean have you
considered it I've thought about getting
a turtle because I like turtles but I
don't I think I don't really want any
pet that I have to keep in a cage just
I don't know I like cats I'm good with
just cats
yeah but it's not like you know a frog
would want to be running around your
whole apartment floor yeah but I think
he's happy in a place like this maybe
like but didn't I don't know I feel like
there's not as much interaction with
them you know like you can't really
snuggle a frog a frog doesn't really
want to Snug he's a frog yeah but they
probably don't really want to be kissed
have you asked them
they look they look like they want to be
kissed
I don't know maybe for it it's like a
lot of reptiles and amphibians are
pretty standoffish
snakes snakes want to give you a big old
hug
s we might like your body heat
they might just wanna
well eat you yes
constrict you
tie you up
yeah my Frog's cute I I'm I'm so
planning to get a aquarium at some point
yeah but now like I'll I'll be traveling
like to Japan for like a month and so on
so if anything I want to get it after
that otherwise I can't enjoy it but I'll
still be paying for it yeah I just I
feel like I'm kind of too lazy
because it's a lot of Maintenance to
like clean the tank you know yeah
found the service uh in in Austria that
like does it for you oh yeah you can
choose like what you want the aquarium
to look like what fishes you want inside
with plants what design what size and so
on then they come and install it for you
for you they come yeah they come like
two to like clean and clean the water
like change the water and they take out
the fish that are dead if there are any
dead they were placed it and also you
don't even have to even feed unless you
want to but they have an automatic
feeder and stuff so I thought oh my God
this is perfect because I want an
aquarium but I don't want the travel
that comes with it
foreign
on getting that I looked at their their
choices and so on I'm excited we'll see
she's gonna get species and I'm also
gonna put in um what was it called the
blue the blue it's not a crab it's more
like um I wanted the crab but then the
dude said he had uh what was it called
similar to a crab
[Music]
not a shrimp a crayfish crayfish oh yeah
it's like stunningly brightly blue it's
so beautiful it stands out so much you
know in in German when I said I want the
crab in German it kind of apparently
apparently is in German similar to a
crayfish so yeah I don't know if I can
get a crap I love crabs but I'm getting
a crayfish crabs are cute have you seen
the video of that person who bought a
lobster at the grocery store and then
raised it as a pet yeah
is
yes I have
that was fascinating I've seen a lot of
those kind of random ass YouTube videos
with yeah stuff like that
I don't want to like lobsters that much
like personally as an animal like as an
animal like I don't find them that cute
yeah and I don't think they're cute
either but you know what I watched also
a video where
um a Korean guy he was like uh I don't
know walking randomly in the nature and
he found like a little tiny not really
even a stream of water it was just like
a puddle of water that was leading to a
bigger water body and there were like a
lot of tadpoles caught in there
and he wanted to help them so he caught
a couple of them brought them home and
then raised them into frogs and brought
them back because like tadpoles so many
of them die in nature without making it
into frog stage because there's just too
many of them and then stuff like that
happens where they end up in a little
puddle but then the puddle disappears
and they just you know they dry out and
also they get eaten by other animals so
it's A Hard fly for tadpoles but yeah he
gave he gave he took some of them home
and then the rest that were there he
helped them go into bigger water and
then he raised them and made a whole
documentary about it it was so cute he's
a tadpole hero
so cute I love those kinds of videos
[Music]
we should raise a frog for now A real
one okay I like
yeah but you don't want to interact with
them I've kissed a frog before
I just feel like the frog doesn't really
care
you know it's like with cats you can
tell that they love you but like a frog
I'm not even sure if a frog really can
love a human you know
I don't know if they're capable
oh understanding love
special they're sweet they're cute
they're cute I agree they're cute I
agree you can perceive them as cute
and then the big frog ones they're funny
but the tiny frog was so cute they want
love you have to love them
I don't know why I'm getting frog so
much love I feel like I'm being
manipulated by Froggy Wawa Spirit
somewhere probably I think the
toxoplasmosis but for us
all right I'm leaving this place it was
nice seeing you again flip and flop
thank thank you for letting us in
have you made also enclosure for frogs
or not yet no I don't have any frogs oh
my God
yeah and you ever need
um actually I still have tadpoles if you
just want to go the easy route I I can
give you a tadpole
so I don't know what place to put them
yet
my axolotls are still living in a
bathtub they need a better place to live
uh the poor axolotls
[Music]
oh well well let's go back I go back to
my place I guess why don't you take a
picture okay can we put the heads on our
heads
can you maybe we can
then we can take a picture with that
yeah you probably cannot work
good idea
is what does it count as a helmet you
can I think so yeah you usually can with
them you can dress up
good ideas cute
and their chest don't oh yeah that will
pose in front of the gate
yes yes yes yes yes
we have to figure out where to fight it
too
yeah we are going for we know about the
easy way but we're going for the more
difficult way yeah I feel like with so
many of us if we do it like in a small
space it will be dead and well I mean
when Council fought the Ender Dragon it
was also some felt it may have been
anticlimactic
Ally because it was too easy yeah
because we like traveled so far but then
it was
yeah maybe pretty fast I heard out your
fight was very chaotic because of
certain memories
will be worse because it's harder
well
no but we're both Pros you know yeah
yeah
okay so picture time do you have like a
um like the one of those filters on or
oh I should turn mine on
was it in video settings no I think it's
video settings
oh really I have shaders here
does this still work
I think the never it would have been way
too dark yeah yeah it was so good for
the nether oh
pretty pretty I'll take my armor off
um
she's pretty the Halo it's night time
now
I'm holding oh friend don't hold bread
okay uh
yeah it's easy
Cheese
look at us
we did it
good job
I'm glad we could do this together
yes thank you
dramatic yeah I think we should probably
try to find like a a big underground
Cavern I feel like that would be a good
middle point between finding it out in
the open and that way we can contain it
a little bit yeah yeah so it won't just
fly away okay we have to fight it really
far from anything we've built because it
can like completely destroy everything
we couldn't even do it like out there in
the mid-zone or so yeah yeah yeah I have
a I have a railway that leads on a uh I
sway that leads all the way to the mess
have you seen it before my missa yes I
have me we can do it somewhere there
underground yeah that'd be good I think
okay nice
yum thanks for you guys thanks for your
luck no
no and thank you guys for watching yes
thank you prep work maybe the next one
the next week after so we can do the
actual fight sometime before Christmas
if you
wanna
um
if this is too short for you guys if you
like if you're like ah elements so much
that was just like it was it was nice
but just little bit more would be nice
then maybe
right for not maybe in 50 minutes right
is it 50 or is it more like 24 hours and
50 minutes oh [\h__\h] oh
really oh then you are okay okay
it's because you too like gave me the is
it is it nice so early
um let me see you
I mean I thought it was supposed to not
be but it is ready if it needs to be if
I could even switch it out
let's see the I have a I have a
a file that is connected that will
automatically like update at GMT plus
zero oh oh no it's not maybe I should
switch it because now I already kind of
teased it
oh no sorry guys no Fallout tonight but
we will now understand that it will be
soon okay someone just as good yes yes
everyone everyone's good I didn't watch
your video yet even though you sent it
to me because it's still in private oh
yeah it's a surprise
I wonder I wonder what you did in your
video well who knows who knows
you guys will have to find out by going
to hollow en dash
advent.com but yeah in any case in 50
minutes there will be an update so oh we
even on the side now um there's been a
couple updates ever since it launched we
kept keep on trying to improve it um now
there's a counter a Time counter that
will tell you so you don't have to look
up the time zone
um and then there is a function now you
don't have to refresh the page yourself
if even without refreshing the page
refreshes itself
um you don't have to refresh it by the
time the counter is at zero yeah
you'll be so so skilled so talented
so overpowered and I can't do [\h__\h] what
do you mean you can't you you play
plausible thing
yes I'm the brains of the operation okay
and you're the brains of this operation
fania I don't know about that
all right let's uh put the put the heck
back
all right
what if you get one more of the skulls
when no we need two more and then just
to mock the Wither we wear them
yeah maybe I'll get confused
or Friend or Foe
I never met with Nova weather before you
must be friends yeah if we can if we can
be the double-headed winner usually they
have three heads but if we stand
together like this maybe they'll think
we're double headed
I forgot about that
um
we're twins we're twinning okay guys
thank you guys for watching good night
good day thank you bye bye and uh in
German we say our our Founders in our
father says
bye
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]