[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
no no no no
no no
no
[Music]
no no
no no no no no no no
[Music]
no no no
well well
[Music]
thank you
okay wow
I was meowing but you only hurt me
actually my cats were answering me
and it was chonkers who started she ran
into the room like
and then I was like meow what's wrong
[Laughter]
okie dokie okie dokie
[Music]
I'm uh I just woke up
a little bit less than an hour ago
like maybe a 40 min whoa what's movie
playing with the tree yeah with the
country and There She Goes they're
zooming right now oh my oh my chunkers
follows movie junkers attacks movie
foreign
I feel like going back to bed but
um so we will be doing uh matches with
with
words of course today but first I want
to start out by trying something
um
I had the PlayStation controller in mind
again
[Music]
um
now practice a little bit something
um I I've watched the video
of all shroomless shortcuts of which
many of them I didn't realize you could
even do without this room I guess they
just really do their best with the drift
boost holy [\h__\h]
um yeah I want to practice shotokato
a little bit oh damn it I can't
a PlayStation controller brain uh what's
the best
ooh thing to I guess time trials
in order to practice it on my own
without getting getting Disturbed
I think I still don't have that [\h__\h]
card
at this point I'm like whatever I'm just
gonna use my random
throwing through together randomly
through together set up
[Music]
where is it where's the one that I was
using okay
sometimes sometimes I swear I swear but
was it not uh
what was this one no this one standard
quad I've been using this weird
combination I've been trying out this
one like here I I heard it doesn't
really matter that much so I'm like
whatever
whatever okay so I want one that I kind
of want to try because it seems insane
is the ice ice Outpost
um shortcuts now I I don't think I'm
gonna learn all of them until literally
tomorrow
wait what the [\h__\h] is it today
for me it's kind of today isn't it I was
gonna take a nap afterwards right ah the
game is okay okay I was gonna take a nap
afterwards right oh my God wait that's
today all right wait is it today
for me oh no oh no
I was Kyle oh my no and my mother
is
oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God
yeah that audio should be there now
okay so maybe let's learn like free
shortcuts I'm probably not even gonna
get to use because probably not gonna be
in that specific map but
I wanna at least take a look at it so
short wait let me let me take a look at
the video ice ice Outpost
oops I thought that was uh upset muted
no that was okay just one second uh okay
so in the ice ice Outpost there is this
part where you uh-huh go around the
corner which corner that is I do not
know and then oh my God how the hell how
the hell would you do that well did that
wake you up I'm sorry
well good morning butter yeah
okay
uh solo race I don't even need to go
through that I just I just wanna
know
I don't think there will be enough time
to really learn these but but as far as
I've seen the other girls
most of them don't really at least the
en girls most of them don't use
shortcuts either
okay uh where where would it be
I'm not here was there something here
too
ah
here here here where do they start
drifting
okay
wait wait wait
return return for the sake of it
um
okay one might notice that I don't have
a driving license okay let's try this oh
God uh
oh okay
[Laughter]
I was almost there should I go from this
side does it matter probably not
okay you realize every car drifts
differently I guess so
ah okay
my curve is two
uh curvy
okay
[Music]
okay one more try one more try
yeah yeah okay
almost and then once you're over there
you can continue here I never saw that
before
and then left sorry oops can I do it
again
my turn
did you guys ever see that one before
no okay stop stop stop stop return
return return
I don't recommend doing the second one
but that one looks fairly easy
okay
that means that needs me to be so
precise oh
I don't know about that mate
I don't know about that
[Music]
real tournament is starting in less than
24 hours
so at this point I guess not really much
I'm not gonna get in that much practice
either because I have to sleep after
this because the the tournament for me
starts at like 5 a.m and uh I I I need
to sleep after the street we have it
yeah okay whatever I I don't think
shortcuts let's just practice this one
then
[Music]
[Laughter]
or
um I also
that uh adiosis thingy ah there's one
here there's one here I never realized
that for the Yoshi one you also don't
need a shroom you can just do it with
drifting as well
I wonder if I can
try that
oh God I'm bad at driving backwards but
that's what you you don't usually drive
backwards in this game thank you for
remember
Nida okay so uh
[Music]
oh go back go back go back
foreign
[Music]
um
might need the momentum from the from
the from you know from this part before
landing here
[Music]
and I also saw someone
um doing
like you know how the grass stops you I
saw someone like bouncing over it for a
few moments
to get get through it quicker
I can't I can't I can't
morning morning
I can't go into the drifting
I need more speed yeah all right where
does it start
[Music]
[Laughter]
s
yeah look into your
[Music]
um
maybe there's a different one that I can
learn easier hmm
there's so many
[Music]
is there one that you guys particularly
know that you think is easy
that I can learn quickly
big blue has a big and easy one big blue
big blue ah meow okay big blue okay I
see it is the last one F zero okay so it
goes like and then oh [\h__\h] no [\h__\h]
way
wait which one do you that does not look
easy to me you kidding me
[Laughter]
I'm out have fun using it have fun
[Music]
so I think pretty much in the beginning
no [\h__\h] what
beginning it's somewhere
somewhere where where the coin line is
the is it here no
foreign
[Music]
but honestly with with this one I feel
like I've been doing quite well I've
improved on on this map really well oh
wait wait what about here
did I see some dropping down here
I don't know maybe not
maybe that was my imagination
uh where was it
here in the video they did it here
[Music]
uh yeah
hey one more one more one more one more
oh that looks so dangerous
that looks so dangerous
[Music]
you're mean that one
what are you talking about this one
because that was the only one that I saw
in the video like that one and then the
same one that immediately follows up on
it
[Music]
you know
I saw good at
um uh playing a little bit yesterday and
holy [\h__\h] she's good thank God she's not
in my team
[Music]
now she was so fast and even
if her speed
she barely got into the top five when
racing against wheelers
oh God oh God
but then wait wait wait where where was
the next one what's the next one
is that really Wi-Fi how much time does
it save me
the over that corner and then
uh go to the bottom one
and then the next corner
oh okay
go to the bottom one
[Music]
without drifting what what what what
I didn't understand that one very sad
please maybe I'll just do the first one
huh
go over that corner the first one and
then go to the bottom and then
no drifting just kind of while
uh turning the wheel to the left
kind of go straight
at least I know how to drift
[Music]
continues drifting
that was a nice story though oops that
was not so nice
[Music]
and
here we go
here it comes Cruiser
[Music]
girl no [\h__\h] okay
I want some I was yeah whatever
[Music]
yeah
wait a minute
I kind of made it oh
but but for for the first shortcuts the
the Boost that I got from the jump
kind of made me go too far
[Music]
can you do a jump while you're drifting
without uh stopping the dirty stuff
[Music]
small small
recommend ghost
but now I just want to try this out
just experimenting
[Music]
I can't even keep up with a ghost you
know
[Music]
oh okay
I can't do the second one oh
[Music]
no
but the first one was very smooth just
now I think
now
[Music]
shut up
no no
you guys recommend me to be drifting
through that whole big ass curve there
or should I stop sometimes
yeah no you don't recommend it it seems
to work though
okay let's go
let's go
[Music]
foreign
I was ready but I was also not ready
guys I've been recently I've been
practicing from bed I moved my switch
over to my bedroom because
um I don't even have a TV in my living
room I only have a TV in my bedroom
because that's the only place I ever am
at
I'm thinking about putting a a TV into
the living room just for the sake of
decorations
or a projector but anyway I was thinking
um
I was thinking
uh I want to play a little bit from my
bedroom because it's more comfy uh
before sleep and so on so I was
practicing before sleep
and then
that was the first time because the the
cable from my Pro Controller didn't
reach
didn't breach
where I was like
sitting at
oh
so I was like is does the Pro Controller
work without a cable
and after using a Pro Controller for
such a long time that was the first time
that I realized the Pro Controller Works
Wireless too hooray
[Music]
so I was able to play from bed I never
oh I never realized but thankfully there
is that option buying that super [\h__\h]
expensive Pro Controller was worth it
after all I mean if the if the original
Julie clowns that come with the switch
work wirelessly then you would imagine
that the Pro Controller does too huh
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh okay
oh okay yeah I don't think I want that
first trip from the bridge from the that
thing
no I can't die
because that gives me too much momentum
anyway okay maybe I'll practice that a
little bit off screen screen let's
finish this race
[Music]
go
let's go free as a free yeah
[Music]
that is apparently according to mine
a video that is all the shortcuts in big
blue at least without the shroom
[Music]
but
for what I can't shortcut I'll make up
for in super badass drifting skills
and such
oh yeah here this is this is necessary
whenever you have a shroom
oh that was fast got myself a PS5 today
no
no it's time to play Death Loop time to
play Death Loop
no don't don't update that embarrassing
time so let me let me I wanna let me
watch that video one more time which one
was really impressive
um
which one was really impressive
um Sunshine airport don't do this Mount
Warrior Adam Mount Warrior one I'm gonna
give a try
that those Corners that they be cutting
holy [\h__\h] oh and then that one in the
forest I never even noticed that one
before I think okay last one I will try
last one I will try
come on
montrealia Wario Warrior
I'm a warrior
okay
[Music]
happy birthday
Antonio
rainbow road has an easy one I I saw a
rainbow world Shield card the shortcut
but they look crazy
okay
let's see if I can do it so try to cut a
really close Corner not here
not here but here
[Music]
wait what ah
wait was it not here
and
[Music]
was it here
where the hell is that they don't show a
map on that screen I know it's not here
it's not here okay
uh it's somewhere where there's like a
cute no I hear maybe yes yes here
okay I had to stop myself a little bit
but okay that's manageable
and then we wait a little bit until the
next one
oops oh God I mean I didn't forget it
just didn't work
oh what the hell
huh
couldn't reach the top
why are you damn let's go
[Music]
yeah
ah yeah these ones I have a little bit
of an issue of reaching properly okay so
here left and then oh I know I never
realized this one before fun sponge like
that does that save a lot of time
[Music]
I should practice how what the best
route is to go through the trees
need a shroom there no I'm not
necessarily
for sure if I had a shroom but I mean I
do have a shroom but I'm imagining that
I don't have a shroom
[Music]
let's go
I love these jumps that's so fun
I got number one here when I was racing
against Ina and Buddha and amen
yeah what's going on with my controller
what's going on
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
that's okay
[Music]
that is not so difficult I think I can
do that like
just on first try as I did now
oh you
I don't want to say that um I seem to be
better when I don't stream and when I
play from my bed although from bed I had
some issues of seeing the the course
sometimes because my TV is fairly far
away
uh a nice excuse chip I will I will um I
will
no there's no cat in front of the sensor
no I will do my best but I might focus a
little bit on the game so that I can
impress you guys
are you guys ready to play with me
oh
yay
okay I mean some of you already know my
tournament number
um so that's that uh
let me write it down though
where is my
where where is the text
got no text layer
next stop
oh that could is that it
was that it from before
is that it
[Music]
is
that could be it oops
don't go
away
uh
uh where the hell did Costa 31 go oh
that's not it
uh uh wait wait wait wait wait two eight
four five uh eight four one four uh six
four seven five let's go
let's go did I input that correctly
everybody show me what you want chat
no you don't have a game console not you
don't have a switch hey go get
this is best console
I love me some switch
oh guys I didn't talk about it did you
guys see the announcement on Twitter
maybe if you don't uh go on Twitter you
may have not seen it but Hollow myth and
Holo console as well as Iris just takes
a little bit longer we are all getting a
New Year's outfit
yay
yay yeah
oh they're always a nice shortcut here
too yeah
yeah I knew about it since of course
longer than you guys and I was I was so
eager to tell you when
um
when uh Holo X and when nanitzi got
their New Year's outfits everyone was so
hyped about it and and the whole time
you guys were like oh well the myth
obviously isn't getting a one because
myth and they got the the party dresses
so that's like their New Year's outfits
and I was like yeah okay so I guess you
can see it like that but in theory we
were supposed to get the party dresses
like months ago that was just delayed
remember when we announced them in
September
they were not supposed to come out this
late there was supposed to be more time
in between the party dresses and the the
New Year's outfits you know it was
supposed to be more time oh
in give me back my item give that that
was supposed to be my item
[Music]
s
okay I'll Focus
even when I focus I don't know maybe
being too close to the screen is not
good for me here
[Music]
what about this this one I'm always too
scared to use this one oh thank you Game
for helping me
that corner is so
so yeah bye no no
okay I give you that I need to warm up
okay
[Music]
what
why are you getting the wind and I'm not
um
[Music]
well sometimes you just gotta do what
you gotta do
maybe when you're going to the usual
room
one month
oh
[Music]
gosh
[Laughter]
[Music]
laughs
life is just not fair
oh God
[Music]
[Applause]
where did the camera go that was good
[Music]
what's happening
what is happening
come on
oh okay
I think let's do One race where I don't
talk okay
Kiana has
a
redef
what's what's for both uh
uh
what's made of a boat
[Music]
okay
Kiana has
a Talking Ben
okay I am not allowed to talk now
all right
no talking no talking no talking loud
[Music]
yeah
um maybe
no nothing yeah laughing is bad too I
love more when I'm streaming because I
don't know I feel like
everything's funnier when I'm straight
away
[Music]
Talking Ben
not talking kibala
okay
[Music]
Focus
focus focus
[Music]
Focus
huh
thank you
[Music]
out
okay
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
hahaha
I mean actually six is not so bad but
still that race was pretty bad I would
say
um
[Music]
I'm not so happy with that but it was
better than before let's do another no
talking one oh muted City we try out our
new skills Oh I wanna do that one I
shouldn't I shouldn't vote so fast
because then it makes still a race start
too early when everyone's leaving
bye bye thank you for joining everybody
one time only please thank you thank you
all around me
[Music]
yes yes no talking City
talking not allowed otherwise Kiara's
butt gets Kitty kicked
oh kiwawa fake Chihuahua who looks kind
of a cat cuter than me
oh everyone wants to do mute City why
[Laughter]
everyone reads the air cookies
[Music]
oh yeah
who looks like Yago to you no one looks
like Yago to me and that round of people
that doesn't look like yeah go how does
that look like yeah go to you
okay
don't you dare use the same shortcut as
me guys just because you learned it from
me
okay
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
oh yeah
[Music]
I went that wasn't different when I
wasn't built City it was uh the big blue
okay whatever
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
laughs
the whole time in the beginning I was
thinking mute City and and the big blue
is the same thing
I was like where is that shortcut I
don't know what already next lap where
was that shortcut
Mario Kart in a nutshell thank you for
participating
but still I was I was doing pretty
decent I could keep up with most of you
guys
um
so I'm pretty happy with that yeah
welcome new people please
and while I am waiting
let me show you this uh image
uh
oh my shot
whole life English New Year's outfit
unveiling relay yes we're doing a relay
and actually we're doing it on Saturday
yeah I think many people think it's like
oops many people probably think it's too
early since the last one but yeah as I
said it wasn't supposed to be that close
together but hey this will also be
council's first new outfit so that's
nice and Iris will be
um joining later on
uh it says in the news article as I
quote due to some circumstances uh Iris
outfit is delayed but don't worry she'll
be getting one too
shall I be quiet again because that
makes me uh drive better apparently
um
not much talking today but we're gonna
read some super chats later okay then we
can talk
anymore
we don't talk anymore
we don't talk anymore like we used to
you don't talk anymore
they don't talk anymore
oh [\h__\h] you
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
my God
[Music]
oh
my God
[Music]
[Applause]
delicious
[Music]
thank you
[\h__\h] was that I fell behind so far uh
like
pretty pretty much at the start
I fell behind so far because of all
those all those
inconveniences thrown at me
[Music]
but at the end yeah when things were
going a little bit better but there were
many times where I didn't get an item
and and then that one time when I was 12
and I finally got an item that could
help me and then I got F by that Thunder
Man
I came back a bit yeah I tried
um
wow it could be better could be better I
do have to say for uh was it dolphin
shows I think so uh when where I said
put the banana up your ass oh the
dolphin shells
um there's this part where there's this
curve right and I always go on the water
but I see most people always go above
water maybe that's the better way to go
um
um kind of want to do that one
I'll I I just always feel like the
underwater and that was cheap cheap
beach oh okay okay okay but then yeah
for cheap cheap beach I wonder maybe I
should not go underwater in that curve
you know what I mean you know what I
mean
[Music]
I know what if you have a shrimp yeah I
still go on the water even if I don't
have this room probably shouldn't I do
notice I'm slowing down a lot if I do
that
[Music]
okay let's go final
also please everybody leave after one
round participation okay
now
[Music]
ah
I know where
[Music]
thank you
look at me
down
okay
[Music]
oh oh
what what what what what what what what
I got so lucky at the end I got so lucky
imagine imagine if if just all things
kind of were happening weirdly like a
miracle and I end up being like in the
top free or so and not end up in a taco
High just by pure [\h__\h] pure luck sheer
luck and I'm like how the [\h__\h] did I get
into the winners cup how how no I didn't
want to be here I'm not supposed to be
here
oh my God imagine imagine if just a lot
of things go wrong for the good people
and a lot of things go right for me it
could happen and I would be like what
the [\h__\h] is this timeline
oh [\h__\h]
would be a hilarious uh situation yeah
um by the way I told Elena she can join
if she wants to okay
you can join if you want I will be in
the clown question
uh
okay okay she might join us
um eventually
I was trying uh yesterday to get into
Elena's uh stream into her tournament
took me quite some time I kept on
joining and leaving and joining and
leaving joining and leaving because it
creates so many different tournaments
huh
um
us okay no speaking
well please stop complaining come tell
me cause it hurts
[Music]
hey Kiara
get the [\h__\h] out of me
[Music]
it's okay it's okay I um I bought the
start of my car too
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay I'll give you some um I'll give you
some space okay I'm also racing oh okay
you're not streaming anymore are you oh
I'm still streaming we're still
streaming oh okay okay I think you
probably didn't even hear my full screen
that was like pure horror
laughs
yeah you probably didn't hear it this
could probably cut it off but that was
that was wow oh no man you give me a
heart attack
how's it going over there Dana oh me uh
great
um items probably not being as bad to me
oh I'm like this morning
this morning was kind of awful but I
don't know
um I feel like luck is just very
important in Mario Kart yes 100
that is very true I've I've been the
past few races I've been doing so that
um I wouldn't speak because we've
noticed that I can't uh play this game
if I talk
yeah which is why I'm now driving worse
no problem
it's entertainment value
I uh when when I did a few races while
not speaking I was much better
okay we do not have the same problem
I do of course I do
I played um I played when I was on the
street and I was like hey I'm actually
pretty good yeah all right
that's where our full potential is
hidden
I know they don't believe it but it's
true it will be true
yeah such is the life of a streamer it
is okay
[Music]
no okay
wait so do we finish up do you want to
go into the same tournament or what do
you want to do oh yeah sure I'll join
you I'll try joining you okay uh
everybody get out of here
cold wait I'll send you my code but oh I
can join through friends I know I think
that's only wait let me close my
tournament I'll make a new tournament
because the first one is I think only
with NPCs
uh I'll make a new one
uh what's this honestly oh okay uh
create tournament
create an online tournament let me hide
the screen and okay
I'm gonna get your cute uh chibi drawing
oh yeah I need to get yours on screen
too oh
I hope that that puts me luck in uh the
race in the tournament I hope I get the
bullet a lot
me too I got the blue shell though oh
that that helps I think the one who
froze the blue shell doesn't really get
much out of it because if you get it
then you're at the end of the race
anyway it's not gonna help you much it
helps the second place yeah that is true
so that the second if there's someone
you really like on the second place and
you can give them number one then
[Music]
no CPU all vehicles smart steering no
smart steering I guess
um
the time settings don't matter as far as
I know
and public to everyone okay
okay
I got it I have the code right now okay
um let me um
PM me
will do
wait I gotta I gotta make sure I hide
the screen yeah yeah yeah yeah okay I'll
try I'm gonna put your I'll find your
image I'll find it
okay
[Music]
for sure and they draw such cute
illustrations for all of us to Listen by
tell us if I commissioned all of those
cute illustrations for every participant
isn't that so nice
I know I watch everybody and it's like
oh so cute
cute and we got like per generation
they're like from the same artist so
it's kind of matching
is there a reason why uh only ID second
gen is participating
uh I'm really not sure
oh maybe I'm really not sure they
participate in last year so they're like
oh let's let's start a second gen girl
uh May halves mayhem's mayhaps may have
look at that I love I love the eyes in
in your oh and your kimono is beautiful
too
love the sparkles in your in your kimono
wait
did you did you get in I might not I got
in but I got in but I'm with like random
people
[Music]
what how's that possible
I'm not even in yet I didn't show them
the Code yet
okay let me get in
oh did you set it to code required
I said no wait I'll exit I'll exit oh
wait
I I said uh
available for everybody
was that was that wrong can I change the
setting up an existing tournament
oh yes you can uh if you check the
tournament and there's a I saw Yes okay
okay
foreign
it is okay it is absolutely okay what
they heard Bales Bales is not in the
voice chat no no
open to everyone code required ah so yes
they just randomly joined the random
tournament that exists right now in the
world it's just not even viewers
probably yeah yeah yeah
okay now you should be able to join
again and this time no one else should
be joining except for
I chose the course
so everybody look at the code new code
in free
two one wait I'm alone here though I'm
alone in here what what
did you go into a different room no
oh yeah make it alone for some reason
maybe how
[Music]
[Laughter]
why why Nintendo why let me uh let me
exit again let me know everybody I'll
just join you I'll just I'll just try
I'll just try to join you okay
join Kiara why is it so complicated man
you should be able to join friends as
well in these tournaments and like um
you know this target device cannot
accept any more connections what the
[\h__\h]
okay okay I'll try I'll try our race is
starting right now so thank you though
way down this one is over sorry that's
so awkward no no no no no no that's fine
I'll just spectate so I can join okay uh
the next one someone looks like konata
do you know Lucky Star
someone made their me look like konata
from Lucky Star
I got an air the target device cannot
accept any more connections that's so
weird I mean your device
I don't know what the target device
means
what does that mean chat do you know
chat chat chat
oh wait that's that's a big blue the one
where I learned the shortcut right what
is that it was that was that yeah a
different one
no that means Kiara's room is full
ah okay then I think I'll tell you the
moment when it's ending because that's
when I joined your room yesterday huh
uh once the other people
um start leaving I think that's when you
should try joining
okay okay okay
yeah yeah baby that was good
oh
[Music]
school doing pretty well so far
this is really awkward like on my end
because I'm not showing any of the game
and you're just like
oh yeah
I can't imagine hello everybody from
odena's stream how's it going
everybody
how is it going everybody it's a live
report it's a thank Nintendo for that
for making it so difficult
yes oh I don't like this one I will I
will wait for you
I'll just play with your tattoo okay
oh
the black do you like the plant I turn
the big Chomp Chomp plant I don't I
don't really like it it's very difficult
to control I feel like it's an inferior
star yeah
although it doesn't yeah it doesn't um
it doesn't help you when driving over
grass and stuff
[Music]
I'm doing well even though I'm talking
nice
I'm trying to hit someone I'm so bad at
aiming the shell so I should never try
to do that what
on Fifth
oh
my God
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
this cord is totally cutting off her
last stupid Discord okay okay now uh try
to get it now now okay okay
it's full it's full it's full
it says there's like there's like a lot
of props yeah it's full let me make a
new one sorry guys sorry guys I'm making
a new one and we'll there's like a lot
of prompts to join
okay I'll make a new one
[Music]
um
create tournament can you believe it's
like for me it's it's the tournament is
today it's less than 24 Hours Arena are
you ready
am I ready you know it is what it is I'm
gonna accept whatever it gets thrown at
me
oh uh what should we name the tournament
today now
um
wait wait we need wait we need to think
of a Combi name you know yeah we don't
have them no because like we're just
Hollow Birds but there's nothing
but everyone is a tory
that is true that is it's not specific
enough yeah
[Laughter]
there's oh let me tell can I tell you
some Idol nerd talk otakutak oh yes of
course I'm a big fan of this uh
um Idol agency called hello project
um you know them
yeah I've heard of them but not much and
they they they had I mean they had their
main groups and then they had some
groups that are like they they were not
that popular and then there was this
group that they called
um I think
and then
so okay for everyone who doesn't know in
Japanese like kako is is the the
brackets on the side the what do you
call them in English uh yeah brackets
yeah brackets and then Katie is like
um it's like temporary only for now like
it's implying as if they would still
change the name of that Idol group
eventually and uh so they started uh
making you know they're doing their Idol
activities making some songs and they
had this lame name with like up up girls
temporary and you thought they would
change it eventually but no until the
end like even after 10 years years they
never changed the name
yeah it just kept on being like a
working title temporary working title
I thought that was kind of like sad but
it made them stand out somehow it's it's
it's stylized in a way you know yeah
yeah we can be like that too hold on let
me just uh yeah I sent you the the code
uh
yes
[Music]
I think um
please wait
sure okay okay I'm changing the code
once I see you in on the map I'll change
the code on my side
okay
we can do searching for players we can
do it
oh you're building a show
yes yes
okay I'm gonna show the code to um once
you show it it's okay you can show it
now
okay bam guys and then I'm finished with
the game this is me it's so cute it has
a like a duck beak
okay
so cute
did you make that yourself
yeah I made it
get some the yellow lips and then
something else uh I overlapped something
else I never looked that closely at the
options that you can do when making a me
ah me too me too like somebody made a
baby rainy with like so they made a
friend a pacifier
I saw the baby Elena yesterday
oh cute it's so cute everybody oh here
they are oh there you go um what do you
want which one do you want
like we really have a choice
uh during the tournament too right yeah
leave it up yeah yeah yeah leave it up
to uh Destiny RNG
okay okay are we gonna be quiet are we
gonna be quiet
we could do a quiet run yeah you want to
try it stay quiet
sure sure
it's so hard
to stay quiet though I basically just
couldn't stop talking
just no I'll try today just
just being quiet not saying just just
breathing just breathing okay
our our uh we can't even exchange
emotions for our like uh like eye eyes
not even yes just it's okay we can't do
telepathy yeah telepathy yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
no that doesn't count laughing doesn't
count
[Music]
creepy
and Mommy I swear I I only got mushrooms
I swear
it wasn't me wait there were three
people at the Finishing Line did you see
if they were just not driving did they
get kicked out
I don't know maybe they had to go to the
bathroom
[Music]
was that you no no no no no no no no no
I didn't I trust you we should talk
right now whatever let's just talk yeah
I know I don't really care it's not so
awkward this is all crap I'm like trying
to not talk oh my God [\h__\h] what is that
we don't have that much like we don't we
don't do that many we didn't do any
collabs recently so we should I know
that's what I realized talk yeah yeah
true true I was really happy like after
yesterday I was like wait I just
realized that we don't even like talk
that much yeah right and then I was like
yeah I was actually really really happy
yeah oh God
I'm eight I'm last basically
oh it's fun oh that's fun it's Mario
Party
no problem yeah but I already I mean I
already told my viewers yesterday
um that we're doing a horotori garlic
phone collapse oh yes yes yes I'm
excited for that oh wait is the game
waiting for the others uh maybe I'm
gonna wait for them
I don't know
there's like three people waiting there
or four people even uh okay okay
communication error let's go
oh
yeah I'm looking I got kicked out of the
tournament as well oh God okay you too
right
um no I don't oh you're still like I
don't
I am still in um should we no no can you
re-enter
see this is how the whole tournament
will be like probably
hold on though for the tournament at
least we can join by friends so yeah yes
something
I'll mess
please let me in
let me in
can you enter
no so search is currently spectating get
ready who am I expecting oh at least at
least no no no no no no no no where
should I get out
no no no don't worry about it
wait is this okay
um I have a full group here you know
what let's so let's race so both uh once
without each other
okay yeah sure of course your race is
already starting is it no it's not
started yet
but you're you have a full group of
people
he asked I can't count but
approximately okay let's let's at least
we're in voice chat together we're
collabing in voice chat yeah we're
collabing in voice chat true true true
true okay okay yeah yes yes even though
we're separated and courses we'll still
together in the VC yeah together in our
hearts together
yes
ten nine where are you what are you
doing now we are gonna be doing Mount
Wario
wait I want to do Mount Wario I think
we're I think we're doing Rainbow Road
or something I and I actually enjoy
Mount Wario Man so many Europeans never
mind we're doing the airport thing oh oh
have fun already yeah I wish you the
best
yes we're gonna travel
since we're oh [\h__\h] we're actually
arrivals in the tournament so I don't
know why I'm so exciting to you
no it's fine it's kind of like you know
those animes you know like oh yeah we're
Rivals let's just do our best and
motivate each other that kind of thing
you know very spicy right
you know we can't be friendly towards me
oh okay I'm sure okay yeah because
[Music]
companion yeah sure don't be me we're
fellow Hollow toys we may be rivals in
the tournament but after that we're
Hollow Tories forever you know
yes
yes I just tried the shortcuts and I
failed miserably no no
I'm gonna be doing shortcuts
oh um if if possible guess oh sometimes
it's like I want to but I can't because
somebody's blocking me or something
why you do this to me why you do this to
me why you so mean
don't be mean to Kiara everybody
I didn't want to take this route okay
okay
[Music]
what happened
I forgot about another shortcut that I
wanted I love tourism
what
politori Taurus
[Music]
oh I just got lightning uh in midair and
I fell into the sea Elena you know what
I was thinking about yesterday uh what
I was thinking I want to do a magnet
song cover reveal
oh Magna the Vocaloid song
can we sing
I'm not sure well yeah that's the thing
that's the thing
we'll make it happen right now
oh well okay we can we can check we can
check you know I'm like down for like
whatever okay
Phoenix friends but because you have
such a beautiful singing voice oh guys
no that's true we haven't done we
haven't done any any covers together
that needs to change we should and
magnet is such a classic for a Duo it is
it is it is okay
um how do we get together again
I will try to join you
I will try to join um I'm probably too
slow now
guys don't join join Dana's race please
don't join
oh God it's taking too long already
um wanna create a new one no no
I'll make it inside
[Laughter]
why does it make you choose your stupid
character every time before you go in
how how is it how's it looking searching
for players
there's a there's a person here called
buttress I don't know what
I don't know
no I'm expecting no no
wait I don't know let's see if it's
really uh if it's really mine
uh the spectating one that one is not
ill no I don't see you
I think no I think it would be faster if
we just like make a new one no no well
you're SP instead of like watching
instead of spectating you can make a new
room and I'll rejoin no I feel bad
though you feel like sitting here you're
doing nothing for like two races you
know what I'll I'll join a random uh
palanashi tournament race and
since you're racing right now too
yeah I mean Meadows
fun too even when we're not in the same
race
yeah yeah it's okay our hearts are
connected together even though we're not
in the same race this is so sad oh
apparently there's 3 000 people trying
to get in so yeah the chances are pretty
low
oh no oh who are these people
who are these people trying to get in
the way just kidding
oh I mean we could also race against
NPCs but I just feel like they're not
strong enough and now we're really need
um strong opponents to practice
yeah I feel like you know even with hard
NPCs just do you feel good because oh
you're always like first or second but
you know it doesn't reflect how the
races will be at all yeah yeah
it's so true oh my God stupid cows sorry
[Music]
banana make hollow Tony proud one of us
one of us has to get into the winners
camp
I know I know I know one of the horror
toys who else is in is tomorrow with us
right she she is right and Julie also is
yeah Louis was with us
yeah he's with us too yeah at least at
least one whole lot toy representative
needs to go to the pro cup stupid
lightning
okay
[Music]
is cute but when she's driving
[Laughter]
my butt is covered by a turtle shell
though
and then I Must Destroy it you must
destroy it and that's all violent but
please have mercy okay my race is done
should we just um what should we do your
race is starting
it's done it's done it's just finished
yeah it says for me currently spectating
but I'm still like I'm not looking at
anyone yet uh
wait
yeah I know
um oh God uh should we I I I should I
make a new one or should you make it you
make a new one maybe okay I'll make a
new one can you understand okay okay
[Music]
waste time Nintendo
do you want to join my old room or uh
maybe I should create a totally new one
I'll try I'll try okay
oh my God
way to please
hide the game screen okay
okay let me try this um
did you come from who the hell are you
these are random here
there we go I'm gonna try to join my own
room
because I'm already in and I showed it
on screen
you can do this
please people people joining uh
what oh no I don't see you I was so
awesome my fault oh no I don't see you
no no no no no no no
I don't even see the seams okay dude I'm
sorry I'm gonna make a new one
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm gonna create a
tournament okay I'm gonna delete JJ A
New Hope okay goodbye JJJ a new hope it
is time to die
it is time to die how long are you
planning to race though
um
maybe one more hour maybe yeah me too we
need rest we need rest yeah I need a
long nap in between
and then it's also Amy's birthday today
slash tomorrow depending on your time
zone
um
and I want to call into her stream for
that
what time is it
uh her stream is at midnight for me so
for you you how how far are you behind
Jail's team
um like two okay then it would be six
a.m for you I think
uh okay the same time as last year I
think maybe yeah maybe I think I'ma
usually streams around that time roughly
oh
my birthday
she's getting uh 78 years old yeah yeah
78 years old yeah she's very old
help people
wait you're older no no no I'm his old
grandma
okay wait which purple nurse is it oh oh
there it is there we go how did you make
it with the same name yeah that is very
confusing no but it has like a different
it has a different icon ah
okay I am in I hope you are you can join
me okay as long as you don't show it's
anyone yet no I haven't I haven't shown
I haven't shown any clap right now
are you ready
getting very close to the third lab
okay I'm gonna I'm gonna stretch while I
wait for you
I'm so stupid
no you're not stupid let's go redeem
that first place yes I mean I had some
lucky races today where I got a I got
seconds twice today against viewers
that's nice
all right let's hope the luck carries
over tomorrow let's hope for the best I
just want to be placed in the middle of
Arena because I don't wanna I don't
wanna go to another cup you know
if you want to go back to sleep you want
to go back to sleep okay
very motivated
they're not gonna scream right you're
not gonna scream yeah I'm not I'm not
going to
um during the teams
and then if I don't get and then I'll
end stream if I don't get in any of the
cups I'm gonna end stream right there
my race is done
I will join you now sorry also to the
viewers for for doing all this uh
um switching and changing rooms I'm
sorry guys
yeah
now hopefully I will not be kicked out
of the tournament anymore and then we
can stay in the same one for a while
hopefully okay so it's um
[Music]
huh
what are you munching on
I'm rocky road I'm sweet oh is that
chocolate
yeah chocolate with marshmallows and
almond and stuff
oh I think I've heard of that before is
that the originally American sweet so
what is that where is that from baby
maybe maybe I don't know where it's from
it might be
[Music]
um
do I see you I see yeah
is the code everybody
okay
[Music]
it tastes so true yes okay I'm gonna
show the game now it's British
apparently well it's British I see
[Music]
yes yes yes yes
Rocky Road sounds like a Mario Kart
course chassis true
get on to my level right now
so sad hold on
ridiculous oh my God
that's going to Valley
British valley girl yes the British
Valley Girl
so how do they say yes if they're
British
wait do British people say something
do they prefer to say something else
besides yes chat
behind us
where the me blindness looks like oh
yeah yeah the blonde one
yeah a Cheerio
oh sorry I keep on forgetting
it is
it is an army parody it is
let's go
[Music]
you know I I bet this is gonna get
chosen I feel like you know somebody's
gonna try to choose this course so on
purpose to trigger everybody else
oh God stop don't hit me
that was too fast
fell off the track
oh
wait for me everybody
[Music]
oh
hi
oh are you there
wait what is this look
no I didn't do anything what
what there's a freaking stupid banana
right like at the shortcut of rainbow
road that's so evil like whoever did
that
No Bananas allowed they should be banned
from the rainbow world I know No Bananas
in the house
[Music]
oh come on
catch up good job kiwala not mayonnaise
[Music]
dude
okay okay okay okay okay
which place we know you seem to be
pretty fun one second what
how are you second I got lucky that's
what happened oh
that's the only explanation it's Mario
Kart
[Music]
oh come on give me Bullet Bill no I want
the fullest
[Applause]
oh I fell
Watson
oh my God
but I mean I have to say this is not not
exactly
my fault like a lot of this is really
bad luck
[Music]
oh my God
all of those
those Stars well no won't help me where
does that go
by following someone else and it
actually worked but then I didn't know
where to go from there
[Applause]
but you know where it is right no not
really
okay I just followed someone into the
void
um
have you been using it
yeah yeah I always use it
let me take take my hand Arena and show
me
I would please don't choose baby parks
that shortcut too I need to learn it
that okay I'll try to learn that one oh
off screen
yeah do it do it okay that one should be
worth it not last at least yeah after
all that
how am I not last
yeah I chose big blue too thank you
thank you
oh yeah I want to do big blue
eyes
with the straightened hair
okay well is that you
she has a fierce eyebrows
fierce
hmm
oh my God wait my Dude Looks Like a Bird
too
oh you're right
it looks so angry though what happened
um
[Music]
yeah yay do I remember the shortcut ah
better Kiana
oh no let's see about that we'll see
who's better
okay I'll Focus Focus time
okay let's focus let's get it kicked
their butt okay
[Music]
what happened
it's getting bullied
okay I can still catch up
now
I got bullied I can't believe it
[Music]
ah I always ah
I never take a sharp enough turn
I managed to do one shortcut but it
didn't help me much
[Music]
hello
where are you behind you okay better
chiaras right in front of me oh I see
her get out of the way
get him get him get him get him
hahaha
trying to wake you
up
[Music]
oh
account forth
where is better Kiana that's all that
matters
oh
[Music]
thank you
nice nice nice nice
[Music]
okay that was an interesting race
that was interesting
I'm using films you are the better QR
are you taking the controls thank you
um
controls what do you mean you can
control when you're tilted wow
I'm so sad I always I don't know my
Mario Kart streams I always get mad at
so many things me too me too I need to
control my aggressions a bit more yeah
you know it's kind of like you know hey
um you know I have to control uh not
show my PDA too much you know public
display of aggression do you see that
pecora
where oh God
oh God what is that you look disgust
no
dude
oh
no there's also another one with like a
grinning oh yeah that one looks funny
it's stairs trained to your soul are you
guys trying to create a horror movie or
something
[Laughter]
go easy on me get out of here get out of
here
hammer shark it does look a little bit
like a
good hammer shark with pickled up
okay you guys are crazy crazy which one
which one do you want to go with
um I'm awful at Animal Crossing so let's
do it oh up to you though Toad Harbor is
also pretty I chose Twisted magic okay
um okay RNG Orange
people really like Animal Crossing huh
uh yeah it came up in this morning's
tournament not tournament I mean YouTube
[Music]
what was your placement
awful my placement is awful that's what
it is part of it right
um yeah oh it's easy Senpai so it's the
same fight was also in there
yeah she was in there uh Elena I'm
telling you there's nothing you really
about a cup where uh so you stay and
told us Empire
I mean at least you know
um the intention is what matters right
tournaments you do
it might be YouTube for them you know
hello it's like their breakfast and
foreign
yes healthy healthy breakfast I kept
getting so bad items like I you know
mushrooms
oh I didn't get items I was doing so
well
no stupid quota get the hell out of my
face
I mean my back I guess
[Music]
I'll see my items fake you know
wow I survived this without items
Beach there's something called beachy
oh God
of course I got mushrooms
what happened with Waluigi
I don't know
[Music]
[Applause]
oh shoot
[Music]
we like a good items now that I'm 12.
did you guys see me cutting those uh
roads short did you see that chat
are you proud of me
spicy
I'm getting I'm playing the game a
little bit risky now
[Music]
oh no blue shell oh I'm gonna have a
different brush there
laughs
[Applause]
[Music]
what the hell
no
it's okay I got caught on like right in
front of the Finish Line no big deal
why don't we always end up at the bottom
it's not fair
uh I don't know item RNG it is what it
is I think
it's not fair it is what it is Chad you
must agree I did better than that you
saw it you saw it I did not deserve that
treatment thank you
God gotcha luck I cut the curves and
what do I get for it hmm bottom boots
yeah
totally not the driving see we have chat
support
and one of them looks like a taco boxes
[Music]
is the child
the smaller sister
okay let's go everybody let's go okay
let's go let's go
[Music]
okay then then count down
I used to be so scared of the Bowser map
and I thought it was so difficult but
now nowadays I like it actually nowadays
um I realized there are uh much worse
Maps out there yeah yeah I don't hate it
as much yeah
[Music]
Royal Raceway what have you been uh up
to recently anyway you gotta update me
on your life
oh this whole week I've been streaming
Mario Kart and Mario Kart only
before that before that that's a that's
an interesting question meaning that the
objection game ah yes yes uh I play that
every Saturday I'm gonna play that this
week too do you like the objection the
objection okay
I I have the game for the DS I think but
I never played it I was always
interested in this though okay okay yeah
I mean like I like those kind of games
it's kind of like my favorite genre so
oh
um look at if you look at my screen I'm
taking a very like unorthodox approach
and pathfinding oh yeah you're driving
against the wall
I'm trying to find secret walls hidden
somewhere oh yeah something like that
well in Mario games there's always some
secret uh yeah
all right right absolutely look at me
look at me look at me in the mini map
oh so sad
oh man
[Music]
once again back to the bottom after I've
seen the top
playing daisy these people are now
trying to
show me some cool tricks with their own
daisies cool tricks
[Music]
oh blue shell
who
spawned that blue shell
oh
[Music]
I'm fifth at the moment
oh I see you
[Music]
[\h__\h]
what happened I had to forcefully remove
my [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] God I got Blue Shield admitted
that's the worst
[Music]
all right it was nice
oh there you are
oh God please
[Music]
wait you're the Bullet Bill no no no no
never mind you're the one in front of me
there's so many is
together
we're always together though
we do that
I don't know
why are there so many daisies I feel
like I want to change into Daisy we're
connected
they're just trying to copy me stupid
copycats they realize Daisy is is the
real yeah
yes the new Waluigi yeah yeah it's so
boring everybody's using Waluigi and
that other weird whatever I don't know
the name I think you have it are you
talking about Roy yeah
it's okay Kiara just because you don't
have the car doesn't mean you have to
say something like that
so true
[Laughter]
you roasted me but she's so right it's
okay we're still best friends right he
is best friends forever is that good out
or what that's so cute
baby rainy I think oh baby now wow
oh I can I can uh
on my screen baby Rainey was socializing
with you so cute oh
Fried Chicken
where's my bubble Pop
where's baby Kiara
I put on my pacifier
too
but I will try my best
[Music]
friend
we want to play what you want to play
please
[Music]
Barbie
Mommy
um
they have to go into the corner for a
time now
[Music]
they have to wear
um
[Music]
I don't I don't I don't I mean mushrooms
he's like Uno parts and people hated me
so much for doing the bubble bubble but
I don't give a [\h__\h] I bubble the [\h__\h]
out of you this is how you uh separate
the wheat wheat wheat from the non-weeds
I don't know how to say that
yeah I get what you mean it's natural
selection
[Music]
on your baby Wing is more powerful maybe
I need to change your way please
she's because she still has that youth
energy you know oh no what are you
implying Kiara
we are we are very very old old Boomer
Boomers
I know for real though my back really
hurts all right
it does my back hurts my back hurts oh
it's because it's because you're covered
you're carrying all that
um
I'm trying to say what am I trying to
say I'm trying to say that you are so
amazing uh yes you were trying to carry
um all of the Charisma and yeah no no
I'm not trying to say Boba no no no I
really just can't articulate myself the
way I want to yeah like you know like oh
the pressure for tomorrow's tournament
and every I get what you're trying to
say right right right
not quite I'll tell you later
oh okay you gotta tell me in the DM I
see how it is I will be waiting for your
DM
okay well what should we choose
I'm gonna choose music part because your
voice is like music to my ears no I hate
music Fork but I don't um I like your
actions of a Music Park for you
um yes
occurred
I'm still in you just fell out of it but
I'm alone with one more person oh come
on okay
I'm dropping out too what you're
dropping out yeah yeah I on purpose I'm
going back in uh
you're going to the same one
yes I'm going to say I'm searching for
players right now okay I'm coming I'm
coming
okay
[Music]
I wonder if there's a higher chance of
getting communication everywhere when
you're on Wi-Fi because in my bedroom
where I'll be playing for the tournament
I'll be on Wi-Fi I wonder if that's a
bad idea what do you think I'm always on
Wi-Fi oh
what is this group of people you're not
in here but it looks like I'm not in
here are you a communication error has
occurred I I I can't get in again
I can't get it I'm sorry
wait how do you how do you connect your
ethernet cable to the switch
option you can you gotta buy an extra
adapter that you attach to the switch
because the switch does not have an
ethernet cable port
the
the dock doesn't have it either it
doesn't
you have to buy an adapter yeah because
that's what I thought and then
I bought one ages ago after like I
remember I wanted to do a a collab with
vatama Senpai
um and then we realized oh my God on
Wi-Fi it's literally impossible for me
to get together in the same room
so I was like where can I put in the
cable the internet cable but yeah it
didn't have a slot so I had to buy one
and the collab was postponed
oh that dog has an Ethernet port wait
but if I haven't if I have an OLED dog
ah but then I'll have to buy an outlet
switch yes I would say just get a the
USB adapter
no but then like if you do that you
can't play docs right
oh but maybe maybe for the OLED the dog
has the ethernet cable thing slot not
the I'm not sure but look at those oh
let dogs oh OLED dog works with old
switch
maybe I'll just buy I hope somebody
uh I don't know I hope somebody uh will
sell it why would you just buy the dog
that's come on also I'm stuck spectating
no I'm stuck don't quit oh God I'm gonna
quit I'm so sad
I miss you I miss you too
[Music]
did you have many connection errors or
no
no not at all actually okay how many
races did you do
um so we had like so one section one cup
is like four races right so we had that
for the preliminaries and then we had
two times of red and blue and then we
had
and then we had some other type of team
Race and then another cup of codeine
race for the last time so it was like
two hours
yeah it sounds like fun
sounds like fun
yes yes oh USB 2 ethernet plugs onto the
dock oh I see
[Music]
I'm I'm in the wrong Lobby again
oops
I'm in the wrong lobby as well I think
because these oh yeah oh by the way I
need to tell you we got I uh I did so
terribly that in the one of the last
races it was like a race each team
consists of three people it was Ohio and
me and uh thanks to me we got a terrible
score but we scored 69.
nice too yeah I just wanted to say that
somebody reminded me on chat
oh
no
why do I keep getting the wrong
my opinion just ended up shoot dang it
[Music]
um
I don't know well I'm getting out yeah
I'm gonna mute my voice on stream
let's go to a different tournament
now we have so many tournaments that we
can choose from
right
there
I'm hiding the screen okay do they hear
me on your side
what
oh I'm not muted
[Laughter]
don't worry can they read lips
caught in 48 KH set
die job one day now
oh wait a minute
I'm using you too did I mute I made a
desktop instead of myself I know I
understand okay okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
new code everybody I'm gonna paste it
now yes me too
okay
numbers
I want to do donut planes because I suck
at Turtle please and thank you is really
good at donut playing so we gotta be
good at so we gotta be decent okay I saw
some sick shortcuts for donut planes so
hard to pull off though
chat is muted no no one's muted anymore
everybody is free to speak
I would never never
mute the chat
in's voices
freedom of speech Yes
freedom of speech
or are you guys coming oh you know with
a beard no oh
okay okay it's an intimate race okay
turn on the sexy music
[Music]
Power Rangers we have all different
colors
what what crime
Taco
Taco's boyfriend
is that Shaggy as it is Shaggy is that
shaggy yeah get out of here Shaggy
get out of here you don't deserve it
oh by the way uh chat I already I
already saw also Elena maybe you would
like it too I already saw cronies
kimono I like it so much oh really she
looks so gorgeous everyone I didn't see
anybody yeah because there is not
happening yet counselors
privately
[Music]
nice the council is getting it one week
later and then Iris will be getting it
eventually
oh okay I hope maybe maybe maybe next
year or so
Indonesia can get it too
yeah me too I hope so too okay I want to
see you enough
yeah I mean now if you want to see him
in a kimono you can see the Mario Kart
exactly
but yeah hopefully we do get a real one
yes
pray everybody
for everybody everybody needs a kimono
in their life oh
it's so peaceful without
a full 12 people race on rainbows
peaceful oh peaceful oh
is it already ending oh no
oh that was fast yeah yeah like this
course is really fast
oh yes
I fell Shaggy too to the void he's
Shaggy with you know oh thank you for
that intimate race now it's time for new
people to come in here what a shame what
a shame
what a shame he says wait that those
those two people of the of the of the
haircuts uh
[Music]
the yellow one is from something else
I'm not sure
the right one is right
yeah did you watch Naruto
no not at all I just know like some of
the characters
me too me too
yellow ones from Despicable Me are you
being serious are you guys being serious
or are you trolling and then they're
trolling
apparently it's Rock Lee from what Enter
the Dragon instead of movie
broccoli
oh man
okay
literally okay I'm literally okay
ruining right now
I like
Japanese speak
Japanese beer what about California
oh I don't know how this is me
they're just Valley girls here okay
I can do that
oh no did you do that I don't like this
rainbow room because I I fall off the
the clip so often
ah
The Edge I mean
[Music]
there we go there we go
oh no oh no what happened oh nothing
nothing nothing
just trying my best out here
okay
damn
[Music]
number two everybody
oh thank you for that thank you number
three everybody
okay
everybody
[Music]
what are you counting how often I'm
falling down okay
[Music]
that was close
nothing helps anymore at this point
nothing they're all so far away oh no
there's a Bullet Bill
[Music]
oh thank God
oh yeah okay
[Music]
oh thank you oh
[Applause]
you did pretty well there
thank you oh my God I didn't fall as
much
just don't fall
yeah like I feel like you know even if
you got the course down if somebody just
knocks you off a little bit like your
drifting's gonna be off and everything
it's just like
and I think space items are actually
pretty difficult to use there
when I use them I get too fast and then
I fall off the edge again yeah it's not
your fault if you're too fast already
yeah yeah speed Phoenix can't help me
right what do we want
I don't know Stadium
I chose ice ice
okay okay because there's a very like
tricky shortcut and you can if you can
nail it if you will help I think
breakfast it's today
but nice I forgot I already forgot which
one it was ah oh if it gets chosen we
can both try for it yeah okay
what a funny face
what a funny which one the one on the
very right the black one
the black one oh yeah I see it
oh
my course oh Ice Ice Baby
[Laughter]
oh no worse they admit their defeat I
like that respect
respect I respect where's Kiara
[Music]
admitting your mistakes is the first
step to get better we say that in German
I don't know how you say that in English
wait
is that not how you say it in English no
please don't
talk to you unfortunately ah I
I didn't do it I tried it and I realized
too late
did you make it
um I didn't complete a full one so it's
like a 75
no that was pretty good I'll take that I
didn't fall nice leaning nice and I said
I'll I'll try there's another one oh I'm
too late for that one though
I'm too late for that one there's a
second one at the end
so I'm gonna try that next lap
what happened I'm just
I've been around oh no
oh no now that I'm tense am I gonna
finally get good items
okay oh we're so close
where are you 12.
no it's okay one plus two is three
uh-huh
so I mean I don't know math
that's not for you how do I how do I get
the second shortcut I wonder do I have
to like drift early
I'll try again I'll try again
no I keep on missing coins and items
no I keep missing
well if we're so far behind we might as
well try
it yeah
there's like this
uh-huh I can you know the first shortcut
where there's two ramps I can go over
the first round but not the second one
[Music]
hmm
it doesn't even matter
where is
we're here
where are you who
where's where's Kiara I wonder
[Music]
[Laughter]
bonding yeah we were saying behind the
Finishing Line just hanging out she was
waiting for me thank you
that's when you know where's Kiara a
real homie in the end we're all Kiana's
yes
it's like
[Music]
hey hello everybody
[Laughter]
[Music]
so please become oh my God
what I'm not a God I'm just followed
don't call me God that's more than I
deserve
I don't understand what you're saying
damn it
oh I don't understand subtitling
yeah that's what everybody says look at
okay what is this okay
oh no
Bubba
bubble oh no I forgot
[Music]
are you sure you should be saying that
oh no I keep not getting items
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
I keep missing the items so sad you know
me too I I keep on missing other things
like curves
I don't know how much do that on this
map
[Music]
that was close
oh there's a cold out there
[Applause]
[Music]
is blindly throwing my items around
oh no
oh so forth
wow
it's okay
I did so awful this morning it is okay I
think Mario Kart's fitting me I I used
to do better too
yeah it's no I know things like baby
part is
such a huge mess like everybody's
throwing around items it's just a short
uh of course like everyone's cuddling
with one another yeah yeah I was so
lucky like the first few laps um I got a
quarter behind me but somebody else ends
up getting it it's only the last part
that I got hit so I was like wow
the gods of Mario Karts are protecting
me for today oh Spiderman did you see
him the new Spider-Man movie I didn't
see it yet oh I did I did I did oh
really was it good
oh it was real good you have to see I
mean if you like Spider-Man even if
you're just like a casual fan uh you
should I am a casual fan I think I only
I only watched Spider-Man once so I
would have to First Watch Spider-Man 2 I
think
ah okay okay I watched like a few like
there's a really good animated one um I
think it's got into the spider-verse or
something oh
yeah there's like an animated movie it's
really cool and I like animation so I
thought it was really cool
[Music]
I back I I basically have not barely
like I have barely seen any any
um Marvel movies to begin with I don't
know any Marvel movies
oh okay okay I just casually watch it
you know
um I just watch it when I can like it's
not like I'm a super big fan but you
know I feel like I just need to watch it
you know because everybody watches it
and it's good anyways [\h__\h]
okay
oh no I missed that item box
[Music]
hey KR hi
what are you doing here
the racing
didn't I distract you with my people I
don't know
number one for a little while
oh it's okay you know um if you get good
RNG you can change the world the world
being this course yes I'm coming back
I'm coming back
okay okay
uh okay okay okay
[Music]
oh shoot I pressed the wrong thing and
I'm gonna uh
what happened
down even though that was really
unnecessary
okay come on focus focus
[Music]
that'll show how good I am
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
oh nice
thank you for not hitting me
Bullet Bill
[Music]
ow I got chilled
that's awful
foreign
[Music]
yeah and then I'll stop some more
privately and then sleep and then go to
Amir and then tournament oh my God
[Music]
um
no don't worry no no it's okay it's okay
it's okay we'll do our best in the
tournament
doing
New
Year
[Music]
I'm also scared no the thing is you know
um Group D like everyone's skill level
is like very very Like Anything Can
Happen basically yeah because everyone's
skill level is really close to Anything
Can Happen yeah that might be yeah
that's just because it makes you you
know it's not a group too right and I
would like to keep up with Ina as well
mm-hmm
yes
yeah oh my gosh somebody's called
zakotato
oh
okay I everyone everyone wanted Grumble
Volcano but we are in the opposite in an
ice world
ice World We Know
[Music]
we need to cool down
no like from from what happened this
morning like even like say uh you think
uh probably like oh we got some really
strong people in the JP park over at G
team yes that is true but also those
same people sometimes they get even 11
you know so it's just a really really
orangey Reliance yeah I'm hoping for
their bad luck
hahaha
I think that's violin I hope Donuts
place never gets chosen
oh God I don't have a problem of donut
planes but for your sake I will hope it
won't get chosen too no no it's like I
don't really have a problem with it
either but there's somebody really
really good at donut planes
uh it's money Central
oh mine isn't Fun she probably got all
the shortcuts down huh yeah no yeah the
thing is like with donut planes it's not
just even if you know the shortcut it's
kind of difficult to pull off
that's why I'm like
[Music]
I got a traumatic experience today it's
understandable
[Music]
so yeah
oh no
but hey uh oh never mind I was about to
say I'm not doing it
I gave up on the shortcuts here I gave
up on the shortcut too
I'm not gonna get it yes kick their
butts
let's go
[Music]
Donkey Kong I will destroy your life and
your family
no no no no no no no no no no no
I couldn't drift at the end but okay
that was a good placement
what the
I hope man I got the shortcut down once
and it was like yeah
so powerful wow I hope we'll get I hope
both of us will get lucky tomorrow
is that a green Mario because it doesn't
look like Luigi
wait what oh that's like I don't know
Mario and Luigi's together yeah a child
both people yes
say something so I can say your name say
something green Mario there's something
green so we can know your name oh my God
Ina with a butt in her face
[Laughter]
what in her face wait are we looking at
the same thing oh I see it at the back
[Music]
oh no
buttface is it a trend because I saw
some uh the exact same face with Iris
though today what no I don't think it's
a trend at least I never heard of it
it's not a trend
watch chat be like you know if it's not
Trend let's make one no what's the name
oh yeah ah just um
[Music]
okay
I see okay
[Music]
okay
like that to idols
yeah what is that why are we on rainbow
road again why I don't know I'm so sick
of rainbow roll
oh they have their butts protected Ouija
has their butts protected I can't accept
this
protected butts
[Music]
[Applause]
behind me oh why am I scared
oh no I was too scared to use my
mushrooms already so now I lost them no
I lost my quota too so sad very very sad
this too
I like the music for rainbow road though
it's really peaceful unlike the track
[Music]
I don't want to use it yet too much too
much
[Music]
oh yes somebody spawned a blue shell so
good
oh yeah
[Music]
perfect timing
yeah this is where the shortcut is
awesome
okay let's round
last laugh
oh God that's awful
[Music]
bats died into the last round I know
I mean it could have been worse you know
[Music]
could have been Sheldon like mid-air or
something true true
oh God pink positive gram what are the
chances that just happened to me
oh God yeah okay I'm gonna play so bad
now because I lost my rhythm
accident
Chad I did not know what I was doing
there I just kind of believed in it
believe it believe him
[Music]
what place are you uh just eight because
I messed up at the end but I I
accidentally took two shortcuts without
knowing it
oh that's nice
make sure you got it down you can use it
in the home button I don't remember what
it is foreign
you can do it without any speed items
though right
um yeah yeah as long as you hit the
thing because I was using speed items
and I think that made it a lot easier
um can we say next one last one
yeah sure let's try let's aim for big
blue okay uh or not you know what I'll
go for swamp ruins because I had didn't
have that one yet today I think oh sure
okay
um
chat um you might want to watch out uh I
might
um
notify you guys on Twitter when I'm
playing privately if I open my
tournaments so I can have some people
practicing with me off screen as well
because it's better than practicing
against NPCs I think
yeah definitely definitely definitely
nice
practicing against people now the thing
is like I kind of want to climb the
worldwide rank so we have like you know
the ratings and everything but I kind of
don't like the fact that you know we
always get 100 cc in the early ranks or
something I want to do 150. oh
Mr squeaks
is there oh wait it is from who I'm
Bruins
yay oh it's been so long I don't
I haven't done this one in a long time
don't remember it at all
[Music]
right or left here chat hmm everybody
else is going left okay
save some of the coins for me was that a
shortcut
wait where oh that looks like a short
time bananas
oh my God delicious points good
[Music]
oh nice music on this map nice music
no no no no no no
no no
it's so medieval
uh-huh he's cool [\h__\h]
I'll try this oh
oh God Australia
oh no [\h__\h] I didn't dodge that void
excuse me
[Music]
so scared
you don't have to pull me back that far
[Music]
then
you don't miss my father
I dodged two Thunders nine I didn't
notice that shell though dang it
nice
yes yes yes yes
ah too late though that's fine
holy crap that was so lucky I dodged two
thunders in a match what I had that
before too yeah when I think I dodged
like two or three funders with but
because I always got a star like one
millisecond before the fun day that was
so lucky oh that's so lucky yeah
wanna try electrodrome or something I
don't know um
or bone dry Dunes I didn't have today
yet either I think
my scheduled nap is starting in one hour
oh
yeah
um but it's okay uh if I uh nap a little
bit later I won't be able to fall asleep
right away anyway how long does it take
you to fall asleep Elena do you have a
problem too to fall asleep man lately
yes because
um I because I don't have much time
right so the only free time for me to
like watch YouTube videos or stuff is
when I'm in bed I'm preparing for bill
so I always end up watching YouTube
videos of like I don't know just YouTube
videos in bed that's it so it takes a
while for me to fall asleep like
probably one two hours
oh
dude for me if last game is so good that
I guess that's why there is the last
game too
we'll rock it but they never believe in
yourself
believe in yourself
Supremacy wait Ouija and bowtracts have
you guys not been here a little bit too
long too often YouTube
to the usual room afterwards I think
this is like your food race or something
I'm not
oh where is he what he's what is he
trying he's trying uh I see what he's
doing he's doing the aqua sent by
strategy
well what awkward sent by Strat he went
all the way back I saw him going
backwards to get good
yeah yeah like with becoming getting to
the 12th Place and then getting a super
dope item
yeah
wow don't face
that works out for you
do do
[Music]
that was monkey
monkey
[Music]
I am a monkey but you know you are a
monkey I realized when I panic I
absolutely sound like a monkey
oh yeah don't we all
do you
yeah
[Laughter]
I didn't realize that rainy it's
embarrassing oh [\h__\h]
it's like when you when you scream in
panic right yeah
I could do a good monkey impression
okay Hollow monkeys yay
and then literally have every member in
it
ow I think that was me should we be in
DK jungle then oh dang it
now that I'm in eighth place will I
probably get something good hopefully
yes oh
[Music]
okay oh yes oh yes oh yes oh yes yes yes
yes
[Music]
why am I still put yourself in this
misery misery
[Music]
I was fine I guess
I wanna end on the high note
okay okay okay
wall hugging yes wall is best friend
dragon driftway is really difficult why
what's this I don't know let's do dragon
Drift Lane
okay because also didn't practice this
one today yet I think yeah this one is
really really difficult okay um are you
gonna leave Luigi or what
uh I'm gonna leave or what
I'm gonna kick him out
and you can
no no was there another oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
I don't know how
um
[Music]
bye I'm trying to tell him
thank you for playing
read the airplanes
you should we should leave
they're doing it they're doing me was
telling him off yeah
game starting ah
this is like your fifth race or so
you don't follow the Mario Kart manners
what why
why Mamma Mia
oh we have some NPCs in here
yeah we got two as if there weren't
already enough people waiting outside of
the room to join
um
[Music]
maybe it could be could also not be
maybe no because I think like sometimes
that looks like a real person driving
yeah okay what what
[Music]
we didn't even get dragon dressed when
everyone was voting for it
oh my God speed
sure
oh no your banana
[Music]
I am getting
F's here
[Music]
foreign
are you freaking serious
[Music]
oh well I guess at least that's where I
get spawns
where I get response you know I was
trying to like
[Applause]
oh wow
what's up
[Music]
random burp sounds be like
is that you
[Music]
you punched me
nice
[Music]
[Applause]
anymore
so sad
[Laughter]
place you like it when your big mini
places
[Music]
hug and Shake Hands You're such good
friends
there's friends forever no best friends
forever thank you for wasting me with
vehicle customization I got a new
vehicle customization I'm gonna check it
out later of course you're not gonna
change it though because you're gonna
rely on The Meta aren't ya
all right
subscribe get out of here
laughs
[Laughter]
dad
oh that was fun
thank you
I'm gonna try to read um super chats for
like an hour uh or one and a half uh but
then I think I really need to go out get
some sleep to be ready for the
tournament and for amen you know
yeah and I'm probably gonna before I
sleep in bed I'm gonna practice a little
bit too but the good thing is that
um I uh I I can practice uh before like
in between
and the tournament I think I have a
couple of hours to practice as well like
two or three hours
um
yes we're still gonna read some Super
Chat is
thank you for coming by for hanging out
doing some fun races even though
Nintendo wanted us to be a part we still
ended up together just how it's supposed
to be
[Music]
on to my office we go
all right here we are I need to fix some
things sure to wait a minute
um
totally late
and now we're gonna turn on some BTM
um
I mean even even with the streaming
debuff like when I stream I I can focus
less even then I was doing
someone okayish in some races but I was
very unlucky most of the time now
mama
sure
[Music]
no
what what should we what should we do
let's do this one and this one
and now the chat yeah kiawa beatbox
and
Bang
[Music]
I hope a lot of people were able to join
I hope I hope uh you guys were able to
play together with me and Arena
hope it was enjoyable and we need to
read Super Chat starting off from
good question are the baby 's here I
stuff I turned off the super stickers
again I'm so sorry baby you I know you
like to send super stickers
[Music]
um
okay Mario Kart and then before the
devil I think we just have to read yeah
deaf Loop and then Mario Kart oh maybe I
can if I'm fast I think I could do it in
one and a half hours we could catch up
which is probably good considering
there's a outfit reveal soon
[Music]
bill will be the first one this time
I'm the top batter butter butter I'm not
sure if I'm
uh happy with that
makes me a bit nervous
[Music]
I think my my kimono is uh very safe
though I think I mean generally like if
when talking about kimonos generally I
think what you can expect is say so
image
um
yeah yeah I will not open this YouTube
channel although I don't think it will
be as bad as as the other outfit reveals
because you don't even because it's only
30 minutes reveal this time you don't
even have enough time to really build up
that big of an audience as
as usually with one hour reveals but
yeah I'll I'll just close the chat again
to make sure nothing happens
and but I'm also worried this makes me
nervous again
but nothing should nothing should happen
uh I guess could always
not that say so
um
but usually usually kimono is very safe
so
um
mine definitely is
foreign
outfits yeah I'm very very happy about
it
um
I must say uh uh for this for this
outfit for the kimono outfit I am
I I I I I guess I had a lot of input for
the hairstyle but uh uh I think for the
kimono itself like not that much but
hookah Papa did a great job anyway it
looks really really really pretty so
yeah look forward to it a beautiful say
so potential yeah do you guys know which
one is me from the silhouette
yeah I think everybody recognized it
mostly mostly the Silhouettes are very
recognizable
um I'm I'm the
that looks like she has twin Tails movie
when something else like wings but last
time you also thought it'd wear wings
and then it was not wings so
it could be anything guys
could be anything remember remember the
last silhouette you thought it was Tiny
Wings
but it wasn't it wasn't
the thing is
foreign
[Music]
let me actually put it up here this now
I think explains the the Sunday stream
yeah the Sunday stream I planned because
of these outfits and that's why it is on
Sunday because the outfits are on
Saturday night and the worms the worms
collab
um I mean it's partially because of our
new outfits but not really it was just
like we were planning the outfit relay
and uh no one mentioned anything about
the collab and then I was like hey um uh
so without new outfits maybe one or two
or three days after the relay we can do
uh we can do a worm school app on my
channel maybe and then they were like
yeah let's do it but it ended up
um being like added right after the
relay even though I didn't originally
intended to be like right after it but
yeah now we have five reviews and then
the worms collab on my channel 30
minutes after Cali's reveal yeah
yes yes so I think it will be a lot of
fun to collab together with our new
outfits yeah yeah and there might
maybe uh something exciting at that worm
school app but that's all I'm gonna say
so
hey
[Music]
um
Freddy is already kind of confirmed we
already have it but it's the question of
when we can use it merch
[Music]
who knows could be merch could be
could be something else
[Laughter]
oh don't worry I think you guys will be
um very very very very very very very
happy and
satisfied and
oh happy
okay I'm gonna read some super chats
let's get through this is
didn't you do a thing there where you um
had a different name for each super chat
but now you change it back to Java rxd
so every Super Chat just says general
raw XT for me you messed up you messed
up gero
Deborah rarick Steve thank you thank you
soon should I read this this is a one
two three four five
I'm doing you a favor don't wait okay
seeing you finally talking my favorite
genre of game I think your sniper skills
in Minecraft will serve you welcome back
to you I mean who could possibly stand
against the girl who took down the Ender
Dragon yeah certainly not the folks you
fight in death Loop you got this
potential am I allowed to say that word
my mom has a background in radio so she
understands more or less what you do and
didn't think it was cringe
oh oh thank you she had a great
Christmas thanks to you and I
that is fine okay
still a bit miffed that smoothie
intercepted my kiss to you for New
Year's but oh well I've sent another in
the mail just in case please accept it a
kiss
what do you mean
oh oh no no no don't send a kiss in the
mail ew
me I miss you about the last few days
thanks for all the extra content with
Ina and tiger video yeah you're welcome
everybody thank you thank you answer 604
for the pinky
laughs
why are you lying about this being your
First FPS experience your first
experience was you snapping my heart on
day one I love your best girl
I guess I'm a good shooter because I
shot everybody's heart
bang bang you shot me down bang bang I
hit the ground bang bang bang
my baby shut me down I like that song
and that was smooth that was pretty
smooth not this move is moving but
pretty close to it
[Music]
one year it was late to membership
because I wanted to watch every whole
life member before picking my Oshi
ah well that's fair you truly won me
over in a sea of extremely talented
members oh thank you I hope one day you
understand how talented you are and how
much we love you I've changed my
username a few times but after seeing
your cute reaction to this one I think I
might just keep it forever yeah I think
you should keep it can I request a job
title for my username from my adorable
Aussie
um
yes
[Music]
which is a it's a fish employee which is
very rare uh uh you could be
[Music]
um
okay
minus kfp
and fish
f-e-e-s-a-h yeah f e e s h caffeine fish
or the chicken of the Cena sounds nice
but it's a long fish okay if you fish
hahaha
it's simple and shorts and it's it's
beautiful
it has a nice ring to it you're welcome
thank you I love your profile picture so
much
thank you for your support and I think
it's very good that you gave everyone a
chance not many people do it they just
maybe look at the most uh popular ones
or they they look at one or two members
and and then they're like okay this this
is what I like I'm just not gonna pay
attention to anyone else but you gave a
chance to everyone and I appreciate that
a lot thank you for finding me out of
all these people for choosing me thank
you
fire Danke Schoen Savage thank you for
the red super chat
I actually I really like my kfp named
salt and pepper because Kiana you gave
it to me so I hope you don't get
offended by my pranks always love your
everything don't care this text uh-huh
because my mission as an agent I'll be
back in two months to Cafe it
you're leaving again
in two months that's so long
no
what the hell no you just came back you
can't go again
why are you so busy
no
one day or
no why why you always leave me
[Music]
why you just
can't you're gonna miss a new outfit you
at least gotta watch a new outfit what
the hell watch the new outfit
[Music]
thank you for your support don't forget
about me okay
Don't You Dare Forget About Me
[Music]
kiss
air 17b 42 Duncan
oh
lunch
Chase wants
the Duncan for the pinky I'll be honest
this game is probably going to quickly
kick your ass
luckily you have experience in dying and
coming back over yeah and over and over
and over and over and over and over and
over and over and over again yes
I I wrote it on Twitter I thought I was
quite smart I wrote
um death Loops oh that's something uh if
somebody knows something about death
Loops then it's me yes yes I know a
thing or two about that
um yeah
[Music]
now um it kicked my ass maybe a little
bit but it wasn't that bad it was very
forgiving
um
running away was very easy and then they
gave up like very quickly so thank you
for being so forgiving death Loop thank
you
thank you for the pinky hi kid I
recently tried to take a break from
streams but turned out that you and kfv
corn are the only things that make me
happy you hear that
by the way I'm planning to play a
drinking game gonna take a shot every
time you die oh during that flip oh I
didn't die that often so actually you
might have not even gotten drunk from
that
me and my liver are counting on you you
are welcome I kept you alive
ironic because it's death Loop yeah well
thank you I'm glad you're back welcome
back I don't like it when people leave
so thank you for coming back stay hectic
Volk walk woke and yolk okay
thank you so much for your support
[Music]
you change your name back thank question
thank you thank you very super chat oh
thank you for the membership
uh I forgot what that was in in Korean
people
people died you also get shot in your
heart
I hope it felt good
we were watching as always dancing
soon
foreign
[Music]
I'm so hungry uh don't worry I died 50
times before I get how things work ah
dying is part of this game oh thank you
you had some issues in the beginning too
okay then I don't feel so bad about it
no I I honestly honestly honestly I
found I thought it would go much worse
and I thought I would feel much worse
about my performance and even though you
guys said that I didn't do so well I
personally think I did pretty well
for like considering the circumstances
that it was my first FPS game and that I
didn't really know the game and I also
uh played it on the console and all that
so I think I did okay
yeah thank you thank you thank you your
aim was trash well I mean that's not
necessarily my fault
um I didn't know yet uh where where like
when I aim a gun like that except for
the last one that I was using in the end
a lot but for the other ones I I didn't
know like where to aim like where would
it shoot if I aim at a certain point but
then second of all the problem was the
the joystick
um it moved very chunkily if you know
what I mean like I try to move it like
just a tiny bit and it moves so so much
um so somebody recommended to me to
change the sensitivity and I will do
that for next time
[Music]
oh thank you for watching even when you
look that's okay too thank you you use
my birthday merch
thank you
soon crafts thank you soon
Blackwater TV thank you
[Music]
and now we need to get out the Korean
translator
Korean translation
[Music]
did you hear that
come here
let me
know
[Applause]
yes yes
baby
how are you doing baby hi
mommy she's so sweet lately she likes to
join me at the end of my stream so even
when I'm still streaming no she didn't
come to my lap but uh
she placed herself on the chair next to
me this is smoothie's chair
yeah my old my old PC chair
I didn't want to throw it away so I kept
it here and now my cat uses it so give
me some company she's so soft
um
I'm a bit worried about her recently for
health reasons but we're gonna take care
of that aren't we each movie
I'm gonna take care of that I'm going to
take good care of you baby baby girl
be me girl oh
and she's okay but like hmm
she's mostly okay
we're going to the vet again soon yeah
she's okay
oh it's nothing serious I think oh baby
not on my PC okay if my PC turns off for
some reason oh no There She Goes she's
leaving already she said mommy talks too
much Mommy embarrasses me no
foreign
boss my brain ran away to Andromeda I'm
going to catch him see you in 24 hours
what's that mean
does that mean that's not just mean I
needed to go to sleep
[Music]
first
what exactly are you trying to say are
you telling the others
the other Champions to escape
when well there's no reason to escape
huh
maybe he means the usual room
no no
no that's again you cannot escape from
the usual room
that's actually where you're going now
[Music]
um
I can't stand it any longer so I'm going
to sleep while maintaining it because
I've been working since 5am
when you say working you mean you've
been working a real job or you've been
watching my stream since 5am
or you were working since 5am look full
shift and then watched my stream thanks
for always good streaming I hope this
translates well
yeah kind of
probably talking about a real job yeah
thank you practice thank you for
spending your time with with my streams
even though sorry even though it's
really tough after a long day of work
oppa
fighting okay
okay thank you for coming to me
I really appreciate it thank you soon
and and and and and please take care of
your health okay
um
[Music]
makes things easier after a long day of
work yeah after a long day of work turn
on YouTube Suki while we're streaming
everything is good again yeah moondock
Andreas thank you
extreme dude Elvis thank you for the
pinky
I thought Kanata was the only monkey on
her life hello Kiana
I I must admit yes I was quite the
monkey yesterday I looked back on the
Vlog at the
if if I ever to learn a monkey video I'm
just gonna cut out the audio from def
Loop and then just paste it into the M
Monkey video that's all I need to do
oh I'm so hungry I'm feeling sick
you know that when you feel so hungry
that you feel sick
oh man I should order food already now
so that it comes before I want to go to
sleep
you guys mind if I order some food right
now
[Music]
um because it'll take it will take like
an hour anyway
so hungry
[Music]
okay what do we want
to we want to eat hmm
what am I in the mood for
um
you guys don't go
[Music]
this is the problem that I have I don't
know what I want to eat
I had pizza last night my frozen pizza
are so good oh I love it so much my
favorite frozen pizza
mmm
wow this one has a good rating let's go
with this one
what do we have
[Music]
it has everything
I don't want a pizza I don't want
another Pizza I don't want a burger
either I think
oh oh that sounds yummy
foreign
Greek never tried that what
oh
nuggets
thinking of it should I have dessert
um dessert is your taco or not much
choice but
[Music]
maybe after my nap I wanna eat
in Dutch
that's probably
already enough
mmm
okay
wait that might come earlier than I
wanted to
you know what I'll hold back a little
bit maybe I'll order in like half an
hour
okay
yeah but I can choose the time too let's
just choose the time then
[Music]
yeah don't you need to sleep soon ah
it's okay it's okay I'll get enough
sleep don't worry about it
talking about it
I need to ask amido when I should call
in
okay
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
I'm not saying I would volunteer to be
ingredients but
but but please feel free to end the
sentence
when were you planning to go offline I
don't know if I think before sleeping a
little bit or ah you know what before
like after that I'm a call in I think
before the actual tournament
um
so because there should be like one or
two hours
yeah so keep your eyes
field for that
um yes
thank you for the recipe I was watching
up on the club archive and seeing a clip
of the Ender Dragon made made me want to
go back and watch the stream where you
took Callie to get an elytra huh it was
funny hearing you two talk about the
outfits now uh knowing now how long it
would be till we saw them
oh yeah how long was that a goal
hmm yeah that one those outfits were
were delayed quite a bit so
it's kind of awkward and now it's we we
kind of are getting two outfits in
the span of one month right on it the
party outfits came out in the beginning
of December
was it the beginning of December
so in one month
two outfits it wasn't supposed to be
like that but because the outfits ended
up being so late people thought that
those were our New Year's outfits which
honestly looking at the edit it could
have been that but it wasn't supposed to
be that so here we are and with another
New Year outfit this time it's kimonos
yeah
but I'm so glad I can finally talk about
it it was so hard to hold back and I
mean I Loki talked about hairstyles
um because I was like you guys want to
see me in the ponytail huh but what
about twin Tails another one was like
ponytail ponytail and I'm like oh If
Only They knew that I'm getting twin
Tails now
I hope they're not they will not be
disappointed but I'm on Twin Tails I put
the twin Tails from the start thank you
hmm
[Music]
I I kind of yeah
twin Tails why you don't like twin tiles
I I understand I understand looking at
me you would probably
uh imagine me with with a ponytail I
think it would look good too oh
but
no
I have to disappoint you it's a double
ponytail yeah
[Music]
extremely fun to watch you play this
game uh hadn't had time like lately to
watch so here's my late happy
happy I wish you luck and perseverance
for every challenge in 2022 that might
2022 might throw at you kfp will be with
you
thank you oh thank you for coming back I
guess you were working hard or something
or hardly working hardly working at kfp
that is yeah but thank you for coming
back thank you for thinking of me and I
wish you a happy New Year and yeah let's
have lots of fun together in 2022 siren
I'm counting on you okay I'm counting on
your support I need you to be a loyal
kfp employee
um
song
the real Loop is the third chance we
made along the way
the turrets are pretty overpowered
aren't they I mean maybe against some
more enemies it will quickly crumble if
they if more enemies attack it but dirty
John was pretty buff pretty uh pretty
long living
Curry Chung my beloved
my baby
my Terry tongue
yeah it helped me I I'm glad I
discovered that I can bring to Rich and
with me at least until until the end of
the map um
I threw one into the ocean that must
have been my accident
when I didn't know yet what it can do
now
oh if I would have known that earlier I
could have used that first
on the first map that turret John I
could have used it to eliminate so many
enemies that were troubling me ah yeah
if only I knew
then you add the end of it like stickers
not that I wanted to I was trying to
bring it with me
I'll count
I was panicking and I threw it into oh
don't even remember you need to show up
in the opening ceremony that is a good
question I uh
because no one show up at that time last
year oh if if I don't have to I'll
probably be sleeping or or doing
something else I don't know if I can if
I can quickly go back to sleep I might
be taking another quick nap if I feel
tired otherwise I'll just be practicing
and if Tola Senpai calls out for people
to join then I might join I guess
on my phone though
yeah thank you
Jesus
Jones
[Music]
thank you for the pinky really happy you
had fun time with your first FB instant
y'all thank you
thank you enjoyed it so I hope we can
play it again
sometime soon probably not next week
there there are actually already a lot
of plans I have for next week so maybe
the week after
um
glad you enjoyed it too and yeah so it's
quite different from what I usually
played on my channel until now and but I
know you guys love FPS games though
I hope you guys are happy now
and Mina FPS shooting again
um
I prefer jrpgs well me too me too but I
guess sometimes it's it's good to give
people something different but we'll
we'll play RJ RPGs again we'll play them
again eventually I mean next up is Zelda
though which is apparently not a jail
project to me it's a jrpg because to me
a therapy is something different but you
know you know what I mean you know what
I mean
[Music]
thank you for the pinky not to get too
hasty but you may want to look into
Hitman it has a lot of ways to sneak a
lot of ways to indulge your alarming
murderers urges you definitely have
permissions for it and perhaps most
important for you it isn't sci-fi oh
well yeah one thing I definitely noticed
with devloop because there are many
different ways you can play Death Loop
one thing I noticed is that I think due
to my
due to my
um panic
uh I prefer to play in a stealthy way
[Music]
I I like to take it slowly step by step
uh rather than
people in the masses
I do better and stealth I think so too
because I panic so quickly
Dishonored I wanted to play Dishonored
uh but I can't and when I realized that
that fluke might be not good on PC I I
wanted to play Dishonored instead but I
can't but if I ever can I will play it
because it interests me I see it's more
on the stealth side um
I'm late for my shift but I'm here now
that's okay I'm super glad you enjoyed
the game I was really hoping you were 10
toys too cool can't wait to see how you
absolutely killed it in the world
welcome to the loop oh I absolutely kill
him you are you are putting uh me up too
high on on the Hope scale
yeah if anything I'm too cool for school
but no
um
I didn't exactly kill it in the vault
I mean I killed some people but I didn't
kill it
um I got on a pedestal on the iris scale
so I hope I didn't disappoint USB X
after you watched the vault
don't get your hopes up too high please
thank you though thank you thank you
yeah I I do like the the whole theme the
death Loop story I like the theme of the
story and I like the the Chit Chat and
the little fights that the the main
characters have Juliana and Colt so yeah
that's pretty fun Daisy thank you for
the pinky poking an immersive Sim as
your First FPS is a bold choice
what does that mean but I have to admit
you did a hell a lot better than I
thought then I thought thank you um
an immersive Sim
what's an immersive Sim
that's the genre
an immersive simulator well how is this
and
is the sub genre definitely belongs to
uh-huh
means you can solve stuff in all sorts
of ah emergency
you can tackle a game usually in many
ways and there's no set way to do a
thing oh well it's wonderful then why
why would you why is it a bold Choice
doesn't it doesn't that make it so much
easier for me
not a photo I didn't know there is such
a genre
huh
allows you to approach your game in many
different ways oh I like that they're
Niche there should be more of them then
I already got those
Dishonored another hotel good to know
that Dishonored is like that too turn
around
hey
to help
thank you
it just says hi are you shy oh fine you
shy
[Music]
suitable
foreign
[Music]
yes indeed I agree I think it was fun
um I was pretty focused on the game I
didn't look at the chat much but
um that was just because it was my first
time and I wanted to focus thank you for
the membership thank you but I think if
I would have not focused so much on the
game I would have done a lot worse
yeah but thank you thumbs down let's do
it again sometime soon okay I am
counting on you to be there mwah
ranking and getting better out of 10. it
was fun watching you learn the way you
interacted with this new genre was
refreshing to see if you ever want to
try sci-fi I recommend Mass Effect I
like Mama told you did too yeah yeah
don't worry I have a lot of
recommendations from you guys a lot of
games but
uh I'm not suddenly gonna play uh
shooter games every week on my channel
but I also you gotta gotta remember we
also need to go back to Minecraft
we gotta go back to Minecraft because
yesterday our server was updated to uh
the 18 the new one I think the most
recent one
it was updated we have to go back so
next week definitely Minecraft block
game
um
everyone ditched the block game and even
now that Pokemon is over people are I
feel like mostly still busy with other
things
because now everyone is playing Mario
Kart
what happened with with everyone playing
Minecraft every freaking day
yeah but we will we will play maybe on
Tuesday maybe
I'll I'll see where I can fit it in
yeah let's see what's changed uh
apparently a lot of a lot of things
changed
I think now with the update people
should be playing more Minecraft again I
think so Mario Kart tournament is gonna
be over soon too gaming clones
your sticky thank you soon thank you for
your first ever Super Chat Maxwell the
first time Christian is
yay
[Music]
thank you I love you too
I have you recovered from your drunkness
do you have a hangover hopefully not
um
are you here probably not
probably drunk drunk in bed
don't drink too much okay
but thank you for confessing your love
to me as everyone should be doing fried
Squad
Daisy thank you for the red super chat I
would die for Kaiser in takanasi Kiara
that is dedication yes for your Empress
you should be ready to die at any time
although Daisy aren't you already a
bucket so you're kind of dead already no
kind of like a Undead Undead chicken
you're like a zombie right now
everyone in the bucket is kind of like a
zombie
hmm
I'll come back soon right yeah yeah so
soon is uh well time is uh how do you
say it time is a concept
um
time is everyone perceives it
differently it's it's maybe soon for me
but not so soon for you it's subjective
and relative and everything else times
who is this
[Music]
is
the best feature of all time
totally late I didn't notice your typo
the first time I read that super chat
yesterday
are you talking about someone else
because every time I look up
takanashikiara I always have this
problem that uh certain devices I think
like YouTube and Twitter they or Google
they wanna auto correct me to
takahashukiyara and that is someone else
stop auto correcting me
[Music]
on purpose the only one that matters
fancy you're helping them you're helping
them
not good
not good Telly maybe maybe you type
takanashikara and your phone corrected
you hopefully not if if yes then you
must throw your phone out of the window
right now
eat
mwah
[Music]
soon Derek see
oh I like that one j w s t says because
it's a kfb Space Telescope it says so
hot I had to deploy my sunshield
foreign
but I am the Sun
yeah okay that's the death Loop super
chats now we go to Mario Kart
s
.com I teach my timkins too much thank
you looking for the top donation
missions ah
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
and yesterday you left me totally so
potential aha now I'm gonna take a sip
every time you restart come back every
time a reason oh well
I didn't do that for very long but that
must have been at least
eight shots or so
big muff muffins
I hope I hope I got you a bit drunker
today
um
well shots are apparently very strong so
even with five shots it should have
gotten you a bit drunk now
what what what what what
why must you get drunk when watching my
stream of muffins
why don't you want to enjoy me Silva
um
am I not am I not enjoyable enough for
you huh
I'm gonna go to an apartment I'm gonna
take all the alcohol and I'm gonna throw
it in the ground
and then yeah
and then you must enjoy me soba you're
on your holidays okay okay I'll
forkeeps in
[Music]
um
boom
baby must have enjoyed the the part
where both me and Elena went full baby
[Laughter]
I'm sorry guys for bringing the most
cursed content to you guys but I think
it was hilarious
oh the baby fights
a baby so cute
laughs
what when is the new outfit reveal um
mine is uh GMT plus one
uh uh I think 10 p.m or so
GMT plus one 10 p.m or jst 6 A.M
don't know what time that is uh for all
the tensions 4 pm EST apparently
um
so it's when when Ina's time slot
usually starts
maybe you remember it that way
yeah so please everybody come to it it's
a it's a sudden announcement but please
please please please please please
everybody come to my Advent for real it
will be a short one only half an hour
but I also prepared something special
for it as I said Eden Eden the tunnel uh
Drew
uh
I said wait it's not that's that I mean
even Exile he didn't turn was a MMORPG
he's an exile
[Music]
in Exile through that background for
Sunday right but originally it was for
like I commissioned it for the for the
new outfit reveal but even Exile didn't
know what he was drawing for I basically
I just asked for you know a a shrine
background and and told him like what I
wanted to look like and all that but I
didn't tell him what it was for he also
just found out yesterday
surprise surprise yes
what a tease
I wonder if he was like maybe maybe kind
of like
anticipating it like maybe feeling that
that it could be for something special
like a kimono but I didn't say anything
and we didn't talk about it it didn't
give any hints I just said I want the a
shrine background
um
mm-hmm
that's all I said
you know I said albino donation uh I've
already read that one um thank you for
the red super chat we're almost done
with super chats by the way man Mario
Kart streams are just so Divine on the
one hand I really enjoy seeing tend to
improve on that game and get hyped when
she's ahead on the other hand I love
this adorable frustration noises and
Mario Kart aren't the answer
that was so so mad so many minutes today
this game just has it all yeah yeah I
was really unlucky today you gotta give
me that I was really unlucky today what
the [\h__\h] man
I hope that I used up all my bad luck in
this stream and then I will be lucky in
the tournament and even if not whatever
honestly I don't care that much
I don't care that much
I'm just gonna do my best and try to
stay calm
um not panic too much and yeah and
honestly I think
I think um
I don't I don't even think it's worth it
remembering the shortcuts the only
shortcuts that might be worth it is the
Rainbow Road shortcut that I
accidentally took today
yeah that must be the only one worth it
that seems to to cut a lot short and the
other ones are too risky to learn in a
short amount of time and even when other
people have been taking shortcuts me
without taking shortcuts still seems to
be able to catch up every now and then
so
um
yeah I think I'll just go normally uh
but the rainbow run I'm gonna practice
Yeah
and
[Music]
yeah
drifts and not hitting edges
I I offstream I was able to do it way
better okay I I must say I was pretty
bad today for some reason no
but also the RNG also the RNG
hmm
I won't get a decent placement well
we'll at least not get last I hope
and a pinky from
jangi
for the pinky comes
um
foreign
[Music]
wow
foreign
[Laughter]
he says that he will love me no matter
how often I fall off the cliff and the
edges but he will not want to be in the
same car as me which I think is pretty
disappointing because dry a drive date
is
like I think kind of a cute thing to go
like just driving together you know
um listen to music and driving around
the countryside or whatever looking at
nice sceneries looking at the beach and
whatever isn't that nice huh huh if I
were driving
and that's fine too
I don't mind being on the passenger seat
I'll be on the passenger seat then
let's do a switcheroo
refresh we're almost done I think
wait there's a bunch of new ones here we
are okay Mr Cow Brown thank you for the
pinky wishing the best verb a high place
and attorney I was able to Wallop you
with a ball bump in one of the races
today and your distinct laughs and
screams have become ingrained in my head
I'm sure the answer will be great too
I'll be tuning in
[Music]
oh good for you
good for you thank you
bicycle date I think is the safest oh no
no no nope I'm really bad at cycling
especially when there's traffic I have
like no idea what to do where to go
and how to behave no not a good idea
for participating in the mario kart
races and
next time you could be a bit nicer to me
huh
putting channels
thank you
thank you for listening to Sparks
strange facts
[Music]
yeah you got your new title nice too
thank you
[Music]
for the pinky yo yo thanks I just wanted
to say thanks for all the streams the
last quarter of the year I broke my arm
in MMA practice is that wrestling and
crushed two fingers at work but your
streams have been good company in my
recovery
oh my God just wanted to say thank you
and I love you oh my God you were quite
unlucky huh I mixed martial arts ah okay
oh my God please be more careful
yo your poor fingers and arms
what
uh please get healthy and uh recover
soon if you have not already recovered
and yeah I'm glad I could keep you
company during those times
yeah take care of yourself okay and be
strong
break their arms instead of getting your
own arms broken okay
break them back
and respectful for doing these Sports
and all that
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
was there something funny about the
Korean name
apparently there was
so funny
[Music]
thank you
oh
since
[Music]
thank you for listening to Sparks
knowledge
a cat that likes to sing thank you soon
um no I haven't I haven't
uh Christine
comes out this year oh remind me again
when it comes out Mama
I'm happy that you like a FPS game it
seems you don't have motion sickness in
first person Vision ah that is a good
thing there are some FPS games that are
not involved shooting hope that you can
give them a chance
I did enjoy using the the machete much
more than I then I liked using the gun
of course I am I'm just better at using
you know a proper uh weapon like that
like a sword or so I am trained in sword
battle uh but uh apparently people get
sick sometimes I didn't uh I got a
little bit of a headache at the end but
that might have been for different
reasons
foreign
Skyrim
one day one day
yeah thank you soon I hope you enjoyed
it Skye thank you so much for watching
and for your love and support
Todd Howard thank you for the pinky if
you like RPG's medieval fantasy and
playing games instead you choose may I
recommend the Elder Scrolls 5 scrim
special edition now available with
anniversary edition update which bundles
together over 74 creation Club items
that sounds like you wrote it like you
know the critically acclaimed Final
Fantasy 14 are you trying to tell me
something are you trying to tell me
something here
you want me to play Elder Scrolls
I've heard much about it
is is taught
um
like uh the the person who made like
who's behind Skyrim and and Elder
Scrolls
that's probably not the real one though
[Music]
um
thank you thank you for coming
foreign
boss I came to work and they're a
strange chairs chairs tables and buses I
didn't Escape
the usual room well there is no Escape
you escape when I say you will leave
that it's not something that you decide
um
so just do your time in the usual room
and if you wear a good Champion I will
let you out again and when you learned
your lesson after watching some videos
and yeah
becoming a better chicken reflect on
your actions okay
reflect how
is
black rich and danke should have a line
thank you soon
it says fried Phoenix
[Music]
kitchen
oh 16 so young
fighting eating donkey soon sorry for
saying your name bro
I think I was thinking about something
else and
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
good night and hello I'm glad to hear
the voice of Phoenix right after get off
work and I will always support you your
smile is what all kfp clerk desires the
most oh it will make me full of strength
I hope you will be able to desirable
partner in my dreams or in reality to be
my desirable partner in my dreams or in
reality hmm I think
hmm
that kind of escalated at the end
the boy is sweet and kind words
[Music]
well at least in your dreams I'm sure it
can happen
thank you thank you thank you yeah
thank you please work hard work hard and
then every day after work you can look
forward to watching my streams at home
when you get cozy and cuddly hmm I'm
always here for you thank you for all
the love I appreciate the general
support thank you rude oh thank you
huh
come tops corn
ER
cute
thank you I saw a lot of Koreans also
joining the Mario Kart race today thank
you everybody for trying to race me but
don't don't forget don't forget respect
the tension
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you thank you um
thank you soon
yeah this is the end of the super chats
uh oh cocoon Bank soon and now we're
done I will now go to
my bed and then uh hopefully eat soon
and then sleep a little bit and a few
hours like at least four hours I should
be able to get a good nap
um I did order the food yeah yeah
foreign
[Music]
thank you guys I had a lot of fun
playing Mario Kart review guys today
there's been a lot of Mario Karts
recently not only for me but from other
members but after that don't worry we'll
finally get back to normal
thank you yeah I will rest well you guys
too please first of all take care
yourself everybody
um we'll see we'll see about that art
stream we'll see if that happens 3D done
kitchen thank you
[Music]
yeah your shift is over everybody
your shift is over
foreign
[Music]
happy birthday okay
I'm a birthday
[Music]
I wonder if my if my gift will make it
in time
[Music]
shift ended happy birthday to Apple
thank you
are you guys done
okay sleepy time although I literally
just woke up before the Mario Kart
stream but I'm always in for a nap oh I
love my naps most expansion oh what is
that that I cannot read
it
thank you yeah you can go home but yeah
I'll see you in my next stream okay
promise Pinky Promise
Duncan happy birthday thank you for your
support
dark master thank you soon guapa
what's that mean again
Brandon wood dankison yes it will be
delicious now I'll be eating food
in my dreams
I love my music
but your your profile picture is not
mommy but it's pretty disturbing Mary
Pippen's Duncan one more
oh oh it's pretty oh oh ah it's a good
word I thought you were saying something
insulting
ah
um
oh ever thought about doing a Twitter
space Oh yeah maybe someday unknown
question
maybe maybe if I'm bored
I'm leaving now
I'll be dancing don't miss this
[Music]
please come to this
Saturday
uh actually for for Japan it's Sunday
oh
please I am I am this one this one this
one
[Music]
don't you want to stay mean cute twin
tails
[Music]
I recognize you just from the profile
picture
oh
this place please yes
okay okay
bye bye did I say it and in German we
say alfina Zane bye bye bye bye bye bye
bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye
[Music]
thank you