I wonder if I'll become a big soul someday.I'm
drawing the outline of me strongly and strongly.Everyone
jumps out and
shows me the mighty water in the daytime.Along
with today's tears, I
put on my empty dreams and spoke to you many times.Let
's go together to see the future.  Let's walk next to each other
10 times, 8 times, 000 times I'll keep trying I
still have something missing I'll
keep thinking and thinking and thinking and finding it in my unreadable wings I
want to prove that I'm unique, right?
Right now, in this land where there is no hope, I
still want to believe in hope, even if the song is a little short. There is
no meaning in me meeting you here.
Before I feel like I'm about to do something dark and gloomy, I
say, "I'm wandering around."  It's too late. I'm
enjoying the reversals while matching the rhythm with you who never sleeps. Even if I stumble or
get hurt, I'll start again from here. Even
if I'm clumsy or small, I'll sing the song.
As long as I keep going, it'll be sunny. The
cloudy sky I pictured as a canvas for
you.
My smile may be smooth now, but if I put it into words, I'm sure it
won't be true.I'm embarrassed, but I'm confused.I don't want to hide my feelings.It's
not like that anymore.
[Music]
These feelings aren't vague.  That's
not a mistake, cut your fingers.
[Music]
Well,
Hello, hello, hello,
haha,
haha, chaos, everyone.
Hello has started Nya Hello Nya
[Music]
Hello, the usual Hololive Sports Festival
2023 eve festival, so
thank you very much for choosing to do it today.
No, no, there are a lot of people. It's a
huge number.
Today, I'm going to join you all.  This is an event where everyone can enjoy the all-night festival and
play together while also practicing a little. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Thank
you very much. Okay. I'll say hello to each person one by one.
No, that's okay. I'll take about 30 minutes to say hello to you today. Is it okay to have a dog?
Yes, that's okay. I'll have a lot of them today.  The
people who are participating today
are the flyers. If you press the tab key, you can see
who is participating. It
's amazing.
31211414+14 is
20 Aja, 27 people gathered together,
so today I thought I'd do some new things like
playing with everyone for the first time, Holmen,
hunting, playing with 27 people,
etc.  I'm
thinking about it, but I'm
thinking, Okay, I'm going to go ahead and talk to all of you listeners today. I've never seen you playing around. I'm thinking, ``Let's start with hunting.'' I'm thinking, ``Let's do it.  I
want to do it,
please do this is the late thing that is the slowest,
but I'm
sorry, but no, it's okay,
here's the place.  [
Music]
Look at me, look at this Subaru
cancer. I know what you're saying. We should get
along after
all. We're not going to get along. It's
not just you. It's you.  It's
not like you're beautiful, you're just like
Sakura. You're
using it in such a way that you don't want to use it properly. You're being looked at
properly, at least.
What are you making me do here? It's really
embarrassing.  It
's being pushed, it's not being pushed, it's not being pushed, it's being pushed, it's not being pushed, it's being pushed, it's not being pushed, it's being pushed, it's being pushed, it's not being pushed, it's
being pushed, it's going to be erased.  I
couldn't delete it because I was worried that if I deleted it, it would affect the system. Even if it was
installed in the system, something would
happen. So what do you do with the button? Miko-san, put a button on it. Hey,
everyone.  Well, this time, let's
start with the red team. I think it's
probably a good balance between the red teams. I don't
think there's a lot of people, but
mostly there are too few white players and yellow players.  Is
it too little or is there too little red?
It doesn't look like it,
so I guess it's okay. Then there are people who will appear in the red group.  Everyone, I know some
people have already gotten it, but there's a book on the table.Let's
go back to where we were before and
get it.Here, everyone.Here.
So, please head over there and head to the school.I
made this, so I'm
sorry that the en version is not yet available, but I hope GT members will
support you.Yes,
yes, see you then, Holmen
Hunting Rules.  It looks like 6 people are selected from each team.
Yes,
it's a game twice, so there are 3 people and 3 people, so there are 6 people.
Yes, the red team will play first, Hunter.  I guess I'll
just decide on the 6 of us and get them together.Okay,
okay, what are we going to do about Boychat?Let's break up.I
think we'll be a little divided between red, white, and yellow.I'm
sure it'll be crowded.The red group will stay like this for a
while.  I want you to stay and go to Bochit, who has been designated as a yellow year.
Naime
Hello
Ede
Kinpika's yellow Kinpika Nene's yellow Katsu yo
Yellow Who is the one who will do his
best Abelbebe-chan is that right?
Mr. Kado Makiwatari,
potty polka, Mr. Anya, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes. All other
people, please enter once.
Please wait outside the venue. Yes, yes, we can do this. Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, we have
entered. These three people who entered,
let's go, let's go. We'll do our best. We'll do our best. How horrifying is this?
It's a test to see if you know the live members.The
head that uses a pounding head is the one with the bread.The head that uses the head is the one with the bread.The head that uses the head is the one with the bread.The head that uses the head is the one with the bread.The head that uses the head is the one with the bread.The head that uses the head is the one with the bread.The head that uses the head is the one with the bread.The head that uses the head is the one with the bread.The
head that uses the head is the one with the bread.The one who uses the head with the head is the one with the bread.The head that uses the head is the one with the bread.The head that uses the head is the one with the bread.The head that uses the head is the one with the bread.The head that uses the head is the one with the bread.The head that uses the head is the one with the
bread.  It's
passion, right? It's yellow, so it's passion,
right? So it's definitely mental and
physical passion. Is this mental
and physical passion?
Is it mental and physical passion? I've always wanted to ask, and it's
menpassion.Last year, Hua
started saying it's mental and physical passion,
but yeah, that's not a plagiarism.  It's
noisy. What I mean by
noisy is that they're trying to take back their mental and physical
passion. I
see, but they're the ones who make me understand.
By the way, do you understand the rules?
Everyone, the rules are completely false.
Who said that?
By the way, I'll explain it simply.
Well, if you start the game now, you'll
become a demon.  If you're one of those people, you'll be warped to a point in front of that friendly white statue over there.I
guess you can't do that.So,
when you start, that theme will be displayed at the top, and you'll be able to
select people who match that theme.  Yellow is  The
first game I'm
going to play is yellow, but it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.The
order is, I'll start with yellow first, then yellow, etc.I'm
sorry, please.Eh
, there are already 6 entries for yellow.  It
feels like 3 yellow, so 3 is fine because this is my first entry.Okay,
there are 3 entries, sorry.Where
does Hunter start?  Let's make
it something like this.
Alright then, I'm a fugitive.
I'm going to make some holes to get you into the fugitive group.
Please wait for a while.
Yes, I'm a yellow member.
Over here, do you want to wait in the audience seats? No
, here, here
, here,
Paki-sama-chan.
Neither Sawa nor Polka nor I are here.
Both cotton and polka pigeons are flying.
If you start, it will start automatically.
Yes, yes, yes, even if it's
over, what's the point? Is there a time when you become a fugitive too? Well, sometimes
when the other team is doing something,
you become a pigeon.  Yeah, that's right,
that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, the
members who will be Ha are decided, but
all of them will participate, right? As for the participation itself, they will be on the
fleeing side.It starts early.
What is volume?  At
the beginning of the volume check, the volume at the
beginning is high The
volume at the beginning of the check The volume at the beginning of the check At the beginning
200%
Meme is 200%
You don't have to do anything. Subaru and the
others are the first to catch it, so we
entered.  It's okay if you do
n't have it. Do you know this? How do you catch it? What does it
feel like to catch it? It's caught when you touch it.
There's this. The leash is handed over to the person who catches it,
so the person who catches it puts the leash on its ear, for example.
When you hear something that sounds like a compliment,
go to the place where it says it's a teasing ear, hit this leash
and pull it, and push the
sign that says pull it to the friendly white statue and you'll be
able to contain it.  Let's do our
best, try our best, it's going to start, it's going to
start, it's going to start, it's going to start, it's okay for
us to run away, oh, the red one, because the
red team, the red team, the red one, the red one, the one to catch it, the
red one, the red catcher, the
stubborn Azuki.
Nice, nice, take me, take me.
Hey, it wasn't red. I think Aki is
n't red.
That one failed. I'm going to catch one of you. I'll
catch you. There
were two people standing there.
My name.  is the person whose name is red, the person whose name is red, the
name is red, the name is red, the white and
white group is the white group, the white group is white, the white group is white, the white group is white.  It's
on the top of the people, oh, it's here, get this,
uh, push this sign, oh yeah, then you
should be able to expropriate it.
It's true, it's the
red one, so it's all over. Now,
it's the white one, so
I'm coming. I'm here.
Hey, it's on top of a yellow-white pillar. There's
no one left in the group. If we catch our friends, we'll
catch them. This is it. Hey,
wait a minute. This could
be a mistake.  Nekore Wanchimiah Ah,
but my life is at stake Ah, but I ca
n't, so I can't do it properly, so I
want to join, but yeah, yeah, I
think it's okay. It'll be fun if we catch a lot of people. Oh, it's a
story. Oh,
stop it, catch a polka.  I can't do it
Wow, this is over. I
wanted to give it a try. However, this topic is temporary, so there's a possibility that you might touch it. That's the clothes you caught Nofu in. Hehe, I was looking at you from above, but if you put the leash on and pull it too hard, it seems like it will come off.
That's why, Ririka, it seems like you can run away. Run away as fast as you can. If you're caught, you can run away if you run away with the sauce. Run to the other side, and do it all over again. This is practice, so it's time for the next one.
Okay, so let's move on to the next one.Next time,
Subaru and the others will be on the run, so
let's go with the fugitives.Fugitives, fugitives, but the white team
didn't enter.
No, all of them are
on the catcher's side.
I see. I see. They're being beaten somehow. Please stop. If you grab the rope, right, left, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, maybe Pol, this is the one that's going to participate as the escaper. That's right, that's right, that's right, that's it.
Even if you are pulled by the lead, run away, run away, ok, yo, oh, you're strong here, you're strong here, you're strong, you're strong, you're strong.
Although I'm not there, I can do something about it,
but I'm sure tomorrow I'll
get a review saying something like how many centimeters it is or something like that,
and I'm learning.
Maybe there is, but if you catch the wrong person, you wo
n't be able to get it.The point is, if you
catch the wrong person and touch the signboard, it will say, ``No
, I don't know the trick, but it
won't fit in.''  If
someone is chasing me, is
it okay for me to lie and say that I'm not like that? Oh, I
can't lie anymore.
What year did you make your debut in 2000? That data is still there, so I'm going to
confuse the person.  You
can't lie in order to do it. Let's understand. I
can't even lie. But yeah, maybe the voice chat is
n't connected. It's likely to provoke the enemy. Yeah, that's right. Because we can't
connect, our voice won't reach you. Good evening. It's time to
start. Yes,
run away, run away.
Let's go, Rigro, I'll
do my best to make sure I don't get caught, I survived.  It's
scary, it's scary, it's not scary, it's not scary anymore, don't
take it, you don't have a chim. Hold on and catch this.
O run to the other side.
All the catchers, the safety guys, all the guys. All the guys are the other way around. I'd
rather get in the way and hit them.  Kaori, are
n't you too smart?
Let's go to the window. White is
trying to catch me
right now. Oh, that's right. It's not red, it's red. I got caught by gold.
Seriously,
I'm yellow, right? Gold, gold, are you serious? It's true, money. It's too high just now,
so why did you get arrested?
[Music]
Hey, gold, I got arrested too. I'm
standing on my feet, all the shops can see.  Ali Iris is also sexy, and
when she crouches down and closes the window, you
can't hear the other side.
I'm aware that if I catch it and crouch down, I can't see the color, it'll disappear,
so yeah,
what, what, shift,
shift, shift, time is dangerous, it's dangerous, run away, run away, run away,
run away, run away,
run away, it's dangerous, run
away, it's red and red.I won't catch you, Sora-chan, it's
okay, Sora.  Chanso boldly, senior, wow, what, what, what, what, what, you're
here, you
're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're
here, you're here, you're here.
Taneane, it's okay, everyone survived.
Survivors. It's not like I'm a survivor. But I have
n't been able to catch them at all. I'm not very good. I'm not
very good. The people who came here are pretty tough. Kanae, this is going to be difficult, isn't it?  Was he a genius? I don't know
if he was a genius. It's true that he hit it repeatedly.
The polka wasn't good because he hit it repeatedly. Hey,
if you hit it repeatedly, you'll miss.  I
didn't. I didn't miss it even
if I ran it. Right? I don't know. I'm sure it won't happen. Please enter the runaway. I understand. Did you get it? It'll come out soon. I thought I pressed it one more time.  Let's
see if I can push it. It's done. It's done. It's done. It's
done. It's done. It's done. It's done. Sora-chan was really bold and ran all the way to the center. It's totally okay. There's plenty of time. Seriously
? There's plenty of time. I'm not feeling passionate right now.  It's
too bad. I'm strong. If I were running,
people wouldn't think I was a hit. I'm sure no, it
's probably just the money.
That's the only thing that caught everyone.  I'm in
charge of you, idiot.
Please do your best. Keep it like this next time. Yes,
but with that shift, I can't understand the colors.
Makchan, you did a genius. It wo
n't become a prohibited card. No, there's a dog tomorrow.
There's a possibility that I won't be able to do it.
Let's go, Iris, it's crazy
here. It's really safe here. We're in the red team. Let's
go take a nap. Erase the colors, erase the colors.
Everyone squat down. You'll
get caught. As you walk, you'll be near the bridge.
Really.  It's the same for everyone when it comes to
squatting down. It's okay if Sora-chan doesn't
know how to
squat. It's hard to understand when you're crouching down, and when you're messing around, you're wrong.  You're
doing a really, really good thing, you're beautiful, you're doing a really good thing. What's that?
When I was catching you, here I was,
squatting down,
squatting down, and my senior was in a lot of pain. I was squatting down,
behind that place.  But here
it is, what is this white one?What do you call it
?A white one, a
white one, yes, that's right.Here and there, here
and there, yes, that's right, I was scuttling with the threads of the clouds, and then I
got caught and did Mi-chan.  It's hard to get
caught.
I mean, it's hard to get caught, or rather, if you're used, no matter how much you pull, you're very stubborn. I was taught that no matter what, you're so stubborn. I got
caught. I said,
stop! Oh, but Sara-chan is running away.
That's amazing.  I thought, ``This is crazy!'' It's a
big escape. It's
amazing, but it hasn't been found out. Maybe it's not
found out. It's dangerous, it's dangerous, no one should act. Hey
, Rika, please help me. I'm getting
hot.  Run
away, you're so hot, you're caught, Polka-san. It looks like you've escaped. Polka-san has devised a sure-fire way to win. Or, go ahead and do it, Polka. You've got to go into the clouds yourself.  That
's right, it
might not be a good idea to crouch down and wait because it's a hassle and you end up putting it off until someone else gets caught.
Ah, I see. It's because of all the cloud threads in the yellow group. It's kind of
embarrassing, isn't it? Lyrica is so stupid. If she says things like paying money, it's a lie. It's dangerous. It's like an in-cap play. It's like a play. It's like I'm going to be played. I
hide and sneak.
About the play.
Yes.  Miasu-chan, I'm sorry.
No, it's totally fine. It was fun, it
was fun, it was fun. I went home. It was okay. Sora-chan and I were
okay. I ran away. Yeah, I got caught.
Hey, you ran away once, right? He's drinking something.
Chanso-chan has been eating and drinking for a while now. He's enjoying it. Normally, you're eating this much ice. It's like you're always
eating and then eating ice again. I'm already
on my way.  Yes, yes, yes, then I
went there myself. I'm sorry, then I went to number 2. Can you please
gather? Yes, I
'll move.
How do I move? How do I
cross kill?  He's
too strong. He's really strong when he's on his side. His life is
at stake. He'll save me. Why don't we do it twice? It seems
like a good idea, so this time we have a theme.
Even though it's the same guy, the actual performance
feels like we're going to go around this again.  Yes,
yes, the topic is completely different, so maybe I just
want to think about it. The three of us should work together to
catch one person, but let's try it with teamwork.
Yes, we
'll see the balance now.  Maybe it's that expensive
As you can see, there is a possibility that the building may be scraped down a little.
[Music] But they were
caught. The antis
are gone. They're gone. The antis are gone. So, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I wonder if they've done it
already.
I'm not coming, I'm not coming, so let's move,
let's come
, let's move.  If you
have a partner, why would you want to practice with someone?
Yes, I'm sure. If you
have a partner, it's true.
Listeners, you've always already decided on a partner,
and
even more so.  It's decided by the team,
so I'd like you to do that with your partner,
so if you
're a fan, please touch that sign.
Only the seniors are here, yes, I
am. Yes, I am. So, I will touch the signboard on the polka. I
will make an announcement on the polka. How about
our team?
First, is the Hasbells team ready? Well,
okay.  You see, it's the entry on the left.
Okay, then go ahead and tell Black that we're off today. So,
Ririka and Suichan are going to have a good time. Ka,
please go to the top. Well then, the people on the bottom too. The
people on the bottom who have to touch the sign.  Toneshita  You do
n't have to touch the person, you're the one above you. How did I
go? I touched it by mistake. I
made a mistake. If I made a mistake, uhm, if I made a mistake, I wonder if I can't undo this?
Wait a minute, I'll ask you. Yeah,
yeah.  Everyone said this.
Only the jounin touched it, so Sora-chan should touch it
. For me, I'll have Matsuri and Ani-san team up. It
wasn't Iris, Iris, I'm
teaming up with Iris. What should I do about this?
When I touch it, it's paired
with Iris, Pol. I'm paired with Iris, and this is what it's like. I'm
sorry, Iris, but how can I ride it?
Sora-chan presses it, and there's someone on top of Col. Is
n't she able to ride it?  I think
Sora-chan is riding her. She's
riding. She's touching the horse. She's
touching the horse. Sora-chan's going to do it again.
Click here to enter.
Oh, that, that, that, I wanted to go.Who else is
Iris, who is not on the team?I
think it would be better to experience it, so
can I ask you to play General Iris today?I said,
Wait a minute, then I'll be on top of Watari-senpai.  That's
right, let me sit on top of a sheep and let me sit on top of a sheep.
This gigiska is fast. Whoever is the gigiska, I
wonder who did this.
Well, there is an iris.  You
can enter the general by pressing the book.You can enter the general by
pressing the book.I open the book and have a book in my hand.No, I can
enter the general.Yes,
yes, that's it, the yellow general's yellow
block.Press the yellow block.Oh yeah,
that's right, Anya.
Mr. Anya, Mr. Sho. I'm sorry,
Suma-chan, I'm sorry, I
'm sorry, Suma-chan. I probably have a lot left over, so I'll just press this. Oh,
please, please, wait, the rules.
Can I ask you to explain? Yes, please explain
. Yes, I can't see it, so I
ask. Oh, then Tuvalu can explain it
to me. Please, I'll go to Jami. Yes,
this is it.  It's a
game about how many times you can kill an enemy within a few seconds.The
only people who can attack are those on top of you, and the ones on the bottom can only move.
Not the number of people  The
team with the most kills is number one and how many points do you
get? It's a kill point where you get points in the wind.
That's right, but the general is glowing yellow.
In this case, Iris is the general. When the general is
defeated, 1 point is added without the king.
So, for example, if the red team
kills a lot and gets 10 points per red team,
but if they
kill Iris twice, they'll add 2 points and
get 12 points, which is crazy.
Whether Iris will come forward and kill them
or not is a matter of strategy.In
this game, even if you die once, you can immediately respawn,
so everyone, it's a game that asks you to come forward and
kill as many as you can.Yes, I
understand.
Please leave it to me.Also, you have 3 hearts, so
if you're on the verge of death, it's more advantageous to go and kill the person with 1 heart.That's
right.  That
's right, it's better to be protected. The general has 5 hearts,
so he can withstand it fairly easily. It's
better to protect him as a team of two. What's the strategy? What are we going to do?
Yes, Rika, we're alive.
Well, at
least I feel like this, but the general
doesn't have to be like that. I'm sure if he sticks around and moves, I
'll keep asking the general if I should stay behind.
There's one, but it's so hot that it's good. What's with the
heart? Sora-
chan, take a screenshot and send it to me. There
shouldn't be any hearts.
Too much heart. If I start wrong, the
heart will probably be small now.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I see. You can change your perspective. Change your perspective. Okay,
how do you change your perspective? It
's F5. F5. Oh, let's go! Let's
go! Let's go! Let's go!  It seems that you
should hit anything other than yellow.You should hit yellow.I
wonder if there are yellows.I wonder if it will decrease.When the yellows are together, you can't touch the bottom, so you
can't hit the bottom, just like you can't hit it.  You
shouldn't be able to hit the bottom part, so let's get started.
Good luck, everyone. Let's move on.
Bonbon. Go, attack,
attack, attack, attack, attack.
[Music]
It's scary.
Yo
yo
kekekekekeke It's scary, scary, scary
[Music] There
's only 2 more people left, 2 more people left,
maybe a little too many people,
where are you?  I
wouldn't be able to do it now. That
's amazing. It's nice. I was
hitting him with a strong force.
Could it be that he's strong? I also used a
bare fist.  I
should have said sorry, right? I have that sword and shield.
That's right, the sword is stronger, isn't it?
But the arm had a longer reach. The
reach was really long. It's true, everyone was
using punches instead of swords, but they were this strong.
That's amazing.Yuu He was able to
defeat a lot of people in the beginning,
but he definitely has the talent to play Minecraft.
That's my Lyrica
[laughing] Well, it's
amazing.
It's yellow, and the red and white ones were
frozen and didn't move at all at first, but now they're
killing only the yellow ones. The
upper mackerel
is moving. That's amazing.
Yes, there's probably one yellow person,
but
Subaru is going to support me today.Alright,
can I have a red-haired one too?
Yes, please, yes, please, please.
That preparation is a little different from that day. I don't
know if I'll be on the bottom or on the top. Is it OK to ask you to do it? Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
then let's do it again at 3.
Yes, I'll do it one more time.  Shall we
do 1? I haven't done Soba-chan yet,
so if I don't do it, I'll be lazy again.
If Ihwa, next time I'll be under you. No,
then it's better to stay stationary. I'm sure it'll be good practice.
Subaru is a lie
, you're already an enemy. I'm at a loss for saying things like that. I'm a
lazy old man who's gone. Nyaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahahahahahahahahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh.  It
was a bit of a mess.
Yes, it's okay, let's go, let's go, let's go. It's
definitely the strongest place.
What about the distance? Was it too close or too far?
Hey, kill da kill da, I understand.
Is this like playing the general again?
Or is it someone else? That's fine.
Who
is the general?
Who will be the real one? Su-chan, Susuba, senpai, senpai, ni, senpai, Jin-senpai,
right? Yeah, I see.  Yes, another person
will do it. I'll do it. I'll do it. I'll
do it. The general vs. me. I'm sorry. I'm a little depressed. I'm
with you now, so you can go home. Then I
'll go. OK, OK. Please.
Then, will you freeze?
Yes, like before, I'll use a sword this time. Yes, it
's definitely a sword. All swords are equipped with
swords. I'm holding a glade. It looks like a glade. It
can't be helped because it's the first time I've heard of its existence. It can't be helped,
right? We're going to practice today.  It's a meeting,
right? Which way do we go first? Well, that's not the
case. I'm going to
cut in and cut in. I'll come to the captain. I'm
asking you to attack. Either way, I'll take your back.
The attack red is going red is going red is
going red is it red?
Oshi,
nice. Maybe this is what it is. Let's hit us. We
're being hit. The low-ranking guy has
low HP. It
was a bit of a shame.
Sora-chan is the strongest. Everyone is strong.
Yaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa, Red, even though I was strong, I was able to do this even though I was strong.The
general was using a shield, and when I was
walking backwards, I was able to grow again and fall down.I
realized that I see.  I don't think it's more
complicated than the general version,
but there's no cooldown time for respawn, so it seems like
hehehehe. Then he'll
be respawned right away, so there
's a lot of white and red.
Maybe it's okay to aim only when the general is cut down.
Maybe the HP is low or it's important to watch the HP.
Maybe it's fishing. Everyone from behind the fishing school.
[Music] Is
this going to be the place or something has changed.  Miko, I
understand.Thank you very much.Thank
you very much.I can do it without running away.It's
fun.If you want to practice with different teams, you can
practice with me anytime.
Let's listen to Harumi, who plays the role.
Well, today I can press the start button, so I don't have to worry about that.
Even if we have different teams to practice after this, it's okay. I
think I understand pretty well. I just have one question.  Isn't that
true? I
never understood how many kills the general would get if he killed something,
but hey, every time the general is defeated that one time, you
get 1 point, right?
Poi, it doesn't matter in the team points mentioned earlier, the
number of generals who died will be
added to the final total, and
if it is added, it will be the same as the victory points for one battle.  It's
bonus points that are
added regardless of the points from earlier in the match.The person in first place will get
10 points for the team in second place, and
5 points for the team in third place.  Right?
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's going to be added, so I
see, I finally understood.It's added to this.Even
if that kill was made, it
wasn't added to the previous one.I
see, for example, the 3rd place team will win the
grand prize by 5 points.
If I killed him five times, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's where I'm
in third place, but it's like getting 10 points, oh, I
see, I see, I
see, that's right, that's so interesting.
If you can't roll it up and it's time for the rest of the time, then I
'll tell you, General, it's not enough to make you cry. Yes, that's right, General. Please be careful. Yes, I understand.
So, what should I do next? What should I do next? Please
check it once.  Isn't it okay
? Daebak,
Daebak, let's go. Well then, let's get over it. Or better
yet, English. What are you talking about
?
What did
you say? I got hit.
[Music]
Oh, we still have the equipment divided into teams,
but I'm sure they have it. Katea is
also
left, and they're fighting each other. This
is the entry. We split up into teams
[  [Music]
Please, that Kao won't be doing this event,
but I
don't care which one you want.I don't care which one you
like at the festival.They're great escorts.Eh, we
've got everything today, we've got everything today, we've got everything.
It's all there, it's all there,
who's the princess? Who's the princess?
Who's the princess? It doesn't matter who you are. It's a festival, right
? Iris, so Iris looks like a princess. Why? It
's okay for you.
Iris' friends are definitely killing each other.  I
guess I'll have to do my best,
but when I first practiced with Lyrica-chan,
at the beginning, at this part, I
changed the camera and changed the camera for the knights.  If you
walk while crouching, you won't fall, so you won't
fall from the back of the room. I
understand. Please confirm this with the management.
As expected, after saying yes, you are
allowed to change your perspective. That's also
okay.  I've confirmed it.I
think it's better to change it.Thank you very much,
but do your best, try your best, try your best.Is it
better for the princess to do that?Is it better for the princess to change her point of view?
Maybe she should change it.  It's better to change your perspective  I
don't know what to say,
but Subaru is easy to do,
so I guess I'll change it.But it depends on the person, it's
fun to try.How
should I equip the Subaru Line?Ah, let's
get Subaru.It's the middle part of the game.
Well, it probably won't go away.
Just hold this. I'll take anything with me, so Subaru,
please hold on to this. I can't drop this.
Throw it. I can't throw it. I can't throw it. It's starting.  I'll
tell you later. Good luck,
work
hard,
but I
can't hear it even if I log out.  I
can't do this, right? Do your best, get off, get
off, get off, get off,
and here you are.
Redna That's good. Hurry up. Hurry up here. Well,
knights shouldn't talk. Knights shouldn't talk. Oh,
but it's okay to be there or something.
Princesses can talk. Princesses can talk.
I'm talking, so everyone nods.  I
don't have Riare or Ria, but you can just shake it.Ah
, press the E button.I
see, it says this, so is this a refrigerator?
No, I wonder if that's what I am. I wonder if it's the refrigerator.
Click on it, click on it. The book is nice and
nice. It's
finally, finally, already. What's the other one? It
starts with white again. Let's do our best. Come on, Lyrica.
This is good.  Yes, it's okay, tomato, that's okay
. It's probably tomatoes, apples, or paprika. What is
that? Oh, what is that? Matsuri Matsuri Senpai is amazing. He's
nodding. Oh, but it's a little strange to nod,
so I'll have to check before the actual performance.
Masu Nice Paprika, uh, I'm hungry. I
want to eat yakitori and uh, Subaru's fried chicken. Yakitori, yakitori, and Subaru's fried chicken. Suru's
fried chicken. How to make fried chicken is written in the ice cream book.
Um, yakitori is just yakitori.It
's a good idea to grill the chicken in pieces.The
fried chicken at Subaru is raw chicken,
Kako Subaru-senpai, and uh, flour.  Oh,
and it's oil. It's really Subaru's fried
chicken. No, no, stop it, stop it, stop it. How many pieces of chicken? I
didn't write down how many pieces of chicken I want to eat.
So, I cut each fried chicken piece by piece on a cutting board. Oh, and I
also cut the flour on a cutting board.
So I'm looking at it like a director, and
then I want to eat it with some chicken and flour oil.I
know I want to eat it,
but now I'm going to add the chicken and flour that I just cut and some oil.  It's
not all oil in it. It's sold as oil. It's supposed to be sold.
Someone has it. Someone has it. It's got it. It's got it. It's got it. It's got it. It's
got it. It's got it. I'm going to put it in the pot.  I
sometimes drink oil, but I
drank it somewhere, and it
disappeared, but please go ahead, Morimochi.Maybe
that's the thing I dropped, and that's
it.I don't have anything else written about it.
name  It's
fried chicken. It's
true. It's true. It's really true.
Thank you very much. Eat it. I'm
not kidding. Eat another one. Yes, it's
okay. It's okay. It's okay.
Hmm, can you tell me the color? The upper right is red. The upper left is pink. The lower left is also pink. I don't know the lower left. I don't know the lower right. Please tell me the color. Yellow. I think it's yellow. It's yellow. Yes, it's yellow.  and yellow yes
No, finally, finally, it's time to kill, kill, kill. It's
time to do it.
Press the button button. Yes, okay, yes. Let's
go. Let's do our best. Don't
kill us. Don't kill us
that long. Ah,
Iris, Iris, that horn player.  Look at me, I
'm forcing you to blow the horn. No
matter where you went, you'll be hiding here and there. If you
need to recover, please go.  It's
out, it's out, it's finally out
Be careful, be careful, hide nice,
do your best, stop it, it's close, hit it, hit it, show it you're good, I
said my HP hasn't decreased at all, where is that?
Okay, top left, is
this?
Oh, this is so nice, do your best, do your best, do your best,
nice
[Music]
I was able to do it. Princess
Isu-hime. She's so overbearing. Why is she so overbearing? First-
hime. Wait, this is a princess. Moreover, Iris-hime.
Now,
I can hear it. Princess. I can hear it.
Princess.  What does it mean? It's a princess. This princess
is the princess of that warlord's Japan. She's a Japanese princess. Is
there really a Japanese princess? There is a Japanese princess.
Wow, that's a princess with a strong fever.
That's what I meant. Just
give up! The princess is really good.
That's right, she was a princess with a strong feeling.
Wow, it's time 5  It's quite different.
Look, there's still a lot of room for improvement.
So, we've practiced. We
can shrink it even more. It looks like we'll be able to do the color. Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's
practice, so we'll only have practice after this, so let's change
the server to 2 again.  Yes move yes voice
back
Go back Yes, it's okay Yes, yes, it's the first princess's street. The
princess is here. The
princess, the princess. Iris was in high spirits
as a princess. That's why she started calling me the
hot princess. Everyone who was hot had that new
cooking menu.  I think it was added,
but Subaru's fried chicken,
fried chicken, was really surprising, right? There was a
special
hamburger steak, and any pancakes.
Yeah, nice. Oh, I want to eat that.
I asked everyone to come over here, and I was surprised by how suddenly I was surprised, and I said, ``Okay, okay.'' I said, ``Yes, I
don't mind if you do it like this,''
but
everyone is doing a lot of follow-up right now, so
please take a look.  I just
saw some people.I want to see.I want to see.I want to see.I want to see.
Chocochi, what's wrong, what's wrong? It's
okay, what's wrong, what's
wrong? I was wondering if they'd suddenly make me [ __ ] again. Wait, I suddenly said something like 'tade', so I thought, 'Oh, it's a different person.' It was me. Wrong.  I'm
sorry, I'm going to follow up with people who want to practice, and what's more, as well as the relays I want to do. I'll practice a little. Those who want to practice, I'll practice. Stop it.  Is
n't it okay to do a follow-up once?
I saw that you can do it with unlimited players right now. I'd
like to try it once again.
There's already a red player, but I
think there's only one player, so I can't do it right now.  There
are three of us who couldn't do it today. Yes, there are three of us.
Look, do your best,
do your best, go to that other server with Chiara.Also, I
think it's okay if we split up into groups.I feel like if we cheer, it'll get messy.Okay,
so let's split up into groups, and the
members who are going to play the match.The members who are going to play the match.  Is it
okay to call number 1? Please move me to number 1. I
can't hear everyone's cheers. I
want to play while listening. Is
n't it okay to play on my own team? Yes, please move to number 1.
Yellow, yellow,
yellow, I'm
telling you to do your
best. Yellow, I'll do my best, I'll do my best.
Sora-chan is staring into space all the time. Are you
okay? That intensity is
like Su-chan's earlier, so I don't want to watch it with you.
I'm infected.  If you do something like that, you'll
be able to become an infected person.
Do your best, star, do your best, do your best, do your best, it's
fast Yomi [Music] Hurry up, everyone, go ahead, senpai [Music] Do your best, God, don't look at me So, do your best, 20 is really fast, but baku
yea ah oh,
something was interrupted, that's it.  I
can't do this all over again. I can
play around with you again. I
'm starting to have more energy. I'll play with you first, after all.
Nasui-chan, I was just using my legs, so I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I
don't know what you're talking about, but I'm going to use my fingers.
Maybe someone pushed me, or maybe I did something. I'm going to poop,
so I'll try one more time.  Let's go, do your best,
Mizu-senpai, do your best, do your best, yes, do your best, go up like Mercury, go up, go up, go up, go up like Mercury.If you want to see how it is, go to the cat's
spectator mode.Press the cat's purple color.  It's okay, it's here, it's here
, it's okay, is it okay? Do your best, nice and nice. It's fast, it's going well, it's going fast. It's fast, no, it's okay. It's still on its feet. It's
still there. There's no problem with your shoulders. It's okay.
Senpai: I guess A has risen because Min has fallen. Chiara-senpai is good, but this is the last one. Where are you? Yes, in the end, where are you? It's okay tomorrow. It's okay. Su-chan, first of all.  Let's
go to the checkpoint.First of all, the first thing is
Ceci.Let's have a chat.Everyone is right.Okay,
what did you eat today?Okay, let's see.What did you eat?What did you
eat?What did you eat?
I ate mackerel.Let's
go calmly and
calmly.  A-senpai said let's go,
okay, but we're catching up, so
yeah, there's not that much of a difference. There's not that much of a difference.
In the first place, this isn't a competition. That's right.
Where is this? Where is this? By the way, Sui-chan, if you
touch the bed
on the right side, you'll hear it. If you touch the right side, yeah, yeah, if you touch that, you'll be
able to respawn, so it's
okay. By the way, you have about 6 minutes to play, so do
n't rush.  Seriously,
don't panic, it's great, it's already 6 minutes, did the piala fall? Yes, it's pretty
good, it's grown a bit, this is what
everyone's faces look like in spectator mode.  I'm
floating to the point of death, and my neck is definitely
floating. My neck is floating. It's scary. I've
caught up
. I've caught up. I've caught up. I'm floating. I'm
floating. I'm floating.
But this
is the route. The route is based on the movements of my guts.  I get it,
just
go for the route. Don't go for the route. Nice. It feels good. It's
almost there. It's amazing. It's almost here. It's here. It's here.
It's here. It's almost there.  That's amazing, that's
amazing, that's what you did. It's okay, it's okay, it's amazing, it's
so important. It's all right, it stopped. How far did it
go? That's why I came to the bar. I think I was in a hurry. I said, "I'm going to
get an Uber."
This is amazing. It's amazing. I want to eat an Uber. It's
amazing. It's already a lot of pressure
. I wonder if the two of us will reach the goal. No, Korehi-chan
did a lot of work too, but he's
going to reach the goal. It's amazing. It's just amazing.  I couldn't  That's
crazy. I did a little bit. Well, this is because it
has 6 minutes. The
cooldown time of the Trident is quite short, so that
's right. I'll have to wait for today. Look, I
can do it all today. Yes, I
can do it all today.  It's just that there is a
possibility that there will be some adjustments.It looks
like it's
time to make some adjustments.Everyone has reached the goal.It's been a
long time.  Wow, it's
6 minutes too long. Even the old people can tell. It's
hard to do without it. It's really difficult, even if you do it. It's
amazing. Nice, thank you, nice, nice. I'm nice, nice. Thank you for your hard work.
Nice. But I really
like the yellow team. It's amazing.
Everyone.  It's not
true U-chan was amazing. It's amazing. It's amazing. Is this the winner? The
winner is the winner. The pressure is on.
Everyone gather around Anya. Noa.
Everyone, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best
Let's do our best with the Fang equipment. That's right, bring the Fang ray
equipment. Yes, you have the Fang equipment.
Please do what I have for the rest of my life, Fuwa-senpai.Why are you doing it now? Do
it the way you feel now, or don't do it
like this.  Do
n't do it, don't do it, grab me. Don't do it right away.
Why did you think to do it
?
Hakosu, please help me. With just one person, all I
can do is tsukkomi.
What's scary is that there aren't that many people on the Subaru Yellow team that day.
Yes, this
is true
. That's right. I'm just jumping in, but it looks like it's going to be fun. Looks like
Luff is going with the yellow team. I
see. Luff is going with the yellow team. I
'm sorry, I'm following the yellow team.  There are
still people who uploaded, there are.
Sorry, I haven't made an entry. Yes,
there are others, but there are no red and white members. Let's
put in a substitute and try again.
Oh, okay, wait a minute.  I'm
going to enter.
Oh yeah, then Nya-san, put your soul touch here. Do your best,
chan-chan. You've already entered into another game. You
might be told that you don't want to go to the middle of nowhere. You
can't enter like that in this world.  I'm
sorry, sorry, I can't enter. Wait a minute, then I can't do it because I'm an envoy. I can't do it. I'm in the middle of a game. Ah, items won't disappear. Items won't disappear. Ah, I tried entering without entering. That's right. Even if I re-enter once.  I
did it a while ago, didn't I? I didn't enter,
and I was able to eat.
Kaanya doesn't have a horse. Only A-san is trapped in the world of Gasen.
Ani-san and A-san haven't fought yet. It's
too bad. It won't disappear. Please help me, but if I
press the signboard of that color, my entry will be cancelled. I
was able to do it. Just a while ago, Aja-san
played Kiba. It's the signboard of the line.  Should I go and touch it?
Yellow, I tried it, and now it's yellow. Yes, I
tried that. It's an open line.
Wait, wait, this is the game star.
Even though there are no entries,
there are no entries.  It has become
Wait a minute, I
mean, do we
have to enter these three teams? Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's
right, try this Lyrica Red, Red, yeah, Red, maybe this. Mercury-senpai, I believe in entering again, I
don't have Ama, so I see.  So I stopped the game. I
see, but I can't do it. I
have a trident. It's the
same thing yesterday. There are
tools left behind.  Once
again, I still have a lead in the hunt.
This was also the case when I was practicing with Ririka in the morning. Let's
check it out. Ten-a-dan Unkochi
Kochi Kochi Kochi
Kochi This entry ah Enter yes
Yes.  I just entered and saw it, so I'm going to press the middle row. I
don't know what to do
. I still have the book left, but it's now a book, so I
guess I can't do it. Yeah, it's okay, it's okay, that's fine.  It's
the one from Ruhrbok, so it's okay. Well, that's it. I can do it. I can do it. Thank you very much. That's what I always do. I've always been good friends with him. He also has 41 Subaru cars,
so I have 41 of them.
There are 41 of them, 41 of them. That statue is already
coming to you. It's going to ask you to get along in the middle of the night.
It's going to come to you with your nipples exposed.
This is all pink poop.
Beautiful aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa  There aren't
too many tridents. Are
you going to point them at that point? Don't do that. A white statue is coming.
Don't get angry. It's hitting you all over the place in the middle of the night.  It
seems that the game master is
angry. The game master is angry. At best, he's coming in the middle of the night
. He's
scary. Do your best. Do your
best. Do your best. Don't try to attack me. The
game must be interrupted.  That's it,
who's that? Toa, Kiara hasn't entered
yet. Oh, let's enter Ani one more time. I
won't make it okay. It's scary, isn't it? Let's
get along. It's scary. Youkai has come. Let's get along.
I'm Nakaamaru-chan,
but I'm Areru-chan, but that's not true.There are all kinds of people, so now the
juniors are also the seniors of Kotomono.  I'm
glad you were able to convey that it's a nice ice cream.It's got a ki in it.It's still a
face, though.It's a smiley face.  I
was making this while saying "Kana", so I'm
not
saying that you're trying your best, but I'm not sorry.
Please do your best with your dirty talk. Please do your
best. Do your best with an open heart. This is good. It's a
completely different layout than when we were practicing. Ah, Nan.
Well, it might have changed. It's changed a lot
. There are updates every day. It's
okay. I
haven't wasted that much. I have a lot of time. That
's right, it's a cat game. I just went to the top.  I
wonder if he was a strong person at the time.That's why he's changed.That's why I'm confused.It does
n't really matter who crossed the finish line first.It doesn't matter.It doesn't matter.It doesn't matter.It doesn't matter, it doesn't matter, it doesn't matter, it
doesn't matter where you were in the end.  Yeah, I see, yeah,
yeah, that doesn't really matter. Goal, yeah, it doesn't matter. Well then, the goal is
reached. Tarama points, yeah, yeah, yeah. I
see. Yeah, I see. I see, I see. I don't
have to worry about it at all. It's okay to play this game.  It's okay to
take it slow, that's right, my own pace 2 Ani-san Ani-san was practicing a lot that day. It's a good thing. [Music] There's also a meter and so on. That's amazing, that's right, Ani-san is really good.
Oh, I have that bed,
bed, bed, touch the bed, yeah, I've
already touched the bed, okay, I should be able to go right in the middle of it, that's
good, right, yeah,
yeah, I see, that's right, it's Beth, I'm back.  You
can do it. If you shift from there, it will
also become slow. It's the
first time I've heard of it. Yes, it's going to be slow motion. That's
right, it's slow. That's right. It's slow. It's
really weird. I
practiced, I practiced, I practiced.  Do
your
best, Ani-san, you'll be fine. Yosui,
wow, what's going on right now? It's too
early, is
n't it? That's great, everyone. By the way,
Chiara is really stable this time.  That's amazing, that's
interesting, 1 point for 10m, so that's
ok. That's right. I
get a lot of points, right? Does this mean I get 20 points? That's
right, that's right, 20 points, 10m, 1
point, so 200m is the top right now.
That's right, the maximum is 20 points, that's amazing.
Yeah, it's okay, I'd rather have a small talk.
If so, let
me know. It's okay, don't talk. You can say it.  Not
at all, not at all, please don't talk anymore.
Oh, what's going on? I
'm listening to you. That's
totally wrong. It
's a complaint. I'm complaining. Even if you practice, I've
made some adjustments.
Masa, this has changed so much that I was
surprised and couldn't wait to see her try. But
Anya-san can do it, thank
you. By the way, she has already won.
Miko I thought it would be okay to throw it to the upper target yesterday, but it
was a high target because it passed quite a bit. There are a
lot of choices around here, right? It's
like making that slight adjustment when falling. The
goal is nice. It's about 20 seconds away, so it's the
highest.  It seems like it would be better to go somewhere else,
but the course will be different on the next day,
so I'm going to make some adjustments. It's the
last one, so if you can practice this as much as you like, it'll
be as good as the actual one. That's great.
321 That's why I was
in the middle of falling [Applause] Yesterday I
felt like it was easier to do yesterday,
but I wonder if it's actually getting harder.  Let's
practice together, alright,
let's practice. Then we'll all go to that gathering we went to, and
next time we'll do the replay, and we'll be able to do it pretty freely.
Either way, I'm going to go to Rele. I'm
going to go, let's go, let's go to Rere
. This year, the system is amazing. The
system starts to
warp automatically when it's the turn of the person who is in trouble.  It's
a bit complicated because I can't do it,
so let's do it together from now on. Let's do our best,
click here, over there, this, that's it, it's the turn of the
relay today. Everyone who will be participating in the relay today. Hey, everyone.
No, I don't think so. Well, wait a minute. I
want to give you a name. Let's all
run once. That's good. That's right, Iris. I
'm here. Iris is No. 1. I'm going to enter.
Black. Good night. So, I'm black. Ai-chan.
Sui.  Chankuro will save me, Sora-
chan, sora-chan, please touch me.
Where, wait a second, where is this done
? Um, it's here, Sora-chan, that's Sora-chan, where is it? Hold on,
press this erotic.  I've
got a book, so I'm
sorry, but
can I get 8 people to enter?
Yes, I'm doing it. Next Lily? Yes,
I haven't pressed it yet. It's okay.
That's the order. It's always okay. That's
okay. That's okay. Well then, Lyrica, I tried it, I did it. Okay, next time.
Wait, it's an even number. What's scary? It
's okay. It's practice, it's difficult, so it's difficult to do it.  The
half without Subaru Shiori-chan
is more difficult. So, okay, Aji-san, you
can come in with Gran, okay. It
's No. 8. That's right, the first time is the anchor.
Do your best, do your best, do your best. No, the first time is not good. Please
go, Hacos.  That's amazing! She played the taiko drum version. Masae-
chan definitely has a talent for microphone racing. She keeps
saying that, and
the other day, she was practicing for the real relay. Well, it's the
first time she's really messed up.  Those
people who started late started at the end,
but for some reason they became number one. It
started so fast.
Kachan-chan is in that book.
To the nine people who are getting books now.
Wait a minute,
there are 9 people, right? There are 9 people, right?
and  I
think, wow, there it is.
Um, the second operator is Sui-chan, the yellow
block, and opens the book. That's what
this is. 7. Yeah, yeah, that's right.
7. At the beginning, 8. Okay, that's nice.  Well,
now that I'm able to do it to my maximum, including for practice, I
can see
that.That's right, so you can ignore Ren.He will carry you properly at first, so I asked Obu to
carry you.When everyone is together,  start  I'm
going to do it, so it
's cool, so I'm sorry, Luka-san. Yeah, it's okay. It turned out the other way,
but it's too long.
If you say so, then you're not a senpai. I wonder if you can fix it.
But you're also a senpai or senior, so yeah, that's
right.  Oh yeah, that's right, I'd like you
to go to Iichan 2. Is this what you mean?
Spar after the polka? I
think everyone has entered, so I
think I'll get the baton. Iris, that big runner.  I
have a baton. I do
n't have a baton. All I have is that book. When I start, a baton appears. I don't have it. Yes,
when I start, Iris holds the baton first, and when she
hits the next steering wheel, that baton
passes.  Yes, I see, you can
do it. Just click on that left button, right? Left,
click, left,
click. Where is the second person on standby
? Well, this is this. This is this. I can't
see Subaru right now. I can't see it. I wonder where it is.
Eh, this is this, this is this, yes, this is here,
this is the start, this is the first half of the bell,
okay, okay, oh, it's come, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's
coming, it's going to go, it's going to go to Eris.
Okay,
maybe it's just the beginning,
Jean, it would be faster to jump. Alright, fine, nice,
nice, show the nice guys that you're cool. Alice,
princess.
Tasu-chan
is not a princess.
[Applause]
Wow, I'm not
sure if it's still good or not. The second princess is coming. The second papan is better. The
second princess is being reborn. The second
princess
is waiting. I can see the princess for about 3 minutes. Jump, jump,
jump. Nice last jump.
Do your best, okay, you
're here, do your best, okay, okay, okay,
okay, teacher, it's really fast, Su-chan, do your best, hurry up,
hurry up, okay, third person, so, do your best, this-
chan, Asui-chan, before, Sui-chan, oh, it's
delicious.
Kesui-chan, do your best, do your best! It's
hard here. I'm really not good at this in the second half.
Stay on, nice star, wait on the pool zone. I
can't do anything. I'm good for that wave.
Okay, let's go. Where is No. 7?  Iru-
chan, do your best, number 7, do your best.Eh,
next Ririka won't be here.Next Ririka.However,
with this steering order, Polka-senpai will be next.  I'm
sorry, but it seems like it's the opposite. I'm really hungry after all this.
But I'm hungry on the way, so I should eat some bread. It's all over
there, so I
wasn't running. Yeah, yeah, yeah, I guess I should eat some
bread.  It's pretty easy to eat the big bread. Left click
or right click. Well, left left.
Click o. Pick it up with the right and eat with the left.
Yeah, that's right. It's nice to use the left.
I'm catching up, fast, fast, fast, I'm catching
up, it's amazing, it's cool, I can see my back, I can see what's next.
Yo mentahujika,
dive, dive, dive, the waves are coming, so
passion, do
your best, you're ready, let's go,
physical passion, mental spiritual,
passive spiritual passion.
Passion, Passion,
Passion, Passion Mental, Fun Passion, Nice Passion,
Nice Passion Don't
think about it Nice
Nice Nice There's
almost no harm to it
Now, we can win, we can win
[Applause]
[Applause] The
lily that was wet falls down.  It's
okay, it's okay, it's
okay, do your best, be strong, be strong, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, Jean, it's
serious there, Rika is good, it's good, it's
okay here, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
here.  Uidameda
[Music] It's already
been a long time ago, it's so nice, it's so nice, it's so nice, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good!  The waves are amazing! The
narration comes from a polka narration.
Okay, do your best. It's a one-piece dress. That's a
one-piece dress. Let's go.
Do your best, nice, nice, nice. It
's okay, I can eat the bread that's lined up. It's okay, I got the bread. I got the bread. I don't have it. Daddy, I don't have to eat it. Push this. It's okay, it's okay, it's okay. I
have to eat the bread.  But I see. I
can go even if I bring some bread. I'll
go. Good luck, good luck.
[Music] I
wasn't nice, but I just
left and left click. It's amazing.
[Music]
Good luck, good luck, calm down.
It's good, you're good, you're
falling, stay
calm, you're the one who can climb, you're the master.
Yes,
yes, yes, I won, please
stop flagging, and I'm sure what will happen. It's
true, I'm wrong.  We're
only giving out 20%, so we're playing the game. We're
finishing up from here. Yellow team
A. That's the yellow one. Akochi is looking at Ako. He's
looking at Aso-senpai. Sora-senpai was
doing this. By the way, that's what Mikochi is doing right now.  I'm
doing my best, I'm looking at you, and I'm
looking at Miko, and the
waves are working really well. Miko, I
'm listening to the waves.
Oh nice, nice, nice.
Oh, it's going to last for a few seconds,
so it's going to show up. It's going to come out. It's going to be rewarding, isn't it? It's amazing.
Ririka and Sora-chan are fighting each other. What's
this space? It
's too hot. Youkai Niko.
Tomorrow will be better, isn't it?  What time is it?
Well, we're meeting tomorrow. It's
a little early, at 3 o'clock,
so I'm going to go to the studio at 3 o'clock in Suva, so I'm
afraid I'll be in trouble. Oh, and sorry, I
'm at work.  I
'll meet you around 5:30pm.Okay,
okay.Okay, okay.It looks like you're already ready for the follow-up.Thank
you in advance.I'll
see you tomorrow.Alright, we'll have
time for that later.Let
's chat.  I'm going to practice after this. There's
someone who wants to practice something after this. I
thought it would be great if I had a voice or something like that, so I want to do it. Yasa Relay.
There's something I want to teach you, so first of all, let's all try to
master it a little. Let's master it.
First of all, there
's no one who says the first half is better or the second half is better.
I
'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I don't know which one it is, but it's the one from
today. Yes, it's from today, it's not from today.
This is the one I posted in the chat.
After all, it changes even and odd numbers. Well, that's right
. 1 is Lyrica, 2 is Kuni, 3 is
Sora, 4 is Lyrica, Ajau is 1 is Iris,
sorry, 1 is Lyrica. Well, 5 is for Polka, 6 is for Bookmark, and 7 is for
Gura. Chan is for 8. The one who
can go is Black.  Yes, that's right,
Iris Is there a way to get to the place where Iris falls?
Please, please.
Here on the ice,
hey,
ice, yes, yes, let's go, that guy, you
have to run right now. I hit the space as
hard as I can. Wow, I thought I was going to run already, so I
got a lot of yellows, but if I have everything, I'll
do it.  The ice is blue, and I'm at home. I
'm practicing so hard right now. I've been
practicing so many times. It's amazing. I don't even know what I was practicing just now without even starting. Oh yeah, but
if there's one more race, I'll do it at all, but I'll just walk normally.  I
wonder how different it is from that. Well, it's a bit different. Is it
okay if I don't use this system? Okay, I
didn't eat bread just now. Yes, there's a
rule that says you can't eat bread. I
didn't eat it.  That's right, I don't have to eat either,
but if I don't eat, I won't be able to recover my physical strength, so it
will slow me down.I do
n't have to eat, but if I'm full, I'll eat.  I want you to
take the pas that you
didn't get. I think it's better to get the pas. Yeah,
no, I don't want to take them. Even if I
don't get them, I can still reach the goal, so yeah, I don't know if I
want that. It's quite difficult.
So you don't have to take it and eat it.You
don't have to eat it, but it
seems like it's okay if you don't eat it later.Isn't it a
violation of the rules if you
don't eat it?Japanese people always don't take it.  Well,
that's the rule, right? Well, Miko, I'd
like to make it feel like each team is together, but maybe it's a competition that uses a system.
Since I can't move, I
think I'll just gather the people who want to do it.
Oh, okay then, yeah, that yellow.
When we have a competition here, I'll
ask you to chat and then I'll go over there.
Yeah, okay, sorry.
Please, please, I'll reach you, Lillee. Let's
do it again. Are you feeling like you're doing it? This is relay.
No, no, no, no, okay. Just now, I
took that Lillet's bread, but now,
just now, I can't eat it. That
game.  You can't eat it unless it starts, right-
click, and eat by right-clicking normally.So,
there's snow behind that ice place.If you
do it right, you'll be able to jump over it.Yes, you can't
jump over it, you can jump
over it.
If the timing is right,
press and hold just the last line and it will say something like this, ``
Wow, that's important, that's important, that's
important.'' Hurry, hurry, iris.  This is the power of the God of creativity, and it's going to
change things a lot. It's definitely going to make other teams
come out like, ``How are they doing it?
''
Where's the best place for the cloud nest because we're going to bump into each other? So
tell me, tell me, where is the cloud nest inside?
But you know, I was confused too,
but it's fine anywhere, but the
trick to not getting caught is not to go there.
That's right, it's better to go straight diagonally.Yes, it's straight, and
when you really turn, you have to turn sideways.  I
think you can do it by just pushing straight on the right side.Okay, so the outside one is better.The inside part
goes in quite a bit, but yes, it goes inwards, but it's
easier to do it that way.It's not complicated, so it's
easier to do it on the right side, but the left side is better.
But it's faster.There are clouds on the left side,
so it might be easier to get
hit.But it's faster, so I don't know which one to
choose.Can I have a look at it
?
Take a video of me! Video
Who shared the video before?
This is it. It was Fu-chan who made a real video
and shared it. Turn around like this.
Wow, that's too good to be true.Video, art, picture, I
thought I could pass that diagonal, and it worked 100%.If I
try to pass diagonally like this, I'll get stuck.I
have to do it straight like this.  We
have to do something. In Japan, if you do
n't move, you can see the web of moths right in front of you. If you don't move, you'll get hit. I see. It
's true. After all,
judgment is based on mass, so Minecraft doesn't have any diagonals.
People from [Music] came here to help.  Someone
please record it and record it later.Actually,
there is a way to go almost without hitting the pool.Is there a way to avoid hitting the pool?  There's
no way to conquer it, it's too difficult to get to the bottom. I
want to write something other than the bottom. When I write anything other
than the bottom, I can tell by those three lines.
There are three lines,
haha.
If you go below the bottom, you'll never hit
it. That's amazing, but the
top and the middle are easy to hit,
so if you sink to the bottom and only come up when the bottom comes up.
If you're that bad, basically  It's
okay, once you're on base, all you have to do is go to the top.
That's amazing. The sky is here for the Kaishi group. It's amazing. It's
basic, except for the bottom. Even
if you don't collide and hit at the bottom, if you
push the pace just a little, you'll be able to go up.  I
think I can go a little ahead of time without bumping into things that much. That's
great. Well, based on this one time, it
's stable. It's safe. It's coming, but it
's stable. It's true that it's stable. Don't run at the cherry blossom spot. It's faster to
watch the timing and fly.
That's a character complex, isn't it? It's
better not to worry too much about jumps.
Maybe jump dash is the fastest,
but when you camp dash, there are a lot of failures. Oh
yeah, I don't know the timing. You know, maybe it's the stairs.  First
jump After that, press and hold to continue.Jump,
press and hold to continue.  I wonder
if it's good or not. Hunting is the same for me.
Honestly, the
problem on that day was pretty amazing. I see,
but I'm a little worried about the polka characters that come off with repeated hits,
so I want to do it later.
Hey, I understand.
I've never done it, but I'm a member. Um,
yeah, that's cute. I'm Hunty. I
want to play. Do you want to play? Well then, Hunting
. Let's try this Tine.  I'll
do the yellow one, and then I'll do the yellow one.
This means you can do both. You can catch it, you can do it, you can do it.
Wait a minute. There should be a turn.
Ok, have you
learned how to do it in order?  Once
you decide who you want to do it,
enter Where will you
do the hunting? Well then, yellow, I've done it once, so who's going to do the grouping?
Okay, Hiro hunting or Hiro
hunting, do you want to go hunting?
Well, I just want to come here just once.Wait a minute,
yellow hunting is good.I
asked you.Yes, I'll wait for you to answer.Please
do some yellow hunting.Other
members of yellow team.Ah, I understand that the red team
was quick.  Okay, now,
what should I do? Ah, then first, you
're a fugitive. Yes, yes, you're a
fugitive. Please push me. Okay, okay.
Okay, run as fast as you can.
That's right, but the color of that name might
be quite important.You'll
be able to tell by the hidden jersey.You'll understand.Oh, I don't
know.If it's not a top jersey,
people who don't have it may not be able to tell.Certainly if it's short-sleeved, that's
it.  Tomorrow I'll wear short sleeves and a different jersey. I'll
wear a jersey. I think it's weaker without sleeves. It's
cute, but the jersey
is really easy to understand. I'm sure it's a jersey, though.  It
's cute, but it's easy to understand, isn't it? It's the one with the
blue color and the shoulders sticking out.
But that kind of appearance is important, and the appearance is important. It's
definitely fashionable, so it's the
title for the second half that hasn't been changed.  I don't like it,
but it's not Red that gets in the way of Red, so
if you were behind the scenes that Red did in the first place, you'd be found out.It's
not like you're becoming a genius.  It's
true,
there was someone hiding there, but it's a lie. They
got caught, but it's normal. Well, they
got caught, but it's not true. They
were strong with Polka earlier.  The one
crouching down by the cloud
was really strong. All of us were
there, and we got along well, and this cloud on the right side of the statue
.
GI 0 people Oh yeah, the red team is playing right now, but I
had to catch the red team, so
it's zero. Oh yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
what's with the yellow team?
Cute,
cute. I like that.  Even if there's no group, there's
no white group, there
's no group, right?
Maybe the title is a princess, and it's definitely a princess. How long will they keep calling her a princess? It
's
okay to look like an older brother.
I'd like to try it a little bit. I'm wondering
how hard it is to catch this
thing. I guess it's just a cage feeling, but it
doesn't really catch me, so I
think it's better to be behind it. I think the strings of clouds behind it are better.  It's
okay, right, right in front of the cage
, but it's dangerous in the end, because it's close, so
this place isn't good. It's because I'm close. That's why I intentionally
put it in here, here in the back, etc.
Yeah, are you practicing? I'm in the middle of the day. I'm
chasing you like I've been caught, but I
can't stop. No, why is it that I
've become a bugger? I
'm in a
strange place. It looks like the constellation of Cancer. Everyone's like a cloud.
Data  I'm just doing this. I'm
so sorry. I'm sorry.
Even if the person who is repeating it ends up falling in the first place, it's okay. I'm sorry.
Thank you,
Akio,
please. See you tomorrow. Please. Thank you. I'm sorry.
Passion power, passion babye, passion power, mental
and physical, passionate
mental and physical,
mental and physical, passion, one more
time. Red should do it one more time.  It seems that it seems that it
is another time, thank you for the yellow escape entry
Yes Yes Yes Yes,
Entry OK Entry OK,
White Gumi
Well, I'm sorry, but our red
team still hasn't quite figured out the motion of touching with the rope.But we
can just practice the first half, just by interrupting it in the middle.
Oh, that's it, right click, move left, right
click, left, right, right click, remove, right, right click, right click, maybe touch left,
wait a minute, touch left, touch left signboard,
touch left, right click.  Touch the sign left Touch the sign  It's
a bit confusing to the left, but there was an explanation that if you left-click, you'd be able to release the rope, but yeah, it's really a bit of a bit of a
bit of a bit I'll try that once, too.  So, it wasn't
written in the rulebook that you
should catch it.It said that you should catch it on the right and then release it when it turned left.Well, I
guess I'll
try it once.That's right.
Fold it to the left and insert it.  I
think so, but I don't think it can be unlocked.Yes, I don't
think it can be unlocked, but there are only
two people left.It looks like there are
two people running now, so it's already a festival.You must
be wrong.People who don't have the theme.  I guess that's
what it would be like if someone was caught, right? That's not the point. When a
person gets caught, they get fired and
turn into a venue. Or maybe it becomes a venue or an auto venue.
Oh yeah, it's not like if they go all the way to Ao.
or try to put them in a cage
Maybe it's
like, ``Let's catch that.'' We're practicing a little bit now, so don't move too much.
Let's try to hit the target.
Oh, it's over, I like you, I like you,
what? You're in
trouble, stop it, I
don't like you, I don't like you, why?  I
couldn't stop thinking about it. Maybe I
like it. Sora-chan moves quite boldly. I
wonder if she should just keep running in this game. Even
if I'm running, some people are
running, and some people aren't.  Is it
better to stay or is it
better? Is it true that everyone runs together? I
don't know if we all run together, so it's better not to stay in one place.  I wonder
if it's like a stack kill or something like
that. If you're chased like that, someone will definitely end up like that. So
even if the festival comes or goes, this is still going on. It's
practice, so let's have them catch it. So,
how did you go to prison for the first time?  I want to get in, it's
cramped and
painful, I forced myself to get in for the first time, and I'm not good at it.Maybe I
want to get in.Catch me, catch me.Hey,
somebody, get me.I really want to get out.That's
how I got kicked out.If I
got kicked out too much, I got kicked out and
got arrested.Oh, that's probably true.  too many people
I'm being chased out, I'm being hunted
, I'm being hunted, I'm being hunted,
but I guess it's being added to the numbers, right?
Maybe, I've been hunted. Maybe I've
been caught. Now,
wait a minute, I'm having a hard time breathing.  It's very narrow, it
's very narrow, there's a lot of people, it's all right,
but as I was running around, the string came undone, and the senkyu came undone.That's right, when I ran in the opposite direction, it got that nice feeling.  I
guess I wasn't caught. What does it mean to turn around? If I kept running towards the Queen Whip, I wouldn't have been able to get into the cage. It's time for me to run away. Well then, it's yellow team Hunter Sora-chan's escape. I'll do it.  No, I don't want to do it.
So, right-click
with Sora-chan and pan left. Right-click and pan
left. Looks delicious. If I don't have enough left, I want to do a port entry. So I can
become the cat's fugitive, so look at it.  It's
okay, maybe we just have to catch all the yellow ones
.
Yeah, that's okay, Pol-chan, let's go. I'm going to
enter Polka, so I'm going to practice.
What's the trick? I'm
desperate for the trick, so I'm anxious. Why are you
crying? Pol right-click.  Left click right
click When you find someone, right click or o
Right click on the target Yellow first smile a little Good yellow
Even if you are not a hunter on the team, please
enter with that fugitive I'll
look for the entry signboard Where is it?
Yeah, it's a signboard. It's here. It's here. It's here. It's here. It's
here. It's really this. By this day,
somehow, I'll have to erase this button.
Click
on the left. It's too late. It's not too late. I want to
leave this on the Internet.
No one will see it.  No, it's okay,
no, it's okay to look at this. I think it's a little off-putting. It's okay to look at this. It's
fine to see this. It's
wonderful to see naked people. It's amazing. It's amazing. It's art. Is it art? Iris.
Iris. This is not art.  I
think it's art. I
think it's fine. I've been kicked out already. One more time. One more time. One more three. One more three. One more.  It's a bird,
so it's not like it's Suba-chan,
so I don't think it's a good thing.Maybe there will be an arrest.I
don't know.
After all,
it's about me, so no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I can't do anything anymore It's scary but it's okay to get along and get along and be white What do you think about it?  I
thought I would answer, ``It's not enough, it's not enough, it's not enough.''  I was
thinking about it, but for now, I
want to catch him.That guy is a
Subaru.I want to catch him.I
want to catch
him.  Left click, then right,
Furuka It was just rejected because it was different from the theme.Ah,
then it's okay.Even this is a festival.Catch
someone from the red group.There's a person from the red group.Also,
everyone is shifting.  It's true in the end  It
's white now white now, it's
not that right chestnut. It's not a left -click,
I don't use it. Left -click is all
right. Right -click in front of this signboard.
Well, I see. You
can release your arrest even if you're being held in custody. You would
n't release someone if you thought it was
wrong. Yes, no one is gone. No one is lying. They're normal. They're being
cut off. To begin
with, there aren't any white people.  this  I'm
hitting you, this is right.
Hey, I know there's plenty of room, so yellow is
here. Yellow is here. Check it out. Pol or Luka. They
put me in here, and I ran like
crazy. Well, I was able to escape.  If I do a dash, I can
run
away. If I jump, I can run away. It's fun. It's pretty crowded. The
inside is getting more and more crowded,
and I can smell the sweat. Excuse me, princess.  It's
scary, isn't it? It's a bit sweaty here for the princess. It's a little sweaty here,
princess. I'm sorry, I'm not here. Okay,
hunting, I understand, I
understand, I understand, I
understand.  Naya, I'll
make the next white,
so I'm going to enter the escape person again.
Euger A little next to the escape  It's
true that it's better to be white. Don't shave it off. It's dangerous. It's dangerous. It's true. It's almost
impossible. It's true. There are so
many strong antis that it suddenly disappears.
It's the antis that have disappeared.  After all, it
might be possible to make it lower, but it's true that it's possible to
follow suit.That's right, so
we should follow Sora-chan's style.
Maybe it's better to run around, right
here, here, here, because it's fun to run, but it
's not here, it's too strong, right here, here,
where, where, where, hey,
look inside this yellow building.  I'm in a cat,
it's very strong honey, it's very strong honey, it's
starting to get started, so
please call me by your name. Honey position is
open. There's one person. It
can fit two people. By the way, it's open for two people.  I
want to go in, right? The clouds are caught, they're caught, they're
caught, right? I can
hear the slimy sounds of the octopus. It's amazing here. It looks like
two people can go. It's
two people. Oh, the swing is nice. Bra. There's
also
two of us. Oh, the fence.  It's so unpopular
that it's dangerous.
Oh, what's that smell of hair?
Yellow and white are fine.
If it was Lyrica, I'd say I don't like it.
If it's true, I won't stop unless you tell me about it in the book.I'm
so excited.Asara was staring at me.It's
okay.I'm
embarrassed to be separated from you.It's my
senior.Our turn will come in 1010 seconds.I do
n't know.  So let's do it here. Let's see how difficult it is to
pull it off. It
's an experiment, sure, but it doesn't matter what happened earlier, I wonder
if it turned out normal. Everyone,
don't hide it, it's dangerous, Noel.
[Laughs]
At that time, I was Su-senpai,
so I was like, Wow, this place is really strong. I don't want that. I was
suddenly warped to this area.  That
's right.
Maybe it's because it's bad, but if there's just one more person, it's all over. I see. It's just
hard to hook it to something, but I
guess it's easy to catch it and take it with me.
After all, you can't move. I
like the empty style of running around, but what's
wrong with your eyes? I was running around this time, right
? I was running around,
but I got caught. Yeah, I was able to run away once, but then I
got caught.  But for some reason, it's
okay as long as you don't go towards it yourself.I
see, if you don't know who the demon is and
go towards it, you'll get caught, but now that you're running around, you ca
n't tell who the demon is.
No way, I don't understand it at all, so I just walked right in front of him. That's
right. The moment Noel and I laid eyes on each other, I was ready to die. I thought it was over, but I was caught.
That's right. I was prepared. I
can't stand up anymore. This will probably
be the end of the hunt. That's
right. I want to do voice work. I want to do it again.
I want to hurry up, wait a minute,
I'll just chat with you once.Next Hime's voice
is good.Skate.Next Hime's voice is good.I wonder
who the voice is.The voice is like a sleepy
princess.I don't want that to become a princess.I've
gotten into a fever.  That's not true.
Even the letters start from the beginning, so that's all I can
say. I read it, but something disappeared. That's it,
Senpai. I can't hear it. I ca
n't hear it.
Hey, but.  Is
this something? Wait a minute. Yes,
the vines are not like that. They just have a long start, and they
definitely won't fall. That's right. I was holding the vines for
a long time at the end. I was a little relaxed at the end. It would have been better to
go to the right at the end.
I can afford it, but I can't run in the opposite direction.That's
probably the easiest pool after all.It's
different from you guys who didn't put anything in the wrong place.I
can hear the laughter of the birds.  I
'm back to Mikomi Kochia 2.
That's
right. I'm going to close the streaming slot soon. I've been
streaming while I'm practicing. I'll also
be streaming. I think it's about time I
cut off that slot.  If you're going to practice something like that, you'll
have to practice in a different way.Okay, I'll
do the ass first.No, those who want to do it can do it, and
those who want to do it can do it at all.That
framework that I think is okay is still here.  I'll
probably go and bring it in for a while.Okay
, then I guess I'll just leave it as is.Okay,
this is it.It's that one from Unteshi, and it's
pretty good.Yeah, I was
getting excited earlier.Which
part is getting drunk?Minecraft is probably drunk.  I
think it's going to be a problem, oh, the knight's
guy has a lot of fang line, oh fang line, fang line, fang
line.The screen shakes a lot.  On
the other hand, I'm jumping
up and down, so it's better. Is it on top? If it's on top, it might be redundant. It's
not my intention, it's more of a movement. It's
okay, it's not okay, it's okay. Yes, it's
better than before. I'm going to practice after this.  It's
okay to do it all, but it seems like I'm going to close it all once,
so I'm bored, so can I have an o?
I'm sorry, I heard that.Hello, I'm
sorry.  I'm
thinking of
leaving the box, but I'm thinking of closing it for the time being.Um,
can I
have you join me in the room where everyone is?Oh, that's fine.Ah, when I
get home.  After closing the frame,
those who do it as they are will be able to do the same thing, and I'll
close it once, so I wonder if everyone gathered together. Yeah, yeah, there's
no
Ospor, right? Sporu, right?  Now
that I'm back, it's okay for the first time.Okay, yes, everyone.
Thank you very much for today.  I
hope we can all have fun together while occasionally supporting the members who weren't there,
so thank you for your support.After
this, I'll call the cat, regardless of the team,
but it's okay.I'll play around with that call.  I'm
going to call out to him as if he's someone I want, and
can I ask him to come at that timing? It's a
little bit like that, and it's the same with the Fukuga line that starts up,
and the same with the floor-up, and the same with Higo. I
can't do it all at once, so I
thought I'd do it now.  It's like I'm just gathering people who want to do it and
having them come, and I'm
going to do it, so I'm going to give it a go, and then I'll
close the slot after this, or I'll
leave the slot open, but I'd appreciate your help.  Thank you very much for your
hard work. Thank you again for your hard work tomorrow.
Thank you very much for your continued support. Thank you very much for your cooperation. I
apologize for the inconvenience. Yellow is
number 5 for now.  So, in the 5th part
[Music]
Okay, by the way, there are people who are still in the frame, so
why don't you continue?
What are you going to do? It's your voice. What are you going to do?  If you
want to, you can just cut it off and it's fine. Well, I'll
leave it to you. Don't worry about messing around. It's okay
.
By the way, everyone, Subaru won't be there tomorrow.
[Applause]
Good
luck to the yellow and yellow team.
It's like, mom,
where do you think it's okay
? Yes, it's Kado, there's a voice here, there's a voice here, where it's okay.
Well, it's not the school building, it's that thing.  Go
to the gymnasium or the gymnasium.
Yes, yellow, I'll join in. Thank you, Ama-chan. Chatting. Yes, that's helpful. By the way, Matsumachi has some kind of strategy. But when the princess calls out, I feel like we'll probably get along quite well. Just now, there was something red, yellow, and pink.  It was something like,
Yeah, he told me that when he was making the road, so
when I said that, I was going to move.I got the
impression that it was pretty easy to understand.  It's
better to squat down.
It's said that if you squat down and plant something, it won't fall.
Oh, that's right. That's great. Now, Princess Iris,
please say something in one voice. That's right, Princess. It's soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!  I do
n't
think it's a big deal, but I'm definitely looking forward to it.If I
don't get around 50 voices, I might get
sick or something.Even if it gets a little tough, it's
okay if you let me down,
so I'm not there.
So, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay. Is it okay for the first time? It's my
first time. It's okay if everyone is closed for the first time. I
wonder if only Mizu and Matsui-senpai have to enter that. That's right,
01 gathered together.  Yes, please use
voice chat 01.
Yes, please, please, please, please. Please, please, please. Please, please. Please, please. Please, please. Please, please. Please, please. Please,
please. Please, please. Yes, please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please. Please.
Yes.  I
hope all the yellow members are there, but
yeah, what should we do? We can be divided into 444 yellow members. I wonder if there
are any. It's
okay. How many are there now?
[Music]
1234567888 There are 8.
Then we can be divided into two teams.
If you can do it, Subaru, I'll keep an eye on that.
Everyone, if anyone wants to team up with you,
please do so. Wait a minute, wait a minute, please. Please go ahead. I'll
ask you a few questions.  I
have a question, but what is that? You
make something and then you guess what it is. Well, the
knights are not allowed to talk,
right? Basically, they
don't say things like "U" or "U".  That's fine,
but words like ``This is that, this and that is always'' will
probably
get the message across, so words like ``Yeah, yeah, yeah, put green here'' and things like
that won't be used.
In that case, it's okay for the princess to talk, and the princess is also okay.If
it's the other way around, then the princess is talking and the
knight shakes his head or nods up and down while asking if that thing is a refrigerator.  Do you
feel like it's a hit? No, it's okay. Is it okay?
It's okay if it's not a word. I don't know, no, it's like that.
By the way, things like that princess's theme can
change on the day.  Too
In terms of title, the first half of the story is
not exactly the same. It's random after all, so if you
play it with the red team, for example, there will
be things like a lot of paprika or a lot of refrigerators.
Miko thinks so,
but yeah, it seems like it's
random, so I don't
really understand, but it seems like someone just
happened to be angry, so I guess it's just a random thing.  The
question is, is there a possibility that the same thing will come out again even if the one that is out now doesn't change?
That's right. By the way, the
first half of the creative people who make it
don't change all that much, but the second question is on that
day.
Does that mean there will be a special theme for Japan? Yes, it could very well be that theme. Yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes,
yes. Yes, yes. What about the orchestra? There will
be some changes, but I don't think it will interfere with that.
It's not a thing, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
oh, yeah, uh,
now I can go with 44.
Yesterday, we haven't broken up yet.
Okay, how are you feeling now?
Okay, right now. Yellow. Yellow is going to gather at 44. Yellow.
Shall we do it now?  So, should I enter as white
or something like that? White looks right.
Change your entry to that white and use the same team that will be on the day.
Make another team with the remaining people and make this
red team. Is there no white team? Yeah, yeah, yeah.  I
want to cut things off. They've already
disbanded. Yeah, I want to do it. They've disbanded quite a bit. But we can
practice even if those three teams aren't all together, so it
depends on how well we can
do it. Hey, let's do it. Everyone, just
let Eto do it.  Okay
then, I want to do it as a princess,
yeah, I want a night.  Oh
please, I want to see the princess.
Then Mio-chan can come as a knight. That's dead. She's dead. So,
please be that Mikochi knight.
Oh, protect the princess. Protect her.
Then press the start button. Ah, the start
button.  Where are you here? Here you go. I'll answer the button. Should we
separate the voice servers? Oh, sure,
yes. Then let's go to the actual show. I'll be the first team number 2,
please. Yes.
Yes, yes, ma-chan, number 2, oh yes, let's
go.
Let's start. Can I have you to protect
me? It's ok, yo,
crocodile's turn. Don't worry, you're white.
Oh, no, you're a little fast, you're
not strong enough, you're strong.  Princess,
don't move, don't move, you're in danger, you're in danger,
right next time,
white, white, white,
white, pink, you're doing it, you're stuck, you're
separated, which is
right, white, pink, red?
Hey, white, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, princess, I'm
sorry, hey, the princess is already in this tattered state.The red is here, next white, pin pin, white, pink, red, please.White pink, pink, red, please.Yes, yes, pin, pin, don't move, don't move.  It's
going well, oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
[Music]
Oh, what's this?
This is good, this is it,
what is this, what is this, ah, the subject has changed.
Amazing grilled rabbit meat and viewer characteristics I
have a hamburger with a rabbit How do I
make grilled rabbit meat by grilling raw rabbit meat
Please do it with U Yes viewer characteristics  For
hamburgers, yes, raw beef,
please prepare potatoes and
carrots. Potatoes, rainbows, potatoes, carrots.
Okay, that's raw garlic, raw beef, beef, beef, beef, garlic.  I'm going to
buy some meat. What should I do with the meat? Mame lysine. Yes, I
used a chopping board to clean it up.
What should I do with it? But what should I do with the beef?
Use a cutting board to cut the potatoes.The
same goes for the potatoes and carrots.And
then grill the ground beef and the cut potatoes and carrots
together.It's going to be great
ground meat.You're just trying to say, ``It's ground meat.''
Please do
this. If you bake it, you should be able to
do it tomorrow. It's amazing. It's done.
Nice look, please take a look.
Where did you go? The
rice you smoked. The grilled rabbit meat is charred. I'm
sorry. Miko, Sanmi-san, this is also charred. It's
okay, it's okay, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's nice, it's
nice, it's nice, it's nice, it's nice.
And
on the left it's red red on the top left is orange orange and on the
top right is yellow hey orange a orange yellow yeah
red orange yellow red orange yellow red
orange yeah bottom left red top left orange top right yellow
Oji, red, orange, not red, this is on,
yellow, red on the bottom, red on the bottom, orange on the right,
yellow, yellow, red, yellow, come on, come on, okay, nice, I
didn't understand at all, nice,
nice, the dream is a battle, it's
coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming
through  It's coming and slipping through.
Just protect it yourself, nice
old man, do your best as an ancient weapon.  They're
all on fire. They're all on fire. They
're coming. They're coming. They're coming. They're coming. They're coming. They're exhausted. They're
exhausted. They're working hard, they're exhausted, they're doing their best, they're doing their best, they're doing their best, they're doing their best, they're doing their best, they're doing their best. It's okay, it's
dangerous. It's already yellow. The
team is clear.  It's not too early.
Why? Who's to blame? No, definitely no one
. I don't want to do it. I haven't done it at
all. By the way, Miko hasn't done it at all.  I'm
not doing it anymore. Sui-chan gets
irritated and stabs me really hard. It's a trident. I
shouldn't give her a weapon. Hey, wait
a minute. Do you want to share the same server?
[Music]
Yes, pop,
pop, pop, it's fast. Praise
me. I want to collaborate.  I'm looking forward to this book.I'm
looking forward to the golden one too.It
means success when something like this
star appears on the body of the other person.  I
even learned how to do a critical hit.It's
amazing, but the person with the bow who came out of Suia
ended up defeating the demon king, and I
wonder if it would be better to do it at the same time as the festival.I
really needed a critical hit with that one
last year.  The sports day was very
critical.I remember what happened last year.There
was mob killing and fencing.
By the way, there
's someone else I want to practice with.It's okay.Follow-
up is also okay.There
are people who will participate in the follow-up.I guess it's
Suisei-senpai.  The
image
is really fast, and Anya too, Anya-senpai.
Ah, that's right. Let's collect the follow-up. Let's follow-up.
Okay, if we follow
up, we'll
disband once. Yes, yes.
Oh, when was the next practice? The 12th
practice is tomorrow, uh, tomorrow. Yellow 1
o'clock to noon. I think I'll be able to go. I
might not be able to do it at first. It's
okay. It's okay. At first, it's the other way around.
If there's something you want to practice, let's practice together for a bit after this.That's the
first time.I've got
an hour left from now on,
but if you're doing it,
please join me.It's totally fine.Well, it's a good
timing to start with.I like it.  Please leave me alone  It's
okay, thank you,
thank you, you're so tired. I'm so sorry. Yes, thank you.
That's right. There's still one more person to pull up.
But who's going to come over? I've been practicing. That's why
Nemiko's stomach is protruding. Please put it away. I was
surprised. Please put it away.  Get out of your stomach, let's
move. Don't mess around there. Please
move. We're already
here. Why are we here? We've arrived. Don't say we're moving.
By the way, we're out here.
Asa, my stomach is
protruding, my stomach is protruding, I'm messing up, I'm so sorry,
but my mom and I are just sticking out.But the moment when everyone's hearts became one, it
became a blink of an eye.Tare, please touch me.Oh, I'm
late.Oh, oh.
Mr. Sensei-senpai asked me to
enter in yellow.If I should make it white, I should make it yellow, then I
should make it red.If so, then you can enter in yellow.Yellow, I'm sorry, I
made it red.Ah, I made it red.
Excuse me, red is open too. Book is open. I can
go, red, go, red, ah, nya.
Entry. I'll see if I can do it tomorrow. Yellow's player is here. Okay, let's start. Do your best. If you do your best, you'll be fine.
Aim for my
power, I wonder who's going to be the fastest. Who
can't go? It's already
begun. I wonder if Miko, the amazing creator, will win
or not.  There's a
battle we can't lose, but a battle we can't lose is
here. We've
created a new word, ``Give it your best!'' It's okay to go to Gaba today,
isn't it
? It's okay.  As expected, I
know the production route, so
if I follow this route, I can get there in the shortest time.  It's too
bad you didn't do that. You're really good, you're really good. I can hear you now. [Music] That's amazing. That's not it. Now then, let's get along. It's
impossible. It's impossible, Mr.  It's amazing how fast I can come
back while I'm falling, right? When I
reach the second checkpoint, I realize I can't do this anymore, and I'm able to
come back so quickly. I'll come back right away.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's not okay, it's mental, so
this game is all about mental Gemental,
mental or mental physical passion,
that's what's important.
So, do your best with
this, you've got it, it's
amazing, it's so stable, it's stable, it's not going
well tomorrow, stop dying,
stop, stop, that's it, yellow.
Subaru is
n't here, so I can't stop him. Seriously, he won't be there tomorrow. Don't stop him and die. I'm
really begging you to come in.
And no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I can't
stop you tomorrow. Seriously, he's not going to be
there tomorrow. Don't stop, you should die."  Yes, I'm with you, Lyrica, please
stop. If something happens, I'll take your place.
Stop it, stop it, stop it, Lyrica,
stop it. Lili, stop it. I wonder if I'll be there too.
Well, I'm relieved that you're here. Seriously
, I'm also a follow-up, so my passion is
going to be messed up. Hey,
everyone's going to be destroyed by the follow-up.
Come back, come here, stay here, Chiara. There are
still people streaming here. It's
messed up.  It
's on air right now It's on air right now
Why did it fall? We're
all watching the follow-up. We're all watching the final last
try hollow up. Tomorrow is the actual broadcast.
That's right, tomorrow is the
actual day of today's practice. Oh,
but I just couldn't reach another route. Good
luck. It's not a big deal, but if I can make it to the top, it'll
probably be almost the same as yesterday's layout. I
guess so.  Well, I made it to the top, but the
bottom has changed quite a bit. Ah, there are three. It's great that you've
reached the third checkpoint. Hey, here you go.
You stupid idiot, are you okay? It's okay.
No, I'll do my best.  It's
okay, there's still time. Go slowly. I'm
fine. It's okay, Ani-san. Please
leave me the speed of revenge. Please
leave me the speed
of ``please.'' Please leave me with the speed of ``please''.
What should I do? There's only
19 seconds left. Bad, bad, bad.
15 seconds left. I can't see it. It
's you. You're stupid. You're stupid. I want to die.
[Music]
[Applause]
That's amazing, though.  You've
done a great job and you've won, haven't you? That's
okay, no, no, no, it
's over now, so this is no, no, it's over for now. Now, after this, practice behind the scenes. It
hurts, so stop hitting like that.  If it's
a hit, then I'll see.If you close the box, please close it.Thank
you for
staying.Thank
you.
[Music]
So I'm going to move the voice channel a little bit.
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you everyone for watching.
The volume was quite full, so I
think it was a little hard to hear or loud, but
it's okay.  I'm
sorry that I couldn't respond to many things, but
thank you for watching. No, I
don't know, everyone. I have no idea
who or what team will come out on top.
Situation I'm looking forward to tomorrow.
Thank you very much. I'm glad that Ame looks like you're having fun. It was really fun
. But tomorrow I wo
n't see Swa-chan's tsukko. I do
n't know what to do.
But it felt good today, so I
decided to go maho hunting.  I'll
be Subaru-chan's big brother in the final battle,
and I'll be fighting as a general, so
I'll do my best, so please support me.The
actual performance will be from 6pm today, or 6pm.  When I
handed it over, Masu said
that this had already begun.
Before practice, I had a little one-on-one time with Nesuma-chan, who
taught me a little bit about it.  I used
to sing, ``Oh, right now, today.'' I
always said ``Oh, right now, today.'' I usually stream until late at night,
so I usually end up saying ``Today,'' but I've
gotten into the habit of saying that.
Hey, tomorrow tomorrow, tomorrow at 6pm, we'll have a real performance.Thank you very much.I've
gotten into the habit of saying ``Today'' in my mouth.I'm
scared, I'm
scared.Thank you very much.I
think I'll take it.  I'd be
happy if you could take a look at the second frame as well.Thank
you.After this, I'll practice a little, go to
bed early, and try to wake up at 1 o'clock with the yellow team.Thank
you
[Music]  I'll do
my best at practice. Good night. Thank you for your hard work. I
need to make sure I don't oversleep. Everyone called me. Thank you very much. I'll see you tomorrow.
Good night.
[Music] Good night. [Music]
Good night. [Music] T.  Even in yesterday's stream, I remember talking to everyone about the point of being a general, which is
different, but it's a big responsibility,
but then I
saw the hero team's chat and the Fang Line pair
saw that written there.
Subaru, I'm seriously in trouble,
and I'm all alone. It's a bit of a shock. It was a shocking morning. Now
that I'm here, I want to do my best. It's a
big responsibility to collect the flag.  It's okay, but
if you can get started, I'll practice here.Thank
you very
much.