[Music]
whoo
my
so
[Music]
what's up
hello everybody i'm too big i guess
this this is
this is more realistic hello how are you
doing
i'm young
come
[Music]
did i rest well
i
i think so yeah i got a good amount of
sleep
and then
um
yeah
good amount of sleep
uh and and and woke up pretty late but
but
i went
for swim
before the stream i know i know
unbelievable
[Laughter]
yeah it wasn't even that hot but i've i
looked at the weather report for
the coming days and it looks like it's
gonna get like
colder and colder like the heat wave is
not coming back thankfully but
yeah i want to make use of
the
decently warm weather as long as it's
there
but
i really i really can't swim for long my
arms are like so jelly immediately and i
have really really really really
struggles strong struggles to breathe
even after
like one lap
which is ridiculous but yeah so i go
like
um
one lap
breathing break
one lap breathing break
and then
that's pretty much it
that's pretty much all i can do
um
yeah
if i went like swimming
uh
like every every day or i don't know
every second day i could probably be
fine by now but
you guys
you probably don't have this issue right
it's so embarrassing
i wish i could swim more but both the
arms and my
my asthma is killing me
um
you guys have
like struggles like that
i kind of do oh thank god i'm very i'm
happy i'm not the only one
um
i have the same problem yay
oh oh i'm not the only one
thank you
[Music]
uh at least you know it wasn't too bad
like i would feel
so embarrassed but like a little bit
embarrassed sometimes when there's a lot
of other people swimming too
but
ah
today they were there was like actually
i was like the only one
in the pool
while i was swimming
so
i could kind of go on my own pace and
not feel too weird to have to take a
breathing break every
after every lap
[Music]
it's really hard to brave i try to like
while i'm swimming to breathe calmly as
calmly as i can
uh
but i don't know it still
still [\h__\h] me up
then
i think it was maximum 10 minutes that i
swam
it's just so embarrassing but that's all
i could do and now it's been like it's
been like um 40 minutes or so
since i'm back but my arms still
feel
so
oof
[Laughter]
they feel
like i can't i can't lift anything
swimming is one of the hardest exercises
you can do
i think one more thing that
makes it
more difficult is i'm trying um
[Music]
i'm trying really hard to stay
uh very much on top of the water so my
hair doesn't touch the
the water as
much as possible
because
well
pool water
is not good for my hair right now
so
um
yeah it's i'm like
trying to keep my body up that high
above the water after a little bit gets
exhausting too
a swimming cab yeah but that looks
stupid
i hated it like at some point
some school
where we went swimming
i think we needed swimming caps too and
or or in a hotel i don't know but it
looks so lame so
ew
i hate that
i hate swimming caps
but it would be a good idea but i miss i
miss dipping my whole head into the
water
maybe i should just say [\h__\h] it
um
who's excited oh yeah yeah i mean we've
been tangenting but it won't start until
seven minutes later right so we can
tangent a little bit
swimming like that gives you really bad
back pain
that's a bad swinging posture it i felt
like i had a really nice poster actually
poster-wise i felt like i was doing well
um
but but one thing another thing that i
wonder like people say swimming is
really good for your shoulders and so on
which i believe but does it also does it
depend on
how you swim
like you know um there's like how to
describe it the one way you go like
um
left right left right that feels like it
would be really good for your shoulders
but what if i just i can't swim like i
don't know how
so i just swim like um
you know
i don't know what how to call it
the normal thing where you have both of
your hands to the front and then back
and in front yeah
what do you call that
like a frog yeah like a frog froggy
wallah
that still makes you rotate your arms
quite a bit and makes you use your
muscles quite a bit as well
but i would assume that if you go you'll
if you move your arms like a wheel
that way it's probably even better
oh
i mean
yeah i feel like i feel like i was using
my whole body because my
my legs were also getting a bit weak but
not really mostly my arms and my breath
as long as i feel like jelly in my arms
i would say it was effective
backstroke a backstroke i like doing too
or like not backs not not not back with
the arms like a wheel but also like frog
that i really enjoy doing but uh
yeah right now i'm not like i don't want
to do it because of my my hair
yeah i should get um
a swimming cap no i guess
i guess
less than any swim time
i don't i don't know how because like
you go with your face into the water and
then you
it's so messy it always looks so messy
when you swim like that
also that makes my hair wet for sure if
i swim like that
i would want someone to teach me
properly before i even try it though
because like when i was alone before i
tried swimming a little bit like that
and i wasn't sure what i was doing i
need someone who knows how to swim well
to teach me actually i think i think one
of my friends is a good swimmer a decent
she had a she had a good form
maybe i'll ask her
no i don't want i don't want like pro i
don't need proper lessons in figuring i
know how to swim i just want to learn
that style of swimming
your back swimming is really comfortable
i like it but i'm always like scared to
bunk my head when it's a pool
so
i like i i i get so uneasy
because like i try to close my eyes and
enjoy
the comfortable comfortableness
comfortability
comfortable
you know the comfort the comfort of just
chilling and then i keep on having to
look up and backwards to see if i'm not
um bunking against something people or
or the end of the pool and when i'm on
in an ocean trying to do that then the
problem is that
most of the time the waves
just [\h__\h] me up suddenly i swallow
one liter of sea water great
can't chill anywhere can only do
back swimming in my [\h__\h] bathtub
anyway it's about to start uh everybody
i will of course not be showing the
stream
uh on
my screen so you guys have to open it up
yourself link is in the description
[Music]
i don't
and
apparently you know japanese nintendo
direct is often
a bit different so if it if it's very
different we can watch that one
afterwards too
doing nintendo direct watching oh my god
[Music]
okay
um i don't think you will be hearing
audio from my side either
anyway it's already live oh 276
[Music]
000 people watching on the american one
damn
should i write something in chat
99 of people watching won't know me
let's go
[Music]
uh fire emblem please uh here i wrote
something
just gotta stand out with my
with my blue mark looking cool
i have um
i i'm i'm approved by youtube you guys
are not
[Laughter]
so sad when nobody says hi chihuahua
this is a different universe people
don't know me
the realization didn't even show up for
you or maybe i got flagged as spam
because i
but the other ones are using caps lock
too
i see them all using cap's luck
hi kiara hello fire emblem please
ah oh there's some people saying
wawa
nice
thank you
why don't they let me write a message oh
did i get banned from the chat anyway
it's starting please note to the code 19
and release dates and
okay
it has begun
for everyone who's watching this as a
bot um nintendo direct logo is here and
gone black screen
if you're trying to sync up
this looks like a
jrpg
four ramps
four four rounds
what
are we starting with fire emblem
oh it looks like fire emblem
let's [\h__\h] go
oh yeah yeah yeah that looks like them
oh
is that fire emblem that doesn't look
like a firearm blended dude
but what do i know that sounds like fire
emblem the music
the style looks like fire emblem
that's why i'm blown right
nice
um interesting um
red and blue
character
but these are completely no wait he
looks familiar wait are these are these
completely new characters
that one's old the blue one
i know the blue and marv marv
what is this n-gage
who's then
you're really awake yeah
is this a remake
or a completely new one
yo those [\h__\h] in the chat saying skip
shut the [\h__\h] up i put you in the usual
room this is what i came for
completely new okay cool
but marv is there
sigger is he also new or old
cute girl
what is this coming up i think it
already did it already say date i want
to play this
cute
girl celine and silica
winter winter
i'm gonna have pokemon and fire emblem
at the same time
big dragon
january
oh
yo wait that art
that girl the blue
that art style looked familiar the blue
red uh haired girl had an art style that
looks so familiar to me
okay okay so it's kind of like after
pokemon
we can focus on pokemon and then play
fire and blend
so we know our schedule
oh
ah
the artistic
[Music]
okay headlines this was my headline this
is thank you for giving me the most
important thing in the oh
what
is this is this just a switchboard
yeah this is just a switchboard
great game
me and kelly played this
i was so
so so so good
oh
okay
okay nice
very touching game yeah
touching and fun
and engaging
[Music]
already played it but really recommend
it to anyone who didn't play it before
i've seen that girl before
what's the japanese title of this
well that's creepy
a fatal frame
she is so cute
is this a horror game
definitely looks like one
may i mean this is actually a horror
game i would maybe even play because it
has a freaking adorable cute main
character and it's it's like 3d so let's
go
oh oh
wait she looks like that girl from
she looks a bit like um
that
other new game
[Laughter]
but in red instead of blue instead of
green
soul hackers yeah that game looks
interesting too
soul hackers
they have like the same hairstyle
external blood
i will play this one day but
once i actually have time to play games
off screen
that's when i'll be playing xenoblade
this is where i say skip
although this could be something for amy
oh my god
i i i'm sorry i can't with spongebob
uh
i hate spongebob
what
okay
it's like one of those dance along games
but instead with like punching
that really
fit this box thing
okay
oh
this looks like a collab game
one two three four five
it's just the fact that it's from
ubisoft that makes me worry a bit about
online play
oh wait
nintendo switch well i mean that doesn't
make it better
[Laughter]
nintendo online
[Music]
yes
best game tunic game of the
year
i am
i swear
i wrote in the chat
game of the [\h__\h] year
go get it
go get it go play it
this is fire emblem but mecca style
[Laughter]
no i need cute girls fighting each other
not not this no no no no
nah
everybody's begging for breath with the
wild 2 news and to be honest would be
nice haven't heard anything new about it
in a long time
nothing in the recent previous nintendo
direct would be nice but don't get your
hopes up
if anything it would be at the very end
what is this
animal crossing um story of seasons
[Laughter]
it's pretty cute i never played this um
series before though
looks like a little bit less um
frustrating than animal crossing
because like in animal crossing
everything takes so much time just looks
like it might not
take up that much time for each action
oh my god they can have a [\h__\h] baby
they get old
oh my god they grow up
revolutionary this barely is ever a
feature in any other game ever
would be nice if then you can take over
once your character gets too old and you
can take over your child
oh splatoon
right
i never played splatoon before
recently everyone's playing it though
damn there's 584 000 people
watching now oh my god
and that's just just on one of the
channels damn
i don't [\h__\h] know
music cute
hey hey
incredible
i like the music it's cute
could be an idol song
[Laughter]
it is an idol song the squid i idols
i've heard something about them like
their idols
makes sense
this is what what snape snap
please don't just be a report of
something
of course it is
[Laughter]
is this octopath traveler
or what what was this oh yeah
see i was i before my debut i requested
to play octopus travel on one
um
never happened
give me time
let me play octopus
one first
i really want to play that
normally i don't like these like tiny
tiny tiny pixel um games
like i i would not choose them now over
something that has like you know big 3d
graphics
but i would make an exception for this
hmm
oh it looks really cool
yeah anytime i didn't
yeah there's so many jar jar produced
like from square enix that i want to
play
[Music]
but you know
yeah
[Music]
japanese members are playing them now
i could play them in japanese i think
but
nice
wait what was the date
i saw it but it didn't enter my brain it
didn't register
when when
february okay hmm
oh
another one of those farming games
harvest moon or what
what is this
phoenix labs phoenix
it's my company
it's a new one
okay
i don't have the patience and
i don't know
whatever
to
go through a farming simulator
whatsoever like animal crossing
[Music]
in general for longer than like a week
but
if it has like an rpg
[Music]
and battle mechanic then
that gets a bit more interesting
but still really the whole farming
aspect is not really something i'm
interested in
nah
generally not
i i want the focus to be on battle and
story and all that oh
[Music]
uh-huh
oh i know those characters final fantasy
xiv
the way he said it
good japanese
sorry i'm roasting this dude
a
oh
wait live alive was square enix
cali played that
uh
interesting
i'm just thinking about permissions
oh
wait doesn't this game already exist i
feel like i bought and downloaded it on
my switch
eh
a sequel
oh
i love rabbits
i mean like i'm not just saying because
you know pickles and but i know i'm
saying like i really like the the
rabbids characters
spikes
rabbit rosalina what king
what are those
stress box
oh
whoa
october
oh nice umbrella it's like a cobalt
umbrella but with rabin's
cool brella
oh
yo there's so many anime games today
let's go
push my antics onto everybody in the
nintendo
following
this
song with a banger
oh
hi
oh hi
they're also marrying
next year no date
[Music]
i don't want a farm chat tim's like i'm
tired of these five games nintendo farm
dialect
i mean it has been a lot of furman games
amazing
this is
yes
wait that's coming onto
oh wait that's coming for free onto the
online thingy
let's go
can we play them online
yes i [\h__\h] loved it it's snowboarding
i played that in my childhood so much
teddy somebody
[Music]
i'm a bit too excited about this
oh let's [\h__\h] go
let's [\h__\h] go
was this
james bond
give me my snowboarding
oh my god he looks like a sim from sims
from sims one
this must be really old game
[Music]
snowboarding
wait the game title is various day live
the game title is
various day life
question mark
what this game looks so much better than
what the title tells you why is the
title some [\h__\h]
i would never touch a game
with that name
this reminds me of a game i played when
i was a child
but it was underground
i think
okay now it doesn't remind me of that
anymore
oh dear
i think dom tendo so far must be really
unimpressed uh with what he's been
seeing because
enemy games are not quite his thing
[Laughter]
jumped handle is a
german nintendo
youtuber that i watch
who's reacting to this as well right now
oh yeah my oshie
wow very strikers that was fun back in
the day
oh my
not my style daisy's cuter
titty kong
who followed that thing
my
wife i love you
huh
rise up free on switch already
wait
we played
wait a second we played one and two
did we on my channel
right yeah okay i'll go again
oh
my cuties claudia
claudia i love you
ah
the chat won't let me in
i'm on timed out
italian atelier
i tell nier
how did he say it atelier how did he say
that
i can't [\h__\h] ride in the chat
oh rey free oh
merry christmas
not time that it's just you know um
what's the what's the word slow chat
thingy
nice
nice maps
i don't i didn't know these maps until
now but they look nice wow peach
guardians looks nice
on
wow
that's beautiful
wait i only saw two maps
does does wave three consist of two maps
i only saw two
i'll just show two but it's gonna be
more okay
how was that
i can't stop thinking about
the beautiful logo of atelieriza
and
[Music]
snowboarding
[\h__\h] snowboarding i love it
1080 snowboarding
but i don't think i played that game on
the 64. i played a game that looked
exactly like that on on pc
i'm pretty sure i played on pc when i
was younger
don't know what it was maybe it wasn't
the same game but it was exactly like
that
oh
konnichiwan
oh i need to visit super nintendo world
like 20 23 or so
i still didn't get to go
uh-huh cute
oh
oh i can't
i thought i never heard of this one
looks exactly like
uh pokemon go
with flowers
cute
wait that's
but like hmm
okay so it's just like an app to count
your steps basically
oh cute pikmin cute
i mean there are definitely people out
there who like to count their steps
because they need a certain amount of
steps per day that they're
that's their goal
so instead of a normal step counter they
could use that this i guess
pokemon go better wait does but does
pokemon go have a step counter
oh trying to make us [\h__\h] jealous
because we foreigners just can't [\h__\h]
enter for two years and he's like oh i
walked to the universal studios good for
you good for you [\h__\h]
oh wait it's not the not the voiceover
guy who walked there
felt like he was like
boasting on us that he's in japan right
now walking to universal universal
studios
thought it was him
what's this
oh there's also pikmin
looks like a movie
cute
[Music]
logo cute but that's that's all the
inside we get
oh my god it's so cute
there's something new on the bottom of
your screen
he's lost he's a lost child
coin
wow
where they're they're multiplying
there's even more
that one on the bottom right that's me
it's just chilling
he's so happy he's so cute
no thank you no you no you
more headlines
[Music]
know
oh
[Music]
ah
it's a good song
but does it have sparks yeah
[Applause]
i'm so sorry my dear and normal nintendo
fans who don't give a [\h__\h] about farming
games and anime games but this looks
[\h__\h] this looks gorgeous
oh
wait
i love
it
i love it
this is my style wait where's the
farming
i thought this was about farming
never mind then
wait there's the farming
but it doesn't seem to play a big role
it's like it looks like like the world
reminds me of like a mix of tales of
horizon and verizon
tales of verizon
i love the art style
bae
never played a bayonetta game either
before
but
definitely something on my list of games
that i want to play at some point in my
life
looks fun
i think i would
more or less like it too yeah john
they all look very funky
very funky
bayonetta
cool logo i'm i'm so into like cool
logos today
gotta appreciate good logos
um
yes logos
style
yeah
more anime games oh my god
i am being served anime on a platter
ew
i watched um the first season of
danganronpa
long time ago
i liked it but it was crazy
oh
a music detective
oh she's [\h__\h] cute
mama mia
the classic
really classic character protagonist
um um oh yes mommy kick me like that too
oh she's
so
cute
oh my god
feel that tongue
more of the girl please oh yes
nintendo chad is like so much rpg why
[Music]
what is this
they're so salty they're so salty we're
just enjoying it because this my [\h__\h]
oh
disgusting
i always salty i never paid so much
attention to the nintendo direct chat
ah tokyo game show week
oh man
i wish i could be there i love tokyo
game show
i love the atmosphere of tokyo game show
[Music]
next year next year
cloud games on switch from like i said
japan the internet isn't good good
enough i don't really understand what
cloud games are and i guess it's like
having it
on like a google drive or what that's
weird
what why
[Music]
oh
reminds me a bit of uh yakuza was like
the input
and that you can pick up things from the
ground like the combat
the combat reminds me of yakuza
where's zelda where's
zelda i'll be like
if we don't get any zelda
guys shut up if i'm not talking to you
guys talking to the other chad if they
want zelda it will be at the end so just
sit [\h__\h] tight
let me play
literally anything is fine
silver gun silver gunner
oh
uh-huh
rocking my breath come on
retain sanity
it's it's funny looking at them
[Laughter]
oh
cool
actually looks cool i like the graphics
endless dungeon
is that a port
[Music]
[Applause]
this gives us a reason to play tennis of
somebody i'm gonna cry
[Applause]
demon spare demon circle
oh
yes
[Laughter]
oh my god it should have been a remake
but okay that's fine
oh
crack
oh my god this is this is kiwa direct
they're doing everything for me
oh this looks so cool too everything
looks so cool this is jrpg direct oh my
god
lego brick tails looks funny this looks
cool
[Laughter]
the moment the moment i saw those wings
i'm like hey yo
hey yo
you know just a still image i'm like you
you must be [\h__\h] kidding me this
can't this can't be this can't be
no way
no [\h__\h] way
they're calling for me they're calling
for me
see i was looking for a reason to play
tesla symphonia too but now we can i was
like it would kind of suck
oh killed kirby i was like this will
kind of suck because you guys um a lot
of you guys probably don't know tesla
from phonia one but i didn't want to
replay a game that i already played but
if it's a remaster maybe i can take a
look at it since some switch too yeah
yeah yeah yeah let's
it go cute too
this looks cute
but i'm like ah i'm like in heaven right
now
i'm so happy
i don't care about anything else right
now
[Music]
just the fact that i saw tales a tales
game in the nintendo direct
makes me so happy i don't know why
and just it's nice to be represented
here
i i feel like i am tails
so seeing
my game there um
yes
my first ever tails off game yeah
getting a remaster out of nowhere
is this the first time they announced
that
like it's
why don't they do like um
a bunker direct for that
i'm surprised
this is kind of a big deal i feel like
for bamko i mean it's just just a
remaster but tesla symphonia is
such a banger game
oh god okay i need to calm down i need
to calm down
ah
sending but
hello
okay last trailer
it better be zelda otherwise people are
gonna lose their shits
oh
that looks like zelda
people are gonna lose their shits
regardless huh
i need to watch don tendo after this
okay
please don't tell me the only thing
you're going to show us is these runes
these moon runes
oh
okay
he's so fast
damn the speed
we already saw him flying through the
air in the last trailer
oh oh oh
sword remake
okay again not much but it's something
oh it has a title
tears of the kingdom
what
wait they lost the breath of the wild
thing completely it's not even
breath of the kingdom
oh
my [\h__\h] it was 2022 but no [\h__\h]
way it takes
until the end of next year
eh
wait
fifth
that's really important
no it must be may right not not december
is it 12th may or 5th december
is it may okay america puts mom first
oh okay okay okay let's [\h__\h] go cool
yay
december would have been so [\h__\h] far
away
wow
[Laughter]
damn i'm
i'm more excited from this nintendo
direct than i thought i was gonna be
damn
um my heart was for some reason the
remaster of the
symphony
it's just ah
made me feel so nostalgic
and and snowboarding
[\h__\h] snowboarding i'm so
[Music]
ah excited too [\h__\h]
and the prize i'm happy to see ryze on
tunic although we already played tunic
but i need to play riser free i need to
oh that was amazing i'm like i'm i'm i'm
i'm i'm i'm like i'm wow
i'm mind broken
five of them your fire emblem of course
they put it in the very beginning so i
almost forgot about it um but i'm very
excited about fire emblem too
new f wait so uh
new pokemon game december
what's the timeline like what comes
after pokemon fire on them
or
what's the timeline i'm looking for
fire emblem tales of symphonia
breath of the wild too
i already forgot the title something
kingdom tears of kingdom
so pokemon fire monzelda
oh
and symphonia
was where
was it was not like february
well well then we are we have a lot of
things lined up then
nice
uh symphonia was just 20 23
riser three was february
i did sinfonia not have a date
january for fire emblem
february for riser oof very very back to
back fire emblem's gonna take a while
but you know ryza why is i don't have to
play right away
um
mm-hmm
hi every stella
um i would have to look a bit more at it
to see if i really would want to stream
it but like the visuals are very
pleasing to me
yeah motion motion has to play it before
me so i so i can get some advice
uh
yeah nice you know since um
for some reason i can't play all those
jrpgs from square enix that i want to
play well at least now we have a new
load of non-square enix games
[Laughter]
that i can
play yeah yeah what's the square next
game what what do we mean ah the harvest
stella game okay okay yeah it's fine um
i'm covered i'm covered with pokemon
fire and blame raiza and
uh
um
breath of the wild too
although
you know i never played the normal
breath of the wild i just watched
two full two two at least two
full playthroughs of it
um
i think i watched one of them a second
time
so i i know the story and all that uh
but yeah i kind of want to play
too
yeah teresa of the kingdom
i kind of want to play it
[Music]
i think i'll play it when it comes out
yeah maybe i'll even watch
a play through again
a full play for again rewatch it for the
fourth time
or just
playing a little bit i don't think i
could play a fall
from beginning to end that would just be
so time consuming for something i've
already kind of seen
just to get like a little bit the vibes
of it we've mentioned it before that
this would be my plan
no a lot of the games looked really nice
to me
a lot of the games
easy 30 minute game i doubt it
yeah cause i showcase tomorrow oh yeah i
heard that for me it will be at midnight
but i heard that there is a state of
play
in
like
seven hours
yeah
for me it's at midnight so i'm not gonna
do it watch long i have to get up early
for a meeting and other [\h__\h]
thanks for watching thank you
are we back in 2021
yeah all those
all those games make you feel
like uh we're looping
the
rhythm of kiwawa
i was i was missing
therapy so this is good this is good
this is really good
[Music]
for
please at the end of the year please
[Laughter]
are you putting on a schedule for this
week oh yeah um you know things have
been kind of butter butter
and in japanese you would say butter
butter
yeah very um busy and all over the place
uh so i haven't even thought about it
but yeah
uh i might make one i'm i i don't i
don't freaking
might even go without a schedule for
this week i'm not sure
[Laughter]
it's um
oh i don't i don't i don't know
i was thinking however to read
um super chats for like an hour now
um just a little bit so we can
catch up a little bit catch up
catch up for 12 hour
12 hours worth of super
[Music]
chats a little bit so we don't fall
behind
too much which we have already done of
course but
yeah what about what about the german
debut of course i'm doing it
what are you asking that for hmm
this is happening in three hours
so
i have to prepare a little bit for that
i can't go for too long
it's in german but you guys are all
welcome to be there
my fourth debut
yo tomato debut
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay i will bless you
with my questionable super chats bgm
[Music]
thanks for the pinky oh my god i should
turn off the super chats
[Laughter]
[Music]
thanks for watching the nintendo direct
with me guys was fun i'm glad i um
decided to stream it
i seen
[Music]
i wonder
i wonder if gemma is watching
i wonder if genma is watching
[Music]
also i turned off the super chats
kitty master
supposed
i don't think she's watching because
she's not answering
guys
i'll tell you a
secret
i did an oopsie
i realized after i did the oops it was
not on purpose
i'm really hoping that she doesn't
notice
because um
[Music]
i can't tell you guys either because
you're gonna tell on me
yeah
scandalous
it is very scandalous
[Music]
i will apologize if my oopsie gets
noticed but beforehand i will not
confess to my oopsie
[Laughter]
[Music]
no i did my homework i did all of my
homework
according to the deadline i've done my
all of my homework
yes
some other myth girls haven't
anyway i'm gonna read some super chats
now so you know we get somewhere
and motion thanks for the pinky i don't
think 2020 me would have believed me if
i told him that i'd be following a the
girl drowned by hooked in this new
english whole life generation for two
years but here we are watching you grow
as a streamer in the street especially
this year with you number one
oh oh
there's more
blowing everyone away at first fast and
finally being able to shut off the
skills you've talked about having since
the start i really hope i'll be able to
stay a fan of you until the end you've
really enriched my last two years kinda
kinda like the warmth i feel from my
morning cup of tea i'd get sepia but i
still get got the member anniversary to
be a dork about my feelings and so i'll
end it oh yeah yeah what is that
what is that
member's anniversary
i told you guys to remind me yeah one
week ahead
27th okay
27th
let me did i put that in my calendar
already because otherwise i'll do it now
[Music]
i did i did already put it in my
calendar nice
smart now i cannot forget anymore now
motion thank you
i'm
it's like for me
i'm so happy to see people who've been
here from the start
to still be here because there's a lot
of people who left obviously
but
i i said i don't expect people to watch
one streamer
for such a long time like my expectation
was all of you are gonna leave me
eventually
um
after a year or so cause i
i lose interest relatively fast in
like
a stream or two especially if i would
watch them every day i'm pretty sure i
would
get sick of that person very fast
so
i don't
exactly blame people who decide to
go for something else after a while but
that makes it even more impressive to me
and very very special to me to see
people like you
um still here after two years thank you
so much
general thank you for the rest of the
chat two years of laughs three years of
smiles three years of inspiration and
growth two years of love and tears and
so many great moments
two years of takanashi kiyaga the
greatest girl i've ever met thank you
both for this amazing blessing here's
another great year yeah
thank you
yeah
very very
full
two years full with many many
memories and feelings
thanks for being part of it as well for
such a long time thank you
[Music]
beautiful red super chat i appreciate it
thank you soon
[Music]
two years i have to say that sometimes
all this
it doesn't feel real after all a lot of
things can change in two years but you
have been giving me daily doses of
smiling for such a long time canna thank
you very much for being here really
really thank you love you love you too
thank you
soon
i'm glad you're here you've been also
around for a long time thank you so much
for staying mwah
ultimate mk2 of redundancy for a red
super chat kiki key and happy second
anniversary
i may have missed out on the first three
months of taka hashi kiara but that
didn't stop me from quickly realizing
that you are my kamiyosi your cheerful
and energetic personality captured my
heart your skills and talents impressed
me what's a rainbow oh your dreams and
aspirations made me root for you and
cheer you on and your streams and
stories always put a smile on my face in
these past two years there have been so
many moments that only made me fall even
more in love with you the biggest ones
of course were meeting you at dokomi and
you stellar 3d performances i still get
phoenix bombs from hinotori i can't wait
for your proper 3dw where you show your
true potential
i might have said it before and i was
saying a million times if i have to yeah
i love you and i'm eternally grateful
for having you in my life and for all
the happiness and love you give i'm
usually not so keen or good at
expressing my face but i will probably
never leave my apartment again out of
embarrassment but this message had to
get out from every layer of my heart
thank you
absolutely no reason to be embarrassed
thank you for sharing your feelings
about me and kfp
with me thank you so much
means a lot to me thank you soon
symphonia collector's edition oh my god
thank you ultimo
um also free maps at the beginning
that's nothing don't worry about it you
basically hear from the beginning
donkey shoon i'm glad that you are not
sick of me yet
[Music]
please continue supporting kiwawa
thank you for being you thank you for
being you too
yay
[Music]
ah
i love you
love you love you
cruz thank you for the red super chat i
know i sound like a broken record but
thanks for all the loves and motivation
you've given me these two years no place
i'd rather be than your side by your
side supporting and cheering for my kami
yoshi as always love my wawa and i can't
wait to see what the year for you will
bring thank you
thank you for the red super chat yo i i
really respect you for
continuing
the workout you know
yeah even even when i
haven't been really working out anymore
you continued so respect
really i wish i had that um endurance
when it comes to working out
go go fight no fight though keep it up i
believe in you
um
you have to continue
forever
as long as i am streaming you have to
work out
don't ask me when i last went to the gym
i said i go swimming instead i went
swimming today did you not hear what i
said in the beginning of the stream
i said i went swimming
yeah
yeah even on a busy day where i have two
streams
why not both shut up
i don't have to go to the gym and the
swimming pool in one day
don't don't pressure me like that so
annoying
if i want to do any kind of workout i
will do it from my own will you guys
don't have
it's not not barely any in the chat like
maybe two or three people but you don't
have to make me feel guilty about not
going okay
i have my reasons to not go if i don't
go
[Music]
how about you are you going to the gym
huh
i want to see your abs show me your abs
show me your calves that you could cut
people with
and lift me with those arms try try
i want to see
where are the abs huh
can you cut
my my pizza with your calves yet
nah and i didn't think so
didn't think so
we had chicken squares so what
what do you expect from me i should be
expecting from you as well
triggered me
you triggered me guys
triggered me hard
so [\h__\h] triggering
[Music]
i can lift 80 kilogram okay i wasn't
talking about you though
cause you weren't
pushing me triggering me
eh
i went back to watch your first karaoke
stream again this morning and it isn't
showing up
my first cutout okay
[Music]
my first r card karaoke i don't know why
that would be suddenly um private
is that really so
it is
unarchived then
no surprise eh
what do you mean
what
well i'm confused
which one are we even talking about
[Music]
better for this one
you're so sweet for going back to such
old streams still
thank you
let me see
[Music]
oh it won't let me
it won't let me go to the last page
there's a button
for go to first page there's a button to
for go to the previous and to the next
page but there's no button for go to
last page
it kind of sucks
okay whatever
yeah whatever anyway continue got ain't
got no time for this
uh kiana's chicken nugget happy second
anniversary i can't believe it's been
that long since you became my aussie
oh
i couldn't be proud of what you've done
so far yeah like the idol you are you
help me be happy and you inspire me
every day and cheering for your future
concert and song release
thank you for the red super chat
thank you soon
oh
i'm i'm happy i can inspire you
um
future concert and song releases
hopefully
i wanna i wanna do more i wish i could
release a new song every month but then
i guess it wouldn't be so special
anymore ever done well but
but
it may take time
but at least they
turn out to be bangers
[Music]
i put a lot of love into them
so please
wait for
future songs and concerts okay
thank you
i know thanks for the rants
wow
oh [\h__\h]
my first ever 500 super chat happy two
years anniversary kiwana these past two
years were probably the happiest time of
my life and it's all because of you
no matter how bad i feel you always
cheered me up you made my life so much
happier you are seriously so incredible
thank you so much for everything you do
danto
thank you for being so sweet
you know with people like you who watch
me every day i wonder what you guys did
before
like how did you spend your time before
who did you watch before
what were you doing before
i'm genuinely curious
anime
i had a life
and now not anymore
watched anime
too much okay most of you were just
watching a lot of anime
or twitch
pewdiepie
only started wow
played a lot of games other streamers to
watch
non-v2 for streamers thinking about life
you had a lot of time to think then
animes games
yeah
i see i see i see flash tubers
[Music]
hmm
wrestling
and video games
i watch at school so not much time for
youtube
oh
that is understandable
[Music]
what what's the what do you not like
about flash tubers the term
anyway thank you so much unknown you're
so sweet i'm so happy to have you around
wait actually it's you're [\h__\h]
kidding me
as if 500 wasn't already enough you sent
one two three four free
three pinkies after that
you're kidding me
unknown
relax
you're the most hard-working person i've
ever seen and i'm always extremely proud
you are my oc i really
wish i could give you back even just a
fraction of the happiness that you
always give us
you deserve to be the happiest person in
the world you're my only ocean i'll
always support anything and everything
you do forever there really is no one
else in this world who is as amazing as
you
while you're truly irreplaceable you
seriously are the best even after two
years you still somehow managed to make
me love you even more with every single
stream what
i love you so much mate what she love me
more than anything ever looking forward
to making many more wonderful memories
with you on kfp in upcoming years thank
you so much
that's so sweet
thank you soon
i love you too
thanks for always being respectful
and loyal
and respectful
and loyal and you know boundaries and
[\h__\h] thank you so much
it's great to have you here
always like a
positive
sunshine is what i feel when i read your
your tweets
at me
[Music]
like a rainbow
yeah
thank you
thank you insane support incredible
thank you was not necessary to give that
much
but it will be invested in
my cats my streams
and my my rent
and clothes cute clothes and everything
everything
thank you
looking for the top thanks for the pinky
congratulations on surviving these two
years of taking a leap of faith and
becoming a beacher
i'm happy that the support of kfb is
stronger than the problems you faced on
or off camera and kept you going you're
a lovely and dorky girl so i'd be sad to
lose you so let's keep going strong
for years to come we're gonna make the
kibaba enter reality
i don't think i can continuously stream
until i'm kibaba for real
but maybe like a comeback once i am
kibaba
and see if you guys are still alive at
that time as well
like a reunion
we have to stay in touch then
um
stay in touch guys yeah
i always wanted to do some kind of
reunion like in like in my life
but
i was never invited to a school reunion
before
[Music]
so
would be nice to have a whole life
related reunion
with my unhealthy lifestyle
for that you have to live healthier
to make it until the reunion
please
live
live on
try
chris didn't get his kiss
there you go
you guys
ah anyway i think you're looking for the
tab
it was also
indeed
a leap of faith
but
i i didn't really have anything to lose
at that moment
because i already like gave up
everything at that point for to in order
to go to working holiday
in japan for one year i already quit my
job and let go of my apartment and all
that so
yeah there was nothing to lose
thankfully i was in a position like that
where
i could take my chances and i mean i had
experience with
things like this so
didn't really have to learn anything new
for it or so
not not anything like really big in
particular but
um
so maybe it was not that much of a leap
of faith
but
it was it was
worth it
and i'm so glad i did it so lucky
so lucky
thanks for the memberships oh
well thank you
more and more goofies
[Music]
i knew it i knew it i knew it was me
i was i didn't want to say it in case i
was wrong but once i saw the art i was
like
this looks like bei's mama artwork i
[\h__\h] knew it i'm so good at
recognizing art even though that it's
not as like
flashy as
her other artworks
did bales recognize it the moment she
saw it though
because i didn't
i recognized
her the first moment i saw bale's
design
i was like this is this is mika picasso
holy [\h__\h]
i wonder if she was um interested in
fire emblem though i don't know what
bay's stance is on fire emblem
in any any case i will i will play it oh
i'm ready for another fire emblem
adventure
oh she didn't realize in her watch along
[Music]
she had a lot of zoomer reactions
what are zoomer reactions
she probably when she saw the tales of
sinfonia remastered she was just
it must have been like a big difference
in reactions
i want i want someone to compare
our reactions to certain things and see
see what the big differences are
someone doing like a side to side for
the biggest
reaction differences
[Music]
she saw golden eye and was just confused
what
she was hyphen bayonetta yeah well i i
would imagine
boomer versus sumo excuse me
the only thing she recognized was a
mario kart ds course
what
how was her reaction to snowboarding how
was there
probably absolutely nothing ah
uncultured fails
doesn't recognize snowboarding
ah
i cultured it so uncultured
she hasn't heard of pikmin
what
mamma mia mamma mia
it it was
besides pikmin because i i didn't even
play pikmin before but i know pikmin but
besides that game
pretty much everything except also the
boxing game what the [\h__\h] but besides
that it was so much a kiwa
directed nintendo direct
please someone
someone do that comparison
cow carrot please
[Music]
um
just for the charm there's no charm
about that game
[Music]
could i really like the boxing game are
you for real
i guess
i mean
it fits her i guess boxing
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
she was laughing at the cell phone game
forcing you to exercise oh the the
pikmin one you mean
when you walk around just that's not
really much forcing you to exercise just
forcing you to walk
[Music]
of course i
am it's a bad [\h__\h] time that i play
rise or free
okay let's go
where was i
i am right ghana thank you for the
double rainbow
and hallelujah there's not much text
here you're a blessed i love you right
ghana
so years thank you for being you and for
being here all of this time let's keep
going on for more many years love you
boss
you are the best try ghana
thank you so much love you too
beautiful rainbow thank you
wait so rigana you've also been here
from the beginning
or not i'm not sure
but if yes and thank you if no then
that's fine thank you as well
i'm really happy to have you around
thank you
[Music]
all right
then we gotta know well
i mean if it's this many then i'm happy
the less text the better
i joined last summer oh
last summer
so that's like a little bit more than a
year or like a year
wow
then you must stay until the end because
you you need to make up for the time
you've missed
but honestly
oh dear
yesterday
i was
um for
for the
um 360 stream
on ama channel
uh
um we
we were asked to
provide some memories in screenshots
and
besides
ame maybe i think amen may have
but she had better [\h__\h] to do
so she kind of asked us but i was
actually the only one
i was the only one providing
screenshots
so
that's why i say i'm the only one doing
my [\h__\h] homework
um
[Music]
that's why there's so many of my streams
but not only my streams i also um
i i i
am provided like the ttrpg as well 15
rpg screenshot
but anyway because i was like going for
streams looking for moments
it's only me
i tried to fill both of the white boards
you know i didn't want it to be empty so
i tried to provide as many as possible
and then i went for some older streams i
went for the first collaboration that we
did on my channel
and hearing my voice
back then hurt me so much it's so cringe
oh my god
oh
i wonder how
i i think i personally think
the sound of my voice changed a lot
compared to the beginning
[Music]
but i wonder how i
will sound to myself like in two years
from now or so
i feel like it already went through
a big change
um
damaged
my vocal cords are damaged
[Laughter]
it's gotten a lot more calmer yeah
damaged
it's both the microphone but also
my voice tone tone of voice in general i
think
[Music]
and also not only that a little bit is
also like me getting more and more used
to speaking english all the time
um
changed a little bit of the way i speak
i
think and intonation and all that
and also getting used to streaming so
much regularly
um
gives you a good feeling on how to talk
like your way of talking will
get better
way of talking towards an audience like
a streamer way of talking
um
i was so cringe to listen to myself
that's why i didn't do another
debut watch along because it's so
[\h__\h] cringe
uh i don't know how kelly does it
but i'm i'm
i'm i must say
i'm
i'm happy she acknowledges
the cringe of the tiki tihi tihi
because i have to be honest
when i was watching it back then i was
also cringing at that
i couldn't tell her though
i was like oh that's your thing
that that that's going to be your thing
the tet you you're going with that cool
okay cute haha
[Laughter]
[Music]
i couldn't say anything
kept the girl though the gun is fun
the guy is fun
it didn't last long though yeah i teased
her about it in the collab and even
though it was it was vr and
our expressions were like the same the
whole time when she looked at me in
silence
i
i felt a feeling of fear
that i've never felt ever before and a
feeling of anger in her eyes
of anger and threat that i've never
never seen before the way she looked at
me like
[\h__\h]
i will kill you if you don't shut up
right now how dare you t
t at me but you
not even 24 hours ago you were making
fun of yourself saying
[Music]
i was just trying to tease her
oh man
[Music]
how do you say cringe in japanese
i i i'm not sure i feel like kimoy is
not quite
the right way for the right word for it
it's not exactly the same because kimoy
is more like disgusting
yeah
hitsui would be it yeah
[Music]
kitsune actually is fitting
is more like lame
okay okay now that we
got that out of the way
continuing
um
let me have a ducation
so that's keyblade thank you for the red
super chat
to use the burnham superchats i'll keep
it short thank you
congrats for the past two years you're
so amazing and wonderful hardworking
creative extremely entertaining the
absolute light of my day in light of my
life every day and seeing you improve so
much as a person and wait uh [\h__\h] it's
so easy to find things to praise you
about gomez
yeah you were
on the
brick bring
bring
brink
b
brink is that the way
yeah
of
going on and on and on and on and on and
on
you stopped yourself there
congratulations you have control over
yourself that is
that is a good skill to have
nice thank you for holding yourself back
but i'm so happy to hear all these
sweet
words of praise thank you soon
[Music]
that's something i don't have
yeah i mean no you do have it in other
ways
don't worry
[Music]
me
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
i slapped my forehead really hard to
snap
it clearly really
in her news show
pick up
amelia
trent amelia who the [\h__\h] is emilia i'm
a translating
sword
in korean
i just
saw in our discord the clip
honestly
what kind of news is that
where did she get her
it
[Music]
how is she gonna explain the reason she
was laughing at them
yay wait i can translate things directly
like if i want to say
sword
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay we're not going to repeat that one
i
[Music]
you guys didn't hear anything
[Laughter]
i just said sword because we're you know
the blacksmith is right there
hi oh where is
[Music]
oh she's getting to it
i mean
[Music]
it doesn't
as well
[Music]
and she's making excuses that she
shouldn't have said it out loud herself
but hey it was korean
is this really newsworthy
it's so hard to explain the situation
ah funny though
wait what
oh shut up fio
okay
everyone
back into your seats
calm yourselves
calm
yourselves
i'm on the road the roasts
someone has to be
[Music]
okay
does coin understand though
i wonder
john bieber thank you for the pinky
congratulations on your second
anniversary so i'm following you from
the debut until now it is already two
years time flies fast my first
anniversary merch comes
today i read it for one year to receive
it when you read this i receive you
you were not the only one
i've seen it
which is
shocking to me and i am sorry
i
that is ridiculous
[Laughter]
that is ridiculous yeah some countries
just receive it extremely late but i
think a lot of you guys had it much
earlier already right like a few months
earlier hopefully
um
it was ems yeah it's not even like geek
jack or whole live or anyone's fault
it's
[\h__\h] ems
not wanting to ship things
so
blame it on blame it on the postal
services
ah
that is so unfortunate but has it does
that mean it has been resolved
does that mean finally
they're sending [\h__\h] out now
at least to germany huh
[Music]
i can't get rain as much why
well the two-year anniversary merch
should be ordered to mate what made to
order i mean
so it should be fine as long as you
order it within the month
showing a lot of leg on that stand up
but
lane is sold out
within a minute that's weird
well you'll have to talk to reina about
that i don't know what they're doing
with their merchandise
and why it's limited
i don't know why
must have changed their system in that
case but
and yeah probably if if there's so much
demand then they might do a restock um
don't give up yet
oh she's talking to management oh there
you go
anyway thank you john bieber i'm so
happy you finally got the merchandise
i'm so sorry it took so long that's
really frustrating
but now you can look at it and since it
came at this really good timing you can
look at it and think it's the two-year
anniversary merchandise
and when you get the two-year
anniversary mention as you can look at
it and think it's the three year
anniversary merchant now hopefully this
time yeah it won't take that long this
time it should be shorter
but you know
it's the perfect timing if you think
about it
if it was like
like three months before or so it would
have been a bit more awkward or three
months after it would have been more
awkward there's a reason it came at this
exact timing so that the arrival would
be less awkward
[Music]
all according to keikaku
can't wait to get my small wawa
i'll be very honest with you guys
i must have missed some kind of memo
but i
was not aware
of these plushies
until
the 360 stream
during the actual stream
where we went behind the curtains
and ammo told us to pick these up and
bring them to the front
i
i was like
when
plushies what
why was i not aware of this
i knew about the acrylic stands and all
that
because
i was the one
to
suggest
the style and theme of the outfits
i gave
um suggestions
and was pretty much the only one because
everyone agreed that this is nice uh the
only one who gave like suggestions of
what they should look like
[Music]
[Laughter]
because i went through a lot of like
idol outfits that i liked and gave them
as examples and they were like oh yeah i
like this one i like this one
yeah yeah yeah
which i'm happy that i liked it
i would like to
personally though
design a full outfit a full idol outfit
because this was just like designed by
the artist inspired but
inspired by the material that i gave
them
yeah the tiny hats were part of it
kelly was like oh i like the the top
pads little top hats yeah we should have
them too
[Music]
yeah yeah
um
maybe it's worth saying that these
outfits
are
at the moment at least or like pretty
sure like for sure
just for this two-year merchandise this
is not gonna be like our official idol
outfits
like you know the the whole live japan
idol outfits
[Music]
one day we'll have them
and in that case i would
probably want
to
be a bit more
involved
than i already was
in the designing process and give more
feedback and
um be a bit more picky and so on
yeah
anyway i want to talk more about this
during an actual
like stream where i need to talk
about things
so for now we continue
uh
james what thank you for
a rainbow oh thank you become religious
congratulations on two years and hype
for kiana year free
ever since i started watching you
regularly your streams have been enough
to make me smile and love every time
really
i'm glad you're so driven to do fun and
great things and i'm thankful i'll be
around to see your third year i'm sure
it will be great
thank you so much
really am i really entertaining i'm
happy to hear that because like
i'm i even have issues um
like watching other people even if it's
funny it doesn't really make me laugh
much like laugh out loud
but i'm happy i can cheer you up and
share some happiness with you
and that my streams are so interesting
to you that you would look them look at
them for a long amount of time
thank you so much thank you chad thank
you
thank you
thank you swagburg
i will have my eyes on you
to make sure you're really around for
the coming year yeah i got my eyes on
you
thank you for the rainbow
yummy next time
thanks for two pinkies
happy [\h__\h] anniversary of battle of
i mean your debut what
to think you've been with us for two
years now and ever since i found purpose
in my life
am i your purpose
a lot happened since then many songs
cover this birthday concert that so blow
me away still have fond memories from
you dokamikan say hey when i was there
hope to see you on stage as part of live
audience again thank you for still being
a lovely phoenix that is worth following
love your tantrum looking forward to
another unkfb thank you
love you too
the dokomi concert honestly everyone who
was there
especially in the second year
i feel like
that was such a precious memory
that will
it's it's a very very
hard to say
vibrant memory
i think
as kfp
we were all very proud to be kfp
at that convention
i was proud to have you guys there
representing me so
what's the word
so openly and
proudly
and
i couldn't have asked for
a better fandom at that time
yeah
yeah the meet and greet hell man you
know took me overall
there were a lot of problems in that
year
behind the scenes
um
that really
make the chances
weaken the chances for me being there
next year
um
but you guys made it worthwhile even
even though you know the whole mess up
with
people not being there at the meet and
greet because they didn't get a memo
and me having to do how many hours was
it
of exhausting meet and greets passed
past the closing time of the venue 9 p.m
that was ridiculous i was so exhausted
but i had to do it and i did it for you
guys because i love kfp and i will i
will suffer
to make it worthwhile for you guys but
it was just so many things wrong
on that day
and
i i'm not the only one who is upset
about it
so that's very sad but i'm still
so happy
about all the kfp who showed up there
and supported me there
and i will never forget
that it happened
um
[Music]
oh yes oh yes oh yes it has been
it has been
shared
the sentiment has been very much shared
but this is not something i should
really discuss on here
yeah
v gamer 311 thank you soon oh wait i
think hokan gets a kiss still i didn't
give them a kiss
thank you
thank you so much
maybe next year at a different
convention
you can also be there
many many many
conventions
hopefully because they're really fun
it's so nice to see people
in the audience whether it's like just
for zoom
or like more personal like dokomi
gamescom well gamescom this year is
already over i don't know about next
year
minigamer311 thank you thank you soon
one two three ten times
ten times twenty that's two reds right
wow math oh my god
incredible the math i've been doing
recently i could become a math professor
uh is it already been two years isn't it
as you know i have prepared yet again
another orange carpet
oh orange carpet
happy two years anniversary potential i
just thought that just when i thought
previous year was already pretty packed
but damn this year was even greater than
previous year without a doubt really
thank you
you're able to perform with senpai's and
jen mates with same stages that you have
dreamed of and finally done pretty
birthday life that yourself and everyone
long waited of course we can't miss out
on a new song as well however what makes
even more special about this year was
that there were a lot of offline events
as well
like the convention appearance was quite
crazy
especially with in a short amount of
time too starting from dokami in europe
crunchyroll expo north america finally
sold popcorn in asia
yeah showing up three different
continents in short amount of time is
really something else that is true like
last year we did i think more
conventions
but it was focused on north america
um
i think there was no convention in asia
that i participated in
and then in europe just document but you
know
um
so yeah that's really cool that we
spread out a little bit more this time
as uh thanks to the big growing korean
fandom that i've accumulated
yeah and i'm i'm very very proud and
happy
that they decided to support me so
strongly really grateful for it wouldn't
have been possible
i wanna be at a korean convention or any
asian convention for that matter
uh again
as soon as possible
spread those wings even more
let more people know about kiwawa
thanks to you this year was quite
special for me as well i was lucky
enough to see you do a lot considering
it talk to me and that was quite the
spicy performance you also gave me a
chance to meet so many kfps as well mmm
we definitely got great love during taco
to the panel from crunchyroll expo
and of course how can i forget about
great and meat
grated beet
what's that i only know meet and greet
that's extraordinary moment i won't
forget i mean
list can go on and on but long story
short thank you so much for the last two
years for being amazing potential and
bring interesting content and effort for
making for us
efforts to making fun for us i really
appreciate it i know you got a lot of
super chat to read and sorry for writing
bit much
[\h__\h]
a bit
but as long as i will be there for
support whenever i can thank you
what is this korean text
a bit
[Music]
or there's a whole number chapter in
korean
germany
thank
you you
sweet
oh for once it's not a troll message
i was about to translate it thinking i'm
gonna be trolled
i have to be very careful with korean
super chats i'm like i'm i have ptsd
[Music]
i'm scared
every time i read a korean super chats
like
someone making fun of me or putting
something in there that's not korean
come yeah bamboozling me stop and
boodling me
anyway thank you jingle
orange carpet
way better than the red carpet 10 out of
10. thank you so much
[Music]
thank you for the pinky congratulations
on your two years of work dental i
wasn't here from the beginning but
decided to join by the end of last year
and i'm glad i stayed it also makes me
happy that the video letter we wrote uh
reached you and that you enjoyed it yes
it raised me
it was very cute thank you so much
and thank you stuart for the support for
two years
or maybe not full two years for you but
still
thank you i appreciate you being part of
it
now that i think of it two years is like
all the jobs i've done in my life
i think the one that i had for the
longest was three years
so
damn if i do this for one more year then
i'll then this might be my longest job
ever in my life
noise
it's not it's not quite that i
can't
do something longer like i feel like
there's certain people certain types of
people
who
just keep on like quitting something
they started
maybe some people in the chat feel like
i'm talking to them
and i don't think i was quite like that
but i did lose interest in things fast i
guess but no i mean
like my last job i i ended after two
years because i wanted to do the working
holiday
because i felt like now or never i have
to do it
early
earlier rather than later
i'll keep a job for 10 years if it feeds
me
you should not that shouldn't be the
only criteria you should be happy and
fulfilled by it if possible if you do it
for 10 years
i feel personally attacked i'm sorry
15 years respect i know that um in
japan um if you quit your job after two
years or so
it
will
look really bad
on your next job application
two years is nothing three years also
not really
like i feel like the earliest you can
quit
is like after five years maybe
in japan
so if i would apply for a job in japan
now my job so far have been two or three
years
and i wouldn't really
like that because it makes it makes them
think you just you're gonna quit again
after two years and to be honest the
chances are high if that's your tracking
record
um
[Music]
loyalty to employees i don't know about
that
but quitting is hard in japan
[Music]
yeah
which is so sad because i i think a lot
of people
stay in a job that they
really don't enjoy that makes them
depressed
or even worse
um
because
they feel like there's no way out like
quitting is not quite an option
that's so sad
i wish it wasn't like that
[Music]
a
yeah
the
i mean
though the job i did for three years i
did for three years because the three
years was the minimum because that was
the the whole system
you do it for three years and then
you're done and it was normal to go to a
different workplace after that i stayed
in the same
industry
but
it was um
three years of a training and at the end
you can stay but not no one who does
that kind of training stays in the same
workplace normally
so
it was normal to leave and then i went
to a different workplace in the same
industry for two years
and then i went to japan
so
um
yeah
but if i think about it if i have to
have the same job
for for like 10 years i don't think i
could do it
i would get sick of it
if it's like self-employed kind of job
then maybe
but
it was like a job like the one i had
before
i would definitely get sick of it maybe
different workplace same industry for 10
years but not
not the same workplace for 10 years now
and especially
[Music]
in my industry where i was before
which was like
um
hotel
work
um the turnover of employees was insane
in the two years i wasn't that one job
at the end of the two years
or 70 even
of the employees in my department that i
met in the beginning was not there
anymore at the end of the two years
if not even more than
60 could have could be even 60 the more
than percent even like the
really the only ones who stayed who is
still there at the end was like the the
the management
hospitality like working in restaurants
and hotels and all that i don't know how
it is in other countries but in austria
the turnover is crazy
everyone gets so exhausted
by the job that they leave
so fast and like everyone's always
unhappy with the workplace they're in
and they hope to go to the next one and
hope that the next one will be better
but usually it's like the same
it's just um
that industry is just
bad
for employees it's just exhausting
physically exhausting can't help it
can't help it
yeah
it's not rewarding exactly and the
biggest reason is because you have to
deal with real people who are really
[\h__\h] demanding at least i would say
that's the problem when you work in the
hotel
um
the better the hotel is the more
demanding the guests will be
and make you feel like
[\h__\h] dirt like a [\h__\h] cockroach
really
[Music]
the way i've seen my colleagues and me
be treated by people by the guests
is so disgusting
so [\h__\h] disgusting
but sometimes like i enjoyed seeing
sometimes like
i
don't you love it when like
um
these situations when there's there's
someone like really pissed off and
complaining and they're like i want to
speak to the manager and then you're
literally like i am the manager
like i wasn't the manager but it
happened to my manager and it was so
funny she was like i'm not taking any of
your [\h__\h] nah
[Music]
that person like he didn't even
give
my manager
a chance at all
like
he didn't even want to talk to her
because she was a woman
and that that was like
wow
[Music]
and then he's like i want to speak to
the manager
and then she's like i am the manager you
have to talk to me you're not if you
want to stay in this hotel you will talk
to me
or you stay somewhere else
good luck
ah
yeah
[Music]
a lot of
interesting situations like that
um
[Music]
deal of dumb google reviews
yeah
well
i mean a lot of them
i think my my place they answered like
these shitty reviews i see often i see
not only like my old place but like
other hotels and so on
they answer
certain really bad really upset reviews
like i don't know what the hell you were
talking about but we stand behind our
employees and we say basically [\h__\h] you
to you
so goodbye
i love that i love when
like
the management actually stands behind
their
their employees like that
that is the right
attitude to have
but not every place is like that
a lot of places are like
always always so
um
apologetic
because i guess it's somehow easier
to
like you at some point you don't have
the nerve for it anymore you don't have
the nerve to keep on listening to stupid
complaints
um
i just like yes i'm sorry you will get
this one night for free
we're really sorry
sumima sorry
[Music]
kian will back us up
you guys don't make any mistakes to
begin with though
there's nothing to back up
i have yet to receive a customer
complaint about you guys
or maybe maybe the
customer complaints are being
burnt
before they reach me
are you guys hiding them
because they eat us no what the [\h__\h]
where where are the customers that's
actually
weird i have not received any customer
complaints should i be questioning that
there are no complaints right please
ignore the shredded paper
nothing to see here nope nope no no no
no
nothing wrong here
i see customers entering but not leaving
what
everyone's happy
okay good to know okay i believe you
i will believe you
i trust you guys and i hope you won't
disappoint me and betray my trust
all right anyway oh
where was i
for the pinky happy second anniversary
to the best boss in the whole wide world
thank you
best boss yes and best boss
i agree thank you you're the best
employee thank you
second 47 all thanks for the reservation
12 hours to celebrate two years let's go
it's been a great time with you and it
will be a great time with you for many
more years to come thank you jacob
thanks for being here for the very
important
12-hour marathon you seem
you seem to have been there quite in the
beginning of it thanks for waking up
early
[Music]
actually i don't know never mind i don't
know if these times are accurate
did whole eyes have to preach at super
chats as well
i think they did right
yeah okay good
oh wait then
this is from
oh wait that said that that's so
preachat i think
but the time zone
it shows me is wrong i think
[Music]
the drawing game yeah that was fun
[Laughter]
is that jst oh could could be yeah
that's gst
[Music]
think of thank you jacob i was gonna say
thank good
thank you jacob thank you thank you
thank god
thank you
big kiss for you please continue
supporting me i would appreciate
perhaps i'll end it here
i have two more hours until the debut
and i've read all of the pre-chat super
chats which
is in comparison maybe not that much but
from
[Laughter]
ah
this will take a while
there is
interesting there's there's uh
oh wait no it says
[Music]
at the top it says super chat 461
ah never mind then it's not 947. she got
to go
there's 400 but yeah it skips the
numbers where there's something that's
not a super chat right like memberships
for example
yeah yeah never mind
so it's 461 super chats and i read 77
wait i guess that wasn't 77 either but
it looks it looks pretty much like uh it
wasn't skipped
uh not much was skipped
[Music]
i don't really see any
any big skips here
yeah
okay that's a bit better that says yeah
much better
yeah people went crazy with the
membership gifts yeah
have you seen the restaurant yes i have
i've i logged in
before um like like yesterday
just to take a glance to see if
like in terms of tc everything's fine
and i just took a glance i wanted to
look at it in detail on stream
but then today i was in piccolo's
empire's stream chat and uh she showed
it all off and now i've kind of already
seen it
but it's it's huge
it's huge but we'll talk about it next
time i stream rest
yeah
i don't know how long they worked on it
but
big apps big thanks
very very
helpful and sweet of them to do that
in the middle of the night for them
it didn't decay no not i don't think so
the tc have like more than enough stuff
in it
okay
agenda agenda i don't know it's gonna be
a normal demo i don't have anything like
super crazy just just a super normal
debut to kind of get to start
the the channel going
start of the channel going
[Music]
yeah
so i'll go prepare that now
um that is three times before yeah
at least this time i'm not nervous
i should just re-upload my other gym no
but that was more of a joke
this time it's more serious
[Music]
i'll see you guys there and then i'll
tell you after that what i'm gonna do
tomorrow i don't know yet
we'll figure it out
thanks for watching nintendo direct with
me it was
[Music]
oh
wow i can blow kisses i just figured
that one out now
see you later alligator
[Music]
do
you