[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
good evening hello
[Music]
hello
how's your day Mala morning morning
not even a tea right
yay I'm fine thank you how about you I'm
fine I'm fine I'm great thank you
12 hours let's go
back to can be 69 will I get um
get some help thank you
uh yeah so tonight right tonight's plan
not gonna be we're
talk
[Music]
what an opening
I I've just started
okay
but yeah uh so tonight plan we are not
gonna be like going for cane before
I don't know uh for five hours for four
hours no maybe it's like
less than four hours I'll hope you have
a nice day today good luck on the stream
and the exciting Adventure we call a few
hour later dude wow thank you
um yeah because
because actually today
I
because actually today I don't really
plan to play Minecraft
but
uh yeah I
tonight I plan to play other games
actually but somehow I just couldn't
manage to find
[Music]
short game
that I can play for
three hours or so and then I feel like
um
I've already gone so far in the Nether
and
I feel like
okay probably just continue this for a
while before I go back
uh
uh to the Overworld
11 months of membership one month before
lumutan and I'm one more
day away from my judgment me totally die
job but this who did nothing wrong in
pre-chat
still good luck
Judgment Day thank you
uh
and then
oh yeah
yeah so
tonight Chiara Senpai asked me to go
for adventure I don't know what kind of
Adventure but we'll see uh
she said that she will
think about something uh spontaneously
so
yeah I don't know collab uh you can say
that but actually it's not like a
proper plan collab you know it's just
like something that um
uh something like
Kyla will play Minecraft at this hour at
this day uh
would you want to like uh
just like you know
um probably
hang out Chit Chat just like that
and then she said that it's okay not to
be like in a fully uh
in a full stream so it's like I can just
pop in whenever I'm ready and I can also
like uh pop out whenever I need to go so
yeah yeah it's it's it's just like
chilling talking and I don't know what
she's up to actually
yeah yeah
um and
at first what I planned
when she invited me
for that
I plan to stream in the afternoon and
then no stream at night so I can just
hop in into her stream but
my word told me otherwise I couldn't
stream in the afternoon and then I just
couldn't find what to stream like in a
very short
time like three four hours I don't know
and then I feel like
well all of my TNT and potion that I
brought to the nether since yesterday
will be like
going to be a waste if
tonight I play other games and then I
just
commit Sudoku
and just go back since I have already
like
so far away in the nether so I feel like
well yeah maybe before I open into her
stream probably I can just grind some
ancient debris first
yeah so that's the plan
today probably my target is just yeah
I don't know if if I can get
only 120 probably that's good enough
I only have like
less than four hours less than four hour
I think
and then
[Music]
foreign
gets some help hello
it's the start of the day here but I
offer you Milo I hope I don't need it
today thank you I always have extra love
for you thank you hola by the way
just fall off an electric kick board I
don't know how to call it an English
kick board kickboard what is kickboard
something like skateboard is it instead
of blaming myself or skill issue or
blaming the rules of random holes I'll
blame you for taking my luck at soul of
you get some help no love but
fastrika free and I hope you're still
good
it's the opposite of punch board nice
have a good night also already for me
sorry also it's okay no worries straight
out again two thoughts from the
thumbnail Karma or Pamela saying if I
fall I'm not doing alone because who
forgot to pack the five protection
potions
now if you look at the thumbnail right
I'm still smiling so it's all daijo
Buddhist
hey what is all of this
strip mine
I already got six I think from the strip
mine
[Music]
yeah yeah
um
[Music]
I'm sorry I didn't follow your riff do
you like lost universe or do you have a
favorite Champion story I
really my most favorite League story
lore is actually orianna I play orianna
because I love the lore It's just sad I
mean I know that a lot of Champions like
a lot of League's Champions are sad but
I don't know
orianas
are my favorite
uh Yama bro just left him hurting a
little bit but I'm okay
check that because sometimes
hurting a little bit is
not as simple as you think but yeah I
hope you're
really really fine yeah
and take all my luck buddy and mcnure
adios thank you Andrew
[Music]
foreign
I cannot do anything
so yeah
[Music]
no buffering issues here yeah if this
one right if like this one it's like
half half half okay half not okay then I
don't know what should I do
[Music]
too long since I still have something to
do print value and before me be back
okay Chris good luck with your work it's
okay
not giving me any attention debris the
strip mine giving me a lot of ancient
history there's something wrong with
your skin
[Music]
dude
YouTube
Ah maybe it's not raging maybe it's
something like uh
some ISP issue
kinda
but it's okay usually something like
this gonna be like
something like this gonna be like fixed
by itself
there is nothing that I can do
Papa
[Music]
foreign
um
no ancient debris at all
[Music]
huh
nothing
[Music]
behind you
which one
this one
that one
ah thank you
ah you have good eyes
no YouTube I didn't hear what kind of
candy think yo
[Music]
this is
Young
foreign
really weird it's just really weird
and there is nothing that we can do
actually
[Music]
that's true 720p lagging then an ATP
safe how is it possible I am
[Music]
got mine only up only upakuda Society
foreign
[Music]
thank you so much
thank you
good eyes
foreign
probably for lemon juice
Maybe
so let me check my Discord
[Music]
replying to kiwawa
so guys
so many people are very busy tonight
[Music]
good evening
foreign
that bye daylight
[Music]
Rios
you're okay there I'm I'm okay but it's
really hard to say that by daylight
one two three four okay
it's been nine months since I started
watching Kyle at nine months since my
lock doku I don't think it's really
[Music]
of course it's not related
I'm not taking anyone's love for sure
and yeah thank you so much nine months
yay
um
[Music]
I just noticed I passed the one year
Marshall where do you want to go for the
get some help but thank you so much 13
months let's go
I'm still trying to think about the
ingots for two years because after this
the Milestone is two years right
now
well already drink a cup of coffee and
still sleepy maybe I need on Ella to get
a spirit or get get on Ella keep trying
maybe a hammer instead we can do that
hammer hmm
hammer
interesting yeah I mean after getting
all of the ingots if no Hammer then what
do we do right
[Music]
hmm
hello I've never been here or chatted
here before
Omni style Z are you sure about that are
you sure
[Music]
what is all of this
hello hello
welcome welcome
I am stuck here
by the way tomorrow gonna be
the day of 3D rainy Senpai are you
excited
I'm excited
[Music]
tomorrow
excited excited excited excited
[Music]
in exactly 24 hours yeah true
foreign
[Music]
hello hello
no TTS is perfect
I'm building up to Ella right now the
second rough project has thousand times
thousand foundation and bundles in the
set of a mouse we will build build their
own buildings
OMG that's
Jai Jen think
foreign
like
I don't know because I don't know if you
watch the
Area 15 uh 3D life
but
it's really really really really really
really awesome
and I
cannot wait to see
polaro's
3D life cited so much so much you and
Milo even though my gut has been dressed
lately
well
I believe that you still have some good
luck
so
thank you
I cannot wait for hollow hero Hollow
hero
yeah
I'm excited too
I don't know why I'm laughing but
I don't know
hello girls what Hollow chaos
[Music]
it's just it's just very funny
I just remember
I don't know this kind of topic just
remind me about the schedule and the
King
not that topic again not that topic
again
[Music]
please don't talk about that Sky you can
see
[Music]
cannot wait to see a certain aerobics
blacks with let's go
[Music]
the practice and
oh
hello if a radioactive spider bit me I
beat a Spiderman can you buy me such a
big um
get some help
study is an excuse for talking about 3D
dancing
hey
sad
I mean dancing makes you feel
fit
refreshed
I mean aerobics as Kaji
had a similar
kind of similar also the same one got
the one two three four five six seven
eight two
[Music]
and imagine the rehearsals when people
when other members trying to
rehearse the dance move at the same time
I'll be also rehearsing
my S kajemu
comedy remember yes very serious of
course very serious
we cannot comedy comedy while doing
escarge you know you will you will be
and talk
okay if you joke joke around while doing
escarge you will be definitely and talk
crack you know
what is and chalk
what is Angel
definition
can I have some of your luck I wanna
pull guitar right now thank you so much
for the luck
thank you so much for giving me La I
really need it thank you
[Music]
not success maybe on SP will get omella
for a new people who join this stream
you should try um
nice try nice try empty NT
very very empty
keep trying
[Music]
um
by the way Kiowa is not
kiwawa pink is not really good
is she lagging
it's not streaming right now right I
thought the schedule is
on 10 pm
still have to do overdose no luck sorry
wife wife what wife magdalenus Rex
no right yeah probably is preparing
materials probably
[Music]
two hours
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
article
um
foreign
get some help
hello
by the way
[Music]
maybe my definition of here is wrong but
a scammer and luxury inner water
kusugage and a cat can be called Heroes
[Music]
what
get some help
Yama bro what
a scammer and locked razor is just so
bad
[Music]
but no luck to give here use it all on
merch limited editions while I crying I
can't get some more if you name seven
random number between one and 56 I can
say nice try rain out of a nice try
but nah
nah
um
[Music]
get some help
foreign
[Music]
fake
I know that's not real
that time on Ella emotes
no one picked that
um
already feel betrayed
foreign
from his eye
is my office since day one no that's
like that's a liar around the summer
button on LLS hello
[Music]
um
get some help please thank you
[Music]
developments pieces I am not
I am not scammer scammer I'm not
following
all of my streams are very serious so
very very serious
[Music]
oh
oh oh
[Music]
I know that I'm cool thank you thank you
thank you
[Music]
black meat
yeah
thank you
so many times the best maybe I should
learn from Omega um Ella almost show up
is never enough thank you
do you know why tonight hearing your
friends my heart go
get some help can you hear my heart
beats just for you no
if your heart beats just for me
you should be like you know
okay if your heart beats only for me
[Music]
what happened when I'm not streaming
that's the logic right
please don't do that
Aloo gets some help thank you
Daniel long
cool
what is what cute and cool on Ella
cute um Ella
[Music]
unlock the trainer I forgot to add wife
Hunter and cool blacksmith the only
thing that is correct is just cool
blacksmith okay Yama bro thank you
uh-huh
[Music]
if you're not streaming I feel dead
inside like a part of me has been
thought about mister
get some help
[Music]
this is unbelievable
don't be harsh it's just living up to
his
concerning
no debris fine
[Music]
today have Target no the target is just
the time limit
no Target
I'm just trying to get
as many as possible by the way why this
is basalt again
don't know
why should be rude
[Music]
no debris
no debris no
no but the beginning
[Music]
get some help please thank you
thank you so much for the southern
membership gifts what happened is that a
Miss click
oh no
[Music]
oh she
is not thing
three minutes
on Ellen next day the Betrayal begins
seemed like Grandma but I never beat
three
[Music]
um on fish you don't need to show up on
he asked
thank you
um
I give you guys chance already
but somehow no one wants to pick on Ella
um Ella so sad already
[Music]
I need a potion
doco
um
and then
hmm
[Music]
Arrow I need Arrow
did you know swimming in lava is bad for
your health well in this case
swimming in lava will
increase my luck
[Music]
adios
thank you
grinding number
um
thank you
[Music]
La Mao used this emote as an emergency
no no no no no no no
ouch
foreign
I will just go to
negatives
[Music]
thank you
get some help
[Music]
can I use up all of this TNT before I go
back
only one way to find out
no it's full already
nice
[Music]
um nothing nothing
nice
I miss when you were able to put a
shulker box inside of another charcoal
box oh really there's a time that it's
possible
when was it
[Music]
it was considered a buck
oh
[Music]
be here imagine right
immediate shelter and shelter shelters
and shelters I'll never I'll never leave
nether like that
shall conception
okay
thank you
I don't know
I I mean
it's still gonna be a time when monjong
really
update so we can put like shelters and
shelter because that's gonna be like I
think
marry my acid button where for this I
can't send actually almost over the case
I already own this item but I can't as
the past few days it like I lost my life
so
you good
but is it really error or this is just a
joke
hmm
I mean you'll be fine
you'll be fine
foreign
[Music]
the other day
is
[Music]
okay
3D
life
3D life I will not be streaming at all
at night so it's gonna be in the morning
[Music]
foreign
look at that in one jump one two three
four five
get some help joke I already have a
girlfriend who is normal and she's human
also she's perfectly normal for real for
real
I mean
am I not normal
[Music]
I had to find temporary Life Source so I
bought
mine is what is that 96 dollars worth of
fake color stickers and some are on
laptop my laptop has many car alarm I
know it's beautiful Marin I think you
really need to get some help thank you
uh
foreign
[Music]
mining no because it's not effective
if you're
if you're I mean
if you want to
fine
nadrite using bad
it's effective
yes I recommend that it's okay
but
if it's if we are talking about
nadrat Beacon project
nah
I will still recommend you to use TNT
for so many reasons
hmm
[Music]
okay
if you don't lift the entities with
spaces will that make the exponent
bigger or not it will be bigger
it will be bigger but still it's um
still it's not really worth it
[Music]
foreign
if you want me to explain why bed is not
effective for the
nether begin project
I can talk about that
first thing first the bad explosion
left
fire behind
you need to like
let off all of the fire
one by one to find the debris which is
very very
slow like the progress gonna be very
slow
and then
[Music]
uh space inventory wise
even if you just bring the wood and the
wool
still
it's very slow
it's very slow you cannot
you cannot be fast
[Music]
and
and yeah I mean it's just not effective
[Music]
but if you really want to like let's say
if you want to find that red for only
upgrading your armor your tools maybe
bad is
a good choice
but if you really want to find like
almost 6 000 engine debris
I don't know I think you will lose your
sanity for
for like doing that again and again
and also
um
grinding for wood
it's not that easy grinding for sand
is easier
its way faster
oh yeah
[Music]
just crazy people search 6K 80.
I considered that as a compliment
[Music]
yeah
and 80 it exploded too many blocks easy
winter wishing after all the luck they
need good night good night thank you so
much for the 69 YouTube thank you
Kyle is crazy and respect her for that
thank you
I mean if we
if we have never tried
we'll never know
[Music]
by the way
uh
uh two nights dinner
just now before I started the Stream
Mama Allah asked me about the
candy progress
I said it's already 60 my Miles said is
it already 50 and then I say well
it's already 60.
and then
because uh yeah I mean Mama Ella really
knows about my schedule right Mama Ella
got
the spoilers about my schedule
so
Mama Ella is like taking concern about
if candy can be done
on schedule or not
because yeah let me tell you
it's gonna be
insanely busy
insanely busy like for real for real
yeah so Mama Ella asked me that
Mama Ella and I
enjoying the dinner time
we've counted together like
um
how's the target
oh yeah
um
[Music]
laughs
foreign
[Music]
thank you
the preparation time is longer than the
stream itself
[Music]
take care good luck that's Gracia
is
foreign
[Music]
nice
I mean if I do project the Kia will also
use my computer is it
yeah right thank you
[Music]
foreign
gunpowder
Jam
a
ICA
spawn
is opposite
foreign
[Music]
Vito
creeperspawn limit
e
mop limit
address
ing
yeah I think that name is Mob cap
e
[Music]
difficulty to normal guys
tutorial tutorial difficulty
tutorials
foreign
[Music]
according to the
push the limit
I'm already pushing the limit like
pushing the limit for everything like
for the time for the
resources
or
four
myself too I'm pushing the limit
I don't know what limit should I push
again
yeah we push for the luck yeah push
pamalu's luck to push all the way
I already tried to be like
uh effective
as effective as possible
okay my hello calm down
how much space will the fungi need to
grow as mushroom as
as mushroom as mushroom as in it's yeah
as mushroom as it is
too
push limit of sleep don't go away
we are not talking about that that's for
sure already
but yeah somebody do it wrong
foreign
[Music]
ah
foreign
[Music]
Naga get some help I'm not a cat
Mom I'm scared
I prove waffles
on already using 1490 upgrade pc10 no
I'm still waiting for December though
thank you
[Music]
foreign
I'm not promising anything at December
though I just I just I just want to wait
for the 1490 TI first it doesn't mean
that I want to get the ti1 it's just
like
I'm the type of person that I want to
compare all of the
[Music]
all of
the GPU thingy
so I just want to compare which is which
one is worth it and I don't want to
regret buying that you know
[Music]
so yeah
the same thing when I buy the 3080 TI
I compare it first
there is like a specific reason why I
don't get the 3090 TI one because it's I
feel okay
personally I just feel like
it's not really worth it
so yeah so right now I already know the
capability of 40 90.
and I want to check
uh the differences between the the 4090
TI and the 4091 and the 4080 TI one I
want to compare that and then compare
means the capability the price is it
worth it or blah blah blah blah blah
blah I have like a lot of thoughts about
that
so I'm still waiting for that
I'm I can say that I'm not an impulsive
buyer yeah
yeah
I'm I I'm I since like you know since I
really understand
not really La um I have enough knowledge
like I have enough knowledge about what
I need what I don't need and
I just I just I I just don't want to
regret anything
so it's like if I feel that I need it
I'll buy it if I feel like it's not
worth it in my case then
yeah I mean he's here right about PC we
have different needs right each of us
have like different needs and
I mean
for PC right
um if we go like overboard
it's also not good to have like the
overpowered PC but we are not using
to the maximum power
it's also not good for the PC you know
so it's not always about like getting
the
the most expensive one and like you know
I don't know like
why not just get the 3090 TI one back
then right A lot of people asked me that
like for what
yeah since I kinda understood I I don't
want to say that I really understand
but I can I know that I have
um
enough knowledge like if enough
knowledge about kissing
so I really understand what I need what
I don't need
so and I don't want to regret
just don't be like an impulsive buyer
and yeah
we'll see we'll see we'll see what I
gonna upgrade later on
hmm
what I mean even though I say it like
I'm still waiting for the 1490 TI ride
it doesn't mean that I will get the 4090
TI one at the end
but I mean I can wait
I can wait why why I say that I can wait
because
my PC channel is still
powerful enough for everything that I do
right now so it's not very urgent
is more than enough to be honest yeah I
mean uh especially right now a hollow
hero still got no 3D right so it's still
a killer
because the
3D and the 2D
uh
uh specs is different
so yeah
for now this is already more than enough
you just I don't know just don't be
impulsive
just don't be impulse
um
[Music]
and especially my what is this my
processor
is the newest Giant
so this is still very powerful I can say
easy is not only about GPU guys
PC is not only about GPU
like because a lot of people that don't
really understand about PC people always
say that
this this PC is better than this this PC
is better than this no it's not only
about GPU
[Music]
yeah true true bottleneck is very
bottling is very dangerous yeah yeah
bottleneck is very dangerous
who's PCP secret and this PC chant
I
uh
CrossFit not crafted guys
I somehow yeah I this is not like this
is not uh by The Market stock one
Assemble Yeah build build yeah yeah
I I did like a lot of research for this
and that I compared this and that
and then and then
um compared means what I really need so
it's like
no regret
[Music]
hello
lay Kayla says hello
hi Mirai Luna says Yahoo
foreign
[Music]
wait
tip mean maxing pieces specs to afford
the most luxa Suga let's go
no because I feel like
if I can save
some money and not wasting
for
the PC specs that I don't really use
you know how many games that I can use
the money for you know
games nowadays are expensive
and yeah
I mean why why why buying
the overpowered one
and I don't use the maximum power of it
and at the same time I cannot buy games
because games are very expensive
[Music]
Ella become voice when talk about this
nice
[Music]
imagine having a top-notch specs
but no games
Kane
game fun Miku 2021 gets some help thank
you so much for the red supas but
oh yeah by the way the summer sale gonna
ends real soon
make sure you check out if you haven't
checked out yet the summer sale is gonna
be like gone real soon
foreign
[Music]
already bought some nice
funny wait
not when you're not streaming do you set
easy time to mine crypto no I mind
gunpowder
[Music]
and then what is this Mario wanna make
an Indonesian can you do stream plus
gift tip what wanna make an Indonesian
what
other school I got so mad at PC prices
last year I bought everything for this
PC use on Eep
but I know right when
there was a time when
the PC
becoming like all of the parts of this
pieces like insanely expensive
insanely expensive
yeah so bad it's just so bad it's like
real painful to look at all of the
prizes
scary
is for very very scary yeah very scary
so no Maki wadham says convandoah
hi Mariah Luna says
like Kayla says con Bando dodo
walking wadham says
I like that I like that accent so much
do
[Music]
I said should I buy Fall Guys and watch
Ella fail what I'm the pro Fall Guys
player akitenkyo
hey
I'll versus you I want armor core 6X so
Primal and Starfield then what stop you
huh what stop you from
getting that
damn it Ally just checking oh welcome
welcome hmm
Keith penguin you only need to upgrade
your Internet to download our luck
faster indeed
indeed yeah nice
if you have two PC you can do 2knb
stream at the same time even better nice
actually that's what Mama Ella say to me
like
uh you have your laptops right why not
ufk in the uh gun powder farm and you
play Minecraft at the same time and then
I say Mama Ella the character need to be
there
character
neither cannot be like that
yay
[Music]
um
I think I think it's wise enough to make
an account for Mama Ella and then Mama
Ella Mama Ella joined the game only for
FK
[Music]
um
so expensive need to save for FIFA
concert I know right yeah yeah yeah true
true that lemon but I don't know like uh
uh if the fifth concert gonna be like uh
the ticket gonna be sale or is it gonna
be like uh
free to stream I don't know I don't know
we need we just need to wait for um the
upcoming updates yeah
Alberto they are not out yet the only
one that I know
it's not out yet it's the actual print
Primal but it's gonna be like out this
weekend right the armor core 6 and
Starfield also not out yet hmm
as
[Music]
ah
why not
[Music]
I know
ah
but imagine if the gunpowder Farm can be
asked for like 24 hours you know
it's gonna be very nice right
just saying
right now PC Chan only rests whenever
I'm in the Navy
because I cannot just go back
if the TNT is
if if I haven't used all of the TNT yet
so yeah
[Music]
okay
Minecraft
foreign
guys
Auto smelter
um
[Music]
foreign
actually
great idea actually
but
do you think
but do you think that my Canby will
still
not yet finish until gen 4. I don't know
if you ask me like when Jennifer I don't
even know
thank you
who knows here who knows
[Music]
senpai
foreign
[Music]
bye
thank you so much for your membership
gifts thank you
bye
[Music]
there's nothing wrong calling Kobo
senpai
I like that bye
Google bye
[Music]
um
bye
so weird to hear you call kobus and bye
thank you
[Music]
foreign
by the way
very bad
you mean they are going to hire another
child even better
I don't know I have no idea
[Music]
no ancient debris at all
there you are this one
[Music]
okay
you pass one really
[Music]
thank you
did I pass it
manada
[Music]
I don't know
foreign
just forget about it
[Music]
oh suddenly it's here
when I dahla
the ancient debris is like I'm here I'm
here
dahla is always the key
[Music]
hmm
just one
give me more
wait what time is it okay
21 22
um
no matter where I go it's gonna be bust
out
[Music]
still matter waste but it's basalt
weird
and it's so far nice
was still so many
[Music]
we need to be faster
another place
cooperate with me
GA Simas
um
foreign
please be nice
good morning Ella how are you doing
today Brussels I'm great how about you
good morning
oh no
[Music]
nothing
fine fine fine fine
thank you
my new ad block costs one hour of our by
80 please
oh night
I don't know I really need to
who got the best R in ID
I need to know
of course you'll feel nice not me saying
that okay
[Laughter]
foreign
[Applause]
I think om can say r
this is my first law after my birthday
hello happy birthday wish all the best
thank you so much for giving me your
love thank you
[Music]
nice
um
Ella
[Music]
foreign
nice
got you oh it's the get some help SC uh
get some help done
I thought it's a joke
after hearing you rolling the Army Head
Start dizzy oh why
let me fix that
[Music]
can you do one minute I think I have
ever done more than one minute I think
I don't know
foreign
[Music]
We're Not Gonna use that
roll
by the way when is that a birthday
surprise once it does well hopefully
have three whole deaths that have nearly
there are quite enough for a stick
feeling cool yeah I don't know
I don't know they they just don't want
to like you know
they're like very very
uh
price it
yeah
they don't want they they just shy shy
you know shy shy
shy shy
[Music]
Miss Essie
Miss Elsie
remember you got another video for
Minecraft
did you still have it or already gone
which one the NFS one is it
or which one
thank you
let's split yes I have donations who
cannot roll ours in shambles after Alice
one need three dude
I don't know I feel like the r is
I don't know doesn't mean that our
donation cannot be like kind of role
there are probably it's just like
uh you guys are not using it
[Applause]
I can only roll my ass on a good day
what does it mean there is a bad day and
there is a good day and then good day oh
yeah today is a good day I can't roll my
r
foreign
useful are many Latin Spanish languages
you said
um
I roll ours when singing even better
nice
[Music]
let's just go past a bit
I can do it since I was two nice
ouch
[Music]
will you include the r in Escada move
how to do that
foreign
but there's gonna be Adventure
and but what I know is actually you see
also still want to finish the what is
that the tunnel I think
so maybe I'll just join after
to finish the tunnel probably I don't
know or maybe she already changed the
plan I don't know
if you want to find sniffer already
change the plan no no no more tunnel
[Music]
CC building plus knicker okay building
right yeah building
I think I'll just join the adventure
[Music]
say hi to KI wow
tea wow
[Music]
wow
yeah I think I'll just join the
adventure okay okay okay okay
[Music]
here you need to hear her arm I mean
your Senpai can roll the r right I think
I don't know
what a topic is this
suddenly apparently rolling arm
s
yeah yeah
she can't wait which one
which one is true can or cannot
yes
[Music]
Ella can you give Mama new MC Project
built since the factory nearly done if
you know
it is
Let's test Italy
see
why you guys say that kiwawa cannot rule
the r
I know that she can do that right
wow
let's go
oh
since the vests are roller in Ian oh
I see
should I practice
should I be afraid right now
get some luck thank you the hybrids
leveling Taco thank you if you sick you
will love me we'll become
very funny
nice
suddenly become competitive this is not
competitive I'm scared guys
I'm scared
[Music]
be afraid
going to take my English pass tomorrow I
hope you will lend me some of your luck
do you thank you so much for giving me
luck
but good luck
[Music]
everywhere
to see the wheel of this
yep
everywhere
oh
if anything I'll donate my luck to you
as I just recharged it and have no
intention of letting Ella spill it this
time good luck on the test
I can read that
bingo
you're welcome
you can read it but you cannot steal it
if I read it I I take it already you
know
I I read it I took it that's just how it
works
[Music]
no it's not done yet it needs some
detailing
oh thank you I don't know what project
I mean I'm still doing my can be you
guys almost finished the factory uh
[Music]
where are you where are you and gender
break where are you where are you
attention
debris I miss you
mentioned every I miss you
I don't like you
can you change it to that one
no
Akito Yuka is like being the mystery guy
right now you know
[Music]
looks like Ella has a lot of oldies song
ideas even very nice
so with Nola I do have Infinity luck
right now wow wow how lucky I am
thinking but you get some help hello
opium
[Music]
best
oh
nice
it's not even 100 yet
[Music]
imagine finishing can be
on my birthday
I'm gonna be epic
no birthday streams
[Music]
said already today maybe I used too much
mystery
I miss three Akito Yuka thank you
[Music]
61.
93 it's not even 100.
this is lucky and thanks for your advice
yesterday hey Captain
okay
and basalt
is that your luck
top 10
.
seems like August will be busiest month
for you uh not really
uh
August gonna be busy yes
but it's not gonna be the busiest
I think
September and October gonna be the basis
August is busy
[Music]
September
is busy busy
October is
busy busy busy
[Music]
foreign
but what can I do
she took our luck power that's why the
light well makes sense
thank you
Ella please please what
please what
good luck I'll have been a while since I
was able to catch a stream dinkyo
welcome back
this is what Boris still bustled bustle
[Music]
Forest is infusing
thank you for the gun battle we got
butter right now yay got battle let's go
but thank you so much for the luck feel
chat thank you
what is going on with this war Forest
really weird
thank you
[Music]
so early no new MC Project
mmm
I don't know I want to say the steampunk
one but I want to do it
too so I know what do you guys want to
do I don't know
I don't know I know
oh yeah map art exactly yeah but
[Music]
I mean
the map art
later later
not now yeah the map art but
not now
there is gonna be a time when
there's gonna be a time when I
will talk about that
just need to wait a little bit
well not really that soon but
there's gonna be a time for that
just wait just relax don't don't make
any map art first
[Music]
laughs
okay
when the time comes I will let you know
all good
[Music]
yoshimashiro get some help thank you
thank you
foreign
I don't know
next update they should make a potion
that lets you see clearly and swim
faster in lava if talking about C
in lafa clearly the the shaders can do
that right now but
faster in lava swim faster in lava
that's gonna be perfect
if they can do that
[Music]
um
they're not Ian
being on YouTube
young Christmas
is
[Music]
okay okay
foreign
[Music]
my super service
do you think the upgrade template was a
good change yeah so that the diamond
gonna be like useful
[Music]
online
foreign
[Music]
I don't know what can I give though but
I don't know
[Music]
give them the location of last year to
give the location is there
the location is there it's obvious it's
very sauce
[Music]
no I have some fate I have some faith
that there's gonna be like a day
and that they gonna be very Epic
because it's gonna be like mind-blowing
not because of the gifts but it's like
how long it's actually there already
right it's good it's gonna be
mind-blowing and this is no new project
of finishing the factory daily amazing
for it hope you like it let's go I would
like it I know that I will like it but
yeah thank you so much for the hard work
you guys yeah thank you
we'll see we'll see have some feed guys
have some fate
time caps
did I put a date I put a date right I
believe I put a date
then you're swimming and lava makes me
feel like Anakin Skywalker because I'm
burning up for you the memories
get some help
[Music]
I think so um
I kind of forgot I think you did yeah
the date of the
the date of the gift
[Music]
you put a date according to all
okay
I think it's in I think it's
the sign
no that's why
that's why I'm not mentioning anything
that's why I'm avoiding spoiler that's
why I'm not mentioning any names
[Music]
running out could you give me your love
because I need to pull
koyan's sky from fgo pretty please no
because I need luck thank you so much
for the luck thank you
but yeah I mean good luck with your
gacha I hope uh you still have some
block after I
took your La thank you one day you mean
next to it
you need to have some faith
I mean it stills
seven months
it's the quotes of the day at the
lyrical phys Eden
thank you thank you for the SC
ale still seven months
I have some page
nice doing gaita while watching Kyla
swimming was a mistake
don't say that
say that
timson Forest
a
even better
[Music]
foreign
happy or happy hours
a happy hour hold on happy hour is um
[Laughter]
and then set r
r
and then Andy are uh
and then
lockless
R is like dying right um
how how to do dyeing are
oh foreign
[Music]
what else
um
addicted
addicted I don't know I cannot do
addicted R because I've never been
addicted to anything thank you and then
what is that
or hungry or
welcome back lay Kayla says welcome back
says hello
underscore Hollow and says hello
nice
so cool thank you pancake thank you so
much
Kyle just curious do you have a plan to
go to Japan in near future fix uh
yes and
I mean
uh
if
time and this war allows me to do so
yeah just go
yeah
and probably
even though
and probably you will never know that I
am
in Japan later on from me maybe you will
know it from
somebody I don't know
[Music]
foreign
can we get a cat cat at home
hi
I'm really scared I'm not a cat hello
because your internet will be better
hmm
I don't think so
I don't think so I mean if there is
probably a ping showing probably yes
like the gulfit one maybe yes but if not
I mean
because you know what even though in
Japan right
if you took legging it's still lagging
you know
[Music]
if leggings still lagging
but I mean if you know you know la
but one thing I'm sure that it's gonna
be
maybe it's not gonna be in the first
three days probably
I don't know
[Music]
foreign
thank you
I am just just bring PC tan over let's
go
[Music]
okay
guys
nice
[Music]
foreign
very nice
[Music]
membership going um well guys
totally not horror yeah it's just it's
just talking about food
it's okay
when you go to Japan it will be Like the
Wolf in Red Riding Hood why is your
voice different why is the Ping low why
do we hear Cowboys
[Music]
nah it's all gonna be fine
let's see let's see okay someday right
someday someday
someday let's see this is already
one zero six I need I need 14 more LA
120 La give me 120 before I go back
[Music]
Andrew
welcome back
get some help thank you
[Music]
morning morning stream gonna be safe
Milan
tomorrow 9 A.M stream
no night stream
go watch
Renaissance 3D life
foreign
after showcase it should be only an hour
no because I stream in the morning so at
night I need to be like working
um
at night
[Music]
maybe it's one leg in the morning yeah
maybe yeah
[Music]
thank you
mine also having to maybe get some f
boys packed with like happy because I
said it gets higher angry gets high how
to get a drunk inside if we'll get
something scary because they're crying
foreign
get some help really you need to get
some help
there was normal guitar what about the
rest no I I haven't thought about that
yet
no no no no no no no no no
no one
oh
four minutes potion
hmm
[Music]
real version
specifically needs suffering and gotcha
game get some
okay
[Music]
ouch
lava all the way
[Music]
example
this is
[Music]
120 before I go back to the Overworld
still a long way to go
for the
to the what is that
another Beacon
but we're getting there
Ella got Trejo not yet
not yet but I know that a lot of people
already tried that
wanna try it then what stop you from
trying
how many is it
1164 more
[Music]
um
four more four more
[Music]
um
two minutes ago
two minutes
foreign
wish
ran
twist
ers
[Music]
what's up
foreign
[Music]
I believe in Crimson Forest gonna be for
the brief for sure
Crimson forests
[Music]
oh
for 80 Wednesday even better
foreign
[Music]
bless
Ed
[Music]
um
nothing though
[Music]
not debris only love
fine fine fine fine fine
is it so hard to just get poor huh
four
[Music]
okay okay four four it's gonna be here
for real for real
[Music]
four
I will get eight
[Music]
zero
y
oh
one two
two more
[Music]
just need to believe
no
hey
this is a joke right
yeah
scale one more time for all my love for
that even better nice
adult people thank you so much for the
luck
[Music]
foreign
nice luck
done is it done is it done is it done is
it done
finally
time to go time to go
I'm too cool
one one nine
no it's 120.
one
[Music]
um
wait okay wait wait wait wait I need to
concentrate or else I'm gonna forget to
bring back things
[Music]
okay
oh
[Music]
many many many many
let me drink
[Music]
502 days
okay
[Music]
um
really
really got a problem I don't know
um
uh
wow
thank you very much arrive today thank
you Kyla
um
thank you so much thank you so much for
buying I hope you like it
please take care of that thank you
we
two things
[Music]
okay all good
no more
I don't know what
[Music]
by onion
Island
imagine I just died and forgot to bring
all of this
somehow
a mobile
ID coverage today
baby get some help thank you for buying
take care of that mm-hmm
okay all good
full okay
okay
[Music]
adios
Kiara underscore Halloween says rip
thanks
appreciate that
like Kayla says thanks
um
Ella when you read C and Ian do you find
it difficult not to read it as like you
will deny it like in the word bounds
for example bounce
bounce bounce
sometimes I I mean there's a reason why
I usually like mispronounce it because
it's kind of not difficult maybe it's
just like um
I don't know which one is correct
probably
right
[Music]
sniffer sniffer needs brass right
oh
[Music]
Adventures said
meets what brush this brush brush brush
brush
I think I need to craft more brush just
in case
[Music]
foreign
let's go let's go
[Music]
Allah
foreign
[Music]
wow
it might be a bit too early when I'm
also GMT plus 7 game but good night I'll
go to sleep now yeah it's okay
James Voldemort I mean press is great
enjoy your rest
thank you so much
foreign
[Music]
I still have 15 minutes
sorry team sorting
[Music]
thank you
okay
foreign
[Music]
all good and then
uh-huh
[Music]
Mari not completed to us but Mama Marie
saw me love so much watching you and she
wanna hear you say
boys
[Music]
thank you
nice
[Music]
money
yeah
where did I put the ancient debris by
the way
black shark box
or the TNT box
ing
okay
[Music]
almost there
by the way
I have
another word
thank you
[Music]
the ocean the the outer portion will be
besides that
but I haven't built it yet
[Music]
okay she subscribe to you now but she
keeps saying Carla nice nice Carla nice
Mama Marion nice
Carla
Carla nice
why it's not fast
why the soul spit oh okay
okay
[Music]
oh
the what the
the outer Bray wing
ocean will be
besides this but I just haven't uh make
space for it it's gonna be like here
but I need to like make us make more
space
I'm just preparing for the nether award
first right now
[Music]
water
fire water
[Music]
and what fire water
fall fall fall apart
I don't know
[Music]
okay
and their chest
is
super smelter
foreign
yeah fire fire just for the knb later on
we can
expand it
okay
[Music]
okay I'm going to the Super smelter
first and then after that I will ask
uh Kiera Senpai where is she
[Music]
oh no wonder
wait
[Music]
foreign
oh
my God
[Music]
okay
wow
where are you
like Kayla says where are you
are you
pierra underscore Halloween says
23-118-1589 build my tunnel
says I am still digging
okay lay Kayla says okay
Kiera underscore Halloween says oh and
in the nether
ah Nadder
okay okay lay Kayla says oh nether okay
my lovely nadir
oh neither
my lovely Nadder
yeah underscore Halloween says if you
want to come here you should probably
come from the side where I started my
tunnel LOL
no worries
nowhere says no worries
[Music]
let me
I give that poem
[Music]
nice
very very nice
probably see more 80 while waiting for
amazing taking e answer Fernando
nether right
imagine
there's gonna be a lord
hello you cannot mine on Ian server
[Music]
supervised wake you up
butterflies like you out
oh no what is this
[Music]
still waiting still waiting
very very slow very very slow picture in
1 million debris use your imagination
developer models one million debris who
gonna collect 1 million degree by the
way
Kiara underscore Halloween says what
happened Kiera underscore Halloween says
I found the other end
says I connected I.T lay Kayla says
Kia underscore Halloween says
[Applause]
lay Kayla says congrats
Kiara underscore Halloween says now I
have to place the ice but if you want
you can help me
Kiara underscore Halloween says but no
need
lay Kayla says I can do it
do you have the eyes like Kayla says do
you have the ice
Kiara underscore Halloween says yes
[Music]
thank you
stop it get something what
Sierra underscore Halloween says let's
meet at n headquarter nether portal
lay Kayla says Okay can do that
lay Kayla says hold on
Kiara underscore Hollow and says nicey
nice underscore holoen says I have a
gift for you what
lay Kayla says what
thanks
laughing face laughing face the TTS know
that it's a laughing face
it's swell already okay
let's go
adios
[Music]
foreign
I just need to find the
expressed
pansu Express uh
that way
and then it's gonna be here
[Music]
I'm in front of another part like Kayla
says I'm in front of the Nether Portal
um Kiera underscore Halloween says ok
one sec
one one one what one sec see what
um
get some help Irfan
thank you
oh yeah well we wait right well we wait
while we wait
get some help
for dinner
nice even better
I believe it's here right
Kiara underscore Halloween says VC in
one minute
okay lay Kayla says okay
December 2020 okay
there's a myths about that and the
coordinate yeah the coordinate is not
that far though
[Music]
sleep
or sleep okay
hold on
FEC
[Music]
thank you
foreign
take your shelter box
no the shelter bus
so no Maki wadum says doki
lay Kayla says shulker box behind you
Kiara underscore Halloween says ahihi
[Music]
lay Kayla says
foreign
[Music]
says Kayla I'm in jpvc
wait what what what
tax is not okay
wait my message is gone I press enter
hello hello
nice connections
it wave
what is that oh no I cannot
you can't connect No like is your
connection dead no but hold on it's okay
uh I'll find a way
double bgm probably let me fix that
monitor only there we go okay
hello Kyla hello what is this connected
[Music]
join
with it
oh no yeah you can't speak English
though can you speak nihongo Kayla
uh I'm nihongo Jojo
that doesn't sound good
please just speak English
yeah but also we're gonna do our own
thing but I don't want to say no to
about them
it's okay
no
oh there you are
she thinks I invited her oh
mine were gone
it's okay take your time because I don't
know what to do with this situation
right now that I created
um
I will explain to her what we're doing
because like I think she's she's doing
her own thing
oh
I I confused like I think I made her
think that I want her to join the voice
chat but
um she's doing her own thing you know
uh uh uh
explode my brain is exploding I I try to
be a social person always but now I'm
exploding
hey
hi hi hi hi
[Laughter]
this is so fun
I am
I am uh
oh God
what did I do
she want to look for sniffer I thought
she already has the sniffer and is
making a house for the sniffer
okay
Kayla she's back
[Music]
it's okay
you're the socially awkward situation
that I normally only make things so that
they're not awkward
hey foreign
this is the one situation that finally
conquers me and kills me
um Kyla where did you go
I've
I'm playing with the animals
inside the portal no in front of the
portal I think
[Music]
what time is it
um
[Music]
she says she she's always small I
already have her on maximum oh
foreign
[Music]
but she's much louder than you wait
maybe I make you more quiet kind of suck
it yeah
how about oh I think okay good balance
this is maximum guys
is it fine now guys
okay better okay okay okay okay
10 seconds
foreign
[Music]
translation
okay
okay let's talk a little bit uh she says
until
um you know until we actually leave to
go for the search of the sniffer oh okay
okay okay okay okay
have you two ever talked to each other
not yet
now it's first time uh I mean first time
talking in Fiji yeah and not really not
really the whole ID cop last year
okay
oh
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
yeah
[Music]
come on
tonight
[Music]
maybe maybe
we will be in the same team
[Music]
August
oh yes yes August
coming soon
foreign
[Music]
S I have some but not so many
oh blue eyes I mean I can take that
first hold on
okay
what is doing right now what to say she
is making a house for a sniffer oh yeah
in the new server right
there
oh yes yes
okay okay
[Music]
don't forget please Resto how many how
many I will take it
little little
how many uh uh
one Chalker one box one box
yeah one shot through
it
[Music]
she wants a full choker box uh the uh I
I want to ask uh the the Redstone is the
the dust or the black one
oh by the way I found some more blue
eyes from my side so no need I think oh
really you sure yes yes is it enough
okay
maybe I have a lot of cactus but just um
blue eyes not so much but I'll mix it
okay I mean I mean I can just bring some
a
H I'm in a tunnel you can just I think
you already know where the tunnel is
right yeah yeah okay okay sure you can
find me somewhere in the tunnel okay
foreign
[Music]
yeah
I see
no no no no no no no no
God no God yes no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no Venus
Venus
Venus because yeah
it wasn't Venus like a like a you know
sensual Gardens
sure anymore wow Venus
I know I know
yes
love and beauty goddess Venus oh wow no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no
no no
no no no no no no no no no
hi Ella can you bring me some torches
too okay maybe two stacks okay thank you
I have a present though for you you will
like it I need to crop it first hold on
hold on okay
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes
yes that will make a house that is like
uh like a forest for the sniffer I said
oh
good morning
Empire
[Music]
yes
um
disaster
is
so
um
[Music]
a song about stress
ing point
is
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
uh
Kyla what's your favorite type of bra
what bro bro no Bruh Bruh
bruh
why sudden topic
don't question it don't question it just
go along
foreign
[Music]
I I know that uh I know that um some
girls have favorite kind of that thing
yeah yeah but but I don't know if I I
really don't have like specific one
um
foreign
[Music]
I prefer non-wired bras but the problem
is you know my friend told me when you
sweat sweating it doesn't stick to your
boobies anymore and then it can fall off
yeah oh really yeah what happened to my
friend yeah yeah oh
so I know
yes yes
okay not personal experience yeah yeah
don't know anything about that no no oh
yeah
yes
[Music]
there's something you want to ask I will
translate it
um
[Music]
actually you know what what time is is
one of my ocean oh
foreign
actually
[Music]
that's why I'm panicking right now
uh
um
foreign
[Music]
oh yeah
how about you how about you me uh-huh
but I I first got to know whole life
foreign
[Laughter]
can you do any impersonations of
whole life members
not really I think
um
I'm really bad at like impersonating
actually yeah
[Music]
um
it's pretty good
I can't stop laughing oh my God
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
Tina
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
I can do better than that
what do you think Kyla of my pickled
impersonation
um you need to
sound higher I think
yeah higher yeah
no no that was her you know she's just
chilling sometimes she's just chilling
yeah my voice just chilling
oh you can go that high your voice
much higher
oh how how about we test the r right now
with watamation pie ah yeah that's
actually good because let's go give an
example because I can roll ours normally
but not in like a Japanese way I don't
know how in Japanese songs
foreign
[Music]
the tip of the tongue is
how do you do it
tell me
[Music]
foreign
on my way I'm on my way
[Music]
you deliver first to me and then to one
of my Senpai okay okay
[Music]
um
foreign
yeah I know I know
worldwide traveler
my Travelers
things
you know Kyla first I wanted a camel but
not a change to sniffer but if I would
have gotten a camel I would have named
it Camilla
I love a lot of people say that the
camel cannot be brought home
can you can but it's just difficult to
bring it home I would say because of the
distance
okay hmm
okay
oh Camilla Camilla
what's camel again in Japanese
I used to know it is
[Music]
then
you go there camel do you know
foreign
to translate your jokes but I'm doing it
or to explain your jokes but I'm just
doing it so that everybody understands
what's going on it's okay I'm here by
the way where are you oh which side of
the tunnel I'm going back to the the
beginning of the tunnel I mean just
enter the Nether Portal
okay okay you can maybe I should have
taken the boat you can maybe wait at the
stairs yeah
wait wait I'm on my way
[Music]
um
this is
foreign
[Music]
how many do you need just take it first
okay thank you that's enough okay
Overkill Kyla the the queen of Overkill
hi
[Music]
I'm coming
Redstone how much Redstone a full choker
box right yeah wow nice Sasuke
good morning
wow
speed
faster than Uber sheets
not God
no no
[Music]
no if you don't know Japanese how were
you like listening to water mainstream's
Clips or
Clips but sometimes just just watch like
it's okay no don't I don't understand
then it's okay
I don't know it's just like comfy
and you get like maybe a general idea of
what's by looking at the screen Maybe
tomorrow
foreign
[Music]
thank you
I think you forgot my gift for Kyla I
still have a gift for you too Kyle
what's going on
[Music]
thank you thank you
ah
cool house cool house
thank you
[Music]
you know
it's hard wheeling again
no no
no no no no no no you are not third
willing it's okay
it just seems very familiar to the
situation I had with Guru and okay where
I was just translating for them
[Music]
thank you so much
please
[Music]
thank you
I I don't even know how to go on but
it's okay I'll find my way out uh
it's okay it's a
bit okay
think
I'm going back to the tunnel Arena
thank you
[Music]
everybody gets what they need
it
[Music]
okay
that's so cute
say goodbye
[Music]
okay okay okay that now I'm not third
Wheeling anymore
I almost died
I I've almost died but it's okay
from embarrassment or
excitement and for from from nervousness
oh but see I mean it was
um kind of weird how this came together
but you got some time to talk to about
the missing by nice too it's okay Chit
Chat
yeah but I just kind of hinted at what
I'm missing by now that maybe maybe now
is a good time because you're coming
back to me so we'll probably be talking
to each other yeah
wait wait I forgot where to go that way
that way okay okay
and just try to get to the end of the
tunnel eventually okay you will see me
but I'm just placing blocks right now I
hope this
actually it might not be enough
oh it's not enough
yeah I mean I can just grind some blue
eyes again somewhere here some some
normal Cactus is fine too yeah a mix
usually is what I've been using just mix
of pectins wait I will try to find Ian
server got a lot of eyes too yeah yeah
where should I go I
nice eyes baby
eyes
need some fun in the future maybe for
the future yeah but oh this tunnel
yeah definitely not enough let's see
Doodly Doo
I could fly around outside of the tunnel
too to find some more eyes okay okay we
probably I can find some
I
I need to get present for Kyle
when I get out of the tunnel don't make
me forget guys
did someone spoil on you what I have for
you I hope not
did they tell you did your chat tell you
about what
I have for you oh no no no no no okay
good don't tell her
please don't tell her
there is no ice here where can I get
eyes
I had to turn back the bgm right guys
I'll turn it back on
we have no idea two days
[Music]
like you have no more
no more ice
I don't know
um no no no no I I use I kind of use a
lot of ice back then or for what for for
the road too yeah from for the tunnel ah
you also made the room yeah and then
that's just the leftover that I have
cool
Iceberg by Omi I know there's many
Iceberg biome Museum only Eon survived
flew by so many of them
I think even on the way from the first
the last that one portal that I made
do I have fireworks no
okay I will go fly too I'll go find some
myself Kyla yeah I'm still trying to
find it too it's okay
hmm
I only
does this count as shaved ice for the
bingo card
um Kyla are you trying to to fill out
the bingo card yeah the Bingo right yeah
yeah
you have to eat shaved yeah the shaved
eyes I haven't done that one in
Indonesia yeah yeah a lot but yeah it's
just like too sweet and I just don't
like it just you just have to eat one
bite and then you can get yeah right
true in in Austria we don't have shaved
eyes normally but I mean maybe you can
make it by yourself right but don't you
need like a shaved ice machine
not gonna use my my cheese grinder and
shape ice with my cheese grinder
or
um what about
um
[Music]
called the
um
not gelato but like a certain type of
ice that's more ice cream that's more
close to like what it is
sorbet yeah sorbet could we say sorbet
is shaved ice not really I think not
really I think
that kind of shaved eyes but I mean like
the Japanese one but
I mean if you say that
shift eyes then yeah it's gonna be
shaved eyes the Bingo will do we don't
we don't have Japanese shaved ice in
Austria but it's okay I'm going to Japan
next week so I'll eat
[Music]
actually I ate shaved ice maybe one time
in my life at a Japanese Summer Festival
um
next time if you come to Indonesia again
probably you can
but I'm guessing you guys have like your
own version of it yeah
I think it's different I think it's
different
how what's the difference
um
it's like
more like the Indonesian traditional
eyes we have like a lot of we we got
like uh the toppings the toppings right
we got like uh coconut
uh syrup
um
beans like what uh black beans black
beans
I don't know I'm
I
usually don't eat sweet so
guys help me I am right all right
red beans all red beans
[Music]
okay guys
these coordinates two seven eight one
one zero two twenty four thousand seven
hundred just so that I don't get lost
write it down guys I'm grinding some ice
right now okay me too
wear my wings
don't call Hot Wings
wings
what
I lost my elytra
well I don't know where you go there's
no way I wouldn't bring it it's in my
house and their chest probably shelter
I did
I take it it's in my home and I'm on the
other side you know where I started the
tunnel
okay then I already checked the energies
[Music]
I thought it was here
ah Kyla
how long do you plan on streaming today
not that long I think I still have like
I don't know like um I a whole idea
gonna be very busy in August
also we have like a lot of homework
homework yeah oh I think I know why
yeah yeah right yeah right yeah right
yeah right
[Music]
yeah thank you so yeah I don't know how
long can I stream tonight
you have to set priorities yeah I know
thank you very much
you're welcome
my pleasure how long how long will you
stream tonight me another six hours no I
think maybe
um another
five out four or five hours
because but not all of it will be
Minecraft because I have the recipe
oh my god do we have to watch this
[Music]
I think they're moving and training
what time was it for me I think it was
like maybe around it's
um 10 p.m GST so it's 3 P.M for me okay
okay I will be awake guys
you will be watching too of course of
course
I asked my peers to watch that too yeah
finally second gen
for a second gen ID to yeah
it got delayed
[Music]
okay you know what yeah I will do
something else I because it doesn't make
sense if we both do the same thing but
it's gonna be fine
oh the Torches anyway
I will torches and I'll wait for your
arrival oh by the way where are you
putting torches and another like um
like because because it's so dark in the
tunnel especially when you have shaders
on okay
you question my
my methods huh no no no no no no no no
no I just won I just wanna know like
what's for but okay it makes sense
guys you made me forget the Kyla gift
again what the hell
forgot to pick it up again I will pick
it up next time I come back
time
and I need no torches
you walk without torches you're not
scared of the dark my torches is the
lava all over the Nether
um
did you lose your things no no no it's
just the the way to go back
yeah I do it on purpose yeah
oh because it's too far away already
let's not look in eyes
eyes ah guys do you remember when I made
the portal uh and then I saw this like
big
Fortress never Fortress oh is that a
fortress or was it a black Beyond you
want to go explore that let's go no I
was I was I just found a really big one
and you know they were like oh my God
that's that's really good it's really
rare
I was wondering because today in the
video that I watched about the new
update I saw that there's
um these
um trimming yeah the trims right in
Bastion and Fortress but where's the
difference between a Bastion and the
fortune The Fortress one is kind of
reddish in color and the red the Boston
kind of black
oh yeah I chapters I found a portrait oh
okay it's Bastion even more rare or
same I can say Bastion is more dangerous
[Music]
yeah Fortress whatever skeletons and
Blazers and what about that what do you
find in the Bastion Bastion is Brut
piglet
foreign
[Music]
yeah yeah of course of course of course
laughs
speaking of things
I wasn't looking what happened fall down
I got I got jump scared by a piglet I
get jump scared so easily you know
it's okay Minecraft do that a lot of
times
[Music]
no I do not
I did not
soil myself
I found one very close to my mess up by
all means oh really
really I don't remember that but so you
go to the Bastion for what the dreams
only for the trains but what about
before the trims oh why would you go oh
no no uh the B4 I just like pass through
it and then I I thought like I have no
knowledge about that and then I just
died I just then lost there and then
nice and then I've never gone there
again after that but I need to go back
there for the trims uh no no actually
they offer
uh uh a lot of
valuable things too inside the Bastion
yeah
they have never worn fashion I have lots
of gold yeah
never dungeon Fallout
some never ride really yeah some nether
but it's I'm not worth it it's not worth
it but that was before now you go there
for Trims and never right smithing
template
[Music]
see oh and a pig step music disc yeah
true true true true
let's see a good night
I don't care about the trims but you
know what I want to do another time I
want to do some archeology yeah yeah the
pottery right the pottery one yeah yeah
yeah my pottery and just like dusting
with the brush dusting the suspicious
and yeah
truly true
that's exciting
sorry you tried the RK did you try yeah
yeah I got some but not all of it um
but the you know the sniffer egg
find it in warm water right not really
it's like we just desert
what
was it
something new you find in the warm water
I thought really
warm ocean
um warm ocean the sniffer no I guess it
was something else oh fruit warm ocean
no that I guess that's archeology
okay I'm confused
yeah there's many things many things
many many things
oh yeah and the Bastion right
um Minecraft
Minecraft
update the requirements for having
natural tools and equipments right now
so we need to go to Bastion to if we
want to have like Madre armor and
Equipment tools right now yeah
why making so much more
but with that updates diamond is more
valuable right now yeah
digging for diamond
[Music]
Diamond potato
okay how's it going how much ice did you
find
I got I I wait
I crafted it already to blue eyes but
it's only four Stacks blue eyes and my
pickaxe is almost dying already pack
size is also fine like a mix
okay okay okay
so should we meet again at the portal
yeah
okay
what is the coordinates of the portable
item
yeah I don't know it's okay it's okay I
actually have to know too much too lazy
to open it's okay it's okay
already how to get there
you cannot see guys are you not watching
the Stream
mobile users right it's too small
[Music]
she didn't want help did she I feel like
I already offered fauna to help with her
big tree didn't she say no you know
oh
what happened
it's okay it's okay it's just the wind
s
nice the wind's like flowing through all
the rooms and then the door went like
yeah yeah
happen all the time yeah
[Music]
kill you
Personal Agenda
shop
little piglets
so Kyle did you achieve what you wanted
to achieve today
I have no goals
but kinda yeah kinda yeah
oh my goal to say strainer is just like
getting
as many Nethers as possible
before August so yeah
yeah you've been doing it for a while
right yeah
getting stronger and stronger
for so long without eyes oh my God I'm
coming back I'm coming back
oh
but it's not a lot and I don't think
it's enough probably I'm gonna fix my
pickaxe first and then I'll go back
that's okay I'll pick up my elytra and
then I go find some more ice if I need
it
um but I don't know I think I think in
theory once I have the ice the tunnel is
finished quickly and then I can go find
the egg but I don't know how long you
want to stay with me that's no pressure
okay it's still 12 right now it's fine
somewhere
you have to look at the screen more
closely
brought the gift
of course I did
uh fffs
you guys got the coordinate for FFF I
don't know um yeah
go there too I think because I have to
probably
um repair my elytra
Maybe
why are you going for your pickups
I still have your pickaxes oh I repaired
one fully
but then I already forgot about that
you forgot
short term memory of course yeah I got
distracted a lot yeah
poor Kyla all the stress from streaming
so much she doesn't even notice that
she's losing her memory
slowly every day
She's forgetting more and more
you you want to fix your ally trace it
maybe maybe I mean I can just fix it for
you it's okay
[Music]
oh I can fix it you see you remember
fixing uh an elytra by giving me a new
one no no no no no no no no no no it's
like literally fixing
I'm here
oh me too almost
almost almost almost almost almost
weren't there piglets in the boat here
before that did somebody removed them
did you remove piglets no
no
maybe it's just me no
at the beginning
I'll kill them now no
no no don't let the intrusive thoughts
no no no no
no no no they must buy they are not
paying to use the tunnel
it's only free for whole life members
[Music]
no they can't even defend themselves
okay I guess they kind of did
see now it's angry
I have the bone interesting
uh
oh oh sugoi
[Music]
this is perfect
or you're putting in even more Kyla here
is something for you look at look at the
inside of the chocolate box yay
you got it like you got you got it when
you stream mine the tunnel no I mean I
wasn't purposefully looking for it but
yeah it was found in the creation of
this tunnel randomly oh
very lucky
[Music]
sweet I can give you this one back too
thank you
now if you want you can follow me if you
want I'm just gonna quickly finish
though I don't know if that's enough
though I mean if that's not enough then
maybe
I figured maybe I can
you can find some ice again what is that
all the time I see something there and I
don't know what it is when I'm
driving by with my boat
thank you so much
I know it's so rare
and I don't need it
usually like I tried I think sometime
two one or two years ago I did strip
mining with my mom
she joined our Ian Minecraft server and
then she showed me how to do strip
mining and we tried to get some never
ride but yeah I don't really need it so
thank you you're welcome if I find more
I can give it to you it's it's fine it's
it's like uh
put one in here okay
we can ride the same boat me oh where
did the boat go ah did you get the boat
no
oh wait I have a blind
okay
[Music]
Road
is this this one is really short oh this
path
okay me
one short one and then another long one
okay
then where is the ice again oh this one
here yeah and this one is long ah wait
okay okay done this is the last one like
the last one for now for now
who knows maybe in the future when
Minecraft adds even more new biomies
then
I have to find them and I have to go
really far
oh
yeah this one is the long one yeah
if you want actually we can do um I've
been doing a right row pack nice left
row blue eyes oh I can give you the
pactas for example
you can do white row if you want okay
pecans
bag guys
okay
let's see who's faster no don't do that
[Music]
I'm good
teamwork
if you ever need help building something
you can ask me for help too of course
I can try to help
I don't like building so much but I can
try
so cheap this is considered as building
though building
are you freezing nice it's fine it's
fine
it's fine
all good
did you place one in the wrong spot no
no everything's good
because I do that too but I have silk
touch
[Music]
she got you made a hole no no no no no
no all good be careful nah it's fine
I had to fill some holes that were
showing lava so yeah maybe sometimes
when you accidentally dig too deep
we'll find some lava not good not good
snitched on
that is the problem when both of us are
streaming then yeah somebody's yeah
somebody's trying to hide a secret
I need more eyes more
[Music]
now stay don't run away right away don't
run away one
two three
four there you go
[Music]
Kyla when should we play Diablo again
I'm so busy like I don't think I can
play it the whole month and that's a
good question yeah
we are maybe longer busy right yeah but
August yeah
ah
it's okay it's okay
we'll find a way
if anyone finds a way it will be you
Kyla
you're the one who
is like the most capable of squeezing a
million things into one day
yes yes not really I just
um I think
if you're saying that I'm good at
squeezing not really probably I'm good
at um eliminating
Halloween meeting other things like
eliminating sleeping
oh yeah but you see I I wouldn't do that
I I don't think I could function on long
term I think I would be very very
exhausted and burnt out yeah don't do
that don't do that yeah
out or anything right no no no because
because for me streaming is like I don't
know for me yeah for me streaming is
just when I want to have fun it's
playing games it's talking it's
disgusting I get that too but I think
even then even when streaming is fun for
you you should always know your own
limits and give your body some time to
arrest you yeah I know
sometimes you feel yourself that you're
fine but eventually your body will tell
you yo I'm not okay yeah but please I
don't know I don't know why but every
single time when
um I feel very tired whenever I touch
grassroot because yeah it's just like
exhausting yeah going out is exhausting
for me but yeah I mean I
had time I told uh my fears about like
okay guys tomorrow I'll be touching
grass and then probably I will still
stream but maybe I'll just go like for
one or two hours and then whenever I
start streaming right it's gonna be like
going hours and hours and hours and
hours it's like I don't know streaming
charge my energy somehow
[Music]
good yeah if you don't like touching
grass how are you gonna do the barbecue
thing in bingo I mean
do that in games
where are you with barbecue simulator or
something like that well how do you do
barbecue in which game I don't know not
yet not yet me
all right that's that gives me another
reason to play raft less
no
[Music]
real barbecue it's yummy it's good it's
like you're just eating food
oh are you really like a food enjoyer
like you're kind of picky of food
okay okay
yeah because I just eat food for
surviving
like I don't care about the taste anyway
actually
[Music]
I mean I can grind again for you
no we'll just use pie test it's fun
it's still fast
my eyes are feeling dizzy
because I'm trying to
keep up okay I'm faster I'm faster
it's like we're already competing
against each other and all right no
don't say that
oh but Kyla we're in the same team right
yeah no no we are not competing yeah
we're not complete
we're in a team
and there is no Lava behind right I just
I just go no no no no backwards and then
no everything's clean and safe
well you know I was looking at the teams
oh wait here there you go I thought the
teams the other team the team that's not
us is kind of a
overpowered strong
but
I think you're the only really strong
one in our team Kyla no no no no no
don't say that you are you're strong our
tree our Dream our team are strong
are all the members decided now because
I don't think I saw a full member list
uh
still
still on progress on process
okay yeah
take it
doesn't matter
is it so there's still like some open
spots in the teams yep still
I think if you need more of probably
some more Ian would also make or more
Japanese members yeah we are we're we're
doing it right now like we are
contacting
[Music]
no worries get get us someone good in
our team
to win right yeah and we're gonna win we
really cracked that Minecraft crony this
chronic participating
um not yet
good as already participating so but
she's in the other team
I have to find my newfound sister I feel
so sad
okay oh
[Music]
oh
okay
now what
you look like a Pokemon kind of one this
is
Let's uh did you bring a boat yeah
okay let's go back to the very beginning
a very nice place
okay and then I just leave my things at
the at my home okay
and then we can fly to find the sniffer
but so the sniffer we don't have to go
to a newly I think we need terrain I
think we need to yeah I think we need to
go to the newer chunk yeah but don't
they all like spawn everywhere in the in
and go to the new ones
okay then in the end after I get my
lights rub we have to maybe go back here
because this is newly loaded here is
newly yeah yeah sure sure
okay
but then how do I bring I know never
mind that's the good thing I just get
the egg and then
but wait how do we get the egg where was
that and the mocking waddam says zzz
yeah
uh the eggs we need to brush right do
you have brush brush brush oh my gosh I
have some brush really for you
my brush oh thank you how do you make
the brush
um copper feather sticks
I'll put feather sticks
okay okay let's go
okay I I got my elytra uh and we come
back here and then we fly to some desert
and then
and then we find the egg okay
but we're in the never we don't have to
sleep guys yeah we're gonna explode if
we sleep here wow cat is spamming
yeah
it doesn't matter
no repairs needed uh I don't think so
maybe for the maybe for the Elijah I'll
check
I can fix it for you with warm ocean
nothing that's what I was thinking
something in the warm ocean you can find
the egg in the warm ocean no I'll get
some help I fed I found the
sniffer from
the
[Music]
the No No not desert um
Beach yeah
[Music]
somebody look it up because we're unsure
this way
but I mean desert also in the warm ocean
though like close by
yeah the desert will not be in the cold
ocean for sure yeah yeah true
use brush on Saucy sand that's found in
warm ocean yeah yeah yeah in the sand in
the warm ocean yeah that's that's what I
mean okay that was right and
so listen yeah
so I think the egg yeah the egg is
definitely only in newer terrain I would
say
okay where is my elytra
[Music]
interability 121.
I wonder if it's enough
you're looking what I have
I have nothing interesting
nah this is interesting see
huh and this one is neither eggs
Who start yours mine mine yeah so you
have a natural tickets
from when I got never right with my mom
look in this this chest this shulker
for you
all right are you are you really okay
with that I mean yes yes
isn't it too much
still had some take a ticket isn't it
too much oh wait oh wait I have more
more
it's also for you
I can help you I'm so happy I can help
you
isn't it too much hello I don't know is
it is it a lot I don't know yeah I mean
I mean you can use it like for I don't
know
upgrading your pink eyes I don't need it
I'm not I don't really care about these
prims they look cool but I don't care
about them I mean I mean you can you can
upgrade your what uh armor
diamond stuff is fine I'm happy with
diamond pickaxes I don't need never ride
pickaxes and stuff
I I I already
oh you took it okay good yeah thank you
but can we go to fauna fancy fish farm
yeah okay because my things are breaking
okay
[Music]
do we fly or do we yeah you know exactly
where it is
foreign
yes yeah yes
yes because yes yes but I I always first
I go with the train
okay I don't know how to go to fly uh
there at first I go to train and then I
fly okay
confidential
okay let's take the uh inferior Subway
of the
and server
is there some card for you too
it's okay I can walk
no no it's a really long prank Kyla okay
I will fly
oh okay um
well I hope you don't Bonk your head
Whenever there is um
a wall it's okay it would be very
unfortunate
[Music]
oh there you are did you Bonk your head
no I'm fine really are you sure yeah you
shine
in the tunnel doing exactly what you did
ah ouch in your couch yeah but it's okay
I'm fine I told you
you will show what is this anyway what
is that here for
should I get rid of this
am I going to the right place I don't
know have you never gone to fauna's
fancy fish farm with the subway never
is it really close
after me at the end of the subway yes
yes but I think the subway now is a loop
so you need to know where to get off oh
really
yeah I mean I just you know okay okay it
stops okay it does stop but then there's
a connection yeah
once we get to PPP I know how to get to
FFF
okay
what direction is this maybe next time
you no I can't because this Subway it
makes many turns so I don't know which
direction it is when I fly
I should just remember the coordinates
but I don't know
I mean I mean I have the coordinates if
you want
FFF yeah I just I just need to open the
notes
oh oh wow I'm almost there hi hi
follow me
this is so slow
it's okay you can enjoy the
stop the view the view of beautiful
trimmed Kyla
oh I think we're almost there oh yeah oh
yeah this feels like we're almost there
is this Subway slower than it used to be
because like damn
we should speed it up I'm gonna call I'm
a I'm a construction oh it's here I see
yes yes yes yes you made it
very positive and then we go
and once we're outside I know that it's
behind PPP
where are you oh here okay
follow me
it's okay it's okay okay
somewhere here yeah this this big
ah oh yeah that's super close
okay okay
[Music]
you got it
I go first so I guess there's two swords
we can move to it
hello fishies are you here fishies uh
where are they we just need to wait okay
what am I
what is what is this dirt going on here
dirt yeah probably Andy move a dirt here
ah
what's Andy doing up here
[Music]
these are so scary
oh scary
okay Amanda and now I do the pickaxe
I should have
should have brought
well
is there an Industries here yeah
yeah
I'm going to die oh okay
okay
your turn okay hold on
oh yes
you're your biggest
this one's oh I'll put it in the in the
chest above you okay okay
[Music]
oh
really oh
how about now
there should be
wait no now it's like triple or double
back double BPM
I don't know guys
yeah uh
I'll just turn it off
hey you didn't hear double really
okay yeah
[Music]
from me what
the fish was sucking the life from me
it went to soccer then
do you know do you know song do you know
Saucon
um
not really
you never heard of sarcon
oh
I'm reading the live chat
[Music]
that that kind of helps me to understand
oh wait I still had the funny fish fast
I'm sorry I didn't give it back but I
needed anyway oh did you see the pickaxe
there it's in the chest oh
[Music]
she waits she was already saying what
what staying it well yeah because
because when when you when when you ask
it like repetitively and now it's like
uh
um
oh man
oh man I tried
yeah when someone asks you repetitively
about something
and I just I just I just I don't know I
want to share my experiences with other
people
fishy.com
there it is there they are you are they
all like arrive at once oh
not as stuffy as the suspicious
suspicious gravel
Yes actually you know how to
differentiate that because
my eyes
cannot see it I mean the the suspicious
oh because we need to like differentiate
it
if we because if we break the sand the
suspicious sand it's gone yeah
yeah we need to differentiate it like
using our eyes
but for me I usually just have three
and I offer my mouse cursor and then let
the F3
yeah I would probably do it like that
too yeah but it's like slower actually
if you can differentiate it with your
bare eyes yeah it's faster
ah
okay I'm done with amending everything
I'm a little bit more I think hold on
[Music]
maybe we need to sleep first yeah
that's a lot of phantom we just need to
sleep
you want some
ah
you trying to sleep I'm trying to
protect you I'm Tower I'm I'm trying to
I'm trying to swing my sword but I'm
scared that I will accidentally hit
I'm a part-time Warrior my official Lord
says I'm a part-time Warrior I'll take
care of us
oh you little [\h__\h] they got stuck
[Music]
stupid
Kyla was that you
no of course not I I did not think
is there any chance perhaps that you
make yourself so strong with all the
never right and all no million items
because you are actually bad at combat
no actually actually right oh actually
right you know what I have my Thorns
armor so if you hit me you got a damaged
so you're saying that eye damage yeah
that's how I got them
but it would be funny if you're actually
like if that's what why you're doing
um all these all this effort to become
stronger in Minecraft
I mean after all I'm just a black man I
mean yeah
I may not need it but it's just my job
right so yeah
it's so fast come here come here
nice
probably fell into the ocean oh there it
is
I got some Phantom membranes nice oh
yummy okay now we go now that we're safe
well we need to go back to
I don't know we need to go back to the
tunnel first right we need to get to the
newer
[Music]
on our way back but I always get lost
when I fly
it's okay we can have the Cordon that's
right
[Music]
people but blow it opens my notes first
uh coordinate MC coordinate okay e n
Surfer
it's a
[Music]
okay I don't have the nether oh
this one right
is this this one the minus two one two
Maybe 44.
yeah I think I think I think so minus
two one two Forty Four
okay I follow you
where are you let me put back all of
these fish first
[Music]
where are you
I'm above you oh thank you okay okay
let's go we go to
negative I think it's first of all this
way we go we need to go that way though
really okay
[Laughter]
flying penguin oh my god I've never seen
a flying penguin before I'm not a
penguin but
oh yeah right oh yeah true wait where
are you I don't see you my mind
straight okay
still there
I don't know I don't see you um
yeah
you're good you're good I think I found
some stuff
yeah okay that is that is that um
this way
it wasn't completely placed right
oh good
where are you no I'm I'm on my way
okay I arrived at the portal okay
should I bring something what are we
doing we just need the brush so we can
get an egg so I need yeah we need to go
to the tunnel first
and then just fly whenever to wherever
we can find our motion right
okie dokie
oh maybe that's my my trail
I left behind by accident
see
I was an accident
you played hologure before right me why
in the whole look here did you play my
character Kiana yeah why you saw how
Kiana lives behind a fire truck yeah the
trail yeah the fires yeah that's so
maybe the forest fire that you saw
[Music]
got it
my character Kion I think I said this if
she doesn't know who who my character is
my character Kiana you know my character
Kiara said Kiara
[Music]
where is the city or that one city okay
I'm gonna make sure that we're talking
about the same thing which said you mean
our village no no it's okay I'm I'm here
I don't think you can call this a city
the Ian city right the that's not it's
not it's not worth being called a city
don't say don't say that it's the
village Kyla don't say that wait can you
give me like the accordance of the
portal like another
portalita
wait a moment wait what is this is not
someone's house right because it's
burning hold on hold on hold on burning
house
oh
oh my God
I don't know this is
a house why how soon is on fire why what
is
okay um
361 should I write it down
361 and they were the Z
minus 500. okay
positive effects negative okay
you guys always want me to sing Spanish
right I found this song today
from Katy Perry with some dude which
they sing in Spanish I think the the
boom boom boom girl that song
but he raps in Spanish so
so it will take me five years to learn
the song
oh yeah Daddy Yankee
I'm here hello
[Music]
let me write this down under my camera
what happened oh no okay
well into the dark okay let's go
what time is it over there almost one
it's okay oh that's so early it's like
good morning time good morning
[Music]
good morning USA
did you know did you know that in Polish
TV
all the TV programs or almost all of
them my teacher today told me
um they're like you know dubbed but it's
like
adopted by like everything is dead by
the same person
really one guy one guy does all the
voices oh really
[Music]
it for the ads or for like everything
for TV shows everything
movies one one person does like older
voices and they will speak over like
they're the original track will be there
too really quietly the original for
example English track and then one guy
reads over it like really like like
monotone like like this and
[Music]
really I yeah
my Korean teacher told me because she
lives in Poland too and in many other
countries
and she told me polish TV is really
weird because there is no like proper
dubbing like in other countries TV maybe
yeah but I mean if that one guy
does all of the dubbing probably I mean
that guy gonna have like a lot of
experience and it's gonna be like good
at some point no you know in in in in in
in like German speaking countries our
dubs there's like different people for
different characters of course and then
they also they're like actors right they
will pronounce things like like actually
with feelings and my teacher told me
that in Polish TV they just read it
monotone and and probably for women
characters there's a women voice sir who
voices everything and for guys there's
just one person who voices all the guys
in that one show or whatever so it's
like all the same it's like predictable
a woman is also a guy
never mind I was just corrected for
women it's also all one really
oh my God that just made it worse
oh my God can you guys not like hire one
more person
that one guy moment that one
but apparently I'm not wrong so what my
teacher told me was was right okay I'm
glad that I'm not lying and spreading
misinformation
in the movie there's a lady and and a
guy flirting with each other having a
really sweet time and then it's just the
same guy talking to each other in the
voiceover I love you you are so
beautiful oh my God I know you're even
more beautiful I would love you forever
oh my God will you marry me yes I will
marry you oh my god oh I'm so happy oh
we should have babies and make children
and like oh I'm so ready oh oh yeah wow
that is very very bad
girl you can
just because crony loves himself
oh you know what I owed us I owed us a
village some torches I mean it's okay
it's okay I stole torches it's okay it's
not okay they're gonna die because of me
it's not okay
no no
I mean
writing down the coordinates okay we're
good nice more coordinates for the
coordinate folder beautiful okay all
good all good all good
you should honestly you should publish
your your
notes all right I know right people know
yeah
because often I'm like looking for
something and I'm like why did I not
write down the coordinates me I have an
eye recording it yeah where we want to
go
anywhere any direction as long as we can
come back it's okay
all colored in it's secured but there's
no yeah totally not that
way maybe which which way
we can go that way
okay I will just follow you I'm just
trying to find some I don't see you
just go straight it's gonna be fine
wow there's so much Sakura here yay
I found the best Sakura by
e whoa this is so huge it's loading so
slow Kyla please go slow yeah yeah I
know I'm I'm going around too it's so
cute sad polish oh my God how many
Polish people are in my chat right now
because I saw so many people who said
yeah that's right that's right I can't
believe there's so much any Polish
people in my live chat maybe not I don't
know I think I have quite a lot
what happened
I don't know I'm okay okay I think I
have so many because I always stream at
European Time
I'm here oh I got it police guy here oh
hello
is this not a warm ocean
oh hi hi I don't think this is a warm
one turtles yeah Turtles doesn't that
mean it's warm I don't know no ouch this
is Jason
normal plain ocean
I think I'm still close here but we can
just go around this ocean and probably
there's a warm one
oh okay
would it say warm water warm water
warm water
I can't even see from here
this is actually my time don't you want
to sleep first bad time no no no don't I
didn't bring a bed I can give you a bag
oh no that's ice again
what's your graphic card
oh I heard that you just change it right
yeah no not yet I have it but I have to
still
um uh I have to uh build it yeah so not
right now it's still the old one yeah
yeah mine is still 38 DTI
TTI 38 DTI
he
[Music]
is this eyes this is cold one
what happened nothing I'm just I like to
scream oh it's in my free time I like to
scream it's okay
it's my hobby you know yeah it's okay
[Laughter]
uh whatever I don't care about this
crying obsidian
hatsu
and she really died over guys
[Laughter]
[Music]
can I tell you a story yes I don't know
if you know the story one time one time
I was playing Minecraft like maybe two
years ago and
um I was just chilling just just
building something and I found really
randomly uh uh I was found I was found
by some drowns
and the first round that found me he was
throwing uh
he was throwing tridents yeah
I've never seen a trident drowned before
that was my first time yeah and then
okay and then and then I kill him uh-huh
the first round I ever see I killed him
and he dropped a trident so it's like
first try I called it the first Trident
first Trident first try yes you still
have it right now
yes I still have it wow cool but the
reason why this was especially funny is
because gooda the the girl who has a
trident as her weapon
um she was looking for tridents in
Minecraft and she was she was farming
them for hours and hours yeah you're
just very lucky yeah I just
without looking for it and she looked
for it so many hours and didn't find it
for a long long time
you're just very very lucky
lucky girl
did you find some warm ocean yeah I'm
not but I'm brushing some suspicious
grateful right now
and a cold ocean okay I'll go look now I
thought maybe
River
I'm not flying straight though but as
long as you have the coordinates
yeah it's okay no worries that's just
normal ocean there's cold ocean ocean
and warm ocean
it's a species
ocean it's suspicious grapple
River oh pottery
Kyla got distracted
by suspicious gravel because it's very
suspicious I need to check it
it's raining now
the sky is so sad
pieces oh
I can get some ice here
there's blue eyes packed eyes
you will not take it but you have
finished it you want to change it again
you know I'm just I just was thinking
because it looks nice
ice spikes
I go look for
warm warm ocean
[Music]
uh-huh
uh-huh I'm scared
I'm scared loads in so slowly oh yeah
you need to go back if it's not unloaded
I'm loading so much there and terrain oh
God where is home
it'll be fine
I don't know where I am
it's okay I got the coordinates
I mean I can go to your place
no
no nothing we don't need this area
Beach called why is it all cold I don't
even know where I came from
um Kyla can you tell me the coordinates
uh the coordinates what the the portal
yeah closer to where we came from okay
um
who's
Lake Kayla says
268-24 796.
oh
yeah let's go
ocean
forever
[Music]
whoa
I found the cherry blossom biome again
nice it's so pretty yeah
um you're not planning to
ouch you're not planning to build
something using that
thing I don't know I maybe I thought
maybe I add some cherry blossom
materials to my villager
um Farm venue mm-hmm where you know
Phoenix done the one I built
I thought maybe
I can make it look cute
aesthetic and maybe maybe I build a new
house who knows
a new house that I don't use
okay I'm going this direction now
because Savannah sounds warm yeah true
true so if I don't want to Sons
still trying to find
Maybe
oh
slow
Nani what did you find oh
[Music]
wait
what do you mean first I'm in the water
oh there's a lot of dirt though
I can't I should
or sand
are you even looking for a warm ocean
now yeah yeah but uh hold on
[Music]
because last time I found a sniffers in
this kind of place so maybe I'm gonna
check this
okay
I'm going completely different direction
now it's okay
if I find it you'll come to me yeah
honestly I mean I think I can probably
uh brush off the eggs alone
and get some bamboo while I'm here
Kyla has learned to ignore my screams
yeah it's okay
[Music]
this one
there should be a suspicious Sun here
right suspicious Sun
just please decide
and you destroy it I mean I destroyed
the gravel not the sand the the sniffer
is in the sand not just careful so it's
fine
you can you make is it true that you can
make blocks out of the bamboo now
ah I don't know
I feel like I heard something like that
yes yes you can oh really yeah
and I just found the bamboo forest so
I'm just gonna bring a lot of bamboo
but it looks the same was that the thing
it looks the same as
normal one
or
it looks different okay okay
I guess that was just about the signs
maybe
um
signs just can't be pink for example
know what I'm talking about no
suspicious son
ah maybe it's because you don't have
your Good Luck Charlie yeah
good luck doco
um here I'm here
good
I am your personal luck shooter
oh that's all ruins like this no you
sure about that okay then
adios
Amigos
bamboozle
okay I have enough bamboo
I go look for warm ocean again
did you guys uh sorry I'm talking too
much yeah so did you guys watch I
thought let's go is that good enough
check check check
I mean am I looking for something
specific
in the
like a monument or so yeah you need to
find Monument or maybe a ruined like a
ruin Monument
okay well I was saying guys did you
watch woman's dream yesterday because I
called in to her streams
the birthday right I I saw I saw the but
is that the poem
yeah
on Twitter I I read it yeah
good one a good one thank you I figured
out that I have a talent for it yeah you
do this ocean was really tiny what the
hell
why is this ocean so small
where where do I go
play
why does the ocean become a river I
thought the rivers speak where are you
right now maybe I need to go to your
place
1500 okay
uh and two five twenty four thousand two
hundred should I write it down okay no
no it's fine
this is not a real ocean this is a plot
no there's a lake
if many rivers
flow into a close
body of water then that's a lake
I think
ouch
baby ocean rendering
[Music]
oh yeah this is the lukewarm yeah
oh you did where are you did you already
find me not really a close close by
um oh I think this is I think this is
the bamboo yeah I think this is the
bamboo that you saw should be here
thank you guys Minecraft geology thank
you thank you I am more logical than
Minecraft
I'm trying to find Monument maybe
there's nothing here Kyla I just want to
follow you can you please carry me
oh okay
um wait
uh
oh yeah probably this is a bamboo that
G you saw before okay two uh one
uh
1500 okay
and 24 200. okay okay
yeah princess carry me please
I just want to turn off my brain and
follow you is that too much to ask
what
blank
[Music]
ery I mean probably we can just go by
boat probably so that we can go together
yeah but you know the problem here is I
found the lukewarm ocean but it's
basically just a lake because it it
doesn't turn into a big ocean it's just
a lake even though it's cold lukewarm
ocean it's so small
and everything around it is jungle and
rivers okay and I cannot I don't I I
seem to always come back to it when I
fly around
okay uh
1500 the Z
and then the Z
the twenty four thousand three hundred
two hundred
two four three right
yeah
[Music]
oh my God my breath I can't hold my
breath
two four three two four three
this is my leg Lake wow
I adopt this Lake
there
grinder yes no yeah because we are like
so far away already and the server kind
of had yeah there's still much much
unexplored terrain of course Minecraft
Surfers endless yeah
[Music]
oh two four three okay close close close
do do
[Music]
I am starting to get
a little bit crazy from my bgm
this is like a very big jungle there
should be a template jungle here by the
way but yeah what what kind of triangle
this jungle
yeah
there's like a monument Temple monument
in the jungle that we can find yeah
because it's so big so probably if we
can find it
we can go look for it have you already
gotten the trims from the jungle yeah
yeah but I mean it's gonna be good if we
can find another
I'm
nearby
I'm once one thousand six hundred and
two two four five
I think Wawa is real I am
in existing
in Canada
okay it should be here where are you
I'm in front of you I am
I am somewhere you have to find me let's
let's please
[Music]
ouch
what was that
why did you hurt me Carla
oh no it's no it's burbs again
Kyla don't worry I will protect you
that's died already what
yes bye-bye share willpower
okay do you want to sleep
there's gonna be a creepers
[Music]
I can catch it
no sorry I'm getting I'm getting a
little bit crazy from my energy drink I
think even though I only drank three
sips
[Music]
wait wait wait
you fly I follow no we sleep we sleep
okay but I have no bed
I can log out though
[Music]
it's okay it's okay we made it I will
protect us
okay yeah
[Applause]
okay Kyla I will close my eyes and you
will fly and find me
the the right ocean because I I need to
find it
it's it's your job
this is Junior I want to give you this
nah that's just one piece
oh one piece
plenty Pottery shirt thank you one piece
I'm not sure yet how I will use this but
I will try yeah you need you need four
of that the same one
okay four yeah for what for the shirt
for four shirts
for short make what uh the the pot
a flower you need bricks flowers I
thought you need bricks uh this is like
the
it got the pattern something like that
yeah the pattern
okay let's go I don't know um
where should we go
go with confidence
and determination
you know what just go with boat
[Music]
s
adios
laughs
[Music]
foreign
songs guys
what do you call that again
you see Shanty see shanty
copyright
ones no way what's uh what's a copyright
freesty shanty
[Music]
oh
see shanty
um there's nothing
[Music]
I don't know there is nothing here
it's not what do we do with a drunken
angel
I won't see Shanty lyrics
lyrics
[Music]
oh okay but how does the
Melody go
maybe maybe now that I can write poems I
can create my own sea shanty even better
nice
what do we do okay
what do we do
nothing here not one thing
nope concealer
nope
what will we do with the drunken sale
what will we do with the drunken sailor
early in the morning way
way she Rises way hanging up she Rises
when you hanging up she Rises early in
the morning shaving
shaving with a rusty eraser okay okay I
can come up with this this is really
early in the morning
for me
I'll write my own right now while you're
while you're rowing row row rowing the
boat I'll registered
what do we do with
no I don't think there's like a way to
go to the ocean to the warm ocean
and walk
kailan Kiana
[Music]
um
guys give me a good line
[Music]
um
don't make everything the same
completely new line guys
you need to be drunk to ride good
shanties but oh well I don't drink
alcohol
[Music]
not thing cannot do we need to walk
okay you guys I don't like your ideas
[Music]
hmm
I want
nutrients load faster
[Music]
okay here I have a couple of lines okay
let's go let's you can join me anytime
[Music]
for it to go to the warm ocean how far
to go to the war um ocean how far to go
to the warm ocean
I didn't think about the last the ending
I can't wait much longer I can't wait
much longer
will travel further will travel further
will travel further
[Music]
foreign
load faster why won't you do that
there's the sun conceived here you want
to go check if there is like three or no
no okay this is focused guys
it's very focused yes no we don't have
time to be distracted
I want you to reload faster
ruin but no
why does new terrain not load faster
[Music]
is it a graphics card thing or a server
no that's the server thing because this
is like already Far Far Away
what is this on our left side that's a
um ruin but it's in the wood this is
this one right this one got a species
gravel for the shards if you want to
check but it's not it doesn't have an
egg right but I'll take a I'll take a
screenshot for the coordinates okay okay
good all good yes I got it
why doesn't the terrain load faster
thing
um
[Music]
what do I finish that with
pumpkin to a mountain I want to find the
sniffer and go I want to find a sniffer
and go I want to find the sniffer Echo
and then make scrambled and goes what
you you want
you can make scrambled eggs with
anything of course yeah we went too well
I think
Okay carry me
carry carry carry
ing
[Music]
okay
I know
Kyla why is it so hard to find the warm
oceans of course of course it's hard
maybe I'll just follow you fly
I don't know
follow me yeah I'll I'll follow you
bye
um that's okay
sand I see Beach as the ocean but no oh
I see I see something cool
I see sheep but no
how to get out of the water when I I'm
in the water just just double space and
right click yeah okay
I knew that I just I just got a little
bit nervous
Chi it's
does the warm ocean always come with
um the fancy flowers and stuff
the lukewarm is yeah yeah the the color
of the water is also different
it's kind of greenish
[Music]
oh no I lost you
yeah I know
[Music]
x 700 and it's that 22
uh
yeah I'm here I'm here I'm here I'm here
okay let's go
[Music]
why can I not find it
and is it even guaranteed that I find an
egg
it's kind of hard actually but it's okay
but I'm lucky I'm like yeah yeah I
believe in you it's fine
foreign
this is a big ocean I think we have
finally found the Atlantic
so I see a deep a monument or something
no no Monument
something glowing
[Music]
no where is she you lost me again yeah
did you get distracted again no it's
really hard to follow someone using
elytra you know
hmm
I am in 708 I've been trying my best
708 and
[Music]
um
24 100 okay
okay I am at a village
you've been here before
Village
is this terracotta maybe you can go to
the village and slippers probably I can
yes but first I take the beautiful
terracotta wait I don't have the bed
with me nice
yeah oh I have your bed
if you don't well it's it's so beautiful
it's orange and and yellow and these are
my colors you know
my my favorite
there's so many enemies here oh my God
oh
okay
you little [\h__\h] [\h__\h] yup
seven hundred twenty four thousand
750 and then 24
000 200.
wait there is no Village here
756. wait wait
okay okay got it getting it
yeah
[Music]
I can take some bad from here yeah
excuse the more
oh you want to sleep yay
I'll think about it okay
no just one second
[Music]
okay yeah right why am I doing this I
have a whole mess up you're right oh my
God I'm so sorry I'll stop I'm stopping
it just looks so pretty I thought I I
need it I don't need it where are you
I'm in the house
okay
I I dodged a skeleton and my his Arrow
hit this villager oh no
you little kids [\h__\h] you
laugh no
okay Kayla
where is the egg
[Music]
front
okay okay follow me
okay let me go this way maybe
slowly slowly slowly slowly
slowly
slowly so so slowly slowly
oh this is such a beautiful beautiful
Valley oh my God
no ocean but
I will find a new ocean
a better ocean are you still there yeah
okay
um
[Music]
now we need an air Shanty are there air
shanties
instead of sea shanties
I've never heard of such a thing but you
know what we we needed
the uncovering
every piece of our and server nice I
think I lost you again but it's okay
it's okay it's okay okay
just go yeah
and then and we see who finds yeah yeah
because like I mean for whatever reason
doesn't make any sense if we go to the
same
direction right okay in the end yes wait
isn't this a warm one no no no no no no
no no no no noise
I found I found I found out really
look why emotion I said the same one as
before no the new one no no no it's new
this is like a lot of jungle
jungle lukewarm is not okay
it has to be warm Temple oh there is a
jungle temple oh wow
well
I found I found something
is this what we're looking for
really what is this
[Music]
lukewarm is fun I found
um
I found
it
try this guy killing me okay okay
good all good okay yeah yeah I escaped
thank God it's like my elytra
I'm not gonna die here no
um
but I found I found what we're looking
for apparently oh really
I'm just gonna build myself a base
really quick or put my bed here
yeah go to bed and then I look for
suspicious scent but if there's drowned
ones throwing tridents at me it's a
little bit difficult
um I'm coming I'm coming okay I can tell
you uh one
1992 is where my bed is 1992. okay and
25 Kiara underscore holoen says 25 800
but okay
underscore Halloween says 1992.
okay okay okay got it what if we get a
trident again
Good Year it was a good year I just want
to go back back to 1999
[Music]
I just wanna go back say Hit Me Baby One
More Time wanna go back wanna go
okay I have my my brush but first I need
to kill
instructions
[Music]
25 I still try that I see Trident coming
at me another another Trident really
yeah yeah
I don't see him but he sees me it's not
fair
you little [\h__\h] where are you
okay is it here no
um I I gave it a coordinates of the bed
um but I'm like in the water ah
all good
yes I will kill him and get a new
trident
okay okay ow
ow I got him
nice
[Music]
all good all good I don't I don't think
he dropped the trident
I almost did too
[Music]
you're using your armor right no you're
using a light try and I think I heard
another trident
wait so many tried in there
I think maybe it might maybe it was my
imagination
so when you try then
there's many enemies
but and they keep on spawning too right
so it's good if I have you you can take
care of the enemies and not look at
suspicious sand what it's in the water
are you in the water no right oh but
right now I'm above water so you could
maybe see me there's like a light spot
in the in the ocean I found your bed
I'm close to that relatively
just go in the water
I saw a chest somewhere here I think
water
mending fishing rod let's go let's go
let's go
don't you think that way the actual
coordinates are 2069.
and the the the sniffer not gonna be in
the Water right
no but the sand isn't I think in the
water oh the sand where the egg is
underneath as far as okay
they told me they told me 2016.
it will be yes yes egg isn't yeah okay
good
2016.
can't open one
I need some water breathing potion
I know I can do that what is it
is this this one
2 800. I
thing
hi
so my viewer said that it could be here
yeah okay can you can you take care of
the enemies okay okay okay okay okay I
look for the okay
uh a suspicious sand right suspicious
[Music]
what what what what's inside wait I
think my inventory is full
I don't think there was anything in that
one was it can they be completely empty
what that wasn't brushing it's right
click
I did it wrong it's okay there's still
plenty of it
yes
breathing breathing um
oh sand
sand
Santa
I will try to look at the others then
have you checked the other not yet no
okay
do you have a door Kyla a breeding right
um hold on
hold on we
we
um
let's craft some door
yes I'm too stupid for this
I don't think I think there was like
just a single suspicious sand here
you
open it
[Music]
I thought I can learn some but no
um hold on ah it's okay that was one
there was one
Oh you mean the one I broke
yeah where is my wood suspicious sense
suspicious
[Music]
like a go and right click red red red
click
shoot
respecting the remnants
I got I got an angler Pottery here yay
[Music]
I'm gonna run out of food
I I have food I have food
oh
um
yeah yeah I don't have much left I'll go
find another suspicious stand
is it always like at the bottom this one
Bigfoot big food
oh thank you
oh thank you stay sticky
oh do you have a water breathing potion
I I I don't bring it but what I can do
is actually maybe I can lend you my
helmet first
this one this one yeah just just just
take my helmet first then
that one one
it will let you it will let you bridge
longer
where
what happened I almost died
no I get it I like it get it
you have been the potion really
I got it
nice beautiful house my resistance guys
viruses things
fire assistance
not the water breeding I I don't
my my energy is still the netherite
set up guys
oh yeah and every suspicious sand here
too okay actually bring another
well uh I will I will try to find some
wood
my my breathing holds much longer thank
you thank you
I think it's 45 seconds right now
so boy
suspicious I grew up first I go up first
any of the structures should have some
okay nice
I'm going first
oh
okay we do the scratch scratch scratch
scratch with no egg I don't think that's
an egg ah is that a pickaxe or something
like that
nanny
oh it was a wooden hole
what
don't give me useless things
I want the egg
suspicious sand
y School let's go watch which it's so
dark
that is
oh a shelter Pottery shard
I want to do this during daytime
[Music]
odd that one okay okay
oh the one that I just got from the
uh treasure map I see yeah I have two
potions I have two water potion you need
that
would be probably kind of useful yeah
and I can give you back to oh wait does
this not work because there's something
on top
[Music]
uh wait what where's that here here
hold the torch
okay that helps a lot yes
[Music]
I got another shard
okay
um
this one is the potion you can just have
it oh thank you let's go just do you
want yeah you can no you you use one too
no no it's fine it's fine I have doors
right now okay
um
[Music]
I think I already found all the
suspicious sand in this little spot
maybe I know one more one more
I heard that I heard ah I am
[Music]
Emerald Emerald
okay I think here maybe no more
okay I go here
I'm mostly looking at the on my
[Music]
um
the letters here so if I'm missing
something guys or if I'm going back to
the same place let me know because it's
hard for me to notice
so big there must be more
should I like get rid of some of this so
maybe I can see more
sad
okay
suspicious
come on come on it's round it's round
not Brown
what was that
no is it just like that guys
call great
wow exciting
I want to open it
wait
[Music]
oh
thank you for the dog
you're welcome oh
get rid of all this good
that's me me it's me it's me
[Music]
I didn't know you could hear the other
person drowning we can
[Music]
and there's a lot of treasure map
they should be at least one I think but
I one egg
one egg this is suspicious sand
speeches son
found e
[Music]
spacious I get it
I haven't brushed it okay just brush it
okay I brush yeah yeah but I don't think
I think it's watering yeah oh okay I
think also okay
[Music]
maybe down here
oh you could probably when I was looking
for
some kind of tree for the like Lush
caves I used that some kind of mod or so
that made it stand out more you could
probably do that for the
cheater
[Music]
I'm using the shaders and people see
that it's very visible but problem just
blind
Me Maybe I mean
two don't worry I don't even know which
ones did I go to before these ones or
these ones
maybe if the chest is
[Music]
empty
there's nothing you've probably been
here portion gone oh already
are you living your shulkers there
later you're gonna forget no
[Music]
no okay
tell me okay sure suspicious and
get Toho
y does it want to the sun is already
done
and that was an ax wow
so golly
[Music]
is it just literally one layer I don't
know
what do you mean
like
the first layer that we saw and then we
don't need to dig down
the cut Sandstone underneath those
there's often suspicious sand I missed
two what
I mean I missed two well I don't know
like where I came from
was it here oh wait I think I saw
something
[Music]
what do you mean I missed two
right next to each other
[Music]
but not here
this one
all of this are said
cool
ah I found one but that's probably a
different one right
the one I took the top of yeah okay this
is not an egg
what is this
[Music]
how long does the breathing potion work
three minutes
okay I can give you some doors after
that
sand
nope
we're not even gonna finish that one
yeah so many Maps I don't know
I go here
maybe also under the chest
oh
hmm
[Music]
my eyes are getting tired from looking
so closely
[Music]
what
sentence
[Music]
and they have a cracked pattern on them
too really
yeah people see that
what maybe I'm just blind I
[Music]
can't stand
I'll just remove every sand that is not
suspicious
isn't that the most genius strategy yeah
you can do that
[Music]
I'll remove the whole ocean
if I have to
why not don't
don't can dolphins attack you if you
hurt them no
oh God
before
I
didn't even find the egg
in the ocean
ah I I found it somewhere else yeah it
could only be in the ocean that's why
people just say that like I was just too
lucky for finding that me before really
yeah
because I watched the YouTube guide and
it said I have to look in the ocean
[Music]
this is the first time I'm I've been
doing brushing underwater
trying to find the eggs like this
is real Minecraft strategies
[Music]
two places in the goose there's one
motion rooms and some sand things
but it's weird that the egg would be
here because that animal normally it's
not in the ocean
why why would it be here it's so weird
and then
I can't even blink
[Music]
it's all
just normal
man
all the sun Islands think you mean those
eggs are so old
I guess so just really really ancient
egg
good
no ah I found something suspicious but
let me breathe first
[Music]
you you want the doors
oh no no actually the helmet is like
really really okay I have fall on its
own
is this the one that I oversaw before
[Music]
and that's maybe that is too dare when
you guys can see it oh no hold on which
one I don't know guys which one
[Music]
I have no problem I'm just blind
which one
not this one right that one
Kayla do you need glasses
I'm fine but it's just I cannot see the
pattern
why did that break guys
was that suspicious this one okay this
one okay
broke like like glass
oh I'm gonna die
what's this
an ax
I have a feeling there is no eggs we are
finding an ax together I think oh yeah I
was so fun relax
that must have been suspicious
and then which one break like glass
um
no my church say there's like there are
like two ways on I cannot see it I'm
blind mm-hmm
it's very visible what very visible
oh don't let them make you feel bad
about your eyesight Kyla I am just as
bad as you with this
right
this one
okay uh
[Music]
I feel like we looked at everything
oh
guys if you see something let me know
especially standing stock I'm not
looking at that I'm looking at the the
words on the screen
that should be simpler
just gonna get rid of the normal sand
again
genius threats oh God I'm getting so
tired from this
okay nothing
is there any more gamer monitors
are ruins guaranteed to Heaven they're
guaranteed to have the suspicious sand
but I guess not the
not the ink
what am I gonna do for my my scrambled
eggs now guys I guess so while I have to
rely on you guys too bad now hand over
the eggs guys hand them over
the chicken eggs
how is the prison page like how how much
how how is the percentage of finding the
sniffer eight guys I guess no
tell me five no 6.7 6.7 is oh 6.7 is the
same one as the
ruined Trails right
should not be that hard
new fresh egg let's go
drop rate oh yeah drop rate yeah drop
rate that's the word
I'm trying to find the words for that
yeah drop radio
hmm
is that all maybe we have to find a new
one
you sure you check all of this already I
think so
this one done
maybe there's another warm ocean close
by
I'm
in front of your shelter though
no more there are ruins on the beach you
can use those as well really
[\h__\h] ruins on the beach
yeah they can be there too yeah you can
check that one
ouch
it's okay all good
I'll fly to find
[Music]
oh the
beds again
okay which side
I don't know I'm too stupid to fly
Kyla
I forgot how to fly
I forgot
there we go
[Music]
yeah it's really hard to fly
cannot lie
oh wow
I found
corals
printing maybe there is another
um and it's warm it's really warm it's
actually Maldives level warm ocean wow
that's definitely not their Direction
where the beds are oh well
so oh this looks like there could be
another uh Monument here really you've
got another one
I think there could be another one
because this is so big
1992 I am let me just look around then
I explore
um
this is still lukewarm look warm look
warm I'm I'm warm
is that a ship
could it be at the ship too
no I guess not but that's a really
intact ship not this one for sure
[Music]
Atlantis
ocean Monument there
ship will have the trim
I don't need the trim
meet them
hmm
going on an adventure because we're oh
yeah I I think we can take off to go on
an adventure Bingo Square oh yeah yeah
true it's very true for that I think you
know Minecraft is okay
okay maybe there are no there's no
Monument here after all
right
[Music]
it's a really easy to feel I don't know
um
yes barbecue you have to do in real life
this is warm ocean
is there anything in the warm ocean
can we find the warm ocean I only see a
lot of corals yeah right
but originally I thought people said I
have to go to a warm ocean
[Music]
I found
I found another like Temple thingy
Monument thingy Monument
or ocean Monument or what the same thing
that we were looking at before okay okay
sure uh where is uh coordinates
uh 2600 600 uh
uh and 25 200 uh oh you should be here
but I there's monster maybe this one oh
I'm here I'll take care of it
oh uh try then there's a trident
really yeah yeah it's okay I'll take
care of it he's not he's not shooting
okay
all good
oh
good really I don't see you
I'm here now I see you hi let's go let's
try to find it
wow this one is much prettier
horse
outside
fireworks
no stop
okay
suspicious sign will will find it here
we'll find it
yes we will
I cannot go home if I don't find what I
need yeah of course yeah yeah yeah
fresh
fresh for three
also I don't know did you bring your bed
because I'm gonna place my bed here and
then maybe we can sleep I'll just
disconnect it's fine okay you're so fast
do you have like a shortcut for
disconnecting no
no
okay
maybe maybe we should go by a system now
I am gonna observe the one where I have
the bed on top okay
so we don't have to look anymore
afterwards hopefully
no more sense
[Music]
and
light protects damage when swimming oh
wow what really
never heard of that before
Pottery shard
[Music]
I found one suspicious sand
Ed
nah nothing
oh
nope
what is even that thing
gold
hmm
[Music]
what happened that is dying but at least
this one's way closer to the surface so
we can go up quickly
good night good night everybody who's
sleeping
I wanna find it and then I'll go read
super chats but it cannot stop before
you're gonna read superchato too well
and I and I
I don't know how to say a lie in a life
English
like like um
yeah what's the right word for it
cannot see it guys
um there's nothing more right
good girl I don't know that sounds kind
of weird
and I sounds better
and that's an actual adjective
diligent yes diligent I think is the
right word
is diligent I am diligent
Legend
[Music]
the legendary Kyla
The Legend and delicious what
um
just all sounds so similar okay there
was literally only one suspicious sand
on this side what the hell
I am now
going to go away from my bed or I take
my bed
so that I know what I'm doing
I'm going to the middle part okay
[Music]
set suspicious and
oh no
oh
nothing
here's something
Pottery again
[Music]
that was one and I just tried to broke
the I just tried to break the the sweat
grass
to see what's underneath
why why does the the sand act so
suspicious
[Music]
not thing
have you even found a single one since
we came here the suspicious scent
yeah but like trash trash trash trash
trash
[Music]
and you know all those books well you
know you're just joking all of the all
of the ones I broke by accident have
eggs in them
probably
so okay you are looking very suspicious
oh that is not good
this one how about this one
we'll see this one
[Music]
all right more trash
who put so much trash into the ocean
magic and inside the center
like why it's blurry yeah
I won't get any suspicious Sun here
no
hmm
[Music]
species oh I mean okay I can actually
see the difference now okay I'll try to
go like this
[Music]
in the future it's just like a little
bit darker
Pottery shard
wait there is no single Sun here I had
no singles there's one two there's one
two right yeah okay I've got an iPhone
okay
[Music]
I can see it now
nice
[Music]
yeah I just like one time you have to
look at it and then
see it clearly
you can what's the difference eh oh look
closely guys
it's sand but like a little bit darker
than the others
I can now confidently and quickly go
through all the sand there's nothing
here really
not single of it
and I'll just leave the bird there
how about this one this one is done
right you didn't find a single one where
you left the door
yeah I'll find it
this is where I already went yeah maybe
maybe you already probably because it
looks like I already dug a little bit
around there
okay I shall try
over here it's not even a ruin a lot I
don't know maybe
this is also already touched we need a
system Kyla to check which one we
already checked
like putting putting a stone on top or
so oh you want to put a
okay
um I'll just put on yes okay
torch on the roof that works too you
know I think this one's yeah chocolate
I'll put torch okay
this one's kind of checked too I think
how about this one
see yeah that one looks amazing oh this
one is suspicious
nanny
[Music]
oh I found myself I think that's one
really you you can't
um brush normal sand anyway right so you
can also do a test with your brush
I guess
but it's gonna take time
oh this is a species
nope no eggs
no eggs no eggs
it's worth removing some of the
some of the blocks to see what's
underneath oh I'm around
I can see it yeah I have a third eye now
[Music]
nope nope it's fine it's fine
um I need the brush I think this one's
done
Place me well maybe under the portal
[Music]
okay this one is
me
I'm gonna check
um
I feel like this one's already empty now
sure
I'll do a double check we don't need to
double take down another layer no double
check double check
especially now that I have my third eye
wait this one has less like different
color but maybe it's just it's the same
color but just darker
it's like in the middle a little bit
darker
where's your Minecraft third eye come on
wait wait wait this one is feels like
it's different color but actually it's
sand
in
maybe I'm just I don't know my eyes just
open your bird eye Kyla
you have to first open your mind only
then can you open it
yeah maybe it's because of the Shadow
um
let's blame the Shader okay blame the
cheater
your shoes make it harder or really even
better then
um
okay this is double checked so it gets a
second torch
let me double check this one
and one done that one done
maybe since you checked this one maybe I
can try to fly and try to find another
one yes please do okay
let's go sorry Kyla I'm very unlucky
today otherwise we could already end it
it's my fault Phoenix luck is not
existing today
I mean I think I don't know I should
have
the luck but I don't know where's the
luck
that's why you want to sleep hold on I
want to sleep this is comfy chat is
lucky chat is lucky I'm not feeling kind
of bad no I am so focused on the sand
I'm so sorry guys
question
it's 9 A.M stream still happening of
course because it's already scheduled
guys
I have I have a stream at 9am
that's in in how many hours
sleep in between right yeah awesome
sleep is what a week
no need for Sleep Need for Speed
[Music]
oh wait this one looks did anyone check
this okay let's find another one
there I feel like there's another one in
here and there must be there must be
because I didn't uncover this
if the cut Sandstone goes so deep that
means that down there there could still
be suspicious sand right really
yeah
guys please help me to see the
ruins is this a ruins
this is a monument
oh no another Trident hold on try then
you need to wait go
[Music]
go
I think I found another one here but
it's just one like the only one what's
done
yeah one building okay I just want to
check it oh I found one
see look compare this and this the
amount of dark pixels is more on this
one
[Music]
congratulations
okay amazing
it's the same place as the previous one
right
oh
[Music]
yes once I've opened my third eye it was
only a matter of time
yay
I guess we will fly back to the portal
four minutes right yeah okay
[Music]
okay let me brush brush this first
and what's what do you planned with that
egg by the way uh scrambled eggs okay
nice
what I need two to breathe yeah well
first of all I just want to hatch this
one okay and then we can talk about
finding another eggs maybe if I'm really
bored on my private time I can try to
find more I feel like here we're done
there's no way they have a second egg
in the same ruin I feel like you have to
be
they're extremely lucky
okay
should be nothing
unless we do I don't even know which one
was it
even ruined
[Music]
and look a little bit closer on this one
I think it was this one
[Music]
oh wait you have you have a sniffer
right uh
uh I
I give that to me Couture
hey
[Music]
that's okay I guess you didn't need it
for yourself
hey it's slime
[Music]
I can can I not secretly breed with
someone else's sniffer
without them knowing
just go there I mean I mean you know
what there's a sniffer in the
in front of the portal the the new
server portal
I I think you can just
but then but then I need to get my
sniffer there but I want oh yeah yeah
it's it's different it's different
Surfer yeah yeah it's different surfing
yeah so I I'll just find another egg and
then yeah yeah it'll be fine once I have
dinner and then another egg
[Music]
yes
maybe braided and got multiple yeah I
mean in theory I'm happy with just one
sniffer but I guess two is good for good
measure
uh I mean the ocean is still huge you
can yeah I'm I'm brushing right now but
yeah you're brushing on the one single
uh Monument thingy and there are
actually two
but maybe not
[Music]
I created a door with water
fascinating
I missed one which one
wow
cute wow oh it's that one
nope
[Music]
I think that's all in this place
nope
Emerald gun oh yeah probably ah it's
okay guys so
Sans and
can't really be underneath there
what are we talking about we're talking
about Snappers it's a new Minecraft
animal
ah okay
yeah yeah torch flowers seeds will be
needed if you plan on breeding them
what about what do I need to make it uh
come to life
do I also need a torch flower seed
actually I forgot what was the thing
that makes the egg go hatch
yeah I I yeah I have no idea about that
I just just time because because I am
the Moss block uh like kind of uh makes
it faster
but you can also just place it on normal
anything I guess
okay
where do you plan to put it
yeah I'm at my home oh okay
do you have other coordinates for portal
okay let's go
um coordinates
okay Kayla says
268-24 796.
um which is that west or south or east
or
waste we just need to go to the negative
X
we are facing now
we are facing the
different
okay one I think
okay do you still have enough fireworks
yeah
oh yeah
this is like a big warm ocean
[Music]
yes
would be funny if we are actually
accidentally back at my mess um
could this be
[Music]
oh
we are going back
yay finally
accomplished
[Music]
omelette have you ever had Japanese
omudaisu before yeah
I can make it for you
we sleep
268. I mean you're trying to find a
sniffer a for I don't know how many
hours and then just going to front yeah
[Music]
what's the what's that coordinate
two four seven nine six
[Music]
I wonder maybe maybe I should make a
house for the sniffer out of the Sakura
materials oh yeah maybe I think visually
it doesn't really match so well but I
mean what did I get all those Sakura
materials for
I said I would build something with it
so
[Music]
dead
or YouTube dead
Callie might love some oh the Sakura
stuff
[Music]
I received her I'll find her actual
current home and then I'll place a
sakura tree right at her house
I see there's some fighting going on
there wow yeah Diane Golem is like
protecting the village so well
the egg is safe let's go
wait there's a flying bat here
a flying oh yeah I put that here before
[Music]
sleepy time hi I should give you back
your helmet yeah yeah
[Music]
should love that in three months when
she sees it Edward recently hasn't cut
uh Kelly been playing Minecraft a bit
more often yeah your helmet
thank you it was very helpful
and then we can go back
yeah let's go
[Music]
I hope
I hope I will not be coming back here
so soon
but if I want to I have my ice Road
ready anytime yeah it's close by right
now it feels like very close
thank you for helping me build that
thank you thank you for inviting me I'm
happy
[Music]
maybe next time I play Minecraft again
at the weird hour I will ask you again
sure sure help me sure I'm 24 7.
thank you thank you so much for giving
me a chance to talk with what a mission
pie too
it's it's currently in my my profession
to help
members communicate with Japanese
members happy
[Music]
I hope my never ride will find a good
place with you you're gonna make more
use of it than me
thank you professional wing woman
be like professional wing woman at your
service
that's one service honotoni provides
professional wing woman
you know wingman yeah I'm your wing
woman or a woman
foreign
you're not the only one
it's really great to have someone you
know that well you're extroverted right
you're extrovert right 100 is true fair
yes no not 100
not 100 really no have you ever feel
like
like you don't have any energy to like
go out once in a while
it might be depression what
um I I I I even have like lack of
motivation to like get out of bed or eat
or take a shower you're good you're good
now now you're good
no but okay
[Music]
but I would really like people everybody
thinks I'm an exit wow
which way
which way I don't know uh you're you're
controlling now yeah everybody thinks
I'm an extrovert but not really I don't
know I I actually like when I am in a
situation with people the only reason
why I'm so open is because I hate
awkward situations more than anything
okay so I just always try to fill in the
gaps with conversation you know good
communication but in reality I I crave
silence and uh to be alone
like I that's why I always want to stay
in hotels alone not not share a room
ideally
um and I I like to travel alone too but
with traveling alone I I I'm a little
bit worried that
some some nobody can put sunscreen on my
back
and okay it gets it gets a little bit
boring traveling alone maybe maybe it's
better to travel with someone
um but only one person and then and then
I wish when we spent like four nights or
something somewhere or outside of my
country then I wish we could have
separate rooms because at least at night
got it yeah isn't it like extroverted by
situation and conditioned and if you say
it like that like well I don't want this
yeah
if they want to say they can say I'm an
extrovert but for me like it's not the
situation it's just I adapt to I see
yeah yeah yeah situation when when
because I just I also don't want the
other person to feel awkward or weird so
I try to make it more comfortable for
them you know yeah
wait if I hatch the egg
uh does it just walk somewhere or is it
automatically mine can I is it safe or
should I I should probably put it in a
fence or I think you need to put it like
in your house no because it's gonna walk
around
can you put it on a leash
yeah um I don't know it's kind of big
[Music]
um build a farm for it yeah because I
want it to farm some yeah area I think
maybe you can put it into inside Phoenix
in this fence
it's kind of big though
yeah
but how do you transport one can you put
it on a leash yeah please no boat okay
so maybe I hatch it first here outside
and then I take it somewhere with a
leash when it's hatched but I make a
fence
yes yes
can it go over
double blocks probably not just one
blocks maybe like like this
I wonder because the camel camels can go
up two blocks and even over fences and
everything oh really yeah
because they have long legs
so we cannot put French
no no no for for sniffers it's fun
oh yeah somebody said in the chat and I
think this makes sense introvert doesn't
mean uh that your shy necessary and
this extrovert doesn't necessarily mean
that you're yeah true true I don't know
I think it's just like
the energy that you got when you are
like um
alone
or maybe with others like in groups it's
about like when the time you recharge
your energy because I feel like whenever
I'm in group it feels like
my energy just gone
oh you know what the good thing is that
probably pretty much all of the whole
life members except Bales and only
are like that so you don't have to feel
bad about hey you know what actually
only Senpai is also very introvert
actually
yeah you think she loses energy
sometimes like in terms of interacting
okay I think bales
id id I can tell you who is extroverted
Zeta
yeah yeah
[Music]
I think you know like this is the only
one in ID though with Bales it's like uh
when was this we did some yeah we went
to dinner with this big group
and then you know in situations like
this she will afterwards be like I don't
want to go home yet I'm
and then she will make the other people
stay and go to karaoke or wherever with
her she wants to spend as much time as
possible when she gets lonely very
easily
but sometimes I really appreciate you
have friends like that too even though
like Yeah because sometimes I feel like
yeah maybe it's a good time to like you
know go out with two but well yeah
I try to fill every day with meetings
and collabs because I want the stay to
be meaningful and not a waste of time
yeah but if I if I live in Japan then I
will not fail every day with meetings or
operations yeah don't forget name tag
and I can name the egg too you're not
planning to put like doors eat not yet
not yet okay it's it's so slow anyway it
won't Escape see
it's so slow it's a slow boy
yeah I I don't know did Bae ever say
she's not an extrovert because I I would
say she is like I think out of whole
life English she's the most extrovert
which is
that is the only ones that are also
say to the perfumers that yes is
extrovert yeah
I think you know about that no
no but but actually cool but actually
cool myself also intro
I met her now several times and from
what I how I see her she seems maybe a
little bit shy towards some people
sometimes in the beginning when she
first meets someone she's shy but then
she's very extroverted to me
I think because it's like one on one
or I mean
yeah yeah but no like for example I let
her meet Cali together I brought her to
Cali
and you know she's always so loud and
active
yeah maybe but but what I know and she
took the past it's showing introvert yes
so maybe she's just in the middle I
don't know
um
no she she definitely told me and Zeta
that she's actually introvert not not
because like right now because we're
like close already I mean Kobo also like
very talkative right now but yeah I mean
uh she took the test and she got
introverted so yeah
yeah yeah yeah you guys should
understand why I'm calling the sniffer
that name
name it already can I
[Music]
no I can't well you don't have to wait
with me Kyla I'm just waiting for this
message
it's okay
I'll be just standing here
wait was it 10 minutes without the Moss
or with the Moss maybe I will sleeping
gonna be like speed up the process no no
no
the only thing that speeds it up is a
block of ma there's gonna
wait uh there's not gonna be a creeper
here right if I stand here
maybe there will it's safe right no what
okay fine I I should sit on it for
immersion
you want me to hatch it for real
I'm looking for oh I got most blocks
let me get them all
block
[Music]
and then underneath I get rid of this
from
is this flower pump
is this better now
I'll sit on it too oh sure I'll take a
photo of this
[\h__\h] I'm so
shaders I should turn on my shaders for
pretty photos
[Music]
soon I think tomorrow tomorrow I'm
building the new pc with all my new
things yeah
and then I don't I don't think I'm
playing any games anytime soon that will
actually you know show
the specs you know the not like the what
it can do oh but oh well
yeah looking cute ah do you want to come
inside and stand next to me on on the
sand block
yes
a picture
and I try unless oh
oh look up
oh cute look at us
um
[Music]
maybe like this
hi
wow cute beautiful
[Music]
looking uh to your Reddit yes wow okay
Too Close wait
oh no is it is it is it oh no no no no
something happened though it's cracks
oh my God am I too heavy oh [\h__\h] I'm so
confused
uh
oh my baby
let's go
sniffer tank
[Music]
I believe in you you can do it come on
how long does it take when it uh cracks
once
I don't know another 10 minutes no
hopefully not
done
[Music]
I'll go out first before I cannot go out
when when will the
when will the sniffer and go ahead when
will the sniffer Echo Edge when will the
sniffer ever hatch I want to name it
well
it will find me plenty new things it
will find me plenty new things it will
find me plenty new things
such as some new flowers
okay it really takes a lot of time 20
minutes in total probably
20 minutes without the Moss block I
think oh and half the time with the Moss
block maybe or or was it 10 minutes and
then five minutes or so but is it really
10 minutes before before the crack at 10
minutes with moss in total oh 10 minutes
with the Moss I see
hmm and now it's on the Moss block so
on TM
[Music]
it's almost 10 p.m over here oh my God I
can't believe
I can't believe a Friday showcase oh
yeah I have a member stream tomorrow
guys what should we do for members kaido
what do you do always for member streams
well
if you
if you ask them probably they will tell
you that I'm just scamming in my
membership stream but no I'm coming yeah
[Music]
we just play games we share and we share
a lot of uh stories yeah yeah
we do love free talk free talk ah okay
okay
that's a lie what a lie I guess you you
like a lot of members what they do for
their watches for their member streams
is watch along yeah I know right but but
I don't do that no yeah so yeah a lot of
options are gone for you
I've done like just once
yeah once at least
um
almost
[Music]
more and more one more one more
now go ahead
were you saying something no no no no no
no yeah almost that but before before
that watch along right before that watch
along I prepared for like I don't know I
prepare for
a lot of sleep beforehand
and still almost
fall asleep I was like yawning so much
oh my God
well I do a mix of games
and some games I play solo some games I
play with the viewers and then I
sometimes
uh do some hand cam streams
for members and watch along this movie
watch and Longs but I I think I never do
like so just talking streams uh I have I
I I have a lot of talking streams
with membership yeah no I'm sure they
appreciate that
I hope
I have done it yeah once or twice and
also art stream yeah once or twice
we need Alice live stream they really
want me to live in this on the stream I
think for you like they would just be
happy that you're doing something good
for yourself you know yeah I I got it I
got it yeah
and and you know if you would do a
stream where like you just laugh out
loud
they would also probably love to hear
that yeah stream where you laugh out
loud
I can laugh right now
wait wait it's almost 3 am right now
yeah but nope
are you okay Kyla
but honestly when I when I met you in
real life it didn't feel like you were
not laughing no because because that's
what I um okay that's what I I think
I kind of forgot but actually I
talk about this a silent love thingy
with my fears when I mean whenever we
meet right we when I meet someone I mean
the official is there right so when
there's something funny we just laugh no
one no one is like focusing about hey
you got no sound in your love like
something like that you know because the
vessel is there but when yeah but when
we are streaming right it's gonna be
like why suddenly silent and then why
why you are not laughing and something
like that right so it's like very
obvious and like yeah and people start
to ask but whenever we meet someone like
and it's something funny we just laugh
right so we don't really yeah we don't
really look at like oh this girl is like
got no sound and blah blah blah so yeah
yeah yeah
because official is there we know like
at least we know
I was the first time
[Music]
it's so hairy oh my God and I think it's
gonna go bigger than that I think is it
the baby
baby
it's already sniffing I think but the
area is too small it's like let me sniff
more I want to sniff more
huge thank you the baby fish can I jump
on it and then after no it looks like I
could
[Music]
come to the world
oh my God
it's so cute we should take a picture
together
I'm always pressing the wrong buttons
it's so confusing here there you go
um
wait I go closer again maybe
is there any like sniffers in the real
life though no no no no no this is
completely made up well okay okay
one on one side
sniffer chance
look at the camera
look look here you're not giving the
sniffers like name tag
I already gave it oh
Kyle can you go one step to the side
no yes yes
[Music]
it's really hard to take
yeah
[Music]
okay maybe
um
come on look to the front yes yes
[Music]
um um
it's sniffing my crotch
[Laughter]
don't don't that's embarrassing that's
why I don't like doggos
[Music]
know how to go out
um well well
well well
I was thinking just just quickly place a
block and hope he doesn't follow us
[Music]
okay I guess that works
that's really weird
that's really
yay we didn't I'm happy I wonder how
long it takes until it grows up into a
big sniffer
it looks so weird where are the eyes
here
somehow these things look like the eyes
it looks like a Pac-Man it does look
like Pac-Man from the front
no no it doesn't want to show its face
oh my God it's Pac-Man
40 minutes
I want to see when it happens but you
put the double door oh yeah now we no we
can safely go inside ah smart yeah
the floppy ears oh it's like a like a
dog that hasn't been like brushed or
shaved in years because the the fur
looks like so what's the word
so
um
what is it
Shaggy matte yeah it looks so matte but
I guess it's probably like supposed to
be more like leaves
I guess
cute okay okay
I think we can say goodbye and then we
can split yeah I will go back to the new
server thank you so much thank you too
for everything for helping with
everything you're the best thank you
thank you for inviting me
I will talk to you again for another
Minecraft adventure
sure it's fun thank you
goodbye
adios amiga
okay
it's been fun
oh
I'm going back
wow what a day
yeah [\h__\h]
we're watching fireworks Bingo clear
[Music]
what a nice job
no it's perfect timing I don't even know
how that works but it works
that are absolute impeccable timing
yay we got the Bingo let's go
thank you so much
question pie
no evidence no what do you mean no
evidence the beauty is there
it's a name watching fireworks with
someone what do you mean watching
fireworks with someone I watch the
fireworks with thousands of people
already
it's not even someone
with thousands of people
time to deal with you that's the road
[Music]
okay
okay I will
I will
um read the stupid chat but gonna stay
here hold on
huh
oh
oh it's random because
maybe it's because Watami Senpai and
Luna Hime
[Music]
I see
thank you so much for the help
you know what guys imagine like
imagine like you're just having fun the
whole day
and then coming home and then the
homework is just done by itself
uh
[Music]
but just wait
okay
[Music]
after this I still need to create the
thumbnail and the thumbnail the waiting
room for
morning stream
[Music]
best gold for this is not a gold Sparrow
Kyle is the Gold's Farm
hello why don't you
build a gold Farm no the whole nether is
my gold Farm
the gold Farm
doesn't need me to be like asking here
even better
okay I'm taking back
my items this one this one
[Music]
okay I don't know why this shelter is
still here
[Music]
okay
um
now I need to find a way to
to bring back all of
that thing
wait I'm confused
[Music]
oh this
okay
[Music]
uh
perfect
okay
and then the night right
nether right neither right neither right
is it done
okay um
um
this one is from
chiaras and I
wait
[Music]
um
wait okay
this one is from krsn I
personally
where is the and the engine or the
engineer
okay
this is like too much you know
here are the important to so much
the car
even though
even though it really helps
on the it will really helps the can be
progress
but
you know right that
I will not gonna use
it's too precious
I can't
I'll just put all of those in the temple
later
rhinologists
put it here
[Music]
okay and then
um
Waits only one right now
where's the other oh wow we got 15 let's
go
minus one for
foreign
[Music]
okay
I'm going back and then
I'll be instead of going back no
just AFK the creeper
don't go back we can go back
some other time
thank you
imagine remembering all of this
coordinate guys you know
foreign
that can be a bingo box in itself
isn't that normal no that's not normal
no
someone says you don't have to just fly
land on the scaffolding you want to you
want to look at that I'm bringing 1500
blocks right now with me
thank you
let me get my camera first
even better nice
thank you
nah
dang
always died against
I was tired again
I always died again
hold on
no always died again
okay okay we got it we first try
anyway
I'll be here
for I don't know how many days
the bed is wet it's okay
yeah I I really need to like change the
scaffolding
to water elevator but every single time
I
go here I just forgot
and yeah every single time I reach here
and then I suddenly remember oh yeah I
sure brought the
brother
kelp and Soul Sand but yeah it's too
late
it's not about the time but it's just
like always forgot
this place makes you lose memory kinda
kinda died then lost lose memory
scaffolding
water elevator loose memory
so yeah
you should write a sign as a reminder
yeah I should have tried a sign in
my storage room probably
this place is kinda crazy I know right
yeah maybe maybe it's just the cost of
like
uh
getting
Ned ride you know there must be a prize
there must be a price for anything
so yeah the function is to place one
it's like a creeper for me the Bermuda
Triangle probably
one
conspiration Theory
I will just
RTA
if the Minecraft disconnected please
tell me okay because I'm not even
looking at the screen anymore
let's start from the SV first
um very good knowing you should we put
another scrap from Kiara to the knb
count what
no
uh
it was the first time talking with what
time is Senpai like literally talk you
know I mean I talk with Watami Senpai
and the whole ID cop last year but
I mean more talk
more memories
TT
I know it's I don't know it's like you
know
it's just like
it feels like a dream like talking
directly to your ushi like
I don't know
it's just
surreal I don't know I don't know I
don't know what to say I'm just
speechless
fever dream
well not directly with Kiara's help
um
but we had the
two minutes talking directly
in the
her house
less than two minutes
eh
but I mean okay uh what time is Senpai
English is
kinda good
get some help
shaders on
yeah
it's very good in understanding English
[Music]
she got English song after mm-hmm
oh
interesting
companies
thank you
adult people maybe this luck will help
you and kiwawa find the ache use it
wisely thank you
thank you
hold on
[Music]
he did do it with Kali where she stand
part in it oh
that's super nice
and then hold on
bye
senpai
Senpai oh
Senpai senpai
send bye then bye
and bye
bye and pie
bye
and bye and bye then pie
CES
hmm
bye
[Music]
uh
uh and then where else
I think that's all for the SB
are you ready to be called Kyla Senpai
nah
I will I will definitely just say like
normally San Francisco
and then
[Music]
um
broke everything
[Music]
my favorite jpen ID feature in Minecraft
together I'm in Bliss yay yay
yes yes yes beautiful goddess what
suddenly beautiful God is Kyla might be
invited as a guest for next girl stock
streaming of gear
I know honestly right honestly
I can 100 guarantee you guys that
okay if you
if you realize Kyle is just
the worst small talk
[Music]
Kyle is one of the worst person to talk
about small talk
that's true the second one it's getting
worse if you're talking about like girls
talk
[Music]
I totally
[\h__\h] list
I don't know save me
save me
like
if like they're like some girls in a
room
or maybe in a group talking I can just
like
okay yeah
and then after that suddenly if it
changed to Like Girls Talk already
[Music]
adios
like
oof
talking to all she is surreal and I'm
glad through games and scsb that we can
eat thank you I mean sometimes
you guys talk to me and um
fast move phobia membership stream
e
h
you'll be full silent yeah I'll be full
silent and I don't know like no matter
how hard I try to fit in
it just
feels
I don't know
I don't even know how how to join the
talk
so let's talk do you excellent
typing talk
[Music]
just just type
this time
that's not even talking no
game talk probably I don't know every
single time game talk right
it's gonna be like
it gonna end up
awkward too
because
I cannot control myself and it just end
weird
at the end
fine
um
[Music]
maybe only you who feels it weird
um
I don't know it's just like I've
okay
um
I can say
that I've never tried this before like
talking
uh about games before like um talking
about games to the other whole life
members
um from my
experience like one year more than one
year experience in whole life I've never
tried to like talk about games like in
talking about really only about game
talk
okay disconnected eyes I see it I saw it
okay
um
but
nice
wait
it's really hard to like
get the
Minecraft working while all tabbing
yeah the intense gaming talk right but I
have the experience of
the real game talk with crony ones
and we
went
for
three hours
[Music]
and I think that's the only one
that's the only one
what game are you talking about with her
oh a lot
a lot
I got to see her
stem Library the the uh she showed me
the
steam Library games and then we
just went over it one by one
[Music]
what what
that sounds like it was fun it was fun
it was crazily fun
we talked off stream after the Ralph
collapse and you know the rough collab
is already like
was already like um midnight for her and
then I think we just
went on and on until morning I don't
know
I I asked her several times like is it
okay don't you want to go to sleep and
then like granny like yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah but we keep going on
and on
yeah it's the only one
it's the only one yeah
it's the only one experience hold on I'm
trying to get back to the Minecraft
um
[Music]
foreign
but yeah I mean
it usually right it usually I will not
be the one who start
the game talk at first
because
I got
past life experience about like you know
uh it's kind of hard to
talk with girls
and it just ended up
not good at the end
that's why I say that
usually it will end up like weird
yeah because because I don't know I I I
don't know how far
this person know about games
kinda hard to talk to girls that's kind
of really
yeah the one you scare new friend away
yeah that's why usually
um in collapse
I don't really usually open the topic
because
I don't know
[Music]
I I'm just trying so hard to like
uh follow the topic
but
that time I don't know
how I ended up talking with crony about
games until
three hours I don't know
I think we are talking about something
and then it just starts there
and we still talk like we still yeah I
mean right now we're still tall and
yeah we are already
scheduling the next round
but uh what date it's gonna be
still Secret
we're we're we're gonna continuing the
raw for sure
the color was in the afternoon right
yeah it's afternoon for me
it's not afternoon for her
[Music]
uh
thing is you get crazy competitive with
crony and game of thrill
yeah maybe maybe it's because she's
competitive in games too I know
even in rough you're competitive
[Music]
not intentionally it's just very neutral
like
at first we already like said okay
okay Carla okay crony this is Ralph okay
we we're gonna do like call gaming right
yeah yeah cop okay yeah yeah yeah yeah
you're gonna do this are you gonna do
this okay okay yeah yeah good good good
and then what happened
we start
I don't know let's just
okay
play around with competitive way
uh Zephyr
Kyle and weakness girl talk yeah I know
true
Ella don't die no I will not die die
Buddhist
almost just almost die yeah black knocks
talking so much psychic damage right now
Teddy YouTube music Dream Theater Panic
attack
yeah true panic attack yeah well
actually I know that um
question pie
uh usually got Panic too right
when talking with other people and I
don't know I feel like
I can relate so much about that
I can
I can relate I was super introverted but
this gotten better yeah I know
and
[Music]
I still remember the first time I can
say that it's better for me now because
I feel like when at first right at first
I joined whole life a year ago
I still remember the first time I had my
first collab stream with Ian members
I couldn't even sleep
I couldn't even sleep because
I don't know it's just super scary
but right now even though
I'm still quiet even though I'm still
quiet in like let's say if um it's the
first collab with new person like it's
like totally the
first time I know that I'm still quiet
but
at least it's not that bad anymore
but yeah why would young members be
scary it's not about even Members Only
my first time collabing with my ID
senpai's
it's also like that it's just
it's just I know
it's just I overthink that
what to say what to say what to say what
to say what to say and then I start
panicking
thank you
he had anxiety
nervous no I I don't think it's I don't
think it's on I don't think it's only
the nervous I think it's already become
anxiety
at this rate
and
I think it's better now I think it's
better now and
okay
[Music]
um
good to hear yeah
foreign
here before a year ago I still remember
uh
I already start panicking the anxiety
level is just like maximum and then
whenever I read the chat people gonna be
like Kyla where is silent Kyla talk Kyla
kinda say something Kyla don't just be
quiet and then like I don't know it's
just like
can I disappear you know
but right now
but right now Pamela is just like
laughing
whenever I whenever I uh whenever
whenever I look at the chat you guys
just laugh
you guys just um
yes and yes and
and then uh
everything's fine
and then just laugh just and then like
uh
yeah so
so I mean thank you so much for
helping
to calm me down a bit
yeah
because
because sometimes
okay we are not talking about
um
I mean I mean right now I'm right now
I'm learning like um some vocabulary of
nihongo right so like the simple simple
one I already kind of get it but
whenever I panic it's just like poof you
know like when you panic about something
it's just like gone everything you learn
everything you study it's just gone
it's not it it's not about nihongo only
it's also the same thing with
English
yeah
so
I realized the moment when I collapsed
the first time with um gurus and pie
whenever I look at that Fury again I
feel like
I just blank out a lot of time
if I watched that Fury I was like
you blank out like a lot of time you
know like whenever Senpai talk about
something and then I just like flying
out blank out black out is this because
I panic it's just because I don't know
yeah but right now
whether when I feel like I calm myself
a bit
um
I I feel like I can understand more
yeah yeah yeah yeah
I thought you were cold but you just
bring out no I I I I didn't think that
I'm cool I didn't think that I was cold
no I just blank on I just panicked so
much
[Music]
yeah so you're cute right no
I'm just
dumb
[Music]
Panic blank yeah I just need to like you
know
calm down calm down calm down
the one with uh
kiers and Pages now
I can say that
it's far better already
from last year like
all of the collab with the
Ian senpai's like I mean
uh I mean
I got all of
uh the English yeah
um
you just blank a little bit at the start
yeah yeah it's gonna be like always like
that because
it's really hard like guys I'm
I am
more than 95 introverted
in my
mbti test
so
I need some time to warm up myself
yeah
more than 95 Grand 400 I should
[Music]
and the collab with
uh
uh I don't know but personally
personally I personally
I still want to develop the
what is that the bigger group collab
yeah I'm still learning that one but I
feel like
it's okay Kyla you don't need to
push yourself
the right now I can say the 1v1 is
kinda okay already
but for the bigger collab
uh
I still need to learn
yeah I really need I still really need
to learn like when I should talk when I
should when I shouldn't talk
um
[Music]
foreign
uh
[Music]
we prefer
solo stream
um
if you ask me personally
I mean I'm still prefer
solo stream like
um
I don't know I'm I'm just very talkative
in my solo stream like on my soul stream
and just very talkative
but in the collab stream
I don't know it's it's not about like
I'm not interested in collab no it's not
I don't want people to get that kind of
feelings but it's just like it's hard to
talk
it's it's just so it's it's hard to talk
with people
it's scary to talk with people
um
foreign
[Music]
Journey
luini
Iris senpai
sama
crony
yeah
dc2
yang
[Music]
um
guiding
uh
uh even though
other language barriers
foreign
[Music]
wadoof
experiences
foreign
guys
[Music]
panla
The Rose
um Adventure
Olive Adventures
uh
gaming stream glute
us
[Music]
OverWatch
OverWatch uh
uh
collab building building
stream collab
Focus
yeah
foreign
totally
but I don't know maybe if it's like off
collab maybe it's gonna be better
I don't know I don't know because if
like off collab I mean I can see the
face and I know that if if if they want
to talk
so probably because because I'm just
like you know I overthink it like
is it the right time to talk
uh can I talk right now or maybe maybe I
should maybe I just maybe I just need to
be like silent right now or maybe maybe
this is okay is it is it is it the right
time for me to talk right now so yeah
it's like
I don't know
but I don't know
it's just scary
and if of call up we can use uh you know
uh body language hand language
[Music]
Maria
h
uh
live stream yeah
[Music]
well guys
I'm very talkative like if it's like off
stream one-on-one
[Music]
gito
today
yeah
Frito
[Music]
among um
yeah
Javier
is
[Music]
oh
ah yeah
Young
Guinea
other day
one honey
deep talk
are they with a small balloon
[Music]
with Ella nice
I don't know I really need to like
increase my small talk
periods
I mean sometimes I really feel bad like
you know it's really it's really nice to
have someone to keep going on with the
keep coming up with the topics but
sometimes
I'm just like feel kind of bad like
I just feel bad I just feel bad like
if only I
can
open the topic like
not gonna be like a one-way one
but yeah
I'm trying
yeah yeah yeah it feels like I want to
contribute
more to the conversation but
yeah sometimes it's just sometimes
I just feel bad yeah
true I can't really it feels like we
don't want to be there even though we
are enjoying yeah
we have great times but
we want to like contribute more
yes socializing is hard I know
socializing is hard
and
we intro
foreign
yeah
nice try through something nice
love that change in the thumbnail
there is like sequels in the thumbnails
something I think it is enough to have
fun even if no one talks after all fun
is independent yeah yeah sometimes I
think it that way but
I don't know sometimes I feel like that
air is fine that's what uh okay
um
personally
for example right if you're talking
about
silent collab silent collab usually
happen when I collab with Muna senpai
but I can still say that it's fun
because personally
I and Muna Senpai is kind of like the
same type
of Person of like streaming way you know
yeah we sometimes just like being silent
even though it's like um
the solo stream one right yeah so when
we are focused about something we just
like silent and the Furious is also fine
too with that kind of stream but I got
it like when
um
yeah I mean different different members
different viewers too but yeah like
if
if like me and when I send Thai collab
usually it's gonna be like a lot of that
air but you know both sides the fears
are just totally fine with it yeah
but I mean if let's say
um me and
okay let's say uh Kiara Senpai sphere
right here isn't High sphere probably is
not get used to of like
uh silent silently like that silence
right so so it's like sometimes I I feel
like okay Kylie you cannot be silent you
need to like talk you need to start
talking about something and yeah
yeah something like that
yeah but it's it's a great experience
like there is nothing wrong about this
and that it's just like um I don't know
it's something like
we just need to adapt I think Hmm
LOL Cafe is used to never-ending tangent
talk yeah
I really I really respect I really
appreciate uh people that can like
always coming up with topics after
topics of the topics of the topics after
topics yeah
um
not even I think they think you're
silent is because you're laughing
[Music]
yeah probably actually right if you
realize
on my even on my solo stream probably
you feel like oh Kyla is actually more
talkative when she's doing the solo
stream but actually it's not you know
all of the topics usually coming from
the viewers
it's like that's why I always read the
chat right because whenever I feel like
okay let's find the topics and then like
yeah you guys are
like a great topic Finders
yeah
morning stream will be at night morning
true I'm not changing that because
there's already scheduled already
yeah but I mean
I don't know
um
Colette
collab
collab means that
we decrease
the level of like reading the chat and I
don't know
usually collab chat just enjoying the
collapse so it's not like Chad gonna
help me with the topics too and it's
fine
and
yeah true true it seems almost rude to
be reading each other a lot well for
laughing yeah
so maybe right maybe even doing on my
soul stream probably I'm also will not
be talkative
if the topic is not coming from you guys
I've I know that I realized that because
when the chat dies
I don't know what to say anymore
like I just gonna say like
it's a chat died
and then after you guys come back
the topic just
go again so yeah
yeah minus one topic exactly exactly
yeah
time to make some noises yeah exactly
but yeah I mean I've been in college
right on column stream I cannot do that
like
oh no the group is like not talking
let's just
not working like that
cool thank you
I know that I'm cool thank you
uh Zephyr minus 25 HP Panic minus 15 HP
how
how much HP that I have
by the way the music conversation
started random
these are all these two random noises
even in collab maybe it works right but
I don't know
like I got a lot of I learned a lot of
things actually from collab
um
some people
just laugh
when they got nothing to say
and then what I learned from here Senpai
is also was also uh she said that uh
she just love
screaming
if there is nothing to do
so probably I need to find my own
thing
right
yeah like um
fauna Senpai say just oh
when got nothing to say just oh like
that right I'm learning I'm learning I'm
I'm learning from the master
yeah right
I don't know I think I need to find my
own
and we do enjoy it for summer
you do gorilla noises what do you mean I
mean
who how works too
you should start as KJ I think yeah
got nothing to say and then
what
um but
Lima
but Lima
actually done oh really that's not a
great idea
I wish I knew what this chant means oh
someday you will know
someday someday all of you
gonna know exactly what it is
I promise
someday
yeah
it's Sunday
I can't always think
I don't know if I'm ready for that day
why
wait faster
but yeah I just want to say like thank
you so much for
all of this journey
uh
I've come so far you guys also come so
far thank you so much for understanding
thank you so much for like you know um
thank you so much for just being very
understanding like along the way
we learn
each other
and yeah
yeah right now
I'm not
uh right now if I need something to read
to call myself I can just read the chat
because
a year ago whenever I read the chat it's
like
make me more panic
right now
it's just amazing
understanding yeah
now we're painting nice
very nice
it is
hello
yeah
uh
Kayla is panicking
yesen
yeah
yeah right now we we still chill already
foreign
[Music]
wow
we love because you damn yeah and then I
I will just laugh because I know that
I'm dumb too yeah
[Music]
pickup is scary
yeah uh because
okay uh I mean probably it's just
because on stream too right because it's
not only like about me and the person
that I talk to because yeah it's like
thousands of people so it's like
scary
and because I mean I feel like if it's
like personal talk off stream one-on-one
I I don't feel like
I got issue of talking like speaking up
about what I thought
I could only be here for part of the
last stream
but you should know dolphins are evil
don't let them deceive you the dolphin
again
the dolphin in Minecraft will not hurt
us though
and
[Music]
John Ryan oh my God Kyle likes krx what
time my three voices that I love to hear
in one stream a trip before the war to
come before the storm of fighting me
let's go good luck Good Luck Good Luck
Good Luck for your test Jonathan Ryan
um
yeah remember that our dolphin is evil
I mean
if I haven't seen
how evil the Dolphins can be
probably
I will stick
to what I believe
all of my life
[Music]
hmm
but they are
nah not until I've seen it with my own
eyes
all the shift I did
fix one Ice Mountain gonna be gone today
nice
I see the truth now that hard lies
leading because of climate change those
ice caps didn't stand a chance
uh
so where is the closest dolphin tour we
can send Ella to I've been there once
I've been I've been to the Gold Coast
before and then I touched the dolphin
the Dolphins are nice to me and they
seems nice
and the Dolphins the dolphins that I saw
is not like the
being in the Captivity one it's like
they're coming from the ocean one
they're like going back to the ocean one
and
it looks nice
they they just look nice
that's how they catch you
[Music]
they look nice I mean I gave them food
I I fit them I fed them
I touch them touchy touchy
and yeah
they're nice to Human
well I mean I'm a human so
it's not wrong but I say they are nice
what did you feed them fish
have you ever considered touching a
shark before what
gura
biologist oh sweet Savage
dolphins are smart enough to do crimes
in the ocean you know but okay
um the reason why I love dolphins are
actually they're smart at least I'm not
wrong about that right
they're not dumb right
[Music]
well
yeah
yeah not wrong right
okay
dolphy are the second smartest animal
after human well
thank you so much for the membership
gifts thank you
they have better IQ than us human
probably maybe not better than human but
maybe better than me probably yeah
[Music]
the smartest the animals are orca orca I
know I know Orca I know orcas
uh
uh they look cool
but they're deadly I know
we're not talking about the orcasian
pirate but yeah
um
[Music]
mystery skit it's so ice to see you
streaming such a cool stream hopefully
these jokes don't get a cold shoulder I
just
know they're bad no no no they're
they're not bad I got it I got the jokes
thank you
wholesome and PR guy wholesome NTR guy
she lied As Natural as he breathed which
one
which one
Andrew get somehow thank you Reynolds
after give Kyler realized so that's how
it feels yeah like why why so much land
right
why
why so much natural
I know
Maria thank you so much
Momo Berry we saved her in return we get
to keep our luck right now
no but thank you so much for saving me
yeah
suspicious not my sense again
suspicious and
stay cool thank you thank you so much
for the membership gifts Grim chalk
pollen and Indonesia is somehow related
because our flags are the same but
upside down the mall have a fun time
with Kiara
thank you and yeah
Paula and Lisa um I don't know in Poland
right I don't know if there is still a
Poland Bros in my live chat right now
but
um I don't know pollen if they have like
um
um ceremony
in school
um weekly ceremony flag ceremony in
school
um
when you are like uh what is that
obviously
what is in English
English English
the flag oh yeah yeah uh the flex
ceremony is like um for the students to
like uh racing the flag
and then
yeah uh there are a lot of times that
the students or the one that the
students that
um
responsible they are responsible to
raise the flag usually
you know
a lot of time they got it upside down
yeah salute to the flag yeah
and it's just like becoming a pollen
flag
and then
yeah
mm-hmm
yeah it is
[Music]
foreign
nice
[Music]
I know that I'm blind thank you
Jason McLean eye surgery fun even better
thick good morning and good morning
hello
um
CC there Kyle update your amphibian
drivers OMG one you're uh talking about
the GPU 100 is it
and then
what suddenly
took the one thing
and vegetables
[Music]
Mixie
James
Magdalene is
dream for me
I don't know I don't know but you know
what the reason why vitamins and Pie is
like
one of my top options is just because
it's very calmary the reason but it's
very calm but
um sometimes she can be very random too
and I don't know I I can relate so much
with her
like yeah and then and then I really
like the
the shorts the the short video
that she made
wow like
it's just mind blown like
I just loved all of the idea like
it's
it's just like
[Music]
perfect
no it's just like
perfect just perfect what time you did
nothing wrong
[Music]
what time we have a nice day like the
contents are very random but
it's just
funny at the same time and I just can
relate
to her content so much
and yeah
hmm
did they ever Inspire some of your own
random Shores uh not really but I I do
realize that I really enjoy
a lot
yeah because because my my what my if
we're talking about the inspiration of
my shirts is basically it's just like
random thoughts like random is very
random like before I sleep and then like
hey why why not do this hey why not do
that and then like
um it's just like whenever I'm having
dinner and then
um
are like talking
in dinner time and then like suddenly
out of nowhere I just think about
something and then like yeah why not do
that why not do this it's just like very
random idea but yeah
[Music]
the bad internet
the never uh what time is senpai
did nothing wrong right yeah I did
nothing wrong right um
yeah if making sure as simple as making
Twitter with making sure in every hour
[Music]
but yeah
that's also the reason why I really love
uh sumugi from Kion
because sumu is the type of girl that
you know um
chill calm kinda quiet but is this super
random and weird
so it's just like yeah yeah yeah yeah
it's like
it's like that right yeah yeah yeah
weird yeah
yeah I really I really really
to girls like Dad
so much
because eyebrows we're not talking about
the pickle eyebrows
pickle eyebrow right yeah we can oh no
we can
pick the eyebrows and make it into
pickles right no don't say that no no no
no no no
[Music]
no
and then
what else what else what else
are you happy to join whole life Ella is
that even the question mom will Berry
thank you
[Music]
I know I mean
I cannot see myself
[Music]
happier than
I'm in whole life right now
yeah
um
she was the best thing ever
you the Mandalay thank you
and by the way thank you so much at
least now I know like from the Native
how to say the demand
yeah very nice Yama but it's funny how
you are in trophy with people but with
us you're just the definition of
Randomness I don't know it's weird right
but yeah
cool thank you I feel all this I
struggle to talk to people or keep
conversation going because I don't know
what to say most of the time our lives
don't match
I don't know sometimes it just feels
like better to like listen to others
talk but
in collab
it doesn't work that way I know so yeah
glad to hear that what
huh glad to hear that
what did I just say Naga thank you
what glad to hear that
[Music]
happy now all happy now oh
vacuum Lafayette
[Music]
's dolphins are smart but don't have any
moral scrapples much like gyms at least
Dolphins don't wage traveled Gangnam
Style Wars on or their arms off gyms do
that
well
uh
obviously
thank you enjoy your food put JC thank
you so much for the 69 yeah orcas are
kind of scary recently in some party
party some parts they've started
attacking boats breaking their routers
and ramming them really they start to
attacking humans too
really
oh
[Music]
um
this is a certain part though
4K Bingo 22 0 8 20 23 as of current
progress six at three six four two A.D
not 61 69 969 yeah nice very nice very
good thank you
[Music]
um
I came here to nap at you have to head
out thanks for the streams and all the
hardware you put in for us Ella much
love
thank you so much but whenever I read
love how I I will give you get some help
[Music]
thank you buddy thank you so much I also
gonna end the stream like real soon but
yeah
and
um
[Music]
foreign
not really
is kind of
bigger the meat
is huh
foreign
[Music]
hold on
wait
sudden collab schedule
uh
[Music]
I mean if if someone asked me to do
color by just YOLO
okay
if no meeting just okay okay okay okay
schedule
today
indeed
I just saw
[Music]
I think that's all for now I gonna
upload a new waiting room
real soon
so it's like
Kyla's stream will never end actually
right
uh
[Music]
9 30 okay 9 30 because uh I don't know
about the breakfast since this is
already like this hour probably
I will try to I don't know if Mama
already wake up or not but I will I need
to like talk to her about the breakfast
too yeah
yeah 9 30.
[Music]
um
uh 120 the breed and then
Adventure
with
Chiara
full
plus collab Adventure
the title is too long
cannot
okay
that's nice
are you going to subtract the money
you'll give to Sion
what do you mean subtract the month
subject the amount of the total uh
debris and debris another that I have
right now
36 versions ah
foreign
the title is only the one that uh it's
like the recap of how many debris that I
got in one stream so it's like
for my database
yeah
if you want to subtract that yeah just
subtract that yeah yeah
it's like my own database like how how
many debris and uh
how many hours how many debris that I
can get in one stream
so yeah that's okay
[Music]
schedule
foreign
still you know even even
um after like the nine months the first
nine months after I debuted still I can
I can still read it somewhere like
now the schedule is like just daily one
the schedule is like at the end of the
Stream
schedule schedule member line even
better nice super nice
yeah I mean right now I can tell you
like yeah the morning is gonna be like
at nine
the last time I made schedule
easy just broke
gone adios
hmm
by again schedule oh yeah the last
schedule I even made the
sleep schedule
hmm
at this point it'll be more helpful to
make a schedule for when you're not
streaming that I mean was even better
nice
my schedule is Monday streaming
there's a stream Tuesday there is a
stream Wednesday There's a stream
probably next one the probably next time
next time if I meet schedule right if I
make schedule next time I'll just like
uh
Monday two streams three streams
streams Wednesday
one stream
Thursday
imagine not streaming for this scary
yes scary this week 20 strips even
better
yes
what schedule
imagine how many debris that you can get
using the time that you make that
schedule
if making schedule like two hours
because you need to think right two
hours okay okay don't say it two hours
then one hour in an hour
imagine how many debris that you can get
one stack
no 50 okay
thank you
[Music]
okay okay I end the stream right now
okay
uh next stream gonna be
in less than five hours
I'll be back
okay
in less than five hours
I will have class in the evening right
I have class at five
if I start at 10 there's gonna be only
seven hours will I have enough time for
seven hours I don't know foreign
okay
five hours enough probably already
I don't know
[Music]
um
will Sila we'll see okay I will I will
make the thumbnail first
I will make the thumbnail first and
we'll see
if I can do it at 10 at 10 la
foreign
let's go
thank you so much for now
uh you go sleep guys if you wanna sleep
if you're working right now enjoy your
work good luck okay good luck and by the
way it's Cara Senpai still here oh
just
okay
even better
here I left the service is still
streaming ah wait uh
this is GMT plus two right
GMT plus two
well it's midnight there it's almost 12
two there I think right
[Music]
I don't know if I can read TR wait let
me see
read direct
um
okay
but I don't know if the rate is actually
effective because
I don't know bringing
bringing you guys there
uh
uh I don't know if it's effective right
yeah you you guys just tired right but
it's okay
just
behave
okay yeah behave
imagine bring sleepy people yeah I don't
know what you guys gonna do but please
behave
I know I know pamalo is already like all
female already but please behave okay
don't type anything yeah bye
sleepy like
and
sending zombie are
really people with silly people
it's okay
thank you so much for now
we'll just say sleepy sleepy penguin
ring
if you see sleepy penguin red then
here's senpai's fear gonna be like
thinking that
I'm the penguin hey you guys cannot scam
people I know that you guys are penguin
but not me hello then uh as always has
been fun cool and happy wait it's
English fashion right now nice
thank you
it is is it called bellock if you read
yes and Yama bro The Mandalay thank you
so much for now I will I'll be seeing
you real soon and please do rest this
did all of you gonna be moving to Kira
Senpai stream and
uh behave adios
foreign
[Music]
you'll be good okay
I know that you want to sleep but you
cannot sleep
I need to ask gay
be nice
get some help
[Music]
ing if you need help of course be
sitting blinking so much
in RGB
does it count