​​​ ​It's so hard to resist​ ​​
​​ ​the tempting smells​ ​​
​​ ​of the food stalls!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's eat over there.​ ​​
​​​ ​It looks less crowded.​ ​​
​​​ ​(munch)​ ​​
​​​ ​Mmm!​ ​​
​​​ ​So good!​ ​​
​​​ ​There's nothing like​ ​​
​​ ​eating good food​ ​​
​​ ​under the open sky!​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you want one, too?​ ​​
​​​ ​Here you...​ ​​
​​​ ​Not!​ ​​
​​​ ​Just kidding! Here.​ ​​
​​​ ​Open wide!​ ​​
​​​ ​Good, right? Hee-hee!​ ​​
​​​ ​I've always​ ​​
​​ ​loved your smile.​ ​​
​​​ ​So keep smiling​ ​​
​​ ​by my side, okay?​ ​​
​​​ ​Phew. We visited​ ​​
​​ ​a lot of stalls.​ ​​
​​​ ​We ate lots of food, too.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yakisoba,​ ​​
​​​ ​candy apples,​ ​​
​​​ ​chocolate-covered​ ​​
​​ ​bananas...​ ​​
​​​ ​They were all​ ​​
​​ ​so delicious.​ ​​
​​​ ​After we rest for a bit,​ ​​
​​​ ​wanna check out some​ ​​
​​ ​of the game stalls?​ ​​
​​​ ​Like the shooting​ ​​
​​ ​game, or the ring toss!​ ​​
​​​ ​...Hm?​ ​​
​​​ ​What is it?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's almost time?​ ​​
​​​ ​For what?​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoa!​ ​​
​​​ ​So beautiful!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, let's find​ ​​
​​ ​somewhere where we​ ​​
​​ ​can get a better view!​ ​​
​​​ ​Phew...​ ​​
​​​ ​What a nice breeze.​ ​​
​​​ ​Perfect for relaxing​ ​​
​​ ​in the evening​ ​​
​​ ​cool after a bath.​ ​​
​​​ ​In summer​ ​​
​​​ ​there are lots of lively​ ​​
​​ ​and exciting things,​ ​​
​​​ ​but I also love​ ​​
​​​ ​quiet moments like this.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hm? What's the matter?​ ​​
​​​ ​What do you mean,​ ​​
​​ ​I look alluring​ ​​
​​ ​in my yukata?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Where did that come​ ​​
​​ ​from all of a sudden?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gosh,​ ​​
​​ ​now I'm flustered...​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, th-that's right!​ ​​
​​​ ​We have watermelon!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll go​ ​​
​​ ​cut us some slices!​ ​​
​​​ ​Mm!​ ​​
​​ ​So delectably sweet!​ ​​
​​​ ​Candy apples are a​ ​​
​​ ​little hard to eat, though.​ ​​
​​​ ​Gotta take care​ ​​
​​ ​not to drop it...​ ​​
​​​ ​Hm?​ ​​
​​​ ​My, why are you​ ​​
​​ ​staring at me like that?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hee-hee.​ ​​
​​​ ​Is it because​ ​​
​​ ​you want a taste?​ ​​
​​​ ​Really?​ ​​
​​​ ​Gosh, I've already​ ​​
​​ ​started eating it, though.​ ​​
​​​ ​But if you don't​ ​​
​​ ​mind that, then sure.​ ​​
​​​ ​Open your mouth.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahh...​ ​​
​​​ ​Mm!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hee-hee!​ ​​
​​​ ​Too bad! None for you!​ ​​
​​​ ​Besides, wouldn't​ ​​
​​ ​you like something​ ​​
​​ ​even sweeter?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hee-hee!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're blushing​ ​​
​​ ​from head to toe!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm back!​ ​​
​​​ ​Look! I got some​ ​​
​​ ​takoyaki from that​ ​​
​​ ​stall over there!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gotta be careful,​ ​​
​​ ​since it's still hot.​ ​​
​​​ ​So, I'll blow...​ ​​
​​​ ​Fuu, fuu...​ ​​
​​​ ​Till it's cool, just cool,​ ​​
​​ ​then into the mouth.​ ​​
​​​ ​Nice.​ ​​
​​​ ​You want one too?​ ​​
​​ ​Here you go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Blow on it first, okay?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah! Just like that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Till it's cool, just cool...​ ​​
​​​ ​Nice.​ ​​
​​​ ​Man, the stalls​ ​​
​​ ​are so fun!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey! That one​ ​​
​​ ​looks like it's got​ ​​
​​ ​some good stuff too!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go check it out!​ ​​
​​​ ​I picked a yukata​ ​​
​​ ​I thought you would like.​ ​​
​​​ ​What do you think?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's lovely?​ ​​
​​​ ​Gosh. Heh-heh.​ ​​
​​​ ​I see.​ ​​
​​​ ​So I look good in it?​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoa!​ ​​
​​​ ​The fireworks​ ​​
​​ ​are beautiful!​ ​​
​​​ ​Such lovely fireworks.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey...​ ​​
​​​ ​You said I looked​ ​​
​​ ​lovely just now.​ ​​
​​​ ​Between the​ ​​
​​ ​fireworks and me,​ ​​
​​​ ​which is lovelier?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hee-hee. Oh, I know!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll always be​ ​​
​​ ​number one to you.​ ​​
​​​ ​And you'll always be​ ​​
​​ ​my number one, too!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gotta say, pretty nice​ ​​
​​ ​fireworks up there.​ ​​
​​​ ​But they're​ ​​
​​ ​also pretty loud.​ ​​
​​​ ​At least I'm not​ ​​
​​ ​gonna nod off​ ​​
​​ ​with this much noise.​ ​​
​​​ ​You know, it would​ ​​
​​ ​take someone​ ​​
​​ ​really shameless​ ​​
​​​ ​to fall asleep,​ ​​
​​ ​right here...​ ​​
​​​ ​right now...​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh?!​ ​​
​​​ ​No, I wasn't sleeping!​ ​​
​​​ ​Nonono, I'm awake, I'm​ ​​
​​ ​awake! It's fine! I'm fine,​ ​​
​​ ​I'm fine... I'm... fine...​ ​​
​​​ ​Ow!​ ​​
​​​ ​Who the heck is playing​ ​​
​​ ​with a beach ball here?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Who hit me?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gotcha!​ ​​
​​​ ​There!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hi-yah-yah-yah-yah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Phew. I'm getting​ ​​
​​ ​a bit tired.​ ​​
​​​ ​What? I'm over-excited?​ ​​
​​​ ​I guess my inner​ ​​
​​ ​kid came out...​ ​​
​​​ ​But hey, we're​ ​​
​​ ​at a festival!​ ​​
​​​ ​What better place to​ ​​
​​ ​let loose and have fun?​ ​​
​​​ ​On that note, we're​ ​​
​​ ​not leaving till we've​ ​​
​​ ​eaten at every stall!​ ​​
​​​ ​Anyway, we can cool​ ​​
​​ ​down a bit with this.​ ​​
​​​ ​This isn't that tiring!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's basically the​ ​​
​​ ​same as a break!​ ​​
​​​ ​And of course,​ ​​
​​ ​we're aiming for the​ ​​
​​ ​biggest prize, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hiii, everyone!​ ​​
​​ ​Guess where I am!​ ​​
​​​ ​Look! Look​ ​​
​​ ​what I'm wearing!​ ​​
​​​ ​That should be a hint.​ ​​
​​​ ​Did you guess?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm in Japan!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hehe, my outfit​ ​​
​​ ​is cute, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​I just wanted to​ ​​
​​ ​show you before I leave!​ ​​
​​​ ​We're about to​ ​​
​​ ​go to a festival!​ ​​
​​​ ​Look, I even​ ​​
​​ ​have a cute bag!​ ​​
​​​ ​And the yukata​ ​​
​​ ​has flowers on it…​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't believe it!​ ​​
​​ ​I'm in Japan!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yippee!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Heh-heh.​ ​​
​​​ ​These sparklers​ ​​
​​ ​are so pretty.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wanna bet on​ ​​
​​ ​whose lasts longer?​ ​​
​​​ ​All right! I'm gonna win!​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on...​ ​​
​​​ ​Wah! Oh, no!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey! Hey! Drop yours​ ​​
​​ ​already! C'mon!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahh! How come?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Aw, no fair!​ ​​
​​​ ​That doesn't​ ​​
​​ ​count! One more!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah! I finally found​ ​​
​​ ​you, dear human!​ ​​
​​​ ​You must hurry!​ ​​
​​​ ​The fireworks​ ​​
​​ ​will start soon!​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh? You think​ ​​
​​ ​my yukata is cute?​ ​​
​​​ ​Heh-heh...​ ​​
​​ ​You think so?​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait!​ ​​
​​​ ​Now is not​ ​​
​​ ​the time for this!​ ​​
​​​ ​We must make haste!​ ​​
​​​ ​I will let you have​ ​​
​​ ​a good look later.​ ​​
​​​ ​For now, let us​ ​​
​​ ​enjoy the fireworks.​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on, let's go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hee-hee-hee, I had​ ​​
​​ ​so much fun today!​ ​​
​​​ ​The Ramune we drank​ ​​
​​ ​together was so tasty,​ ​​
​​​ ​and the fireworks​ ​​
​​ ​were really pretty!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, no! The strap​ ​​
​​ ​on my geta snapped!​ ​​
​​​ ​Am I hurt? No, I'm fine.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm... But how​ ​​
​​ ​am I gonna walk​ ​​
​​ ​home like this?​ ​​
​​​ ​I didn't bring extra​ ​​
​​ ​footwear or anything...​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, hey!​ ​​
​​ ​How about you give​ ​​
​​ ​me a piggy-back ride?​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh! You can carry me​ ​​
​​ ​in your arms, too!​ ​​
​​​ ​Take me home like this! ♪​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh?​ ​​
​​​ ​How peculiar, I daresay.​ ​​
​​​ ​I really did find​ ​​
​​ ​a tasty-looking​ ​​
​​​ ​shaved ice stall,​ ​​
​​ ​I daresay!​ ​​
​​​ ​And I daresay​ ​​
​​ ​I'd already decided​ ​​
​​​ ​on Blue Hawaii flavor!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm...​ ​​
​​​ ​Where did that stall go?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm?​ ​​
​​​ ​I daresay I sense shaved​ ​​
​​ ​ice in that direction.​ ​​
​​​ ​This time,​ ​​
​​ ​I've got it for sure!​ ​​
​​​ ​I daresay, it must​ ​​
​​ ​be over there!​ ​​
​​​ ​Come, come!​ ​​
​​​ ​Have some faith​ ​​
​​ ​in me and follow!​ ​​
​​​ ​I had​ ​​
​​ ​so much fun today!​ ​​
​​​ ​The fireworks​ ​​
​​ ​were so beautiful.​ ​​
​​​ ​I could gaze​ ​​
​​ ​at them forever.​ ​​
​​​ ​Did you also have fun​ ​​
​​​ ​at this summer​ ​​
​​ ​festival with me?​ ​​
​​​ ​What?!​ ​​
​​​ ​G-Gosh, you're gonna​ ​​
​​ ​make me blush with​ ​​
​​ ​those compliments!​ ​​
​​​ ​...​ ​​
​​​ ​For next year's festival​ ​​
​​​ ​and the year​ ​​
​​ ​after that, too...​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanna go to​ ​​
​​ ​them with you.​ ​​
​​​ ​I love you.​ ​​
​​ ​I love you so much.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hee-hee.​ ​​
​​​ ​Going to the festival​ ​​
​​ ​today was so much fun!​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanted to win the​ ​​
​​ ​video game from​ ​​
​​ ​the prize drawing,​ ​​
​​​ ​but I'm pretty happy​ ​​
​​ ​with this adorable plush!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hm-hmm 🎵​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Remember how​ ​​
​​ ​I wanted to eat at​ ​​
​​ ​every single stall?​ ​​
​​​ ​I thought I was​ ​​
​​ ​up to the challenge,​ ​​
​​ ​but I guess not!​ ​​
​​​ ​There was karaage,​ ​​
​​ ​yakisoba, takoyaki...​ ​​
​​​ ​And I wasn't prepared​ ​​
​​​ ​for there to be so many​ ​​
​​ ​baby castella in the bag!​ ​​
​​​ ​Maybe next year...​ ​​
​​​ ​"Let's go to the festival​ ​​
​​ ​together next year, too!"​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay?​ ​​
​​​ ​Heh-heh!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is the XO​ ​​
​​ ​and professor's​ ​​
​​ ​latest invention.​ ​​
​​​ ​An summer festival​ ​​
​​ ​simulation button!​ ​​
​​​ ​People don't wanna​ ​​
​​ ​go out in this heat?​ ​​
​​​ ​This secret weapon​ ​​
​​ ​will make them​ ​​
​​ ​fall into indulgence!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's try it out!​ ​​
​​​ ​Click!​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoa! It's so immersive!​ ​​
​​​ ​All right,​ ​​
​​ ​let's have some fun!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah-ha-ha-ha-ha!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh! That was close.​ ​​
​​​ ​We ended up​ ​​
​​ ​indulging the most of all!​ ​​
​​​ ​But you also wanted to​ ​​
​​ ​experience more, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​Click!​ ​​
​​​ ​Mmm!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gotta love the sights​ ​​
​​ ​and sounds of a festival!​ ​​
​​​ ​Like, look over there!​ ​​
​​​ ​The lanterns​ ​​
​​ ​are so pretty!​ ​​
​​​ ​When it's summer​ ​​
​​ ​in Japan,​ ​​
​​​ ​you just gotta go​ ​​
​​ ​to a festival!​ ​​
​​​ ​There's so much to do!​ ​​
​​​ ​Baked potatoes,​ ​​
​​​ ​karaage,​ ​​
​​​ ​shaved ice...​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoops!​ ​​
​​ ​I'm just listing food!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's right!​ ​​
​​ ​The fireworks!​ ​​
​​​ ​You can't have a festival​ ​​
​​ ​without fireworks!​ ​​
​​​ ​The show's gonna​ ​​
​​ ​start pretty soon.​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't wait!​ ​​
​​​ ​I hope we can see​ ​​
​​​ ​lots more pretty​ ​​
​​ ​sights together.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a promise!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gah!​ ​​
​​​ ​I missed again!​ ​​
​​​ ​But I'll get it next time!​ ​​
​​​ ​Just you watch!​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​What?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, how is​ ​​
​​ ​that allowed?!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is totally rigged!​ ​​
​​​ ​Darn stupid...​ ​​
​​​ ​That does it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes! The prize is mine!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's what​ ​​
​​ ​I'm talking about!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah-ha-ha-ha!​ ​​
​​​ ​There's a lot going on​ ​​
​​ ​at this festival.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's about​ ​​
​​ ​time for dinner.​ ​​
​​​ ​We're going to a​ ​​
​​ ​sushi place, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​That restaurant is​ ​​
​​ ​supposed to have​ ​​
​​​ ​a great view of the​ ​​
​​ ​fireworks, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, what are you​ ​​
​​ ​apologizing for?​ ​​
​​​ ​You're right, more​ ​​
​​ ​people came to the​ ​​
​​ ​festival than I expected.​ ​​
​​​ ​I see.​ ​​
​​​ ​With this crowd,​ ​​
​​​ ​we'd probably need​ ​​
​​ ​a reservation to get​ ​​
​​ ​into that restaurant.​ ​​
​​​ ​But, don't worry!​ ​​
​​​ ​I had a feeling​ ​​
​​ ​this might happen,​ ​​
​​​ ​so I went ahead and​ ​​
​​ ​made a reservation​ ​​
​​ ​at that place.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, look! You can catch​ ​​
​​ ​goldfish over there.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wanna give it a try?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hehe.​ ​​
​​​ ​I swing my scythe at​ ​​
​​ ​humans all the time,​ ​​
​​​ ​so catching a little​ ​​
​​ ​fish is gonna​ ​​
​​ ​be a piece of cake!​ ​​
​​​ ​Watch this!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm... There!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah, I broke it.​ ​​
​​​ ​That was just a​ ​​
​​ ​practice round, OK?​ ​​
​​​ ​I've got the hang of it​ ​​
​​ ​now, so I'll catch one​ ​​
​​ ​this time for sure!​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on!​ ​​
​​​ ​That was the​ ​​
​​ ​perfect timing just now!​ ​​
​​​ ​Why is this so hard?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm back!​ ​​
​​​ ​And I got shaved ice!​ ​​
​​​ ​It was hard to​ ​​
​​ ​decide on a flavor,​ ​​
​​​ ​but I picked​ ​​
​​ ​an old favorite!​ ​​
​​​ ​Mm! So cold​ ​​
​​ ​and delicious!​ ​​
​​​ ​Want some?​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, but both​ ​​
​​ ​your hands are full.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, as thanks for​ ​​
​​ ​carrying our stuff,​ ​​
​​​ ​allow me to feed you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Open wide!​ ​​
​​​ ​C'mon, don't be shy!​ ​​
​​​ ​Or what, you don't​ ​​
​​ ​want it from me?​ ​​
​​​ ​Ha-ha-ha!​ ​​
​​​ ​Brain freeze?​ ​​
​​​ ​All right.​ ​​
​​ ​Smaller bites, then.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's enjoy it together,​ ​​
​​ ​a little at a time.​ ​​
​​​ ​Whatcha doing​ ​​
​​ ​over here?​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you tired?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, it's really​ ​​
​​ ​crowded here.​ ​​
​​​ ​I think I'll rest​ ​​
​​ ​for a bit, too.​ ​​
​​​ ​So, what do you​ ​​
​​ ​wanna do next?​ ​​
​​​ ​Wanna watch​ ​​
​​ ​the fireworks?​ ​​
​​​ ​This is just a​ ​​
​​ ​suggestion, but...​ ​​
​​​ ​wanna sneak out of​ ​​
​​ ​here, just the two of us?​ ​​
​​​ ​No one else​ ​​
​​ ​has to know.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hee-hee! ♪​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, have you heard?​ ​​
​​​ ​The school in the​ ​​
​​ ​neighboring town​ ​​
​​​ ​is cursed!​ ​​
​​​ ​Heh-heh-heh...​ ​​
​​​ ​"So anyway,​ ​​
​​​ ​I decided to come,​ ​​
​​ ​'cause I'm invincible!"​ ​​
​​​ ​"Hah!"​ ​​
​​​ ​"AAAAAAAH!"​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, sorry,​ ​​
​​ ​just to be clear,​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm not a ghost. I just​ ​​
​​ ​came here by myself​ ​​
​​ ​because I heard​ ​​
​​​ ​it's a good paranormal​ ​​
​​ ​sightings spot.​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh? You're here​ ​​
​​ ​for the same thing?​ ​​
​​​ ​Darn,​ ​​
​​​ ​I was hoping I'd run​ ​​
​​ ​into an actual ghost.​ ​​
​​​ ​Too bad.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, I guess I'll​ ​​
​​ ​head home for today.​ ​​
​​​ ​You should probably​ ​​
​​ ​be heading back too.​ ​​
​​​ ​Just so you know,​ ​​
​​ ​I explored quite a bit​ ​​
​​​ ​and found​ ​​
​​ ​absolutely nothing.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hm?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hello?​ ​​
​​​ ​Wha...​ ​​
​​​ ​Whaaat?!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's the good stuff!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahh!​ ​​
​​​ ​'Ey there!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ya barely drinkin'​ ​​
​​ ​at all! Come on!​ ​​
​​​ ​Or, what?​ ​​
​​​ ​Ya can't stomach my​ ​​
​​ ​ramune or somethin'?!​ ​​
​​​ ​No? Okay, then drink up!​ ​​
​​​ ​Chug! Chug! Chug!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, are you okay?​ ​​
​​​ ​Not feeling well?​ ​​
​​​ ​I know just the thing.​ ​​
​​​ ​You just gotta​ ​​
​​ ​drink more!​ ​​
​​​ ​Thanks for inviting me​ ​​
​​ ​to the festival today!​ ​​
​​​ ​Everything was fun,​ ​​
​​​ ​but I really liked​ ​​
​​ ​the shooting game!​ ​​
​​​ ​It was hard,​ ​​
​​ ​though. Heh-heh.​ ​​
​​​ ​I was amazed that you​ ​​
​​ ​managed to win a prize!​ ​​
​​​ ​When you were playing​ ​​
​​ ​the shooting game...​ ​​
​​​ ​you looked so cool!​ ​​
​​​ ​I was really happy​ ​​
​​ ​when you won​ ​​
​​ ​this prize for me.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll be sure to treasure it!​ ​​
​​​ ​It'll remind me of the​ ​​
​​ ​special time we spent​ ​​
​​ ​together today. ♪​ ​​
​​​ ​W-Wait up!​ ​​
​​​ ​(pant pant)​ ​​
​​​ ​I almost lost you​ ​​
​​ ​in this crowd...​ ​​
​​​ ​What's so funny?​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't tell me​ ​​
​​ ​you did it on purpose​ ​​
​​​ ​just to see my reaction!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmph!​ ​​
​​​ ​If you're gonna be​ ​​
​​ ​like that, I'm not gonna​ ​​
​​ ​talk to you anymore.​ ​​
​​​ ​Really?​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, if you learned your​ ​​
​​ ​lesson, I forgive you.​ ​​
​​​ ​You're lucky I'm so nice.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's hold hands,​ ​​
​​ ​so we don't get​ ​​
​​ ​separated again.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's right!​ ​​
​​​ ​Your job is supposed​ ​​
​​ ​to take care of me!​ ​​
​​​ ​Heh-heh! ♪​ ​​
​​​ ​I like how calm Japan​ ​​
​​ ​summer festivals are.​ ​​
​​​ ​You don't have to​ ​​
​​ ​act wild and crazy.​ ​​
​​​ ​You can just enjoy​ ​​
​​ ​them quietly like this.​ ​​
​​​ ​I like that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh yeah, I bought​ ​​
​​ ​some sparklers.​ ​​
​​ ​Could we try those?​ ​​
​​​ ​I've wanted to do​ ​​
​​ ​that for a long time!​ ​​
​​​ ​Great! Let's​ ​​
​​ ​light them, then!​ ​​
​​​ ​You win if yours burns​ ​​
​​ ​the longest, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna beat​ ​​
​​ ​you for sure!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is gonna be fun!​ ​​
​​​ ​That festival was so fun!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm so glad we got​ ​​
​​ ​to go together.​ ​​
​​​ ​So... hey.​ ​​
​​​ ​How much​ ​​
​​ ​did you enjoy it?​ ​​
​​​ ​Going to a​ ​​
​​ ​festival with me!​ ​​
​​​ ​What was the most fun?​ ​​
​​​ ​The shooting game?​ ​​
​​​ ​Food stalls?​ ​​
​​​ ​Goldfish scooping?​ ​​
​​​ ​All of the above, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​What's that look​ ​​
​​ ​supposed to mean?​ ​​
​​​ ​C'mon, don't run away!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ha-ha! Gotcha!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll always be the only​ ​​
​​ ​one for you, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't you go to festivals​ ​​
​​ ​with anyone else.​ ​​
​​​ ​Got that?​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow! The ocean!​ ​​
​​ ​I'm so excited...!​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh? Why do I​ ​​
​​ ​have a swim ring?​ ​​
​​​ ​No, no! I know​ ​​
​​ ​how to swim!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm an agent!​ ​​
​​​ ​So of course I can swim​ ​​
​​ ​like a professional!​ ​​
​​​ ​You might be enchanted​ ​​
​​ ​when you see me.​ ​​
​​​ ​So, you know...​ ​​
​​​ ​The swim ring... is just​ ​​
​​ ​special equipment!​ ​​
​​​ ​Japanese ninjas​ ​​
​​ ​use this too.​ ​​
​​​ ​For real!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna test out​ ​​
​​ ​this equipment now.​ ​​
​​​ ​Super ultra nin-nin style!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahhh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Help me!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sorry for the wait!​ ​​
​​​ ​I didn't mean to​ ​​
​​ ​take so long.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, now. Where​ ​​
​​ ​are you looking?​ ​​
​​​ ​You're just going to​ ​​
​​ ​ignore me when​ ​​
​​ ​I'm standing right​ ​​
​​ ​in front of you?​ ​​
​​​ ​There. Now you have​ ​​
​​ ​to look me in the eye.​ ​​
​​​ ​...​ ​​
​​​ ​S-Sorry!​ ​​
​​​ ​What was I thinking...​ ​​
​​​ ​Heh-heh.​ ​​
​​​ ​A-Anyway, the water!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go for a swim!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm feeling real warm​ ​​
​​ ​all of a sudden.​ ​​
​​​ ​For some reason!​ ​​
​​​ ​So come on, let's go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you know​ ​​
​​ ​what happens​ ​​
​​​ ​when a robot​ ​​
​​ ​like me gets wet?​ ​​
​​​ ​I think I'll test it out!​ ​​
​​​ ​Splash-splash!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ha-ha-ha!​ ​​
​​​ ​You should see the​ ​​
​​ ​look on your face!​ ​​
​​​ ​Of course, as​ ​​
​​ ​high-spec as I am,​ ​​
​​​ ​I made sure to record it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm, it looks like​ ​​
​​ ​water this shallow​ ​​
​​ ​is safe for me.​ ​​
​​​ ​But if you're with​ ​​
​​ ​me, maybe I can​ ​​
​​ ​go even farther?​ ​​
​​​ ​C'mon, won't​ ​​
​​ ​you join me?​ ​​
​​​ ​All right! Summertime​ ​​
​​ ​at the beach!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm excited as can be!​ ​​
​​​ ​The shining sun!​ ​​
​​ ​Swimsuits galore!​ ​​
​​​ ​And the cutest​ ​​
​​ ​of all is me, Ollie!​ ​​
​​​ ​In other words, this​ ​​
​​ ​summer is basically​ ​​
​​ ​the best summer ever!​ ​​
​​​ ​All right!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's enjoy ourselves​ ​​
​​ ​to the fullest while​ ​​
​​ ​the sun's still up!​ ​​
​​​ ​Beach volleyball!​ ​​
​​​ ​Take this!​ ​​
​​​ ​My ball!​ ​​
​​​ ​Relaxing in a swim ring!​ ​​
​​​ ​The sunlight is so nice!​ ​​
​​​ ​And lastly,​ ​​
​​ ​watermelon smashing!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait! I'm not​ ​​
​​ ​a watermelon!​ ​​
​​​ ​But you know,​ ​​
​​ ​this is kinda relaxing.​ ​​
​​​ ​How mysterious.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah, so relaxing...​ ​​
​​​ ​Hm? What's the matter?​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, did you want​ ​​
​​ ​to ride in this too?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's only meant for​ ​​
​​ ​one person, though.​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you sure your heart​ ​​
​​ ​can handle squeezing​ ​​
​​ ​in so close with me?​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh! Here's an idea.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't have to​ ​​
​​ ​ride the swim ring.​ ​​
​​​ ​I can let you​ ​​
​​ ​hold me instead!​ ​​
​​​ ​Well? What'll it be?​ ​​
​​​ ​Heh-heh.​ ​​
​​​ ​Sorry, time's up!​ ​​
​​​ ​That was your chance.​ ​​
​​ ​Too bad you missed it!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm back!​ ​​
​​​ ​It took me a while​ ​​
​​ ​to get changed.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hm?​ ​​
​​​ ​Why did you​ ​​
​​ ​freeze up like that?​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, I know!​ ​​
​​​ ​You were too​ ​​
​​ ​captivated by​ ​​
​​ ​my swimsuit!​ ​​
​​​ ​If you want​ ​​
​​ ​a better view,​ ​​
​​​ ​all you gotta do is ask.​ ​​
​​​ ​Pfft!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, right!​ ​​
​​​ ​Quit staring, weirdo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hm-hm-hmm ♪​ ​​
​​​ ​Hm-hmm...​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow! So pretty!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's try to find more!​ ​​
​​​ ​Look!​ ​​
​​​ ​This shell is so cute!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hee-hee. Let's bring​ ​​
​​ ​lots of them home!​ ​​
​​​ ​Should we put them​ ​​
​​ ​in a bottle to make​ ​​
​​ ​a decoration?​ ​​
​​​ ​Or just line them up​ ​​
​​ ​in a pretty design?​ ​​
​​​ ​I know!​ ​​
​​ ​We'll just do both!​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, we've got to​ ​​
​​ ​find more, then!​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on, help me out!​ ​​
​​​ ​"(Ooh, that's a cute​ ​​
​​ ​little tushy. I can tell​ ​​
​​ ​she's a hottie,​ ​​
​​ ​even from behind.)"​ ​​
​​​ ​"Hey, you here alone?"​ ​​
​​​ ​What? Oh my gosh,​ ​​
​​ ​are you hitting on me?​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, I'm cursed to​ ​​
​​ ​be hit on no matter​ ​​
​​ ​how old I get!​ ​​
​​​ ​So what can mommy​ ​​
​​ ​Marine do for you? ♡​ ​​
​​​ ​"Okay, not quite what​ ​​
​​ ​I was hoping for..."​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh? Wait, where​ ​​
​​ ​are you going?​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't you want to rub​ ​​
​​ ​sunscreen all over me?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey!​ ​​
​​​ ​At least buy me​ ​​
​​ ​some yakisoba!​ ​​
​​​ ​Man, this feels great!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're getting too hot?​ ​​
​​​ ​Maybe it's time​ ​​
​​ ​for a swim, then.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey! Come on in!​ ​​
​​ ​The water's fine!​ ​​
​​​ ​Take that!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hehehe!​ ​​
​​​ ​That oughta​ ​​
​​ ​cool you down.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, now you've done it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ta-da! Have a​ ​​
​​ ​taste of this!​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you all right?​ ​​
​​​ ​Our summer's just​ ​​
​​ ​starting, you know.​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on, let's have​ ​​
​​ ​some more fun!​ ​​
​​​ ​Boo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hee-hee. Did I get you?​ ​​
​​​ ​Sorry you had to​ ​​
​​ ​carry all our stuff.​ ​​
​​​ ​Phew...​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm tired, so I'm​ ​​
​​ ​gonna take a break.​ ​​
​​​ ​Being with you​ ​​
​​​ ​always fills up my​ ​​
​​ ​batteries in no time.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hee-hee.​ ​​
​​​ ​Your face is all red.​ ​​
​​​ ​Got you all​ ​​
​​ ​flustered, did I?​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​My face is red, too?​ ​​
​​​ ​That's just...​ ​​
​​ ​you know...​ ​​
​​​ ​because of the sun.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ooh...​ ​​
​​​ ​Stop that! You're​ ​​
​​ ​making it hard to​ ​​
​​ ​look you in the eye!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gulp... gulp... gulp...​ ​​
​​​ ​Phew...​ ​​
​​​ ​Hm?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, quit staring​ ​​
​​ ​at me like that!​ ​​
​​​ ​It feels weird.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, let's play with​ ​​
​​ ​this beach ball next!​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoever drops it​ ​​
​​ ​gets punished.​ ​​
​​​ ​Here I go!​ ​​
​​​ ​And... toss!​ ​​
​​​ ​Got it! There!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hah! Too bad!​ ​​
​​​ ​Time for​ ​​
​​ ​your punishment.​ ​​
​​​ ​What should it be?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm... Oh!​ ​​
​​​ ​I know!​ ​​
​​​ ​I sentence you to​ ​​
​​ ​be buried in sand!​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on!​ ​​
​​ ​Resistance is futile!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hello, everyone!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm not alone today!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm with holoh3ro at the​ ​​
​​ ​beach for several days!​ ​​
​​​ ​Woohoo!​ ​​
​​​ ​We have planned a lot​ ​​
​​ ​of things to do together!​ ​​
​​​ ​Can you guess​ ​​
​​ ​what have I planned?​ ​​
​​ ​I'm so excited!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hehe!​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanna play​ ​​
​​ ​games here!​ ​​
​​​ ​I have my PC-chan!​ ​​
​​​ ​And this!​ ​​
​​​ ​And a portable​ ​​
​​ ​internet connection!​ ​​
​​​ ​Aaand...​ ​​
​​ ​a portable table!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahh...​ ​​
​​ ​Now this is perfect!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gaming time!​ ​​
​​​ ​[10 minutes later]​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, why is it blue​ ​​
​​ ​screen? Overheat?​ ​​
​​​ ​Nooo! PC-chan! Aaah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Can... Can we go​ ​​
​​ ​back home? Please?​ ​​
​​​ ​Heh-heh.​ ​​
​​​ ​Have you been waiting​ ​​
​​ ​for me this whole time?​ ​​
​​​ ​Were you that excited​ ​​
​​ ​to see my swimsuit?​ ​​
​​​ ​Then it's your lucky day.​ ​​
​​​ ​Cause I'm gonna​ ​​
​​ ​show you now!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ta-da!​ ​​
​​​ ​So, how do I look?​ ​​
​​​ ​Gee, your face is all red!​ ​​
​​​ ​Heh-heh.​ ​​
​​​ ​Did my swimsuit get you​ ​​
​​ ​all hot and bothered?​ ​​
​​​ ​Why are you staring​ ​​
​​ ​at me like that?​ ​​
​​​ ​Staring...​ ​​
​​​ ​Y-You're starting to​ ​​
​​ ​make me sorta​ ​​
​​ ​embarrassed... sorta...​ ​​
​​​ ​Ooh...​ ​​
​​​ ​I-I'm letting you off easy​ ​​
​​ ​for today, you hear!​ ​​
​​​ ​Here I pe-go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wh-Whoa!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ow...​ ​​
​​​ ​I messed up...​ ​​
​​​ ​I pek-hope my​ ​​
​​ ​nose isn't all red...​ ​​
​​​ ​Can you​ ​​
​​ ​inspekt it for me?​ ​​
​​​ ​Ha↘ha↗ha↗!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gotcha back-o!​ ​​
​​​ ​Now your face is all red.​ ​​
​​​ ​What were you​ ​​
​​ ​expekting, hmm?​ ​​
​​​ ​Take that!​ ​​
​​​ ​Heh-heh! I win again.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wanna have​ ​​
​​ ​another go?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm...​ ​​
​​​ ​Heh. That's the spirit.​ ​​
​​​ ​I accept your challenge.​ ​​
​​​ ​All right. We start​ ​​
​​ ​shooting on the​ ​​
​​ ​count of three.​ ​​
​​​ ​Three...​ ​​
​​​ ​Two...​ ​​
​​​ ​One...​ ​​
​​​ ​Too slow!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ha-ha-ha! I win!​ ​​
​​​ ​What, you​ ​​
​​ ​wanna go again?​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, if you say so.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll gladly​ ​​
​​ ​play you all day.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hm-hm-hmm... ♪​ ​​
​​​ ​Nobody's​ ​​
​​ ​watching, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanted to do​ ​​
​​ ​this at least once.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, what?!​ ​​
​​ ​I was streaming​ ​​
​​ ​this whole time?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ugh...​ ​​
​​​ ​Heh.​ ​​
​​​ ​You know, you guys​ ​​
​​ ​could've told me sooner.​ ​​
​​​ ​But, I suppose you just​ ​​
​​ ​want to see more of me.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, of course you did.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll let you get away​ ​​
​​ ​with it this time.​ ​​
​​​ ​See you next time.​ ​​
​​ ​Muah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay! It's the ocean!​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't swim,​ ​​
​​​ ​so I made sure to​ ​​
​​ ​bring a swim ring!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wa-ha-ha!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okey-dokey.​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoa!​ ​​
​​​ ​The swim ring popped...​ ​​
​​​ ​W-Watame did​ ​​
​​ ​nothing wrong, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​But I can't swim​ ​​
​​ ​without it...​ ​​
​​​ ​So you'll have to teach​ ​​
​​ ​me how to swim!​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on, let's go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm...​ ​​
​​​ ​We've been here for so​ ​​
​​ ​long and still nothing...​ ​​
​​​ ​Are they scared maybe?​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh!​ ​​
​​​ ​This feels like a big one!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna​ ​​
​​ ​reel it in, okay?​ ​​
​​​ ​Mmmmm... Hup!​ ​​
​​​ ​Aah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't look...​ ​​
​​​ ​Hahahaha!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm right here, so​ ​​
​​ ​where are you looking?​ ​​
​​​ ​We came to the​ ​​
​​ ​beach together,​ ​​
​​​ ​and all you wanna​ ​​
​​ ​look at is other girls?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm kinda hurt.​ ​​
​​​ ​What, looking at me​ ​​
​​ ​too much makes​ ​​
​​ ​you nervous?​ ​​
​​​ ​Really?​ ​​
​​​ ​Even so, it's not right to​ ​​
​​ ​avert your gaze like that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well? Did your​ ​​
​​ ​heart skip a beat?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, what's with​ ​​
​​ ​the stupid grin?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm starting to​ ​​
​​ ​get hungry.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go grab a bite.​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't wait to eat at the​ ​​
​​ ​beachfront restaurants!​ ​​
​​​ ​If you've got any​ ​​
​​ ​recommendations,​ ​​
​​ ​I'd love to hear them!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hup!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hoh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, there you are!​ ​​
​​​ ​I've been waiting!​ ​​
​​​ ​The next match​ ​​
​​ ​is about to start!​ ​​
​​​ ​C'mon, join in!​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh? What's that?​ ​​
​​​ ​You don't wanna, 'cause​ ​​
​​ ​you're out of shape?​ ​​
​​​ ​You can't be serious!​ ​​
​​​ ​Summer only​ ​​
​​ ​comes once a year!​ ​​
​​​ ​Fine, let's do some​ ​​
​​ ​warm-ups instead!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, are you listening?​ ​​
​​​ ​What are you staring at?​ ​​
​​​ ​You wanna sit back,​ ​​
​​ ​relax, and watch me?​ ​​
​​​ ​Cut it out!​ ​​
​​​ ​If that's the case,​ ​​
​​​ ​you'd get a better​ ​​
​​ ​view if you play!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's such a beautiful day.​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't waste it​ ​​
​​ ​sitting around!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, I'll start!​ ​​
​​​ ​Here goes!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hee-hee, this is so fun!​ ​​
​​​ ​Take that! Yah-yah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gaa! So sawty!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ptoo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Augh...​ ​​
​​​ ​Sawty food is good,​ ​​
​​​ ​but why does the sea​ ​​
​​ ​have to be so sawty?​ ​​
​​​ ​If seawater was​ ​​
​​ ​cwear and tasty,​ ​​
​​​ ​wouldn't that​ ​​
​​ ​be wonderfuw?​ ​​
​​​ ​Cause we could use​ ​​
​​ ​the sawt fwom the sea​ ​​
​​​ ​to make wots​ ​​
​​ ​of tasty snacks!​ ​​
​​​ ​If I said​ ​​
​​​ ​to make snacks​ ​​
​​ ​out of seawater,​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm sure my Lu-knights​ ​​
​​​ ​would wush​ ​​
​​ ​into action, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​You'll do it, wight?​ ​​
​​​ ​Then off you go!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's finally here.​ ​​
​​​ ​The beach episode!​ ​​
​​​ ​Now then!​ ​​
​​ ​Where do we start?​ ​​
​​​ ​What do we do first?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm...​ ​​
​​ ​Beach volleyball?​ ​​
​​​ ​Watergun?​ ​​
​​​ ​Standing in the water​ ​​
​​ ​and splashing​ ​​
​​ ​each other?​ ​​
​​​ ​Burying someone​ ​​
​​ ​in the sand!​ ​​
​​​ ​Or maybe getting carried​ ​​
​​ ​out to sea in a pool tube?​ ​​
​​​ ​What about that prank​ ​​
​​ ​where you put on​ ​​
​​ ​a fake shark fin​ ​​
​​​ ​and scare people​ ​​
​​ ​in the water?​ ​​
​​​ ​Or sitting under a​ ​​
​​ ​beach umbrella rubbing​ ​​
​​ ​sunscreen on each other.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahh. Man,​ ​​
​​ ​beaches are the best!​ ​​
​​​ ​There's so little time!​ ​​
​​ ​Let's get started.​ ​​
​​​ ​We gotta experience​ ​​
​​ ​the true anime​ ​​
​​ ​beach episode!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm back!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ta-da!​ ​​
​​​ ​Well? Check it out!​ ​​
​​​ ​My swimsuit!​ ​​
​​​ ​Isn't it cute?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hee-hee! ♪​ ​​
​​​ ​Right?​ ​​
​​​ ​H-Hey!​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't stare!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sure, I told you​ ​​
​​ ​to check it out,​ ​​
​​​ ​but when you look me​ ​​
​​ ​over so intently,​ ​​
​​​ ​it's embarrassing!​ ​​
​​​ ​A-Anyway, let's​ ​​
​​ ​stop wasting time!​ ​​
​​​ ​There's so much​ ​​
​​ ​to do at the beach!​ ​​
​​​ ​So? What should​ ​​
​​ ​we do first?​ ​​
​​​ ​Play with​ ​​
​​ ​this beach ball?​ ​​
​​​ ​Swim in the ocean?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's have lots of fun!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ack!​ ​​
​​​ ​S-Sorry...​ ​​
​​​ ​Take that!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ha-ha!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gotcha!​ ​​
​​​ ​My plan to​ ​​
​​ ​use my cuteness​ ​​
​​ ​as a distraction​ ​​
​​​ ​so I could soak​ ​​
​​ ​my assistant​ ​​
​​ ​went off flawlessly!​ ​​
​​​ ​I've once again​ ​​
​​ ​demonstrated my​ ​​
​​ ​exceptional brains!​ ​​
​​​ ​Eek!​ ​​
​​​ ​Argh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Now you've done it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Now it's my turn!​ ​​
​​​ ​Take that! And that!​ ​​
​​​ ​And that and that!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ha-ha-ha!​ ​​
​​​ ​Stop it, assistant!​ ​​
​​ ​That's cold!​ ​​
​​​ ​But this is so much fun!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah... Ah... Ah-choo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, I'm might be​ ​​
​​ ​feeling a bit chilly...​ ​​
​​​ ​In that case,​ ​​
​​​ ​the best way to​ ​​
​​ ​warm up is this!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gosh,​ ​​
​​ ​I'm such a genius!​ ​​
​​​ ​Augh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey! Behind you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hehe. Check this out.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hee-hee.​ ​​
​​ ​How do I look?​ ​​
​​​ ​You think​ ​​
​​ ​I'm cute? Hee-hee.​ ​​
​​​ ​I know, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you, thank you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hee-hee.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ugh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ouch.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh.​ ​​
​​​ ​Everything's all​ ​​
​​ ​spinny now. Whoa.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oi! What are you​ ​​
​​ ​laughing at, huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​So this is the allegedly​ ​​
​​ ​haunted place?​ ​​
​​​ ​No, I'm not scared.​ ​​
​​​ ​What, you don't​ ​​
​​ ​believe me?​ ​​
​​​ ​Look, if this​ ​​
​​ ​place is haunted,​ ​​
​​​ ​that means it's​ ​​
​​ ​full of ghosts, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​In other words,​ ​​
​​​ ​the stories of all​ ​​
​​ ​those dearly departed​ ​​
​​ ​are gathered here.​ ​​
​​​ ​If I'm lucky,​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll meet some​ ​​
​​ ​of them, so I can​ ​​
​​ ​archive their stories!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey,​ ​​
​​​ ​maybe I should​ ​​
​​ ​try to summon​ ​​
​​ ​the spirits myself?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'd love to see the look​ ​​
​​ ​of terror on your face...​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, don't be​ ​​
​​ ​such a scaredy-cat.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ghost stories are mostly​ ​​
​​ ​superstition, anyway.​ ​​
​​​ ​Here,​ ​​
​​ ​I'll prove it to you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Say cheese!​ ​​
​​​ ​See, as long as we're​ ​​
​​ ​giving off happy,​ ​​
​​ ​positive vibes,​ ​​
​​​ ​it'll scare away the​ ​​
​​ ​negative ghost energy!​ ​​
​​​ ​...What's the matter?​ ​​
​​​ ​What?! Is that a face?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh gosh!​ ​​
​​ ​Let's get outta here!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, just a little​ ​​
​​ ​to the right.​ ​​
​​​ ​No, you went too far!​ ​​
​​​ ​If you don't smash that​ ​​
​​ ​watermelon open soon,​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna beepin' die!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's so hot out here,​ ​​
​​​ ​if I don't get something​ ​​
​​ ​cool to eat...​ ​​
​​​ ​then all the emotions​ ​​
​​ ​inside me are​ ​​
​​ ​gonna burst out!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, keep​ ​​
​​ ​going straight...​ ​​
​​​ ​Now stop right there!​ ​​
​​​ ​And swing!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah! Nice!​ ​​
​​​ ​You smashed that​ ​​
​​ ​watermelon open​ ​​
​​ ​real good!​ ​​
​​​ ​Here, lemme get​ ​​
​​ ​a piece for you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's eat together!​ ​​
​​​ ​Mmm, it's so good!​ ​​
​​​ ​Thanks to you,​ ​​
​​ ​my radiance is​ ​​
​​ ​even brighter!​ ​​
​​​ ​The sun is so bright...​ ​​
​​​ ​I guess that blinding​ ​​
​​ ​light is how you know​ ​​
​​ ​you're at the beach.​ ​​
​​​ ​What?​ ​​
​​​ ​No, I'm fine just hanging​ ​​
​​ ​out under the umbrella.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'd rather not​ ​​
​​ ​expose myself to​ ​​
​​ ​that harsh sunlight.​ ​​
​​​ ​We'd be missing out​ ​​
​​ ​if we don't swim?​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, you can go ahead.​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't mind me.​ ​​
​​​ ​If you're having fun,​ ​​
​​ ​then so am I.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmph.​ ​​
​​​ ​You said that on​ ​​
​​ ​purpose, didn't you?​ ​​
​​​ ​You know how​ ​​
​​ ​easily I sunburn.​ ​​
​​​ ​If I go out there,​ ​​
​​ ​I'm gonna turn into​ ​​
​​ ​an itchy red blob!​ ​​
​​​ ​And besides...​ ​​
​​​ ​being seen in​ ​​
​​ ​my swimsuit...​ ​​
​​​ ​is kinda embarrassing...​ ​​
​​​ ​Fine, you win.​ ​​
​​​ ​But only if you help me​ ​​
​​ ​put on sunscreen, okay?​ ​​
​​​ ​Heh-heh,​ ​​
​​​ ​c'mon, what are​ ​​
​​ ​you blushing for?​ ​​
​​​ ​You shouldn't tease​ ​​
​​ ​if you can't take it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Look!​ ​​
​​ ​There's cotton candy!​ ​​
​​​ ​This one's​ ​​
​​ ​blue and fluffy...​ ​​
​​​ ​Isn't that basically me?​ ​​
​​​ ​Mm-hm-hm~ I bet you​ ​​
​​ ​want some too, huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​Here, you can​ ​​
​​ ​have a bite.​ ​​
​​​ ​Is it good?​ ​​
​​​ ​If the cotton candy​ ​​
​​ ​is anything like​ ​​
​​ ​me, it must be...​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh? Why are​ ​​
​​ ​you making such​ ​​
​​ ​a funny face?​ ​​
​​​ ​You're being silly...​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, I know! You're​ ​​
​​ ​just trying to trick me!​ ​​
​​​ ​But I'm not​ ​​
​​ ​gonna fall for that!​ ​​
​​​ ​I know cotton candy​ ​​
​​ ​tastes really​ ​​
​​ ​sweet and yummy!​ ​​
​​​ ​Aahm...​ ​​
​​​ ​Waoh! The inside of my​ ​​
​​ ​mouth feels all tingly!​ ​​
​​​ ​And there's this minty​ ​​
​​ ​breeze in my sniffer, too!​ ​​
​​​ ​Eh-heh-heh, it's not what​ ​​
​​ ​I expected, but I like it!​ ​​
​​​ ​And I'm gonna​ ​​
​​ ​make you like it too!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ey-ey-ey!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's summer!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's really hot!​ ​​
​​​ ​And I can't wait to​ ​​
​​ ​get my paws wet!​ ​​
​​​ ​So here we are!​ ​​
​​ ​The river! Ja-jan!​ ​​
​​​ ​All right! Time to play!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah-ha-ha-ha-ha!​ ​​
​​​ ​C'mon, you too! The​ ​​
​​ ​water's nice and cool!​ ​​
​​​ ​A change of clothes?​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't worry about that!​ ​​
​​​ ​If you ask me,​ ​​
​​ ​when it's this hot out,​ ​​
​​​ ​it's better to cool your​ ​​
​​ ​whole self in the water,​ ​​
​​​ ​clothes and all!​ ​​
​​​ ​You too!​ ​​
​​ ​Come on, let's play!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ooh?​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you getting​ ​​
​​ ​all flustered​ ​​
​​​ ​because you think​ ​​
​​ ​my wet clothes will​ ​​
​​ ​turn see-through?​ ​​
​​​ ​Not today!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm wearing something​ ​​
​​ ​underneath, so no​ ​​
​​ ​see-through for you!​ ​​
​​​ ​Did you get​ ​​
​​ ​your hopes up?​ ​​
​​​ ​Fwah?​ ​​
​​​ ​I smell like a wet dog?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sniff-sniff...​ ​​
​​​ ​Th-There's no way I do!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm a good puppy!​ ​​
​​​ ​And good puppies​ ​​
​​ ​don't smell bad!​ ​​