[Music]
notifications
so
[Music]
[Applause]
hmm
[Music]
up
it's been a little while thank you
welcome
thank you for the memberships hello it's
it's been a while
what what what what what
how are you guys hello
uh oh my god what did i just move
hmm um
it's been a while it's like it feels
like it's been like a long while
like it's definitely been has it been
over 48 hours at least
at least over 48 hours it feels like
such a long time it taste
uh i was supposed to actually i was
planning to take today off
and stream yesterday but yesterday i
[Music]
didn't feel so well a few hours before
the streaming time
so i decided yo i'm not gonna first
myself
so also i still had some issues
to figure out with my switch yesterday
and and i wasn't really feeling it
actually i was
uh no not a bird flu
bird flew ha ha ha ha ha and no no no no
no no i was quickly gone actually i
didn't tell you guys but i
i had um some
pain in my throat for the past few days
which is my my miracle my
miraculous miracle me
it's gone like a miracle now how do you
say my red colossey miracles
and just with that i would have
streamed anyway but then yesterday uh
i also had some pain in my stomach and
was like wait is this the is this the c
is this the could it be
do i have to see flew
but and the stomach ache was gone after
like a few hours and the fro pain in my
throat is gone too so
whatever chicken
bird flu is much more serious don't joke
around with that
i think many people died because of that
i am immune against it but
yes uh also many people make jokes about
me
eating chicken soup because apparently
that's what you do when you're sick
but nobody made chicken soup for me
although i do i would have appreciated
some soup
because like having someone make soup
for you when you're like sick oh my god
that's the sweetest thing ever
actually i remember like i i actually
rarely get sick
of
i usually don't get sick like really i
never get sick like
okay that thing yesterday i wouldn't
even say i was sick it was just for a
few hours
but like i usually don't get sick did
you know that
in japanese uh there's a saying
like uh
if you don't if you never get sick like
if you never catch a cold or something
you're an idiot
i don't understand why there's this
saying
but hmm does this mean
i'm a idiot what is
yeah well actually i wonder if that
saying is only in japanese have you guys
ever heard that in your language i've
never heard that before
er no no no no it has nothing to do with
bottom left
anyway so today i felt better already i
still had to do some things you know i
went back to to my house
and did some things because i had to do
some things
and then i came back here again to
my manager pc actually no no now it's my
pc
it's my pc and the manager's internet
this is the godly combination no one
can destroy this combination actually
last stream was also with my pc but
apparently something went wrong there
anyway
um what was i going to say oh yeah oh
yeah
and then my manager helped me figure out
what the problem was with my switch
because if you guys remember
the last time i streamed with my switch
was with fire emblem
and even though the stream before that
was stable and alright
although maybe not exactly stable like i
did have some issues before the stream i
think probably anyway
but that's during that stream
my capture card kept like like i don't
know
messing around and just turned black and
then it came back again and
oh my god it was so frustrating i didn't
know what it was
and uh i maybe you guys remember so
since then
i bought uh all the cables new because i
didn't want to believe that the
fault was on my capture card
[Music]
so i bought all those new cables
turns out it wasn't the cables it was
also not the capture card
it was also not as i would have
otherwise expected
it was also not any hdmi slot or
anything like that
it was just a
the apparently the
switch charger was not
properly connected to the
electricity yeah and now it's
all good it's all fine everything's cool
it's stable
and i bought three new cables for
nothing but that's okay because hdmi
cables i i might need again and again
and again anyway that's all good
but yeah i'm really happy that uh uh
capture card is is not dead
yeah i don't know um apparently it was
like a loose loosely connected or
something i guess
but now it's all good i tested it before
stream
and today we are celebrating the revival
of my capture card with
and actually this game let me switch
this game i recently
i recently got myself this game
and while i was very inspired while i
was watching a certain senpai's
stream on this game and i was like uh i
wanna
challenge her
vision too loud oh goddammit
yeah anyway is it better now i know
so so i saw her streaming and she
streamed maybe for two hours or
something
but i bought the game instantly but the
download took so much time and i
ended up not being able to challenge her
um
soon
and anyway even though i just told you
that i just bought the game recently
i uh i uh
i'm a professional um
uh mario kart player
it's just that i maybe i just
bought this one recently but all the
other mario kay oh i definitely have
lots of experience um i'm a very good
driver
uh in as a phoenix i have revived many
times and uh
i've lived many lives and um one of
those lives was
possibly i will not say that i was not
but i will also not say that i was
um so of course since i'm such a
such a professional we will get right
into it and play with the world
wide rivals who wants to challenge
the dangerous me
yeah i must say it's a
not a good idea to challenge me
by the way is the audio fine now
do you better not challenge me
let me show you my skills
i am speed i
i am speed does this matter what i
choose
i am speed don't challenge me
[Music]
gotta go fast here we go
let's go
of course i will i will go for
number one by the way of course
oh
what an original name
hurry the i don't have time for this
you are facing the number one
mario kart player of a previous
lifetime previous dimension
you think i got time watching you like
that
i've been looking at these shitty
drivers man so depressing look at those
shitty driving skills look at them holy
horrible oh my god that's ridiculous
does not even
get on my level friend oh ridiculous
oh my god look at that little green elf
boy
just kidding
with his banana he just put out his
banana
is that the only thing you can do here's
your banana
huh that's all you got oh you can look
ridiculous
come on show me your bananas huh if you
think
if you think you're brave enough to show
me your banana come
do it green man
now of course i don't care because i'm
just so good i know every
every map uh v minor best
compassion as you would say in german
uh how did i say that in english my west
pocket
west pocket i know
you doing uh do you see who who is me
and the orange
one oh god they're
doubting me they're looking at me
they're like oh my god we don't want to
fight this
chick she's she she's the skilled one
she stands out despite being orange
happy birthday king wolf
it's my my godly aura that's standing
out here
what did we what are we going for see my
992 that's like a really good good yeah
well yes here we go let me show
you how i go fast
go away
that was just them to help the others
obviously it's not fair to suddenly like
unpreparedly
rise against such a goblin
[Music]
racing party
um
[Music]
i was just kidding um in reality
obviously i can hold the first place
constantly
more interesting for this
[Music]
this time um bring me down
seventh place unlucky number one
every number is a lucky number in some
country
i'm just um
[Music]
better take care when you're driving
oh yeah
[Music]
this something is wrong with this car
ooh look at that
[Music]
[Laughter]
i'm dizzy windows is in my waist the
windows window opens um
eight eight
yeah that was just um i was actually
playing with my feet right now
i
now i will use my hand
[Music]
what voice louder i can't make my voice
louder than this i'm eating the
microphone
i'll turn the bgm down a bit
did someone leave the group because i'm
just too good now down here
ah where where is speed i just showed
you speed but that was
foot speed i will show you now
hand speed
[Music]
what a german name okay this time
i will not mess up this guy
uh many many of my previous lifetimes
what's with this camera it's just like
[Music]
the lights are irritating my eyes
my majestic phoenix eyes
[Music]
babies
nine
[Music]
wow
german guy god number one what about me
hello
what place
i have yet to show you my true power
the german guys doesn't look safe for my
broadcast
[Music]
energy
let's go i'm the only one who was so
brave to choose random huh
oh wow i didn't have much choice there
with all of you
choosing the same goddamn road you
little
skirt chickens
this time i should have never played
this rook before
[Music]
report brush
why am i always
[Music]
what is my existence
don't see what i truly am
[Music]
my english is uh not
uh working well to my job
[Music]
with my english today what the hell i
think you know um
what i'm not very good with most past
kids
driving safely takes a lot of
concentration
[Music]
[Applause]
wow what is that red super jet
thank you very much
why is the plant not doing it for me
what did i even get you for it huh
this is why i don't water you goddamn
plants because you don't need me
anywhere anywhere useless goddamn plants
who needs plants huh
who needs
i want to say that for it but people
keep on saying
chiara language so i'm trying to control
myself but i just really want to say it
i just really want to say it
was i ate again i'm not even looking at
the numbers anymore because
i don't care about numbers numbers are
not important
it's the thought that counts and the
person behind it not the number
so in my heart i'm your number one right
so yes
[Music]
just messaged me on discord
well yeah of course she messaged me
because i messaged her first
nothing special about that but
yet nana t
i shall write this
race for you
[Music]
i can do it
again
let's go drive safely it's wet here
why is it so wet here why
why
gotta go fast why am i so slow
okay do this god skills
god skills you saw that that drift my
friend and now i go
boom mama ma
i'm coming better watch out
this one i don't know hello
this one i don't have to control because
this is a good one
unlike that stupid piranha plant
[Music]
i'll do it for you i'll become number
one
screaming
what is the hell with the curves like
how am i supposed to do this
oh my god what how how how is everyone
doing this
please drive for me
i'm trying to drift i was looking at the
chat
[Music]
i didn't even reach the finish line
don't drift oh wait now you don't want
me to drift
[Laughter]
this one i played on the phone i think
so yeah i'm using tilt controls who
gives a
who cares huh
what are tilt controls anyway
by the way today i'm using a pro
controller
oh because i'm a professional mario kart
driver
but that was in my previous life what
i'm using tilt controls who gives them
[Music]
the only one i know give me mumu
this one i know from the phone too i
think from the phone
from the phone
[Music]
no maybe not
there's
oh yeah howdy cowboy music here we go
oh my god that's like a rollercoaster
holy
are you destroying my phone here my
father wasn't goddamn disneyland
why would you do that to me ah ooh side
road cause i'm
special oh
wow
[Music]
i prefer the cowboy music right now
though thank you
let's just come on wow
get your
[Laughter]
[Music]
roller together hey where's my ipad
where's my item
you cannot let the german guy win but
she seems
quite close to me actually what is the
german guy doing
in the back huh
i'm
maybe if i connect with some stream
stream snappers maybe they let me win
[Music]
you guys might think stream snipers are
always bad but that's not true because
in like
in my fold live stream they're all
helping me they were trying to wait
waiting for me and like telling me how
to climb and how to jump so they're not
always bad
okay here we go
[Music]
[Laughter]
i'm
[Music]
oh there's one more german guy let's see
oh party
[Laughter]
wait what what what place did i i didn't
see what was
what was my number seven
goddammit this looks easy
game boy
actually okay i gotta say um i played
mario kart
on the gamecube when when i was a young
burp
and i played the more recent one was me
playing
uh mario kart on the smartphone when it
came out
i was quite addicted i even paid what
was it a gold pass or something like
that
thing called this is how i do it did i
do it right okay i think i did all right
here we go good start here we go
here we go this looks like a cute road
like a cute easy
easy road good for beginners right i'm
not a beginner obviously so i don't need
that but
i tried to trim i tried everything
nation
is the thing right now
and thunder
i wasn't sure what i was going for there
but now i'm the big one huh
you guys keep on bullying on me but now
i'm the big one what you do now huh huh
now i'm scary huh
oh here comes the stupid plant again who
cannot control itself so i have to
control it
stupid useless plants never water plants
okay if they cannot lead you
to victory what are they good for huh
we don't have to stress ourselves about
such a game huh
huh no need to stress myself out here
we have one more one more round to go
after
not a big deal
let's go let's go come on come on
show me what you got
i chose you for a reason because you're
cute now show me you got skills to
show me it's more than just your face
and your cute butt
huh
nice that was good that was good okay
actually guys does it matter which
character i choose
i guess probably the characters don't
matter but does does the card
and the combination of whatever i use
matter come
nine nine nine nine nine
nine
i thought you were a pro yeah but in a
previous life it's written in the title
in a previous life while i was reborn i
i
excuse me for not remembering all the
skills from my previous lives
excuse me
okay
excuse me no let me win please random
come on i can do it
i am i believe strongly in myself
just like you guys believe in me and now
please answer my question again because
i
am talking so much as the chat doesn't
know what to answer to
does it matter which card i'm using
yes am i using a bad cart
or am i just bad am i using a bad card
answer to that question
or am i using a bad combination yes
yes but actually no yeah bad bad car
what okay it's not my fault but
by doing that attached to 90
animal crossing i recognized for the
trees oh
i love animal cresting i mean i only
played the most recent one
and only for a while then i got sick of
it but i still love it very much
i wanna play again i wanna play it again
i got sick of it but i love it
i'm not like um i was like
i'm not that probably not the perfect
type
to play on animal crescent but i really
like this but i got to get it
but i really like it and i want to play
it again
oh blue panther thing
strike you down whoever is in the front
yes
it's a good good chance for a
collaboration maybe
did did i actually didn't watch that
stream excuse me but did you not make
any
no no did she use like something she
created before or
[Music]
did she make something new i don't i
feel like she didn't make anything
ah should i do two but mine is like
super
super old oh
[Music]
is
what this is this is beautiful though
this looks nothing like my island but
it's beautiful
did you guys know that in german
autobahn
uh what does that mean german um
german uh speed roads
i didn't even use my last item hello i
wasn't that uh
i'm i'm not the last one at least look
at that
and what was i saying did you know that
in germany the
highway highway i'm on the highway to
what hell
in german highways there's no speed
limit
nineteen
previously i told someone about that and
i told someone japanese about that
and that person was so surprised she was
like what
i went to like a million uh accidents
and actually no it's not even that bad
right it's like
i don't live in germany but i've been on
the german
highway before and uh even though i
thought i was gonna die because my
friend
who i was in the car with thought it
would be fun
to go as fast as possible
almost kill everyone who was in the car
but that was fun huh but hey we didn't
die
you know you usually even if you have
the chance to go full
speed you don't do it usually
unless you're on a road that is like
really empty
i mean normal people would do it
and then there's always the people
trying to flex with their
beautiful class you know i don't know
much about cars this is one car that
they don't build anymore i've forgotten
is it something a very majestic
car it called wasn't something with my
majestic car suitable for a queen
oh yeah it is
yes yes yes yes see that's something
that i would want to drive but i will
never drive actually i
i i made a promise to myself
that i will never get a driving license
and i mean if you look at my let's be
honest i was lying to you i was never a
professional mario kart player
shook what did she just say she lied to
us
i believed her oh my god devastation
um but yeah can you imagine someone like
me on the road
no no it's better if i'm not on the road
don't you
see that here also i suck at
multitasking and driving scares me i
don't want to be in an accident even
though i just said that german
roads are safe it's a lie it's a goddamn
lie i'm just lying to all of you
two idents
don't destroy my music
okay after that when maybe we choose our
uh
cardigan but then i got kicked out of
this wonderful
group that keeps on letting me win and
then i have to re-choose my group and
then maybe you guys
you crazy guys are in there and trying
to ruin
my obvious wins even more
[Music]
what
i'm trying to read comments while i'm
flying so comfortably
okay okay okay okay change cards because
obviously this is all the fault of my
card
why is it why okay why okay can i
are you guys gonna give me enough time
okay rosalina is not at fault right
rosalina has nothing to do with this
right
so which card do we go for this one
looks good
this one looks like speed
what do you think about this guy
let's go for this for now let's go for
this we got no time
press plus and why i don't want to get
out of the script
but
for your stats i can see the stats huh
it but this is why or not this is unfair
why don't you just have all the bikes
and the cars
have the same stats and have it all fair
but this looks good this is not is it
better than before i mean at least it's
a bike
[Music]
okay new new vehicle
here we go new chance to start a new
life here
you oh my god
[Music]
balance
keep your trash
for until you get home like how hard can
it be
[Music]
firebird attack
the evil spirits in my head i'm hitting
those things
what oh my god i hate this road oh my
god
[Music]
1.8 eyes
you ruined my drink
never give up
this never happened did you guys like
tell me to use the bike because it's
horrible
what are you guys trolling me this is
probably for like
for other kinds of people not for the
people like me
it's easier to dress well first i gotta
figure out
when and oh my god i refuse to be the
last one
no no
what what this is
there
uh traction what the hell is traction
your mom is stretching as
ame would say this is a fancy one
[Music]
acceleration wow
okay i guess we're going with that did i
even uh
push okay i don't think wait that's
saying someone looks like piccolo is
this one of piglets and perspires
because
like all the fakers said by viewers they
are trying to look like her
let's see let's see let's see
akl i maybe not
was this person around the whole time
okay different bike let's see how it
goes why is
pack there's a pac-man skin
where is that pac-man what oh
bye i am going the other way
this is how you win this is how you
encourage
the cool yeah what let me be free
let me leave me i just
[Music]
why can't i just be myself huh
why you take this away from me
i just want to go backwards
okay it's okay i mean there's not so
much space between me and the front
runners
there's not that much space then we can
totally still manage things
[Music]
oh yes
you guys know where i got that from
spain
[Music]
that was my um this is how i would sound
when i will cover
einstein
is this good bumping against those
things is that good
[Music]
i don't have friends i don't want
friends
we will never be friends okay
i would like some friends
look at how i'm rocking now hello well
wow
[Music]
but luigi just
lazy i'm your ghost friend why are you
not liking me go away with your stupid
turtle thing
[Music]
my english is top-notch today top-notch
english show i finished as
a star because baby alice died
not bad not bad we have improved i would
say
what english i should just okay
next next and next to unleash
my true german power my true speed
i will go full german next uh
race looking
[Music]
buddy
uh
[Music]
is
okay
[Music]
um
is
[Music]
that was english speed but still
um cannot get
over seventh place apparently
john
[Music]
even though i speak german the
the language of the of the
non-limited speed aggressive
speed lords
why why why why why
cheap cheap beach yo i know some cheap
cheap beaches
i can show you some of them one of them
is sitting on this bike
here we go here we go here we go
i do not know how to put
items on my ass
yoga
[Music]
itself against me
what okay i will try next time if i
gotta use this item
which i get the whole time then i will
put it on my ass
and stick it up all the way in there and
then it is where it belongs
[Music]
okay i don't think i should stick this
up my ass
wait wait kfp crew what
i will stick this in your ass
[Music]
drift come on beach
i take back everything i said i am a
pure idol
actually you know during my german debut
i really wanted to be like
known as the pure one
[Music]
bottom left confirmed hell no because of
you on the rope against the wall that
would have totally not happened
if you would have not superchatted but
thank you anyway
you were driving me against the wall oh
my god
i went in there with the fullest of the
first speed though
thank you kfb crew for going behind me
that is very nice that's actually really
nice thank you so much for
losing against see this is a really
wholesome sniper
this is this is just how kfp
works this is how my stream snipers are
they're just
so kind and sweet and lovely
[Music]
workers would join in to the room and
let me win
please
i think it's eight more eight more
please actually we could really try that
would you guys help me
i think okay maybe there would be one or
two trolls but if we get enough
of good people with a good heart we
could um
let me win i believe in you guys i
believe that you guys are not just
the same trolls as in certain other
streams
although i do enjoy it kfb one more hey
welcome welcome
i don't i'm sorry if i hit you guys
actually i really don't want to hit you
guys
excuse me if i do it's just so so much
more exciting with stream stoppers
oh did that guy just stop driving on
purpose because of me
focus
[Music]
okay i don't need items i gotta hold
some stream snipers
[Music]
why did i just hit me wasn't that a
first place there blue
thingy shell shell
oh yeah it's not panter it's
german the german in me is coming
through
can't be staying real close to me to
protect
he protect but he not attacked
the chick chick attention
hello hello i don't see where's my
janitor
clean this up kfp janitor when you
ask
i'm not paying you but you gotta do your
job
gotta do some drifting i gotta do some
drifting
[Music]
janitor
you will never never get a promotion
if you don't clean up oh my god
[Music]
there's like at least two stream snipers
who are
of positive supportive nature and the
most i can do is number 10
or what what
[Music]
is
oh here we go finally my two items and i
was waiting for
my whole life
six six six
sixth is it isn't this the best we did
oh
thanks my lovely employees wait
it was only one after all where where's
the where's the other one
where did my other employee go what
was only one now i thought that was two
okay wait you know what uh what what
how do i get out yes
let's try to form a group with
only kfp workers how do we do this
do your best do your best and stream
snipe the
out of me
make me number one or make me nothing
what colt i don't know a goddamn cold
how would i know
you just try to get in there on your own
let's go
let's go okay let's actually now we have
some time
to choose
uh i don't know man
who cares about this anyway do i want
speed yeah
oh wait
wait they don't give me much speed do i
want traction
guys do i want traction or acceleration
handling is what i want
traction both huh
let's uh use this
what have i done is the same what do i
want here
it doesn't change man
come on
oh oh that that changes a lot
[Music]
i think this is the bestest company
combining nation
come in my friends make me number one
where's my kfb crew huh where you're at
you gotta change your names to kfp
related names otherwise i don't know
why you're here where you come from
can't be known
[Music]
no no please not that road that's out of
all
the roads in mario kart that is the one
i
hate the most
there's one more joining one more
acting kind of suspicious excuse me why
i'm already being fully honest to you
guys i suck
okay i have
admitted that i am a fraud i'm not a
mario kart
professional driver
huh
what are you really talking about so
where's my kfp crew
nowhere i always know what is that it
shows a related name to me
i want to see kfb names
still
if anyone is in this group sent me a
super jet whoa that's b
what the hell was that
is this okay around
okay we got a drift in this one focus
i'm number one what the hell
this is just a small minor setback
look at that
come on kfc i believe in you i hate this
round so much
oh no i played this one before the
stream
i was trying to you know see if the game
works
and this is horrible i fell off the the
road like a million
times okay we're not doing that
bad
are do they all just suck or boy is this
actually kfp
dominated group oh
[Music]
foreign
this is what this road is it's just
trash cool
come on
why am i 11. it started out so well i
was the only one who did acceleration
what the hell man
okay yeah just keep on falling out that
this is just a joke okay this is just a
joke
don't take this seriously because this
road cannot be taken seriously
yeah see what i'm doing like items are
useless in this road because you just go
straight off of the club yeah that's
just how it goes
up
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
kill me now
you need i need to check i'm trying
whoever is behind me you cannot be
a worse driver than me so whoever's
behind me
must i was going so slow
they must be the viewers of the stream
really sweet ones too really kind
of like
[Music]
you were too far behind excuse me
ex i was trying okay i was just trying
my best thank you masha
for it like actually helping where is my
kfp
crew at where are all my buddies
come on join in i'm using childcare
oh here's why did curfew just join in
yes hello hello at least one
at least one feels familiar he is using
tails controls
whatever the that means
let's go my friend you and me were in
this together
you and me my friends
let's go let's go
honestly the previous road though that
was it was not my fault okay
it was just made to fall off like how
how are you supposed to not fall off the
road there
tell me there's no way to not fall off
the road
of that stupid road
drift i was drifting
i was drifting for my life
speed oh i love snow
wait this one was on the phone for sure
i said i played this one on the phone so
many times so we gotta win this one
what is the difference between let me
see
what is the difference between that set
r and r
it's both trampolines
well there is a back oh let's just go
back
kfp crew trying really hard to just stay
behind me and not
not
jose disney jose disney
hey today today i was nihongo or josued
i've complained previously that oh my
god
where am i previously i complained about
people not telling me that my japanese
was good because it was just so good
that they didn't feel the need anymore
to tell me about it
because they thought it was just natural
but
um today someone told me my japanese
[Music]
thank you
zelda be sending me friend requests like
what the hell
i am as you can see a star
you can just become a friend of
phoenix like that it's not that easy i'm
a mythical creature
but what do you think how many people
want to get into my feathers huh
okay so i didn't check the comments
right away so i still don't know what
the difference between
that r and r is would you like to tell
me again listen to your comments
i'm gonna look at the comments from my
side
what's that's up
the end
[Music]
r is what
uh oh i guess i can give you guys a room
yeah wait wait wait
i guess we can try that what so what
kfp kfp in third place
you have betrayed me i thought you were
there to help me
how do i do that the room thing
top 10 anime betrayals unbelievable
why won't you do that
tournaments
that's tote flying around there so cute
create a tournament should i maybe not
show this part is there anything i
shouldn't show
i'm like scared i'll show you something
that you shouldn't see
well here's a useful comment that is the
big one on
top and is the small
that's not useful i know sorry good
avocado i know
that i know that said r
is under r and r is over r i know that
you were supposed to tell me what's the
difference
in the functionality
okay wait one second uh create a
tournament
yes let's
go
yeah let's go
i can't see
[Music]
you better make me win
speed
okay the rule is that you make me win
no teams normal items blah blah blah
smart steering only stupid only only
stupid steering yes
what does that mean maybe i should keep
it smart
ah what
wait what wait
what why is it weeklies
this is not the right thing why did you
tell me to do this one
time doesn't matter what is this
what am i setting up hide the screen
okay
thank you i was figuring that something
must be
dummy yeah what am i doing
change the time to now
turn it to private okay code required
you mean
do i have to change the time to now
[Music]
set it but how many races
can i not make and oh no limit there we
go
uh start time oh yeah
yeah but then i cannot start it like
right away wait if i'm
it could it can start in
six minutes i guess
wait this is like what the hell just let
me do it now
i know
[Music]
huh
what do you mean artemis why is everyone
saying hello itemis
when did you see artemis
huh speed
okay yeah you gotta you gotta let me win
guys you understand the rules
you know the rules and so do i
where is our dummies what do you think
argentina where you say artemis is here
[Music]
shark shark
anyway i guess i gotta i gotta hide it
again for some reason
and then i go and then we see what
happens
how do i get into my own tournament
join
this tournament is currently closed but
you can still play practice matches
hell now i'm going for the real i guess
we gotta wait for like four minutes
do we gotta wait for four minutes
huh why is there really no option to
just start it right away that's
ridiculous
four minutes until my victory
what are you guys talking about
where did you see god do i really gotta
look for
5 million comments to find the shark
woman
hello items i found you
are you gonna drive against me are you
gonna try to battle the phoenix
this is a this will be a legendary fight
[Music]
spit challenge
this is like taking so much time oh
straight let's do some hydration
everyone got their drinks i got some
water
[Music]
okay that was one one single sip
by the way guys tomorrow e i has a
stream
on cali channel collaboration on kelly's
channel
and if you check out her schedule it's
written there anyway i think
oh wait did we decide on the fixed time
it's somewhere in the evening time
japanese standard time
and we're playing a minecraft together
oh thank you for the super chat
i love you i love your toothbrush video
and for everyone who doesn't know it's
nothing sexual okay it's nothing sexual
about
there's nothing sexual about brushing
your teeth i mean
reminds me now that i talk about it
reminds me of monogata
now that i think about it now that i
think about sexual
sexually brushing your teeth the only
thing that comes up in my mind is
monogatari and now i cannot get it out
of my head awesome
can i join my finger yet no let me
in do you you guys all have the
the code right oh
blah blah can't let me in
yeah is my favorite anime
is there no way to okay i'm checking the
comments now tell me is there really no
way to just start it right away
you gotta plan it in like 30 minutes
tacked
is it really like that do it be like
that
just go in i cannot go in
nope
you're not in the lobby no i'm not in
the lobby
because it starts in a minute
are you in the lobby because i'm not in
the lobby can i
could i please get into my own room
yeah okay now now i should be able come
on
oh wait practice matches means ah
[Music]
i think okay are you all in there and
can't you
yeah are you is there no space for me
now anymore
[Music]
huh tournament is now open from the next
game on
oh the tournament is open my friends ah
let me
let me in it's my tournament
now if you want let me join speed yes i
join speeds
yes yes yes yes let's go let's go i'll
show you the screen in a second
join speed
searching for players are you guys in
there you better let me win
oh here we go oh my god what
are those good people
uh it stopped did it crash
who here crashed my interweb
i thought uh uh they were already
driving oh okay
okay guys you can still join
i don't know the number anymore but did
someone write down the number
i could write it on the on the screen we
just finished one
eh
also why are there two npcs in there
are you telling me you couldn't fill it
up with more
kfp employees
oh is that the number really
chat called go like
oh we can use that one
so okay okay let's make a rule everyone
who was in the race
one time leaf
[Music]
apparently this is the number you better
be right with that
everyone who was in there wants to get
out of there
but i'm not gonna be doing this much
longer
let me tweet about it
now with tournament code come let me win
away
okay better be some
better be some nice employees who let me
get my deserved win after all this
struggling and
learning how to play the game in the
first place which i still don't know
because i still didn't even
try putting an item in my ass
oh
yeah that's the right number right
oh can you go faster what the hell
making you make him your boss wait
you're all not getting your tips tonight
don't make me wait i want to go fast now
oh it's almost done
i was saying it as if today you don't
get tips but you never get tips
[Music]
what what do you mean by what do you
mean by you're my side right you're
gonna
well they're leaving even though they
didn't drive against me yet
huh huh
okay you know the rules let me win oh i
should have chosen now can i go back
i should have chosen the road that i
that i feel like i can
[Music]
handle
i mean pig oil stream snipers are always
pretty damn intense but i feel like
they would go easy on me right
[Music]
no what but what about the fall guys
stream
all the stream snipers were so sweet and
like helping me
i believe in the goodness of your hearts
faster faster
i believe in all of you
fire kfb yeah one more
name that is related to the party
okay here we go let me show you how
whole some
my viewers are kiana
what what what's the matter with you
that was on purpose huh but i know how
it is
you always believe the ones that you
love the most
is this germany is this germany
german highway here we go
german highway of course someone german
is leaning
this looks like germany this looks like
a german highway
[Music]
i know you love me show me your love
i know usually you like showing your
love by bullying but how about
one time in your life you show your love
by
showing your love because you know girls
don't actually
like it when you bully them
you might think you're like being funny
or whatever but we don't actually like
it when you bully us
trying to show me your love by by by
like saying me
saying how how stupid i am or how bottom
left i am
i'm not happy about that it's okay
it's okay but
since
let me tell you something about girls
okay i know you maybe don't know
how to speak to a beautiful phoenix like
me i know you maybe don't know how to
speak to me
how to address the majesticness that is
me
everything is so peaceful nobody's
attacking me but nobody's like
protecting me
anyway you know what you're gonna do
when you see
uh in the wild and you're like damn we
gotta be both
okay first of all don't propose don't
because i'm taken and you all know that
but you may show me your
what your appreciation and your love
bye bowing down to me
and say praise takana
ki kariki what the hell was that why am
i not number one none of this is
this is not what we talked about that
was supposed to be number one
okay get out all of you get out where
are my real kfp
employees you all are
import posters imposed
imposters
i mean i don't know if even so many
people are trying to join back in
but i would i would like some nice
people to join
why are they not leaving
is this really all we got left this is a
higher chances for me to win
do you not want to drive against it i
guess this is the way to make me number
one because i'm so bad that even if
you're not trying
to to win against me
even if you're not trying to win against
me
i still stay behind
every goddamn time so there's just no
helping it so you just gotta leave the
race in order to give me higher chances
okay i get it i get it okay let's just
do this my friend
this means wait how many were there this
means i cannot get below like
seven or something well that is
beautiful that is beautiful
not
bumble oh
that was a useless bomb and you just
took my double item
get this fire kfp you dropping down
[Music]
i'm the last one how is it possible let
me win
you're fired
please
i still don't know how did that was it
said r did they say it's that r to put
an item in my ass
come on number five is not so bad um
nice i see like literally no one in
front of me they're so far away
they're just having fun down there huh
[Music]
um
drifting drifting like a bro
did you see that drift did you catch my
trip
what does that
well number six not bad
um six out of
ten of course of course
6 out of 12 6
welcome everyone i hope everyone who was
here before
leaves because you did not understand
the rules the rules is
let me win
get out of the room if you cannot follow
the rules
just play around with some numbers
[Laughter]
six is a five i don't see a six what
what what cold is five
i'm glad that man the code is red oh
okay
okay okay okay
[Music]
kiki reiki
okay one thing is for sure i will not
lose the cancer because you're making
fun of my greeting and i do not
accept such a thing
who is that stupid cakey wrecking guy
who is it
show them who the boss is there's a
cookie guy
number one if you look at it from the
backside
[Music]
i'm doing some good drafting here okay
i'm getting better at drifting
that's for sure speed
please
where is everyone why is everyone so far
away
[Music]
there for seven million years now what
the hell
thank you applesauce you're you're a
sweet i like your apple pie
sorry that i just bumped into you but i
actually really appreciate you
your existence and bye
why am i not number one why
why am i not number one
speed
[Music]
that's what i say to my kitty cats when
they do something stupid i say
nine nine house nine
well number nine huh um
leave all of you bring me some people
who actually do their job
correctly
this is my last name
[Music]
okay guys this um this
and one more race and then that's it
so two more chances to make your boss
win
unless you want to be fired
do i get a promotion you you
get a promotion you are the only one who
gets a promotion
hell yeah good job
and you can stay in the race because you
giving me higher chances to win
yes you may stay and yes you get a
promotion you get promoted to
hmm what would you like to be
and what were you to begin with what
okay we still got some talking to you
change your name oh i was i was first
for a second
i was raised for a second don't go
drip drip drip drip drip check
check
[Music]
i feel like in this road is pretty easy
like i can i can
do well on this one i might be number 10
right now but this might change in a
second
it's all good here doing
doing quite well um
applesauce my boy oh
[Music]
yay come on who wants a promotion
if you want to be promoted you can be my
private secretary
who wants to be my private secretary
make me win
[Music]
don't use your items everyone to stop
using your items and let me the
win
i did not deserve this okay i just
looked so much
better
[Music]
come on please
one time in my life i wanna win
one time in my life
i hate you
kid i mean lucky night
last road so all of you get out of there
so that the others get some chances
get out of here
bye-bye love you
i also hate you
i love you and i hate you it's a very
complicated feeling
ah where are all the new people
where are the new people i feel like
nobody left and nobody
joined this is the last race though my
friends
let me win cookies
read the air
come on please
what the i don't think i like this road
[Music]
now
okay last chance to win let's do this
[Music]
keep that for a good moment get the
i was doing so well for a second okay
what the actual
no
this item who needs this stupid
boomerang
[Music]
oh
too fast
can we still remember i've seen some
miracles happen in mario kart so
i wouldn't give up yet drift
dubba i hate this spot
yes oh
it led me to a secret secret road
oh well that didn't change anything what
the
[Music]
yes
let's check this side
[Music]
no
lead me to victory
[Music]
i forgot to push
huh
this time
you are
you are all fired mina kubinistava
you all are fired from kfp
have fun playing on your own
ah
[Music]
well i mean um
i'm very happy today you have witnessed
the power of a true mythical being
showing her skills from her
previous lifetime as a mario kart
professional
racing driver you are
welcome
today this shall be
hopefully a lesson to all of you for the
future
to not
okay so what will we be doing now my
friends
we will be reading the super chats
i have uh
some reading to do and i had fun though
thank you everyone who joined the stream
today thank you for everyone who also
joined membership thank you so much
and we also do some donut me
all of you are fired to donate me
everyone who um what was i going to say
everyone who watched the stream i hope
you enjoyed it
and i might i'm thinking about i'm
always like planning my streams really
spontaneously like all the other members
have like a weekly schedule but i'm just
like
whatever i'm deciding on the day before
sometimes even hours before i hope
that's okay for everyone but
i'm thinking of maybe uh now that the
switch works
before the minecraft collab with my
waifu
we could continue a fire emblem tomorrow
maybe if i
if i feel like it and
so i actually didn't i want to reuse the
thumbnail previously because the stream
didn't go well i was like i'm going to
use this phone again because i'm proud
of it
so tomorrow um maybe my
maybe fire emblem on my channel and then
later on a collaboration with cali on
kelly's channel so
everyone who wants to leave now thank
you for watching today i hope you
enjoyed it but we'll be doing some
chatting in between the super chat
reading so if you're gonna stay
there's always some fun time in between
reading the names
so it's it's not it's not a waste of
time that's for sure
today
[Music]
ah well
it was funny like some people
actually because i announced it this way
some people actually thought that i
would be good at this
[Music]
actually like you know um
i've read some comments about my gaming
skill
skills previously some people were
pissed off because every game i play
i'm horrible at
but i feel like this is
also a skill to have
to be bad at everything it's just you
know that
it's not easy to be bad at everything
okay
we have
[Music]
and honestly that's not true okay it's
not like i suck at
every single game you just haven't seen
me play the games i'm good at
but i mean i'll get better okay like
this
no you always start somewhere you can't
be
good at everything okay hello uh
did i do a super chat reading after the
overcooked no okay i guess
so i gotta read the overcooked super
chats and the ones from today
[Music]
gotta give it to my manager to read
through it honestly like
um recently we've been getting uh super
chat
checks before we read it but you guys
are so well behaved
there's never anything to like fix
with my super chat ratings i always give
it over to the managers and they're like
oh everything's
so just in case there's like some some
something hateful or so in there but
there's never anything hateful in there
not
asking for it right now okay but you
know
thanks all of you for being good people
being decent people this is why i love
the kfp
crew because all of you are so
so sweet and respectful
and lovely and welcoming and kind
of social
so let me let me copy that
sorry this always takes a little bit of
time
[Music]
almost almost
okay i have handed it over but
as as far as i know you guys there will
be no problem
i wonder if this would have been today
if this would have been even
worse if i was not playing with a pro
controller
because oh yeah btm oh i'm still hearing
the
the the game vgm that's why i didn't
realize sorry but thank you for telling
me
thank you guys everyone's like pgm you
don't just want to listen to my voice
only
uh
i actually like nobody jam
someone who enjoys just listening to my
voice but i get it like it's kind of
boring
did that only destroy my ear also oh my
i probably have it mute did that yeah i
had it muted in
i had admitted in streamlabs you guys
are so lucky that just killed my ear
you might know me a necklace
you guys didn't hear it didn't you
you're lucky okay what about this
is this a good volume
[Music]
but wait now you're very here on the
game let me close that
up a little it's good okay i'm just
gonna leave it this way
maybe
um i'm a bit exhausted
i did a lot of swearing today i'm
extremely sorry i'm not
but i'm sorry
i did so much swearing
guys guys guys guys i didn't tell you
about this yet let me tell you about
something
everyone who who stains gets to hear
this brushes
precious story but i'm not sure how much
i should tell him um
the other day and honestly i think uh
yeah that day i was
i was feeling kind of down i think if i
remember correctly
[Music]
that was on the minecraft i was like
feeling down and
had like a huge cry after the stream
but then a few hours later i had a call
with
with money senpai and oh my god let me
tell you it cheered me up so bad i wrote
on twitter afterwards
that i was smiling so hard the whole
time that my face was hurting and i was
not kidding like honestly
ah it was it was like so goddamn happy
another
[Music]
so basically um
it was like a call to get to know each
other
and uh i was like before that i was like
really nervous i was like oh my god what
am i going to talk about with her
like i really like maddening senpai a
lot and i've watched quite a bunch of
her streams too
but i wasn't sure like what what to talk
about with her in such a situation i
honestly would
i probably wouldn't even know what to
talk about with
baccarats and by ever
but yeah i just um the only things
i had the only questions i had prepared
to ask her was what was it
uh if she really wears um
if she really wears clothes that are
dazzy
because there was a stream that she did
previously with
uh um i think it was oh yeah it was
yeah it was uh it was a collaboration
and they were like introducing each
other as like everyday clothes
and marine senpai was like made fun of
the whole stream
because apparently she was wearing like
really dark side really lame clothes
and i was like
does she really write that so i asked
her that but i will not tell you the
answer
but yeah funny
what else what else did i ask
[Music]
oh i asked her a question that didn't
even come from me i will not tell
who who this question came from let me
just tell you it was not from me okay i
got
i asked her
um actually this is even embarrassing to
ask
this is so embarrassing um
um
[Music]
yeah to translate that that to english
it's um
it's embarrassing i don't want to
translate
how do you um
how do you
handle your uh horniness recently i
guess that's how you could say it yeah
i don't have to translate muramura to
being wet
wet i guess it's more like how do you
control your horniness recently
but i was also like you don't have to
answer this question you don't you don't
have to answer this question
anyway we got along really well
we talked a lot and we also talked about
like um
future plans and
to collab and to hang out and stuff like
she's so
open and she's so so kind so spontaneous
[Music]
so
um japanese people are very shy and very
um reserved i guess i don't know like
they don't
they don't like if it's the first time
you talk they don't
like offer you suddenly to like
go on a vacation with them
but bonnie and sam fight is like
what like i knew she wants out
like the open type
know she was a really open type of
person before but i didn't think she
would be like that to me like
right away so that that made me really
really happy
honestly like oh my god i love her i
love her i love you so much so
i think i think there will be some
wholesome
collaborations in the future and we
already have some like
um like really original
um collaboration plans that we came up
with while
while we were talking to each other in
the in our first conversation okay
we were like hitting it off so well
so there's there's like what i mean why
are you laughing at my
whole wholesome what what did this say
did you say something wrong yeah she's
anyway
stifle for real
you don't
[Music]
foreign
oh my god guys okay you guys know that
i'm like
crazy about whole life okay i was
previously
some people say say like i'm one of you
okay let's just
have this back in in your mind okay
hearing like this was the first time
that i
spoke to someone from whole life
senpai's directly not through a stream
or something
this was the first time i hear someone
speaking directly at me through discord
and it was like
i was actually for the first for the
first i would say
30 seconds 30 seconds at least i was
just like screaming i swear i was
just the moment actually like uh malin
senpai
entered the discord channel a bit too
early then i
i wasn't ready for it okay i was not
ready for it and suddenly she enters and
just by seeing how her name entered the
room without even having her talk i was
like
the whole i swear i shouldn't be
screaming too loud right now but
i was screaming so much and then she
starts talking she's like oh it's cool
she was like oh her voice is so high and
it just kept on screaming because
the moment i heard your voice it made it
even worse i was like
oh my god oh my god oh my god
so can you imagine if i'm like this will
find my name senpai
how will it be with nicolas and i really
have to learn to control myself
[Music]
today but
um i i i calmed down i controlled myself
but this is like just
so weird to hear her voice
like speaking to me
that was such a surreal thing and even
like after a couple of minutes even like
after an hour i was still like
this is so weird is this is this
actually happening this is so
weird is she actually talking what
and then she's like not only talking to
me but she's just so
goddamn nice to me
[Music]
foreign
amazing it was amazing and just
after that after that i was so happy it
made
it made the whole day million times
better
oh and right after that like she she
she ah she oh she's so sweet
she messaged me right after the
conversation to send me
something special for a future stream of
mine she sent me something that i can
use
and and then she already right away she
messaged
uh piccolo senpai to like you know
talk good about me and be like hey kiana
was pretty
chill pretty good doctor she can speak
japanese fluently so don't worry about
it you'll be fine you'll be fine
and so yeah if all goes well
yeah she's like a wing wing woman now
[Music]
this is so weird though can you guys
imagine to like speak to someone
that you've been listening to for
four months on stream
on youtube and then and then you like
talk to them directly that it's such a
weird thought and it actually happens
like
[Music]
what
oh super jam still not
ready
is it so many this time
i think almost done
you say like it's a bad thing
is the 500 one the one that came in the
beginning is that still didn't run out
they take so much time to run out huh
chad frost what no i see the chat
[Music]
actually today i also i tried to like
you know slowly make friends with my
senpais but
i don't want to be like too pushy or
anything so
now i have officially added
how many is it four one
two three four
i have i have added four fours and fives
on this card as friends
foreign
going well one of us one of them
the collection grows oh yay
which four well i mean marin senpai
and the other two have secret
i hope i hope they
i think everyone i chose so far
chose sounds weird but everyone i've
contacted so far
are like quite the open friendly type
[Music]
of
yeah extroverts
who's the last one eh the last one
well yeah okay i guess that yeah that is
one of them
and the last one is secret
no no no no no no no
i i did actually hmm i did not add
jungkook as a friend on this couch
did i i don't think i did yeah i did not
i do i have like a message from him like
he he messaged us but i did not add him
but actually not because like not
purposefully
not trying to like
not trying to say anything on them
i think i think we're done
yeah of course everything is all right
again
pretty much looks like no problem
[Music]
we bridged over that time with a lot of
talking now let me try to get through
the super chats is
a bit quicker
i'm starting with the super chats from
the overcooked
collaboration
here we got my friends everyone we say
thank you after each name so
you're welcome to add danke should
spam the thank you soon
[Music]
let me get my cough drops because i
already feel
oh wait
let me take my honey cough jump to
smooth
um
in german it's called who's them
what i'mma make what
what
oh i should probably show the superchat
thing
reading super chats
well
[Music]
first and only read super chat we love
you cat i hope you're doing well my
birthday money go blue
oh happy birthday thank you so much
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you
happy birthday dear dear my fam happy
birthday to you
everyone wishing my boo happy birthday
thank you i'll be there i love
refrigerators thank
[Music]
nobody was muted wait nobody was muted
ever even not in the beginning of the
overcooked stream
because actually i didn't check back on
that stream i actually didn't have time
to check it out they were muted okay
okay
because i checked streamlabs at that
moment and indeed
uh the desktop audio was muted so there
must have been area
yeah but i think later on when i already
unmuted them i think that
some people were still trolling
thank you thank you
[Music]
amelia was so loud the whole stream
shut up okay
thank you it's the fps issue possibly
related to pc unable to capture gameplay
and broadcasting smoothly
honestly i don't know what was the
problem yesterday because like
[Music]
that was not it wasn't yesterday it
feels like yesterday but it wasn't
anyway like um overcooked too doesn't
seem like such a heavy game
but i thought the same thing about
minecraft oh
okay guys i got happy news for you i
decided
to buy even though i got absolutely
nothing on my bank account right now
i swear but i'm like uh gonna
have it deducted from my paycheck i am
i am ordering uh the 380.
what the 380 i don't know and everyone
told me to get that 380 so i'm getting
ready to go
getting the goddamn 380. not getting a
whole pc
because um the i think the rest is
alright
and then i hope everyone will be happy
i don't know when it will be it will
come but it should i hope it will come
soon
i had a 3080
the pretty 80 is the like i i saw so
many recommendations in the chat
everyone said
get the 30 80 get the very 80s i was
just like okay i'm just gonna
i will not i don't know about
computers but since everyone said
use the 3080 i'm getting pretty
and then once i move back to uh
the other place with my other computer
i'll just
ask someone to insert the
that card in there because i don't know
how to even open up the computer
but yeah you guys seem to be excited
about that card so
all good then hopefully it will
come asap maybe if you're lucky maybe
next week already
you will need other parts to complement
oh what do i need
well the cpu seems fine fine
what cpu was the issue
what do i need
no the ram is my ram is not japan
power supply is a power supply
ah
you all say ask botan but i don't want
to annoy her with my why would i
annoy both on senpai
i know she knows a lot of that stuff but
i don't want to annoy and never member
with
my computer issues
if anyone i'm going to ask someone
from wherever who knows their
who is not a talent because i'm not
going to annoy
she will be grateful yeah yeah but like
i have not even had
a single word exchange with her except
for like
on twitter and on the first day or
something
like the replies that we have i'm not
gonna out of nowhere and be like hello
slide into her dms like what do i need
for my pc
well okay i'll ask someone who knows
computers some more things about this
do you need what what what what didn't
do we have the power supply and the
compatible motherboard for your free
money
you know i don't know but we'll find out
okay
i was actually thinking like wait if i
get this card do i need anything extra
again
to make the card work this is like an
endless situation again where i buy one
thing and then i need another thing and
then i need another thing and then i
need another thing
then i might as well just buy a whole pc
i might as well just buy a whole goddamn
pc
yes
you have to be compatible interesting
okay you know what i really
gotta talk to someone about this let's
continue
[Music]
hey
hey kara even though you had some hard
times with streaming recently we kfp
employees don't mind beloved streams
regardless keep it up and also don't
give up learning with kelly
thank you so much for supporting me even
though there's so much trouble i mean
some people said like oh she had
troubles and every goddamn stream until
now that's not even true that's not even
true
did not ha i did not have troubles in my
arctic stream
but you know i did not have trouble with
my fall guys stream i did not have
trouble in my extreme i did not have
trouble in my super mario 64 streams
i did not have trouble in my karaoke
streams see the list goes on and on and
on
[Music]
i mean if you only want to see the
negative things then yeah that's what
happens but
how about you try to see the positive
things
yeah i mean personally for me it also
recently felt like
everything was going wrong i felt like
that too but if you look at it
like with a clear mind it's not true
thank you mine thank you monkey of chaos
thank you
extraordinaire fox 17
[Music]
be
yes i will get a pc and run it on linux
okay you said linus right and i'm in
linux
isn't it linux like we're talking about
something else and i i i somehow thought
of linux
what is linux then
why did i think of linux
what what no what is your problem guys
with linux
[Music]
thank you
briefly w thank you by the way about the
collaboration
i translated bitching kitchen
to slump and cushion in german
but um
it's not quite a correct uh
translation i translated it into
something really bad that's why i felt
so bad about translating it into that
[Music]
if you translate it back again into
english it's kind of like
kitchen of horse
because that was the thing i came up
with when i heard
in kitchen and i was like oh what
could that mean in german
because i did not really understand what
bitching means i'm so sorry but that's
why i felt so wrong i was like oh my god
is it really okay if i teach them that i
was like
i kept on saying like i feel so bad
about saying this in german it feels so
wrong i kept on saying that
the german speaking people were very
entertained but
have let me known that bitchin
doesn't really mean what i thought it
meant
i i hereby deeply apologize
for
making such an inaccurate translation
i'm sorry
what did you think it meant well i
thought it means kitchen of course
[Laughter]
but like but like cool cool cool horse
well i apologize
let's move on
yeah uh everyone repeated it after me
trusting in me
kylie said it good i said it i said it
we all said it together okay
i did not let them say it alone okay
ah a bitchin as i'm like bitching around
like being unhappy with something mecca
here
i mean i i like my translation
i do like my translation you're good
the ic thank you for your
again
thank you so much what types of games do
you want to play in collabs going
forward
um i think in the future we might have a
lot of minecraft collaborations
but also there's a collaboration coming
up with subaru senpai and the game that
i have
chosen is just so fitting
i will only say it is so fitting and i
have also
gotten permission so
from this it's all it's so fitting it's
just it's so
fitting it's all i would say
uh but also i will uh one one game that
i wanna play
in collaborations is this game where
there's like so many games
i had a game with so many games i think
there's like 51 games or something
yeah yeah yeah 51 games such a a
clubhouse games yeah
yeah yeah i want to play that one with
someone
like i think inna and ame played it
together
right i also want to play with someone
i didn't i didn't buy it yet um
oh well i
in in burp school in very very small
birth school
i used to be in the chess club
just like the unpopular birth i was
and then there were times when our chess
club
went on a
competition and
i was one of maybe two people
who stayed behind because i sucked so
bad
well
i hate jess
[Music]
foreign
did you know fire emblem is like chess
yeah
[Music]
strategy but i'm doing a much better job
at fire emblem than i'm doing with chess
i would say
[Music]
m
my company is not black okay there's
nothing illegal about
my company kfp just because
i receive all of your salary it does not
and this is just how the system is and
i mean it might have been written in the
smallest letters possible on the
contract but everyone who joins in now
knows it for a fact so do not say i did
not warn you
[Music]
the stream will be delayed 24 hours
well i mean maybe i would give you guys
some salary if you would let me
win in mario
[Music]
all i can say is never compromise your
health
and push to your limit after what i've
gone for today cherish your life i don't
want their faith
to be yours what whose fate
what are you talking about
but yeah um don't worry i'm generally
like if i feel bad
i'm definitely not the type to force
myself to
work uh yeah
i took care of my health puffing quite
well
will you rehire us back
um no everyone who was fired because
they did not let me become number one
you are fired forever
well maybe not oh i'll hire you back
come on come on
but next time you better make me number
one
[Music]
is
did you improve your english by watching
my streams recently
[Music]
their english
for my streams
oh don't worry about missing my streams
you can always watch the archive
[Music]
just keep on watching my streams and
you'll have perfect
english in no time i will not promise
you this but let's just watch
it someone faked your name
someone faked your name you gave my free
free one thank you
vegan my free free wonder question 311
is so much easier to say i must say
i'll see you okay if we cringe cash here
thank you
we be gamer 311 action i know it looked
it looked like you just saw 20 people
role playing as me
and preach out but we we're actually um
you know what i can't explain this
but it was more than one person in the
in the super chat it seems like only one
person and
personally a few i think you can sue
that person for impersonating you
i think there's a law against that
[Music]
what the actual f happened
in those like 48 hours while the
pre-chat was open it opened
what happened i i looked and like i
checked it out every once in a while
i saw you were talking about soup for 48
goddamn hours
what how can you talk about soup for
such a long time
[Music]
in it
foreign
what is this soup story
i will hereby
officially announce
the addition of pumpkin
soup limited
time limited at all kfp stores worldwide
which is one store
origami if i won't get a pumpkin soup
this bottom
i will just make it myself
just told the japanese people that
hokkaido
pumpkin soup is like a huge thing all
over the world hey they don't know
they didn't
um
oh i want some soup now
supposed
but i also love potato soup and corn
soup
corn soup ah potato soup
oh
super jets oh yeah send them some super
jets
soup
oh
any chance we could get a head pad from
the tent to herself love you and your
content here's a little something from
me and for the others
that kind of super chat to show that we
appreciate you thank you so much it is
so kind of you thank you
i am i don't know how to give you a
headpiece
uh let me touch the microphone
did you hear that nothing stay out
that's all
no i was rubbing the microphone okay
i'm not gonna do that again that was
very weird
pat harder that i have to hit the
microphone i'm not gonna hit this
microphone was expensive
boy you just verbalize the pad okay
okay let's go thank you so much for the
super chat
thank you thank you for your support i
really really appreciate it and yes
hashtag wrote to 300k might be a good
hashtag for tomorrow
i don't know where are we at now
somebody
foreign
oh we need 10 more cane oh
[Music]
i don't mind not reaching it tomorrow
but
we'll see we'll see it's just that the
previous days i
did not stream much due to issues
so i feel like i fell back a little bit
but it's okay we're almost there
it's almost in my hands it's almost in
my hands
maybe if tomorrow is a good day we might
reach it
no no no no it's not ready time you
don't need to post on reddit
no no no no no everyone on reddit
is aware of takanawa
if they did not decide to subscribe to
me yet
then i don't i don't think they want to
so besides everyone on reddit
must already be subscribed to me
yeah but yeah no needs to post anything
about it on reddit it's okay
you can post on it to congratulate me
afterwards
that would make me happy but don't tell
people to subscribe
to my channel let me do that
yo subscribe to kfp
invest in kfp stocks
soon we will dominate the fast food
market all over the world i shall bring
fast healthy quality fast food
all over the world the only thing that
will be suffering is my employees
because they work overtime
24 hours a day and all over the year
365 days and they don't get salary
because they pay me salary
well but that's just the price you got
to pay so subscribe to me invest in my
business
[Music]
oh thank you guys for like i saw a lot
of good feedback from my thumbnail thank
you
i'm glad you like it i had some like
real issues with thumbnails in the
beginning i was like everything i do
looks like but recently
the one from minecraft i was quite quite
proud of
and the one for today for mario kart
also does not
m well this one was easier i just wanted
to
make it look like speed speed
anton thank you soon
[Music]
how do you say that how was it
yeah i know it looks like i look it
looks like amma gave me something but
don't worry
amber did not give me anything i'm
getting stuff from
getting that stuff from her ties is a
bit expensive
construction potential please what the
also everyone who writes out the words
to tell me how to read it
you're basically just writing it the way
it's written
how is that gonna tell me how to read it
oh my god
oh how do i read that writes the same
word again
oh my god
so it's concoction that's such a weird
word it's such a weird word
yes write it with k and that that like
write it as a german would be able to
read it
or like how a japanese person would say
it maybe like
japanese uh pronunciation i guess
then i understand don't just write the
same word again
i can't read it okay i need to i
need to slow down on the
f's
how to say so
okay why are you pressing x what is
there to doubt
pour some say-so-sauce over me ah
ah a little more okay so much
so much about to say so
oh god no
[Music]
today's my breakfast i have some money
thank you and happy birthday to you
you can't read the name
are too are that are too dumb to get
sick to stone
ah don't notice that they're sick
[Music]
but i think i know why they say that in
japanese
[Music]
i think it's because i can in japan
people
are like when you get like a little cold
or whatever people are like
oh you didn't take care of your health
properly
so maybe it's like if you are not able
to take care of your health and your an
idiot
is
wait no forget what i just said because
the saying is
if you don't get sick you're an idiot oh
that doesn't make sense
it doesn't make sense i just thought i
made sense of it but it's the other way
around
people they say people who get get sick
are stupid
but if you're able no wait wait what did
you say
people who don't get sick are stupid is
what that japanese saying says
okay i get it they say that because you
don't you don't
notice that you got sick and that's why
you're
an idiot but i it's not like i don't
notice it i just really don't get sick
usually
so i'm not an idiot
he's waiting to knock
[Music]
do we get um now guys
i can confirm that idiots tend to get
sick more often
than not idiots see
[Music]
that
here is the proof this is what i would
say
too
the emperor is fake no
once you dream you dreamt about me
graduating and
i'm so quick it's not even one month
left
uh over
don't worry i'll never leave you
concussion ah concussion i heard that
word before
oh i thought you write that completely
differently
concussion ah it's like when you hit
your head really bad
huh no
oh wait you do write that differently
it but that person wrote it like
c-o-n-c-o-c-t-i-o-n
wait did that person write it wrong
is that does that word even exist he did
write concoction or something
[Music]
concoction
okay
scared me too yeah
it was just a dictionary website
thank you thank you so much
i agree with you mister
[Music]
nicholas sorry i don't know
i said the name right but well london
don't have one comment
in coding
press one of the shoulder buttons when
jumping and more coins
oh yeah i know the coins mean a bit more
speed but that's like
barely any speed
but i need to practice more kaiki's
rakzira thank you look at you it's been
a while since i saw your first video
it's always so cool to see you're having
fun kiara
i really like your streams and i see how
hard you work to maintain this wonderful
vibe a hug from a fan from video oh
thank you so much
oh that's so sweet thank you
i'm glad you enjoyed the stream thank
you the silver tank slacker danger
hey kiara my two month old loves
watching hey
you too are you cute i should stop
swearing that i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm
really sorry
i cannot control myself i'm sorry she
probably doesn't understand it yet does
she
your bright colors and cheering
personality have him transfixed and with
and you managed to convert my wife to
convert her to what
convert my wife also you mean to like
victory fans or like whole live
otaku oh god what did i do
thank you son thank you for watching my
stream i hope your
two two-month-year-old baby's first
words is
going to be um really loud
and obnoxious
sleepy doctor in danger don't really get
a chance to catch up this is the big one
that is still
on the screen don't really get a chance
to catch the live streams and want to
say
that your streams have been extremely
fun to watch ooh
against someone who's watching their
archives mostly
hope you get to catch a um
a live one sometime soon
so because i think like live one is
always more
fun than archive although i'm personally
the type of person
who prefers to watch archive so i can
decide by myself when to turn it on and
off
the energy you bring in your expressions
and reactions are pure entertainment
thank you
so no matter what the concept may be or
what happens during the stream you're
just
it being yourself nice and enjoyable how
to watch that oh
that's that's a sweet german there
that's something that um oh i think
only people who know a bit of german
would say
all i come up with thank you thank you
so much for your support i really really
really really really appreciate
your investment in the kfp stocks
thank you so much
it's really really appreciated we will
we will make some new burgers and new
soup with that
and hopefully i'll see you in a live
stream
sometime soon live not archived
joseph thank you very thank you
thank you
i'm getting really exhausted now i gotta
make an end to this
s 17 b 32 pixel master danger
ooh kevin duncan letter fly dancing
looking for the top pancaking supersonic
1995 thank you
thank you very very duncan hello oh my
god
very very very very very
thank you for your support this is
someone who did some
amazing kiara fan art
on twitter thank you
thank you i really loved i really loved
it thank you
thank you shadow fox 2 3 0
[Music]
oh
a bunch of german super chat
[Music]
is an austrian dialect
you know i hate i hate it when people
write german in dialect in text camp
i don't understand if you speak it in
dialogue but if you write it in dialect
what the hell is wrong with you
do you sort that on a voice it's so hard
to read dialect if it's written out like
that
industries like
this manchester united
[Music]
it's a lot
is
[Music]
okay to roughly translate
this person is telling me
and he got flashbacks from my stories
he was very very or he is very very shy
but he had some trainings during his
education and job of
trainings and then
uh
and then well
was this comp it gets gets kind of
complicated anyway
he started watching anime in his breaks
and in the evening he would ride his
motorbike cycle
motor bicycle motor motorbike
and that's how he got through that
stupid job
and then
well he's not stressed anymore because
his new job is great
and um the only thing that's missing
is a girlfriend that's the point where i
start laughing
because i feel like he was about to
propose to me
but the thing that gets in the way is
his shyness
so he says when he would
uh be on a date with someone like me
we would probably uh
not talk to each other because of
shyness we would just uh
talk okay and that's it
yeah what
and i don't think so because first of
all well
i mean i'm very uh
i hate awkward silence so i would
always try to fill it with stupid
talk but um
yeah but i'm taking i'm taken
by cali see he's got a sick
well but you know how i am on the road i
don't
i don't like writing writing anything
yeah it was like a bunch of super chats
okay now let's get back where the hell
was
m
i'm going to add my message onto the
super chats so that i don't extend your
super chat ratings but i'm glad you
what does that mean thank you thank you
so much for that
generous a super chat
thank you really really really really
appreciate your support
thank you with all my height
oh i was not supposed to read it
okay wait let me go back to the to the
german story
i am not sure what what exactly
the point was but if the point was you
asking me how to handle shyness
um let me think
hotel will come i think this is really
um
i know that uh you would try to
um how to say it but let me say that in
german
situation austin
[Music]
um
thank you
and top left kia that was also
entertaining to watch
yeah i guess today i was very toxic
the little sprinkled here in the short
time you've rocketed to the top of my
list of whole life favorites
keeping yourself your adorably insane
polyglot fin
phoenix i already forgot what polyglot
means
but thank you so much for your support
i'm glad i'm glad to be one of your
favorite
[Music]
applesauce is done thank you for your
really really gracious
gracious patience
gracious that's not the right word
generous just i keep mixing up these two
words
thank you for your generous donation
i want to keep mixing up these ways i'm
really tired now
looking for the top 10 questions
thank you
[Music]
my mouth hurts like the inside of my
mouth
[Music]
this refreshment i'll give you a few
seconds
and then i will refresh and everything
that comes after that i will not read
anymore
please understand last call ding ding
you
photon ray are you
a tales of symphonia fan or what
wasn't that a skill
hold on ray isn't that like a skill
yeah it was a tail skill right i wonder
if that was though
uh yeah for the outmatch for rain i
think was the name
nothing i wonder if that was actually
the reference they were trying to
uh maybe fgo oh
huh i wonder which one oh red super chat
kitty
and you said you were in the uh-huh i
always said i'm an rpg fan
sorry move the microphone
okay i'll refresh now three two
one wait
okay how my neck hurts
ah freaking one girl
[Music]
where did i start
oh
okay
some new some new super jets says show
me your stomach
in german thirsty as hell but okay
i have no idea where i stopped
no idea
[Music]
think here
maybe oh
actually this one already okay okay
found it
optimus prime thank you thank you
what
a great r v
gamer thank you
[Music]
refreshing and endearing i had tons of
fun and i'm glad it seems you feel less
pressure keep up the energy and
burdenate
all the things i should ask you thank
you
thank you
shin
breaks for to be done
[Music]
meme executive of kfb here another fun
stream today
kiara thank you there ah they are always
so fun too
but you remind me of popping g what
now pop into never change all the
pressure
gang says hi hi i can't speak anymore
sorry
hello
[Music]
thank
declining damn
sued that tool a while to figure out but
in topic of moving kelly talked
about moving soon i was thinking it
would be fun for you to to to move into
cover well i would not mind that
she would maybe mind it
but only on the outside not on the
inside i'm sure she would love it
anyway yeah we're not moving in together
it's a bit too early for that even after
millions of years
that we have met in the underworld it's
still a bit too early
by run say jordan john red red zack
tankeshin ice cream cat pancaking
[Music]
foreign
trying to make me say a tongue twister
but it wasn't really much of a tongue
twister
[Music]
okay
people people
something i thought of cynthia japan
nice it's really
super good you should get in contact
with pota and she could either a build
for you
help you build your new computer or b
teach you how to do it yourself
one out of two it's actually really
empowering to be able to work on your
own machine build yourself just not your
situation
thank you but i'm not gonna annoy both
of them fine
like as if there's not other people
who could can help me out with that i'm
sure she's busy and like she doesn't
really haven't even talked before
hmm and i'll definitely get some advice
for someone
from from somewhere else though let's
figure out what i gotta do
thank you thank you though thank you
thank you
[Music]
what's it called again graphics card i'm
too tired
then i feel like oh i can bring that
back to my country when i
know when i need to leave but if it's a
whole pc i cannot
probably break like i have too much
other that i gotta bring back to my
country
yeah so i would prefer but just like
small stuff that i can
put into my hand luggage even
anyway
is
[Music]
brilliant
oh she's buying parts here
wow
the doubt in your reactor yeah because
herpes scene was like crashing in the
middle of the stream
[Music]
many times
no i don't think the airport security
will have a problem if the gpu is in my
if just the gpu is in my hand longer i
don't think it's a problem because i
carried laptops in my hand luggage
before so
hello break past dan kashin takada
kashin memory of twilight thank you
vegan murphy eleven dan kashin
okay
[Music]
is
i can't speak anymore
[Music]
what
oh b movie screen oh my god
see i'm so tired and you give me this
i'll give you a kiss okay i hope you're
happy
thank you
daniel
[Music]
oh wait oh yeah i love the highlights
from nexa thank you so much always
i love the highlights you're doing such
a good job thank you
thank you sharon ghost
rabbit hole i've since checked out the
older whole live idols and i like them
too i look forward to watching your
future cards
thank you and i'm glad i'm glad you're
addicted now
thank you so much
and that was a very tired tired kiss
next eight for one predomination we're
done laptop
me
good
[Music]
in
and there will be a collaboration with
cali
but first i shall sleep
thank you for waiting with me on mario
[Music]
sleep
kill me now
[Music]
yes
so
[Music]
is
i know the mic is on this is my thing
i have a microphone
because i'm too tired to speak up
[Music]
alright
telling me my microphone is not muted
i know
but now i shall say goodbye
canada your microphone i know
you think i just talked to myself like
that
might not be i know
[Music]
those tonight
stupid
ahmed
[Music]