foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
mm-hmm
okay
[Music]
what it's not awake how rude no
it's over you can't just ask someone oh
my God is that a wig or like oh nice wig
like even assuming it's awake how dare
you assume my hair
hahaha
okay
[Music]
no that looks totally natural hey they
told me it looks totally natural now I'm
feeling embarrassed
[Music]
uh
yeah
delayed embarrassed no I'm so
embarrassed they'll call it Pepsi here
no it's not Pepsi it's also not
toothpaste and also not that candy that
you guys have in some places
pepsiara
no and
I'm trying to cosplay Fire Emblem
protagonist
a tide box
uh
if you think about it there's
surprisingly a lot of things that have
this color combination that are you know
in our daily lives very uh common huh
oh yeah
okay let me
oh okay
I am back to Australia
isn't it I won't be back for that long
but while I'm here I want to do many
many many uh
hours of Fire Emblem
because uh four days ago
new Fire Emblem game was released and as
you may remember
um I played Fire Emblem as
my first
RPG welcome back thank you welcome back
thank you
was it my first RPG
or just my first long game I'm not sure
oh was it
oh I remember you almost felt a tutorial
ah yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
this game looks so fun
really I I know some of you guys have
been playing it already
I'm gonna play the end up oh oh
I don't know I haven't thought about
that what did we do
in the other Fire Emblem
did we have Japanese dab on or English
dub
uh
I feel like
um
Japanese
so what should I do now wait let me make
a poll I'll make a poll because I need
to engage
how many puns in terms of engaging well
we have
uh which which dub
okay
Japanese
did that work
uh
is that is that up there
there's I don't think there's a German
dub
who's getting engaged
um yen is good for podcast gang but I'm
a weeb so
you just admit it like that
play Japanese so you can see the
differences in localization
I see
no don't make it 50 50.
[\h__\h] you guys
[Laughter]
ah
okay one one more percent
for Japanese
ah you guys are
not helpful
uh
my usual streaming environment how I
missed it
so nice
though
[Music]
I'm playing with a different Pro
Controller today because I couldn't find
my actual Pro Controller first
so I I unpacked the panda switch
controller that I got
you know for the sponsorship the gift
yeah it's it's nice it's kind of cute
it's very cute
um where the cats happy to see you
um I think movie was very happy and then
chunkers was more like holding back
uh for most of the day
she because like I came back
what was that I came back and
um you know this movie greeted me and
chances was just like you know chilling
but ah we're already going into tangent
[\h__\h] okay just this one tangent and then
we play the game and then we'll see what
happens
um but uh I noticed chunkers
you know my brother took good care of my
kitties I would say uh I think he
cuddled them a lot and that was my main
um concern
uh and I think he lived up to that but
problem
he for three weeks I think I was gone
for three weeks
he did not I guess realize that you have
to brush my cats so the thing is
Smoothie doesn't really need brushing
but chonkers definitely does
um she'll get uh not if you don't brush
her and
[Music]
yeah so if you don't brush her for
a week then she'll she'll get knots and
he didn't brush he was like I have to I
have to brush them I'm like of course
and the breast was even like really like
he knew where it was it's not like he
didn't know where it was it was next to
my bed
um
but yeah uh so she had a lot of knots
and then I immediately like started
brushing her and cut some knots out yeah
no not time to shave no I would never
shave my cut you know
[Music]
yeah I use scissors too yeah yeah so I
cut some knots but then yeah generally
until like later late late in the night
she mostly ignored me
like when I was taking a nap during the
day La yesterday
she wouldn't join me well smoothie would
join me but drunkers wouldn't join me so
sad
but now I went back to normal and
everything's cool she was a little bit
but very cute though both of them very
happy and sweet
um
oh
okay
Japanese dub it is surprised though that
so many people did vote for English
seems like the majority of the chat was
uh actually asking why am I not moving
was asking for a Japanese stuff
well hello
I had to update our thing you know and
maybe oh what's that
oh what is that
hello
Moshi Moshi
I'm moving on my on my phone
it is hollow eiendo so what are you
serious
it's a championship they usually have
Bella dubs in English so
um
well let me um oh wait you probably
oopsie wait did you see something she
probably did hahaha
uh
not so bad yeah yeah it has been seen
before
um let me use maybe I should maybe I'll
use an
um no let me restart
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay let me use different
I updated it because it's the first time
I'm streaming from home again but
ain't looking so good
so let me try
um
this one I guess
I
mm-hmm
and I need to
put on the hat was that possible here
wait that's
that's doing this no
if I use this version I can't put on my
wig
nah inacceptable
let me no no no no no no no
no no no no no no let me just restart
this again maybe it works now
oh yeah it works
okay
ah
hi okay
let's play the game no it's on the wing
no
no no no I'm not a PNG tuber all right
let's open the game uh
I wonder if you will be able to hear
this
foreign
black screen
did you hear that oh yes you did oh yes
you did
oh did you hear that
[\h__\h] did you hear that one too the
second one
first time I'm opening the game so
excited
oh
[Music]
can I play that
well I will
what is this uh
sound is kind of [\h__\h]
oh
do these English letters make sense
new protagonists
it's the first time I see this opening
hi hi
oh they look terrified what's going on
well what what
oh she likes fire
big dragon
we will not have this male protagonist
to now I would play through I think
girls only oh the ring the ring my
precious
there's a ring in this
game too low sound what came to low
sound you mean game sound too low
engage Fire Emblem engage okay I'm gonna
make it louder
that was the opening
game oh yeah wait I didn't think about
that but no I don't think that's why
because you can could always engage at
least in the previous game you could
also engagement they didn't call it
engage but
in the first game you could also get
engaged now
sorry Dragon shot should we look at that
no no Fire Emblem engage
what you you're asking me to engage with
you that's a little bit fast I I don't
even know what you look like I only
heard your voicemail I don't even know
who you are and then he's going to
asking me to engage what the [\h__\h] what
kind of a player but okay let's go
ah
I love idle guard why do they write
emblem Adel guard and then with Dimitri
and Claude in Brackets
as if they're like like Side characters
what is it because they know I played
idle card
they are such
you'll know later
they know who matters
but I didn't get the DLC by the way I
don't feel like it yet emblem Tiki has
been added
ah I haven't thrown your group when you
trigger the event at look outrage
insomnia even without the DLC I'm
receiving the weapon refinement when you
enter oh yeah I didn't I didn't
um I didn't play the phone game and I
didn't bother to
oh
I look artist DLC this is ultiasu oh
okay I didn't bother to
um like install the phone game to
connect it later on with the game just
for some free stuff someone told me
about it thank you for that but I know
and I didn't bother about it yeah so
let's get started
oh select the form well obviously
yeah yeah by the way in case you didn't
know the character designs it's very
obvious for them
damn look at that pretty it really looks
exactly like Mika Mika Mama it's the
artist who drew bales who birthed bales
yeah uh so obviously girl
is her name Alia oh by the way the the
voiceover is probably English right now
we might have to change that earlier
should I change it to my name
I guess oh but okay just this once I
will capitalize the first letter
capitalize
doesn't sound right I will make it big
wow so crap for today thank God
the letters exist holy [\h__\h] is this name
okay characters cannot be displayed that
cannot be displayed will show oh there's
like censored words oh I am allowed and
a birthday
um I think
that's right right
I'm pretty sure about that it's like
difficulty level no more last time we
also did normal definitely need to be
normal
um
I think
follow me let's return the next
battlefall news our last forever every
decision counts wow that one's
interesting because previously we did
Casual obviously because it was my first
Fire Emblem game
ah
I don't I don't know about doing classic
now
hard casual is a good mix
in there
classic is more fun for stream yeah but
then when we lose cute girls
we we don't get them back no
[Music]
Hard Cash winning hot okay okay okay I
will do hard casual heart is at least no
just the middle stage
yeah will I regret this
will I regret this
um
don't let them die wow
unconnected okay start the game are we
sure about this
[Music]
heart is hard well duh
uh connect oh can I do that later too
go back to options why
you can do hard you have experience hey
but it's been a long time but I have you
guys so
um
[Music]
do I have to decide it now
delete
uh wait how do I cancel this stuff here
there we go
whoa
so if we're going back how anticlimactic
so we must end wow
language text English voice
ah Japanese
so my Japanese Bros can also understand
what's going on
[Music]
it was real yeah it just rewinded rewind
we run they don't have rewind in
um
engage
oh she
said go glorious new hongo
okay
not even koala no no it's just Kiana
holy [\h__\h] what's going on I don't
recognize myself
[Music]
yeah it's okay
so this
seemed to be accurate then I guess we're
going for hard
yes I do have experience and we're going
for casual is this changeable later on
too
I'm connected okay
here we go here we go
Mama's daughter
[Music]
let's go
where are we going
I love you
oh yes I love that lady
again
[Music]
ah what wait does the protagonist have a
voice
hey roll the credits I guess because
we're already at the end of the game
yes I don't remember you don't know you
never played your game
and good to see y'all let's do engaging
oh
the water will be over well that's like
it I guess it's gonna be way short I
guess I have to cancel the other Fire
Emblem stream that I have for this week
it's just this one yeah
can I read this how did I do it back in
the day did I read
over the dubbing before
did I read on top of it
I didn't read over the dub did I read
afterwards
that is felt hard to clear the pack for
us we can't let them down
I guess most of them are undubbed
oh
my my grave but I just got married I
didn't even go on honeymoon yet
same thing
okay route the enemy route does that
mean kill
your face
will it now remain by your side
um
moving units to move select your unit
with a then select where to move without
oh this music is really sick
the blue spaces indicator units range of
movement
press a again to confirm your unit okay
okay I remember this
it won't show anymore
okay we'll go straight straight right
why would we not go straight let's go
straight
after you move a unit you will see a
list of commands if you do not want to
take an action select wait
ah I can't attack from here I guess I'm
in like a close combat
you want to give my brother a shout out
I was kind of the same with him back in
2020 but that was it and you were also
taking care of cats for three weeks
can you probably mean looking for a job
right
thank you thank you thank you
okay waiting
[Music]
and once all of units have taken action
the player face ends and the enemy phase
begins
once both phases are completed the turn
ends the next turn begins with a new
plant phase
that beat Jam is really cool oh
he's gonna attack
oh let's try
to attack move your unit close to an
enemy and select attack
you can also begin an attack with a if
you move your cursor over an enemy and
see a attack
oh wait no I guess first me and then
whatever eh
like just standing here would be fine
right but wait was it a vein with fire
on them that you can like
get more damage if you attack them from
behind or so was that a thing
can't go behind but can go sideways
yeah no no yes facing doesn't matter and
there's not in this game
oh
oh okay
oh all right uh
what what no I mean
I
am I Am The Liberation and I shall
Liberate the world from you
foreign
[Music]
oh we attack a second time automatically
what I was a like um a counter to his
attack engage
when the engagement is full select
engage
your unit will merge with the selected
emblem and gain access to special engage
weapons
loves a set of special skills the
engaged State lasts for free turns oh
okay where where is engage
where is where is engage what
here okay just click on myself several
times
uh what What's it called pixel arts on
the bottom left cute and I'm a dragon
apparently
what the heck is engaged well we'll see
now it's like I guess just like a we
combine our powers and then we're
stronger and I guess you can have
different emblems and then get stronger
in different ways
thank you
oh
[Music]
and we're engaging with old Fire Emblem
characters which is cool but uh it it to
me it feels like
something you would do
for like an All-Stars
phone game
sing ah so let's go
it's an anniversary game oh that makes
sense we're now connected and can
unleash a powerful attack together
say my name say my name hello star rash
engagements can use a pal can use
powerful engagement text engage attacks
are abilities that new units can use
once each time they engage
for example Lord Sarah steals heavy
damage to users engage attack select
both star rush and 11. we're gonna lose
anyway aren't we oh it's all a dream
oh
Colgate Jammy came Colgate Chand light
because her colors are lighter now
here we go
oh do I choose
this weapon my physical attack and hit
is up but
speed and a bow is down
but I'm guessing that's what they want
me to do
let's go
but
wow
I thought I was scripted to lose
you have nothing to celebrate
this itself
but I did
[Music]
hey this tutorial went way better than
the one previously
thanks to you this world was saved and
my work here is complete
came clear oh yeah that was fast not
that I will always be with you and that
will stand together again as we did this
day
foreign
[Music]
I don't know I only know you from Super
Smash Brothers
that you will remember all of us who
took up arms to fight by your side
the twelve emblems
same I mean I know like who he is and
that is like part of a big fire emblem
game and like a main character right but
the first time I saw him I'm pretty sure
it's from Super Smash Brothers
um
yeah Roy Roy too sounds familiar yeah
yeah yeah okay let's actually save file
what
same same
wow well I am moth
oh
that looks like Bales love those eyes
huh
hey
[Music]
oh
did you know
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oh okay because it just saved right
uh
oh [\h__\h] uh what
do I
I just have to load it right
[Laughter]
did you know that people used to sleep
in with in beds like that with like the
curtains around in order to keep um the
heat within there because the houses
used to be really
um cold and they preserved heat in there
with the cream I just wanted to tell you
that
and you're welcome yeah not really those
mosquito curtains more like proper
curtains you know even even bigger
houses from like kings and queens even
those they would do that because uh the
houses were built with such cold
material that doesn't save heat so they
oh and also like families of like six or
so would even sleep on the same big bed
that's why the beds used to be bigger
yeah they would sleep in the same bed in
order to like save more heat as well
ages
I'm so smart
one more time
hmm thank God I saved Fred before
not gonna press anything
bales
[Music]
that seem like brothers and sisters
foreign
[Music]
no I'm Divine Phoenix not Dragon I can't
see Guy
[Music]
she's like yeah
I like her face expressions
cute
wakey wakey you know what you do when
you wake up you brush your teeth with
Colgate hmm
right
[\h__\h]
which all this rock is about
oh
metal sounds
do
design Phoenix Kiana
it's a miracle
and not America the Divine One
awake at long last
ing
then I might live to see you standing
before me what an honor
what the [\h__\h] are you new phone who this
is cute
oh
foreign
hello survander
[Music]
.com
there is no need to address me in such
simply Vanda will do
that sounds a little bit like Canada
who said buku h
[Music]
we were telling the truth
I don't believe I got your names
[Music]
can you hear it
sounds a little bit like her like maybe
her if she had like a younger brother
we're so excited we forgot to introduce
ourselves
my name is Clan
Clan I would I would say that sounds
nice
[Music]
Glenn I can roll with but frown I don't
like that name what a weird name
but okay we got cute twins very cute I
like their designs
[Music]
how long is forever
to chat and shadows I doubt there's a
single Fram in the chat
that's too much of the Phoenix our
mission is to protect and provide for
you
generation after generation of our
predecessors wait for you to rise from
your slumber
I am astonished to see it has finally
happened
foreign
was I was already like sleeping since
then
what the hell what
oh you slept fasting years
[Music]
Divine Dragon Monarch as long we waited
to stay
well you a Divine Dragon yourself have
awakened it surely signifies great
things wait I have a mom that's like
alive
foreign
[Music]
sleep
typical protagonist doesn't remember
[\h__\h]
that's so typical
but I don't even know who I am
is
the Amnesia
fret not social abscess and memory are
to be expected after sleeping for so
long
you are a Divine Dragon a member of a
royal family of dragons referred as
deities
[Music]
rules of the Holy Land of lifers Rufus
what should we call it Lifest or luffos
foreign
[Music]
you divine one are her only child
Daddy
um
I feel like I can almost remember but
wait sorry is your mom still alive or
not
because
if she's still alive she had a thousand
years to make a few more heirs
and she didn't bother
I'm the only child that's not very safe
for such a like important role
wouldn't you want to try to make a few
more errors
[Music]
oh no spoilers okay
tell me right so
um
normally after a thousand years you
would expect for the mother maybe to be
dead but I mean it's difficult being
it's a Divine Dragon so who knows how
long they live
father didn't survive the pregnancy does
it have to be him though
it have to be him
I'm too smart for this game
do not travel yourself trying to bring
it all back at once because this will be
a long long ass game and you have more
than enough time to remember everything
that you lost
I've heard many a tale of your kindness
nobility and bravery your unflinching
heroism
[Music]
that's a lot to live up to did he always
speak more in Japanese so far
[Music]
will be thrilled to see you
perhaps a reunion will help stir your
memories is the Queen the queen is not
my mom right
it's just a queen okay
I believe
oh she is okay okay well done there you
go she's alive
oh
it's an art of ready
that's art it's not moving okay
in the sky
all this time I've been sleeping in the
sky
you have yes it's a place where you
sunburn is known as to some Neil um
The Fortress built upon an Airborne
Island to ensure your safety well that
is very safe indeed
those fluffy clouds man
and it can never rain because you're
always about above the the clouds the
rain clouds so nice always nice weather
[Music]
it is perhaps the most secure place in
all of areas only a select few can set
foot there
[Music]
I see you free lived there with me
always
[Music]
we spend our time caring for you and
managing things around the thumbnails
[Music]
so we work as hard as we can to keep it
ship shape
you may believe not every mythical one
okay so smart as our attention for any
thousand year power naps and make sure
she would have a harem of 10 minimum at
least one kid for him
yeah like oh my God like really I follow
like
especially
British uh
kings and queens history
a lot
and yeah you need many heirs to protect
yourself because
um you know they will also be a target
for assassination
in all kinds of ways and the more the
merrier yeah many many a heirs
true it's true one is just
one it's just Reckless just making one
baby when he was
when you imported position it's just
stupid
Rebecca thank you thank you thank you hi
you really like it's over hey I love you
too welcome uh we'll be today will be a
long stream I think you know just got
back and I missed streaming so
we'll take it easy and we'll we'll you
know inhale this story with an inhaler
hardcore inhaling
[Music]
foreign
but like
that no if I use your logic then that
would mean that an intercourse of a
dragon takes more than the Intercourse
along a time than the Intercourse of a
normal human being
for you to
for
because
okay I understand that thousand years
you know it's short if a dragon needs
like
um in human time 50 days for one
intercourse but no I assume they just
need you know the normal amount of time
anyway
oh maybe the pregnancy takes a long time
well it's time for Googling how long
does a a pregnancy
of a dragon list
bad
oh oh come on
I guess we do have dragons in real life
X will then take up to nine months like
humans develop before baby dragons are
ready to hatch
ET full-time just like humans so
yeah gestation for lizard egg can last
up to 12 films as for how many eggs we
see clutches of various sizes and future
except
[Laughter]
dragons are not Divine beasts well
unfortunately there is no lore on how
long the pregnancy of a Divine Dragon
takes but I will take this as comparison
as a sample
we're all family members visit us all
the time we'll visit you really okay
at deeply religious country oh [\h__\h]
visit especially often I was like
culture
[Music]
they pray next to you like this then
they just talk for a while like they're
chatting to a friend
foreign
[Music]
unless I already did Am I Dreaming
knew that I remind you that you're in
the presence of the Divine Dragon but
[\h__\h]
how many times
Divine one please forgive this
embarrassing breach of decorum what the
[\h__\h]
what does that mean I don't know
[Music]
the castle
the Divine Dragon Monarch is there you
said
I suppose a thousand years have passed
since you've been home
don't worry we'll be right there with
you
supposed to be flaming English which is
French for flame but flaming is actually
that exactly that word is German for
um Flame
so I guess they probably were trying to
give her a German name
[Music]
ano Co
yeah but now with art it's with l
but if you write it with L even in
Japanese it turns into an R
so maybe that was look back translated
or so I don't know
oh
in Japanese let's just put on I don't
think it has anything to do with the
German word though to be honest
especially if it's written Fudan
in Japanese
that sounds more like French though yeah
[Music]
you can hold my hand if you like
thank you
oh what's the engagement ringa
that's the one thing you question about
yourself
a family marami Belle thank you how long
have I been wearing this ring since
before I fell asleep
that blue stone it reminds me of that
super old Fire Emblem protagonist
that I think I saw in Super Smash
Brothers before
um
oh
what what what are those
[Music]
foreign
videos
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
look scattered all over the map cool
so dangerous
[Music]
let me fight
all right
I will
okay let's go
let's go get him play a face
oh
yeah
oh yeah I didn't even realize that that
was there bushes we can be in the bushes
oh yeah
the rain provides various effects from
Battle For example it is harder to land
a hit on the unit positioned in a picket
pickets also caused more movement for
ground units to pass through
you can see terrain effects in the
information section at the top left
corner follow the screen uh use terrain
to your advantage in battle okay
[Music]
um
all right
I guess
I'll go ahead right away and attack this
one
attack
wait I forgot can I move all my units
or just one oh yeah I can move up okay
so oh you look at that students have
various types such as Cavalry Quee Adept
and mystical what the [\h__\h] is clear
depth units can use the chain guard
command to redirect attacks
and I just sent allies to themselves but
we'll have to test it out each tag has
different advantages check the unit's
type on the stats screen
what what is she a dragon
users gain additional effects on
engagement well she's a special case
Capital units have the highest movements
I remember that
their High Mobility allows them to cross
the map quickly to land a first blow or
Aid an ally
she adapts martial arts
do I have like I wish I had an AOE
attack I guess I don't
all right
[Music]
maybe I should have attacked him from
inside the ticket but I don't know if
that was even a choice right now oh wow
oh I can't control the top two okay
[Music]
how could I you guys are like dying
thank you
[Music]
cringers are Alice I can't control oh
nice because of the airbow a voice
avoids plus 30 years
nice come come on attack me try if you
wanna
face ah they do what they think they
need to do
[Music]
you are right
wow
it's not safe for you here Retreats the
castle
hey
leaving all the works to us
two miles thank you
[Music]
critical hit avoidance Dodge avoiding
his syndrome
that's just for critical hits
[Music]
yeah you just turned It's very effective
I'm not Banner get all these it is
oh no I'm good I'm good vulner that's
what you call it unit of zero hit points
can no longer fight use items like
vulneros or restore HP use of all the
way select the item's command
okay well
[Music]
should I just finish this one off or
should I walk away and attack him in the
hopes that he will run after me and
attack me and then I'll counter attack
and then kind of get two attacks you
know
you know what I'm thinking
I'll finish them off
tutorial yeah so what
already have to practice thinking skills
[Music]
he is gonna run after me isn't it
well I like my logic of going away too
you know
because he'll just come after me and
I'll just kill him with a counter attack
[Music]
if one sound
foreign
[Music]
there he gets another kill
I gotta put that Bram you run the
monsters don't scare me
oh you should be scared never hit and
you're probably dead
well there
yeah
they just say continue running
okay so I'll
send him after this one because he has
more movement
can he go there it's kind of far ah but
now he will attack
now he'll attack a
and she's close enough
you better not miss this time lady
please
[Music]
this is why I would be game over if I
chose the other place
laughs
[Music]
so dramatic hey hey this is not classic
okay this is casual this is really How
It Ends I'm so sorry everyone
[Music]
the protagonist can't die
so what you telling me
[\h__\h]
I did use hard mode though so please
keep that in mind retaining speech
Dragon reset ESPN try again
eh
why would I
do I get extra ASP this way
oh oh the mission objective was that I
don't die yeah
okay
ah yeah
[Music]
um
and make sure you don't get stuck
forever at all
how embarrassing all right all right
okay
[Music]
it's not my fault she was missing uh
oh but you don't miss okay you don't
have to show me that again
[Music]
come on
nice I think wait is this like
are is this gonna be the exact same way
as before I wonder
[Music]
I am in the bush I mean the other one's
in the bush at least
good
delicious oh my God it's like like an
album ring where you guys were like stop
growing stop rolling stop dodging
Christmas two times missed in a row on
my side
oh that's really low damage dude one
damage to Vander It's Not Gonna Get You
far
e
[Music]
okay okay I will now not run away
take down this enemy first
okay give me those experience
okay and now
um
[Music]
so also take you down first
way too common
um
oh cause he's in a bush
that was a strong move and we were not
even in a bush
okay now we have to run after that dude
um how far okay
okay but that already makes him attack
me and we are in the bush
and then you
thank you
what if I go here okay he will not
attack me if I'm here supposedly
all right okay so far no damage on her
by the way
this is the greens anyway
s
[Music]
somehow yes you can remember oh
he's speaking to me
Kiara
he's talking to me oh my God yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
a lot of things are going on here there
you go you must remember Kiara
I was pressing all kinds of buttons
book now
um
yeah how dare you forget oh
oh
foreign
wow
[Music]
who is Mrs emblem
really that's all you got girls
I can't be that strong
okay it's for the drama for the drama
come on guys show me the power is
supposedly have
[Music]
something
yeah
you're setting him off already
he didn't even use your special attack
who is she talking to oh
[Music]
I guess we're not going into a mental
facility then
hey thank God
[Music]
we might just make it will you join us
Oh I thought he was leaving
Motorola
of course I will fight alongside you
from here forward you Ally until the
very end
king of ambulance a unit can fight
alongside an emblem this is called being
synced
while sync the unit has increased power
and access sync skills
there's a perfectly placed Bush right
there
so go go there I'm with Mark strikes
quickly and repeatedly dominating foes
with his Nimble Grace
the sync skill perceptive makes it
easier to avoid enemy counter-attacks oh
the engaged weapon rappier deals bonus
damage against Cavalry and armored
enemies okay those look pretty armored
to me
the engage skill Divine speed adds an
additional less powerful attack
engage attack loads of rust is a
powerful and blendingly fast forward
blows
what should I do
engage
oh
yeah engage
which one are we using though okay do I
choose now okay
I guess I choose now
what about the skill oh
[Music]
why and also why did you leave him with
two HP
a Hulk
all right no problem
moving
so well
[Music]
you need to charge
I feel like I remember in the previous
game
Caroline defense ah no Maybe not maybe
not wasn't that weak after a minute
but looking back it kind of feels weak
but
[Music]
feel all those misses
Paladin is strong wait was it
repelidan's a thing in this game or am I
just like thinking about the games now
gosh
[Music]
no more attack is fine has like two HP
left
am I the first one in whole life to play
the game I didn't see anyone else
starting the game yet and I even waited
four days
what's up with that but I saw like
surprisingly way more
members interested in Fire Emblem this
time around than last time
so Cali was interested
crony two red bells too right and odena
too
hmm
I was surprised
I thought like most of them wouldn't
touch it because they normally all don't
really play these long JRP cheese most
of the time although Persona is an
exception
hmm
yeah yeah I know crony said before she's
a fire emblem fan and I was back then I
remember I was like oh let's go
Coolio
[Music]
they're busy playing persona well
they're probably gonna stay busy for a
while
to find one
oh yeah and sorry this all happened
because we ran ahead
well you better
learn some battle skills so otherwise
I'm not gonna hang with you anymore
I'm the one who should apologize you put
yourselves in Danger trying to protect
me
it's such a relief
foreign
[Music]
I think that's your mom
that that might be your mom
oh yeah right across her head no nice
oh
[Music]
mommy mommy
I love her design mommy but she looks
like she could end up being evil
actually she looks like you know on
first glance of course you know she
looks
like a powerful good Queen but that
design looks like it could have an evil
side to it
um
[Music]
she's pretty like well don't don't
that's not spoiled for people who don't
play it but yeah yeah
thank you for saving us
ah
gotchi what a choice
Mommy Mommy let me look at you well well
pretty
I gotcha hi
wow
Mommy
cute that's colorful like hard to hug
her though I think with all that [\h__\h]
armor around her whoa
oh that's kind of cute
um
she really sounds like an older version
of chocolate to me
when I sensed you had awoken I flew here
as fast as my wings could carry me
way longer in Japanese
okay
[Music]
foreign
maybe it's a good thing I forgot
everything or maybe it's a bad thing
even though everything's traumatic but
then I forgot that she's evil
I take this to me and you've forgotten
everything
[Music]
I suppose it's to be expected a thousand
years is a very long time
explained that I've been sleeping since
since some more that happened back then
over a thousand years ago
yes you suffered a terrible wound and
because of that he's
a
wounded
or anything not anymore
[Music]
don't fret a young one I will speak to
you of all you have forgotten
regardless of what you remember I simply
I'm glad to have you back my dear child
[Music]
hi
still this isn't the reunion you've
hoped for okay now see here here the
Japanese dub was way shorter she just
said yes good idea
oh don't worry about me it's Solace
enough to just hear that sweet voice of
yours
[Music]
once more into your eyes what lovely
colors they are Kiara oh
[Music]
however I don't look like you at all
what's that about am I adopted I stop it
at the battle you can explore the map
freely and Converse with your allies oh
keep an eye out for items on the ground
to finish exploring even move to the
exit or press plus to open the menu and
select the part
huh
how big is the area I can run around in
all of this I know oh
[Music]
no just like close by
Adam that's
oh
Lisa would go nuts over these nuts I
said it
[Music]
looks so incredible on the battlefield
of course you did you're the Divine
Phoenix
what did you get injured at all I hope
not if any feeling though I'm fantastic
at it ah you're a Healer now hold up the
boy I was a bit I was a bit worried but
we made it through we're safe because of
you to find Phoenix
hey what happened to that guy who popped
out out of your ring he's like your old
lover or so well
jealous
it hardens me to see you and queen
lomara reunited that last the memory
loss may have come as a surprise but she
seems elated nonetheless
let me look at her mommy wow
yeah but do you see what I mean like
with that design
they're trying to make her look like a
good person
but I definitely see the evil in the
design
look on a cool design
is
[Music]
the point of it yeah it's stuff like
that like her weird shoulder floaty
thing is
I don't see it
you can say about anything no I don't
think so I will
we will see
in 20 episodes when she turns evil and
you I'm gonna be like I told you I told
you and I think it's a purpose
[Music]
Define evil
this has this evilness inside of her
I know this because like they are Richie
character designs I've seen millions of
them
[Music]
many of them
and I can sense it you guys think I'm
crazy now but
trust me bro
I've got experience
also I've got chips and you know do you
know um the chocolate called joto
um g-i-o-t-t-o
I really like those
um
but I found a special edition in the
supermarket
that I had to buy because it's like
it has a special taste that I've never
seen before
but it's like um a special
um Christmas cookie taste symptom
I don't I don't know what to call that
cookie in English because I don't think
it exists outside of Europe
but it's kind of like a cinnamon cookie
a star-shaped cinnamon cookie with a
sugar coating on top
and that's the taste of the joto
Christmas going over time yeah I was
surprised to see it I never saw like a a
Time limited special edition of Johto so
I'm excited to taste this
um
anyway I'm so very very happy to see you
it's like a dream
however we had passed that linger for
too long there may be more enemies
lurking about like me
huh
[Music]
did you hear that laugh
I think that you don't need any more
evidence that she's evil
any more items or was that one the only
one let's go it's cool you can run
around on the battlefield that you used
afterwards so it didn't have that I
think in the previous one right
pretty short that wasn't the thing
that's cool
hmm
that art it shows Adam oh no
[Music]
oh no I missed what or is that the one I
already took
um
what the [\h__\h] there's a bird
what there's a I don't see you it's a
pigeon I can't interact with it though I
thought that was an item
no no hold on no I think we got it all
uh it looks like you guys
oh that's how we go there well it's like
a
speed Uber those wings
interesting Dragon design how did Mika
Mama designed the dragon too I wonder
she definitely did all of the character
designs I've seen like
uh like a sheet with all the designs
foreign
[Music]
hmm but it's a cool design love the hair
well thank you it's my real hair
[Music]
oh
this is
Amazon
probably
is
can we pass
do we have to fly right
evil dragon
that is
[Music]
Dragon form I guess
no no hold on
it's funny when the dragon talks so
normally
[Applause]
skip what's there to skip there's
nothing happening
yeah it's kind of weird
[Laughter]
with the voice whoa
[Music]
here we are we are saved Within These
Walls
[Music]
at my online mode most of the time guys
I'm so sorry I know you like want to
cancel me for that excuse me
so this is lapis leave us Castle it's
beautiful
she didn't say that she said for you I
want to say welcome back home Kiara see
I'm gonna auto correct her
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm home
Arigato yes you are thank you
cry mommy
I feel overwhelmed with joy I may cry
thank you for all you've done you are
worthy stewards indeed
new and your predecessors watching over
my child all these years
I am ever so grateful how come they can
live for such a long wait nah
they don't live for that long right they
don't have such a long lifespan it's
just because the Vander He also
mentioned that there was a different guy
appointed first in his position right
you saw that thank you for all the
memberships
[Music]
generation yeah yeah okay
you are too kind
of
nice of you to say that I'm starting to
feel woozy
um
we just got praised by Queen Lamar
herself
the happiness of this moment aside I am
troubles to see the corrupted here in
life
thanks for renewing your membership for
two the corrupted
those enemies you were fighting out on
the grasslands
I didn't like those things one day
just sign up that made my blood run cold
the corrupted dark corpse is revived by
an evil power
the Bell Dragon used them as his
soldiers in the world before the start
of that bitter conflict
had known peace
youth Cinema
but then a dark presence emerged Sombra
somebody
and oh I just thought you know
[Laughter]
that's crash Tony
aren't you guys Happy Anna is back huh
aren't you happy
[Music]
as you should be
finally
did she say something
interesting in her last stream
[Music]
in her Chit Chat stream
what kind of question is that right
question to ask
[Music]
laughs
you're saying you didn't watch it well
you can watch like all holy and streams
or what
[Music]
no I'm just wondering I saw him she she
killed her setup or something
um
the valkyrie connect one
it arrived finally why did hers arrive
so much later
[Music]
that can be set on
laughs
my tireless searching
we could not determine where we'd come
from I wanted to make a joke about
tireless
[Music]
but I guess it would be too much of a
rage man
and let's get it
but seeing the distraction he brought
there was no doubt of his evil
intentions
foreign
[Music]
once more this may be a sign of his
return
[Music]
I wonder if it doesn't mean a
coincidence that you awaken this all
this unfolds
I'm here to save the world
foreign
[Music]
child
the mirror
I guess I'm not the only one he listens
to being called by my mommy and he
immediately comes out and shows his face
it's been glad
it's been quite some time Lumera
that it has thank you for Lending your
Aid against the corrupted
you're welcome but of course I could
help only because your child remembered
me
you know it is possible the others are
awake now just as I am
[Music]
have you heard of my waifu idle guard
perhaps I would like to see her again I
don't need you I want the little card
please
perhaps you're all right
sorry but what do you mean who's awake
there's something I should show you
follow me oh are they like in like tanks
or so stored in tags oh no
it's not that creepy
[Music]
that's like
that
the best ones behind the DLC okay I will
buy it for 30 bucks man
box for adult parts
unbelievable
I will do it very little time though I
think like what the [\h__\h] though
okay I'm gonna test this chocolate now
by the way what is this place
the rainbow it is where the emblem rings
are enshrined oh can I switch them out
those of the Holy Night of the sage Lord
and of the Azure twins rest here and if
I had the DLC would she say more
universe
no money no honey
she wouldn't uh-huh okay okay
as well as the Ring of the princess X
South and finally the Ring of the
instructor edelard
thank you
h12 within an emblem ring as marf
resides in the ring of the hero King
hero King
hero
hero king ring okay I'm testing this oh
very cinnamony smell ah
wow
that doesn't taste like joto anymore and
oh wow it's good though
hmm
oh
um
wow
it's like
you know those crumbs around the joto
are now just crumbs of a Christmas
cookie
good stuff
um
so counting marks there are six emblem
Rings wow yeah
six here and six
entrusted to the other countries oh we
have to go pick them up there
as a precautionary measure oh see I see
yeah so then you don't like immediately
get all of them in one spot when you're
evil like like you
what do you mean
the emblems Grand World altering power
to Heaven has all 12 rings
it is
for Generations the Divine dragons use
this power to ensure peace and
prosperity in aliens
that was how we locked away the Bell
dragon
foreign
I think
precisely the Rings offer their power
but once every Thousand Years
so isn't that that why I woke up after a
thousand years
because my rings kind of helped me wake
up
but wait so
if I woke up earlier than that let's
just say I woke up 500 years earlier
that marf wouldn't have helped me
[Music]
it's a long cool down yeah what the hell
a massive coincidence I'm sure
so that's why I sleep that long
um
five more minutes yeah you waited nine
thousand nine hundred ninety nine years
and so on so many minutes but but
and just uh five more minutes until it's
really thousand years and then I'll come
out
at which time the Divine Dragon travels
across aliens to collect them from each
nation's ruler
ah so that's me so now it's the time
that I collect all the Rings and then
get rid of the evil stuff and then go
back to sleep and fast news later we do
the same thing again huh oh
you're gonna do it if a thousand years
having passed since last time I was
planning to carry it out myself
[Music]
dragon is after the Rings the emblems
may be summoned before I arrive
this comment
Ary
my child so late who does it now you or
me I guess it's gonna be me I'm not
talking
oh you must be talking about the phrase
that popped into my head
an invocation you mean what was it
shine on emblem of Beginnings
I wasn't even thinking about it the
words just fell from my mouth
um
foreign
that was how you summoned Maya
so not okay what was your focus your
intention when you spoke those words
I didn't want to lose them I want to
protect them
your focus was on helping others
remember that intention whenever you
summon emblem
not to keep the power for yourself you
understand
may protect others
I just did it for stream content that
one dance
okay we're gonna do it here
[Music]
you need to train your body and mind to
unleash an emblem's full power
is there school again in this game or no
because I like the school life
you'll be aiding my child in this battle
against me
even in a practice battle I could not
turn my weapon on you
no oh man
um
please do put your heart into it I know
I will
oh
I think she's into that kind of stuff
tried the church
maybe it will
I will
[Music]
oh she's something she some of them
from plants and rocks they don't look
like they're made out of plants and
rocks
their abilities are the same drop your
guard and you could be hurt
you're really unsettling can we try to
do something else
give me the chills
you are my child the protector of all
the Divine Phoenix Kiara
okay we can't be baby anymore
order
I'd like to bring us victory
thank you everyone
so okay there's two little minis in
front of her
um
so I will take down the small ones first
I guess
Divine when some of these enemies are
carrying long range oh okay
therefore they can write with arrows
upon us from afar
aha each weapon has a set range above a
range of two can attack enemies two
spaces away
weapons with a range of one cannot count
to decent attacks um weapons with a
range of two cannot counter adjacent
attacks
[Music]
how far can you go oh you can reach her
all right then I might do that what
interrupting me
sing this enemy ax wielders are at a
disadvantage against swords yeah I
wasn't gonna go to him with my horse
swords are strong against axis axis
against lances and then lances against
swords and what's strong against the
bows
identities
if you have met your well you can break
their fighting stance for an advantage
in combat
[Music]
Magic
okay
try it strike the sword after their
stance is broken they'll be open to
further attack
aha inflict the brake status on an enemy
by Landing an attack with a weapon that
has an advantage broken units cannot
counter attack until after their next
combat oh this is your chance to attack
swords have advantage over access access
overlances and lenses over swords
I have advantage of a Bows Oh tomes and
knives oh
Hearts somebody else said that any melee
I was wrong
okay well I
I am gonna go here because he can go so
far and quickly take down this
fabrication hopefully
[Music]
but you left it with 2hp however we
stand right in front of him he can't
attack me back right yeah yeah
and then whoever you
[Music]
fabrication
you can see how much damage you'll do I
see it
your problem I do see it
what am I supposed to do
can't change how much damage he does
you see so it's as strong against axes
always keep such weapon advantages in
mind
enemies
a good time
foreign
[Music]
magic is often effective against enemies
with higher physical defense oh
Miss cleaners ignored terrain bonuses to
a foe's void rate when attacking with
magic
oh mystical units can land attacks from
a distance even when an enemy B should
be hard to hit
oh
well I wanna
wait everything that's red is in my
attack range right
I can stay far away if I wanna
I'll go here wait no
okay never mind
no ah huh
never mind now isn't anything red is in
my attacker okay I had to get kind of
close to take him down
[Music]
good job
okay okay
when they fight close to each other they
have a friendship increase
[Music]
with her
[Applause]
you know what I can do some mean healing
with my stuff not only that I can take
some incoming hits for nearby allies but
it's fine when I do yeah
is that all you can do normal attack no
stapes are atoms with which your units
can help allies or hinder enemies only
certain classes like martial monks can
use them a heel staff for example
restores an ally it depends on the
weapon not on her skills
stamps are useful but they break after a
certain numbers what
oh but I guess that's the case for all
weapons and
is it
she can punch hmm
uh
it wasn't Queen what was it what did you
guys say she
[Music]
she only staves have charges uh-huh okay
normal weapons don't break okay okay
cheap
adapt units can use chain guard to
protect adjacent allies from Attack
[Music]
let's with chain guard the Ally does not
take damage instead Chi adapt takes
damage equal to 20 of their own Max HP
okay I don't know what you're saying
it's only available if she adaptunes age
principle okay well you guys have to
tell me when to do that
brain too slow for this I don't need to
heal anyone everyone's full HP
I'll stay in the bush
attack hmm
but no one's a Jay scent now so I'll
just wait
can attack but probably not very strong
oh [\h__\h]
oh thank God
because he's the weakest link in this
Triangle Man rude
and I can't attack
[Music]
and she's gonna attack me wait if I
engage
it's for free turns but if I engage do I
get a bigger range I don't think I got a
bigger range so I shouldn't engage yet
right
[Music]
bushes
no okay
I'll wait
[Music]
oh yeah
I mean when how far can you get oh yeah
you can attack
let's do that I hope I won't regret
though not so damaged to take any 15
damage that's halfway pretty good
sorry my queen I must hurt you yeah my
child tonight you must feel that we're
all as best as you can attack me
let's go
I missed
unbelievable
[Music]
but we make use of our heel for the
first time it's not a full heel but
pretty decent so I wonder if I go here
she's probably gonna go to attack the
Mages and she
come out there
maybe like block her ah I can't really
though
[Music]
I can't go into that bush
um
I want to attack but I'm worried that
she's so strong she's got on like one
hit Clan
[Music]
let's arrange after I move right
I'm gonna probably be in one hit
if I stand here I wonder if she's gonna
walk around and attack me but she would
have to walk through bushes so maybe she
can't go that far
I'll try this
I'm gonna risk it do some damage
[Music]
he's gonna miss he's gonna miss
oh okay she went for our lady
let's see how much our countenance
okay count the girl Focus
and we're gonna take her down with the
next hit I'm pretty sure Dragon child
level two
[Music]
do we get healed after fights or do we
stay with this HP
[Music]
question mark
okay
[Music]
so possibly could take her down if you
don't miss
you okay
[Music]
between chapters
I didn't need to
I couldn't reach her before that's why I
didn't engage because why would I engage
when I can't attack her anyway
[Music]
yeah
chill
fantastic work you fought together
splendidly
look at plenty years
let's move on right over there a moment
[Music]
well something
more
this time I'll be more Hands-On
identified as if
she's using a ring
[Music]
I'm inviting an old friend to join us
What's it gonna be
ah
[Music]
um I might have seen his face before
looks like an adult morph
ew I mean yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
I am
if you require strength and swiftness
I'm all too happy to oblige
or how about you say your name he looks
like a strong opponent
[Music]
emblem has their own abilities when
allied with them you can call upon their
unique powers and skills whatever
Secrets it won't be the same as Mars
open
uh we so far
my wrap year is effective against
Cavalry I like those enemies I like
those enemies over there okay okay
once we engage you can use my weapon try
it against that foe
okay okay
what's that
emblem energy sometimes an emblem's
energy lingers in the space if a sink
unit finishes their action or weights on
a space containing emblem energy their
engaged meter will feel completely oh
[Music]
ah family from cigarette is only Japan
uh-huh
this mission is a fun one why
let me see what are you you have an ax
so I remember sword is strong against
that let me
danger radius when you place the curse
on an enemy you can you will see yeah
okay I don't know that impressive to see
the danger ranges of all the animated
ones okay thank you but I'm gonna move
over here
and attack
am I synced now or
[Music]
I'm a synced right so when I stand there
now this happens automatically right
it will charge
the thing right
yes I am synced
not a good attack why
[Music]
lots of contact if you get hit there
okay
well then let's not charge
an attack from the bushes
[Music]
we're broken though
maybe we didn't have to worry about that
because we would break him anyway hmm
[Music]
some I'm gonna go stand in these bushes
to wait
I was fine before I mean some comments
made me uncertain
stand here attack
let's go can't attack back
oh we killed him
ah lovey-dovey
I let her join too
no heel
um yeah I'll Stand I'll stand here
I don't know about shielding them
well does that mean that she takes the
uh she takes the damage instead but I
don't know about that man because like
she has way less HP than like for
example the horse guy
[Music]
chain guard the weak guide
then I would have to stand here
twenty percent
the guy attacked is zero oh okay
did I chain guard correctly
well he wasn't shot anyway
oh
hey
I did chiangai damage okay okay
well they all came
to see me but I feel like
I'm gonna
attack him with her
oh wait he's a lance oh oh [\h__\h] Lance is
strong against sword I'm guessing now
[\h__\h] I thought that would be smart
can I rewind
[\h__\h] no I wish I could rewind
okay
um
then I guess the Mage gets the excuse
wrong game
Nice kill though nice kill
okay I was gonna
Advance with him
but this dude's in the bushes too
hmm
[Music]
ah
she cut an eye
are they gonna come over here
not if I stand here
[Music]
I might stay here after all
okay
yeah the free houses didn't have also
nice mess didn't have the weapon
triangle
thank god oh any of the ones that are
adjacent to her
oh that's really low
and look at that
I did not expect her to go out of the
way to see me here
oh oh what's that because of the chain
guard
oh that was lucky that I did that
expect unexpected the power of wishes
but he wasn't standing on the bus was he
Lord is remarkably Swift perhaps perhaps
we should be grateful this is a mock
battle
damn son oh
yeah heart mode be hard man okay
um
I would like to uh heal
uh
[Music]
anyway
and get in the energy pool but it's so
far now
it's so far away is that worth it
[Music]
uh
what was that
it's worth okay
and I just wait here because I have no
other choice
um
[Music]
go in Bush
attack
um
[Music]
let's Miss
and then
I guess it's best to finish him huh
[Music]
there's no person s now though
oh wait on the left side
the the hit percentage is is that so
seven percent says I'm missing
[Music]
okay
oh and he can't counter and even nice
okay at least one damage down one enemy
down
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
she broke me
oh no that's the Healer
oh [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h] that's um a problem Oh not my
mate but he's in the bush oh
[Music]
um do I ignore the horsies and just go
all out on the lady
I'm fully charged at least
but look at my HP
I might die
die
actually wait if I get countered then
that's dangerous can I heal from here
no
okay
[Music]
at least heal first then make her move
over
I would say
[Music]
because with free HP that's too
dangerous
oh
should I let him attack first but he
can't even reach
[Music]
you can't even reach
can I attack from here no okay
is this in the bush because there's a
little bit of the Bush on my field I
don't know if it's if it's considered
[Music]
in a bush in a picket
no that's what I thought but from here I
can't attack from here I can
she'll likely go for him though right
but that's maybe good like even if he
dies at least she wouldn't attack my
main character because if she dies then
the game is over so
let's just go for it
[Music]
and you think she's gonna attack the
protagonist though
all in our window as much as we can
[Music]
okay well
we have to do this
so I'm gonna go here
I guess
[Music]
and engage
and do I choose something specific I
can't
I can't engage
okay and now
I hear I change it
they said something about using the wrap
here right
oh 13 10.
61 percent
39 39 is really low
use the special how do I use the special
wow when now it shows it
and
with with the Rapier though right
[Music]
okay
um can we get like a critical hit is
that possible because damn
I want the kill
I'll just make her attack again next to
her if she survives that is
[Music]
oh man
that triggers
oh they had a bond level up though evil
plus 10 at the cost of crit minus 10
when using a sword
[Music]
I don't know if I like that but okay
I like to fight alongside emblems
getting Bond XP increasing their bond
level as their bond levels increasing
its gain stats and access new effects
well
[Music]
I can't reach her to attack her so
should I try
to how much damage would I do
oh I could at least kill him because if
I think about those two going after my
units
that worries me deeply
so I'll kill him
[Music]
[Applause]
okay will I survive oh
the protagonist
s
you say you have to attack even though
she's the one attacking
okay let's go
oh
I was gonna worry about if she counter
said attacks
she gets the EXP
ERT
bye bye friends
oh no more heels
[Music]
we got the kill
okay okay okay okay okay
um
I wonder though
when I attack now
can I do the special skill again
um
I don't think I can
yeah what if it misses and she kills me
once per engage okay
but
[Music]
I wanted this
92 percent 87.
well I should find should be fine right
[Music]
ah
you one I'm proud to see you working
together so well
bam
stage clear MVP Clan
rude what about me
this for once
okay
saving
Mage MVP uh he had some good kills I
guess
that's
that's quite the feet
there's much to improve upon but this is
a wonderful start great work Kiana hi
[Music]
I believe we have to fight against Queen
Almera yeah well I can't believe we won
yesterday
power seems to be growing already Divine
ones
am I getting them
oh I guess no of course not
[Music]
this is the sword you are using isn't it
that's a sick sword though
cool cool cool design wait a second body
with boobies
close to the handle like on top of the
hand though you know what I mean that
looks like a woman's body
I see it too and I think it's a purpose
you've seen what you want to see no no
no
no no no no
I see it thank you I can say thank you
thank you she's single yeah
I see a sword
well well you have yet to be enlightened
[Music]
an ancient light that can be wielded
only by Divine phoenixes
it served me well for many years but now
it is yours consider it a prize for your
Victory today
[Music]
thank you someday I'll prove that I'm
worthy of the sword
I have no doubt
what are you giving it to me that ring
I don't even wear this ring
oh I guess okay
I get it oh it's confusing I'm not a
whole another fancy ring
foreign
[Music]
no it's purely ornamental you see before
your Slumber I made you a problem
what was it
I said I'll give you a birthday
presented you perfectly
yeah guys because of the two colors
[Music]
I was working on it in private but I was
unable to finish it in time
that birthday has long since passed but
I would quite like to give you this gift
now
[Music]
huh
why
Divine Dragon why
no why
just a ring guys
because you can't remember the promise
well
no come on just take it why you need to
make it so complicated
[Music]
foreign
it would feel wrong accepting it like I
was taking a present meant for someone
else
it's offered me this gift again once
I've remembered everything
[Music]
okay
everything you say
like how evil I am oh I hope you will
not remember that one
did facing mean battle steer anywhere
collections
no it didn't didn't help at all sorry
you don't need to apologize it doesn't
matter what you can remember right now I
only held that one day you'll think of
me as your mother
as you did a thousand years ago
I already think of you as my mommy I'll
gladly take you
you might forgive me I was so thrilled
to spend time with you again I suppose I
got a little carried away didn't I
no it's all right
I don't mean to put you on the spot yo
I'm up perhaps we should call it a Dame
that's a great chat in the morning again
thank you promised all this one I'll
remember hopefully
yeah yeah
are we gonna do pinky pinky pinky no we
didn't
man
okay but the tutorial maybe over finally
it's been man I've been like dragging it
out because I I sometimes I or most of
the time I wait for the Japanese dub
give it some time
so you can hear it
before I read so things have been taking
much longer thank you Jen thank you
Alston
Dragon it out
[Music]
overall you did great at the tutorial
out come on don't don't lie to me
you've been speaking over the top yeah I
mean because otherwise I have to because
otherwise it takes too much time it's
already been
taking so much time I've been trying to
give it some time to shine but I don't
think we can do this all the time but
I'm I'm guessing that just a tutorial
was very dub heavy and maybe the rest
not so much
[Music]
um
well we got a weapon
by the way I've been like
very intrigued by her body type her body
shape I mean
she has a interesting
like curve on her hips
quite interesting but I like how she's
not too thin
yeah yeah
it's got she's got a good body a good
body
long legs not too long
it's good is that a cat oh
yeah look at this big cat holy [\h__\h]
I know where some items
I see one over there did you see the
Twitter post I made about my kitty cat
glasses and the cup
I bought those
first we've had my money because like
when we were going down that shop
another cat
and that street of all the shops hi
cute
I actually had no more cash left and
then I was like oh my God I need to buy
this though I had to Borrowed me some
money
cat free cat say hi it's a black cat
borrowed me some money and then I
um went to the ATM to get some more
extra money oh
more berries
so in love with those glasses and you
can get them online by the way I saw I
think in case you want to like you know
match with me
hello
Felix you look so amazing I swear I'm
gonna get stronger too especially for
you
well I will hope so you've been actually
quite helpful in this fight I need the
healing
I was helpful yeah at least a little I'm
going to keep being helpful to you in
Phoenix
okay
you fought magnificently going forward I
will continue alongside you as Unite
gladly I will have you by my side
please rest for today we'll chat in the
morning okay
and after
okay
that's kind of creepy
foreign
music that makes it so creepy with the
echo
there's so much to catch up on so much
to see and do together
okay that doesn't sound so evil anymore
but still
we can chat for hours take long walks
share meals and then she just noticed
that we're listening to her halfway
through and then now she's like oh I
have to save this somehow
oh
if my child's memories are truly lost I
wonder
hmm
Moses
I am here
there's something I'd like to discuss
with you
yeah eventful day
Queen lumara seems so kind and caring
I'm sure she was a wonderful mother
mm-hmm
[Music]
if only I could remember those days
I must have found so lucky to be her
child
yes there are some family problems here
maybe maybe we should go to what's his
name Dr Phil or so
oh [\h__\h]
memories
oh maybe I'm the evil one not my mommy
come on
[Music]
interesting
foreign
I'm indulging by just that it seems like
something
inside me even but if that was the past
if my Mommy has seen me evil before
then why is she so nice to me
um
what was that was that me
are you all right it looked as though
you were having a bad dream
s
yes I'm all right
are you here this whole time
you were wearing my ring when you went
to bed
we should see a doctor not me you're
talking to her right I'm normal
I'm sorry I forgot to take it out
it's all right
and if something happens I will be able
to help
besides after a millennium together I
would feel uncomfortable if we were
separated now
he's got separation anxiety
freaking me out I need my space I know
how do I tell him
[Music]
what was I like thousand years ago she
asked
um
you must be able to tell me something
you were kind as you are now
there's no need to remember everything
at once
take your time he's back into your
memories lamera advised that too didn't
she so does me
myself
yeah she did sorry I didn't mean to be
impatient
yeah but why would Marv cover something
up isn't he like a good guy
but I was thinking the same
a fake morph I guess what was that
I want to drink iced tea right now
I have a sudden craving for
uh Nest tea I've seen specifically
nesting
the others
okay
[Music]
let's go
I look new to you oh I'm just Kiana
oh we're going straight into a fight
what
quite there don't hit your voice
[Music]
[Applause]
of course of course that's what they
want
us
and they don't look like the corrupted
ones
okay they have the the Pegasus is the
flying horses
already
hey yo
item icons and enemies indicate that you
can get something for defeating them ah
[Music]
and you can obtain will be highlighted
in Green in the enemy's inventory okay
review information about the unit by
selecting them with x
check the detail screen for information
about weapons and skills
return to battle by pressing b or X
[Music]
supposed to win this they have like a
[\h__\h] ton of units
no way
we're just four
[Music]
well I guess maybe these ones will wait
for me all right
until I get there
what about them though I can't even
attack them
plants
I had to restart it once
so
okay
[Music]
so your Lance your sword and I already
forgot everything besides sword being
strong against ax but
can I see that triangle again
is it anywhere on the screen I don't see
it
[Music]
x-speed plants I don't have an accent
right oh no wait he's he's gone
okay okay
sword ax
on the lower right doing battle
[Music]
but it does show me something like a
sign that I can break him
good first move I would say
ball flying okay
I don't have a bow
so let's not be here can I attack from
here no I can't
[Music]
yes I'll finish him
I don't think I want to engage yet
[Music]
liberation
is it okay to use that
I got I go bye-bye didn't kill him
[Music]
God damn it
I kind of saw that one coming damn it
damn it
I'm sorry
um can't really do much with him here
top guy will attack him if he's here
look he's an endangered Zone everywhere
[Music]
and then we didn't counter
true I'll just wait with him here and
then we could cover one of them with
friends
or both I guess
I should have stood on the hair
[Music]
no rewinding right
but wait can I rewind within my uh
like turn selection thing in here
good plan bad position yeah but maybe
we'll be fine
nice
[Music]
genius
pretty good pretty good
we did kind of level up
a Fram oh
they're all closing in here
yeah
make it to the ring ball that's what I'm
thinking
someone would come by I don't know what
I was hoping for it we'll just do it
right
I got it
cute is that the princess and the prince
she looks like she could be a princess
she looks spoiled
yes this one
now let's go oh
yeah boys if someone's coming
up
oh this is like opening for that Zelda
uh Ocarina of Time
oh
so cool do you send
not like an annoying piece of [\h__\h] where
is the introduction
cinematic introduction of the princess
though I would have liked to see that
one
he stays on the horse though Prince
Alfred of ferine you said
could it be
are you done Divine Phoenix
that's amazing you know I've waited ages
for this to happen
there's so much to talk about later of
course after we're taking care of these
scoundrels
thank God
who are they anyways
we're not sure
whoever's in charge
these are my retainers
that's not a princess
foreign
that was not a princess
that's okay
another photo maybe we will get a
cinematic introduction of the princess
eventually
he's the princess no he's the prince
lead the way Divine one
thank you for your help
but can I control them oh it seems like
it they're not green
oh
hi cutie
you like her
he got green eyes very pretty wait so
he's uh he's Lance huh
and the other ones are Lance too uh
uh Lance maybe strong against sworn
Maybe
I forgot
oh yes looks like it
oh yes yes yes yes because I can break
them
okay what else do we have we have an ax
and a bow
foreign
[Music]
some weapons have icons to indicate that
they are effective against certain types
of foes such weapons inflict bonus
damage to foes of the indicated types
nice how far can I be it seems like I
can attack this one from there but
uh what if I go here oh
[Music]
that's a big relief
okay
um I can't even oh how about
[Music]
either I help out with him and give uh
Kiana the
kill or I help out with him and give the
kill for that one maybe
I can
and I help out with this one with
another character the Lola one
[Music]
I can't finish either of them so
up
[Music]
let me see something first
how about
huh
I'll build this
[Music]
um
was that a crit oh God damn it
I got plans never work
Ed
[Music]
oh man okay one
that hopefully is enough for me to kill
it off afterwards
my plan was to not kill him and give the
kill to myself
massive tactician you can do it I hope
so
I I honestly like I can't unless I
couldn't
maybe it's time to engage I don't know
if there's something really strong
coming for me
just by engaging without using a special
skill wouldn't I already be stronger I
hope so
[Music]
it's only for free turns too oh but I
asked there's a refill
okay
[Music]
myself
there we go finally level three
you need to grind
oh sweet titty bright defenses views
attack breaks full a unit makes an extra
attack at 50 damage
sick that's amazing
that is incredible
now so should I make an effort to attack
this one even though I'm not effective
with with him
yeah
yeah I should
why not why not guys
hell yeah I should
and then
I'll stay here oh and I can't chain
guard oh
[Music]
okay I'll wait
and you're so far in the back so come on
boys let's go oh
extra oomph
unit can add chain attack to an allies
assault they will join an ALICE attack
if they're in range
it's a little bit too late for that
I'll just uh
hmm let's go here then
foreign foreign
[\h__\h] bastard
[Music]
it's one hit with her so
bring him down quick quick Revenge
[Music]
I'm gonna heal the protagonist
guys while we're here
let me tell you one more thing about my
ketokatos while I was gone
I did tell you right that they were
actually smoothie specifically was
trying to
open the entrance exit door of my
apartment
right and my brother was sending me
videos of that
yeah I think it was because she was
missing me
makes me think I should make sure that
it's
one second so
um
hmm
my brother told me I have to arrived
that she actually
ended up
succeeding once
yeah should I finish him off for this
one
[Music]
like my brother was sleeping and
eventually he woke up and noticed that
something is wrong
because normally when
he wakes up just as when I wake up they
would go come up to him and be like
but he noticed that none of them were on
the bed with him when he woke up
so that was obviously sus
oh I see I see what we can do here
[Music]
and then he stood up and he walked
around and when he stood up they came up
to him
because they noticed oh humans awake
[Music]
so
he sees that the door was open
so the whole night smoothie and jonkers
were probably chilling outside and
the whole way
and since then
he said that he has been like locking
the door properly like normally it's
like an auto lock you know
but from inside you can just open it
normally but now we have to lock it from
the inside too
but before she would just like jump and
then hang on to the handle and drag it
down but she wouldn't be able to like
really open it properly
but I guess eventually she figured it
out which really makes me worry right
now Slim can I check really quick if the
doors isn't open just to make sure I
don't know what they're up to while I'm
streaming let me check and maybe let me
let me lock
I'm not worried
[Music]
foreign
I wonder if
smoking will stop doing it because I'm
back because I do think I will get my
off the credit I don't think she was
doing it because
she was missing me and she knows that I
keep on going out and in of that door
that is a smart thing
um
[Music]
so he was going to fly to Japan to see
you
yeah um yeah yeah no it's like from
outside you can't go in even if it's not
locked because
like you can double lock it but it's
already locked just by closing the door
you know what I mean but from inside
if you just pull the handle you can open
the door but now I locked it extra
yeah
okay so my plan is
[Music]
I was thinking if I get both of them to
attack we could take him down but I
won't be able to really reach
him with both of them if he stands there
already
oh well
my brother is gone now I sent him off I
told him already before that when I'm
back
he has to leave
[Music]
and yeah
okay
I'll just stand here
I'll say I'll stand here
[Music]
kill he will come back soon enough oh
so chill with my cats again but it was
nice to hear that they got so used to
him that they would sleep in bed with
him just like they do with me but they
didn't do it from
from meaning
they don't do it with anyone okay they
needed some time to warm up so
thankfully
[Music]
should I just walk over there and charge
or
[Music]
I don't want the XP right
I'm already I'm still engaging anyways
[Music]
and next can you reach anyone from here
obviously not so let's just move on
closer
oh he can get prettier
far with the horsey he will immediately
be a Target though if I stand here he
won't
[Music]
maybe I'll I'll wait here and then the
next turn I move on
[Music]
and move away so she can charge
it's a tank so he could take it all
right
I don't know they'll come to me oh I'll
come to them eventually
wait
and
um I don't think I'll look heel
hope that wasn't stupid oh he's the only
one left
oh he could get so far but I'm just
gonna move him
foreign
[Music]
like is it the same for me
oh he for XP that's right it gives exp
too in this game
ah okay okay
Archer
uh
[Music]
okay
ah goes away when it's my turn
so
[Music]
closer
all right
[Music]
so far I'm really enjoying myself
foreign
story so far has been like pretty
um well basic but still enjoyable
but I love the character designs and I
like this battle system you know I was a
noob to this kind of
strategy jrpg
although not 100 though because I did
play something like this when I was
younger before
I did
good
um what was it called I think Gladiator
I think that's like basically the same
like strategy Style game isn't it
Gladiator
[Music]
Pepsi hair yeah on the GameCube yeah
I think that goes like this too like I
remember not being able to move very far
and then you know they're being tiles
and all that
okay I charge now
can't do anything else because there's
no enemy close by
there we go
and then maybe from here
[Music]
attack
not very much but better than nothing
I love GameCube
[Music]
but I feel like people are just very
biased towards whatever console they
grew up with right so for me it's the
GameCube I mean I had previous
[Music]
ones too but like Nintendo 64 and so on
I was too young to really remember
playing with it
the cube is just the one that stays the
most in my memories had so many games
for that
you had to wait too but I guess I didn't
play that much with the queen
oh I could I could finish this one
I want to do that
[Music]
I used to play spiral on some console
too it might have been PlayStation
because I guess it wasn't on the
GameCube
hey I got a Wii U last year not a Wii
it never had a Wii U when I was young I
only had a normal week
[Music]
mainly plane stations oh
she's a not a copy paste NPC
well she's got a big ass she is like my
other wife
we got shielded oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
where did that come from
foreign
[Music]
I need to like hold him back a little
bit
yeah no we're not just normal soldiers
lady
wait who's left are there still enemies
left okay
oh yeah these two wait no just this one
is that also okay two two
only two can we get some kill this one
this one I should be
even though without engaging
[Music]
because maybe maybe uh get achievements
as I just saw
okay easy targets
easy EXP
Ron keeps soaking it's been getting even
stronger
always be healing for exp okay yeah I
need to
heal him anyway
[Music]
but using boneries doesn't give me XP
right
you just mean her right
will I be able to use these new
characters
in the future or they just know
he just he deserves some EXP
loits level one wait man there's still
level one what do you mean he's level
one I Funny already had level up
keep them
okay
[Music]
he's already promoted ah
so he gets less EXP
[Music]
okay I'll do the kill with my name
oh she
she was able to shoot back
okay I'll do the kill of the mage
he deserves it
yeah
see I think we got a lot of time to chit
chat during the day
battles in the future today as well I
could give you some more tangents looks
like we cleared the way let's get to the
ring balls
okay what if they're all stolen suddenly
from my mom and she flies away with them
whoever it is
which is too small
she's small
um
because mom is here Dragon Boy
get a hold of yourself
are we back already oh damn you it
missed a nice cutscene a little bit of
it
I know it's too late
she just like took down the Dragon
so the Rings are going to be stolen
indeed that's really what's happening
oh
you trapped something Mommy
wow tear animations
let's go
[Music]
oh yeah
one of those cases
[Music]
foreign
I was so deep into the cutscene YouTube
what's wrong
she just realized she can't heal her and
they were saying like oh oh that means
that uh she's like dying basically if
she's losing her power that means she's
dying
yeah yeah okay okay are you guys back
oh is everyone back
okay
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
am I the queen now
she's hella emotional for someone she
doesn't really remember but
I guess
just
hmm
damn those cutscenes are really good
heart knows
um
yeah she didn't have enough time
man
I didn't have enough time I wanted to
see more of Mommy
why is it always the hot mommy
characters
that I don't get to see enough of what
[Laughter]
tomorrow
hmm
we did a funeral already do you know
more
it was the final service we could
provide Queen lumera's two ways
[Music]
look how hard this must be unusable
gotta hold it together
laughs
[Music]
I'm trying but there's no I don't see
any tears in your eyes girl gonna try
harder
what
I just do like brothers why do they look
so similar
I never thought my paths would diverge
so soon
and to leave a child behind I did that
in death a bitter memory
my vow to protect your Offspring your
actions the mirror
[Music]
coheritance is common amongst royalty oh
really
if we could ground out power now
Marv you know that's not possible
without the other emblems here
yeah I guess
this is awful sorry I couldn't have done
something
[Music]
common Trope and Fire Emblem games
hmm I guess there's a lot of blue and a
lot of like green too
in the previous ones before free houses
that's what like at least one more I've
seen
no Prince Alfred without you our losses
may have been even greater
though I must ask why did you come was
there something you needed
[Music]
the leader of the blue Army that the
player controls
[Music]
they're not related oh they look like it
could be his like bigger brother
our kingdom is in danger my mother sent
me to ask Queen lumair for
helping our people are being attacked by
these creatures
what kind of creature
these things are like people but cracked
almost crumbling
that's what you call them hi
show a timer
brought back to life like zombies
no wonder they wouldn't listen to us
they just keep attacking everything
we send our nights out to hold them off
but it's a losing battle it's
Kingdom has been destroyed
Scott egg yolk on his shirt
a big egg yolk in the middle
will you help us
[Music]
and gladly I'll go
what can I do was my mother's help you
wanted not mine
yeah but you're in her position now
you're the divine
family
I've seen so many beautiful egg yolks
while I was in Japan recently
so now these things stand out more to me
perhaps
[Music]
we need the power of the Rings to
suffering and only you can do that wait
so for real though did the girl the
crazy girl managed to steal the ones
that were here
like maybe
not sure if she failed or succeeded
[Music]
I don't mean to press the topic
we'll do what we can no no take me of
you immediately yeah
let's go
damn it's so weird to see like such a
familiar art style being implemented so
like one-on-one
perfectly implemented
into a game I'm playing
you know what I mean because I've seen
like so much of
Mika Mama art before
um
hand down there
tonight
it's like I'm watching bears
all the characters can look like they
can be in corner like a YouTuber what
English doko
MC really looks like a bell sometimes
well I mean that's just how she draws
the eyes
but I guess like for this one for
example for guys she draws the eyes like
smaller but for girls pretty big eyes
usually
yeah so that's it will automatically
look like they're related I guess
love how she draws eyes yeah me too but
like I was to be honest like when I
first like saw that she was gonna be the
artist for this game
was excited but also I was like
that's so weird
someone's so familiar
drawing the art for it so weird
it's cool though
don't want more families to be torn
apart more people to suffer
even if I'm scared I have to push
through my fear
great job
surreal yeah
foreign mm-hmm
[Music]
everyone looks so beautiful yeah yeah I
wonder like
how many people
um are like interested or going to play
it because they're fans of Mika Mama
because she's got quite the backing too
um
[Music]
interesting for a protagonist to be so
scared yeah right
she's like a baby
that's me oh really
oh
again I know Picasso
now that my mother is gone it's my duty
to step into the role of the divines in
Phoenix that's right
he's protecting rings
has one correct oh
yeah it's the girl
then I need to go there anyway to honor
my mother's requests
foreign
's request for Aid
s
so far it's always us that needed help
and now we're trying to help others
[Music]
almost all my favorite artists
contributing to it somehow oh that's
nice
hello I forget
refreshing because not all empties
should be confident in another part at
the start yeah she does have other like
common things though like the
protagonist amnesia
[Music]
okay let's go happy to help Prince
Alfred
this outbreak is fine I've been visiting
you at the Samuel since I was a boy oh
into the sky
think of you as uh
very very old excuse me
I appreciate that actually I can't
remember anything from before I fell
asleep
[Music]
this world is near to me
I appreciate having friends who can
teach me about it
I'll do my best so
rely on me
can't say I'll know much compared to
queen Lumera but I'll try thank you
thank you Alfred
[Music]
Tomodachi zoned that's all right I
wasn't really going for him anyway
as allies fight next to each other or
heal each other they gain support points
and eventually unlock support
conversations
oh yeah I've seen that you can be a
support conversation
I was the same as the link before it
feels like the same on the thumbnail or
world map to increase the support level
between characters
[Music]
units of support levels gained stat
bonuses when standing adjacent to one
another
horse is two
oh let's talk
[Music]
I cannot make up for what you've lost
but I am at your side Divine One
[Music]
he don't care you were just reunited too
it's so unfair it's like
oh this sauce is such a common RPG thing
or like movie thing in general like a
general thing for anything really where
he
works
most of the time but conveniently
sometimes it doesn't work for very
convenient cases for dramatic purpose
ooh Bond fragments
how do I see the map again there
Let's uh
-huh
like arvin's dog yeah exactly
[Music]
Queen Romero was always so nice to me
but now now I'll never see her smile
again
unless you or open The Cask
not that you should do that
yeah exact same thing can be healed
normally but only can't be healed now
yeah exactly
I'll be your sword and shield to find
one and a flower
oh oh okay what brings more Comfort than
that okay okay
we got flowers around your head okay I
guess you're really connected with
nature
thanks for agreeing to help us I hope
you can do something to say Vereen
I'll try just for you just for you
yeah revive the dead for plot reasons
let's set something then
and conveniently will not work
Queen Romero when word gets out there
we'll be mourning all over fareen
okay
well let's all stop being subscribed
babies and go to the rain next chapter
oh that was a chapter oh I felt shorter
than the other one
a base of operations
base in the sky
that's really cool
she actually said Oh you mean the place
where I was sleeping right now
she she said well if we can use it I
would be happy about it but I don't know
how we'll get everyone
if we'll be able to get everyone out
there oh it's pretty close that one was
close
[Music]
yeah I can what about the others as a
Divine Phoenix you can travel there no
matter where you are in the world sooner
discuss I just put everyone on my back
and then fly up
hmm I can't
yeah
[Music]
indeed for tomorrow one can only enter
the Samuel with a Divine Phoenix's
Powers
[Music]
couldn't have said
this is what makes it a safe haven
can the other evil dragon enter though
hmm
o
um
are you gonna say bye bye to Mommy one
more time oh
um
[Music]
as much damage
hmm
damn here that's like almost exaggerated
sound effects for his movement
thank you for watching over me all this
time chair
s
this journey will be a long one but
don't worry Vander and the others will
be right beside me
and I will find all of the Rings just as
you asked
and then I'll return to your mother
promise
sweet
Ness
here we are safely return to the
thumbnails
and realize how spacious this place was
[Music]
fill it up with some peeps
if someone to supplies of equipment
something to consider like a shop
yeah okay where do we get that
[Music]
it also has those two colors
but I don't think it's even me
someone else
[Music]
a piece of jewelry I don't recognize it
Crystal looks unusual
where did you get this
foreign
[Music]
could just be someone that she met
before in the past thousand years ago
the audible
foreign
okay let me look around though
let me check it out
oh it's cute I guess they put in like
these these uh pixel
uh artworks gifts chips because it's a
anniversary game right and then this
makes it nostalgic maybe the Sprites I
guess Sprites
maybe for a nostalgia's sake
because that's how it used to look like
hey cute
the Samuel is your base use this area to
prepare for the next battle and interact
with your allies
additional activities and areas of the
thumbnail will unlock as you progress
for the story
open the world map to continue your
adventure access it from the event menu
or by using the accent in the plaza okay
cool oh dear looks like a uterus
wait what does that YouTubers look like
I think it looks like that
[Music]
it looks exactly like a uterus
what
don't you wear green
sure he does agree because you don't
know what your uterus looks like
I'm in the map
[Music]
right I'm right I'm always right
hmm so far I've always been right
she took off her arm hmm
[Music]
she has those pies
yeah fries I think for a second
compassional clothes
yeah I guess they're okay
I mean
I think it would be better if it wasn't
like a one piece
jumpsuit kind of thing
oh and it's fine
and she goes fine
wow it's like a spa like a hotel Pooler
whoa can I swim no
but this really looks like it could be
some Hotel
pool area
[Music]
nice
makes me wanna go to a pool
all right let's explore this uterus
marf is in the uterus to No Surprise
the pain of losing Lumera runs deep yet
the familiarity familiarity of the
thumbnail is comforting
Queen lomara said the emblems can roam
here more freely due to the Divine
Phoenix's power
ah so you're just chilling you're just
hanging here
oh there's actually
items over there can I use Dash
if yes then how
wow this is pretty
little Garden area
pretty Pebble R1
all right wait what's R1
huh
ah there we go
nice um milk and eggs
okay I can make some breakfast with that
should we go in here
oh stable is locked up okay maybe once
we're able to have a stable
then we're able to
go into this table
[Music]
um
oh secret path
nice strikey well a nice try
more Secret
wow
what is this
foreign
[Music]
not yet usable
are these items gonna respawn
well like at least different places or
so
eventually
[Music]
and I do
what's this
Tower of Trials
okay maybe that's for
fighting
like a fight Tower
The Fight Club where we don't talk about
it
you know up this way
every time I beat a map okay yeah
[Music]
oh did I go here yet no
nice wanna Grill some marshmallows even
I don't particularly like marshmallows
but it would be nice anyway just for the
sake of doing it
I would prefer to grill some sausages
Joe
let's Grill something
like this
can I fish later
[Music]
whoa oh no it's on the petals are even
falling
pretty okay there's some items and
people over here
oh
wow
comfy place I mean you know so far not
necessarily comfortable
with all the stone
walls and all that but
definitely pretty and soothing
thought on it can't deny it's daunting
to come here no matter how often I do it
but I'm glad you're with me
gift
[Music]
no nothing
not to you horse manure oh
we have the gifting options again though
is there also tea time
as always
quite something
so the Sunderland
Orchards ah I should check them out if I
don't get lost first
no no not for you
[Music]
no tea time
oh
who spoiled from free houses when this
is an anniversary game
shouldn't have less or nuts
less features should have an equal
amount of features
does it make up for the lacking tea time
and anyway
Club one time
there are other features
what
they also dress casually oh
Cafe Terrace Terrace
is relaxing communal space with access
points to other facilities using music
box to change the background music on
the thumbnail the bulletin board is full
of useful information you can use it to
invest
in Alias or check on your chip invest
do they mean investing in the common
sense like what I'm thinking
stonks
please tell me no because I don't know
how that would fit in here
well Divine one night to find it easier
to relax in everyday attire
you look like a butler in those clothes
though
which I don't think you are
[Music]
okay lamera laughed to stand at the edge
of the thumbnail and look down on all
the pretty clouds
support
because of our bond
oh we can already have a conversation
like this
[Music]
foreign
you know I like her but she's kind of
like
so pushy that she's ruining her
potential with me
[Music]
just like we for real for real
ah I'm sure she'll chill out later on
well it would be better for her I know
[Music]
um
you were indeed very distracting girls
[Music]
you're not not distracting me what a
nice way to say that
I'm sorry sorry
fan club
um girl
I don't think I need a fan club
um
that's why I'm here giving you extra
motivations
uh could you maybe not doing so close
foreign
how far
[Music]
and who's our favorite
oh yeah
that didn't help
screaming louder because she's further
away but yeah sweet sweet I guess
okay
um
what did I miss
um my room
I have a room
oh yeah
I don't know whoa it's this one this is
your room a sacred place so I can't
slept for a thousand years just like me
for real for real
so like rest to take a nap yeah
hopefully a short one an advanced time
on the thumbnail we may hear some
interesting things while resting wear
headphones for the best sound
I think a normal player that doesn't
stream wouldn't really be wearing
headphones
and even play handheld with normal
open Sound or
or on the TV
you're lucky I am wearing headphones for
streaming but what is this like ASMR
hey I don't like chaos
[Music]
well as long as she's not like moaning
at me then maybe I'll listen to it
select reminisce to view past support
conversations and scenes again you can
lower the game's difficulty Oh by
setting selecting
yeah the difficulties anymore you cannot
raise it even if I lowered once can I
not raise it anymore
that's so weird I can only lower it
[Music]
I can only lower
I can never go back
so you don't choose encounters
no I mean the only thing that I would
have maybe done that for is like when I
have to grind off screen just like
levels and levels and levels to be
faster and more efficient maybe I would
have gone uneasy
uh but okay I guess I'm not doing that
because we're not doing them
no need to grind are you sure about that
what's this because something important
belongs here
what would I sleep for
time will pass okay but it's not like
I'm waiting for something
maybe maybe another circumstances this
would be necessary oh wait
who is entering my room
let's see
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
she definitely sounded a little bit
distant though
but she's just coming into my room while
I'm sleeping and
the creek
quieter
nah
some space she's like a cat just like my
cats
hmm I guess so
but that's okay I forgive it if it's my
cat
[Music]
oh
the music
friends
you know what I didn't talk to you yet
uh the the ATM whatever her name was
where is she
how did I miss her wait is she
that one over there
oh
is she there
she is looking for you
[Music]
am I underdressed with insomnia I feel
like I don't belong here but I'll help
however I can no you're super cute don't
worry about it here Pebbles
[Music]
and happily accept any gift that Divine
Phoenix picked out for me
currently um because there's no one
better around she's my current
girl my current Beach you focus on
give horse manure
would have would it have been better
[Music]
wow
that's cool very cool
yeah I like this place
I think I've checked out
pretty much everything now
now for now
20 years
wait there's no more items there though
how did I not pick them up
are they
[Music]
um
there should be one here yeah
foreign
that reminds me you know what I did
the other day because my bro told me
about it
um I guess I was already kind of aware
of its existence but we have something
here and
[Music]
Austria now
um it's an app called too good to go
[Music]
where you know when restaurants and
supermarkets and so on close up at the
end of the day they can like give away
like surprise
bags packages at a cheap price you will
not know what it is but sometimes you do
I guess but mostly not
yeah to not throw it away
and
I mean
I don't really have to
like save on the money I spend on
groceries obviously
but I did just spend a [\h__\h] ton of money
for my Japan trip like several thousands
so I felt like saving some money right
now anyway
[Music]
so I was like you know what I'll try it
out because even even if it's not so
much about the money it's just about
for the sake of like the principle it's
about like saving some food from being
thrown away like why not I get it
cheaper and an exchange it won't be
thrown away
yeah so
I signed up and I got really excited
because it feels like
it feels like like I don't know a
surprise Santa or what's it called local
surprise Santa what's it called
secret santa secret Santa or it also
felt like an advanced calendar you don't
know what's behind the door and then
yeah so I was walking to the supermarket
I'm like oh what am I gonna get it what
am I gonna get and to be honest I guess
impressed by what I got out of it this
time but I want to try it some more
often and it's not like I got anything
that I couldn't eat I got like one big
um rap thingy that I think I'll eat
tonight for dinner it's pretty big I
mean it was uh yesterday was I think the
expiration date
but I think it'll be fine for you today
and
um
and two big ass oranges and
uh ah a lot of bread
that I put in the freezer
a lot of bread like
at least seven pieces of bread I think
like different kinds like special kinds
of bread
and
I think that was
on my fan I actually took a photo I
yeah and the best thing about it
was
um like a fresh cut fruits cup with
strawberries and pineapples and
raspberries and blueberries and normally
when I buy those most of the time
there's like a lot of the fruit are
already [\h__\h] and even though this one
was expiration day today
actually this was one of the best fruit
cups I've ever had from the supermarket
so it was actually pretty good
hmm
it was actually good
you think European bread would not kill
amen likes Japanese bread oh I don't
know I don't know like what the
difference is in ingredients and so on
um Mama winning yeah so anyway I'm I'm
open to trying it again
sometime and it was definitely much
cheaper than buying it you just don't
know what you'll get but you know since
I just came back from Japan my fridge
was kind of empty anyway so I needed to
fill it up I went normal shopping too
like I bought normal groceries too but
you know
you had strict regulation what can go in
the bread yeah
who tried three kinds of bread only
Japan bread is for her
well she's never been in Europe so who
knows maybe she would be able to eat it
[Music]
Kingdom of foreign
I hope you're not worn out
I'm fine
good good listen I'm sorry for twisting
your arms to come with me
I'm fine that's all right I wanted to
come on
but before we arrive at the castle you
tell me more about this Kingdom of yours
bird person exploration therapy
wasn't it already at free houses
[Music]
uh I think it was
the previous game
[Music]
is one of them the four nations of
aliens in the Southwest
yeah it was
you guys
hot Mommy and she's alive
[Laughter]
wow clean Eve we're known as a Land of
Plenty
how did we get over that like
like because that Island wasn't it
surrounded by a lot of like evil stuff
looked like we couldn't easily go over
it but maybe we just flew
but hey we have yet to turn into a
dragon though we have yet to see our own
dragon form so I guess we didn't do that
teleport
our people value peace above all else we
haven't seen War for centuries
you must come from a long line of
capable leaders
it's kind of you to say peace doesn't
always come easy
mother had to hammer out a
non-aggression pact with our neighbors
oh like what like a neutral
[Music]
that says that there won't be a war
between us some and brodia
that doesn't that leave one more Kingdom
out
but
the queen them of Freedom okay there's
never Queen guys is that the I wonder if
that's the the here in the desert
and Brody are the kingdom of mine
is
an open-minded country they've always
had good relations with foreign
he's always launching attacks on
illusion to expand his own territory
[Music]
hold on
everything part of the alliance
therefore
honestly they're so far away we don't
interact with them too much
we know it's snowy there with long
Winters
and that's some Illusions worship the
foul dragon
[Music]
people can't believe what they believe
he also said that it's not like the
whole country
believes and and supports the fellow
Dragon
sorry I didn't bring it up to turn you
against delusion
it's not them I hate right
him and the one who killed my mother
can you tell me more about the emblem
ring that was entrusted to foreign
[Music]
sister
I look forward to meeting us
[Music]
new sister
um perfect perfect
uh Flora Milltown the class is closed
down we'll just cut through here and
enemies
appeared
there might be trouble ahead
yeah the village was attacked by the
zombies
and thank you for watching the make sure
to watch the VOD okay and next time
we're streaming again the day after
tomorrow I think this game in particular
they're everywhere
foreign
[Music]
I love you
tonight
don't worry we're right here you don't
have to warn us
in there
anymore
[Music]
foreign
I feel like I don't know all the voice
actors but they all sound familiar to me
they're all famous probably
you know
before you begin a battle you can manage
your items and my rings and the team of
allies who will join you
oh
once your preparations are complete
select the fight to begin the battle
okay
oh
uh-huh I remember this afternoon to
choose which allies will join you in
combat okay all right and let's
highlighted in green cannot be excluded
okay okay each map has a set number of
allies who can join The Fray
okay so I have to include okay
[Music]
um
oh wait another oh fighting anyway I
don't have to exclude anyone
if I understand correctly
well well done
okay okay
foreign
[Music]
can I stay in her kingdom forever
I love her
[Music]
a friend
what are you doing here I thought you
were with mothers
marching on the castle
no I'm not talking
about
I cannot say I don't know before they
arrive mother sent me to warn you see
um
[Music]
stayed behind so that I might have a
chance to escape
[Music]
oh she escaped in our Direction
absolutely
sitting
do you have to I
kind of saw Alden ring instead of emblem
ring for a second do you have that
emblem ring
oh I can use it right away
you hear you awake
hey
yes
[Music]
I got it
the words start coming to me
[Music]
whoa
I do not know her but she is gorgeous
oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
I am emblem I detest violence but I will
always fight to defend the innocent
thank you for answering my call
ring
[Music]
just like me
oh my God
okay so you probably has an ally that I
can't control yeah she's already green
okay okay she's by our side
I must protect the people of this
Village and ensure Luis and Kuru is
safety record
oh oh we give it to her
Oh I thought I was gonna use it
[Music]
oh she's a flying Lance
uh type nice
I really like her design too like the
hairstyle and the voice with with that
design fits so well
um
eh I forgot to equip circus ring by the
way
but what if I don't wanna
[Music]
for smart that was on purpose totally
I don't even think about changing it
um
then it is then it is huge waste what
it's broken as fudge
You're Gonna Want Sugar's ring oh
[Music]
laughs
not on myself
give it to Alfred uh-huh
ah your inspired family I won't be able
to get very far with these artists
everywhere
okay okay she takes on the uh Magic uses
and he gonna deal with the Arches
no but I know her voice from something
else too
[Music]
foreign
it really bothers me right now
what that is
[Music]
I guess tonight yeah I probably know her
from there
what
but she didn't have those yes Mommy
Vibes back then I think
foreign
him specifically
if you head into Babylon connected to
the network Spirits oh representing
other players past battles may appear on
the map oh
Spirits appear where many Allied units
have fallen earning XP and bonding speed
while waiting yeah
[Music]
run
kill anyone
happy birthday
[Music]
happy birthday Alex
purple spoons appear where many foes
have fallen waiting new spaces to pick
up the items they left behind
that's also for online only
wait she's not green she's actually in
my team
[Music]
what is she mate Mage is she a mage
and she's a mage
uh
uh I forgot what Mages strong against
I don't remember anything oopsie what
um
[Music]
for real side quest so if you visit
houses to warn them of danger you may
receive items of gold as a reward to
this move an ally to the lit space in
front of the house and select visit
watch out first we try to reach your
house before you and Destroy them no I
will not let them well then I'll
actually I'll do it with someone else
[Music]
well then princess yeah
it was your voice I heard on the way
from the castle I'm glad you're here
with me
[Music]
until this battle is over probably I
will protect you hi I'm ready
cute emblem silica Wheels powerful magic
attacks she's a valuable asset against
corrupted foes the sync skill holy
stance reflects some of the damage
received from corrupted foes against the
attacker
[Music]
oh
the engage weapon Sarah from deals bonus
damage to corrupted foes
skill Echo allows the unit to initiate
combat twice using a Tome at the cost of
50 damage
what
[Music]
oh
nice
the engage attack wait why would I do
that if it's 50 percent
[Music]
ah in case it's enough to kill two
enemies each
the engage attack or Ragnarok teleports
the user to a space New Edition enemy
ooh and attacks of powerful magic Wow
to be able to reach close
and noise more quickly
[Music]
that wasn't really my plan for you
though
um
but we could teleport here and there too
visit the houses right
thank you
Javelin
all right see you later
can't get so far
[Music]
I can attack him but at what cost
s
[Music]
this doesn't reach either should I go up
or right
it's got to use the X guy to go to the
right
[Music]
maybe him no no I can reach the top
though
can reach him
wait him but that's Lance
maybe him and combination
all right attack
better than nothing
both ways
keep them together
[Music]
and well some people say go both ways
and some people say stay together I feel
like we had this issue before when Fire
Emblem free houses
[Music]
I'll go this way
I'll split
different tactics for different people
this and now
but on a counter attack it might be
enough to take him down so
I'll bring my Mage up then
oh another almost killed
okay
yeah oh yeah
and then
it's a center here for now
for a chain guard
and you oh
wait can can she also finish him
[Music]
so they give him the experience I guess
it's better than taking damage
thank you
it says one membership for takanasi
Kiana did I get the membership for
myself it's kind of a weird phrasing
so I can heal the damage it's a waste
I mean I wouldn't say it's a waste what
else should I do with him
[Music]
should I just
um
he gets way less EXP
[Music]
y standing next to him
Maybe
[Music]
and the girl
okay
[Music]
the princess okay
very Noble of our night
[Music]
oh wait I can
look I forgot uh
I forgot does she take care of the major
slower of the arches
ah
and I know I know the house but
she fights the Mages okay
Archer this one
[Music]
estimates you said
should I do this is this dangerous
[Music]
is that dangerous place him on the
castle oh on the castle oh that's an
option
why
[Music]
wait
I hope she survives that
all right
oh oh it protects him better from the
Archer
Maybe
and maybe for the Mage yeah he's going
for the best
[Music]
that's pretty bad
[Applause]
thank you
she's all alone up there now I should
fly away
I should fly away
oh no no no no
oh my God
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
I
what
baby
[Music]
okay you know what I actually don't care
about the house you can have it
questions
it's glowing
[\h__\h]
do you get some special strong magic now
please
why do you know what this is
foreign
Crystal an artifact capable of reversing
time itself
it will give us a key advantage
oh
get such a thing
[Music]
Crystal huh so it's not just a pretty
piece of jewelry
since we have it I suggest we put it to
use
[Music]
I might want to do that
can I return
time now this
it's not too late
it's too late just because people died
right
because I'm not Perma deaf
you can use a draconic Time Crystal to
rewind and retry actions
you take in battle
select time Crystal from the menu use up
and down to select how far back you
would like to go and confirm with a
well then
um
see if we can do this better
does it start now
from now on it's Counting
yes
I restarted Japanese no yeah but we lost
two units already and let's see
this is quite difficult I think she will
have to retreat
but even when I attempt to retreat it's
I can go down here
there's an Archer there though
foreign
[Music]
if I go here yeah that's also not good
I don't want to restart the battle
[Music]
yeah but this is the safest spot for her
at the moment
seemingly
maybe we can even take down the Archer
before let me just try let's see if we
survive okay
um
don't give up so easily
he needs to heal but down here they need
a heel too
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
I have only one Healer right oh wait was
there something about her being able to
heal
[Music]
at least when she's engaged
had it
[Music]
okay
um ax so it's strong against X right
sword strong against X but I want the XP
can I go here well you have to move
first if you Retreat a little bit
because ideally I want to do this
foreign
[Music]
okay and then we finish him but
damn damn
I'm already gonna engage now even though
I don't need the damage right now but I
don't know
oh on the fort
[Music]
does that help me
in terms of damage
okay I guess I'll do that
[Music]
thank you
take
uh liberation
[Music]
wait am I not on the top
she's on the ground though it looks like
I'm on it looked like I'm on the top
though are you
I was looking for the top there we go
she is on the top
okay
and now I wonder
will he go for this
damaged ones or will he go for her if he
goes with her I'm fine with that but
if he goes for them then just in case I
would want to protect them
with a chain guard but
I also kind of want to heal them
but this way I can protect both of them
and go for the kill okay and let me
protect them
how do I get it and to not die hmm
well first of all
what was that
[Music]
ax is strong against Lance
that's the strongest lands well then I
can't one hit him though
unfortunately
[Music]
we have a problem
now I was gonna move away a little bit
uh
attack him
to finish him off
[Music]
and then
does that let's see
[Music]
I think our
uh Archer will die
[Music]
she looks pretty much
okay
[Music]
um
wipe away no what what's that called
gonna attack two separate times nah
[Music]
okay so
fire his ass
oops
[Music]
I didn't need to be right next to him
no no
[Music]
no no no
no
no no no no no
yeah
you survived
yeah I want to restart now
[Music]
oh may I no let me just restart please
uh
until I restart
loose and keep exp oh
[Music]
um but nah
yeah okay
what a cheese straddle
all right try to kill me
[Music]
and I feel so bad I'm just letting them
die on the battlefield
foreign
I did bring her to safety
oopsie at least someone who didn't have
to suffer
oh I could have ended the turn
let's see
[Applause]
[Music]
I don't want to see another one
in my heart
no skip skip I don't want to see all the
pain
[Music]
I can revive oh
no I don't want to
huh
I wanna die
though I chose this
yeah okay
[Music]
and but can I do the the crystal thing
you know can I give him Crystal can I
give him the ring now
wait that that street it's not cheating
if the game gives you that option so
obviously it's not even like I'm trying
to use a bug or so an obvious game
option
okay uh emblem rings
select emblem rings to partner your
allies with emblems once partnered an
ally can sync with an emblem in battle
a parent Ally in an emblem select an
ally followed by an emblem ring
are they like like fitting once that I
wanna like
give to certain people
you guys told me about this one at least
okay so what this one makes him able to
attack twice or so
it's already powerful so that's pretty
good
yeah I might wanna swap some places or
Reserve this
ah what can I put them here no only
within here
and
[Music]
acts against land so this would work he
would reach
thank you
acts against that lens also reaches
yeah
yeah it looks good
something before just didn't reach that
I wanted to reach so that was
disappointing but
you can let them come to you
allow him to move further attack
multiple enemies at once and move away
after attacking oh
hang up on you
you want me to wait and have them come
to me
is that really what you want me to do
anyway yeah I'm okay unit selection
everyone's in so
vital
only summer
oh I can skip this okay
one more time yeah
we're gonna look at this a second time
because she's pretty
yes
a good lady
[Music]
skip it to school
here we go
I'm on um
heart difficulty which I regret very
much right now
[Music]
all right
I know
I hope that it's okay to do this first
actually I don't know
[Music]
attack
don't mind you learning the difficulty
later we'll see how many travels I have
with it really I mean it's it's all
right so far
it's just like for streaming purposes I
guess like you don't want it to have too
many like redo's restarts and elements
don't want to drag everything out to
Eternity
and
ax Lance on it
yeah sword X
sword ax
do I go
I can't get that far with her anyway
[Music]
okay
it doesn't kill though
it doesn't kill when I attack him with
my mage
I want the kill though
this doesn't kill either
[Music]
she's okay
well it's not super effective but what
do I do
I can attack twice with him right
but two horses down there
[Music]
if I send him up here I can kill this
dude because I can attack twice
try engaging
Oh I thought it was already showing me
the engaging damage
I don't know if I want to send him down
[Music]
you seraphim with Celine
for what purpose
[Music]
no I was running around with him
what
ah this way okay okay it still doesn't
kill unless I attack the same person
twice this one still doesn't it's the
same damage
[Music]
ah there we go when I change to writer's
bane of kills
and it also kills the lower dude
yeah I guess I might do that
he can't
attack twice
it can move twice
[Music]
or
um
okay we'll be fine I'll just do whatever
uh
do I override
I guess so
no I want to keep it maybe I'm fine
staying here I think
nice nice
oh I can still move though
I did a normal attack though right
[Music]
so able to attack
hmm
they all wanna go and attack him though
I don't like that
that
and I go here no it's both wait
and then
[Music]
since we have two horses down there
I think
[Music]
hmm
hi
[Music]
you guys are saying warp with her but
where where
I wasn't planning on bringing her that
far away
[Music]
so how do I do this I just
foreign
[Music]
would go with her I wanted to be all
alone somewhere either
[Music]
is this an AOE attack
because it kind of looks like it
don't do it to rescue
not alien okay
well then
then should we really engage though
because I'm not really using it anyway I
think I'll just
[Music]
okay
see this time I didn't stand right in
front of them so I didn't get hit back
Jesus
they're very powerful all right all
right now let's take care of the top I
guess
I do want to know if I send everyone
down here
well they come after me
I was just chill there for a while
what do we do about them because
previously when I put them up there he
died so I don't really want to repeat
that [\h__\h]
[Music]
so I will take this dude down
that kills him right oh but I also get
oh no damage
yeah yeah he just got too many attacks
what do I do about
that
I go Archer will still attack me huh if
I go here he won't
have a place like this
I almost feel like I just want to hide
him for this turn
[Music]
and attack him from here I'm alone
maybe I should just close this for now
[Music]
should be safe now okay
it's a tricky situation up there
[Music]
oh
we chain attacked
still was not enough but I was thinking
of finishing him off
with
I keep making away from him you can
check everything no problem okay
oh no he looks like
no everyone was ganging up on him before
so
and traumatized
okay what can we do with you where do I
bring you up for it and I guess it's
this part this is
it looks hella strong right I think we
need some reinforcement here
and then healer
goes here
and chain guards
doing much better
oh
okay
access is X
[Music]
why do you go down for him just stay up
on the tower dude
at least we did some damage back
[Music]
hello you just joined
yeah I don't care about the houses now
Crystal's glowing oh yeah we already
heard that
time crystal is available
[Music]
oh he healed 10 HP okay Okay so
I could even go for the kill of the Mage
the house still seems fine right
will I kill the Mage or help him on this
sign
I should kill the Mage and then Albina
in a picket as well
but wait when I'm this close to him
he'll come to me right
when does it stay in like how many
[Music]
hits
it takes me
uh
Mike
if he'll have time to counter I don't
see it
for the same
[Music]
lands will kill before Mage can counter
someone
[Music]
oh fires don't get the bonus from
picking oops
oh well lose that before the finishing
attack what
when I attack him
um javelin
no the javelin doesn't do enough damage
though so I can kill him but only in
exchange for some damage on me
[Music]
uh uh
all right
[Music]
maybe I can mint block
S
I wanna be lucky too for once
hey what happened with the bridge was
this always broken
[Music]
some reason I thought this bridge was
intact
maybe I was thinking about this one
okay next
and
we have these eggs not here but he would
still not kill that is very
disappointing
well we'll do the groundwork and then
we'll finish him off
with one of the others
yeah it is nostalgic also like really I
haven't streamed like properly in my
normal streaming environment for such a
long time
I did miss it
[Music]
and now I'm back
oh
[Music]
you know what I'll attack and then go up
on the tower maybe how about that
[Music]
it's good to have you back
cute cats yeah
yeah I mean I honestly I I when I left
[Music]
laughs I had really torn feelings I
wanted to
nice
oh he can't even attack backness I
wanted to go back home finally because I
I I my social batteries were absolutely
drained
but at the same time
I also wanted to stay because
trufus I'm coming back very soon and
it's almost like stupid to go back
but
I do appreciate having some time
here in
the usual environment
[Music]
a lot of love indeed but
of course
you know I think you guys understand
after I met like 25
Senpai is I think
at least 25 and it was a lot a lot
[Music]
after a certain amount of time it's just
she needs to go back to being a hiki
komori
and we're out we were on the ground yes
I was you called them awesome
[Music]
fans totally relax unless you're at home
yeah I just really wanted to make the
most out of the
[Music]
time I had there which you know wasn't
much but
I want to make the most out of it so I
squeezed something on every day I
originally I had some days planned to
just chill a little bit
but
I ended up filling up those as well
there was no chill day I'm kind of not
sure what to do right now sorry guys oh
can she not shoot the guy up there
well how do I attack him
here I can
I was gonna go for the ax dude I
wait oh he's behind it looked to me like
he was on top of it oh she don't need it
well then
[Music]
Joy made the best of every day
yeah some Goods
[Music]
okay maybe you notice I am just trying
to give exp to main character oh [\h__\h]
was that nothing
ouch
I'll kill you no worries that's what I'm
here for
no one else really needs a big feeling
right now
[Music]
and then finish them off
liberation
oh yeah guys I had a 20 you one hour
flight I mean with connection I had I
had a connection flight
and actually I I flew with thin air
let me tell you a little bit about that
I was
the flight to Japan was fine
and I had some time in the Helsinki so I
was walking around the airport and they
had a they had a movie Buffet
f-i-n
they had a Moomin Cafe and that's where
I got some Moomin chocolates for mume I
was like oh oh wait Woman chocolate
I will give this
I'll give this to movie
they have like women merch shops and all
that at the airport this is kind of
tough that's rough you might die
afterwards should I
wait oh
you come up here
whatever yeah
okay
[Music]
crazy
okay
am I not done oh this dude is still
almost killing but only almost
yeah and oh I flew him
I flew with premium economy I think I
only told you that like I had troubles
in the first flight because
and in the long flight because I had
cough a lot and all that and I felt
really sorry for the people surrounding
me
but besides that everything was okay on
the flight to Japan but on the flight
back
a lot of things went wrong
uh even before me taking off
nice you are alive
because
so originally I thought that I booked my
flight for the 22nd
therefore oh oh Chloe
I also booked my hotel until the 22nd
eventually when looking up
closer on my flight
schedule thingy I didn't realize oh
actually
my flight back is on the 21st which
wasn't such a big deal because the
flight was very late at night which
means that actually having the room for
the whole day
ends up being
kind of chill for me
no
you can chill in the hotel longer and I
also didn't really have any specific
plans for that day
yet before I realized so all good all
good on that side
in in the neighborhood thank you
I guess while we're here I might as well
do this
[Music]
and then
so I realized okay my flight is one day
earlier than I thought well no problem
eventually three days or so before
my
flight I got an email
telling me that my flight is canceled
and
that there are
no alternatives
no alternatives for
for my flight that was canceled and that
I will be
uh reimbursed
they will refund
the money
[Music]
to save Chloe
yeah
[Music]
here
okay
um yeah so my flight got canceled and
then I was like what the [\h__\h]
drink oh can I go back uh
whoopsie how many times can I do this
per fight
[Music]
10 times oh okay uh went to where do I
go Celine visited I guess okay
and can I do it after moving
[Music]
oh yes okay
yeah I think I'll move away anyway so
just be part of a group you know
[Music]
okay
yeah
but I was like what the [\h__\h] will I need
to go home and what do you mean there's
no Alternatives because I looked them up
and
they're wear with the same airline
definitely alternatives
so I didn't quite understand
and yeah
so I I went into like a support chat
first of a bot and then with a human
that I I was like what the [\h__\h] is this
why what do you mean it's canceled and
why is there an alternative I saw
alternative for the next day
the first they were like well
uh you
can still be on the same flight it was
actually not canceled
it's just that the airplane this is kind
of dangerous
[Music]
it's just that the airplane
is not available
[Music]
because we're still we're using a
different airplane
heel oh
using a different airplane
and but you can you can fly with it if
you want to if you're okay with premium
economy
and I said hell no and no if you came
with economy and I said hell no because
I'm flown
of economy a million times and I don't
want to be like hey economy no it's just
because like I have really severe
chronic pain and I have experienced like
12 hour flights and economy many times
so I know how it feels and I know I
don't really want to go through that
voluntarily you know
I'm sorry but
I said no to Dad
so I paid for it
so no thank you
[Music]
don't blame me thank you
and
yeah the guy whoever I was chatting to
wasn't that helpful it was kind of weird
but
um
eventually I guess I kind of like
tickled out of him he's like well if you
downgrade me how about you upgrade me
instead of downgrading me like I know
this is possible in hotels
you can do it too no that was completely
ignored just repeated himself like oh we
will refund you please wait for the
contact from our Airline
we will refund you after you're being
contacted I'm like no no no I need to go
home so
give me an alternative
eventually I pushed and was like uh how
about the same flight the next day I see
something available so
why not just offer me Dad
oh there's more reinforcements okay
customer service at its finest mm-hmm
no it wasn't the bot it was a bot at
first and then a human switched in yeah
so anyway let me go here and heal him
real quickly
[Music]
and then finally he booked me like he
changed my flight
to basically the same time almost the
same route just a little bit more
um Transit time and
in Finland
[Music]
but one day later and I was up with that
because at least this one was premium
economy I was just very worried that
they would cancel that one as well I
didn't want to be canceled again
foreign
yeah but thankfully that didn't happen
however another thing that happened is
like they
um on the day before
damn it this is not a good idea on the
day before
when I was doing like my online check-in
I noticed that it said luggage zero like
check-in luggage zero and also said I
cannot
[Music]
and purchase extra luggage for this
flight
I'm like what
what
[Music]
do you mean I can
I can extra luggage I need to break my
breakfast home
I was very confused
yeah I was thinking maybe I guess I'll
just go to the airport
there the thing is
thin air
even though it's a long distance flight
oh Max they will like first the flight
is with zero luggage and you have to
book the luggage extra by default and I
I was like confused oh didn't I do that
when I first booked the flight
because I did pay like 140 bucks extra
and I haven't received for it but I
wasn't sure if it was just for the first
fight or for both plants
um you have to yeah
sounds like a lot of stress no it was
okay I was just very confused
I don't know does that mean I wouldn't
want to increase my level okay
okay
[Music]
wait wait a second how much damage would
that do to me I
super annoying yeah so I went into the
chat again which you know I had to wait
like
half an hour so to talk to a human
hmm
but eventually I finally reached a human
this was not the best idea maybe we
should have just finished him off of
someone else let me just
[Music]
can I even I can't reach from here
can't reach for me either
um
only if I move away with him
now
I'll just wait here
kind of stupid but but if I do this here
[Music]
I also get damaged unless wait
15 I should kill him first right
anyway turns out that it was a Oh yes it
was a mistake
when they rebooked my flight it was kind
of disassociated the luggage that I
booked
so everything was okay in the end yeah
so on the last day
very late
in the evening me and Jenna made our way
to the airport
and this time you know it was actually
the same place so we said goodbye
it was the same place
as like two years ago or so and we were
like oh this is kind of nostalgic and
also kind of sad but this time we don't
have to be sad about saying goodbye
because we'll see each other again
before two years pass
so all is okay
no worries
and the last time we had a goodbye there
at that airport
janma cries no that was also pretty
teary back then
but I think I cried way more once I was
sitting in the airplane
I remember that she's like sitting alone
looking outside the window and crying to
myself
[Music]
um
this time no no crying but I looked back
at General like a million times I walked
like five meters and I looked back and I
waved and we both laughed and I walked
never in five meters and I looked back
and I waved like ah
repeated that until it was really
impossible to see each other
it's always helping me no one's here for
me
just like when I left pain and the mold
is down
that was sad to like in in times like
those I I usually I can't
cry
oh nice
nice I can't cry immediately
[Music]
no
until it's really hits me or until I'm
like alone because then I feel more
comfortable with crying
also another thing I actually for the
short connection flight that was just
like two or three hours or so
before that I had like five hours
to waste
in Helsinki Airport
but for the short flight I actually
since I got an email that was offering
it to me
I actually upgraded myself to business
for the short flight which was actually
really cheap
and I wanted to try it out I've never
done that before
oh
it was like 69 Euro nice
and I wanted to check it out
for like a big flight it would be way
more expensive but since it was a short
flight it was kind of reasonable
the thing is though since it's a short
flight that used a normal airplane the
business seats don't have like super
special oh nice Miss
super special seats at all it's just
like the normal seats but there's a
curtain that separates them it's like
free rows and you usually sit alone
unless you book love to people but if
you travel alone
then you get to
sit alone so
and also I was served
a full on meal but in this case it was
breakfast
because of the time of day
yeah it's really fighting hard
while all the other economy passengers
didn't get a meal
but normally for like a two three hour
flight I feel like you don't really need
a meal so
I think it was like a big deal
but the breakfast was good
they just survived at helsink airport
at like I think it was like 4 30 or
something like that
and the airport was so quiet and eeried
I was like no people walking around the
only people really were us who came from
the flight just now
oh it's a village I can only visit with
him
or I can kill this person
another turn then I'll visit
spooky
airport was so quiet
and uh-huh going for a house which which
Bandit
[Music]
I'm just gonna ignore that dude
should I not
[Music]
I just killed him okay good
oh yeah I rap so early
and actually in the in the airplane
in the first one we had dinner and a
breakfast right
the breakfast was really [\h__\h] so I
wanted to get another breakfast
at the lounge because with the business
upgrade I got access to a lounge
which I thought was really helpful
because I was going to stay there for
five hours
but since I arrived so early it wasn't
open yet wasn't open until I think like
6 a.m or so or 5 30 and I have to wait
at least an hour
or more hmm
but then after I waited it finally
opened and then I got a breakfast there
and no surprise it was [\h__\h] in that
Lounge took they had like a fresh
looking
egg
cheese tomato omelette yeah
[Music]
and it looked really nice but I when I
was cutting through it
I already noticed oh this is the [\h__\h]
egg that's not real egg it's the
packaged egg I can't kill him
[\h__\h] sake
so I knew it oh I knew already it would
taste bad I tried it and then I was
proven okay this is [\h__\h]
yeah but the other stuff was decent
there's like bread with some salami and
cheese
where am I even going with this
these characters
salami and cheese and some salad and so
on
so that was my second breakfast then I
waited endlessly and I was like oh I
just I'm not pass by faster I just wanna
go home it took endlessly
and finally after
895 61 what
8 961 years
finally
why can't she attack
and why can't she not attack
[Music]
seriously tell me
a little fire with the bow
this one I can attack oh maybe she was
too close
anyway never mind okay
YouTube
yay almost killed
oh you know what oh I'll punch you in
your face it doesn't do enough damage
oh that's so lame
I can't I can't heal from here either
[Music]
I mean not the one that I want to
Folk
I feel the you get the heal
[Music]
ER
[\h__\h] oh wow
[Music]
she's okay she's okay she's okay
oh my God we're almost done here
no worries
what do we have left one magic user and
this guy okay
well done
eventually I finally boarded the plane
and that was the first one to board the
plane because of my priority the axis
and
[Music]
oh
wait I forgot something I wanted to say
my premium economy flight from uh Tokyo
to Helsinki
in the whole premium economy class you
know there's like seats for I would say
20 people or so maybe more
maybe 25 30.
but it was empty it was only like two
people including me
it was the whole flag was like super
empty and I saw the economy class was
also pretty empty
yeah so actually I moved my seat
eventually into the front row where I
had lots of leg space
here uh the cabin attendant maybe
because it was so empty
she was giving me all her attention she
was so sweet she was so excited I think
I heard from when she was talking to the
other passenger she was saying like this
is her first time flying on this route
such a long flight yeah yeah it was a
Japanese lady and she was so so excited
so cute
foreign
[Music]
like I don't know lifted my mood too
it's really sweet
she was
uming me
price and I spoke such good Japanese
yeah
oh
[Music]
what's that
well anyway
was pretty decent first I've let I slept
for the whole thing like I I was I had
like the dinner and then I thought it
was like 12 hours something to the
destination
and then I fell asleep and
once I properly woke up it was already
breakfast time or so
they were only like two hours left
I I still woke up a few times in between
but I think this is the
the most proper sleep I ever got in an
airplane
I still felt uncomfortable in my seat
because I couldn't really lay down
but it was pretty decent sleep
I was pretty hyped about that
I'm still engaged though
[Music]
time passed fast in that airplane in the
lounge not so much
[Music]
um but yeah
then on the final flight I was served a
third breakfast so the first one was
like in the airplane at like 3 00 am
let's say like
what would be Helsinki time then I had
the second breakfast around 6 a.m and
then I had a fruit breakfast around
eight nine a.m Helsinki time
yeah last one was the best one
turning it's so hot but yeah
I told the weight the the the cabinet
was like this is my third breakfast this
was actually the best one out of them
I mean it's not like it was like super
special
at all but still it got me really
excited you know
where should I go I'll stay here
[Music]
yeah yeah
breakfast can be so simple and yet so
satisfying just like a piece of bread
got some butter and some Jam
good sandwiches no I didn't have any
good sandwich I think
all right are we finishing this [\h__\h]
it's a magic dude but
oh I can't attack him yes
um
[Music]
this battle is taking so long I wonder
how long it would have taken me with uh
easy mode ma'am
[Music]
oh yeah really
have zero deaths
[Music]
foreign
like a shop or sell
[Music]
anyway
like a celebrate here and um yeah these
ones I don't really think I'll move them
up there so how do I
and turn there you go
I think this is fine
[Music]
a legend
he wants to be a legend the man who
captured the princess of serene oh she's
really far like you can't even see her
from here probably
I've been protecting him
okay
[Music]
what event at an age
nothing was exchanged
hmm
okay this will do a lot of damage
you can't
was that scripted I don't think so just
think we're losers
all right liberating from his Shame
Shame
[Music]
you [\h__\h] idiot
wait why is that RNG
is he a meal to me
[Music]
no I thought I was just like kind of
missing or something
what about what about us
[Music]
on it
what
who do I attack him with just the magic
I need to break him I guess
can I
I just kill him with the Mage next turn
[Music]
okay
walking into the room
well yeah
that's okay
[Music]
oh wow
oh that hurt though
[Music]
cause I'll take off
Clan gets the kill
good for clan
[Music]
yeah
what a long long long fight
putting in so much work yeah Mage Opie
nine turns it doesn't even sound so long
but every turn took so long
expect even longer in the future oh is
it not just on me
somewhat of a noob okay
environment
um
pretty normal really
I was taking my time too though
foreign
at the same time Manuel
Manuel don't be like that
don't be like that okay
oh my God
Hoshi
hello I love her
you should know by now that's true
that's just how I stream
that's how I've always been streaming
like
I like him
oh no she's cute
she also looks like toothpaste
they can be
also like honestly for these streams
this is what you can expect because the
Fire Emblem streams they'll be long
and you should know about my now I don't
like to
I don't I can't just 10 hours
100 focus on the game because I don't
want to because I want to share some
tangents especially after this long trip
I have so much to tell you okay so
yeah
and also sometimes yeah maybe I'm just
stupid at the game but that's well let's
just also just who I am
I'm trying to entertain you at the same
time
I don't know why so after over two years
need to explain this
trying to entertain trying to share
tangents and when you stream a game
things don't always enter the brain the
same way as they do when you play the
game normally
try it out if you don't believe me try
streaming a game to
hundreds and hundreds of people for
hours
and you will see it's not that easy
always different than just playing it on
your own
saved my life thank you
[Music]
you know I feel like a design like this
it doesn't seem both she and the other
chick our protagonist they don't give me
those typical Fire Emblem Vibes though
is that just me
maybe it's because of the art style but
I also think it's just a design
they stand out to me
it feels a little bit a little bit a
little bit
I don't know
not so much uh Fire Emblem
well that's just because of what you
know I'm used to it must have been like
that for like Atelier
when in the earlier games
you're not complaining okay I hope so
because sometimes it's very much sounds
like you're complaining but if you're
good and we good
what was I gonna say
for Atelier
they used to use the same artist for the
early games like again and again and
again and then later on they started
using different artists and maybe
maybe it felt the same way like oh this
is so unusual
but
I only really got into the atlio games
after they started switching artists
so I can't quite relate to that feeling
until now like for fighting I feel that
a little bit right now but I only played
one game before that so
yeah I wonder how actually your fans
felt when
the usual style was suddenly changed and
then everything's so fresh
of course in a good way they didn't use
a bad artist but
so different than what you used to they
had like this
typical
style to them always hmm
I am I mean I don't I didn't think 5 MLM
uses the same artist all the time but
art style stands out so much because
it's so vibrant you know
[Music]
it's so fresh
it's like hey hey it's 20 23 now
let's try something different anyway who
is this cutie patooty it was nothing
really I only did what anyone else would
do
are you here by yourself
hmm
I saw the fighting
and fun I could help
[Music]
and that's all you say in Japanese are
you pray but then I am I can't stand the
corrupters
oh she said
she said more of what was translated in
the second part I was so style I
couldn't think
it really started you really saved my
life
oh
[Music]
okay
I haven't introduced myself yet I'm the
Divine Phoenix
what a lovely name
beta
hey babe
[Music]
even with the corrupt is gone and may
not be safe for her out here
perhaps we should escort her homework to
an end
but who is she what Pusheen she looks
important that's a good idea
hey Vale do you live around here
I stand by my theory that the
protagonist has schizophrenia
imagination
this is all a dream
where is she my
monkey
I should have
held her hand then this wouldn't have
happened
I wish my hallucinations were cute life
was a
she's real Divine one yes my pretty
cutie patooty Serena
yeah
small with long hair Barefoot monochrome
because she didn't
so let's go okay thanks Mom did you need
something
I wanted to thank you
[Music]
Alfred tell me that you accepted
fareen's request foreign
[Music]
foreign
I think that's just I think it's a
normal designs I think this is just
because you guys are brainwashed
and like seeing anime designs shouldn't
be Troopers but like YouTubers they come
in all shapes and forms now
some of them look like our petite
characters some of them look more normal
and some some are not even like human
looking submerged animals or whatever
yeah
and I mean this Celine girl in
particular she does remind me of a
YouTuber but
that's just the hair I guess
here I find that you're a rattle more
human than I expected perhaps we can be
friends
sorry I can't jump scared by this movie
suddenly jumping up on my table hi hi
what are you doing here
foreign
[Music]
she misses me sorry guys
what do you say Celine friends
I would be honored do I need to make you
some space hmm
or do you want to sit
yeah I'll make some space here if you
want to go there
oh she's going for it I get you I get
you Papa
yeah make some more space
get rid of this oh she likes it
you sit you can adopt the animals you
encounter what while exploring and
bringing them back to something that's
okay I already have smoothie
after you adopt them you can let your
animals graze in the farmyard they may
even drop goods and ingredients that you
can use oh
if you donate to countries using the
bulletin board you will be able to adopt
more animals oh cool
so those kitty cats we saw we can adopt
them
okay
I'm busy with this cat right now though
cute she's so soft
she's such a smart cat if you think
about it being able to open a door
because you have to pull down
the handle and then oh oh she's flopping
and showing me her belly
and then push it pull it towards you how
do you do that without thumbs
oh
she's showing me her belly
it's getting belly wraps right now
the things she did with the food yeah
no that one that one I'm genuinely mad
at her for the door one I can't be mad
at her because that is just so smart and
like I I respect the effort and when I
think about the fact that she did that
because she misses me that's so sweet
you can hear the purse really
my headphones are kind of blank
oh
yeah no she's not even purring right now
what are you saying even though she
should be purring she's broken
this situation she should be purring
she's not purring though you're
imagining it
yeah it's just me
oh
she's not purring
a cat in the game
what could it be it might just being him
sound
[Laughter]
Chad hearing things
yeah I think it might be the windmill
it's creaking
so slightly
oh
she's so cool
hello
all right guys I can't ignore her uh I
will try to let go of her in 10 seconds
10.
nine
eight
seven
six five
four
hey
about 10 minutes
one
oh
there's so much can I get another 10
seconds
yes nine
[Music]
hey
seven
eggs
[Music]
four
oh no I forgot what comes before
[Music]
my English
has escaped me it's so elusive
line yeah I think I missed I missed a
at night
it's nine
what
this is what I'm confused did I really
miss it
[Music]
9.5
you know time to start over
no okay okay you just stay there maybe
every now and then my mom I will touch
you can you squeeze paw squeeze
[Music]
okay maybe she'll stay here she doesn't
seem to mind me talking
what are you guys up to
so it was such a magnet for enemy
attacks oh you you definitely were about
you survived I was surprised even the
second time around
oh
good job Alice may give you blonde
fragments if you have conversations
while exploring use Bond fragments on
the thumbnail to create Bond Rings or
train with emblem
on fragments on the summoned wanderings
blunderings I guess is just like buff
for everything
when you finish exploring you'll receive
any available Bond fragments that you
missed
oh oh well nice
I'm glad we found Celine but I'm worried
about the castle let's head there as
soon as we can
oh well that dress
I hope that mother is safe at the castle
I wonder what
wait really who was that girl though
because I must find out eventually hello
I'm Chloe I can't thank you enough for
saving princess celine's life
she's hot
yeah she's hot
the Divine one I presume I'm Louise
thank you for coming to my princess's
end
oh yeah welcome sir
but with this uh some normal NPCs here
too and we got some iron
thank you how can you watch the flowers
grow
that takes ages
eggs
[Music]
hear something
more Bond fragments I like all the girls
so far yeah
I also don't think I dislike any single
they're designed so far at least for the
girls for the guys I'm just like
I don't really pay much attention
oh the blue and pink flowers are rather
rare it always brings me a smile to my
face to find one
should we really talk to all these NPCs
maybe only hours
some that are female
ha wait actually I like their addresses
set like their
uh
local fashion
has some dandel inspiration I can see
that
Louie is an Untouchable God in my run
he did quite feel Untouchable for me but
he was
on the strong side yeah
foreign
[Music]
yeah that's what I bought
uh the blue ones are my characters right
there we go
you were amazing in that fight I felt
like I was getting a workout just
watching you
know she got abs by the way I've noticed
kind of cool she looks cute but she has
some sickening abs
respect Which movie was up changing
position
won't expose your belly to me anymore
I'm so accustomed to the battlefield I
must work to remember the peacefulness
of levus
wait what did they do to that sheep over
there why did they
only
shape off the butt Part
it's kind of embarrassing
didn't I talk to you already
yeah what's the difference between
the blue ones and the white speech
bubbles
it's the difference
adopted oh can I
I'll treat you better I will not shave
your butt
if you're adopted
blue I talked to her
well unique White Ice Cream ah okay okay
okay I think I talked to
and these ones I know blue so they're
not that special but I still got bone
fragments hi
wait the doc and I adopt that one too
oh I can can I adopt too many
or is there no such thing as too many
did I miss a cat or so wait what's that
chicken
I don't know how to write what do you
mean I don't know how to raise it they
don't know who I am
I can't adopt this Callison chicken
because I don't know how to race it see
the donation section of the bulletin
board I know how to raise a chicken more
than anyone else in this place
look at all those chickens I've raised
in the chat
oh wait she's purring now I think
[Music]
come here
and you're being cutesy you know
you told her
she'll pray Elena
this movie has very selective purring
syndrome
well chonkers has the always purring
syndrome once you look at me I have her
syndrome
once you look at way away I stopped
purring syndrome
mind if we bend your ear dogs
her they have good am I getting shot
people
I saw you trading funds with those
things figured you might be in the
market for supplies
even if we have to provide you with
quality weapons and items
hell yeah please
anything to defeat those creatures they
pose a terrible threat to traveling
Merchants like us
would you like to live in the sky oh
away from everyone
sorry I'm moving the microphone
would you like to live in the sky away
from everyone else your family and other
Library people you know where it's
really difficult to like move away
without my support
of course
you don't have any facilities
at least there's no monsters up there
damn look at so many down there
yo
oh
world map use the world map to select a
destination or move the next chapter to
continue the story move Kiara to
United's nation and press a manage your
inventory or return to this to the
thumbnail using the menu I think I'm
good I'll move on
[Music]
yo now it's already been almost six
hours wow
I do have a super chat rating by the way
planned for tomorrow right
so I don't feel too pressured about
reading super chats today
maybe just like one hour at the end
would be
called for
um
I'm happy for that are you I guess I'll
use the tangent roulette again tomorrow
maybe once or twice
although tangents do take up more time
than
hey
how long will we go on today I'm still
fine I'll go a lot longer how many
chapters are there by the way is there
information on that already
probably at least like 50 or so huh
well maybe some chapters are longer
um should I like change something here
did I get a new ring
no I didn't
26.
oh but it feels like 50.
so we're already at five
there's not different routes that I can
take here right that was like a free
house is special
thing
Inventory management
when I imagine an interesting weapons
and lines about as long as your allies
equipped when using manager items units
can trade items from the conveying
around the house
when they are
okay okay
that's sad I really liked the
I don't know the excitement of being
able to choose my own path
[Music]
and even within that own path
I could choose another own path
a few new things insomnia I'll check
after this chapter
uh
automatically outfit your allies from
the Convoy select optimize equipment
quickly return on given analyst Health
items to the Conway's restore oh okay
oh man skills from the inventory manual
to see your allies skills and equip
inherited ones
mucho textile allies can inherit skills
from emblems in the ring chamber on the
thumbnail
[Music]
just let me optimize yeah what did that
get rid of
hand ax
doesn't do anything
it got rid of her Wolverine no we don't
want that
[Music]
oh I guess no she's a Healer she doesn't
even really need it
can she kill herself
though how many heels do you have left
12. I think it's enough for another
chapter
how to optimize all
oh I can't
after you've selected your fighting
minions during battle preparations oh
ah I heard of all the ring it doesn't
take away interesting
why they take it away from the other one
it got rid of the javelin is that okay I
guess you just picked it up when finding
an enemies you can't use it anyway
see that that one actually makes sense
[Music]
um
for whatever reason it changes the order
I don't know about this this thing looks
fine the sunset
only removed from Healers
if you don't do the dinner event you
can't really progress to support it yeah
okay
I have to do a dinner event
fine but ah
because
a formidable martial artist if you train
her right
that's not true
and I picked hard difficulty
help me
it's been already very
challenging
so far
the air and the brothers Sophie what's
Transportation training is now available
okay as you raise the blood level
between them and you will unlock one
conversations and yeah I already got one
of those didn't I
phone conversations uh-huh
after I fight side by side with someone
I find myself seeking them out in the
thumbnail
Bond
s
it is good that we can talk after I
spent so long silently watching over you
that's crazy
I know what you mean
[Music]
I'm really glad to have you and my side
supporting me in person
oh that's it
that was a short talk
[Music]
unit can inherit this emblem skills uh
noise
okay wait so what what do you really
need me to do here I mean okay we can
look at this new step
[Music]
s
let's see what you got
[Music]
okay cool
the shop will stock additional items
later on
so for example I don't know let's just
go here
[Music]
stop that magically shines through
Darkness illuminates a seven space right
oh there were Dark Places I forgot about
that
torch too
wait was that a thing of free houses
because I don't remember that fancy
thank you
I'm having a chill time
how long since we last played a
long jrpg
[Music]
also planning on finishing Tales of
arises week finally
I got perms to finish it so
I was like why not I guess I mean I know
it's been a long time and we're kind of
disconnected from it emotionally but I
think we'll get some feels nonetheless
foreign
[Music]
tomorrow's a busy day so I thought I'd
get it out of the way now
let me take care of that you should get
some rest so thank you
that's all right I can handle it
that one too I'm gonna have to insist
[Music]
not just me
stewards before me spent their whole
lives waiting
is
now after a thousand years I got to
serve you it's like a miracle
please let me do it honestly truly I
would be honesta
thank God
you are my personal mate now
still one
oh
this calm down calm down chill
ing
now that I'm free from turning up I'm
gonna get some rest okay and he'll be
watching you while you're resting
don't worry about it though
it's part little CA so what weapons do
we have
um
probably only lame [\h__\h] that I don't
need right now
[Music]
go
yeah I think
oh this one's
overall much better though but it's a
mini bowl I remember that from
uh Fire Emblem free houses they're like
I always had like two bows with me right
the mini bow and like a normal bowl
because
yeah
for short range so I can shoot the one
that's right in front of me right
[Music]
yeah yeah okay well we should buy one
cow
soon
[Music]
the rest oh this one
a light unusually
accurate unusually accurate
should I get one of those two I mean I
got the money
why not
my daddy my daddy
okay who else
um
you are safe for now but I'm worried
about fearing Castle let's go as soon as
we can okay Donkey
don't worry but what was this about
having the dinner is that even an option
right now
oh
Florence Melton was the fastest way of
skill we move on to fairing Castle when
you're ready
you know not a lot oh okay I'm all of
them
oh
ah okay on the map it also shows
which ones
are like light blue
to talk to
uh
also some more items I guess
can't have enough of these nuts right
by the way I I know I woke up at 8 00 am
but don't worry guys I just got a nap
with my kitty cuddles
so generally even though I've been
yawning a lot I'm fine but
look at her
oh
thank you nice hand
hey
look at her
casual she's like a rifle
oh oh oh it's movie you're like half
half on my keyboard
that's not good you're gonna like
accidentally close something oh
I stopped moving for some reason is that
because of something you did something
you pushed
foreign
just turned around and got into a better
curled up sleeping position she looks
like a oh wait there's an update that's
why she looks like a snail
wasn't her was just a coincidence
there you go
[Music]
fish movie
I think oh there we go
[Music]
find for me to sacrifice my sleep
schedule thank you sleep time
thank you
no matter where I look it's also lovely
and picturesque
I love her
here please take this she's on the horse
anyway so this actually makes sense
this is from my Pegasus no it's for your
Pegasus
what
what's what even is a horse manure I
don't know what that means
was that bad
she didn't like it huh
oh it's pool
no I
just for a horse like a like an
accessory
[Music]
like uh maybe like like a saddle or
something like that
wait does she dislike me now
uh
but it's interesting how she assumes
it's from her horse yeah maybe maybe we
can say that I picked it up because her
horse made some poop somewhere so then
she'll feel guilty about it and she'll
be like oh my God I'm so sorry my
Horseman don't have it under control I'm
like it's okay
don't worry about it
um I picked it up no problem
oh
The Fight Club
doesn't do anything negative okay
why am I going around picking it up so
that nobody step on it
strength training now available
[Music]
oh
how is it wait let's support first
Twilight pets movie
foreign
like basic he looks the most like basic
NPC
like
but something about him is kind of
charming like
he seems like a like a gentleman like a
nice
good guy ah he's a normal guy here
despite you seemed a little worn out
um
[Music]
I am indeed feeling sort of sluggish
right now
are you reading properly free meals per
day yo I even had free breakfast
I don't think my diet is easy
about the usual
foreign
getting a sleeping fine but you still
feel groggy it could be stressed
is that why I'm always so [\h__\h] tired
I'm also looking for a solution wait I
stopped moving again
restart
one reason why I went to Japan recently
recently so we could we could say this
is jet lag but
I don't know I'm always like this I'm
not am I not I stopped moving again
why you do this
stop
stopping
I hadn't even occurred on me
my stress belief is
and I stopped moving again so that is
really stressful I think we'll have to
switch version but then I can't put on
my hair
can't
but I already was wearing it for like
six hours so
we're good right now
[Music]
no not PNG but
this should be fine
foreign
[Music]
well
no head Chihuahua kind of refreshing too
isn't it I have several ways to blow up
steam like going up a mountain alone and
spending some time quiet
he might be a good match for kisado
[Music]
sounds relaxing
he's inviting me to the
one-on-one fishing date
the Alone part of it is optional really
what do you mean I mean if I go with you
because you have to show me then we're
now alone like it's only us right
foreign
[Music]
okay oh
I'm getting a light warmer before my run
a hundred reps of push-ups sit-ups and
squats
you go girl
I respect that I couldn't be middle oh
that's where the poop was from
well who would be happy about receiving
that maybe it's not for giving to
someone maybe it's for crafting I don't
know
[Music]
um
is there anyone who appreciates it any
empathy not NPC but a character anyone
wonder what I think we've seen
everything so I'm gonna go
joke gift it has no practical use
oh
well then moving on the Green Castle
I feel story
what
begin
say it first hmm maybe we should have
saved
oops
oh
whoa that's pretty
beautiful
that's a nice Castle hmm
there's a castle Yeah
you said they were marching towards the
castle when you left yes
they probably made their way inside
already
[Music]
there's another mother going to die
just when I arrive it's like I have some
kind of curse on me
please no no way
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
white hair two horns
stories
[Music]
ears that are pointy
foreign
ah
mama
[Music]
don't kill her
me
I'm going to meet you I'm glad you've
come now we can see ourselves if the
princess has the ring oh we got three
rings actually but don't tell them
please leave my children alone
of course as long as you tell me where
the ring is
we'll have to kill her then Prince too
for goodness
take her majesty away we'll continue our
conversation later
it no mommy no
[Music]
no
Mommy
[Music]
another Mommy
hello
[Music]
all right enough of The Dramatics
you look all familiar oh he recognizes
me oh [\h__\h]
are you sure it's been the Thousand
Years look at the calendar lady
I am the Divine Phoenix
oh maybe we shouldn't say so directly
koala
such lies the last of the kind
no
noise
[Music]
shows what you know the Divine one was
asleep for a thousand years
really when did that Beastie woman have
a child
very well perhaps you're gonna tell me
what happened to Dear lubera then she
died
I've been so worried about her since
that awful battle at least
oh
she wasn't the floaty one right
how do you know about that and how do
you know about that foreign
[Music]
thanks
you'll never take them
out
I won't waste my breath on explanations
but I will tell you this year
who
oh the Dragon
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] that's a problem
that's a big problem
of course even we couldn't have
accounted foreign
are we going straight into the battle
[Music]
yes we are
yummy chips
[Music]
to start with feed these soldiers and
take back the castle
I'm not going to let them hurt Queen Eve
or anyone else yeah please
set up this like dungeon gives me
like free houses flashbacks I like it
reminds me of the good old times that's
catchy
um
I was hoping you'd say that oh
oh she disappears for real
I wonder if we'll still fight her
eventually for the emblem rings
you can just keep the lightness right
however
can I take them all
oh yes
10 out of 10 now
nice we have an emote for that
[Music]
um
yeah yeah the monastery basement yeah I
think that's what I was thinking of can
we do this battle in less than an hour
up
yeah I think so
I would say so
we can also still save so I'll do that
now
and then let's do this
guy
has to be defeated
player Facebook page
as a door
is locked what should we do uh we're
gonna break walls again maybe
okay
but maybe there is actually a key
you can destroy those by attacking them
a thief can use the door command to
unlock the door instead of destroying I
don't think we have a thief though
what else is there
Treasure Chest here and some charging
thingies
[Music]
um is it worth going to the treasure
chest
it will take us way more time
because we'll have to fight all of these
mobs
[Music]
treasure is worth it
uh yeah but should we split
I mean it's like splitting completely
for now I feel like I will split some
UPS to take care of these ones but it's
not like I'll go into the door directly
okay let me see I forgot uh ax or Lance
okay
[Music]
let's do this
barely does any damage what the [\h__\h]
well the access is effective
doesn't do [\h__\h]
there's a tank
damn
damages
oh [\h__\h]
and when we get weaker the more damage I
do like when I break him or so I wonder
[Music]
where's my Mage I'm blind I'm here
oh
[Music]
it's much better looking
um
um but I don't want to
oh
hurt
although that is a dangerous position
wait I should maybe rather to go down
here
chain guard
um
[Music]
let me finish with them can I can I
see
[Music]
um
normally can I take him down no wait I
can't
[Music]
if I can't then
I don't know
dosio kiwawa can kill him can I yes I
can't reach him though
[Music]
can get far enough
no that's stupid I don't want to do that
I will just chill here
and
hmm
show how good I am
I'm not looking good though
[Music]
um
oh I could like teleport up here
I don't know
smoothie what's wrong
something will corrupt did you hear
something that I didn't hear
go back to sleep she's been sleeping on
in front of my monitor in front of the
keyboard in between the Monitor and the
keyboard so cute
the pillow offers High avoidance be
careful waiting near them
good
High avoidance kind of sounds good
[Music]
thanks guys you too nice
foreign
I'll put them here to protect
the princess
[Music]
already just putting them in positions
so that we can move on faster I'll bring
him up though for more damage
[Music]
and I guess we'll bring you here
whatever
first move is
away the pillars
and
what do you mean
wait and see if
what did I do wrong
foreign
that hurts
okay Archer versus stick nice chain
guard
that was worth it
I mean I think we'll be fine without her
but it sucks
thank God this isn't permanent death
so what was this about the pillars
celery start
I mean I don't want to restart
but
we can go to where I moved here
[Music]
where is she safe
here
so if I understand correctly if I put
her here they're not gonna attack her
or if I put her here it gives her a void
Plus 30.
[Music]
yeah I'll just put her here
that should be okay right
[Music]
now
and the rest seemed okay
[Music]
okay
I should skip that
ah
I don't think it's anything important
okay okay this time they're going for
blue Chevron
he also took a lot of damage but
it's fine
so
how about we move him here
[Music]
let me see actually I want to see the
difference iron X compact ax
iron X Factor one second what did I say
about my HP am I gonna die
okay let me go back
I kind of saw that
coming
thank God for the time Crystal
you can play it
[Music]
um
why must you take so much damage
[Music]
he will not be able to attack back right
so
let's do that
well I wonder
if in hindsight that would be very
dangerous for her
we might be able to take down him but I
don't know about these other ones
[Music]
I did attack him with that but
and that looks like he'll still survive
that
engage though
[Music]
engage him
attack
that is a certain
kill
okay
[Music]
and then maybe if I move here yeah
they'll focus on him huh
that's better than them going on my
Archer I would say
and oh wait
I didn't kill
[Music]
I missed
ah
that sucks
foreign
how annoying
[Music]
oh wait this this dish should kill if
she doesn't miss
yeah yeah
I'm good with that
um
okay
wow they're bonding so sweet
by the way since I'm eating potato chips
I think some of you guys were maybe
wondering why that potato chip idea
didn't happen
like when I I did ask about them and
stand by hey
can we do this
um but at the time what time is Senpai
told me that
we would have to book the studio
um and I that was like at a time where I
wasn't sure like how easy it would be to
book the studio like for life to do
stream
so I kind of just said okay maybe next
time
yeah
but yeah next time I will try to get as
many potato chips as possible
if they fit in my luggage problem is
potato chips they they take up a lot of
space
because they're in that bag with the
vacuum
[Music]
I don't know how many I can really
realistically bring
but there are some shops that sell
overseas snacks
in Japan so I can get some extra there
and maybe if I buy some in the airport
next time
I don't have to put it in my luggage I
can carry it you know in a shopping bag
Maybe
[Music]
ah ship some to Japan ahead of time oh
why did I not think of that maybe I'll
do that
maybe I will
[Music]
because honestly
if I even if I put them in my normal
normal luggage they would probably pop
right
[Music]
why why why you don't do damage
I'll go here
no no no no accident
[Music]
s
axes all the way over here can't reach
maybe the magic
[Music]
oh yeah okay that kills
thank God for Magic
but oh yeah I did meet Fatima Senpai
though
and I think I already told you that I
met her like coincidentally in the in
the studio right
I think I told you that part
[Music]
yeah and then uh
I was invited I actually I told you that
part already too like really roughly
though right I was invited to
a lamb Shabu Shabu it's like hot pot
with lamb like really really thin slices
of lamb meat they had some other meat
and like vegetables and so on too
but the land was like the main
traction basically
yeah cause she has like a collaboration
with that place with the restaurant and
this was already the second oh Archer
oh well alrighty the second
collaboration
that they did
I can't chain guard hmm
wait heal
and it's been like a year since the last
one and this time they have like
everything new again like new
merchandise new illustrations and so on
and new menu items
they had like a lot of really
fun fancy drinks
and maybe you already saw some photos
from other members who uploaded photos
that went there
I'm gonna upload some photos too maybe
after the stream or something
[Music]
I think I might just leave this one like
this sorry
[Music]
unless we have another death
oh
she's alive
she survived
yeah yeah yeah
I was kind of nervous about it but
it was fine
um I got to talk a lot with
because we were at the same table
because we arrived first so we just sat
on that table
[Music]
came a bit later
and I I guess I actually even though
they sat right next to us like the other
table was
just like 10 centimeters away but I
still uh 57 it's really low
so it ended up not like we all generally
fingers
sorry smoothie Sorry Seven don't don't
wake up
I
both tables were just like kind of
having conversations with each other
mostly
not really
yeah talking much together so I thought
I thought this would be a chance to talk
a lot about the person but it turned out
it wasn't that much
but it's okay I still had a lot of fun
and it's not like I I didn't
change any words with her at all
just a little bit rewind time I don't
know
how to improve that
[Music]
and now okay
let's try though
um
oh it's movie stretch good stretch
you're gonna stay or you're gonna go
pondering oh
I think she's leaving oh bye bye I love
you double cuddle later okay
bye bye
now I have space for my potato chips
again
which
I know you guys are probably like hoping
that I don't eat potato chips but I
can't help it it's a long stream okay
[Music]
foreign
can you do it from here oh
remember the magic
[Music]
well I haven't talked to a old rmt for a
long long time
oh wait I remember while I was in Japan
she sent me
like um
Bill she received a letter from a bill
Oh Yeah from my
I think from my
Insurance it seems like I owe them some
money
and it also seems like I should probably
change the address
surprised
[Music]
I'm ready but
the doctor visits are not even fully
included yeah yeah
[Music]
wait what do you mean she missed Miss
well I didn't even
[Music]
like it's scripted it's inevitable
you [\h__\h] kidding me
well I'll I'll try with
Chloe next
that's so annoying I don't have
endless charges
second item once you did it wait so if I
did the same it would miss again right
like that's already set in stone
I assume
I'm gonna take this bastard down
whatever happened 69 percent
nice but is it really gonna be nice
you know what the difficulty
did she
did
with free different
attackers they all [\h__\h] miss
well is the RNG changed now though in
case I attack with Celine again to the
same person would that have a different
outcome possibly
um the pillows gave a voice
that's so stupid
new RNG okay come on okay
[Music]
what a waste of my time oh that could be
a Kill
[Music]
84 and he's not in the pillar
sounds like some good Arts to me
[Music]
yeah I'm rely on
Celine never gets
level up what do you mean
[Music]
in real life
um angry lion rely on
[Music]
Mom I'm back
the game's been tough on me
well upsets RNG
[Music]
so that one was good just now
anybody with his ring
with someone to rely on
[Music]
um
hmm
[Music]
okay for the rest of them I don't think
I can really do anything besides moving
should I go up to try to attack them
from above
[Music]
I go now though I'll try to attack me
I go here he'll come for me so you know
what I'll wait here
[Music]
I guess I'll heal
although someone else needed to kill
more
desperately
bathing is a good idea really
cool
so tactical much strategy wow
[Music]
oh I could also bait him with him
we're second
[Music]
sword is strong against ax
so maybe not
maybe not the best idea
[Music]
and what are you doing all alone over
here must be scared
join the group okay
[Music]
alert successfully
and they are joining okay okay okay
so
sword strong against
I'll actually move her
[Music]
um
yeah now wait let's do this
somewhat smartly
who can you attack him okay
[Music]
you would do that much damage what about
foreign
what about you
seems like I need to do two hits at
least unless
[Music]
yeah that's also two hits
you'll see good overrides because I have
never used that before but like how do I
use it
oh that's a one that killed
don't even need to do the
thing that you said
it's all enemies in a line oh does he
have to be right in front of
them or can he stand here put him more
Kiara is okay
then
I'll try to do some helping damage just
in case it doesn't kill them all
I don't know how much it will take
[Music]
we're broken too
okay okay
now let's try this override
this is how I do it oh yes oh see it
actually really doesn't kill all of them
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
he ends up on the other side ah
interesting
[Music]
go here then
okay then
who wants to kill
you
you can have one this one
he killed one of them but um
come on
[Music]
let's let me look at that
oh that's not good
that's not a good Exchange
[Music]
that looks like a good exchange magic
opium
thank you
kind of going backwards but I want to
heal
I want this game don't get it
if you like garbage juice if you like
strategy I produce if you like fly
emblem
if any of this applies to you
then this might just be the game for you
[Music]
okay I guess we'll move this way
wonderful
go next
can't you be super squishy and die in
one hit oh
well yeah cause damage because magic
users usually where
wool clothes
can't use steel plate armor right
and to be like that
oh struggle
[Music]
hey does the door need several hits
I'm assuming yes
[Music]
two
I could start by it
leaving her here and attacking but
still quite far the chest
I don't really need like everyone to be
[Music]
there oh well I will
bring her at least
no
mistake
[Music]
I wish I could move them as a group
sometimes oh
he wants is he gonna throw like one of
those throwing throwing axes at me no
no no no no no no
[Music]
no no no no no no no
self-improofer
now the hand X
L and R to select them fast
oh is that like the only ones that are
left that I haven't moved yet now the
hotel thank you
[Music]
I know I know but I didn't feel like
worth a charge
[Music]
okay
here we go
oh
battle music is so cool
enemy face bad Museum
we baited too but they both went for the
same person
[Music]
well well well I will never remember
I will never remember this
acts for Lance
Lance for sword
okay
no no no no no no no it doesn't do that
so weird
it doesn't even do that much damage
though
oh can I if I use the javelin I can take
a step back and you wouldn't attack back
I assume but
should I do that
[Music]
nice shot
that's what I like to see so he is
broken now
[Music]
um
mmm
that doesn't do any damage
never mind
I don't like this
that is not good either
[Music]
maybe you can't reach damn it
yeah trying to use the mechanics happier
is effective against Cavalry and armor
units
wait who had the Rapier her
no it wasn't her
who was it
maybe him
[Music]
even though I I still don't quite
understand this logic even though he
should be more effective against Lance
he does way more damage against the
sword is that just because like he is
heavy heavily armored
[Music]
engaged for it
because oh it's because he's broken
hmm
okay that's
can we get the crit out of that four
percent crit probably not
pretty decent damage though
[Music]
we took a lot of damage too from them
and she
nope
[Music]
like this he's still the target of one
of them but
damn it
no Shield
[Music]
she can get pretty close
she can attack oh she can kill the one
up there
okay I'm going for that on the percent
hit
[Music]
engage an echo to hit two
I'll use it next time
next time next time
almost done
[Music]
oh we might be able to kill that one
yeah
[Music]
cause we still got a number
right here on the right side
[Music]
I'll move over here
yes
yes I mean Vander ends up getting the
EXP but whatever 76 66 76.
76 that could go wrong
rip selling what
no she'll be fine
she'll be fine
do I get it back when I kill that enemy
please tell me I do
please say yes
okay thank God
[Music]
I don't know is that we're rewinding
foreign
[Music]
oh man
okay at least we have less people to
move
around
I'm standing way to prevent it
um
thanks for the membership
[Music]
alpacas maybe you're part of my
collection now
I'm supposed to do thinking
yeah I have a lot of units still
positive thinking good
okay right so the one that stole it is
there when I if I teleport over there
wait what type is that
beef
[Music]
if I teleport over there do I have a
chance of killing him
[Music]
it was her right that can teleport
yeah
[Music]
that's how I do it
why Ragnarok
is this worth it
it does kill him
just don't know if it's worth it
but if I understand correctly like he
could exit over there
[Music]
with okay
Philly
devastation
get down we got the armor Slayer
[Music]
I can't
I would have wanted him to open his
first because I can't open it
how do I open the other one then
[Music]
oh we can open I was wondering about
that wall because it looked kind of
suspicious
okay then
we don't have to go all the way back we
can go from the side nice
once the terrain is destroyed you can
pass through the area freely I thought
there was something weird about that
[Music]
let's do it that way then
oh
this dude he
is an Archer
uh hmm
my Mage is too far
what's better against an Archer a lance
or an ax guy but
if I stand right in front of him unless
he has a mini bow he can't attack me
anyway right
[Music]
hmm
punching better punch
I don't have the option for a punch
[Music]
let's see
uh-huh
ah
if I send him
he can walk back and let someone else
through
right
then I can get a second hidden
[Music]
smart
um
[Music]
one more punch
one more punch how much percent 86 76
okay let's go
[Music]
you know
at least it was a sport oh wait there's
an enemy here I'm seeing you
uh
sword against axis now
yeah well
[\h__\h] I would die because of that [\h__\h] no
let's start with some magic Amy
uh wait where's my major here
uh
[Music]
yeah
he breaks oh
it's okay because even then I wouldn't
have killed and this way I kill and I
get the XP
see what I did there
bye
[Music]
oh yes good morning
PST
[Music]
what time is it where is it morning
right now not even PST is morning
[Music]
better this way thank you oh I'm proud
of myself for making that decision right
now
s-e-a oh the underwear I was thinking
backwards not forwards
hold on
good morning SCA Ohio goes by Mass
it's like what six a.m in Japan ow
oh
foreign
[Music]
can I choose which one
five A.M
Sam well good morning good morning
actually what the [\h__\h] it's already 10
p.m here
I started
seven out whoa it feels like I was doing
maybe for four hours the time goes by so
far
[Music]
some staves hinder enemies by stopping
their movement ah like that
or placing obstacles in their path
oh that's how we could have maybe stop
the thief or something maybe I don't
know
[Music]
okay now let's get it moving
let's get it grooving
ice is breakable
yeah I don't know when I'll use that
ever
we'll see
if it ever comes in handy
so wait it said something about me only
having to kill this guy right
I wonder if I go up there because it's
kind of like a shortcut
if these ones will follow immediately
hmm
[Music]
it would definitely take them a moment
right
[Music]
um
take me quite some time to move all of
them
okay well
no Hill I forgot again
so now I think we can start opening
destroy oh
what what should I
oh
[Music]
I can't completely break it one can
almost break it
I'll just do the fight book
quiz works
oh
I've been in a terrible terrible Rabbit
Hole by the way please help me guys
I've been watching so many
um
did I already tell you murder
interrogation
uh
uh videos documentaries
many I
have rabbit hole before
and now I'm in it again
and can't help it
I love those
they're so interesting it's like it's I
guess it's one thing about it is just
it's nice to watch people who are like
more [\h__\h] up than
anyone you know
which kind of is a little bit of a
relief I guess makes you feel like oh
there's worse people
nice
is it really nice though
[Music]
I healed
and hmm I guess the other one is just if
I ever end up hang on in that situation
oh [\h__\h] nice
and then I know a lot about how to not
seem suspicious
no but there's actually some really
insane cases there man
so insane
okay girl can you go over there to heal
no God damn it
God damn it but you could heal the
Dragon
foreign
it doesn't have to be that I get
interrogated for something extreme like
that I might it might just be
interrogated for something more harmless
and you
and uh yeah
um
should I charge her well now it's kind
of too late I already opened up the
gates to hell
[Music]
foreign
no I have nothing to tell you but
you never know what happens
ah
spoke with Gouda recently about this
um
man good I have been talking more
in the past few days
she gets me enough she gets the rabbit
hole
told me she wasn't that one too
I think everyone falls into that rabbit
hole once and I don't feel so bad about
it
has she been doing well
um
[Music]
no this is not enough for a clip
don't say Clippers hello I have really
nothing to say except that I talked to
her and then she's doing well
[Music]
and let me think
guys should I move her back up to charge
I don't know
it's already too late isn't it
[Music]
should I oh okay okay
well done
[Music]
I moved the top guy first
oh dear okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
five second clip
no one clip it
maybe it will become an advertisement
for my Fire Emblem stream
that's dangerous
I could go there and heal myself or I
could go there and attack
and I don't like this
currently
[Music]
huh
um thank you
dramatic zooms and flashbacks down the
streams to cut to True Crime clip
very very
dramatic choke the point with Louis
Louis who's Louie
I am I already moved him
um
okay don't go there let's just go here
that seems like I could survive it and
I'll heal myself
thank God he's got a vulneri
foreign
[Music]
don't know about charging him again
charging himself don't worry he'll be
fine
she might be charging though maybe it's
shorter if I go this way
okay okay okay
okay
let me stand by on my team uh you know
we've lost Empire
it's really like
weird because
you know
I would say
we just like talk normally
uh the guy arrived and we ate some food
and I mean we had just like a really
normal
really yeah
really normal conversation and then we
stream together and it was all good but
it wasn't until after the stream that we
really
connected over music because she's not
only
into J-pop
like me
like idle group specifically
no she's also really into K-pop as well
[Music]
so that got me really excited like no
matter what group's name I would uh
mention
she would know it except for new jeans
new jeans is the only one that I could
teach her about
and she really liked it I was so proud
[Music]
I was so proud showing her you good bro
showing her new jeans because like they
are just something to show off
they're so fresh
their sound is so nice
[Music]
they're so cute
she immediately found an Oshi in the
group too
this is good they really can't get much
further because they're blocking
themselves
foreign
[Music]
right so first
you go over here
did she show you any groups you did not
know I know all of them but it's just
that I'm
[Music]
I
in terms of Japanese idol groups I
mostly care about hello project about
others I don't care that much
[Music]
even though I know a lot about the
groups but I don't really support them
but she knows and supports a lot of
Japanese algorithms she's like a DDD
that a demo dice
foreign
[Music]
she's very very
knowledgeable
showed me I guess she showed me
something I didn't really know like uh
she likes some
some male J-pop groups too
like some big ones
and she showed me some like concert
footage and was like look at this it was
really cool I'm like I guess yeah that
they do some cool stuff in their
concerts yeah
[Music]
move him out of the way
or should I just attack oh never mind no
I don't mind
[Music]
wait did he already attack
I'm confused is that just yeah no he
didn't attack
but this is
are they all gonna throw access at me I
don't think that's perfect
I don't I don't wanna okay so I when I
what I want to try is put him here
coaster
because it doesn't kill that dude though
but wait I still have wait then let's
give the EXP to the Mage Charlie
oh wait that doesn't do any damage to
him at all
[Music]
so difficult
why is it so difficult
[Music]
IES
marvelous
[Music]
okay
I might leave her here because I don't
think she can do much
there yeah
and now oh wait now at least he can do
damage
I guess I broke him or something
worth it weapons
[Music]
but now
he's a target for a lot of attacks they
both are but they're both very bulky I
think so
[Music]
okay okay
y'all said he would be fine
I bought a hindrance to divide Phoenix
in this shape for now I must fall back
yeah
[Music]
was that the boss
no
it was maybe the other like strong guy I
don't know strong looking guy
[\h__\h]
what do you think I was so fine I think
we have still enough units it's getting
a little bit uh close though
[Music]
Louis Vuitton like it's nothing
that's why he gets away excuse me he
wasn't stealing on let's do it
[Music]
okay you can go now
wait can
she could teleport now right
do I really want to send her into that
Ward Zone
[Music]
don't want to
he could come closer though but it's
kind of like you know everyone's in the
way here
okay we can take this one down make some
space
I'll break him even won't get any dams
back
[Music]
oh my God
thank you
[Music]
I won't let that stand
it's really difficult right here though
I got no space
[Music]
attack armor knight of clown which one
is the armor line
[Music]
I don't know this one
plan yeah it's not a kill though
but we can do that
or I attack this one then the RNG
changes then I should then should be a
kill but um
[Music]
thank you
I won't change ah this alone could
change the earth
okay let's uh go for the big guy
and then attack the small one again lose
my lens
true that changes to RNG too okay
[Music]
come on
82 is really more than enough
that's what I like to see today
six Shield really looks like could be
one of kisara's shields
okay
now
I can move him here but it wouldn't be a
Kill
uh
maybe not
as he waits another round
so what's a what a waste
I can't really get her in any range
unless
if I move her
maybe here to
heal
from
uh
Alfred I mean
then I could move her here you know what
I mean
what timezone was not kind
of water in Japan trip Tangerine was
delicious let's make more money thank
you I'll read it properly sometime
[Music]
it's gonna end badly good oh
um look at that
but when he attacks now
oh wait never mind they'll go for her if
she stands there
it's gonna say that the counter will
kill him
but yeah no that's
she'll probably die
okay
[Music]
I think
I think I'll do a warp oh wait I can't
warp there
wait no I didn't even
mind
Okay so
I can warp here
[Music]
she's just who do I wanna kill and she's
a big Target for everyone if I put her
here though yeah work behind Louie
[Music]
okay and then they come take down him it
leaves them
[Music]
not good
no another one hit kill unfortunately
that would be too easy
it's not an AOE right
[Music]
mmm
I reminded before then or died
no we'll be fine we'll manage this
should I go for the 1hp or should I save
this for another time
[Music]
what
warp strike General use Archer on Ax use
it that's so much detail how about for
finish them up and sit in front of
Celine what
thank you for the effort but I don't
understand
I don't understand and um
I'll just bring her back normal name
start to spear guy downstairs move
bander where he is
Bender's gone
Bender's dead
accident
[Music]
but if I don't move him here
they'll also all go for him one day I
have to put him here
for protection sake
yeah
that will protect my Mage at least
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] hey why did that do no damage
you could have killed him there
oh you can move away uh but then yeah
well
then he's not protecting him
it's not like he my Mage Will Survive
dead Ryder's Bane though
lower difficulty
[Music]
we're in trouble here we are
maybe he'll miss is there a chance of
him missing
[Music]
I could kill that dude with a warp still
but that's such a waste of a war but he
is a really strong soldier with that
weapon
the question of how much is that worth
to me
is my biggest problem yeah besides the
boss
[Music]
is he safe there at all
I feel like I'd rather lose my Archer
than my Mage in this situation because
there's nothing for her to shoot down
anyway is there
[Music]
what do you think about that using her
as a meat Shield
that's true right
over that's a plan do it make the
sacrifice or we sacrifice of the warpers
already and we already made her move
all right I'll do it
[Music]
I can't take down the iron guy right so
um might as well do some damage to this
one
[Music]
well don't look guys don't look United
don't look death is coming
thank you
six bags
blocked the ax nicely but it still hits
some important organs
in her body
oh [\h__\h] wait oh
sick please
why don't they attack the mage
salvageable Die Young
is it though
thing
okay
[Music]
this is still kind of shitty because
I can really not do much in this
formation
but
well
[Music]
shall we start by taking this one down
with magic
he won't attack back right
from the looks of it no he will
oh he will
um
I still have my healer
oh which one do I heal first
[Music]
Louis is like in the middle of the
battlefield you know
kind of needs that heal
[Music]
doesn't he needs to attack though too so
he can't take a voluntary whatever
so I need to heal Lily hi
guys
he's a really strong steel and meat
Shield right now
[Music]
that's good
um
can't kill them
shitty healer too
I might go came over on this one
[Music]
and she was charging I couldn't move her
until now she was charging
but I don't know if I should move her
down this path or
oh
secret skill
you're right he could strike this whole
line
but
I would have to move away the mage
and
but he could still move after he strikes
them
because I was worried about his HP
afterwards but if I leave him there
I know four is better
[Music]
indeed
What if I
attack this one then finish him up with
the Mage but that's like such a waste of
potential I feel like
and the next turn
I don't know
why is it so difficult
ah after I take down this one I could
warp her in that exact spot take down
this one hopefully I might not do enough
damage though
[Music]
no
link an attack from Alfred's place
[Music]
so should I just move them away from for
safety now
[Music]
with him here
and then have Celine do do something
hard gold is hard
yeah
yeah it's really difficult to move him
now though
don't move him away then everyone goes
for my weaklings there
[Music]
I can heal he can use the healing item
yeah
I wish I could just like switch those
two
[Music]
right now because I feel sorry for him
because he's making my diet
if he dies then
wait that's here
it goes down to free HP if I do that
[Music]
so we have an acid to lose my friend
should be prioritized
Alfred should be prioritized
[Music]
with that and move Louie there instead
let them die without killing them
[Music]
no no no no no
see he does 12 damage but the dude has
19 health
the only way to make it a certain kill
as if I first threw some damage with
someone else
which can
well I can't
I can't first of all see
let's move him away
let's heal him
see what Celine can do
[Music]
kill him
100 okay
that is helpful
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay okay
thank God I love her
she's not only cute
and then
I worry about him now though
What if I
[Music]
am in
I can't
write his pain
you can't use that right
so my options right now is do some
damage on the horse and then I I don't
know I couldn't even finish it with both
of them
I think they will go to kill him
the Mage next turn right
it's too bad
[Music]
wait he can use the right of Spain
right is being against what
and the only thing that worries me then
is that they'll go for my healer you
know because she stands right there
but maybe she'll survive for one ahead
oh it can't kill it we'll leave him at
one HP but then I can use some magic and
kill him off
wait
[Music]
no no
it has no charge left there's a zero
[Music]
one HP is frustrating yeah
and my my protagonist is so far too man
she's just like
[Music]
sucks
well
okay okay close your eyes again it's too
faithful to look at it
she's alive
[Music]
how long though okay okay they go for
him
[Music]
yeah
it's okay don't it's not like my healer
can do that much damage but we do kind
of appreciate the healing oh
[Music]
that's okay that's okay that's okay it's
okay friends it's okay
free for whatever you are
oh it's not a thief
cure
[Music]
there's a line here I could do it with a
Warp
but it won't reach all the way here
right
but I need that damage right now I think
I think I'll do it
[Music]
it isn't my sucker
Alfred engaged to oh wait why am I
saying no no not that one yeah yeah uh
Alfred Alfred that's what I want to do
is it what if I move them away could
they reach no right
you can reach when engaging
okay
[Music]
definitely
do some important damage here
how does it work again
is that how it works
override with the writer's Bane
yeah okay
two kills one almost killed
oh that's that's like oh two kills
oh yeah
oh oh yeah baby
but I
don't know if I want to keep him there
moving back to the left or maybe to the
right
oh wait oh
that's that's not very safe
their arches
[Music]
okay I can take this one now seemingly
not giving up yet not giving up
oh
92 92 okay okay okay
one Archer down
don't say that it's looking good again
not gonna give up
no you must have gotta
God you existently
then
I could but maybe from here yeah kill
that ax guy
[Music]
not if I kill him first
we'll see if that was worth it
but the
[Music]
this one
oh
oh let me go back then
[Music]
hey I don't wanna warp though
actually
would it have been a kill if I engaged
[Music]
probably
we'll see we'll see I I
am engaged
but after that I guess maybe I'll
teleport with her up to the boss but
then the others are still so far you
don't want to have her fighting up there
alone and who knows maybe the bus
has more HP than it really seems
like
also that didn't really help
but it's okay I guess
[Music]
no I do want her to stand here though
don't allow them to spread out is this
me allowing them to spread out
why because I'm scared that if I walk
here then the path is free for the
Archer
to attack my Mage but he might even do
that from here I don't know
I don't think he will
there's magic in melee
[Music]
I'll shoot her then
Choice man
what
[Music]
you want me to do them huh Echo
ah
[Music]
that they can't counter that's what you
mean
okay I guess so
it's a good argument
to
um
okay
now why is this [\h__\h] still so far away
[Music]
got more
uh range by engaging even right like
walking range
rip Clan yeah
yeah he'll cleanse when I use an item on
him I can't do that huh
oh yeah so this sucks is the unit
huh
hero always arrives last no it shouldn't
be like that
[Music]
it's okay it's okay we can still do it
maybe
if not then I'm gonna cry and don't
wanna redo this it takes so long
oh yeah bus which is not this early
please survive not Clan necessarily but
yeah I saw that coming but I want
I want to do a warp after this so please
please survive that
[Music]
that's a lot of damage man uh
kill me now monster
oh
[Music]
okay I have one two three four units
left
they have more units than me
but
I don't know I don't know
should I just
immediately warp over there
now because she doesn't have many turns
left
just wait one more turn noise oh no
that can kill one
and
[Music]
yeah
I can you can recharge down there huh
I guess they will not come at me they
seem to be stuck there
okay
then maybe the priority would be her not
dying right now
[Music]
do some kills first then
just do what I can right now
[Music]
finally Kiana is doing some work for the
first time today
took you long enough
[Music]
okay
she's not engaged yet that's okay for
now
let me put you
here and use a heel
she got plenty
okay full HP let's go and then
it's too too close
[Music]
if I'm ready I'll I'll I'll I'll wait
I'll wait here
or do I want a bait maybe I do want to
do I wanna bathe I bring at least that
one maybe just the one here
[Music]
do you have vulneries
foreign
[Music]
I'll use one I'll use one
full HP okay
oh it's a horse yes
I feel like I'm doing a soccer match to
announcement thingy oh
I moved they all moved
I didn't expect that
okay okay and let's take the other horse
down with a ride is Bane too how about
that
[\h__\h] go we can do this we can still
do this
never give up
give up oh he's alone he may have two HP
bars but I think with four pretty strong
units
[Music]
I think uh it's okay
just want to cover
um selling because I think she has the
least like defense
[Music]
and
how do we do should I just go here or go
here wait maybe here and then
um depending on how many vulnerries I
have okay
one here just for safety okay okay
now
engage I'll I'll go for an attack with
qawwa now
[Music]
and unleash a furry of blows
okay okay okay okay
is this how we should do it let's get
engaged okay do it do it
oh we're doing it
feels it feels proper to do the first
hit and maybe also the last hit we'll
see of kiwawa I'll show you no mercy
prepare
to die okay
[Music]
when were you ever looking my boots
please get away from me
[Applause]
[Music]
let's go girl
hell yeah
[Music]
half down
on the first HP bar anyone you're good
this one's a tough opponent he can keep
on fighting even after taking the Fatal
blow
and it's that job
they have Revival ah are they warning me
about the second age people
keep attacking these enemies until they
use up all the Revival stones
category
should I do it should I do the work I
have to I have to I have to
I can do it from a distance too though
[Music]
don't underestimate my princess
foreign
[Music]
looks so nice
me I'm real scared
I'll rip you another [\h__\h]
oh
sheesh lost my Lance
[Music]
12.
it's a bit oof but
wait what if I die it's really nearby
oh he didn't break though
didn't he
oh wait no he broke
almost
killed oh he broke
okay we're good
maybe with all our power combined we can
take him down
[Music]
Ryan's being 76 I don't want to risk it
risk that so I'm going for Iron Man
[Music]
no
my precious
[Music]
he's an absolute MVP in this one
I have to give that to him
yeah this could be this could be uh this
could be it this could be it it was so
[\h__\h] close
wait he'll die if I do that though wait
can I get in the kill like one attack
from here
oh yeah I think so
yes
yes oh he's broken
well anyway we'll do it before
cleaner kill
one hit
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah
he's running
he's a coward
oh we got a sheriff robe cool
Spencer Grant Max HP plus 5c user
permanently X expend what does that mean
expend I can use it once or so
uh
[Music]
I don't know send this one then
one time use okay
don't know who I will give it to maybe
the protagonist
so
so devastating if I played it on classic
we would have lost so many units oh my
God
that was quite something I really
thought
this might be dangerous
really close call it
I've read mother is in the background
she's okay
that's a relief
She's Not Dead really I mean My Curse is
broken
she looks fine
thank you all of you for rescuing
my children you're safe what oh really
we have a guest mother someone came all
the way from Lifest to see you
Divine Phoenix
it's an honor I'm glad I could break my
curse of killing mothers
and see you so alive and happy Oh
[Music]
I love her hair
this is my absolute pleasure to welcome
him
we are just in time to rescue Celine
the Divine ones summoned emblem
extraordinary
thank you sincerely you have my teeth
my family is safe because
[Music]
don't ask don't remind me again we
should have written everyone a message
on Discord like hey Queen remember that
don't ask me it's kind of like breaking
my heart every time I talk about her
ah
I know
[Music]
she did my mom did will you be my mommy
now
that's awesome I'm so sorry
[Music]
some Intruders entered the castle they
tried to kill me but
she gave her life to protect mine
foreign
[Music]
the pain of losing their mother
yokata
I got rid of the hair because uh it
wasn't working
next time next time and put on my wig
again
my heart goes out to you
look at me we've only just met and here
I am laying my grave at your face I just
wish I could have saved her too summer
[Music]
um
Pepsi week well I cannot take away your
sorrow perhaps I can help you bear it
foreign
[Music]
I can only imagine how painful that was
yeah
it was a short lived time
for now allow yourself to grieve knowing
that I crave with you
until I think she should be adopted it's
that simple
thank you Queenie
no kindness It's almost like she's here
with me
how are you feeling hi
um
right now
I'm sorry Divine ones
[Music]
but if I hadn't left when I did what
might have happened to you Celine or
your queen
I'm proud to serve people in need like
my mother did
thank you
philosian leader she said her kingdom
released the Bell Dragon
are appearing in Aliens again
now there's no question that the Bell
dragons after the Rings
which means we need to hurry cut them
off before they can reach the next one
your country's ring may I take it
can I also take your daughter and maybe
possibly not 100 necessary but your son
too
send you some money just a daughter
would be fine
of course the king that mothering gives
it with love trust and Grace
well can we take her
there's something you should know
however
most
come on
my kingdom has another emblem ring in
possession
[Music]
does that math add up
I wouldn't know
another ring
it was Kept Secret to avoid conflict
that's really smart though
behind it
knowledge of this ring has been confined
to the monarchs of the Ring
however now that the fell dragon has
arisen it is best to dispel the shroud
of secrecya
six rings and [\h__\h] okay well yes okay
laughs
it is commonly thought that the Divine
Dragon gave one rank to each country's
leaders
why
so no never
um
sounds like a girl
ensure that no one would find that the
ring was hidden away from the castle
it's down here
let's go look for it oh man I thought I
could see it now
rest in a shrine on the brilliant border
okay I was on our way to Brodie and we
can get it
you know what
yeah mother took me there after father
died of course there's always one parent
that isn't alive
why why is that a thing
she told me to keep the location in mind
at the time I didn't know why maybe
budget reasons
[Music]
now it makes sense
I Was preparing you for the day you
became king
[Music]
yeah we also don't know who my dad is
I'll take everyone to the shrine from
there I can continue on with the Divine
Phoenix
[Music]
why did I say the Vine I just realized
that I
used to say that I'm really a Divine
Phoenix am I
or am I not
so you are leaving Alfred
I want to do my part to end this war
m
yeah
blessing mother I'm going to help the
Divine Phoenix bring peace to Elias
[Music]
she's going on her own I don't have to
offer candy
mother I would like to join as well
I like them
[Music]
look how have them gladly
you have my blessing I know you will
serve the Divine Phoenix of Honor
able
this is a difficult promise to make when
you play on classic
oof can't swear that can we
and one condition swear to me that you
will come back alive
I can rewind don't worry I I'm not
playing classic ladies it's fine he'll
come back she'll come back
thank you very much
spend eight hours by the way
I trust that you will take some time to
respiratory
the journey ahead will be artists but
you know that you are all in my prayers
May Good Fortune shine upon you know
oh
I love my cat Paul cup
so nice
more money
oh you finished
I think and my throat is kind of dead
but
oh yeah I guess we still have to talk to
them and then we can go
all right
oh sorry you had
n't sorry About You movie
yes you did out it yourself I did you
did you did outdo yourself I had to read
my success to close monitoring of the
enemies movements
no you attribute it to me please and my
genius
I can't thank you enough for saving
fareen but let me start by taking you to
the shrine
hell yeah gladly
my Mother's Day thank you for all you
have done for us shall have my Aid in
return
please get some rest here before you set
out I will be praying for your safety
um
foreign
talks let me pick up some items
oops
oh
[Music]
iron ingots and on the other side and
then it will end the gaming portion here
for today what the [\h__\h] I feel like in
eight hours we've barely achieved
something
but I guess
yeah that's just how it is these battles
especially on the hard are kind of long
this place is gorgeous
it's gorgeous squishy
damn so big
I finished five chapters out of 6 26.
yeah I'm true but still
on easy mode we would definitely be
taking less time for all this
hmm
heart is very challenging but
I know if maybe for the sake of
you know
progressing
efficiently
if we want to move to easy mode
in the future I don't know
I don't know
[Music]
I'm not hiding up
ondo motto smoothie could show
[Music]
yeah for entertainment purpose heart is
good
although I don't think some people will
get frustrated
but for
for
entertainment purpose the easy is also
good because then the streams will not
be like then I will not leave like 30
parts and we can move on to another
thing
earlier
I don't know I'll think about it I'll do
another part in heart
I think the next one will still be in
hard
hey there you're the Divine Dragon right
got a second talk oh you want to join
mine too maybe
[Music]
okay yeah we need a Blackness and a
clove here okay
okay
no need to even discuss this
I'll give you a ticket straight to
heaven
can promise you getting back till ever
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
classic mode for him
oh
my channel
[Music]
who is that she looks short and she's
floating
[Music]
I was expecting to get at least one
machine
please don't support me
this music is so freaky too
at least now I know that the mayor is
dead
yes but there's another Divine Dragon to
take her place I can't believe that
Beast had a child
let's explain why she was so willing to
sacrifice her life
[Music]
just really long arms and hamsters
questions
the battle at the first castle took its
toll we're in no shape for another
confrontation
my best I know for a spell believe them
be for now
okay
interesting
sounds familiar
um I don't think that's a character that
we already met in the game
at least like in terms of voice I don't
think we've heard it before
but probably you heard the voice
somewhere else before right
amiibo gazebo is open
I don't know well I will oh
I will no no uh
safe
who's on
it's been seven and a half hours of
gameplay
8 hours and 13 minutes of stream
um
that good job today thank you
we will continue Fire Emblem The Day
After Tomorrow
is Super Chat reading we'll focus on
super chats
[Music]
foreign
and tomorrow yeah so I think I said
I would like Read Super chapters maybe
after this but I'm tired and we're
reading them tomorrow anyway
so is it okay
[Music]
I've been tired the whole day
yeah tomorrow
dedicated Super Chat stream
tomorrow at least I don't have you know
like a limited studio time or whatever
tomorrow I can go as long as I want so
I'll do my best to hopefully maybe even
finish
yeah so that way finally have that out
of the way
if you haven't seen the schedule for
this week then check it out it's on
Twitter and on the community board I
posted it there if you remember and you
haven't downloaded the members only
wallpaper yet then do it now because
month is ending soon
and now we'll get for more than just
four super chats I promise
listen
I'm telling you
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] suddenly YouTube wants to
confirm my identity
[Music]
why would you why why
was I logged out or something why isn't
this is so Random I wonder if maybe it's
because some like general or so
dinner so
and let me confirm it's me
because you went to Japan we're about
done wouldn't it be before I streamed
um
anyway yeah well well well
I had fun today
so nice to be back in a game like this
and a game where I feel comfortable in I
mean the hard mode has been stressing me
a bit but it's been overall fun it's not
that stressful because at least you can
take your time to think about you can't
even reverse
even though that feels like baby mode
but it's a feature so
back at the uterus map
it won the last fight yeah
and I really really really looked very
impossible at some point
after screwing around so much oh
more shops wow fancy actually just
wanted to pick up that item
yeah I turned it around
put the pebble
okay
I'll probably have to pick up pick it up
again next time oh well
look like your chest game hey yeah
um what's the rack with brute forcing
brood forcing
[Music]
who's best girl for you right now
the the black and white girl and the
princess
so far but
I think I will suffer many many doki
dokis
in the future Parts because there's
still so many characters to meet
it's really exciting but I wonder is
that like a
it's definitely a maximum of how many
warriors I can always take with me but
what about like uh recruiting them to
come into my insomnia is that pretty
much unlimited like whoever
I meet I can bring up here
that's unlimited okay wow okay I will
have so many choices then
this is so calm right now I feel like
I'm in an mmorp in an anime free to play
anime MMORPG
honestly the graphics
kind of it could be
the map there and all that just lacking
on like an interface like with my
hotkeys
F1 to F12
you get what I mean give me those vibes
right now
um I'm uh on a calm server 3am on the
marketplace there's no one around not in
the most popular
City where all the high level people
gather I'm in a low-level City
those times of
anime producer
I loved those so much
I love those
since our DLC is it the same DLC as the
one where I get the uh
free houses characters
I might actually get those still waiting
for blue protocols oh yeah but they
actually announced
um I already forgot when it was but
there's progress and it's releasing I
think there's a release date or so
[Music]
season pass okay okay
so I think I'll be playing blue protocol
and when it comes out and that's it
I'm so excited so you guys get
guys let's go find the link I never
remember pretty of my taste you know I
played Final Fantasy before and I liked
it but it's not really like my ideal and
more pretty
so I want to play Blue protocol but I
think the Japanese version comes out
first
and I don't know if I can hold back
[Music]
playing it waiting until the
no
overseas one but I might have to maybe
I'll just play like one time on the
Japanese server if I can
and then after that just wait until
en server yeah
oh I'm so excited
online games
knit
just tell us when
I shut up I already forgot when it was
releasing but I retweeted it when it was
like announced
recently actually not that long ago
I hear the tales of remake Ambassador no
I'm not but
I want to you know play a little bit of
it when it releases anyway I don't know
if I will play the whole game but um
because I already played Tesla Symphonia
in my life you know
maybe it won't be a full playthrough I
don't know
depends
[Music]
it's just a little bit problematic that
we have so many
uh like our jrpg is lined up right now
already
um
if I could spread it out more that would
be nice but then again certain things
certain games are just way more hyped to
play right when they release of course
so
have to think about it no I'm not
planning on playing Persona on stream
because I think we've got enough members
latching on to that already
and it's it's a very long commitment
[Music]
oh
thank you Muffin
it's a near raid
in Final Fantasy 14
. it's cool
it
I have to check that out
yeah after the Riser was delayed by one
month
from my point of view they can even
delay it another month
I don't know if I'll play that though on
stream
depends maybe maybe if they allow
monetization because like Honestly
though it's it's gonna be many many
episodes and
how long how many episodes did my
previous Riser games have streams
how many
[Music]
this was just like one stream you know
whatever can't monetize it whatever
but
it would be probably at least eight
maybe ten parts
it takes up a lot of streams yeah at
least 10.
that I can't monetize
maybe they will allow monetization this
time I don't know but
as a traditional thick waifu yeah well
but the thing is you know right now we
already have a chill long jrpg
if it overlaps and I definitely will not
play it right away
um at the moment it looks like it will
have at least a little bit of a
um overlap
um
we have very good time sync yeah yeah
everything's so time intensive
that doesn't seem right but yeah
oh yeah I guess uh GTA was like that too
but I think I was able to get super
chats right I forgot about ryzer super
chats were also I think no no not sure
anymore I'm intensive 10. come intensive
yes
time consuming yeah
anyway
yeah it's nice to be back guys
it's nice to be wrecking my throat once
again why do I always get so tired doing
these man I really need to start
drinking coffee I need to become a
coffee person
ah that would help so much because I
don't want to like drink
energy drinks all the time
that's so bad for your health
it's been it's eight and a half hours
almost
does not wake me up at all there's no
nothing in there that would wake you up
[Music]
coffee not good for throat
um
definitely better than an energy drink
my eyes
foreign
[Music]
let me see
oh pretty late okay I think I'll
schedule it schedule it once I wake up I
want to crawl into bed with my kitakatos
now has been so nice cuddling with them
again foreign
[Music]
they're the best they're so cute
thank you guys
[Music]
more Fire Emblem following soon
uh I'm not installing it feels weird to
say goodbye
uh I want to play more
but I'm too tired
thank God we're playing more very soon
um
okay guys
thanks for spending your time with me
out of all the people you could choose
foreign
thank you
I'll see you soon what time is it mom is
half past 11 pm here
but I woke up at eight and I did have a
nap though a good nap um coffee so sleep
slap slap yesterday I took
wait yesterday I arrived
like
I don't know what time in the morning or
so you know I had an early morning
flight
obviously I I guess like wait tangent
because like I think yesterday I was
awake since like four or so because
uh
uh uh that I had to stay awake on the
Helsinki airport and then and then in
the small flight I didn't sleep in the
small flight so then I got back home and
then I took a nap at like what 12 or
something like that and then I was awake
and then I took another nap and then I
was awake and then I think I took
another nap and then I slept for real
but all those snaps were pretty short I
think one was long and then two short
ones like really short ones I took so
many naps yesterday free naps free
breakfasts
free cats no not for
unfortunately not free cats yet
[Music]
two hats
two cats one raccoon
three pets
could save free pets
seven breaths
oh five onion rings
and five onion rings
eh
five onion rings
free big naps free breakfast free little
pets and uh and two little hats on onion
head
okay that's good okay yeah I'm good I'm
good
well Phantom Rings oh twelve emblem
foreign
that's a good one
okay okay I guess I'll go on
I was just chilling
all right
[Music]
um
bye-bye and in German we say happy
nothing
[Music]
mm-hmm
Oh wrong side sorry
accent is there oh [\h__\h]
don't look at that
Dragon something weird behind me bye-bye
[Music]
and now
oh the real proper ending it's back
[Music]
wow
welcome to the usual ending screen
[Music]
wow wow
wow
yeah we'll be wondering where my body
went and the hands
[Music]
nice everything back to usual
um
foreign
[Music]