[Music]
This program is
sponsored by the following sponsors
[Music]
Worker 19v
Young and
talented  Goods Good
evening,
everyone. How
are you doing? Welcome back, everyone. I
always explain the program at the beginning of the talk, so
please wait.
Default talk is an interview talk show about English-speaking models.
The purpose is
While live interpreting, the
main
purpose is to let people overseas know more about Japanese talent, but Japanese people are
also welcome, and
it's okay to write in Japanese.This is
provided by the host Takanashi Chara.
This time, it's the 19th time. No, it's me.
[Music]
Everyone says yes.
[Music] It's
Wolf Mio! I
'm the crackling Wolf Mio. Please take care of me.
[Music]
No, I don't
call it the Unusual House.  It was so rare that I
realized that it was terrifying.Chara was talking
about what happened earlier, but
Chara probably lived in the Kansai region before, so she
ended up focusing on the house.  I do
n't know what to say, but I'm so happy Yay yay! It's
our duo. [Music] Greetings from us. Yes, it's Uchi Uchi. It's Wolf Mio.  It's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, I'm always
asking for that, so yeah, it's
okay, it's okay, I don't
know why.  I can't do this, so Bill
Sabin Asias,
Ikebukuro Moment IsIt'sback
otheren,
and that
one, I wonder if it's not compatible with YouTube
[Music]
How can this app also crash
?
But then that one is also a standing picture  That might
be fine. No, no, no, no, that's not the only problem. That's the
problem.
[Music]
Yesterday.
After that one time, I
tested it and it was fine.  I
wonder if it's going to stabilize. I'm still a little bit still. I don't want to give up. I'm going to get my seniors back first. [Music] My OK OK [Music] I'm back. I'm back. I'll adjust the screen here. Okay.
[Music] I'm
sorry.  I'm sorry, but things have
suddenly gotten weird since yesterday, but things
may have stabilized.
So, let's get to the questions now. I
hope everything goes well from here, and I'll
do it.
Ok.
What kind of activities have you been doing
lately
? I
go to Aso on Monday mornings,
and I always do it once, and then I
sing and sing,
and I'm
also playing some
simulation-type games.  I'm playing a game like this.What's the
simulation like?
Oh, I
want to make fireworks explode in a residential area, which is dangerous.Also, I want to make fireworks explode in a residential area.Also, I want to
hit the sun with the sun.Ah, the goddess.I see, it
seems OK.That's
interesting.If you
hit the sun with the sun, it will
explode.  The
sun will disappear, and both suns will disappear. Or the whole universe
won't disappear.
This one won't disappear, but the Earth will
disappear. Wow, Mr.
Okeyami.
Someday, when there are two suns,
what will happen?  You know what's going to happen.
How did Miyu-senpai find Hololive in the first place,
and
what was the reason for the file? Ah,
Hololive was,
um, I
was classmates with Fubuki at school,
and uh,
Fubuki was my friend who played that game with me.
But recently, I
thought that people weren't playing with me.
[Music] I was
working on Hololive,
and then I saw Hololive and
thought I'd like to try it too.
So, umm, I
had an interview.
[Music] I see,
especially.  Was there a reason why you decided to enter the game
rather than the usual ``Diary 3rd Generation Student''
?When I
auditioned for Gamers, I
told the shop name that I like playing games.I
see.  I had the misconception that Yago was an
extremely good at playing amazing games.
[Music] I
see. So we
decided to create Hololive Gamers, and when we joined, we decided to
create Hololive Gamers.
That's right, Miyu-san was the reason for that. That's
interesting. OK
[Music]
Mio-senpai was
Did any of the other gamers other than Fubuki-senpai have regular live shows at that time? They didn't. That's right, Mio-senpai.
Well, since they're so good at games, they
decided to make a game, so I
guess they started looking for other members.They
said it was too late for that, so the second
generation members debuted that summer.
Since we debuted in the winter, there
was a little too much time between us, so we
decided to form a new group, and
since I love games, I
played the Hololive game as the leader of Fubuki.  I
see, the
two of us were in Gamers,
but the two of us
made our debut in Games. Ah,
that's
interesting. At that time, I
hadn't really watched Hololive yet.  I didn't
understand it at all.I'm glad I was
able to do it Miyu-senpai.It
's quite unusual.I feel like it's
unusual.I don't really do things like this anymore.I
see.Okay, I
'll ask you a few questions.  There are
things that I wanted to convey to people overseas that I couldn't say due to the language barrier, but I
think that's true quite a lot.My
Japanese is Japanese, or rather, my English is
really
bad, and I end up saying weird things,
so
[Music]
That's right.  I
guess I can only speak very simple English,
so
even when people from overseas are watching me,
it's difficult for me to answer them.Hmm,
but I
know that they are watching me.  So,
like all the Japanese fans,
I'm really happy,
and
even though I can't speak English, I'm really grateful.  I
think viewers will probably rely on the subtitle clippings a lot.
[Music]
Also, there's someone who translates Myuu-senpai's chat
into English. I
wonder if they'll give up on Twitter.  I
get translations in various languages ​​such as English,
but I wonder
how it goes on broadcasts.I wonder if
people who can't speak Japanese are good for going overseas.You either have to
rely on translations or learn Japanese.It's
a bit more.  I just want to work hard little by little.
Good luck.
[Music] I
mentioned it a little bit, but
what's your favorite type of streaming so far? For example,
games, karaoke,
chat collaborations, or the big projects that big-breasted seniors often do.  What do you
like most
?It
's difficult.I really like planning,
but Chiara-chan also does it, so I
think you can understand it, but it's
quite difficult, very difficult, and it's
very difficult.Well, I
can't do many things like this.It's
true, but it became really interesting.
Sometimes I feel really happy,
don't I?
That makes me really happy, but
yeah
[Music]
But I like streaming songs, I guess karaoke is what I like most, but I
like singing, so I
think it's great. OK, so
imations.
Baby Wanadu
Senpai
is there
[Music] I
see, next
Next
question, but yes, I have
prepared an image.Eh,
distribution.Hmm,
heart to Towels-san.  I'd
like you to tell me. I'm
really curious too. Is it
okay to translate that difficult question? It might be difficult.
Please go ahead. Well, to
explain it simply,
we're
planning a project called Hololive Kindergarten,
and we'll have a drawing competition at that kindergarten.
Yes, I
asked them to draw a picture with the theme, ``I wish there were animals like this.''
Fubuki
drew a pigeon towel, and I was
like, ``
Is this what it looked like?''
Completely
no.  It's the one who drew Daddy's
Fountain,
but wait, I
think there's the original blizzard one. So I'll stop here. It
was like this [music]
[Laughs] It's so
nostalgic. I wish there
were animals like this.  No, I'm in trouble.
No, I don't know. Fubuki
played the role of Uchimomo, a teacher, but I
see, she was
n't a kindergartener. She
was a teacher. She was
trying to please the teacher, and the
lower half of her body was a wolf.  It's cool, so I
said something like I made the lower half of my body look like a wolf.
Ah, I see.
[Music] I haven't
collaborated with Nifubuki since yesterday
[Music]
[Music] It's
been on the bottom right screen ever since.  Yeah,
but first of all, why did you start using it all the time after you just wrote this?
Well, then, I wonder
if I should say um, um, um, um, um, uh, uh, uh, uh, this, uh, um. My teacher
said ah, bodyguard, ah.
[Music]
Papa Izumi.  He wrote it for me, and
then for some reason, the
people who run Hololive, after receiving the illustration, made it work in 2D, and it was really
cool,
so he sent me a GIF image of Gifu.
By putting it on the broadcast screen, it's kind of
like a talisman. It's amazing. Amazing things happen. [Music] That was back when I still had the time to do things like that. Yeah, that's right. I was the type of person who really reacted to the material. The
action wizard side
[Music]  ]
& I
'm Izumi
I.
[Music]
What do you mean?
Thank you for being Naoya. Tell me more about it.
Subaru's ASMR was something like that.
Subaru's ASMR is sold for 100 yen.
Or I heard that too.  That's true. I
see. Desposition. Let's move on to the next question. I sometimes hear the word ``miyoru.''
Please explain what it means.
[Music]
Night
[Laughter] I wonder if it's a
maid
[Music]
[Music] We
made our debut, and it
wasn't even a month after we debuted.
[Music]
We all had a Christmas project.  So we got together,
and if we
lost the game, there was a
punishment game where we
ate cream puffs with wasabi in it.When
there was a punishment game like this,
we
lost
and we ate cream puffs normally.Yes, we
got on the broadcast.  I made a sound that I shouldn't have, and
then I saw this.The festival was the Summer Color Festival.I started saying, ``Look at me, look at me,'' and I said, ``Why don't you do that?''That's why
vomiting
became the common name for ``Miyoru.''  I
see,
yes, it's OK, Sondekuru Sponation is
Christmas,
Wasabi, Cream
Puffs, Survival Sunset
[Music]
Since then, there have been incidents like that from time to time.
Ah, well, sometimes, sometimes, I've
gotten angry, actually.
[Music]
Something bad has happened.  When you put something in your mouth,
like a taste you don't know, it
's quite sensitive.The
inside of your mouth is
n't a sentient team in that sense, it's a
warrior in the original sense,
or rather, it
's delicate.Yeah.  I
think it's OK, Miyu-senpai. I
want to go shopping.
Shinshu skywith
jepto
[Music]
[Music] I
think it's plablema too, so let's
move on to the next question.
[Laughs]
Well, let's talk about vomit.
[Applause] I'll be
saved in the end.  What do you mean?
Oh, that's helpful. Well, actually, now,
yeah, my cat's
name is Tiger. But
yeah, that's why Tiger is often used in that sense,
but in
the past, my cat's name is
Tiger.
What should I say? I know, a water bottle. I used that bottle to
fill up that room with warm drinks, and I
brought it in a water bottle, so
when I opened that thermos bottle, the
sound of the water bottle
made it squeak.
That's right.  Raise the water bottle! It
makes a sound. [Music] When it makes a sound,
everyone screams at that magic water bottle. It's a
water bottle made by a manufacturer called Tiger. I see, it's made
by a company called Daika.
[Music]
Company. I see.
So it has
nothing to do with cats. It's a
relationship you can't see.  No,
it's said that Tiger Tiger can save you. And I've been told that so much that I ended up naming it because it's so weird.
[Music]
Nao.
[Music] I see. That was the
first time I'd heard of it. Well, then, it's
called Cat.  My
senpai
loves cats as much as I do, and I'm
sure the topic of cats will come up a lot in the stream, so I've
prepared a clipping of it.
Let's watch it together. Let's
move on.
[Music]
Enjoy!  Today, I
would like to share with you an audio-only story of the merciless battle between the owner who absolutely wants to be brushed and the cat who absolutely does not want to be brushed.With this, I would
like to wage a war.For now, I
feel that it starts with who is looking for it.  The cat is
probably
feeling something, right? That stamp-like face
is the owner of the cat.
[Laughs]
Sorry, the
owner apologizes for keeping you waiting. Anyway, here
's the first report on the results.  I'm going to let you
do that.
[Music]
Report on the results of the first round.
This is Burn.
So my knee is pretty bad right now, but I
still hate you. I hate you. You
hate me. I get it. It's okay. I'm going to
bite your left arm as hard as I can right now.  I'm
sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm sorry, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, but it
feels surprisingly good, right? It hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it feels surprisingly good, right?
My arm,
my arm, isn't a chicken wing.
Anything, cat.  I'm
sorry, stop it, stop it, stop it,
stop it, I'll get angry, I'll get
angry, we'll get angry too. I'm
sorry, but please
don't try to escape. I
caught you. I want to touch you. Yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes.
Well, this one once
escaped, but as
expected, I think it's important to show who is in a higher position
when it comes to grooming, so
it's this one. I was
getting carried away though.  But even if
it was for you, it's also for you. Yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes,
that's right. My
older sister told me to
shut up and that I
was a very good girl, and that I was sorry,
but I'm a liar. I'm a liar.  I
lined them up,
and this is
what I saw, and the purple one below is the one that uses cat hair as a
tool.
Well, I
kind of thought it would be a lot of work. I see,
it's really
hard.  Well, it's
like this, right?But that
brush, the brush that I use.I
tried using it on my cat, and when I use it,
my cat doesn't like it either, but
when I use a different flush, I never use it.  I
don't mind it.
Ah, maybe I shed too much. I think this type of skin doesn't
like it at all. After this, I'll send you some recommendations for pores.
[Music]
Cat: By the way, the English word for us is
CATSready.  I say,
Crazy Crazy Kate Lady -
That's
right, she's so
fluffy and
fluffy and looks like an alpaca. She
's so cute. She doesn't have any hair, but
she's
fine. She starts doing things that I don't like,
and then she follows me
around and
jumps on me.  It's coming. It's
amazing. It's the
type that comes out. It's
amazing. It takes
courage. It takes a lot of courage.
[Music] Let's
move on to the next question. I
want you to tell me the origin of the fan mark tree.
Yes,
um, we're
here now.  Well, it's
just a little bit, but there are some spiky hairs on the sides of her hair,
right? That
first costume, Caffeine's costume,
had really spiky hair,
and that's what I
thought.The silhouette looked like that tree.
So you
said let's make it a tree with a fan mark silhouette.
Well then, you
said that even before you showed off your design.
[Music]
I see, it seems OK. That's
Okami Mio-senpai.  For example, some
people think that the push mark is a wolf, but it's 3.
Yes, it's no. I
like it because it has some kind of special hidden meaning and people who see it for the first time wonder why it's a tree.  This kind of thing makes
sense.Oh, it's not too easy to understand.It doesn't
feel that way.Yes, I feel like this girl is hiding some kind of secret.It
feels strange.Maybe I'll
get excited.Maybe I'll
want to know more.  It seems like I can't help it.
But when people like that
grow a lot of trees, it kind of
reminds me of the universe, mountains, forests, and wolves.
[Music] I see.
So,
next question 2. Let's
go.
Miu.  There
are a lot of people who like to perform at Ureru at the supermarket.What
made you start playing Ureru?
Well, I
can't play any instruments at all,
but I think
being able to enjoy going to the supermarket makes me a better singer.
That's why I heard that.
Hey, that's why I
wanted to be able to play something.
[Music] I
heard that it's easier to hold down the strings on the ukulele than on the guitar.
[Music]
That's why I
don't have any grip strength.  So, I
thought I'd try playing the ukulele, and I thought, ``Oh, it's easier than the guitar,'' so I
decided to try playing the ukulele.I see, then I found out that
the ukulele was quite fun.
Now you can play the song. I see. With that attitude
[Music]
Week
Grips I'm
already seeing comments in both English and
Japanese
saying that they're feeling soothed.
Thank you, thank you
[Music]
Even better.  I'm really looking forward to it.I'm really looking
forward to it.I
mentioned it a little bit at the beginning, but lately I've
been doing a weekly broadcast called Asami-yu, and
what it's about is
Asami, and lately, it's been
like radio.
For the first 30 minutes, there is a corner where you can read letters, a
corner where you can read letters, a corner where you can
read letters, and a
corner where you can read emails.  It's like we're talking about troubles. I'm
deciding on a theme from time to time.
Ah, I'm starting to like breakfast and what kind of breakfast I
like.
By the way, the
day after tomorrow,
what Asami will do if she wins the lottery.
Hmm, I see. I
registered and posted with the tag Kita.
And then in the
second half of the 30 minute
period, we're doing a corner called ``Reading.'' And in the second half, there's news about the scissors. It's been a
week's worth of Hololive members'
news, and it
looks like they've done it.
On Monday, they're
going to show off their hiragana.
[Music] It's probably
7:30 Japan time.
[Music]
Oh yeah, it's over. Around that
time, it was supposed to be over. The
new time is probably Monday, Japan time.  I'm a talented person,
so it's probably already over.If I
can do it properly this time, that
's the key.I think I
can do it.Today, I was
able to broadcast it like that, so I don't think I'll be able to do it next time.It
's
scary,
scary.I'll
translate it
[Music]
Actually, I've
prepared that for you.First of
all, I would like you to tell me how you
started fortune telling.Yes, when I started fortune telling, I
was the youngest of your juniors.Oh, I see.In
Hololive,  I was the youngest, the youngest, the
junior, but
at that time, I
was a senior [music], but I don't
think it's possible for a starter to say all sorts of things.I see,
so
even seniors can say so many different things.
When I was wondering what it was like to be able to talk about things like this, I
thought I'd like to try fortune
telling, so I decided to try a little bit of fortune telling.
Please let me
hear your request. I
can't post the card on the stream right now,
but I'm going to tell you about the character's fortune-telling.
The card on which that card can be placed
will be submerged in water.
Ah, the cat and cat knocking over the humidifier.  I was hooked
[laughter] I happened to
find a
tarot card where I knocked over the humidifier, and that's when I got soaked.
[Music]
Imagination Let's do it with our imagination
Yes, but we have the cards,
so
yes.  Well then, Tiara-chan,
please tell me what you want to see.
Erasing tomorrow
[Music]
Kiara is
obsessed with my cat, and for years now all I
can think about is her
love for humans.  I can no longer feel that kind of feeling about love
.
Well, it's just a feeling of love. It
doesn't show up at all, I'm
not interested in it at all, and
that's why I'm already worried about it. Um, I'll
love the character again someday.  Or is it possible to love humans? I see. I
'll translate it a bit. It
purifies the air. It's
like a purifier.
Yes, please.
Tarot cards
have very different meanings between upper and lower. Yes,
upper and lower.  I
want Chiara-chan to decide whether to
place the tarot on top of that. I see. Please choose between the right side of the tarot deck that we have, or the top left side.
Right and left.
Let's go. Let's
go.  One was about what Chiara-chan
thinks about love at the moment, and
the other was about [Music] [Music] the future, and the other was about the near future.
Well,
[Music]
Reality and the future.
The reality is now,
the future is now, and the future is now, I see,
and a comprehensive card,
total,
total OK. What is a
good card? It
doesn't really matter if the character stays with that cat until they die.
Actually, any outcome is fine, but if you
host it,
yes, it's
true that right now, yes, it's not so much.  It
's not good, or rather,
the teacher is
isolated from the world right now.
[Music] I
forgot the words.
[Music] That's
right. Um, because I'm
isolated from the world. Yeah, I'm being [
Music]
[Music]
Yeah, that's right, so the current card is.
Right now,
there's a ninja card called the Ninja card,
and Hermit, and
that's the current card, and
Hermit appears in the opposite position.  I
get the impression that they're a little isolated and distant, so it's
true that it might be a little
difficult to fall in love.
[Music]
Ok, I
see. The future is
near.  The future is a star, and a star card
appears.Maybe there will be an unexpected encounter.There is a
possibility.Yes, pass.
[Music]
[Music] It
's a total card.Yes, it's a
journey.
But overall, I think there are a lot of things that don't go well, but the future
is a star, so
yes, the future is a star, so I feel very hopeful,
but I
feel like there are many things that don't go well overall.
Well, I'm sure that
advice is,
yes, the
Wheel of Fortune card in the reverse position, the
Wheel of Fortune card
in the reverse position, and the
advice is
so
strong that it makes me feel like I'm not going forward.  It's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, I haven't gone all the way towards love,
so I see, I don't think I'm going to
go well, and yeah, it seems like it's better to talk to each other
alone.I see, that's like [Music], I guess.
Even if you find someone you love, it's
probably best not to get
too obsessed with it.I guess it's okay if you can't find someone you love anymore.It's okay, it's okay.
[Laughs]
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
never.
]
[Music]
[Laughter]
But you know, that amazing tarot card
has that major arcana and the show. You
know, I don't know if I should call it that big. It's the
jackpot card and what we
all call SSR.
There's something like a card, and
there are three SSR cards right now, and
out of the four I've drawn, it's a
good thing, so it's kind of a good thing.I
mean, it's a really good thing.Overall, it's the type that feels refreshing and refreshing.
After something like that, I
thought it was an emotion, or perhaps something bold to do today.I
see, he's a man with a strong destiny.Hoshi-
sensei, I
won't plant it.I see, that's
interesting.Thank you,
Senpai.It
was fun.
[Laughs]
Ever since I heard that Myu-senpai was doing fortune-telling using tarot cards like this, I've
been curious about the characters.When I was
younger, I was
interested in tarot cards, so I
bought books and cards like that.  I used to buy things like that.Oh, it's
cute, isn't it? Even with things like tarot, I haven't been able to
fully develop myself as much as my seniors have.I
still have a lot to do,
though.I got them too.Oh, I see.That's how I
learned so much about
[music].
So, just
to change my mood, I'm
going to speed things up a bit from here.
Let's do it. It would be helpful if
you could answer me properly in English. I'll
do my best. Fighty Fighty. So, are you
ready?  Is the
weather hot or cold? Which do you prefer? Gold Kono
Gohan or Menkaan
Rise
Gust Turn Saizeria? Gashitosa Twitter or
Instagram or something like that? Should I
run with apple or orange juice?
Which do you prefer?
[Music]
Yes, on top of the pizza  I wonder if I'll put pineapple on it. I wonder if it's
cold.
[Music] Do
you prefer spicy or sweet?
[Music]
Ok, do you like tea or coffee
? Do you often drink the above pichires? Do you travel in famous metropolises
? I
see that it's a metropolitan city. Do you
sleep naked?  Should I
hang up my clothes?
OK
[Music]
Favorite events
: Halloween, Christmas, Tanabata Easter,
etc. Well,
Christmas, no, no, I'm a
senior at a sea of ​​Christmas trees.
Family Mart or Lawson? Do you
prefer
text messages?
[Music]
I see. Walking the distance of one station or taking the train.
Um, my hands are on the train.
Yes, what color are my pants?
Even now, I'm
not wearing them, so I'm wearing no pants. I'm wearing them
in this studio
without panties.
After taking a bath, I don't have to punch anymore. That's
helpful.
Actually, I have a question about that
next time, so I
have to explain something. What do you say about that
[music]?
Please tell me about the health method.
[Music]
Well, what is the
no-panties health method? Well,
by taking off your panties at night before going to bed, you
can improve the blood circulation in your lower body.
[Music] Is
that all? Well, my house was
completely burned down by my grandmother and my mother, and by my mother.
It's a healthy way to maintain good health. Seriously?
Mr. Toshi
[Music]
What kind of pants are you wearing? What's the
material for those men?
Noodles are somen noodles. No-
no ramen.
Somen
noodles. Erm. Noodles
are English. For men.  I could put on my pants.
[Music]
Look at Infinity.
[Music] If
there was something like that, it would
be delicious.
[Music] I
learned a lot. Is
there any proof that this is
good for your health?
Well, I do
n't know because those days are so common in medicine,
but apparently wearing panties is bad for marriage, and it's
constricting.  The
person who asked the question
NEXTQuestion
[Music]
Wait a minute.
OK, the balance of those games like Sports
Day was so
detailed and clever. There
were contests like Wolf and Abandoned School, but I
got the question wrong.
[Music]
And then there's the singing activities.  I
think you're doing really well right now, but what are your
thoughts on singing and what direction do you want to take the Congo challenge? Yes,
there are a lot of people who are good at singing, but
[Music] There
are songs that only Mio Ookami can sing.  I
wish I could sing it
[Music] It's
not about being good or anything, but I
want to be on the show because I can convey my feelings like this. I
definitely
think that Howling is a song that suits Mu-senpai very well. Thank you very much. I'll do it
in the future.  I'd like to sing some of those cool
songs, and I'd also
like to sing some kind of ballad type of songs.I'd
like to release an original song.I'd
like to release an original ballad as well.
[Music]
Hey, I'm
sure you said in the comments that Senpai's
cover of Sparkling, Sparkling Low Cover Park, and Sparkle Spark
was really good,
and I'm sure I've heard it before,
but I think a ballad would be a good fit.  That
's your voice.
Thank you very much.
[Music]
And then
[Music] I'd like to
hear your thoughts on the song Amo.
Yes,
right now. Do you have any confidence in that song
? How do you feel about it?
Song
Right now, I'm
going to [music] voice training, and I'm
going to voice training,
but
I still feel like
I still don't have the body or technique to sing, which is the way I want to express myself.  I
see, that's what's going to happen in
the future. [Music] We want to fill it in and do our best, but we want everyone to feel that influence as well.  I'd like to go see the eye cutout. The
foggy day has nothing to do with the question, but let's take a look.
What kind of cutout is it? I think it's a
cutout that shows Myuu-senpai's motherly side, Mom.
Please.
What if Mio-chan says, ``I'm going to leave Mommy?'' Soba-chan
goes looking for a new one, so much
so that she can't help but burst into tears at Lamy.I've already
prepared some spares.No
offense to the hairdresser.  Hey,
hey, we
can't be friends if we're no longer together. We can also be friends.
Well, I guess there's a movie about that kind of relationship. I
kind of want Mio to be my mom, but
Mio wants to stay friends, and
that's just her mom.  Delicious,
please, Subaru is a bit crazy.
That's crazy.
Welcome back, you're calling me crazy. It
makes you feel sad. I
didn't say that, but it sounds weird.
[Laughter]
[Applause] Crazy. I'm
bothering you right now.  That's funny.
[Applause] It
felt a little good.
[Laughs] I
wonder if it's okay to be happy even if someone says something painful to me. I'll try it.
[Music]
[Laughs] It's
not like it's going to stay that way. That
's a lie.
What should I do when I'm caught in the middle?  No, it's
not my mom. No, it's not my mom.
No, I
didn't give birth, so that
's a lie. I
might have given birth, but my
memories are being bought out.
[Laughs] Ah,
she
looked down diagonally and laughed, her eyelids twitching.
[Music]
[Applause] When you're in
trouble, when you talk, you just quiet down and
sit down. You're enjoying the reaction, aren't you?
When everyone says that
they were bullied by each other, it makes me wonder which one of them is really bullying me. I'm
thinking about all sorts of things.  I
can't do anything wrong.
[Laughs]
[Laughs] That
's brave, isn't it?
TT.
This isn't Mama Mama. Well, that's
right, I made a mistake.
More than that, I want
everyone to see this gathering of these four people.
I also wanted to get an explanation of the group.
But let's change the room a bit. OK
[Music]
Google. I
'd like to know what kind of group this is and how it was formed.
Ah.  But originally there was a group called OK FMfams,
and yes, that was the initials of the six members,
but
somehow the four members of Smog happened
to collaborate, and we came up with the
name of the team.  Sometimes, I
used the initials of OK Femmes and
rearranged them, and I got a smoke.
Hey, I
wonder if those four people are especially good in the middle.Oh
yeah, of course, the members of OK Femmes are
also really good friends.  But,
Okokoro, Kazu-Korone, and I get along really well,
and Subaru and I often play together,
so when those two became that set, I
feel like they go well together with Smog.I see.Soo,
Kayu-senpai, this is it.  Hey, Senpai
[Music] It's
Fubuki Senpai.
[Music] I'm looking
forward to hitting him with all my might. It's
natural. Now
that you've seen that, let's move
on to the next question. It's a bit
long, but,
uh, how
do you allocate points and balance the game at a sports day?  You've
worked as the MC for many collaborative projects that don't rely on digital games, such as Word Wolf and Haiku Contest. Are there any considerations or things you need to do when working on projects like that
?
[Music]
Well, the most important thing is definitely  I
think it's the casting part.
Casting the members. Yes, that's right. I
guess you could call it a hardship. Well, I guess I
haven't really talked much at all,
but I've talked to a certain extent more than the members I haven't had much interaction with.  You
may have thought
about things like, ``I'm good friends with them,'' or ``I want to get a group of members together.'' ``Yes, yes, yes, yes,'' I think I've been thinking about things like, ``Yes, yes, yes, I want to get a few members together.'' It makes each member feel glad that they participated in that project.  It's
about working hard to make a point where you can shine.
Well,
memo is memo,
number one, and I'm listening to it. I was
inspired by what my senior said, and I was really inspired by
it. I'm sure you've already thought about that kind of balance
a lot.
However, I thought it turned out to be a good thing. I'm
sure there are members who can bring out the best in that girl in her everyday life. I
wish I didn't know that she was really thinking about it
.  [Music] [
Music]
[Music] I
was like, wow, that's amazing.So, are there any
hardships?Ah, it's
dark.As
expected,
what about the preparation?
Other than that feeling of intoxication, most of us are like this.There are
quite a lot of projects that are new to us, and we've done them many
times.  Rather than making the same project, we
create new projects all the time,
so I guess that's true.Every time we create a program,
or rather, a project,
from template 1, it
's quite difficult.
Preparing for that is probably the
most difficult thing.
[Music]
Interesting, certainly.  I have
n't repeated it all that much.It
seems like I've
made everything and then deleted everything,
but on the other hand, I've
heard quite a few people say they'd like to do it again because it was so good and it
was amazing.
Ah, thank you, can you do it one more time? I have a
lot of projects
[Music]
Yamagami: I have a project that I want to do, so if I can
prepare a template for that, I'll do it again.In a
strange way,
[Music]
Hololive since the 6th generation has arrived.
Kindergarten
Kindergarten Yes, Kindergarten Kindergarten
Kindergarten is the hardest to prepare for. If you're seriously
going to hold a kindergarten, I'd like you
to invite a character as well. Because
there's a bubbly pacifier in that casual costume.
Kindergarten.  No, it's not a nursery school. So, if you
have anything else you want to talk about,
please go ahead and move on to the next question. Well, let's move on to the
next one. The next one is
also related, so I've
worked on the next action so far.  I
would like you to tell me about your favorite project that you are proud of.
[Music]
That's right.
[Music] My
favorite is
this. I don't know if I can translate it, Chiara-chan.
[Music]
In the pot of pressure points.  Yes,
there's a fairy inside the vase.
So what kind of plan is that fairy, me, Subaru, and the shrine maiden? I once
did a project where we confessed our worries to that fairy inside the vase. I see.
When? I
wonder when it was? It feels like it was quite a while ago. Maybe last year, maybe last year's face, or maybe last year. 2020 will be the sweets teacher. [Music] [Music] [Music] The fairies talked about their troubles.  It's kind of like he's giving me some advice. Oh
yeah, that sounds interesting.
[Laughs]
That's um, I'm
glad it's crazy. A
natural 10-part special is
crazy. It
's morning.
[Music] I'm
curious, so I think I'll go check it out.
Senpai.  It
says that Tsukkomi's role was good.Actually, it's a little
bit of this.It's a little bit of this.I
found it.I'll paste the URL, so you
can see it.I see.Thank
you very much.
[Music]
How do you come up with ideas like this?
HELLyoufingDS
Sleeping  All of a sudden, I can't
think of anything. Also, Subaru and I got on a call with that Discord, and I was like, ``Sure, this project looks interesting,'' and then it
escalated to the point where it became like, ``
Play Story,'' right now.
[Music]  They're a
good match.Beautiful-
senpai and Subaru-senpai.Maybe it's
good that they're both good at different things.I
see.That's
true.Next
question on OkOk.It's almost the end
of our first anniversary.When
Nyuu-senpai is nearing the end of his first anniversary, he will be broadcasting, ``I
want you to get taller.''
When we talked about it, Ogetsu-senpai told Mu-senpai
that you were like miso soup and
encouraged him. That scene moved many people's hearts.
What do you think about your height now?  Do you feel that way?
Ah, at that time, we had
only been active for about a year, so
when new members started coming in, I
felt like we were losing out in terms of individuality. Hmm,
in terms of composition, I felt like we were losing out in terms of individuality.  I was
thinking about it,
and then there was a part of me that
wanted to be more unique,
but I couldn't be as unique
as I wanted to be, so I guess I
wanted to make an interesting broadcast, but I
was really worried
[Music]  I
understand, but when I talked to that rice porridge, it
was like, ``Yeah, Gomi Mio-chan is miso soup, so it's like miso soup.'' [Music] She told me that there are a lot of people who like miso soup, and that packaging is fine.
Also, miso soup always
comes with rice,
so it's an absolutely necessary part.Even if I
eat steak every day,
there are many times when I'm having a hard time and I just want to eat miso soup.  It's
okay to be told that being a miso soup is your individuality.That's
right, right now,
even if I'm not unique,
all the fans who support me are the ones who are my current Uchiha.  I
don't worry about things or try to force myself to change, but I think it's okay to have fun
in my own way and
dress in a way that suits me, so
maybe I won't be in such a rush like I used to be.
At that time, I thought, ``It's okay to do it at home,'' and I
still do now. Well, that's when I
realized that I
can do it peacefully and happily,
and that's OK. [
Music]
[Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music]
Sorry for the long story.
No, I think it's a good story. Seriously,
when I saw the cutout of the character, I
was really moved.
[Music] There
was a time, right? I see,
Miu-senpai. I
know exactly how you feel.  It
really resonated with me. I'm sure the person in charge of the MC is
someone who does projects like Kirara-chan and Caterpillar, so if the
MC stands out a little more, the
guests won't stand out.
[Music]  ]
There are times when I hold back a little, I
see, and I think
that's
the kind of person who wants to stand out, so maybe
there's even a gym group,
etc.
[Music] I
see.  I'm sure there are people who like me
among my fans, so I guess it's just a little
bit. I'm
going to cry.
[Music] Let's
go to the questions.
NEXTNEXT There's still one more thing.
[Music]
That's it.
Mestermio-senpai recently celebrated his 3rd anniversary.
Congratulations
[Music]
Masude
Eh,
what plans and goals do you have for the coming year? Yes,
this past year
has been
difficult, but I've
been doing it for a long time, so I've
been doing it for a long time, so
don't forget to have fun.  I
think I want to stream it. I see.
Yes,
Shiseido seems like it.
Also, I've been saying that
all of Hololive
wants to go to Budokan together. I
see, but Makuhari Mess is already gone. Well,
Hololive Japan is going.
Makuhari Messe
is already big enough,
so I've reached the point
where I think Makuhari Messe is bigger, but I
guess it depends on the hall, but which one is
better?  When it comes to spacious
[music]
halls for live concerts,
Budokan is
different.
There are a lot of stairs and things, so I guess that's true
, but my
third-generation live performances are also
held in arenas, like super arenas.  I
wonder if the Tokyo Dome Tokyo Dome City Hall is doing things like that, and I think it's getting to the point where it's almost within reach.It's true that
even at the Budokan, Japanese idols
are very famous.  I
think there are a lot of people who have it, so
as an idol nerd who knows how it feels, I've heard it a lot. So, it
's the Big Budokan.
[Music]
Makuhari Messeim Regran
Budokan. I
want to go to it. I think I can go there someday.
[Music]
Makuhari Message
Makuhari Message  Up until now, I
think it's pretty big to go straight from the venue to Makuhari Mess, and it's
true.Up until now, there have
been times when we couldn't get customers in.
Even so, there were a lot of
people who wanted to come and visit us in person, and I
guess because they all supported me so much, I realized that the
management was always a little bit small.It's
not like I set a goal, but somehow it
sold better than I thought.  There were a lot of things like, ``I thought I
got the ticket early,''
but
maybe that's why I had the courage to rent a big venue this time.I see.It's
true.Isn't it
tragic
?
[Music]
Um, the ending.  Actually, there is a certain color to the song, but
before that, the last question is yes.
For my seniors, I
think of Hololive as a group of friends who will run together to the end. Hmm, I see, it
's an OK attitude.
[Music] This is the
first time someone has said something like this.  I think this talk I heard is good. It's
cool, it's cool, it's cool, it's
running all the way to the end. But it's also a little howling. [Music] I feel like we're going to run all the way to the end.
Yeah,
OK. I
wish we could all continue to run together like this. That's great.
Finally.
Advertising before the publicity song public.
Please promote this.
Thank you very much. Here is the preview
of
Fubuki and
Mio's Waku Waku Every Day
. It was
announced the other day and is currently being
distributed on Apple Music etc.
If you'd like,
please ask.
Yes, that's right
. The
other one is here. Please click
here. Since it's our 3rd anniversary, we're selling
3rd anniversary merchandise
at Hololive's official goods shop.  It
's on sale now, Ok Google
[Music] I hear there's a set
deadline for it. It's
until the beginning of January,
so if you buy the whole set, you'll
definitely get an
autographed postcard
[Music]
Action
So, in closing.  I waited for a moment to say hello. No, I guess I
shouldn't go back. OK, now let's
say hello. Thank you everyone for watching today.
I
would like you to tweet your thoughts. Everyone,
how was your day? How was it?  I
was really happy to be able to talk to Chiara for such a long time today. Thank you.
We're also happy. She said she got really excited talking about cats at first, but she says she's really happy about the cats she was talking about. Someone who understands what I'm talking about. We'll talk
again and collaborate again.  I thought I'd like to do
that. [Music] I'm going to say hello in German, but I think I'd like you to say it with me. OkOk Well, to make it easier to read, I'll write it in the chat and in Discolo. [Music] Something like this.
Yeah, OK, I'd be happy if you could watch this together and tell me.
[Music]
Well,
tomorrow, we'll see Chiara's
new product, the
new watch, so please take care of it, everyone.
Yes, please.
Miyu-senpai
[Music]
Majestically  In the midst of the passing scenery, in the
sad
days, the
hand that was extended to me is gentle, and the
slight fever that
drips with my heartbeat seems to defy the wind.Because I've
lived my whole life, when I
meet you, I realize that I'm not alone anymore.
[Music]
Because I have you  I wo
n't get lost, I'll walk
down the shining path
[Music]
Because I'm helpless, I'm
looking for a friend
Because I'm spilling out, I'll
light a fire and
evolve with my bad luck No
one will blink like this I
believe in you
Because I've decided to believe in you I'll
be able to overcome this
darkness no matter what.  The only
flower that blooms,
whether out of fear or admiration,
I'm running through the night sky and across the land, competing for it.This
story that you hide is not forever in the future.I do
n't want to
lose, so let's
ride this passion on this love.  I
chose my fate
[Music]
When frozen, the memories reverberate silently, resounding over and over
again, confirming each other's scars
[Music]
You are the only one who is afraid of the realizations and resounding echoes of the
night where the silver-colored village grieves together.
Morality is
transmitted through the airwaves.  My
thoughts are
in my heart. Let's go there.
You're next to me, so I
won't get lost. Let's walk
down the path one by one with light.
[Music] My
hair won't stop.
[Music] [
Music]