[Music]
N
voodoo
[Music]
uh go
to
me
Hmm
hmm
[Music]
Hmm
[Music] N
pandan Yeah,
good, good, good
[Music]
Moody
Hmm
[Music]
tnd
Enter
ana
[Music]  ]
Hmm
[Music]
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu
This show
is so big!
[Music]
wh
me
[Music]
t
ni nare
me
Yeah yeah
tan
[Music]
Yeah yeah yeah
This program is brought to you by the sponsors you see
true
ttt pr
Jishu Senpai 3 has been muted.
pane
Niki stupid woman ha
ha ha ha ana Lagoon Morning French pen goods also join non-humans
Fine I wonder how everyone is doing Japanese people please keep posting comments in Japanese.  It's
Sian-senpai, so don't get anxious.
Ahhh
. Well, first of all, let me explain this talk program once again in English. Ahhh, I
want to think about it.
Video s a My mother, who has a stage 8 child, is about to go watch. Pusha
invites the family home.  Guttopapolis is a toilet seat beauty salon
Life chance l I'm in a prestigious club
rr 2 vs match house sam derose views Let's
play Healing Savage House
This is an interview talk show for Takanashi Kyarahoru and Kohane's English polishing for overseas audiences.The
purpose is to let people know more about Japanese talents through live interpretation.My
husband is, of course, Takanashi's character.Western Confectionery
SectionCome
on, everyone.  Real people, Sach
8 So,
there's already a cat here, but before you take it out, everyone, please take a look at that one.
Hey, I want Ross to win, right now, if I solve it, Akasha Ross Woohaaaa p
1 The
tree is 130,000 yen, so let's make it to Hasegawayama Prefecture.  It
looks like Shion-senpai is awake, but somehow he's awake. Kamimae Bye
Shinsei
Aaaaa
[Music]
porn
Avatar
Keiki
Me
Ohayohayo 8  It
's early, meow meow, Saya Iyo
2 The only blue bee-handling chick that fits 6
ana That
's cool English 4 Surprisingly thoughtful zepp I have no choice but to become fluent in English The hot
springs are cooler
Thank you for coming Sian-senpai, actually.  I was really worried that I would be late.Ahaha, I think I would
be late if it wasn't for Yara-chan.
cardwirth h Stahl 3
Moon r asb to do in forever Copper r Yesterday,
I was still in bed. It's my
first time broadcasting since 1 o'clock, Senpai. I wonder if I'll listen to that girl who's waving. Well then, it's time.
Hey, this is
good for Hanta.Honda I was thinking of going to sleep, but it wasn't raining, so I had to get up early, so I
guess I thought I'd never oversleep.  There are so
many people coming and going, haha,
but while I'm planning something to stream on that discord, I'm on the 2nd floor.I
wonder if I'll be able to get up to hear that fresh person speak directly to me twice.  That singer
has passed away.
If I were to say it myself, I'd be really worried. I didn't want to
bury him. I dared to
do as coarse up to do as I dared to do.
Because I'm a good girl, today I asked about the total abolition of that Shion,
or
something overseas, and the information that is known is that Spring Senpai White is the
red Micra, and it's a war with Aqua Senpai.  What I'm doing
Turn that's what I'm doing now What's that good about that garlic? When did I touch it?
What is that? I
heard that Ness song recently.
Sugai-kami, who is a person, so even if you pick it up from here, you can see it a little.Then, the scene is that you can see the sky, it looks like an onion, and when I asked him what he was called, he said, ``Hmm, 4-chan is called Garlic.''
Japanese people don't listen when people say that it's being talked about.People do
n't really appreciate it.I don't say it.Well, there's a
possibility that High Rock will be mentioned in the future.Oh, I'm not going to go.I
miss it.Garlic is delicious.I
don't like it.  What happened when I was about to leave it behind?
ii choked down white 3 season en us mon spanish oily innova
gay site minecraft 4 s back senpai anh head wig c 3 e 5
e 9 server touch breno 2 japanese nkaaha xcg
kun p jellyfish ooz driver aer  I wish I
could go to Hawaii, but actually, I don't.  We are
also being told that 3 is a bit like that.If we don't have a hat, we are also
said to have an orange ball.When the
temple bell is worn, it really looks like that.Whether you put it on, or take it off, or
take it off.  Wait a minute, I
can't show you anything, so I'm going to say Zukki, but
this time, c 4th senior, I hope you'll take advantage of the opportunity overseas to learn more about this.  of  That's why I'm
doing it. I'm
not in my head.
So don't worry, everyone's eating vegetables. It can't be helped.
Ah, that's green onion
rapoli.
[Music] What's that? Meow, I want to
join.  It's a lambda and overpayment.
The prefecture's apex is up a little bit in 2019, too.
Abu-chan, you guys, and the senior city profilers who have ever seen it.
Child Hot Springs Pine Ichiban Rice Hey Hey Hey,
self-introduction is simple, easy,
detailed, self-alienation, etc. When something strange was aired on ACOM, I swore to be a radio regular.
a Please introduce yourself in detail Egg book model
in Japanese It's okay in Japanese Power Sukune Last Live 2nd generation a Cute witch girl Neko
mini a This is Shion from our company
[Music]
Understood Cleaning Asoka
rar
cac  sanjusangendo r chi zoom generater
coner fa
as the pure idol 4 nenga cpr patch 2
abu apparel fish in zu moon c the
why big ppe aaah
On the 4th, hey, you know, I'm the host of Higashi-ku, where the bar goes up, so I
thought I had to learn a little bit about that guest, so I did a
little research and
saw a lot of things, like
Can House.  4 and rin Poupe Dinnerware Watching etc. Fins
Optional Senpai Miss Good
Reese N Larch Huh Spice 9 fe I
bet you saw that Shion Senpai's debut broadcast on Sir.  I'm
wondering if I should release the Bach negative ion senior star on 2020. Hmmmm
ni
ani
aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa I'm
already relieved and I do
n't worry about it I haven't changed since my lowest day
Barena
name then never Today's card holder ring
aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah
After all, it's a good egg and
whatever. It's just a time person.
belen deforide lenco aderin aderin specter
4 sp to do scene
agricultural tools favorites aa ta  I
used to speak in honorific language, but now I don't.
Is there a reason why?
Well, I'm starting to get used to it, right? To everyone,
to Asuka, it's okay. I started speaking in honorific language. And I can't speak in honorific language anymore.  That's what I thought, but
maybe. Well,
as long as I think I've released the first release after that, I don't really care.
Booba was good, even more, oh, but it's so interesting to see it now, it's white. It
's white history. It's
white, and reporters and masters started the rainbow from there. It's
white history because I grew up in the hair.
Nemuro
's pretty oh is cute.  It's more of a lie than it is.
Booby is mixed in with Cyan Pile. I want a good bird. In the end,
Patty is released.
Yesterday, I was the only English-speaking person in the 4th class and I
bose, and I was completely out of control with everyone who has a Japanese brain, but I saw
that
frog cap on YouTube and it was
flexing. Wow, I see.
At the end of the day, I searched for it and asked a question, but that's what I thought.According to the above and sister agreement, IA,
sex and space, new 10th round, 9 Ford, s 6, Nekoi Sake
Brewery, this is what I thought.
So the first question is, what are you doing as a tiepin?
Lately, I've
been playing a knitting game called Doki Doki Literature Club. That's
really strong. It's
really interesting. It's not like it's a cute girl. I love dubbing.
Shion's happy sweat with that girl is a peaceful game. She's really happy with her
appendix. She should get used to it. It's really
rotten.  It's
a bit like that. I know the truth. It's a little scary.
I think Masukuru-chan must be a Ruyer.
She's a strong girl. I'm not good at things like hora, so I really need a lecture.  It's bad, see l It's effective, well yeah
, yeah, well Seahers finger
Utteka Dokidoki mo Chuomachi chocolate opening
Hirase pointer 3 thumb arm 5 boo
boo sa 1 helme barrel eade  I liked Eighter Leader. Hey, I
think his name is Tsunami, but if he does, please remember that.
That's Jaguar's original summer fire.
If I say that, it'll be dangerous.
Monica. Ah,
okay.
No, at the waiting party, the doctor has always loved only Tsuki Tsuki.It
looks like Holu Talk is about to explode, but there's Arima,
and someone tells him
r f 0  f 5 a trender movie
motor ap still romen daimon cars oh
this is os Everly is gone example 3
Saaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa too
Natsuki, the person who appeared there, is sick,
right? I don't know, because we played together.
[Music]
If you boo, you'll be fooled. The lure is also 29 sen be to do on eyes
away putin Ice cream koc have to do
anger I see.
That's what I did. I was also looking at the basics of fog for a moment. Ah, that's
amazing.  -
Steve khan It's
a little bit right that the people who can only say rice from Atsugi and their families also did it.Recently
type no no yes Yes What happened? There is an
error when you cry while watching Pekora's live concert.  I was thinking about the
direction and making some seeds.
wai
Is Usopp serious? He said it was cute. I
was cute. Ch is the Spanish Lime Scrying Bag Run Monopoly. The catfish is dead.
Voodoo
file No. 4 down walk, Haru-senpai's is Vienna Gabat. Now, the
next question is, I think a lot of people are curious about it.
Mr. 3, how did you find so much moderation, or what was the trigger for that?
Well,
I was thinking of
using a Showa skirt, but that's what I heard.
Ugh, stores are generally sweet.  It's like it's working. It's
really funny. What
kind of person is Nakata with that face? It's
over. I
wonder if that's what it's like.  It's
decided by Hmm, but I haven't decided whether or not to include it yet, but I'm asking them to
put Hmm in it.  It's the
first time I've ever felt that kind of count, like pure, and now that I've been doing it for such a long time, I can really understand the
feeling.In the beginning, I'm
glad I joined.I
think, my
life has really changed.
a
usa sosus raden audition  beso nonce air conditioner
teraso zu aa me as she wants to do so are
lecture
nu do
system en wedding star wars good choice join a day
cheese and r iphone
pleakley there were so many
rumors aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa  My senior moved while being conscious of his presence.Hmm, I
knew about the diver by default, but I do
n't know.When I tried to go home, he was completely gone, so I decided to apply for an audition in a rural English-speaking area.
From that time on, I started and waited and thought, ``Maybe I should get into this.'' Looks like it's interesting.
Okay, so I decided to get ready and try it out. Did I get a lot of great impressions
after trying it?  I applied because I thought Kani would be a good fit for the inside autograph note.I got
really passionate about it and decided to
try my best to get Josh in.It's great, and things have changed.Wow, I'm serious.  I
really don't know, teacher, compete for sponsors, go ahead, boss and 3 a n
derby spin Antigua, come on, turbo star is here, zoom in on the funk, a little big
star palmy bar
ios, good Baba version, r abeno, cheer on butter rice, 3 minutes
Addition
on danse be  sure to do as to win the
audition me up nippon chin5 smooth pou dou dou
After all, if you
get into the 5th, it's something Chinese, something is okay  I was
planning to stream something like that every day,
but it was
n't so good that I was robbed of something like, ``How many times should I do it every Friday week?''  I
thought it was that house that didn't get answered,
but long ago I did something else and became too passionate, so Arthur is a patient who does it every day.That's
right.  It was like, Okay, I'll stop.  That's
right,
moresale arenas are you doing
After all, it would
be fun if the investigation was mixed into the comedy. It's not
fun, so it's fun to talk about it.
So, the next person to ask the question was Khan,
Aeton,
Edo language.  I've been living abroad for a long time without a home due to rice restrictions, but there's something I've wanted to tell you for a
long time.  I
guess we can talk about more than just the power of the concert. We can talk to the listeners who are the mainstay of our concerts and the listeners who watch us overseas. It's been a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time. I wish I had done it properly.  I don't know
what's going on,
but the people who are watching me overseas don't even understand Japanese, but the fact that they're watching me
makes me want to do my best to be able to speak the same language.
Or I want to do my best, but
that's okay. Look, the
hem width is a little wider than that, but the width is even better, but everyone has their own problems.
Hey, Haya, since you graduated from Starbucks, have you ever lived overseas?
Yamaha is advanced.  Hey, aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa TonoShe
graduated from Chikisu and Sasakawa worked hard at Harvard a long time ago, and that sister
doesn't have it in the script in Japan.
Yes, I know, I heard that the virtual Bach is Harvard University.
9 Hanyu
graduated from Harvard University, isn't he?
Hey,
cats are killing each other. Well, it's a love school.
But it's a bit long ago, and even with this, it's a lot of cards. I
can't get rid of this one.
Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah
download as
co wither soa patty acc zu long riding door saa book going to work
ringspipe hmmm
[music]
voodoo
chain jsaa rb harem
inu style soko garp f Eikura-chan or something like that so I can collaborate with Grachan already
That's right I
won't practice  If
you really want to talk about that with Money-chan, you
should ask Kihara-sensei to teach you. Nanaka
Eikura, yamaha.  If you're a graduate, you
should be able to memorize a few words with just one press, right?
aol
aso carendar ender car teacher red pou dou
dou
aso please help 6 ef 4 h club asukyante  That Push Pim Matsue
Branch Manbooth, your voice is
a little bit, I've already told you this in the English speaking area.  I'm
going to be taught some difficult words right now, so I don't know if I'll be able to remember them until the end of the rebroadcast course.  The
sound face is amazing,
but the
fur is amazing, but it's really difficult.Ah,
wow, both of them are
stupid.I can say that it's
nice.I'm a bit of a 1st person, so English isn't my native language either.  A
bunch of cone woofer faces
Gabe ok Let's make normal
[music]
into normal words Well, let's
get them to remember it Bar Yes,
what's the pronunciation?
Waiting on the plane
Petit artwork
Ono Raccho Parents and
Matcha A pair of macho keys and Miyuu Autou
Please remember a certain peer Oooooo Payon's Maa Dopia
Let's sing the onomatopoeia
Now onomatopoeia
[Music]
Eh panamera
a The meaning is onomatopoeia
Onomatopoeia Onomatopoeia I
wonder if you don't know that?
If you graduate, you can afford
it.Onuma p.
Full recovery 4 damage butter cotton cloth leg show tool Aburatsu Yume mama's pianos see Nah aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa Let's go,
let's
go, let's go to the mountain,
what do you like to do the most?For example, this kind of utility distribution is the most fun, so it's
like operating games, cats on, etc.  I
like the maintenance club, but I really like everything about it, so I like going to parties because they're fun.But
recently, I've
been really bad at singing, but I'm really into singing in front of people.  I
used to like singing by myself at karaoke and such, but I
got nervous singing in front of people and couldn't sing very well, so when I played cherry blossoms, I felt kind of sad,
but now I'm getting better.Wow, I
feel like I'm growing up, but it's kind of fun.  Singing has a lot of bad breath
No, it's giving birth to old criminals. Is Hemana my boom? There
's no reason to be worried before distribution. It's okay, after all, they're idols, so they probably don't sing a lot.
Introducing equipment for idol warfare. Yeah
references to  do paper burner lady say bubu bubu her
in dream water color green
usd e to do not to do this piece key fun
tsusukyu
What do I like most?The location is still Subaru's sound Shion is kind to Senpai This is Shun  It
's nice of you to reply to questions even though it's a stream where you ask Senpa questions.But
if you're curious, it's the first time I've spoken in Canter, so I'll go first.I do
n't really like Kin Karaoke.  I
like shiotan because it's fun because you can do it without having to worry about small talk.Maybe we'll
do karaoke too.Ina-chan is solo.Iccho
[Music]
Recruitment aron up when bar chiba more far away pa
8 virus ana
stone lobby a
sas  is a new wonderful old bill to the ASCII box Pinir Senpai Shinshu Tamakiuchi is cute That
face I guess he cares about the family too
ab 5
lick it to you early
ran I don't know
what else to do - I went to that spa quick read stream that naga  I'm
ranked 5th in Yume's number 5 for both Spa and Reading, but he always ends up talking about something else,
so I
guess he's talking about it while he's reading it, and it should have taken 30 minutes to read, but it took 3 hours!
When I read Supa-chan's comment, I'm starting to get angry, but I'm not sure if that's the case.The
survey will make me really happy, so I guess it's okay.Pants,
right?They're some change, pkg eyes on me.
Next question: Eighter's originally non-incisional festival was held this week.It
ended with a boom.It feels like it was a long time ago, but I've been training a lot.
Hey, the specs are 10 times higher. That's when we
set sail. The house did it.
Hey, you pulled off a perfect performance.
How do you feel now after the live show you resisted? I
think the earphones section will come out again and again.  But no matter how many times I talk about it, I do
n't need to talk about it.I wonder
if it's true.6 It felt amazing to have completed everything.Even
though it was only recently, it felt like a long time ago.  Put it away  I
taste it, but it's still on the left.I used to sing in front of people in the karaoke broadcast, but I was
nervous about exercising in front of people, so I wasn't good at it, but I
can't sing or dance anymore.  It's the first time I've ever seen a color in my life.It's just that my
feelings have changed quite a bit.Yes,
that's true.When I
was in character, I was
nervous that it was still pretty good.No, I
was
really nervous.  did
But at that time, it's this year. It
feels like it's been a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a year.
The filling is
also a play plax, so I'm trying to pull it out in the garden.I'm worried about the separator, too.I'm so excited about
the 3rd year of the year.I
want to do something like a concert.
Hey, next time, yeah, let's do some captures. Let's do some driving together starting at 5 o'clock. I
hope someday I can collaborate on a song with that grachan.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa nice  I
want to do it
falorni starfish Kureha Barbaker
Core On Stage Ogura Uza unfinished k pop Isuman
voodoo moe  Ah, that goods chamber is coming to me, I will come to the leuria. I'm
always ready for the money 4, I'm
looking forward to it.
What was the most fun part of preparing for the card festival at Welch No. 8?  What was the
most difficult thing for you? I want my overseas fans to understand how much time and effort it took to come that way.Ah, I
see.  Is
n't it Pearl that I tried to go back to the song I sang like this? Hmm, I had them
make it a little easier than that, and I had them think up the choreography. Hmm, I
did that Besson, but I still tried my best to dance. I don't usually do that.
No. Well, it's difficult if you're not anxious.
It's difficult. How long did it take me to remember that gesture?
But somehow, I wonder how long it took for me to memorize it all.
50 Asaan
Five months.
Well, all of those songs are amazing. Not only today, but there are also Bach compositions,
so it took me a long time to really burn through all of them. I
did it with everyone, too.
Yeah, it's been a long time, two months, oh, it's amazing. I've been preparing from a.
That's why it seemed so hard. It was really hard right away.
It was hard, but it was fun. Oh, it's so good.
Muscle pain,
muscle pain,
muscle pain.  It's so quiet after that, so that's amazing. The first one is already too amazing.
Hmm, I guess. Well, that's what you say.
Car forever to do Armor ua Nuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuwb white
blue pawn
booby  erde morenote manometer arref half
Farre Mars
At the Biker Star Shoin b All you have to do is run away to Niihama's grandparents and you'll be defeated. Hana ga Paan
ap sing for mature Fei close is so good, it's so much fun.
Well, the
next day I forget most of
what Inoue did.  Let's give
some salt to the teacher who teaches us the miscellaneous goods. Hey sister, this is how it is here.
[Laughs] It's
weird that there's no 8 lister. Neo. It's okay if you say it. It's heavy, right? Go
to the beginning. If it doesn't work, sleep.  It's a bit dangerous, is
n't it? Hmm, but well, if you do it all over again, you'll probably get stuck in your head more and more.  What
can do Yamada is drunk Topiaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa a
name a massive code see branch school bag dress the
next coo bad announcement is Jindo arson is the queen of making a rakuspin bakery
nb bear dog dobe pile teacher in den price shake do
ba boss darts in korean and chinese impa  I didn't put in the hot water and it looked like an angel  I
see. Let's move on to the next question. Yes,
a. Not all members of Japan Live will be participating in the next Bloom. c.
Please tell us how Oto-senpai came to be affiliated with you. Actually, I live in that Shion-senpai's Khan.
Hmm,
Japanese Japanese fans were curious about Cat's question, but
Axion Senpai was
saying in earnest, "What's so good about this?"  I do
n't think I've ever had the impression that I'm
active, so why are you thinking of participating in Bloom now?  I was
really confused
about whether to carbonize or not.It's amazing how
hard it is to learn dance and practice other things, and it takes a lot of time.
Yeah, I don't want to worry about it too much because it's going to take a little bit of time to get to grips with it properly.There were a
lot of things going on, so I was really at a loss, but I don't know what to do.After the live performance, I thought, ``If I
have a big goal, I'll do my best to achieve it.''  Valjeannerie,
yeah, that's so fun and exciting, and the feeling of accomplishment after it's over is just
amazing.
That's right, I really like working hard towards a big goal.
ua Drink and have fun while doing it.
Parka.  I wanted to smoke ano  onna son den den den
carabe iphone 5 au dodo
boo boo sr to do ri aan
sakuraya village ca 6 c 5 ea vale parka
carus way
andere 50 re so mare fuzz dondon watch hai
zam complex wear these bid headway staff
facer pou dou dou bread  with big After the rant,
this is that town Hollow  I
saw the second face - when I saw the clock, when we went together at the same time, those guys were
talking about Noon and making him tougher.
That's why I think it's the same for the English-speaking people in South Africa when he was an MC.  I made it more vivid for the people who watched it with me,
but Futaba was completely abolished.
At the very end, you said in your voice on stage how you felt about today's concert.  I've
already interpreted that, but at that time, I was sure of Care.Until
now, I
didn't really think of myself as an idol,
but there was something about me that the mayors did like this.  I'd be happy if you thought of me as an idol.When I
did that, I said,
7th generation, I've been
doing this for two years.Why,
why can't you think of me as Airo?  ta
me  I
guess it's because I'm a kid who thinks I'm an idol,
but I do
n't think I went into live shows with the intention of attacking others as idols and doing my best as idols.  It's
already a lie. For the first time, there's a Kaneko concert in an empty lot, and everyone
tells me that Unchan is an idol. In my opinion, she's a really wonderful idol.
So, even if I don't think so, everyone has money.  I'll give it to you
Hmm net it's a good thing so i like it
yaaaa can dir en watch also big eyes
ais earmo can you do
voodoo arc en en us ide are home terindu bos
aside ah
tefcas aetherfighter no earth ev's up to do
fighter
arm  shisaada
west cd star s with charm and fan psb joint season fincar
position
senses charm of bno reeder others  ECA Fighter
Maisa Ah, I'm going to bobber, now branch pon -chan Neta cheese Yeah, good pants
stick glue Glue FOUR EYED palm Stone is Sapia Burpin Pawn Sevens Edition
Pass
Want You  At
the beginning or mid-first, or rather at the 5th bar,
I was
n't really aware of what I was doing as an idol.  You
just think it's about broadcasting, right? I play games with Nee-san, so I know there's a price tag game, so
this is a shade. But when you
say that work is part of it, you're like, well, you're
already what I call an Internet net idol.  I wonder if that
's right
Mr. Price Raise Pik Isn't that a moving Kakashi Buri kid? Well, he's a virtual idol, isn't he
?
Man's Land was super fast.
Hmm, well, that's it. Maybe he doesn't realize that he's an idol.  too
Nowadays, everyone likes the complete abolition of Shion, so
don't think too much about
being an idol.If you do it too much, things will turn out to be hard.  If you're going to do that, then I
don't think you're suitable for today's world of broadcasting.Oh
yeah, that's right, it's going to be the main feature of that live show.  I
have to use honorific language, etc. I'm not
good at the Japanese calendar. I ca
n't talk to the sound of the bell.
A
roa some star s orito turn signal sr desde
meant to do app puff all are ress winner it's time to
farm tomorrow life is already a pet.  Touching with a pass
Nizumida webtoon en female doctor smartia degrees two pieces of pi dosu
party
muju service fan and helped me ahaha
No, we talked about something deep. I can't go back and talk about it, so that's what I'm looking for in this talk.
Ah, so I want to talk about it.
Yes, this is good. I
'll ask you the next question.
Cheer
Or ever Officially, it's a pretty tree,
but I've never seen him raise his muff.Tune,
please show me some magic, Senpai.All
of them are animal gate fireflies.There
was an index 5 programmer,
etc.3  With d streaming, you can't really do anything.
Without the power of Mutsu and that Arda Maid 3 d, it's
a bit tough. If you don't
become a woman hunter, that's a bit tough.
en 3, the room was like a great cut, but I'm going to give it a collaboration tool
can.  you do ned I love Finland so much
rockn doc Hasebe Kung Fu do you search by
daruru ne now I'm a cat girl
He's a princess with negative equipment symptoms, so it might be a little difficult. I'm
going to have to ask him about it. It's in that costume. He's
making me look like he's floating. He
's a high-class professional.
Eun-seo is like that, isn't he?  You don't want to ruin your image
[Music]
Option to say Boo Boo
Glue Shiina's name view enjoy
After all, it's
not Punch, it's a good thing about Philly Case 7 I get it, I'm
not sick.
Yes, I often embezzle in my car, and my new senior's 3D broadcast is also for the sake of his license. I
see. He
was using magic here too. He
can also use magic, Kanuma. I'm
sure.  I can tell you that, I was using it,
and then every 22 seconds,
well, those pants were completely visible.
bathing 213th ah
rear xtender would do do buttsverter color suse
suse hahn gardener 7 if the hot water was shaking p it would have caused my sister to have a
hard time ah the one
from chihaya would
have definitely sold well ran club the
skirt was a little something  It sways and it's amazing.
It's my sister's catch that makes me cry. It's
difficult, so it looks so low. That's the magic. Do you
know anything else?
That may be true. I was shocked when I did that, but it was magic in such a situation. It was because I was
shocked.
Raku was selling well, so I guess I'll
just translate that later.  I'm in
a hurry Ah, I want to
take a moment to remember the story
ran ah ah
ran
naite iru meb Sean You png water the mars apks
Well, the layout Fields Forever Sealer 2 pass borders Well, ge sebas
Ah, well, it's a pity that I can't really rain at the store right now, and in Agato's plan, I
'm sorry, sister.  It's
been a long time since I've been diagnosed with uma gkn.
Hey, Avaspik has prepared a spelling quiz for the fresh-faced Vera.
[Music]
Yes, question board
Um, it's like, ``What's going on?''
cf 7 I'll ask you to answer right away.Okay, don't think about that at all.Jon
Sweets  Barco lottery is wide and cute housewives are good Tess order Maedate Renko 1 piece
ep
related costume tour in another
original Dan batch
Hume maybe  Male Volume Uwaeka Papa Eyes Bimyeon Caster & Chaste Berry
Signature
Well, I haven't thought about how to translate this, but
Wada: It's too early, so I can't help it.Let's do
it.Well, I've prepared some music for that, too.  Naaba Yasubei 24 a
obe
rush
jobi bai ka
osake the
enemy is a cold target
a cold book carment dawn
gas and kansai de au
what a great figure  It's
been a long time since I've played Taiko
Girls Reader
Ah, I've never been able to keep up
Ran I'm stuck
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa We'll
do it at the same time I
can't make it work
Okitsutsuki 8 Mountain Climb Yeah Yeah Well, that's how I
run It's a quick
cocker Sekine, is
n't it Pizza?  There are a lot of yeses to put on the pie rack.
kok Senpai is red. 10 Pie Corone Senpai either. The rice porridge is
also open. It's already tonight's ska.
Eh, let's go to the Oda container. It's
pretty sweet to hit something.
Name:
Okoitaa.
Ryoko with the blue-colored art. Or maybe she's famous and traveled in a big city. When she
fills in 10 medals to travel, she has one stomach, one leg, and that blizzard.  Is it old sharpeners or urine
a
Rain this 7 That glass is half full - whichever is half
full It's good that the nest is Rugby glass and water n a Is it the mother that is half full?
7 Bar Family Family Girl 7 Casbah Actually Rosso
Fan Meow
Yeah, I'll
text him or I'll sit at the bar in front of him, I'll give him a big present or I'll
get it.A I want to ride the Arcaden Chale even one station away.I
wonder if I'll have pants  What color is
Big Way? The
end is 1st place. I
looked at the color of her pants. It's
not pink. As expected of a cute princess.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Well, maybe it's a bit of a mix-up, but I was told that I was being bossy when I opened that file kirk, but I
chose the big one.I
love everyone, and I have free time, and I'm getting
married tomorrow, so I'm getting married tomorrow, so the chopsticks are really out.  No,
if you're going to get married tomorrow, it's always going to be skin.
[Music]
[Music] I
couldn't translate it, but aaaaa So,
on this day, the question is, are you a negative person from that positive city?
4 I guess it doesn't really say that in Japanese
. I thought you were talking about water in a glass, but if there's a glass of water in it, it's ok.
Well, it's a color version.  Are you saying
that? That's right, it's like, are you joining us from the
beginning? Well, it doesn't really get across well in the country. It's just as
negative as that. I do
n't know if they said they were joining us at the meeting.  Kappa
The taste is half of the story about what's in the cup, and half of the story is about Chon's Omi
Honoho, and the other half is about salad.I think I'm
negative.  The virtual car is
still a perseus wedding gangland argument ano
porridge Beijing nude japanese came you do it's a
good idea pink supplement serve already other fans don't throw it at Sky's amazing
line I see.
Well,
if I were to answer in a negative way, I'd say that half of it is in color, in that English.
Hey, uhm. I'm
going to the bookshelf doctor,
peel off the pizza. I wonder if I can find the pineapple roux. I'll paste it with flowers.  It's delicious, isn't
it? It's more delicious if you eat it only when it's cool. It's delicious even when it's just cool, but I guess it's not very popular in Japan,
but it's becoming a hot topic overseas.
Ah,
whether Peterlee is allowed to wear clothes like that.Ah, is the
ship full of tanks?This was a war battle, and when I made my debut on Twitter, I
took a survey.  But it's really
half of the Bakkart number 10.
Gradually, the good people are also being administered, and the other half is
riding on the other half. It's
really amazing.
Rear guard pipe large demande anti-fog 5 the voodoo
boo boo pinapolone.
Have you ever eaten it on pizza?
Ni ko Samorana is a branded
bar. You've never eaten it for generations that it's okay to put it on.
At a party, you
can't put it on a ticket.  Oh yeah, it's going to be fun from now on.
Yes, Earth fc, it's Chirai for August. 5 The peace facility ridge in the pie dap zone is also in bloom.
Because of the shrimp tape, it's 4 Nataina Pon 3 p  That's an amazing 102 days ago, so I'm
happy. It's really refreshing. It
tastes quick, so it's a major hit. You're really delicious, but I'd like to try it. I've never eaten it before,
and I'd
rather eat it.  I'm sure
there are people who don't like pineapple on a large pizza because they've never eaten it.8  I
also learned that Japanese people don't talk too much about that Thai 9, well, that
pizza doesn't really happen that much about Tainan's professional pizza.
Well, that's
true for Japanese people, but bread and pizza aren't that popular in Japan anyway.I'm a bit of an
idiot, so if someone suddenly says something like that to me, I don't know if I'll see them again or not.  It seems like it's
not good anymore.That
's what people say.The
tropical feel of Yayoi c
makes me sing.Ira
Darcy Sites to Do I died of natural causes wearing boots at a festival.That time,
when I tried it, I
thought about it.  Please tell me, Ryu Anately, I just finished the cross speed quiz, but I'm going to
go back to being a normal wife. Hurry up, posh,
feather, papa, papaan, here.
Foot a Eh,
no, ah, ah, 3rd place in the room, ah,
method
putter, all agents re, Abe Zumukan, oh
yeah, this is ok, Asaki Hodo,
Air English, yay, here, sky, Japanese, read it in Japanese,
ah, I'm a little confused in my head.  But the water is
poisonous, and then there's the Astis Pi kid.The color is 3 pairs, Future Leadership, and I'm a
pension.As I
mentioned earlier,
Shion-senpai has been expressing her dislike for Instagram for quite some time,
but when I looked at her surroundings, she turned into a perfect girl bar, and Instagram was good for that role.Ah,
there's no particular reason why she's so peaceful  However, I don't really want to hate it because I can't do it,
but I
guess people think that Instagram is content created by really cool people.
Yada's Airi High School,
where the committee member carried it, is no good. It's a lie to think that there is some kind of situation at the Sakurai store.
No, I see it's from dark roots and dark rice. Wow, the
customers have gotten in. The
ridges are also worms.  3 likes in the previous translation
caso deinem r stingray t ender ender
rasen usa reer reer enea reac car blinker
push up bar
pr  Bye bye bye, push the Fiscard appointment, then that's it. I'm a
little concerned, but why is Twitter OK if Instagram Sakura is not?
Everyone at Fishing Star Suneo's house is using it. I see.  I
love you
[Music]
2 Shunsen
What's that lonely Garn
Hey, I
think it's a bit difficult at home
then Inushikura no no no no no no that's fine
rc  thunder ir advice earena game phrase kc sound place
4 f 4 sne line ota ku number
pearl pink cre per hour 6 move tour adventure
pa
But recently, Twitter has become a bit like Instagram,
but what should I say, Preet?  I really can't forgive
it, there's no need for a certain Watase, no one's fine with that. That's
cool, Sugiden. Seriously, what kind of series are you going to do to make it look like it's going to be a good one? Then
seriously, no.  4 Nyan Moment Island It's the
one who's the one.
Spain, eh?
Use me to do.
ani
he ran,
Bach Yoshii, that's what I wanted to hear from Yugami Sepa, who was a bit irritated.
Darker Nep 5th row from Harukawa Hugh
Chain Pile Scene Senpai
ee 6 e Ah yes
All the time Maa Gaaai
Um, before this happens, Yes, you know that the first foreign minister of that hood talk was Marin Senpai, etc.
Thank you for your knowledge.  I know you'll do that, but it's been 9 years since I said goodbye.When I
asked if you had anything important to support your seniors, it would be nice to talk about your memories with Shion-senpai.  I'd
like you to take a look at that scene. Yes, I understand. It's
okay if you take a look. Is it a haiku?
Well, I'm just looking at it. I'll show you a little bit right now. I'm a real [ __ ]. I have so much back pain that I'm sick of it. Hey, did you want to
eat ROC?  Please,
TBS, I'm going to do Anna
Hey, why Shion, when I
was next to the person in charge, the
night was impressive.
Delicious 5-minute audio app sa dena 1
with me mmf 4
3-minute suction morning pete dangerous lead senpai It
's long, but actually it's a sepcial Shiontan is pretending that
night didn't happen
a It's covered up  Yes
z I don't know if you're saying it's retribution
Hahahaha that's right on the pine Sakushi-chan then the range is
2 minutes Hasher minutes ana  Gathering the values
Birch Arc Ichimura pin half body close-up
Since the eyes of cows, scrapes, and bikers met, Kondo Shion-senpai will also be on the talk show.Let's
read and listen. Directly is fine. Please
listen, please.  - Chiyon Senpai Information Company It's a big problem Asuke Hatsu
C Sensei Apen Yes
Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes it's strange, so I'd like you to tell me a little bit about the truth about love. What
happened?
Well, it didn't happen.
At the meeting, I was a little curious about something,
so I looked into the difference, but I didn't
know what it was.  Later, Shion-senpai said,
n one to do 3 items
window you say you have to do ni
Fielding Christine
Darby Harper's product Isn't something stuck?
Nothing ee Ah ha 4 I have nothing to answer.  It
wasn't there anymore, no, it's just coming out. There was nothing there, but the
staff and the piata pen, Yamaji Sebu. Do you
say that you love Cebu, who lives in Aisai City and is sweet?
No. It's true that my
seniors, picture books, and Chong are the same. A 21 sen
.  Jiyabai-san is a suspicious character who is a cheese synth Bezos last month, but my game is a 9-button multi-claw season, is
n't that strange?
It's Dodge Challenger.If you
say it's true, it's not matcha.It's
magic.Batch is also a truth schoolmate?
Yes, it's a fan.It
's natural to hear that.Cheeseler, always prepare two
can you do the oscars.Strong,
hmmm,
naoko.That's it now.  Well, that means that we were having that flirtation.
Hey, it's
not too much trouble, right? It's okay to do something like that.
Tanai-non-chan, Yayoto, Yuo-gayu.
Yes, that's right,
Oshio prefecture, right? Are you ok, so I'm sleepy - a dreamy image
ga Ube author, person senior exercise size,
voodoo, control and other wired by Atowa, the
side of the group, if Seungsung 2 b wife is coming soon  It's my wife,
now,
what is Emai-senpai? Was it Aso's star-shaped eyes
? Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa?  Did you
think it would be in Aso?
Nabegoro
johan Then it's a loss to play around with Athena Paint North Barb dissatisfied spoon ingredients
Case 2nd Daijiko
Kamp Mr. Shiun Senpai or someone like that No,
Ryomo  Until Ruel knows apb Hanyu's API number
Hey, this is also a species that can't be erased, so it can't be erased.  It's
okay, do
n't act like a criminal, it's
Eightman
re 4
Yeah, yeah,
well, until it happens, this
will happen to Marin-senpai, so I'm praying for Avocene.
But we slept in the same bed, right?
This Pad Zeniba CC 2 strokes behind Oda Pettypon in 9th place
Private area
But some people spent money on something, but it's the head.  There
was a time when I was supposed to do 3 seniors in Iito no Fuku Lab, but I was like, well, I stopped late and Japa was like that.My
physical strength was bad and I had a hard time leaving, so I couldn't react, but I thought that was childish.  When we were working together, we
talked about sharing the same bed in that house with Mayu-senpai. Boo, I didn't want to have
another bird, so I put Ai on top of me.
Una looked at the market price or something and told me about the furniture
Blue 1 was like, oh
well, but in the end there was no off-collaboration.
re an rora me to do for seniors ea are
ide ah
amane j rem # ncp  2 good 6 action for
nec working poor
In the cool Renu app anime, the senior couple and Mine senior are like that, and the
card needle to the buggy, etc.  I
want Meowth to do something wrong. Clean and plant trees. A scene where Pinata goes wild.
ee. Fink Koi, the owner of Nissei and Pen. I think everyone is better about what happened.
Well, that's it for now.  Let's buy it. I
'm going to ask my sister and Edge student circulation company Matsuki. Hey, yeah.
Medal. Wow. It's
almost the end and we're getting closer to the inter.
That true face 2021
is coming to an end, but do you have the most important memory of 2020? I
asked my seniors this question a while back, and the story that came up was that story about Shin 1000x. The
corner where I was sitting, the
station, etc. I took it with me.  I also thought about the house, there is
nothing to do,
Sabai disc sank is a pop star 4 scene senior barback pjs acquisition too,
big big 3-item set TPI  Well, I'm going to raise my standards and go to the hot springs to
tell some nice stories, so I don't think I'll move on and talk. Hey, yeah, that's right. I wonder what
2020 will really be like.
Pictures too.  It's
been such a rich year that I can't help but remember everything, and it's
already 2020. There were two concerts where I felt like I was already there, and I couldn't believe the other one.  I really can't  It
feels like it was before, but the
live shows have gotten bigger. It's great
that the 4th generation
members have joined the group, right? Well, they
must have been around for a long time.
Everything is new.  That's why it's still in my memory. There
's something special about this kid's broadcast. Even if this project happened, did you ever use it?
Planning mother: I wonder
what it was. It must be
easy.
[Music]
This project
Think about it, you can't get the role you want unless you write a book recently.I'm going to translate it.It
's a fantastical story, but the cat came here.Yes, it
was this day that I came to the city.  It was
really fun to be able to meet everyone and see Sakura melting away.
Oooh,
the center is great, but it also means that you can meet me too. I
can meet you.
Let's go to the oil painting - Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu and and the
4 door and sa with the rainy season and the rainy season and the
Prime Shin
voodoo
for you as the roaster with the special force charlie
and the Tomikawa Kameido 4aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa to.  swing john irving us
waaaaaaah 6 ea s see her to do sports
schwann am
mummified house mcu  Enter chiasoi blanket panpipe serie to
take 3 selection party etc. cuc dedication wiki curve amarone
burner meeting monow moni surplus azabu ab 9 pin
5th party It's
not just the 5 songs of those 4th generation students etc.
That's right Guest Indonesia 2  The new students have joined.
No, it's really a zone. No, it's
already grown big in 2020.
Hey, next time I'll be talking about something a little bit better than Kaa. I saw that I had a good relationship with that lady, but I
fell in love with her a lot four years ago, four years ago.
Yeah,
well, that's so much.  At first,
Sora-senpai caught my eye, and Gover was already there that year,
but Shion-senpai was already there, and
somehow I noticed how many people are increasing every other year.
Inside that  There
was a photo shoot, and as soon as I saw it, I
felt like wow, the original 6 had gotten bigger.No
, that's true.As a
new senior, I'm happy to see more and more people surpassing me.  Give me a break,
aren't you saying this?
Ah, no way! Co
Saitar Racer Semester Day
Urban Open 4 ag 4 a scam Loss No. 8 Ender Sora Senpai
nandemo ap pojo nodus cero good moon
usi arm  perseus fc wife in place for a
Picard future cp 5 owners are you doing
Together we have become a big family Hey,
really, but I think the size of the current folder live is just right for me every morning and evening.
Ah, I see. It's true that there's already a lot of them. That's
right. It's like a burger with this already. It would
be a bit dangerous if there was a collaboration at all.
Oh, turn, there are 4 cards, everyone is really big, so I can't get any more than this.
I was already crying. Ranran, what did you do? Kozumi,
this is about it.
I think it's just right.
rerere menon this Sakura Matcha.  Rufuruha foma Book is form
me some btree Earthprep iso 4 a to do ni
Mishimame is playing around
and calming down with Emma
Well, I'm happy to have any kind of person.
Well, I think the current number of people is accelerating and makes it feel like a family. Yeah, it's
true that if there are too many people, there won't be any live
shows. It's okay if we don't have a mode. 3 d Well, it might be a thing,
maybe next year.  The house and so on have participated in Indonesia and so on. It's going
to be three days. I might buy it. A
woman and a star.
In advance, by karin. The inscription is also peep. Dame bxx. Come on, mirror Kansai.  I'm
watching Boom Mappy in Paris, and it's sweet and peachy and muddy.
Hero Wing Shirley Majer's cauldron's major zun. Phoebe
Mabe opf eraser in Kansai style. Well, I'm
looking forward to the original Chinese version of
English. I don't know what that is right now. I
feel like a diva.  I'm doing that audition
r Thin Fabi Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaabackry tell see tell me about it soredemo right away ber
n-year-old chair Kanpaku c Nokke
8 a I can't get over June's person either
yeah  I've
come to my goal for 2021, but
something has happened.What I want to do is this.It's the closest one, so I choose it.There
are 6 rooms, so see.  I
want to release a song that will achieve this goal, like
1 million people,
right?
[Music] I
won't say it.
Well, the samurai association passed away on the exam, panties temple, let's all register.
[Music]
Thank you. I
hope most of you will register as well. It
's Shinobi Town, the shadow of the entertainment industry. Couples,
etc.  I want to do it.
Hmm, I want you to see it. I'll do my best to speak as good as it sounds. It's
just right. 1 It's cold and it's first. It's a total extension of the new Daisuke.
Chesou Pina menu view dog pointed out good looks too
A Watcher Cafe is going to be a Baikin Panyu gender renge
Aizu Aburikko Pointer Resher with my tongue
Line jersey boom is really looking forward to Nezu Underground Bloomba What is this time
?  It seems like they're
going to do it not only on the internet, but also in layers.That scene is good for 6 days a 8. I wonder if he'll get it.  I
'm trying to tell the staff what a good day is and what they're going to tell me. I'm going to get caught out. I wonder if I'll get a seat to take a breather. Written by Mr. Minami, who used to be a castle. I
'll definitely go. I don't have time to do the same demonstration this time.  I'm going to watch it live
from
rerere se b
ameblo pper we are so op pop were to
do
Saito Zebu Akanchan  The
horizontal screen is full of 3 Bokan birch and Y-san Ste 1
However 3 I'm looking forward to seeing Cyan-senpai's more idol-like appearance
Hey, Dorsey's sister Good luck with your practice I'll do
my best yeah
3 Last question  But this is not the case.It's
okay for a while, but for Shion-senpai,
what is
Houdai Club?
life is  I
think it's because of the big drive that I had, it's fun every day. Thank you.  Thank you very much for
reading my story today. A for reading the gum. A for
pulling the electric load.
Horn. Thursday. The last part of the inter-room challenge.
A.  A little note, everyone put energy on their foreheads
Ohno mappy
[applause]
Ono again, the actual machine business Ah,
what kind of 8 is that?
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa can use 20 det er jab ager big seam
Songha is the number of team possession
Harvard bench screen how are you  Doing
is definitely true.HarvardWell, it can't be helped since it's overseas.The
Japanese language is more of a problem.It's already amazing for a good girl.Who
is Dow? ana
anh  I can't talk to you, Eibach
andere noreen japanese soup love anos in
japanese Ah,
that's why even Omi, who has already been introduced to Asia, is a good friend of mine.
But
yeah, in the end, they say Ao Bida Hussein, Ao.
Thank you to everyone today as it seems to be a place full of sunrise that supports and meets the Nippon Line, Blue, Second, and Three.  We're
both going to sleep
Yes render
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
[music]
ta yeah
me
[music]
ana
me
tee
[music]
th  I'm
having
e 7 a
[music]
dea