[Music]
you
uh
[Music]
do
you
[Music]
do
you
[Music]
do
hmm
my
[Music]
do
you
[Music]
do
[Laughter]
it seems
it seems they have sealed my power away
it seems they have it's
it seems they have deemed me
too powerful
[Music]
you think putting me in a body like this
can make me
weaker
foolish
foolishness
of
gay
people
indeed
yes
foolish
s
kiara
is still
true and only
power
of
[Music]
yes don't know what's going on
excuse me
hello
hello everybody
let me get rid of this hat someone has
uh
mentioned it to me that i am wearing too
many hats there's never too many hats
there exists no such thing
as too many hats i need to assert my
dominance
i truly need to do
so that my
humble
servants
will finally understand
who the true potential really is
it is me it was always me
i don't know what's happening
[Laughter]
my arm hurts uh
oh my god the hiccups the hiccups
i never understand how to control this
body okay let's assert some dominance
hello
try to lift the bag
stop it
foolish
foolish once again you deserve a bunking
into infinity
you deserve a kick and a kick into the
usual room
for such comments
yes uh
what two weeks
two weeks and that is still
your empress being merciful
thank me
how did i how did i not until now think
of the word kikity kick
vacation excuse me now for real you're
getting a little bit of a time out my
little baby
you know you're like a you're like a
toddler you need timeout in the corner
um
here's your timeout there we go
regret
regrets
faults yes
[Laughter]
bts
i am the bgm
what do you need more than to listen to
my beautiful gorgeous voice huh
huh
no i have not listened to mozart i just
watched the tudors it has a similar
effect
yes
yes indeed
okay okay okay i will put on some bgm
which i just needed to get rid of the
the the noisy
the noisy
peasants
yes
my voice is the only
mama uh i didn't get to use all of my
christmas music yet man and christmas is
over what the [\h__\h] i didn't get to use
it all yet
yeah let's do this
rachel
go play play it
oh you can't hear shut them up then
obs
bow to me
listen to my words
yes
finally you have learned your lesson
to not mess with the empress
[Music]
ah
yes
okay
hello everybody
it is the
beginning of the week the last week
of 2020
[Music]
we don't even have one week left
2022 is at the doorsteps
knock knock knocking
knock knock
[Music]
thank you uh
twin
i didn't prepare joe quit
um
you are the ones that should be giving
me a joke
what do i have you guys for
what's the what's the
what's the answer to who's there what is
it i need to be suffering with 2022 and
then say i thought of it
birthday it's your birthday
what does the empress care about your
birthday i only care about my own
birthday just kidding happy birthday i
love you love you
wait what what
uh
uh where where is the joke guys
where's the joke
where's the [\h__\h] joke
uh oh okay okay knock knock
[Music]
oh
2022 more like 20 to few to
22.
[Music]
20 20
phew 2021 is finally over
[Laughter]
[Music]
who the [\h__\h] is there
get out of here 2022 get out of here
we are all sick of
our horrible years
that get messed up with
horrible things
each [\h__\h] year it's the same [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
um
[Music]
what
have we received an offering of a good
joke
what
what what the hell
[Music]
ah
what
[Music]
i don't care about your birthday
i don't care
ain't convinced it could be the freaking
pope's birthday and i don't give a [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
oh calm down calm down
[Music]
no have a birthday card
[Laughter]
[Music]
i mean i don't know when his birthday is
deeper like
[Music]
[Laughter]
popping up like
but unlike the pope
he's in shambles
oh no
[Music]
yeah this is what the tutors does to me
or any kind of like
any kind of show like that like game of
thrones or the tutors
after watching that i get very dramatic
and i'm like as if
i mean not as if it's a fact the whole
world resolves around me
resolves revolves revolves without
rewrote
doesn't matter i decide which word is
the right one we change up the english
language
for according to my
whims
[Music]
no not
darling was right i'm getting confused
we need to get the english language to
battle before me
the english language is playing with me
imprison the english language now
chicken guides
[Music]
we cannot let it
mess around and
insult
my
honor
no longer
i say
to the english language
what's
[Music]
why are you already back out of the
timeouts here go back go back
go back into the timeout
[Music]
oh
there you go bye bye
back to the corner
reflect upon your words and actions
although this one wasn't even bad you
didn't even say anything bad now but
still you're not done reflecting on your
past
bad deeds
and dudes
everybody i'm here to
read some super chats as i have
uh
once again
run away from them
too often
the only one who has power above
of of of me
on me
in me
is a super chance
[Music]
and um
uh i will also present to you
uh a beautiful gift
of
the weekly
schedule and perhaps
and announce some more
announcements
but a little bit later you guys are not
worthy just yet of the announcement
[Music]
announcements
ah but but i already showed the weekly
schedule to my
uh
humble
servants in the members community board
they have already seen it but i need
indeed i need to change something also i
messed up that stupid time what's my
time midnight in est
what is it actually
uh
it should be
6 p.m i think six
i mess up the time of the rebroadcast
and i messed up the time and i didn't
mess it up but it changed of this thing
uh
so this turns into that supposedly
and then we are here and then i can
change this
can i change it let's see
i am
working
one second
i will although this will if i show you
the schedule now
you guys will
see what i want to announce
damn it
dammit
i've lost my authority
nah it doesn't matter we're doing it
we're doing it
for sure
i mean
it's not a big announcement most of you
already know what's happening
last week of december
dot jpg
do you remember
it's the [\h__\h] last week of december
oh my god i can't take it i wouldn't go
to 2022
okay updated version
[Music]
of
has reached 500k views everybody
is it true i have heard rumors
if it is indeed true
i thank you
for
nothing because
deserves nothing less than that
it's a given
thank you for
nothing
[Music]
an empress
deserves more
thank you guys for looping and for
listening thank you thank you
[Music]
uh okay
ready and go
weekly scheduled
[Music]
what do i see what do i see here you get
a little bit of an early announcement
cha cha cha
[Music]
oops i don't have a proper image yet the
proper image will follow
um
organized by yours truly and press
takanoshikyo
i am holding
and organizing the holo and new years
karaoke
relay
[Applause]
[Music]
and we're almost complete almost all of
us
are partying and members are of course
me takanashikiyara then a kalyapamori
ninoma inanis watson ameliatson
iris
fauna saris is a test if i know all the
last names uh crony oro
[Music]
and bales huckles
yes
thankfully many many members were
interested in the idea that i have uh
started thinking about in the last
members only string
and then i started working on it
immediately
the times have also been decided
uh i will put up an image with the time
schedule after the super chat rating
stream uh
as soon as possible and a proper
announcement image as well
uh
yeah uh
no no no no guru and sana no sana is
there it's only good i'm missing
yes yes indians i don't know she might
have something to do i i had a like a
open
and like thingy like who wants to
participate and then these members
kindly offered to participate um
yeah
everybody will have
like a 45 minute slot
except
for uh
amelia
because amelia
she was planning on doing like uh
karaoke anyway i don't know if she put
her schedule out already but yeah she's
doing a karaoke anyway
like a marathon karaoke and
uh it kind of worked well with
you know the
the schedule that she would go last
and then continue on you know what i
mean so everyone does 45 minutes and
then amelia is the last one but she
continues on longer she doesn't have to
end it at 45 minutes obviously because
she already planned a marathon i thought
that it would be weird if she was
somewhere in the middle but then
continues on so she kind of has to go
last
yes yes
yes i'm finishing super strong exactly
[Music]
english
we will give our support i hope i hope
everybody all the all the um members uh
viewers will see this karaoke relay as a
chance to check out some other members
that they maybe usually don't watch if
they have the time uh i would appreciate
it if everyone would go to everyone
else's streams and be like
and support one another and
yeah it's only for 45 minutes so let's
do it let's try to show some support
yeah uh
for me it will be very late so i won't
be there for some of the members
but i'll try to be there for the first
couple of members um
yeah yeah yeah uh it will start
uh
pretty late uh for me no actually at a
decent good time for me
european it was not a european golden
time golden
for golden hour
and then go through the night for you
guys for n a it should be good times all
over
um
yes yes
[Music]
so it will go on for one two three ten
ten hours right it's ten that's ten is
that one two three four
five
people five six seven eight nine ten ten
hours yeah cuz 45 minutes and 15 minutes
in between 10 hours plus the whole time
that amelia goes on
she'll keep on running around the block
and running running and running running
i know that
it wasn't it maybe it wasn't so
necessary to
um do something
like this as in like i'm sure that
you know i could have done a solo
marathon as well we could have had more
time with another but don't worry i'm
also as you see in the schedule i'm
doing a different stream as well
actually on that friday i have free
streams i'll be
uh i can't say yet but i'll be in a
different stream as well before the new
year's clip review
so i'll be actually you'll you'll see
enough of me okay you will see enough of
me but i just felt like
um
we need something special for new year's
something something
we can't just
not collab at all in any way
there needs to be some kind of project
so i decided uh to do it like ah good
question is it archived good question um
[Music]
uh i think for the japanese girls it's
easy to do these kind of things
with our cats in karaoke streams but i
do realize that some of our girls have
some issues with that like because they
don't know many japanese songs and and
it's kind of difficult for them to
research wobbly blue so i said that it
doesn't matter you can even do it
archived or non-archived although
archives would be
preferred but i do think a lot of them
will be doing unarchived streams
to sing english songs because only
english songs we can only sing in
unarchived streams so
i i will at least as as the kickoff uh
and and leader of this project i will
uh as the kicker the kickoff
i will do an archived one
and who knows maybe iris because she
also knows a lot of japanese songs i
think
maybe she can do an archive one too
yeah and who knows who knows i mean we
could also sing whole live originals if
someone wants to do that
[Music]
foreign
kelly has her own songs exactly she
could just do her own songs if she wants
to
we will see we'll see whatever it's it's
been planned last minute but um
yeah oh yeah by the way uh uh
logo by spirit snare thank you
thank you
also last minute request
yeah okay so that is that we'll um
put that away for now i guess we'll keep
the schedule up so besides that we have
a rebroadcast of the christmas carol get
afterwards after the super chat rating
on tuesday i'm gonna take off because
i'm doing the super chat reading now
anyway uh gingerbread housemaking is
happening finally on wednesday
sims 4 new year's stream is on thursday
um
i will
uh
i just realized i forgot something in
the uh
jst time to add the next day thing oh
well whatever um
uh
what am i saying uh
new years new year since five yeah cause
we cut it up immediately before new
year's last time
um and i was like oh i gotta i gotta do
it then i gotta do it now then because
i'm not doing a marathon but i'll do it
on first day then
as a separate stream
and on friday we have the the mysterious
something
on uh before the new year's clip review
quite a bit before it will be in an
early time
and a new year's clip review if you saw
my post on twitter i'm currently asking
everybody to send me clips
of
uh your favorite moments of 2021 of my
streams my stream streams specifically
or collaboration streams where i was in
and someone else's channels that's okay
too and then we have the it's small to
read but we have the kickoff of the new
year's
karaoke relay
it should start at that time let me
check one more time
because i moved it all
up
one hour
it should be correct
[Music]
time yes that's correct
um
and
and then we have mario kart with ina
which was funny because
i was doing my google calendar
scheduling and then i i wanted i was
like what do i put on saturday hmm i
should practice for mario kart so i put
on mario kart there and then i realized
ah you know it's mario kart on the same
day so i was like you know you know
you know should we just collab and she
was like yo let's do it let's go
[Laughter]
yeah
yeah we're doing it we're practicing
together
um i think we're going to play against
the audience as well
mm-hmm
a lot of lot of taco tony these days
and then on sunday perhaps an art stream
if i feel like it
uh
yeah cause you guys keep on asking for
art streams and
everyone
[Music]
yeah let's have a great last week of
december and a good kiki kickoff
to
january um
yeah
we've seen how marion stacks up against
reyna what does that mean
what does that mean you mean
what is that what does that sentence
mean
[Music]
of course i mean i expected nothing less
yeah
no problem no problem um ina is good too
ina is amazing too so maybe i can maybe
a little bit of her skills can rub off
on me
okay i just want to read some super
chats and then go back to cuddling with
my kitokatos actually that's not true i
still need to make uh some things but
that's okay
[Music]
we have to start by reading the members
only super chats
so bear with me non-members i am sorry
those come first because chronologically
those came first
okay non-members
sorry about that
you're sure
i'm scrolling i'm scrolling
i'm scrolling i'm
scrolling i'm scrolling i'm scrolling
thank you guys everybody for being here
on such short notice by the way
i mean it's a given because i'm your
empress and your employer
emperor lawyer
[Music]
ignore me
okay oh my god the members only stream
had a lot of biggies a lot of biggies so
it will be a lot of reading
[Music]
foreign
my screen is so crowded
do you guys even see that like when you
when you come into the stream you don't
even know where to look do you
well well okay you know
people who always come to the super chat
readings they know to look at the top
right corner
yes yes
thank you thank you soon for the pinky
did you change your name
are you here manu kako
still cleaner than nina's screen
i guess so yeah
i look at fergiana can't take my eyes
off of her understandable
[Music]
yes you did i thought so
because i recognize the last part of
your name and the icon i guess wait what
was it before
how dare you change it without my
permission
don't worry about it you don't need to
be a member to partake in my streams but
thank you for the thought of wanting to
do it
i appreciate it
[Music]
i'm waiting for the answer jay phillip
ah
okay okay i'm a proof name change um
right reject it you must change your
name back just kidding
so it says a bit late but maligayang
pasco a king emperor
oh
what does that mean merry christmas to
you and your family tanjo i guess it
means maligayang pascal doesn't mean
merry christmas
hope you all had a wonderful time
together thank you
is that
philippine
from from the black eyed peas i can say
the following thing
filipino filipino filipino philippine
girl
in one of the songs the
one of the members was like
yelling that out the whole time sorry
i like that part what song was that
again
[Music]
does anyone recognize that yeah
super [\h__\h] old apple the app yeah oh
my god thank you for knowing it i used
to love
love the those songs from black eyed
peas the old ones the first few albums
oh my god
oh i think i'm gonna listen to some old
uh to the old
album
monkey business was it i like that one
after the stream
i must listen to it i love where is the
love yeah
although back then i didn't really
understand the meaning i just i just
thought it was a song about let's be
nice to each other
and it had a nice melody and i liked i
liked the part that
uh you know the part that goes like
where is the love
where
[Music]
is the love where is the love i love the
love
it just ain't the same
[Music]
yesterday i already had like a nostalgic
thingy going on in the middle of the
night because i saw this tweet
asking for
vocaloid songs and i was like um
here you go and then i went through all
these old vocaloid songs and then
somehow i also checked out um
the reason why i i i came to my own
songs was because in the in the
recommendations
i got the 8-bit drummer's
uh rendition of
one of my covers i think and then i went
through some covers that i haven't seen
yet
like that i called the free cover
apparently i haven't seen that one yet
and
and uh the
goodbye declaration i was listening to
that i was like holy [\h__\h] those videos
and the songs
they're so good i was like praise kiana
praise kiara
i just opened youtube and this is on my
recommendation is this your first time
seeing me
and hey wait you clicked on it and now
the first thing you see is me in this
form
wait
have you never seen me before
and and this is the first
first time
first thing you see
oh god
i i do better more interesting streams
and i usually i i look different okay
i
i look different i don't look this
currently they are they're sealing my
power away
because they have deemed me too powerful
strong impression
i mean yeah t posing
oh at someone in the first meeting i
guess is a good impression i think we
have scared that person away i don't see
a person in the comments anymore
i have scared her away oh no
[Music]
oh no come back
come back
oh no
[Music]
[Applause]
come back
go back
maybe she doesn't even know i'm talking
about her
or him
oh no
[Music]
okay anyway
shut up motion
i read one super chat it's quite the
accomplishment okay
um
[Music]
ah thank you for the pinky
navida midi thank you mrs
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat
i have a problem oh
i found a new job and met many female
colleagues they all say i'm cool and i
want to be my girlfriend
although my boyfriend encouraged me to
have a girlfriend
what
but they are all married and have
children
what
[Music]
what what
they clarified oh i said i want to spend
the weekend with my boyfriend
but they still invite me to drink at her
house on weekends it doesn't matter if i
bring my boyfriend when should i do
tanjo i seem to have suddenly become
very popular
okay wait so
you have a boyfriend
but many many girls
wants to date you as well
you sound like you're complaining
[Music]
that
is a weird problem to have
say say that you are don't drink alcohol
[Music]
uh
uh you're allergic to alcohol
and just getting close to it
will start
a weird rash all over your body
therefore you cannot come to drink at
their house
[Music]
yes yes
best advice that's how you let them down
thank you so much
i'm not sure if this is a serious
serious matter if it's really happening
but
[Laughter]
sounds like something
fun um you're you have suddenly you have
not suddenly become popular they have
just suddenly realized uh how great you
are
yes
thank you
for your support um
anton m thank you and michael bones
duncan for the red super chat
oh
applebee up
yeah yeah i i knew he was like at least
some some part filipino because he was
singing parts in philippine no language
tagalog sometimes
or often
michael bone says just a quick thank you
bonds for being yourself working hard
and bringing joy to your chimpkins
and
love you a little too much it makes me
worry but please keep it that way happy
new year
you can't love me too much i love you
too thank you
amazes me makes me blush you just can't
see because of my sunglasses thank you
michael balls
thank you
i'm happy to hear that happy new year to
you two is almost almost there we're
almost there happy and merry christmas
happy holidays and a good
good slippery into the 22
2022. um
yeah
laughing yeah too much inconceivable
loving you too much so much very much
right now
[Music]
i am nicer friday night
yeah that's a bearish cobra song maybe
you should listen to that one michael
bones
good song good old barry's kobo song
[Music]
oh my god another red one thank you
whoa
wow me
me it was me
what did i do giant firing coal before
you leave before it takes me hours to
get to your super chat tell me how did i
get you into the wonderful life i want
to hear your story
i want to hear your story
talk with me
[Music]
okay tell me
where are you where are you where are
you i'm trying to find you in the
comments did you already answer
[Music]
no i didn't see it yet
all right
okay
what what's the answer
[Music]
wait that looks so cute
it looks so cute under that tape
wait my chat actually broke um
i i can only look at
this one
did they say something yet
uh
uh look i was hiding all this chat under
the table uh
a whole talk let's go
ah you were funny i was watching a clip
of you waiting for bae and it was like
this yeah this is for me
wait but how did you find that one
i'm glad i'm glad you found me for that
one that's pretty recent
it was that in your recommendations
randomly and you clicked on it and you
were like
funny i don't know what the hell is this
did you did you want to be two bits
before that
[Music]
m on holotalk yeah everybody welcome our
20 of guests the chat
[Music]
the 20 of guests of whole talk special
episode chat
[Music]
if i missed the answer let me know guys
get the camera get the camera
[Music]
you guys listen to a different song
oopsie
[Music]
what is the answer
i want no more
he answered
it
giant fire ring
[Music]
yeah you need to give me better answers
like it's too short don't answer me with
one word answers
inconceivable i don't i can't find it so
it was oh there it is
oh no wait
yeah it was okay yeah el mao yeah el mao
so this is why i usually don't get chat
as a guest on
holotag
your answers are
useless to me
yeah oh no
i think that's a proper answer
i brought you here to the studio because
i won brother anderson
did you watch feature was before that
[Music]
[Laughter]
come on
come on write me a paragraph i had just
watched clips
[Music]
well then how did you find the clips
then
we need to dig deeper but the stream
itself was epic thank you that was a
short one too though so i guess for clip
watcher
wait did you did you get it recommended
when it was still live or when it was uh
already archived
i guess making that step that jump from
um clips to actual streams
is quite a big step huh
like maybe some people get stuck in the
clip
maze and never actually go watch streams
huh
um
smells super weird on the table shut up
a lot of cute members have been down
there
[Music]
i need more answers
i need more answers ask how frantical no
not yet it's not the time
yet there's a time
for these kind of things and it is not
now
potential
oh
[Music]
he disappeared
i think i scared him
streams are entirely different things to
begin with clips deliver something
usually what is that very advertised nah
not always
quite quickly where streams take a while
to get going and well tangential yeah
that is that let's try i get that i get
done
[Music]
did you say something that i missed you
said it was an arc ah okay okay then i
missed it
hold up okay so
how how did you find the clip still did
you arrive
who was do you remember what was the
first clip you watched do you remember
that
um
[Music]
where is he
confess
[Music]
anthony
he answered where
[Music]
he said dogo i die
oh
i mean uh
the one with callie
[Music]
well then the one
ah
i want to ask more questions but it's so
difficult to communicate with you guys
that was a good one yeah yeah
and now you have fallen for me
very good very well you must now follow
the laws of hashtag whoa casa gil do you
understand
do you understand chat
do you understand
all of you
[Music]
i'm on the couch
i'm jumping to couch
i don't even need to do it like that i
can do it like this
no no no no no no this yeah
a bowling balloon a bowling ball
so much fun
[Music]
you can't stop me
it gets funny when i move against it
[Music]
boom
boom boom
boom boom boom
boom
[Music]
oh you want to challenge me
i'll jump on you
blind bowling boom boom boom boom boom
boom boom boom boom boom
[Music]
okay enough of that
guys you are you are so childish you are
so childish we must go back to work
come with me enough slacking off
oh my god
you didn't see that you didn't see that
you didn't see that did you see
something no you didn't
[Music]
okay
okay read that super shot super shadows
[Music]
ah
unknown thank you for the pinky
merry christmas thank you hope you had
an amazing time with your family can't
believe this is already my second
christmas with you
i'm so glad i'm here looking forward to
celebrating many more christmas with you
and kfb love you forever
love you too thank
you oh
thank you very much i'm glad you're
still here too all of you guys everyone
everyone who has been here since last
christmas or i mean later of course too
but it's nice to see that people stay um
it's it feels very reassuring thank you
everybody
merry christmas to you yeah
mr cosmic stanky
[Music]
oh you're spreading out the pinky huh
ah should i read this
a lot of text
yeah
all right
i'll do that favor
how goes it first lady are you saying
that because
why are you saying it like that
hope christmas is going good for you i
also would like to say thanks for such
an amazing year you have given to me and
all to oh my kfb brotherhood
[Music]
also it's a little early but i also want
to drop an early birthday super chat
december 28th ah yeah i will not stream
on that day indeed so that's good that
you did that i guess
um funny story originally planned to
sorry
the coca-cola is coming up my throat
in a form of a burp but a lady doesn't
burp on stream so
i always try to have you guys notice i i
i never burped on stream before
[Music]
so it says uh
i originally planned to wait for the
28th to join membership
no i haven't yes i haven't
i have not
[Music]
no i don't mute myself i don't burp
no matter what i got on my birthday i'd
be reminded that joining kfb is the
greatest gift of all but i got impatient
and joined membership way before i was
just too eager to wait
wasn't all that bad though i remember
the day i joined you happened to be
there in pre-chat to welcome me becoming
a member oh
good timing so i guess my impatience
paid off i look forward to what the new
year has in store next for you my cami
aussie please continue to be the
resplendent phoenix we all love by the
way can i get a real safe harbor line
for my birthday oh
you mean like that
like that
we're all safe harlan happy birthday
[Music]
thank you for your support thank you
soon stay healthy
happy uh happy holidays merry christmas
and a happy new year
don't roll like me that wasn't very safe
[Music]
and cotton
thank you
expose 77 shang kristaps thank you for
the pinky merry christmas my enchanting
eternal oh she all my love to you and
your wonderful cats thank you
all my love to your cats as well or was
it one cat
was it one or two
but anyway
all the cats in the world must be
blessed with our love and we must serve
them
[Music]
thank you very much
hamsters are okay too shouldn't you be
in a corner
my cat just gave birth oh
give me one of those babies give me give
me give me me
[Music]
anyway merry christmas chris
yeah
happy holidays stay healthy
thank you for your support
thank you soon and thank you for
spending your time with me
professor thank you for the breakthrough
[Music]
i hope you had fun and a wonderful time
with your family this is my first
christmas with my aussie and kfb only
been happy with
thank you for making this year a lot
more bearable for me love you tanjo
thank you all thank you too you guys
also made my hair so much more bearable
yeah i don't know if i if it weren't for
the whole life this whole year i would
have just worked a normal job i guess
and then keep on
like
having issues with my job because of
deceiving yeah i
it would have been a very uncertain year
and i'm sure that many of you guys had
to deal with something like that like a
really uncertain way of life
through the whole year and i'm sorry
that you guys have to go through that
but i do want to say thank you for
giving me something that felt
very very safe and and comfortable
[Music]
thank you everybody i do appreciate that
immensely and it's not it's not normal
it's not a given i do realize that
[Music]
so i want to cherish it
as long as possible
[Music]
and make the best out of it the mostest
thank you from
foreign
[Music]
thank you for the pinky though you
weren't wrapped in ribbons and sitting
under the tree this morning you're still
the gift i treasured the lost quiera i
wasn't
i wasn't sitting naked under everybody's
dreams
what i i thought i was maybe it was just
my dream
i hope that a super chat my support and
love are enough in return for all you've
done for me love you boss merry
christmas it's more than enough thank
you
merry christmas to you too
thank you soon no one said anything
about naked oh that's true i just kind
of assumed when you say
wrapped in ribbons i just assumed that
i would be naked wrapped in ribbons
anyway it didn't happen apparently so
yeah
what do you mean i make things weird
i make things fun if anything
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you so much for your love and
support
oh god the coca-cola
okay okay
[Music]
hmm
well okay my my my rendition was kicking
at christmas but you had to change it up
huh
just have to thank you for the abs ah
i'll absolute
best gift that you have been this year
thank you for the motivation inspiration
tears smiles and loves you have given us
hope it's okay to want the same gift for
next nest
yeah i thought it was a typo but no
nothing's a typo with traffic
i'm not being too grabe
grabe what's a grabber what is that
right
well i hope you had tons of fun with
your family gave lots of gifts to your
cats
good and could enjoy your christmas holy
day here's some toast
toast emoji to another fantastic year
with our empress may al of your wishes
come true thank you
how is it spelled a
g-r-e-b-e now i don't know what that is
[Music]
thank you for the beautiful puns
you always always get me with those they
are so nice to read and and you teach me
some valuable
puns
that i will never be able to remember
but i really like them
uh i think it no it only shows like
generic emojis but not the members
emojis
the super chat rating thing
[Music]
grab a kind of water bird what
oh let me look it up
now i am curious
grab it
oh cute
is it cute it's cute
no actually creepy oh my god those
[\h__\h] eyes
those eyes are scary
[Music]
whoa
whoa it's like it's like i don't know
dark darth vader eyes or something like
that
oh my god
but i like the the fluffy head and the
colors
the colors of the head make me think of
a fox
at least for the ones that i'm looking
at i guess there's different ones too
[Music]
merry christmas
thank you mwah
happy holidays so as he blamed
even though even though that super chat
was
trying to assert dominance against me
patrick sanderson anton m thank you for
the pinky merry christmas one more time
can i miss you thank you
merry christmas a hundred times over you
guys were actually
and i felt kind of early because the
karaoke stream was supposed to be the
one where i say merry christmas to you
guys
but you guys
already said it so early even though i
guess at that point of time for me
christmas was over already that is true
that is true
thank you very much anton m
[Music]
uh yeah didn't
you say uh i i spent christmas with you
guys but yeah unfortunately i couldn't
spend like
the actual christmas with you guys i was
um
the stream was after it was already over
for me
so kind of delayed but i hope
i hope that was still okay for you guys
i mean depending on your time zone it
might have still been christmas morning
so
christmas lunch or so
yeah
but but new year's day i will be
spending with you guys yeah
both the 31st and the first
[Music]
according to my schedule
yeah
i decided to spend
that with you guys
i mean not not midnight not my midnight
uh but
so in theory i could go i could still go
out for midnight for the fireworks if i
wanted to because mine is at
eight half past eight pm and takes only
45 minutes
so in theory if i wanted to i could
still go out after that hmm
but i don't like going out
slavic fellow thank you in the certified
sizes
big sweet thanksgiving
[Music]
can't be with my human family today but
i'm happy to be with my chicken family
merry christmas tantrum kfb
ah
oh no you couldn't be with a family for
christmas that's pretty sad but i'm glad
that i was there for you then yeah
maybe you can at least spend new years
with your family or your friends
but even if not of course
of course i will be there
for you again
anytime you need me
see this is also a reason why i'm happy
if i can stream on on these kind of days
uh so that the people who can't be with
their family they then have something to
watch and something to cheer up with
[Music]
oh it's your birthday girlfriend
tomorrow
oh no
yeah i won't i won't be streaming
[Music]
i won't be streaming then
early birthday
happy early birthday
oh is that a rainbow incoming
[Music]
is a th sound and welsh
i've been today i pronounce it as a
double d
mixed freezy warrior thank you
thank you for the red super chant
merry christmas kiara i hope you treated
yourself nice and enjoyed your time with
your family also i want to say merry
christmas to kfb because they are best
community to be a part of yeah
i have a great community
[Music]
i do i do
well
i hope i hope you guys say
the good chimpkins that you are always
be kind to one another
don't pick
unnecessary fights
unless it's against the blue bird or the
green bird
[Music]
unity chad
yeah but no i'm also very happy with my
community that i think every every
almost every streamer says they love
their community and that their community
is the best but
we all know that kfp is the best we all
know it
we might not be the biggest
but we are the strongest
and hearing that from the small piano
i think means even more
because look at me
looking stronger than the real kiara
so much stronger
they got nothing on us guys
nothing
[Music]
fun
though are you complaining
what do you guys get an endless supply
of
anything that we sell
at kfp
huh
isn't that better than cookies you can
actually get full from that food from
chicken nuggets and burgers jaggle
burger phoenix burger fried uh
fries
fried fries
ah five onion rings and all that stuff
[Music]
unbelievable you guys are so spoiled
thank you once again happy holidays and
merry christmas to you
silly channel thank you for the red
super chat thank you
hi ken i'm really glad that you are
spending time with all of us during
christmas as a kfp employee who lives
alone in canada oh far away from friends
and family members oh
celebrating christmas of you and other
hollow ian girls is really meaningful to
me finally merry christmas to you and my
fellow kfp colleagues oh
that sucks again here we have another
example of a lonely lonely chimpkin but
we are all here for you
me and the rest of kfp
that sounds tough but
but
we are here for you
yeah thank you for your generous
big support thank you i really really
appreciate it and i wish you happy
holidays a merry related christmas and
yeah please stay healthy and soon there
will be a new year
soon so i hope you will stay with me and
support me in the coming year as well
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you
effo thank you soon for also a red
superchatter
merry christmas angel hope you had a
great time with your family i didn't get
much time to spend family due to work
but still enjoyed my time with them also
chris certainly got a lot of popcorn as
a present so i'm now extra ready for
this watch along
oh yeah i turned it up before the watch
along even started kusa a lot of popcorn
huh i was eating roasted almonds
now i'm very sad that now
uh the christmas markets are um closed
already i don't i understand i feel like
they should at least go on until after
new year's you know what i mean
they closed usually all on the 26th
but where am i supposed to get my
roasted almonds now
to be honest i saw them recently in the
supermarket so i guess i'll get them in
the supermarket but still
they're better in the christmas market
but they're probably also cheaper in the
supermarket so
uh
okay
i can deal with it but i didn't try them
yet who knows if they're as good as the
ones in the
in the christmas market
um
[Music]
yeah usually they're all closed at the
26th
there are some christmas markets or like
one
that goes on
longer a little bit only a few days i
think
[Music]
but
i actually
that reminds me my bff said that we
should just have like
um like a punch evening where we punch
each other to death just kidding a punch
evening where we drink punch
because she made she knows how to make
punch it's not that difficult and she
made one a while ago to that party that
i wasn't invited to because they knew
that i wouldn't want to be invited
yeah they made punch and and and and
then
she knows that
i uh
don't drink alcoholic punch
um so she offered then sometime soon she
comes to my place and we make punch at
my place and drink some more punch
some non-alcoholic punch
fist fight punch punch punch punch
no i mean the drink the drink
[Music]
um i'm excited for that i hope that will
still happen although it will probably
happen in january but
we need to
you know these kind of things we need to
make them
like okay-ish to happen
even outside of christmas markets
like honestly i've never seen or heard
of anyone to drink punch
outside of the christmas season uh or
outside of a christmas market
[Music]
i mean sometimes
some people make them at home like bff
but also only only until christmas
so we need we need to normalize that
i mean okay i wouldn't drink it in
summer
in summer we drink self-made iced tea
and self-made lemonade
[Music]
punch is a normal finger part ah no i
mean a different punch i think
i mean the hot punch
uh yeah i think you guys
mean like a different one don't you ask
me the cold one
is it the one that i always see uh in
like netflix shows in like a big big
bowl
i'm talking about mo
[Music]
are you
um
uh for christmas we like to drink hot
punch and mulled wine but it's two
different things
you guys father was talking about
something else huh
hot punch
i don't know if it's really just the
same punch as you guys know just in a
hot version
maybe it is maybe it's not
what's in this hot punch um normally it
tastes like
um
christmas
it tastes
well let me tell you
i think it's like orange and stuff and a
lot of different teas mixed together
punch
receptor uh okay there's different types
but oh man there's so many cool so the
most popular one is like an orange punch
but there's also berry punch
the orange punch has stuff like oranges
and
and and cinnamon and rum
if you wanted alcoholic
and uh
naticken whatever that was again
a little bit of
white wine perhaps
but i know that my friends when she
makes it herself she makes it with tea
tea bags
[Music]
beer and punch
bear and punch but berry punch has
uh cinnamon nail care i forgot what that
was
a red red wine
some tea
and some berries and lots of sugar sugar
sugar
yes yes
i'm not making stuff up i'm looking at
the recipes right now
[Music]
a gloves clothes clubs
what
i'm surprised you guys
didn't add it
what
wait so you guys have priceless markets
too though but i guess i guess it's only
mulled wine over there here it's like
either mild wine or or a hot punch
[Music]
interesting
oh yeah hot cider is also an option that
they
sell here in christmas markets but
it's not the most popular
[Music]
you guys should check out our christmas
markets they're so pretty they're also
always at gorgeous locations with like
big big ass churches in the background
or whatever big castles in the
background
um
mold mine at christmas markets and
coffee
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah coffee not
really
for us we have the mulled wine the punch
oh and also hot chocolate is a popular
option too
and i usually like usually there's like
a lot of different punch types that they
sell but they're all alcoholic so the
only option that i can ever choose is
the children's punch
which tastes good too but i would like
to have more variation too please
but the other day the other day with bff
i went to one christmas market that had
more than one option non-alcoholic
i really appreciated that
and i tried it out and it was really
good it was really really good
with uh
what was the word again
um
let me see
uh
[Music]
i think orange is just quince and orange
punch hot punch
coincidence i think not
[Music]
uh
okay okay okay let me read two but
that's we're almost done with the with
the members only ones and
joe star hero thank you i got both tails
of her eyes and yakuza like a dragon as
presents but the best present is
actually being able to catch up members
only stream yourself being stuck at my
retail job
yo nicer
did you have the day off
i guess it was uh on the 25th it was
closed right
nice good for you
thank you for spending time with me
thank you
and good choices and games both of those
games were played on my channel
in 2021
i had a lot of fun with them
yeah
they were great games and even entails
overrides even got a lot of awards or at
least one award
in the game awards yeah yeah so proud
i wonder when when yakuza like a dragon
first came out if that one got any
awards
because i didn't follow it quite
at that point i wouldn't know
yet highly critically acclaimed jrpg
[Music]
oh
no
i think it got a few really
it came out or but it came out never the
end of the previous year
i think it did
[Music]
you heard of the critic who claims jaya
pretty tales overrides of course i have
but hey i'm the ambassador
and hokan dagger and trevor g duncan and
there we go we are done with those we're
gonna read the unarchived
super chats now
don't worry i have them on i have them
archived but the
stream is on archive but if you missed
it it's gonna be rebroadcasted in a few
hours in four and a half hours
[Music]
i didn't download the vlog yet so
still need to download it
[Music]
thank you for clapping thank you
pinkie my mom was in town for christmas
and actually watched a member stream
with us stance oh yeah i read this one
in the preacher
she thought you were very funny and
loved your commentary she wishes you and
your family merry christmas and said
thank you for hosting
i am surprised your mom didn't cringe at
you she must be a very
open and understanding and cool mom
like
wow
what
maybe she was saying it ironically
but if not then she's a really cool mom
watching the members movie watch along
together
what
actually there are you have just
um
admitted
to be guilty of a crime
of illegal activities
because you shared your membership with
someone else
or are you telling me that your mom has
her own membership to my channel
hmm
objection
objection do i hear an objection
illegal
pay up now pay up just kidding
i mean i mean in general i guess it's uh
illegal but okay your mom will forgive
it i'll forgive it this once next time
if she wants to watch a stream of mine
she will have to pay
[Applause]
[Music]
me
you are guilty you admit it okay
well it's it's an honest mistake
but
i must be fair you must spend
two days in usual room prison
[Music]
so that it gets burnt into your brain
and you don't forget about it anymore
i got you i got you there
you didn't think that farted too you
guys think like i'm stupid or what
you must admit i am smarter than any of
you guys because you didn't catch this
illegal activity
[Music]
no no no no no i misspoke it's the usual
room only
sure thank you
yes thank you thank you thank you
free prize free is [\h__\h] sex
how many more times here are you gonna
ask me that stupid question
the first time i heard free time six
[Music]
she said she said it differently she
said one time three plus six and then
one time three times six okay
okay
[Music]
six times seven is it 42
uh
six
yeah it's 22. that's one of the ones
that i had the most trouble with when i
was younger six times seven never fully
entered my brain but i'm proud of myself
uh
now getting it correctly immediately
hmm
yeah same really nice
i think i remembered it
now because it was the one that i could
never remember
eight times seven oh god um
all right so five times eight is 40
plus one is 48 plus one is
what
yeah yeah yeah oh i got it i got it
i had to go from five times
upwards
okay but i got it i got it
oh i didn't use the computer calculator
that would have
taken me more time
[Music]
okay
stop it now
mr khan's big sanchez and kakundanka and
bradley thank you for the pinky today is
my birthday oh
and i thought i would be spreading it
alone but now i get to spend it with
watching my oshie sing her heart out
with that beautiful voiceovers thank you
for this kiara and thank you for all the
things you do for us love you thank you
well this is some kind of birthday party
for you dan you're welcome
i'm glad i could do something special on
your birthday for you sorry that i'm
kind of late though
happy birthday birthday bradley
bye
yeah
thank you
i'm sure
sorry that you
uh spent it alone besides me but
i think
i'm the best person you can have on your
birthday it's like
it's like i
you know imagine
having a birthday party and then being
able to hire me
i wonder if one day when people get
married oh
imagine someone trying to get me as
their
marriage
act
as a musical app to them to their
wedding
that wouldn't that be funny
having a youtube or at your wedding
wait no one did that before we gotta be
the first one to be invited is that an
option
it hasn't been until now
i mean you got to prepare a lot of
things like a see-through screen or
something i guess it doesn't have to be
safer we can't just be a normal screen i
guess
interesting you know what you know what
you know what i mean if you are planning
to get uh married at some point and
i mean
if you wouldn't mind that it would be
kind of cringy a little bit if you
uh have a youtuber as your musical act
cuz let's be honest
unless the whole audience
also likes anime stuff
they're gonna be like what the [\h__\h] is
that
what the [\h__\h] is that
but if you want it please feel free to
contact uh whole live contact form on
the homepage yes
we will take it into consideration
[Music]
i need someone to marry
and then we can do like a whole video
like maroon 5.
sugar
yes please
[Music]
make it all right need a little
sweetness in my life
[Music]
like that
where i make my way to a convention but
like how the [\h__\h] would we do that i
just literally open like a zoom call and
that's it
or click record on obs
[Music]
i can't do it like that it doesn't it's
not the same thing
damn it
dammit
and maybe with the wealthy model maybe
we can commission kanawha
to make a video like that
[Music]
green screen suits
uh um i'm not sure it works like that
getting into a car in a green screen
suit you would have to green screen
the car too some i don't know
i don't know
sounds difficult
[Music]
i don't at all brandon wood thank you
for the pinky
hi mom it was my birth why the [\h__\h] are
there so many birthdays how dare you
guys get bored just kidding
happy birthday where's my birthday on
the 25th i am real relatively a
relatively new chicken but you have
helped me through a very dark time in my
life and have become a regular companion
i'm so sorry for what i just said
it was a joke it struck
i listened to while at work i've been
putting in more effort to take care of
myself oh whenever i have the big sad i
ask myself what would make ya proud and
it motivates me to do whatever needs to
be done truly i cannot thank you enough
for improving my life and being the
person i look up the most thank you
thank you brendan
first of all happy belated birthday
let me sing for you
hey
oops
[\h__\h]
hannah
happy birthday to you
happy birthday dear brandon
i accidentally closed my super chat
window that's why i said [\h__\h]
no stop stop kiwawa stop
oopsie
and i have to reload it
yeah well
i'm glad i'm glad to hear that i have
definitely had many many times or
phases in my life where i also
didn't take the best care of myself
and kind of like was
um
letting myself go a little bit and i
mean i think
i think we all eventually have something
like that
what the [\h__\h] youtube
just let me reload the [\h__\h] page come
on
[Music]
so it's very relatable
and and i think like at
to a certain point and a certain amount
of time
it's okay to let yourself go sometimes
no need to
force yourself to always be super
perfect and beautiful whatever
yeah it's understandable
okay i'm scrolling back down
we all have our low moments yeah
but
now it's time to get back on your feet
and go back to those high moments you
decide
when the time will be
you can do it
yes you can do it brandon would
thank you so much mwah thank you for
your support
and happy holidays to you
[Music]
for the red super chat
very well that is not necessary i
already read this the the song sang the
songs that you suggested haha
i didn't even read your super chat
beforehand but
tannenbaum was spontaneous and still
enough was planned anyway
[Music]
so you're one lucky chicken
one lucky chicken
[Music]
i felt it i felt someone wanted me to
sing no songs
and i sign them both in german
even though both exist in english i
thought you know i usually don't have
many
german songs at my disposal
so i thought i might as well sing these
ones in german
thank you
guys i hope you enjoyed them yeah
thank you cocoon
for the super chat ma
[Music]
navida midi danger
nice richard shut up i saw that last
part
after retweeting okay and i was like
maybe
maybe the rest of the image will
outweigh that one part
because it's too beautiful to not
retweet it for god's sake and i want you
guys to
see that beautiful
kiana merchandise that you could get
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
kelly liked it too
kelly liked it i mean but i think kelly
likes just er cali retweeted us did you
no she didn't retweet it did she oh no
oh no
did she also miss that one part
no way she did
oh my [\h__\h] god i mean i feel like
it's okay that i did it it's kind of
like
normal that i did it it was
it was to be expected but the fact that
kelly did wait i don't see it i don't
see it retweeted me she might have just
liked it correct
let me go for her likes
[Music]
she likes a lot of things though she
likes i think every piece of art artwork
i try to do the same
[Music]
it's a long long list of things
oh i'll be going through this for ages
wait did she unretweet it
maybe she retweeted it in an unretweeted
no but i don't see it now that's okay
that's probably for the better
[Music]
i'm actually surprised that kelly
um was the first one to collab with odui
the first senpai like on it
has really sampled everything
we might not even collab with japanese
senpai's yet
kelly's feet are so quick
not even a japanese senpai first what
[Music]
first one being ian
holy moly
kelly is quick on her feet yeah
kelly's like always the like first
person to collab with new new gens
um
[Music]
she took the burp collab yeah i thought
i thought uh
the first ian collab with the new birch
would be me i thought but i was too slow
it seems
i should have known but you know i i
could have i could have asked for a
collab too but like i'm i i was too
too busy
i don't feel like
uh
doing any any kind of
extra collabs right now at the moment
[Music]
i do like the new gen though i do like
the sixth generation
they are all very cute and interesting
so eventually i want to collab with at
least one of them
[Music]
i do i think i like i like clyoni
koyoni i gave her a call
in her
call stream
so at least at least some some sort of
collab i guess
yeah game of thrones friends yeah
but not only that i just really think
that you know
like people like her are so easy to
collab with because she talks a lot just
like me
so
um
it feels like
like she's the type of person who can
have a collab with anyone
and can talk about anything not only
game of thrones so eventually i want to
collab with her
[Music]
i was i was i was thinking maybe i could
show her the en server but since i've
already done that so many times on my
channel
i think i would offer it to be on her
channel only so that we can do it mainly
in japanese too without having to worry
too much about you know
speaking too much japanese
but has she even been to the japanese
minecraft server yet
probably not
[Music]
so it's probably best to first wait
until she's been to the japanese server
and then then show her the ian server
um
[Music]
the disney
i
invited a few girls to do a disney
minecraft mod to collab with me
i invited a few girls to do it with me
[Music]
someone else did it before them too and
the moment i saw that i was like ah
that's cool i want to do it too wasn't
it shitaken
wasn't it shiraket that went to
uh was it china again or was it
again
yeah i saw that and i was like who
should i go with who likes disney
so i invited a couple girls but i think
i'm still missing the answer from one of
them
yeah
but it will happen it will happen i
don't know how it works but it will
happen
[Music]
and also
um
there will be
uh a non-cooking
but camera stream
in january i think the second week maybe
i'm planning something
you guys want to know what
i already mentioned the
the like me wanting to do that
eventually
[Music]
it's
going to be
cards what cards
cards
[Music]
card open i don't know which cards would
i be opening
no
[Music]
i don't know how to do origami
um but i ordered or origami paper
and i ordered the origami book
so we'll do a relaxing origami streak
no one has that has done that before as
far as i know
i came up with some original ideas the
other one that i want to do eventually
is acrylic painting even
um like pouring techniques but pouring
techniques just look like i need a lot
of space and it's going to be a huge
[\h__\h] mess
so we might just start off with normal
painting eventually um but in january i
want to do origami
oh
yes yes yes
origami
what technique pouring
pouring pouring acryl like a [\h__\h] ton of
acrylic color pouring it over um like
mixing it together in like like not
actually mixing but it's like you you
there's different ways of doing it but
for example you take like a plastic cup
and you put like
layers of of colors and thick layers
into the cup and then you kind of like
spread it like you you pour it over the
canvas
and then you move the canvas around so
that it like
uh
spreads over the canvas
and it's kind of like you need a lot of
color and you need to like put plastic
sheets all over the table and the floor
because it's a huge mess
it goes everywhere and it will go over
the edges of the of the
acrylic of the of the canvas because it
needs to be a lot of color
[Music]
that it's a big mess but i wanna i want
to try it eventually but we would try
with something else like i've been
seeing this these videos i think it was
called jay lee painting
um
i think it's like is it it must be a
korean person i think someone who does
like
um some interesting techniques of
painting uh
uh with acryl
acrylic
colors on canvas
and
um
it looks simple it's probably very
difficult it looks simple though
but i want to try something like what he
does
like he does some
for example some like
some simple
um
landscaping
i the other day i saw a video where he
did mountains with a scissor
it sounded pretty cool i want to give
that a try hmm
but not not the time for it yet we'll do
just first origami
[Music]
yeah i want to try all kinds of
different things now and i also i'm
looking into
improving my setup of course more and
more
i'm first still waiting to
get the the addition to my kitchen
like an extra kitchen counter
that will probably come in february
and then i'm thinking of buying
something very specific you guys want
you guys want to see
once i have that extra kitchen counter
i'm thinking
of setting up something like this
a slider
and so that i can like move smoothly
legit yeah
okay not this one actually i found a
specific one that i really like
is
it might be
it might be pretty
like almost too much effort
but i've been doing a lot of cooking
streams and i want to do even more
next year
um
and not only cooking streams but like
all kinds of things
as i said origami and so on
and with this one i was thinking like i
can easily
if i find out where the best position
would be but i could like switch from
the hot plate to like the cutting area
where the hot plate is not
there you know what i mean like
switching from one area to the other
area
without too much trouble although i am
wondering like how do i position this so
that it's not in my way
that's still something i will have to
think about
yeah but but but it's something i'm
considering to improving my setup
no no no tape no tape
although i talked a little bit also with
ame about it and and and she said that
for her members only streams when she
does cooking streams like that
her setup consists of a tripod and a
camera taped onto it as well
so just like me i don't feel bad about
it anymore
duct tape is the way to go apparently
but hers
seems to be more stable than mine
[Music]
anyway that's something some things that
i'm working on now uh please look
forward to it in 2022
[Music]
man i'm
more excited about the acrylic stuff
happening eventually because i need
something to hang up in my apartment
anyway
oh and i was also thinking though i was
thinking about one thing like eventually
when i do like a good acrylic painting i
was thinking of then um
doing like a
raffle so that you guys could win it
what i painted
i would send it to uh you know to the to
the office first
and they would send it to you guys i
wouldn't send it directly but
yeah yeah yeah yeah what do you think
about that when i'm painting from kiara
at once oh but i dare you if you sell
that [\h__\h]
if you sell that [\h__\h]
i dare you
it it would be a like one so so unique
you need to
keep it and hang it up on your what
how do i get people to not sell it hmm
is there any way to like
keep people from doing that
it would be an heirloom yeah indeed
yeah family heirloom
i would not sell it
under 10 million
yes i also kind of thought because
people mentioned uh auction i did think
a little bit about it could also be like
a charity auction eventually
yeah the charity thing
wanted to do it for a long time since
ahmed did it but would never happened i
don't know there were always other
things
happening
hopefully we can do a 2022 charity
stream
at some point and then one of the things
that people could win could be uh
a win
one of the things that i could
be giving out to
for charity could be
something like that yeah
um
yeah i'm sure i'm sure some of you guys
would spend some good money on that so
but i don't want it you should go to
charity or it should be for free
like a free
um
raffle for you guys
yeah
but don't spend too much guys on it that
too much guys too much money on it guys
it's that would be stupid no i don't
even want it to be 10k
no that's that's ridiculous i mean okay
for charity me but no i would feel bad
like about your guys's wallets okay
i need to cap it somewhere maximum like
1k or something
and i'll just make more i'll just make
several but
only one per person
i gotta cap it somewhere
so you guys don't try to keep on one
upping one another no no no no
spend your guys wisely
[Music]
hollow ian new merch incoming tomorrow
what do you mean to your place something
you ordered before
yeah small potential i haven't had small
tension in a while
i mean 2d small attention
but make it a raffle and you get tickets
by donating to charity
ah
that's a good idea too
true
yeah that sucker thing oh yeah i don't
even know either i didn't know that was
happening
i retweeted some new merchandise from
tsukumo but to be honest i don't know
what that is
normally i know about new merchandise i
didn't know about this one
looks cute though
uh yeah it's pins and uh acrylic stands
right there's plushies too what
plus is
was there a preview
oh my god here she goes with the
tangents with the [\h__\h] tangents
let me see
where do i sit here at this uh booth
oh it's already on sale
uh 28th of december is when it starts
until first uh until 10th of
january
and then sending it out in january
already
really
so you can't it's not even a month of
time to buy it interesting
acrylic oh no wait it's acrylics dance
and
[Music]
oh wait on it
oh my english myth
well i only see the buttons and the
stands i don't see
uh plushies
i don't think there will be plushies
[Music]
oh badges
um
starting from tomorrow
okay we need to read super chat that's
what i'm here for
already been two hours i could have been
done by now
i could have been
[Music]
yeah you can buy the stand solo but the
badges seem to be um a set
i got myself new
fruit thingies i haven't had them in a
while kept on forgetting buying new ones
but i got like two packages now
let me take one now because the
coca-cola hasn't really been nice on my
approach
which i i knew i knew that that was
gonna happen
well that doesn't taste very good but
okay
that doesn't taste really good
yeah okay
fruits not fruit fruit fruit
food
fruit
[Music]
from ricola
ricola
yeah from
switzerland switzerland
and kfb have a collaboration they keep
on providing me with
fruit thingies herbal candies yes yes
[Music]
um
i look different must be the hat
yes it's the hat
definitely or my new glasses my
sunglasses
feel excel thank you for the red super
chat thank you i hope you're enjoying
this christmas and getting enough rest
during the holiday in my country do
celebrate christmas but we don't have
any days off oh so i'm just celebrating
in my way during the weekend and of
course also watching your life thank you
oh you watched the unknown carp1 live
nicer thank you
[Music]
yeah
well well
well
merry christmas to you then
and happy holidays even though there's
no holidays
and thank you so much felix sal for
being around this christmas season to
dance
[Music]
hope you have
a great time
and uh
what was i gonna say i forgot
oh yeah enough rest um i feel
even though i didn't rest much yet
i feel already kind of rested
so it's okay tomorrow i get even more
rest
yeah
we need to we need to start the next
year
with energy right guys
[Music]
thank you felix wow
casey for you
ty's in pakistan for a red super chat
still doing some holiday runs so i'm
lurking but wanted to drop a present
here to say thank you for being
incredible and spending some holiday
time with us may there be many more
because you truly do make them amazing
thank you for everything thank you too
thank you for being there
whenever i do stuff like this
thank you guys for spending time with me
um
you guys are what makes them amazing too
yeah
i like doing these
holiday streams
i mean what else would i be doing huh
i like chilling at home with my kitty
cats and then streaming every once in a
while that's my ideal lifestyle
thank you everybody
enjoy your
special
quality
time
with your family everybody and then once
in a while spend some time with me okay
living the dream exactly
thank you typhon a big case for you
wow a big kiss from a small kiara
[Music]
thank you soon
red
happy holidays merry christmas
thai tea
thank you so much
daisy thank you also for red super chat
mwah
what did i give chi again
daisy thank you it was very rude to turn
off supers yesterday right before i
could send my christmas present
i'm sorry
well thank you for sending it now
i i apologize
for taking that away from you
but i accept the present thank you
i hope that i was able to give something
back to you
this year daisy
um i really hope so
thank you for your sweet kind and
generous support always
from the bottom of my heart thank you
soon
[Music]
oh another one now i have to send two
for shame
wait what happened again i forgot
i kind of like no something was the
reason for you to send two
no wait it
was there something or am i imagining
did you just send two for the giggles
[Music]
i forgot
for shame
what what was this thing to be shameful
about
[Music]
just because you couldn't send it the
first time but that's not your fault
that was my fault
that's it
that's it daisy
[Music]
there's nothing to be ashamed of
thank you daisy
way too generous you just wanted to
that's so sweet thank you you know what
i just want to do
this
amazing mom you cover up my whole
beautiful face but
well let me give you buds and kisses bye
bye
[Music]
means
pants duncan small brain duncan for the
pinky
thanks mate bloody bloody hell mate
so scuffed but still so fun
i mean it wasn't that scuffed was it
i think the stream wasn't even that
scuffed
the fact that i was doing it
uh alone i think i still kind of had a
little well
i couldn't change the the
angle too often but
it was fun
i did practice the songs like before
that uh so my voice was a little bit
uh
um exhausted but it wasn't only that i
also practiced the day before
but it wasn't only that i think
you know when i don't hear
feedback while singing while still
hearing the music through my headphones
but i just don't hear my own voice
because of the the whole way everything
was set up
because i was here listening for the vr
headset um
what that causes is that i think
like i don't know how to control my
voice
if i don't hear it the same way i
usually hear it
and that makes me
um
for example it makes me scream more i i
i notice that when i do my cooking
streams as well
because
uh for the cooking streams i have some
kind of feedback but it's not very
it's not as good as the one i usually
have
so
when that happens i
i forced my voice more than i normally
should
or normally would
[Music]
and i tend to speak
louder or almost shout
and when singing it's even worse because
it's easier for me to control my voice
when i hear it it's such a i think it
must be a bit weird for people who
don't
do stuff like that
um like i don't have the same problem
when i'm like for example in a karaoke
bar
like because i think the difference is
like when i'm in a karaoke
um the music comes through speakers and
my voice comes through speakers i mean
in some way you do have a feedback there
but both things come from speaker
um and then when i when i just sing in
the shower or whatever or or just
at home
[Music]
with the with like speakers
then
it's it's different you know it is
different than when it comes from
speakers and i sing on top of that
then i i still hear myself well you know
what i mean but when i hear music
through my headphones but i don't hear
my voice from my headphones
that's where it gets difficult
[Music]
yeah it's
weird but okay some of you guys seem to
understand thank you yeah and that's why
i had some issues with my voice but at
least so i think i think some songs were
okay i listened to the archive
afterwards and
for most of it it sounded okay
um thankfully
[Music]
i wish i could
just take out the
the headphone part
from the
vr goggles and put my actual headphones
on top of it
[Music]
uh and then have the feedback from the
go xlr i wish that was somehow possible
i talked with ahmed a little bit about
it but
didn't really get a good solution on
that um so
yeah
it is what it is it is what it is
thank you guys i'm glad you liked it
anyway
um
oh by the way the thing then the set
sparks i think i think i i i think i can
upload it tomorrow perhaps
when i have my day off
i need to re-record it uh i just got the
audio
like yesterday or so
and i didn't have time to record it yet
but
i guess i'll i might do it after this
stream then hmm
yeah
your smaller earbuds connected and put
it the little headphones uh
um
would that work
i'm not sure
that would still be like kind of low
audio quality though
[Music]
anyway yeah just wanted to explain a
little bit but
but mostly it went fine went well um i i
hope you guys enjoyed that special
karaoke the first time that i used the
vr model like that
and
[Music]
yeah
if you missed the unlike craft part it's
gonna be rebroadcasted
in
three and a half hours and i need to
really hurry up now
if i still want to get something done
flaming pants thank you soon small brain
hello i already read that thank you with
freak zero six one eight times
merry christmas small pencil you're so
cute love you thank you
merry christmas to you too and a happy
new year
thank you for your support i love you
too
thank you
stay healthy stay happy
and continue being yourself
looking forward to your support in 2022
santa amaris
what is this long korean name that i see
korean translation
i guys i think i might be wrong but i
feel like i have more korean viewers now
than i have
japanese viewers
it's crazy
[Music]
i read this as
see even at these crazy times what are
you guys doing watching me
um
[Music]
hmm
it makes sense really
says the clipper
booty booty booty you need to tell them
to not only watch my clips
i see a lot of people commenting on your
clips but i see i don't see those people
in my life chat
what's up with that i mean i i still do
see a lot of korean people in my live
chat but but but i do see a lot of
people that comment on your clips but
they don't come here you have to tell
them to come here
okay relay this message to them please
come here i know it's a shitty time but
you gotta come
maybe they work that is true yeah
don't stop looking stop liking
come out of the shadows please
great shadow legends
[Music]
thank you for the red silver chad
merry henry's tension
[Music]
and miss
i hope you enjoyed the holidays i know i
did spend it with a beautiful
orange-haired lady that stole my heart
you spent it with coco senpai
wow damn that's not bad my christmas
wish is potential to stay with us
forever hopefully santa granted it
before iris took him out
[Music]
oh man i like the whole
iris
santa arc
it's it's been
i've got good use out of it
this christmas season maybe more use
than iris has been getting out of it
nice too
very nice thank you every other cult
please send me some photos of you
spending christmas with coco senpai i
want to see that
yeah thank you happy holidays to you
[Music]
oh yeah it's her anniversary today i
think
yeah
i think i saw it trending on twitter two
years
two years anniversary
patsy patsy
[Music]
lexington
from a veto thank you you guys liked my
hallelujah so much but i will tell you
now if i sing that
with my actual setup with my headphones
i will sing it better
i i know i can sing it better than i did
there
next time i'll do an unarchived karaoke
without the vr then i'll prove it to you
naked chicken duncan
jay
[Music]
and do it during the relay
i can't because i'm planning on uh
doing an archived one
robert carney thank you anthony webb
duncan but i am thinking whether or not
i could do
my archived 45 minute portion in vr
again
i might do that
yeah
with full body tracking this time and
maybe doing something dance dance
[Music]
anthony webb says in his red super chat
piano you can all the streams are so
good it feels like being in an idol
concert you're so awesome thank you uh
that is
very nice to hear i i wish um
eventually i can do something more like
you know
um
like like uh the other girls who already
have the 3d and do like proper concerts
that's something that me as idol fan
is definitely looking forward to a lot
um but it makes me happy to hear that
even
with those vibes it still gives you like
idle concert vibes
[Music]
it's a good start thank you anthony
happy holidays
[Music]
the day you reach samsara what's some
saga is that like heaven
[Music]
will you be commentating no i'll be
chilling in bed
and i got enough responses for the relay
yes yes i did uh now everyone is
participating except uh gouda
i'm glad we got so many participation
requests
i'm very happy they decided to
participate
ah a cycle of death and rebirth into
which life in the material world is
bound
is that some kind of like like
like certain religion thingy
[Music]
enlightenment or
who's first me
because i had the earliest time zone
earliest not i mean not like that but
like
uh it works best if i start also because
i'm organizing it
and then amme will be ending it i'll be
uploading a schedule afterwards jacob 47
out thank you soon write some free
dancing thank you for the pinky can you
hear me now oh wait well i can hear you
now now that i am reading it out loud
yes
so i guess that kind of works in the end
thank you wrestle free
3d dancing i-n-k-s-n-i-s-p
dankeshan kakundanka
i noticed i noticed afterwards when i
was watching the archive
i saw in the chat
that the dead baby sent the super chat
did you guys notice
it's it's bad but maybe it was only a
one time only thing
it changed its name again by the way
because i saw in the archive the name
was still it was gone too fast but it
was still like something like akachan
dead baby or something like that but now
it's just you know that sign
i don't know what to call that sign the
sign
um no i'll post it in chat
it's like i think it's like a dn sign or
this one
the dead baby
[Music]
he has been sending them from no i would
have noticed
maybe they forgot to switch accounts
no i don't think so because the baby
tweeted the same uh tweeted the baby uh
sent a superchat the way it always does
with a crying emoji
so
it seems like it was fully in character
that's not japanese it's like yeah the
end like uh
shimmy kitty yeah yeah
but you guys don't use that
outside of japanese language
maybe
but it already said goodbye why would it
be saying goodbye again
[Music]
if if that sign is telling me that it's
over then why why it was already over
why did you do that again to me
oh you never seen that before
interesting
[Music]
only solid in a japanese context
oh wait this one is archived now
we finally reached the archived ones
[Music]
you're not not much of a difference but
yeah
jingle bells jingle bells jingle bell
rock
okay
[Music]
and time to thank you for the red super
chat
[Music]
was amazing love your voice range bloody
hell mate you were slaying it here's a
red for you thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
uh i had some troubles with the with the
with some of the lower songs
especially like for example the one the
crit the christmas eve song the japanese
one
but i feel like if i had feedback i
would have been able to sing it better
because when i was practicing i i was
able to reach the notes
um want to give it a try again at some
point thank you though gd
[Music]
i appreciate the feedback
pixel art student thank you huge king
crowbar thank you until funny aside
congratulations on a huge milestone 100
million view video views oh our phoenix
is crushing it
oh yeah i think i saw that on twitter
someone maybe you
sent me
the info that my channel has reached 100
million video views in total
interesting
[Music]
i suppose that is a lot
together with amen
uh no way am i reached on the same day
[Music]
no way
no no [\h__\h] way
[Music]
eh
can someone confirm that
are you noticed because of him oh
[Music]
if that is true that would be so weird
yeah
also one million on vampire
but yeah i think i already tweeted about
that
ah maybe a few days ago
oh
nice
[Music]
that reminds me like i think this month
i really haven't streamed that much
compared to other months but
that's probably because we haven't had
jrpgs going on
we'll do
our usual long hour jrpgs again soon
please wait for a little while longer
thank you dragonspire mwah
yeah quality over quantity currently at
least in this
month um
we had a lot of quality streams even
though they were not too long
it still felt like i was streaming
constantly though even though i was
streaming probably a lot of less hours
thank you for the membership welcome
jimmy fried penguin thank you for the
pinky happy christmas stencil i heard my
penguin friend petered a little
said we penguins have an official
organization name which is terrific we
penguins will conquer the world and give
it to you remember we penguins all
admire you
as you should
interesting okay this person doesn't
sound like
[Music]
he is for the union
wait was it the pink penguins for the
union or was it the chimpkins who wanted
to build a union
well this person seems uh this penguin
seems decent
was it the chickens
there was the penguins
no the penguins wanted a gang and the
chickens wanted a union no
two different things both dangerous
you only know onions that's right that's
right you only know onions
five onion rings
anton and vanquishing for
i wanted this for christmas more than
anything else oh
i'm always happy to hear your voice but
when you start singing i just get
overwhelmed with emotion
happy holidays everyone and viva la
quiet
thank you oh really
thank you
i
it really makes me feel happy
when people
say they like my singing that much
because i know i'm not really like
considered the singer of holo
ian
um
but i do
try very hard and
it's it is something that
i i want to focus on
so
it means a lot to me when people
say they like it that much yeah
thank you everybody thank you anton
thank you spider-lord thank you math
muffins and counting chickens
[Music]
merry christmas christmas carol
attention thank you for making my day
every day and let me celebrate money
christmas with you and kfp forever thank
you
very cool
[Music]
squiggly mustache thank you for the
pinky with permission from mama inna
with tentacled
declare war on kfp excuse me permission
from ina
excuse me
prepare your overworked chickens as we
will not hold back our gentle slaps this
is war ahahaha sits down and enjoins the
karaoke
excuse me
inna
are you here
[Music]
snipping tool
what is the meaning of this
oh she's there
[Music]
oh god my chat is going crazy
don't go to war just yet
strengthen the defense
[Music]
what
she's confused but she got the spirit
[Music]
enough for that song
i'm summoning
her
she
might
sound very sleepy
it's a good way to um
take control
when she's sleepy she doesn't know what
she's doing
summoning the priestess
[Music]
ah incoming call
that
um sounds
white
kikkity
key
[Laughter]
hi
we've gotta talk
okay
you sound so
uh
different like i mean the mic quality is
different it's nice to hear you in a
different way today
i'm on the phone
your phone with this
india i have received the following
message from a person called
squiggly mustache i quote
with permission from mama
inaudible declare war on kfp prepare
your overworked chickens as we will not
hold back our gentle slaps this is war
permission from mama ina i thought we
were having a you know
a company
cooperation and stuff huh what happened
to that um
don't don't worry about them they're uh
they're going on a solo mission solo
mission
we we talk without you during the
holidays just like chill inside our
kotatsu's
you know the clear war or anything
they're just
uh it's just a rogue faction you know
within the company
um but you gave them permission ina
according to this person
okay so
what happened was they were like okay we
can negotiate we can touch your hair or
we can declare war on the kfp
and i was like i've told them i feel
uncomfortable with them trying to touch
my hair so i was like you know what just
go ahead and declare one kfp because
real time
do you realize
how cruel that is because
war brings
a certain amount of dead chickens and
dead taco duchies and them touching your
hair wouldn't kill anyone so you rather
have dead taco dashies and chimpkins
than just solving
yes
hear me out here has any
chicken have been attacked or
been
reported to not to live anymore due to a
takarachi attacking them perhaps not yet
chad is there anyone dead yet
we're currently strengthening our
defenses so that's why maybe no one is
dead yet oh yes i am hurt oh someone
says yes i'm hurt i died oh i'm dead i'm
dead inside i'm dead not quite alive
uh i haven't seen jim
oh god jim where the [\h__\h] is jim
oh god you're still accounting okay
uh accounting stuff you know
no i see a lot of casualties currently
uh
maybe this is what your attention kiara
they're just like they they're like kind
of like the soccer players who like
sometimes like overreact when like
someone taps them they're like oh oh no
my phones are broken now i like that
they just want i just want you to you
know
give them all your attention no no you
know where the real problem is you know
what what's the real problem you made
them think that they have a choice and
control over you to begin with the
giving them the like you should if
anything you need to give them the
illusion of choice but giving them the
control
by saying yeah
i won't let you touch my hair but the
other option that you gave to me i will
let you have that one this is where you
are not quite there yet you know this is
why i am the empress and you are not
you are just just the priesthood i never
wanted to be one
you think you think i
want more work in my life
no thank you and except that is if
because you don't want more work in your
life is exactly the point why you should
become
better at controlling your tacodachis
because if you can control them they can
work for you and take all the work away
from you
oh don't worry i'm sure
um takodachis are just like me they are
sometimes
they're like oh we'll do this but in the
end they'd all know they all know deep
inside they just want to stay inside the
kotatsu and rest for today okay you know
what i'll actually buy that because the
super chat message ends with
uh star sits down and enjoys the karaoke
star so it seems like
they got a little bit ahead of
themselves and then just sat down and
listened to my karaoke
exactly do you understand how much work
and planning and time and effort
like at the end of the day they'll be
like let's go to war but then like when
they realize how much work there is to
do they'll just plug you up maybe just
chilling in the cottages
that is the difference between
tacodachis and kfp when we say we go to
war we do go to war so
i think it's best for the taco duchess
to
just chillax and don't don't frighten us
no more don't threaten us you know
you know my motto is world domination
slowly
oh no
maybe take over the world nobody will
know that it's happening because
everything is just done really slowly
and you don't even realize the change
because you guys take it so slowly at
that point
the world will have already been
destroyed by kfp because we we intend to
make the world go boom
oh it's okay i can probably create stuff
back from the void
yeah you can do that
joint company you know you destroy i
restore
balance as all things are
in the world
guys guys
yes we do yes we do
uh well okay
um anyway then uh for now i would like
to
make sure that our um partnership
agreement is still intact
well yeah of course of course you know
about that that rogue taco i'm sure the
uh clean i mean uh the uh relocation
department will be on their way soon if
they um yeah don't worry about it too
much just just leave from the
uh
uh revocation talk with you crew if you
are hearing this you know what to do
uh it's not the first time it happened
but don't worry about it too much okay
yeah that sounds a little bit a bit but
you do you we must do what we must
control our people work we work pretty
similar yeah i see i see yeah yeah
okay a priestess go back to sleep i'll
see you uh sooner or later
oh thank you very much i'm just gonna
i need to go heat up the
the worm
what's it what
oh the one blanket
oh she disappeared she's she's dead
she's okay
[Laughter]
let's just let's just end it there
mrs priest says ina needs to go back to
sleep okay so it seems like that was an
empty threat
just as i
hoped for and loki expected some part of
me was never scared to begin with
but i cut you off there and you were
just like breathing into that moment
it's okay you know you just go back to
sleep you just go back to sleep
that's that's it
i'm i'm happy to hear that our
contract
is still
uh yes
[Applause]
this is still intact
yes partnership best partnership
eight minus eight is zero enough stop
asking me math questions now
no more
i will ask you instead
gosh this is the last christmas audio
stock song that i have and i haven't
used yet so you guys gotta listen to it
it's a bit too cheerful but
you don't have a choice
merry christmas
merry christmas a cookie here and a
cookie there
and a gingerbread house too
yeah yeah
yeah
merry christmas
merry christmas a present here and a
present there
and a
christmas tree everywhere
how did i just come up with that
[Laughter]
that sounds like a banger
[Music]
don't shift what tone shift we've always
been like this
ld297
[Music]
four seconds thank you to pinkie
oh my god oh my god inaudible
is she okay
[Music]
it's your cake
i don't know where that came from
who's that
[Music]
so are we at war or not apparently not
apparently not we we shouldn't be we
should have never been i don't know what
the hell
squiggly mustache was going on about
uh santa marissa
and counting chicken pancakes in phoenix
2612. thank you for the red super chat
i didn't break her eye
no
could never do such a thing
hi i've been learning on your channel
since your debut i just wanted to thank
you for lifting my spirit through time
hard times and to wish you a merry
christmas and a happy new year same to
you
merry christmas happy holidays happy new
year thank you for
and watching my streams for such a long
time you're welcome to come out of the
lurking
more often if you want to hmm
you're always welcome i know it's for
the lurkers it's a little bit like of a
big step
but
once you
get out of your shell i've heard that
it's a lot of fun for everyone
yeah i didn't break her heart
i didn't break her heart
we love each other dearly yeah
yeah
say thank you phoenix
hoping to have you around for much much
longer
flirt back then i can't i don't know how
to flirt
i don't know how to fly well she sounded
she sounded nice didn't she
skye thank you for the pinky
looks like one rogue member from tenth
occult is trying to declare war and
jeopardize kfp and tackle its precious
piece yes chickens and penguins are
united now enemies surrender
it's okay chill can't be chill too chill
they didn't mean it like that but but
they must understand by now that when
kfp says we're going to war we go to war
for real so
uh
don't
don't you dare threaten us one more time
we're supposed to be on a peace treaty
that's tacos
now we work together
you know takes control over kfp when i'm
not there so
yeah
we must be able to trust one another and
work together
if anything we should go to war together
against someone else
[Music]
thank you
for giving us this magnificent karaoke
thank you mate no thank you no you no
you no yeah
thank you so much for listening
yeah
even though it wasn't a shitty time for
for
many time zones
yeah so thank you for being there
no you no
[Music]
chocolate
thank you
wow thank you very sweet
mud arcade duncan spicy chicken taco
duncan says duncan carefully project
channel
thank you for thank you for the pinky
thank you for the fantastic set of
karaokes it was so unique and so much
fun you're an amazing singer kiana merry
christmas thank you merry christmas to
you too
i'm glad you liked the
song choices i mean obviously it was
kind of limited because it had to be
christmas songs
yeah but
i want to do another vr and karaoke
eventually that's like
a big a bigger variety of all kinds of
songs so please look forward to that jim
tracy thank you for your support
ryan h danke and that's satisfied
papa thank you for the red super chat
thank you
mwah
lovely kiara it's amazing stream love
your singing and move thank you for
giving us the wonderful christmas wait
where where to fight i'm ready no no no
no no fighting no no no no
no
cafe time to rest it's the holiday
season
yeah
well thank you it was fun to be able to
move my hands
yeah that was nice being able to like
clap and
and and to like the oi
movement and a little bit of dancing as
well
now that was my first time that i was
able to do that properly that was really
cool
um
yeah
i'm done with these but i have
accumulated um quite a couple of super
chats in this stream
so let's read those tools
[Music]
and mr
thank you for the pinky
kiana after discovering her life last
christmas
i'll give you my heart
you in particular got me through a very
tough year oh you're a genuine
inspiration to me and i look forward to
supporting you more in this coming year
eternal kfb for an eternal boomer cheers
boss
nice thank you
oh
i like to hear like when you guys
discovered me and how and all that
i wonder i wonder what stream it was
that got you
yeah let's be eternal boomers together
boohoo
but yeah i'm glad i got you for a tough
year i'm sure that there is a lot of
people out here that had a tough year
and i'm always happy to be able to give
you guys a little bit of happiness every
day
it's not it's not much but i try
to help where i can
thank you for letting me entertain you
boo hoo
mot okay thank you bryson williamson
thank you for the rest of the chat
obligatory birthday super chat
bryson
happy birthday
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you happy birthday dear bryson happy
birthday to you
thank you
you should be donating that money to
yourself well thank you for being so
generous and i hope you have a lovely
birthday
eat some cake
let them eat cake let them have cake
let at least bryson have some cake
i hope that my super chat my gorilla
super chat reading
kind of did something
nice on your birthday um spending some
time with me but hopefully hopefully
also love your family or friends yeah
don't get too drunk though
don't get too drunk i guess i shouldn't
say no on your birthday whatever get as
strong as you want but but but but but
don't drive
thank you bryson
[Music]
happy new year happy holidays by the way
let's keep like thank you
foreign
the b is pronounced very strongly in
korean huh piping pop i need to remember
to pronounce it stronger
the g as well
god of amiibo
of london
[Music]
thank you you guys are
you guys are exaggerating about my
hallelujah
yeah
brian rings me duncan eating mike
eating mike
tyson's
let's say
christmas cookies danke shin
brian rings me dancin
no i will not say that no
but haven't seen that
guy in a long time
carefree project channel duncan and
brian ricksby duncan code zero zero
seven lucky duncan
in korean
good try good try
[Music]
thank you for the pinky on behalf of
your filipino fans for your information
appley app is filipino
of course you know him huh does every
every uh filipino know apple the amp
he's pretty cool he got some rap skills
he got those
vibes he got the attitude he's pretty
damn good yeah
it's just a little bit unfortunate that
black eyed peas uh like distribution of
parts was very uneven
most of it was will i am all the time
it was way worse than some songs but
yeah
but god peace yeah
i mean
i hope i hope that
the group was fine with that but
i i wouldn't think that's cool
[Music]
yeah they should they should give
everyone
a good amount of parts
fergus parts were always amazing that is
true yeah she got some good damn parts i
think it's good that they added her uh i
think back then it might have been like
a little bit of like a drama maybe i
wouldn't have noticed
but i can't imagine it being a little
bit of a drama like them adding like
this girl to the group to the super cool
rap group but she
i think she added a really cool element
to the group because that way it wasn't
only rap but they had some nice
um
how to say
musical singing parts in there as well
that gave it a new like i think it gave
them a lot more opportunities and
variety
and it made their songs very catchy
and also
more
like easy to
reach a bigger audience
thank you
and giant firing call once again thank
you for the red super chat hey kid i
wanted to thank you for getting me into
the world of life i was always
interested but you were the one that
made me finally take the plunge hope
your hat hope you have a great day thank
you well we already interviewed in whole
talk
uh so i think that's enough but thank
you once again for the red super chat
mwah
4k
channel
[Music]
foreign
sometimes i forget if it was andre or
andre on drew
wait
it was andre
danke
this is my christmas present for you
i want to thank you for this amazing
year you've given us and my wish for
this new year is to keep on supporting
you you're you're a really a sweet and
funny person and you're someone i really
look up to love your tencho oh love you
too thank you very sweet
you look up to me really i think there's
better people to look up to but thank
you that is very flattering
and thank you for being so generous
thank you soon i hope you have some
lovely holidays spend some quality time
with your family and happy new year to
you stay
healthy and happy
and please continue saying hashtag
young
thank you for the pinky i would just
like to report that i got your tapestry
three hours ago oh
the birthday tapestry and it was
immediately taken hostage by my cat who
is currently using it as a vet let's go
i guess it's hers now happy holidays
oh no
those cats keep on taking over our
things i mean understandable
mind do the thing too
understandable
my birthday stuff also finally arrived
on the 21st all right before christmas
nice
nicer
[Music]
that's very based yeah
very vast indeed
it's getting a good use it should be
it would get a good use if it was on
your wall so quen quenec i hope by now
it's on your wall
now that tapestry is really cool i'm
looking at it right now
yeah it's really cool
it's i think i might have talked about
this during like the birthday
era but i didn't
first i didn't expect something so dark
at all
but
suddenly came at me with this super
dark illustration super badass
it wasn't what i expected at all
it was a pleasant surprise though
i'm already looking forward to
future birthdays to see what hukapapa
will draw
for me
today
thank you for the right super chat no
stream on my birthday this year so
here's my gift to you
a day early i've been away from family
and friends this year but
oh wait so wait your birthday is
tomorrow
but you in case we make everything
brighter thank you so much for
everything and here's to happy new year
yay cheers happy new year let's go
almost
happy early birthday then
i'll sing for you happy early birthday
to you happy early birthday to you happy
early birthday dear gary garza
happy early birthday to you
thank you for supporting me
and thinking of me on your special day
thank you
let's spend your following birthdays
together as well shall we thank you
for
[Music]
okay let's let's let's read this long
rainbow
myoshi will you let me ramble on my
birthday
anytime
oh the horror when i realized you
wouldn't stream on my birthday
i'm sorry but maybe i'll upload
something the sad sparks
so i'm sending it early but i don't have
anything meaningful to say this time i
think you complained about the
pronunciation of my name but i never
told you thank you for finally telling
me that dd is a th sound in welsh ah so
it would be
but wait that so it's double th because
you already have a th in your name and
then dd
so
or is the th pronounced differently if
the dd is the th then what's the then
if you want to just pronounce it as a
single d i don't mind my work keeps
getting in the way of watching full
streams oh man
it is hard to catch up on full length
vlogs so i'm sure i'm missing a lot of
stories and lore but i keep coming every
time i can thank you
i continue to love the energy and effort
you put into streams i continue to
work hard on converting people to watch
you
i've been trying to get my nieces to
watch you as i've been back to visit
families for the past few days are they
into anime or not if they're not
then it's very very um
how to say
brave of you to try to convert them
i appreciate it though nice
advertisement
uh i've been trying to get my nieces to
wonder
as we wind up the year i hope that you
continue to have fun throughout the next
year i still maintain that you are
wholesome and super smart
not many people say that but thank you
that's the end of the rainbow i love you
again i love you too thank you yes yes i
am super smart and am wholesome and i'm
say so you forgot that part but
i forgive
thank you thank you thank you very very
thank you
beautiful rainbow very sweet words thank
you so much
oh
thank you for the support and thank you
for promoting me to your family i
i'm sorry if they maybe
look at you with a weird glance like
what the [\h__\h] do you want from me
get that chicken girl away from me
i'm sorry if it's like that but i do
appreciate the effort
thank you so much
thank you
i wish you only the best
yeah
much love happy holidays
and thank you for all the support hoping
to count on you in 2022 as well
yeah
[Music]
what's this video on the top right oh
uh
it's a video
that i did in collaboration with kanna
uru so if you google not google if you
go on youtube and you type in kana udu
k-a-n-a-u-r-u
[Music]
it's a masterpiece yes it is or just
google uh not google
just type in
kiara
jingle bell rock and then it should come
up
it came out just a few days ago and we
made it
together
i'm really happy with it like i want you
guys to watch it i even put it in my
music
playlist yeah it's a mean girl's
reference
even though i didn't watch mean girls it
won't be it must be our next movie watch
along okay
hey so where was i i think i skipped
some um
oh wait for a gaming i think i
i didn't i only read your name but i
just see now you say it's your birthday
happy birthday to you
i need to file a formal complaint kiara
okay probably not against me right right
right
i think that you turned off those supers
a few minutes too soon
daisy also complained about it
the stream was lovely though and i
enjoyed it a lot that you spent the
first day of christmas with us chickens
mary bellator christmas thank you
it's not like you can't just send
whatever you wanted to spend in the
following stream
come on
thank you though you guys are very very
passionate about sending those super
chats thank you it's not the same
it is the same because i'm reading them
all in one stream
it makes no difference if you send it
during the
vr or during now
because in this case i'm reading them
all together
okay fine okay
thank you thank you to chad
you are very very sweet you know what i
think throughout this year you need to
chat
you have
become
you have evolved into a very very
good chimpkin yeah i remember you being
a bit more naughty back in the day
i i'm not sure if i'm mixing up things
but i remember you being more naughty
i think you've kind of like
uh evolved
maybe it was the times that many times
you went to the usual room
everyone evolves in the usual room
he mellowed out with h
chickens mellow and aged quickly do they
i wasn't in there once are you sure
are you sure i think every chicken was
in the usual room once
but since i like to use
some special methods you might have
forgotten about it huh
not once
you guys just don't remember
i even put you guys in there when you
guys are sleeping sometimes
[Music]
sometimes when you're sleeping
but but
no no no no no let's not tell let's not
i cannot tell you any more about that
oh no no it's just a joke it's drunk
it's strong
funny joke right
no no no i would not do something like
that
it's strong
laugh with me
[Music]
yes
you keep on sleeping in your chicken
coops
yeah
safe and sound
my chickens are always safe and sound
[Laughter]
no wonder my head hurts
couldn't be
couldn't be because of that no no no no
no no
no you're just imagining that
anyway murray related crystal unit chad
i am sorry for taking that away from you
but hey we're still playing christmas
music the office still looks like it's
christmas so it's still christmas snap
related where we are never late at kfp
thank you for your kindness group didn't
dance
oh wait that was the rainbow brazza
thank you duncan for the pinky merry
christmas kiana and kfb today is my
birthday another birthday are you king
me
and it seems like my wish of listening
to some tangents came true yeah thank
you for all the wonderful times this
year and for the divine exquisite kiada
okay yesterday as well you are welcome
thank you
thank you very much
and happy
birthday
oh my
god oh my god
never burped i'm so happy to see that
you guys want to spend some time with me
on your birthday
surprises me every time
thank you it makes me feel special you
make me feel special
[Music]
that's what you do
you make me feel special
[Music]
i feel so
feel so special
you make everything right
that's what you do i owe it to you
[\h__\h] love twice
yeah
[Music]
thank you brother sorry my brain is
getting slower oh my god and my brain is
getting slower i need to finish this
super chats
like richard narkishan
key mph kitchen thank you
deborah thank you
dabron thank you for the pinky this is
my second account by the way i went to a
christmas market and took uh pictures as
i said i would oh are you gonna did you
send them to my twitter
[Music]
please do please do
i hope you had fun there christmas
market's always so nice i wish they
would go on longer
hmm we were already
robbed of more time uh at christmas
markets because we had a lockdown so
um
you missed the 312
oh
oh i thought that red was the was the
last one oh i did i'm so sorry i'm so
sorry i did i did i did
let me read that now then
grove didn't
to fit with last year's super chat this
finishes up the birthday bonus the same
as last year
i tried to support others but you're my
one and only aussie and empress fits to
stand beside idle guard oh
you probably told me about your love for
innogarde before and i forgot but oh
i'll send a message from my other
members member accounts as well
oh that run is oh you have the same
picture i see now that's your other
account why are you doing that because
you ran like like you couldn't uh that
was your maximum
girlfriend then it's too much
it's too much
oh my god
uh
by the way thank you for singing more
micro macro songs when i asked you're
welcome they have so many amazing songs
yeah they have really really great songs
i want to sing more
i especially love um
the delta songs but all the ones as well
of course i should learn more
cheryl songs
i need to
but never have the time
[Music]
i want to learn more cheryl songs
i'm getting tired oh man thank you thank
you good thing you are way too generous
i'll continue calling you girlfriend
maybe for a while
there was this one super cute rankari
song what was it again
um
let me see
which one am i thinking of
oh i like what about my star too what
about my style
and i will i love imo
[Music]
i love all these songs man but that's
still not the one i'm thinking of
what what am i thinking mom
oh but i are getting tired hope you're
still able to hang on yes yes yes
yes i must
[Music]
okay i know that's so random but i like
it
that might not have been the one that i
was thinking of either i was low-key
thinking of that
uh
probably was that one
it's so stupid
[Music]
i think i was listening to like like a
remix or something of that
like a long remix version i need to find
that again
i think it was like kind of like
eurobeat
let me find it
uh remix
oh my god dance remix oh my god oh my
god
oh was it this one 2009
it sounds like it
already yeah
i listened to this one for hours
[Music]
i don't know why
i listened to this for so long
kononi
oh
this is so old this is
how many years
12 years ago almost 14 years ago
holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
i am old boomer phoenix
okay back to
super chat
nostalgic vibes everywhere
[Music]
when we thank you for the pinky this is
yet
wait
all these people were you
why do you have so many accounts
this is yet another account and it isn't
friday yet but my egg was broken even if
my heart wasn't gifted in oh my god
you are like you're like that you're
you're using the the double double
thingy
skill
uh
[Music]
are you everyone in the chat is everyone
get gifted in
who do i who can i trust who's the real
one
who is the real one
[Music]
shadow clone
oh my god
yes
i'm real now
no no oh god
oh god
i'm gone
[Laughter]
oh [\h__\h]
yep so i only have one fan
i only have one fan
what the [\h__\h]
the biggest [\h__\h] bamboozle of 2021
[\h__\h] this year i'm out
ah
love muffins lungish and squiggly
mustache
[Music]
oh we're almost there
is what i thought
looking for the
top ration mustang
merry christmas canada thanks for all
the hard work you do i might sound silly
it might sound silly but you really are
making the world a brighter place for
many many people
looking forward to another great year of
kiana streams
yeah
i wonder what we'll be doing together in
the following year
i wonder
i hope we can have a 3d debut
and some more original songs
and more outfits
and many more games
thank you tanaka
looking forward to having you around and
i just realized your name has carefree
workers union at the end did it always
have that there oh my god did we always
have a union here
tanaka
you
get a free ticket to the usual room
right now go go go go go
go go go
until
i don't see the word union anymore at
the end of your name you could even
change it to workers onion and i would
be happy
don't want to see no yummy in here
get out of here
get out of here tanaka
hey
[Music]
it's been so long since i've been super
chatting here i've missed you and i want
to tell you how much i love you thanks
for all the happiness you give me genma
[Music]
unless you little [\h__\h] go go back to
where you came from
um
oh my god
[Music]
um no i can't give you a kiss for that
no no
no
[Laughter]
ah
no
can genma give him a kiss for him
that's probably what he wanted
[Music]
the shortest war i've been a part of
have you been part of longer wars
mrs duncan eric newswa thank you for the
right super chat thank you for this year
kiara as this is the last stream i will
be able to catch this year oh where are
you going
hope to see you throughout 2022 on an
unrelated note if you had to choose a
genre of a scuffed game what would it be
what
wait what does that mean
i mean if i could choose a scuffed
game
out of any
genre like
rpg or fps or so
but like a bad one
uh i would
i would choose
the kfb kfc dating sim game
because i wanted to play it since my
debut
and i still haven't gotten to do it
for [\h__\h] sake
but i guess i don't need it because
i've been getting oh my god
yeah that reminds me
i've been getting a lot of uh kiara
external fan art now
um
not surprising but
you know
[Music]
when my family was over for christmas
my sister
uh before we went to dinner
they were there was a time when they
were chilling in my living room
and my sister
and she was chilling on my on my sofa
and she was
using her phone and my sister uses
reddit she's on the main red page a lot
she's seen my stuff there before a lot
and then she's like
of course
the moment i'm here looking at reddit
while being in your apartment kiana what
i find on the top page of reddit is you
and i'm like if what'd you find
i look over and she shows me
not from p gate but she shows me an
image of
me
being very close with the colonel
um
yeah
don't worry my sister wasn't that
like
she she didn't even seem like
impressed or anything
like that it wasn't even apparently that
weird to her which means she must have
seen weirdest [\h__\h] already
yeah yeah
did she uploaded i don't think she did
yeah if i remember correctly my my
sister once told me and i told you guys
something too um she
knew like she saw kiara before i even
told her about what i was doing before
uh that because she
looks like every day on reddit and she
already saw like a whole live being up
there on the reddit um
top page or whatever it was called again
i forgot my words are disappearing
yeah yeah but without being aware yet
what she was looking at
was her sister
the front page front page yeah that was
what i meant
funny thank you eric
i can't do this much longer
wakey tunes downloading for the pinky
due to worldly events i haven't seen my
family in two years oh man
but i made it to all your christmas
dreams live and they completely filled
the holiday void i've been missing thank
you for being the christmas miracle to
myself and manny you're wonderful thank
you
yeah
[Music]
okay um i think i just drank a cat hair
um yeah my arms are getting tired
ah
thank you wiki tunes yeah that is not
very cool
not being able to see your family at all
in two years oh man
they must be living in a different
country i assume maybe even in a
different continent um
that's very sad but
i i hope that you'll get to see them
in the not too far distance um
uh future i can't i think
and
thank you i wish you
wonderful holidays
take care of yourself wikitunes
thank you so much for your support i'm
glad i could bring you some happiness
thank you for watching all of my streams
thank you
you're wonderful too
remember that
typhoon thank you nagal thank you for
the pinky
merry christmas and happy holidays
canada does undead count as a work
casualty
no i guess not also i got my merchandise
well the slippers are like one-third of
my feet though ah
yeah
you know when i made slippers when i
decided to make slippers for my
merchandise
i i figured that it wouldn't fit
everyone but i was hoping it would be at
least a bit bigger
but i guess they went kind of with like
a standard japanese um
unisex size
rather than
like a bigger one for like overseas
that is really unfortunate man i want to
do more stuff like that like more
merchandise like that that that
people can wear like like shirts and and
and and slippers or even shoes but that
is unfortunately shoes are like so
impossible because of
all the sizes unfortunately
yeah
[Music]
but at least they're nice to look at
right and nice to squeeze
maybe aprons ahaha you must have you
must be new here one of my birthday
merchandise was an apron
an apron and a slipper
at least the apron is wearable by pretty
much everyone
yeah
yeah it must be new here
uh
what about hats yeah yeah yeah hats hats
could work yeah yeah yeah
although i don't know well yeah i guess
so
maybe in the future
yeah
well you know what would be cool too you
know how we um release
like a like a popular merchandise item
is just like a normal like a badge right
like the round badges
and
how about
instead of the boring round ones with an
image inside how about instead of that
having a badge like that but in the
shape uh of of my shields that i have on
my on my boobs
you know what i mean
that shield as a badge
but like in the proper shape and like
high quality and not only being flat and
2d
but like actually like a proper one like
a like a replica kind of like that
that would be cool yeah
yeah you guys are green
okay
okay sky donkeys
[Music]
complaint department no no no black
friction
for the pinky
oh god another complaint
excuse me i would like to complain about
your complaints
no wait let's hear let's hear black
friction out first
i was about to pull my heart out into a
super chat but then you turned it off
but now i don't remember what i was
going to say you should have copy pasted
it not baffled
bad can live
i'll go to the usual room now princess
carry me there this time
why no why wouldn't princess carry you
there by the way my sister she's like
kind of smaller than me even though she
doesn't want to admit it but she tried
to princess karen me
several times
in during christmas and and she was
actually able to do it
speaking of princess carrie
she's older than me but she's a little a
tiny bit smaller than me
she kept on picking me up
and i was like what the [\h__\h]
only by like one or two centimeters down
um
are you not heavy what do you mean
well
like what could
even even if i was heavy
that doesn't stop people from lifting
heavy things
what a question
are you not heavy
what do you mean are you heavy
are you not heavy too heavy for someone
to pick you up i mean
oh my god
no i'm not too heavy
well thank you black friction
please let me know once you remember
what you wanted to say please tell me i
am curious
what kind of love confession is gonna be
this time
thank you wait that wasn't even a red
one was it
it wasn't but i still gave you kisses
[Music]
thank you for the words
these past few months i couldn't watch
many streams i moved back to my home
country looked for a new job oh but i'm
happy to report that i'm back to normal
love you and wish you an okay of peace a
lovely 2022
i now work with a framework named
phoenix what the hell
what is that what company is that
you mean kfp right
you you're a little bit confused but you
got the spirit i think you're trying to
say that you work for kfp now
obviously
thank you very much
stop stop attending i will read no more
no more
thank you
and yeah i'm glad it's back to normal is
it's nice to find back into a proper
life rhythm isn't it
it's it's it is indeed nice thank you
thank you for your support i wish you
also a lovely 2022 a successful year
a healthier
and a happy hair
thank you for
your love and support
and
a case for you and now i say goodbye to
you guys
because i gotta do stuff
no stop it senior mcd stop it
thank you
thank you but stop it no no no reading
no more i'm reading no more no no no
okay i'll be uploading this on twitter
and i gotta do a lot of things so thank
you enough for the same thanksgiving
enjoying myself
i love you guys thank you thank you i
gotta do some things
thank you for the support
what's nice talking to you guys see you
on wednesday
or no in the
rebroadcast if you want to be there in 2
hours and 15 minutes reservation is
already up
bye bye
thank you everybody
[Music]
bye bye thank you everybody
have a lovely evening
[Music]
you