questions
[Music]
assistant
questions
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
again
thank you
[Music]
hello everyone good evening
how's it going guys
[Music]
I am a little bit nervous
uh I don't know why
so
uh
[Music]
um
so I I don't speak Korean which I think
means but
[Music]
I know a few words a few basically
so we'll try to build on that the few
basic words that I do know are anyohasia
um
[Music]
and I think it's baby
ayegi I don't know could be wrong
so a few words like those I picked up
before because I was watching uh I told
you guys this before I was watching this
show I was like really really into this
this Korean show uh
what was it called Superman
uh the return the Return of Superman
the The Return of Superman what was the
Korean title for that
super what's it called
Superman
something like that something like that
you know what I mean you know what I
mean what's so what's up what's that
Korean pronunciation for that name for
that show I don't know
um as I was watching that yes you know
you know okay okay I was watching that
so much
cause I don't know
if it's so cute
[Music]
is that is that does that mean baby is
cute I think yes
Superman
yeah it sounds like it's not like
Japanese to me
[Music]
that was just this girl that was like
half German yeah there was this this
German wife of a Korean uh I think
soccer player I think and they were both
super handsome and they had this cute
baby uh who was speaking uh German a
little bit and and also uh Korean
obviously uh and then there was this
other family well where with the with a
Korean guy who had a Japanese wife and
they had also the cutest girl ever
foreign
[Music]
ly but there was a time where I was
watching it for weeks months every day
so I picked up a few Korean words
because of that
[Music]
I also
um I listened to a little bit of Korean
music but only girl groups because they
are cute
um let's see can I think up some of the
top of my head like uh
uh
did
twice like you probably don't pronounce
it exit I think mamamoo
um
[Music]
red velvet yes
I love her she is so gorgeous she sings
so well I love her ah black pink and uh
Girls Generation not so much yeah
yeah yeah
very good very good
foreign
yeah I I I I like a bunch of those
um
now I cannot i i a lot of the groups
that I sometimes listen to probably now
I forgot about them
even though I like them
see yeah hell yeah let's go need to you
well that's kind of like a J-pop group
but I know they're produced by like a
K-pop producer and yeah yeah yeah so
they kind of have that K-pop vibe to it
it's so such a great group man ah
[Music]
I have I have a little bit of uh an
interest and Nikki who that's something
else
everglow I've heard of them I've heard
like one one song from them I think
Tiana
wait was there a group that
that's yeah I think I've heard of that
group too isn't that like pretty old
group
[Music]
yeah no it's more Korean I love me
really
yeah I've heard that uh Korean Villas
have been calling me kimara
[Music]
which makes no sense because they call
me that because apparently my Korean is
good but it's not that we could you say
star oh yes sister oh I love them
yeah they they say my I think my
pronunciation is good but I don't know
many words and so on so I don't know if
I deserve to be called that but for you
guys for my Korean viewers I I have the
chicken today the turkey don't don't
tell my viewer says chicken is turkey I
mean officially it's turkey we never we
will never know until we bite into it
yes but look look this is for you this
is for you Korean Bros you can have a
bite here
unfortunately I did not have time to
practice the alphabet beforehand so
that's basically what we have to get
started with uh yeah
let's go wait my music is too loud I
think is it
the website was too quiet that's for
sure wait a second
can I make it louder yeah
say that again ah wait
down down down maybe a bit louder there
you go
ah this is the maximum that we can go so
let me turn down my music a bit
a tiny bit
okay is that ah is that oh yeah it
should be loud enough hell yeah it's in
the orange area okay
[Music]
okay
that actually does look a little bit
like the a letter I can I can try to
connect that with the Ayla I mean not
like this A letter because this one has
a different uh font but okay I'll try to
remember that ah
oh God thankfully Korean doesn't have so
many akura
Korean doesn't have so many letters so
oh there's a circle with a stick and
another stick on the right side
yes I mean that was not that difficult
for me to get I don't think I deserve a
nice job for that oh
this all or this all oh maybe that's all
it's a stick on the ground with a stick
going up and an all
and uh let's say it looks like the
profile the the like a passport picture
of me
these are the shoulders this is the neck
and this is the head okay that's all oh
[Music]
excellent no don't don't praise me like
that I didn't do anything
[Music]
what oh
wait that's not ah because it's
connected I was not connected so I guess
it's this one
huh
[Music]
it doesn't really sound like ill ill ill
ah but I guess that's it
oh
[Music]
okay that one is the the pro the
passport picture turned around to the
side okay
uh match the pears ah oh dear okay this
is uh because it's not connected this is
all because it's the password picture
and Ale is the password turned around
continue
hi bro thank you thank you thank you
thank you shut up I'm the better boob
here and
[Music]
oh oh
wait I already forgot wait no I didn't
forget it's the password picture now oh
passport yes yes yes oh it even talks to
me yeah
[Music]
Master pairs oh dear okay and uh okay ah
easy easy okay okay step by step step
and a step down
[Music]
and by the way for me to you I'm a big
fan of Nina
[Music]
yeah yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
one day streak nice yes I have just
started let's see how long I can
continue what a gift with this one's
times three freeze you can miss one day
yeah I don't care I I don't need that
right now review my lesson beautiful
thank you can I I don't want to equip it
okay okay let's learn more of the
alphabet
listen
is that the same lesson is that a new
lesson e e
it's it looks like the ah but without
the stick oh remember that why are they
so similar they look so similar oh
e e
looks like ah without the stick on the
side
oh
that looks like that looks like the
password picture but a little bit
um more of the body is shown because it
continues
on downloads okay what oh okay oh the
longer the longer pass my Pikachu
[Music]
continue e
wait
wait a second we learned e and ooh right
yes okay and this was ooh
ah short time memory let's go what
[Music]
what are you saying
I can only guess it must be this because
it's not e
it's probably also not all
okay is
the head with no neck but with shoulders
oh dear oh dear
or isn't that also the e but turned
around
because it looks like the a without the
stick but turned around
they look so similar it ill if
what
it means something
[Music]
okay so just like in Japanese language
like kanji the alphabet also has
meanings like like they mean a word as
well
I thought Oh I thought they only had
like if I thought it was only like like
the letters
okay
so oh I
I got it oh
I must be one of the new ones
so
um
they all look the same
[Music]
[Applause]
is it this one the one with the long
passbook picture but no neck
oh god oh they all look the same
[Music]
oh
okay I cheated a little bit because I
listened but but my first idea was
correct I think
hi
[Music]
means child
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
shut up shut up shut up
okay it means just child means child
oh and I ayegi means baby right so like
how I said before
match the Paris oh God okay this is ah
[Music]
[Applause]
I forgot all the others
oh
this is
[Music]
why do they look so similar
ly
I'll cheat a little bit
[Music]
uh
ah
I should write it down one second let me
write those down once again
[Music]
it's just perfect uh perfectly prepared
and next to me I have this like like
like study
um word note thingy
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
I have a pen I have an apple apple pen
okay so ah which one was ah uh this one
ah then uh oh which one was oh
this one this one was ooh
help me chat
this one without the neck right okay
oh
which one was e
[Music]
h
why you type the t-pose wait which one
is e
ah the side head with no neck
e which one is that
oh
I'm cheating you guys are on my teacher
now
[Music]
is uh
they always
the one with the neck but sideboards
okay
foreign
which one is left over
this one this one is this is this yeah
okay easy okay let's go
tonight the characters for it oh
[Music]
okay easy now with my cheating sheets
this is easy okay so I know this is uh
um
[Music]
this one
and
um
and oh wait I forgot to write down oh oh
why do I need to write all down what
what's oh who is uh wait wait don't tell
me don't tell me first of all wait who
must be this one the password back to
the password picture is oh
the one with the neck looking to the
front with shoulders is all
right
yeah yeah yeah okay okay okay okay okay
oh and then e is the sidewards head with
no neck but shoulders
I it's very complicated uh-huh you won't
attack me again child only child
and Donna
okay continue
yeah yeah
[Music]
let me write that down on my Note
immediately
oh my God what happened with this
human's body it's turned around and it
has two bodies sticking out of its
shoulders or actually you know what you
could say that's just like one body yeah
okay so sidewards head sidewards
shoulders and a thick body
means yeah
[Music]
okay
the thing turned back
oh yeah this is like brain explosion oh
my God okay
is a what you you
yeah
this is you this is you guys it looks
like you just with no neck where did you
leave your neck guys
you need something to carry your head
select the collect correct characters
for yeah yeah it's um this one yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
I guess you
so this is uh
password picture with a really thick
neck and shoulders
[Music]
let me write it down fake neck shoulders
is probably you'll
wait I forgot the other
damn it oh we got we'll get back to that
okay yo
continue what sound does this make yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
maybe this one
I would say this one because it doesn't
sound like you or you
oh
let me write it down
fake neck sideboards is yeah oh but it
sounds like yeah
thank you thank you for throwing things
at me that I've never seen before and
expecting me to already know them it's
okay
you must be uh this one you oh
nice we're making crackers yeah
what
child milk
this is a
this is a little bit confusing but okay
milk huhio oil
wait a second this is all
and this is you oh you or you or you
will you
real
will you use milk
Cali
[Laughter]
Kelly give me milk
that's all I needed that's all I needed
from these lessons
[Music]
match the pears okay
let's start with you it's a sidewards
head with a figure
and uh yo is a fake neck downward yo
what are these descriptions man
um
this one is you you and uh
I'm just cheating right now but I'll
I'll remember it eventually then I can
finally read your Super Chat names guys
finally
uh well this one we learned in the
beginning it should be easy
wait this one is
yeah yeah
I will
what
hi
[Music]
wait a second ah
wait isn't it both well yeah this is ah
e and then this is uh
oh no not oh this is
foreign
[Music]
and oh
yo yo
[Music]
yeah baby milk a child milk chocolate
milk
is it saying child milk
[Music]
child wants milk don't misunderstand
child
wants milk child Ahi
foreign
I wanna learn more
but we first have to learn this alphabet
we can't do anything about it right now
Master pairs
[Music]
I don't remember there's so many odd
ones yeah
um this one yeah
[Music]
York
you you
will cheat a little bit to make it
faster
red Super Chat thank you I'll read the
Super Chat in the Super Chat reading
yeah yeah
[Music]
it doesn't really sound like it's
written which makes it a bit difficult
okay one more yo yo is fake neck you
[Music]
you you
you yeah yeah uh this one yeah yeah
yeah it's German it's German we're
learning learning German here yeah nine
we get this year
yeah yeah nine yeah
okay alphabet more alphabet Oh dear
there's more oh there well now now
you're now you want to confuse me oh God
okay
[Music]
um
how to describe this
this is a
this is also a face I know what this is
a Ninja Turtle face because if you look
at it this way
then the the oh is the circle is the
mouth
and then there's others he has this this
towel around his eyes with holes for his
eyes do you see what I see
do you see what I see
if you look at it like this
again he has like a an eye eye patch
like wrapped around his head and it's
the eyes and he goes like oh
yeah I gotta be creative here so Ninja
Turtles sideways sideways Ninja Turtle
is yeah yeah
[Music]
baby okay yeah
oh my God so this ninja turtle
um is sick of the the bandana thingy uh
because it hurts his eyes so he put it
on his forehead and now his eyes are
closer to his mouth
I only see faces right now
okay usual he's surprised by how freeing
that feeling is when he takes off his
bandana yeah yeah
that's the sound he makes he's like yeah
yeah
[Music]
Ninja Turtle let's go
uh yeah yeah is when he still has it on
oh my God this is actually this actually
helps me yeah is when he still has it on
and then and what
oh God he lost an eye oh God
oh my God he lost an eye
I feel so sorry for this Ninja Turtle
oh God
[Music]
well tough life man that's what happens
I am studying Korean
for you
Mama
[Music]
um
I am just trying to to use the the
Korean the Korean that I've just learned
I'm being a good student I want to
immediately use the Korean ah this is
and you are now a moderator on my
channel
hey
where where is my oil
where is
[Music]
Junior
okay what
yeah that's the Ninja Turtle who lost
his eye we're getting really creative
here
[Music]
he lost his eye but he still uses his
um
his bandana okay now actually His Eye Is
centered so he he's like uh what do you
call those those
things with one centered Eye Center no
wait what was it what's that called
Cyclops yeah what the hell am I talking
about so this is a cyclops
collapse riddle
I can't
I'm just trying to somehow find a
connection and connect it in my brain
yeah yeah is when he gets puts down the
bandana and he's like whoa this feels
good yeah yeah yeah yeah okay okay
yeah yeah oh yes yes yes yes yes
yes yes yes
Master pet okay okay easy easy uh we
start with this one which is yeah yeah
and then he puts it down which is yeah
yeah and then he loses an eye yeah he he
has it still down ah this is basically a
lesson that he should have never taken
off the bandana in the first place
because it protected his eyes and he
took it off so he lost an eye so then
we're at a
it the I being y because the Y
disappeared now it's only a you know
what I mean
[Music]
so he's like okay well now I guess
I better put on the bandana again so
that I don't lose my second eye
[Music]
this is how you build bridges in your
brain yeah yeah when you study what yay
yes yes yes
yeah yeah it's all the same
just you could have just asked me for
one of them yeah yeah yeah yeah
or is it
yeah yeah yeah or is it could it be
could it be yeah yeah yeah yeah which
one is it
what are you trying to tell me
[Music]
really it couldn't just have been one
word
yes yes yes yes oh my God Duolingo
you're killing me here
okay okay easy we start the story again
uh Ninja Turtle with a bandana is uh uh
yeah yeah then he takes off his bandana
it's here yeah then he loses an eye and
it's in
no no not this one
this one then he puts the bandana back
on and it's out here
and then
oh
God thank you vital fighting
so like the character I just put it uh
that's after that's after he loses one
eye but doesn't put the bandana back on
I think no wait no actually no I don't
have to try wait it
is uh this one yeah he loses the eye
doesn't put the bandana back on okay I'm
making it more complicated and it needs
to be
hahaha so like the chord graders were
out here
when he has one eye and puts the bandana
back on yeah perfect
[Music]
oh my God we're almost done with that oh
but the alphabet lessons go on for so
long man
[Music]
let me write that down that is beautiful
it's uh and it makes yeah this is Ina
this is a wall she's covered on in you
and she's like wow baby hey
what are you doing here
this is against the wall saying bye
[Laughter]
you just need to see it through my eyes
guys it will make it so much easier I
oh what whoa
okay blah
I guess it's
War because we already had one hmm
must be warm
so this is
this is Ina
[Music]
um
at the supermarket
[Music]
um I guess uh this is uh no no she's at
an ATM this is an ATM
and she's uh she's Korean money is one
right so she's at the ATM asking for
whoa
um
but nothing's coming out hence the wall
[Music]
this is an ATM
wow it must be tough to live with such a
big brain sometimes I I it is it it is
it is quite tough sometimes
whatever you say yeah
oh funny
uh
uh this one
I like how she says it's like longer
like me
[Music]
uh
I I don't really know what to say to
this one
um
it's uh
[Music]
um
her neck is gone yeah
um we mama
mama has
[Music]
no neck therefore her cupboard fails or
whatever I don't know anyone
[Music]
trying to retrieve her
long neck I don't know where where yeah
good question
isn't well like a question
in Korean with where
where we mama got her neck back so now
she can actually covered on this is
getting ridiculous this is getting
really ridiculous uh it's wine
that does not sound like that okay okay
[Music]
boys ATM we're trying to get one
okay this one I think is a good good
bridge that I created
friendship and raincoat is the same word
oh
wait a second let me look that one up
because I want to see uh
oh no wait which one is that
that's an ooh and uh
and uh
[Music]
but it sounds like
okay okay okay
let me write that down
somewhere later on here uh
uh this one and this one
is uh
not a practical word it's
um
friendship
and raincoat really
[Music]
I have to trust the Green Owl
correct pronounces did you pronounce it
incorrectly
[Music]
nobody uses it oh
okay okay no problem
match the pairs let's go okay
um the Ninja Turtle story was really
really good this one is a bit more
difficult so the one is
on this one and then wool is the ATM wow
and this is we who lost her neck B and
this is all air
where and this is yeah yeah okay okay
is that this one B yeah
Master pairs okay let's go we got the
Ninja Turtle mixed in
um this is the Ninja Ninja Turtle after
taking off the bandana so it's here yeah
[Music]
and this is
wow and this is only way okay
okay hey not bad I didn't even look at
my notes okay so like the color
characters
[Music]
this is wall
this is VA so this is
[Music]
hey I'm learning learning
what sound does this make
this is a new one
this is a new one no it's not this is
you almost got me there I wanted to say
where but it's not it's
okay
[Music]
uh oh dear oh God this is this is Ina
meeting the one-eyed Ninja Turtles
and she's she wanted to say why but she
was so shocked because he only had one
eye so she was like what
[Music]
okay I can make up
full on story books Let's Go
[Music]
me
what
me we
um
this is me going to a second hand shop
trying to buy a Nintendo Wii
foreign
wait a second I need to write it down
[Music]
next page okay uh bye okay that's Ina
meeting the one-eyed Ninja Turtle I'm
going like what what
[Music]
by the way this is UE
this is me buying a Wii so it's we
and this is the one-eyed Ninja Turtle so
that's uh after putting back on the
bandana so I think it's I I think we
yeah okay wow I can actually remember
this tomorrow I'll have forgotten them
eh
wait this is new this is new this is new
where I guess this one
[Music]
um so that's
that's oh my God so this is Ina after
meeting the Ninja Turtle first being
surprised because of the one eye but
then being like don't worry you're
beautiful even with one eye so she takes
off his bandana
so that he feels better about his own
face
which doesn't really lead me to where
in any way but it's okay
at least we have a story that's
important
[Music]
oh wait wrong language we we we we we
means above on the buff stomach
both above I need to write that down
uh
so wait that was me going to buy a Wii
we means above
and stomach as well
and on okay okay okay okay
I actually you know I I just wanted to
learn uh the the letter so that I can
read the super chats from Korean viewers
uh properly like the names that was the
original motivation behind it I didn't
really plan on taking it too seriously
but now I'm writing down everything in
like a in like a studying memo thingy
um so I don't know maybe I will be
taking it seriously
I didn't plan on it originally but I'm
having fun so maybe I'll try to get on a
on a decent level hmm
master pass okay okay bye bye
um is the one where Ina meets the
one-eyed Ninja Turtle
we is me buying uh a Wii V
um
and then
uh this one
this one is uh where
uh yeah yeah this is Ina telling the
Ninja Turtle he's beautiful even with
one eye
[Music]
okay I don't know after putting back on
his bandana and this is yeah oh my God
hahaha
[Music]
oh man so like the car guys well we we
is easy we because for some reason that
was really easy for me to remember was
that Lee Story okay let's go Master
pairs okay we is um this one we and this
is
[Music]
um
is this weird
where yes this is yeah and this is all
okay okay
where uh where where we just had it we
just had it where is when she takes off
the bandana where
[Laughter]
and this is we and this is
[Music]
um
yeah this is yeah and this is
why I think
I didn't even have to guess those but I
did let's go
perfect thank you
[Music]
nice we finished alphabet one we can go
to alphabet two now
how many more letters do I need to learn
how many did we learn
you learn all of them
I don't think so probably not yet I want
to finish the alphabet let's go
and then I can practice by reading the
Korean super chats
what da
oh dear there's way more huh
um
[Music]
I need to think of something to remember
this
it doesn't really look like anything it
looks like an ear
on someone's face this is ear this is
the face
uh well okay let's go with that
adjust that one is D really
[Music]
da
Ka okay
[Music]
um
I I can't think of any more stories man
this is the ear turn oh this is a the
human losing his ear and listening to An
Elf's ear trying to trying to get an elf
ear
[Music]
I don't know
Ina's ear oh
you pronounce this uh this one
I don't know the others yet oh God I
will learn those as well uh-huh
[Music]
snake
this is a snake sneaking up to my face
Lee
this is a snake
who has eaten my head and sits on top of
my shoulders
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay it's like the character cards for
Odie okay Lee is a snake
sneaking up to me
oh dear she's I should have seen it
coming I should have only seen it coming
I don't need to write this down this is
uh let me rip that out and
[Music]
this is the snake now
um changing its form trying to recreate
my body so that people will not notice
that the snake has overtaken my body
no questions please no
oh oh what this um
no no this is the snake realizing that
it ain't happening well like you can't
try to become human
it's not possible you are a snake and
you will will always be a snake no no
snake no bad thing
[Music]
is uh the snake um capturing me
and this is the snake uh coming up to me
so this is this must be
yeah okay okay
okay
so g e is
[Music]
um we're going a little bit back on the
story this is this is me eyeing uh oh no
no
no this is the one eye oh my God we're
back in the story this is the one-eyed
uh Ninja Turtle falling in love with Ina
and now Whispering uh flirty words into
Ina's ear
laughs
and she's like okay
[Music]
thank you
I don't know what you're saying it
doesn't sound like any what these look
like no
no
this is to pronounce it
[Music]
foreign
okay
this is like Ina's love story
oh man okay
um this is uh this is uh this is uh
someone sitting in a ramen restaurant uh
here
this is the seat this is the counter yes
yes nail is a ramen restaurant okay now
no I don't know why you pronounce it
like that though okay
[Music]
um
the snake trying to recreate the human
body
[Music]
uh no no no no no no ah this is the
snake realizing no I can't do it I'm I'm
always gonna be a snake yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah okay
[Music]
I am a genius
okay uh so that the characters will get
kick kick kit this is uh this is a ninja
turtle
um Whispering sexy words into Ina's ear
and she's like okay
[Music]
then ah this is the ramen restaurant no
yeah
okay
[Music]
who's getting more and more complicated
well this only looks like the Japanese
kanji for hito to me
for human what
[Music]
some
time
[Music]
a person behind the door I like that
yeah I can connect that with uh with the
human country yeah person behind a door
thing like knock knock
okay thank you for that help chat me
what me me
b b b b is it me
a person comes closer and I really
realize oh that's me
okay yeah that's that's that's a good
that's a good connection okay so sa is
the person behind the door
and then cool
oh
[Music]
this is this is a wine glass
um yeah this is this is Cali's wine
glass
foreign
oh dear oh what happened with this
I cannot explain this one we will have
to
um just go with the flow and remember it
just like that okay I wrote it down
[Music]
with me Ah that's me
oh this is
ordering something again
oh dear
this is me at the ramen restaurant
saying we're at the ATM and being like
more money more more give me more ATM
more more
human
at the ATM okay
means what really
[Music]
this is uh
this is something this is quite
something I cannot tell you what it is I
don't know what to think of this one
this is the one I uh Ninja Turtle doing
something but I don't know why
I don't know what
Che
okay continue
[Music]
this looks like a Japanese kanji
this looks like
um
this looks uh which one was it
a Japanese kanji
yeah that one
okay next page and this is uh this is
OTA this is Japanese tea being served
what's up
[Music]
foreign
it's the cat being scared of the Ninja
Turtle
[Music]
is the question right the question what
um
is me at the ATM saying give me more
more and more just like twice things
and then JJ is uh something that I have
no idea how to explain
[Music]
um
the tea good
oh my God and Chad is the cat being
scared of the Ninja Turtle
this one
[Music]
oh my God it's getting more and more
complicated oh dear this is uh this is a
Japanese kanji for Wolf and now kanji
but Katakana
[Music]
I am I am lost I have no more ideas for
this so Ninja Turtle looking at a
Japanese looking at a cute Japanese elf
anime girl and like being like yeah it's
okay oh no no peeping no I said it's a
Ninja Turtle peeping secretly and an elf
girl in an Onsen and the girl notices it
and she's like yeah
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
what
[Music]
okay this is um something
this is
this is this is this is um
bunny ears jail
pecona behind me behind bars and and
bunnies make peon noises
yes yes yes yes yes
[Music]
makes sense right I would say so okay
this is not connected okay
[Music]
oh God how many signs
why is this not enough
fun fun
wait a second I just realized
if you have a ton oh my oh my God
that's right you have taught a ton wait
but wait a second someone wrote in the
chat that like these are combinations
why are they not just teaching me the
basic ones and then tell me how to
combine them
because this seems to be a combination I
guess that this one this one at the top
is tea
and this is o n or something like that
because it's still angle yeah
ah
[Music]
so so this one is made up by what by
which two letters
or is it free is it free letters
ah this one is the T
oh why do you not teach me that first is
to teaching it backwards
[Music]
oh my God
t-o-n it's free letters saying
I just realized okay so how many letters
do you have in Korean and we say a ton
this was just me naturally reacting to
it but okay no cat
a ton okay
oh my God okay
[Music]
wait so
yeah
wait a second let me go back to the
Ninja Turtle
wait no no no no no it's not no yeah
yeah yeah
so I guess this is pee oh
I had to realize that on my own
doing with you guys Duolingo did not
teach me that oh so
God
this is the Ninja Turtle that was that
still has a bandana in both eyes which
was yeah yeah yeah
and then oh my God this is the P why not
just tell me what p is why
okay I write it down I'll write it down
I'll write it down
yeah here
okay it's a word you don't use oh really
we don't even use that really
oh come on
come on
was the bunny behind bars
two
this one
it's a huh
um I'm guessing this was yo what's that
you wait a second let me go back in my
notes
do I find a you yes
uh the no I mean wait a second
this one is not used either this is used
really why
chill t t plus yo this doesn't exactly I
mean I guess it's without the without
the head the head is replaced by the T
oh
[Music]
okay I'll write it down even though you
guys say you don't use it it's still
important to write it down
okay
oh that's a tree
of crying a crying
tree
[Music]
but that's Japanese true true
this one is true
that looks like the Japanese kanji for a
tree
[Music]
if I die die die die die big big big big
okay big crying big crying yeah choose
big crying okay
[Music]
how many candies do you have how many
alphabet letters do you have in Korean a
ton ton yeah okay and
[Music]
this one Joy
it must be
oh God
oh God so they're actually teaching me
all those combinations first before
teaching me the actual single ones
it's the last thing ah it's the last
name in Korea okay I actually think
yeah yeah I've heard that before
dun dun
[Music]
it's the Ninja Turtle who lost one eye
and put the bandana back on listening to
wait a second did we have this one
before why
isn't that the one-eyed Ninja Turtle oh
peeping at the elf but but actually with
a bandana yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah which
was Kia before but this one is okay
[Music]
yeah there's a lot of things I have to
write down here
elf ear Ninja Turtle with one eye okay
[Music]
God yeah
I'm just gonna cheat now yeah
[Music]
is a this one
okay okay okay I can do it
shoe is a big crying
and I remember that one and Troy is uh
this one yeah
foreign
[Music]
I guess I guess so
no didn't we already have that though it
can't be
cool cool
sounds like a k c it doesn't sound like
a t but okay
[Music]
because that this this one the e is a t
okay okay okay okay
do that this would be much easier
[Music]
okay
oh my God this is quite challenging
[Music]
I see I see boobies
and boobies boobies
or it could be a dog's face these are
eyes this is the mouth I don't know I'll
leave it up to you guys whatever you
want to imagine
[Music]
oh
is that Titi Titi
Titi
he
Teddy
[Music]
twice booby dog
I think
yes
oh this one is very similar
it's like looking at a picture it's like
the office and they're like please find
the difference between those two beaches
and I'm like they're all the same
oh it's a person with a hat it's me he
he
this one
TV
and
a person with a hat
person trying on a hat in front of a
mirror
oh this is what H is the someone well
you guys are so nice for writing it down
the Hat the person with the hat is the
age
the the body is the W the I is the wall
is the mirror oh
hat is age
[Music]
set is
is a Ninja Turtle about to to kill two
people or or starting a fight Ninja
Turtle starting a fire today
[Music]
don't stop just go your own way yeah
okay tto is uh this one I'm like TV oh
dear
um
uh okay I know that this is the this is
H because of the Hat you guys taught me
that
and then it's uh it's the Ninja Turtle
with with one eye taking off the bandana
which was uh I don't even know anymore
hey hey
me looking at these things
next page
that person
okay
didn't you already teach me that
no way that's his eyes move didn't they
wait a second I didn't finish drawing
the first one damn it
say
[Music]
this one so this this uh this part is
that SS
and this is yeah because that the
bandana he takes the bandana off and
he's like yeah right
[Music]
fire
and then Ninja Turtle with eyes okay set
set oh
you know this is this is a
do-it-yourself style you guys are
teaching me what I really need to know
and Duolingo is teaching me things that
are additionally also important
[Music]
H was uh I think this is this one
because H was the hat and then we no
wait a second I'm not sure I take it
back no this is not the one who is the
one standing in front of the mirror
looking at the Hat
[Music]
this one was the other one that said hey
this one is hair
yeah yeah yeah okay
okay
[Music]
so I guess this is KK
and and then this is
not with the O in the middle
ah
oi mama
okay
I can't remember that
okay okay
this is then this is
um SS and yeah must be the the the the
the the bandana taken off
see yeah this is with the start of fire
today
this is H uh this this one no no this is
me uh this is me looking at the mirror
of the hat p and then this is TT and o
yeah okay
[Music]
whoa it's good
I'm learning this is pretty difficult
now okay okay okay okay are you guys
following the non-koreans are you guys
following obviously the Koreans are
following but I don't know Koreans in
the chat following
our fire start a fire today say start a
fire today
huh
[Music]
uh
hey
h e h e
last last one I
this one
the hair this is H
so even this one on this one that's this
one here yeah because of the bandana
s s
[Music]
yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
understand completely
oh I'm so proud
so proud of myself we continue it's not
over yet wow this looks like a cute
doggle face again
[Music]
Dogo eyes is I guess the pp part
this is the this is the it part I'm
guessing
this is maybe the W and this is the PPE
maybe or this together is why I don't
know or or this is why and this is
I don't know
ah PP one is p and this is PP and all we
seriously don't use that I have to learn
it anyway for Duolingo otherwise I will
not be able to continue
[Music]
you don't use it what does it mean but
has does it have any meaning so
this one
Maybe
I don't know it's just a sound oh oh it
has no meaning what the hell
this one so it sounds like it could be
either of these
this one okay
uh that's it why am I even writing this
down
so that I don't fail at my test
so eyes bandana okay
let's go
play
oh this one
[Music]
Must Be This One PP it's two so it must
be peepee
Kitty
[Music]
and then this one okay
what's up
[Music]
I don't remember it's even I don't know
I don't know which one is it
[Laughter]
oh my god
um
[Music]
remember your stories uh yeah I do but
um
oh thank you
[Music]
cjwo is the fire the JJ with the human
at the ATM whoa whoa
whoa yes yes okay okay okay
JJ
is uh no that's correct I guess
oh
oh my brain is burning
[Music]
I'm out of brain juice
well we just had
[Music]
okay
it just sounds so similar like it could
be both
and they didn't teach me the alphabet
first so now I'm lost
[Music]
okay two two two
football
full
[Music]
and I'm writing it down right now
[Laughter]
[Music]
what is this play
no maybe it is yeah
yeah
oh dear he's a lot of JJ's
but this is because of the peepees
uh okay what ATM
[Music]
and uh this is Joy I think and this is
ah difficult very difficult
people just had it I think this
[Music]
okay we good that's the pass let's go
hey
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
what is the ATM it's well
um starting a fire at the ATM
this is play
and this is
attack
sit sit sit chill
I think so okay okay oh
[Music]
um
ATM always think of the ATM yes yes yes
well yes was ATM yes yes yes
do it
toys
um
[Music]
this one
[Applause]
oh my God I'm smart
thank you
it continues I'm not stopping yet I am I
am feeling it right now I feel fine
inside me I have to continue
oh God
KK
no way good it must be
this one
[Music]
um KK OT
owa that's flower oh
I will hopefully remember that you're
sure
[Music]
okay car
car car snake ear human this was was
this the was this the G and this is
something
snake was a snake can you break that one
up for me
g-a-l is snack the L no a snake is the r
but just pronounced as l
Carl
hi
snake
ear
okay okay I'll try to remember that g a
l okay l l l
quote quote is the flower
it looks like a flower maybe with much
fantasy what ah
ah
I think it's I think she's saying at
is that supposed to be the A and that's
the T yeah that is the a I remember from
the very beginning 18
a t
eh and then the T
huh right yeah the circle is nothing oh
what does this mean
um no well it's a it's a g and an A
and uh this is not a t
here
[Music]
uh a and then the P okay okay
oh my God it's so I will not even say
that out loud
no okay don't say don't say it don't say
it
[Music]
T eight eighty eighty laughs
but what is this one
okay
c a k
oh we're really studying this so
seriously right now damn
it what
this one
it doesn't sound like she's saying tea
but according to the letters which I
have now learned uh thanks to the
audience it must be g-a-t no
is it
yeah right yeah yeah okay okay
Gap Gap Gap yeah pee in the hmm yes it
Rhymes almost
oh what this
what is that a snake turned around aims
which are peas I think yeah those are
peas PT uh snake was like something and
then another piece so pop
pop is this pump
[Music]
pop because there's a p in the beginning
and the p in the end and then and then a
and a in the middle
and I guess this snake gets ignored oh
[Music]
oh this is so much easier when you can
actually when you actually know what the
single letters mean it makes it so much
easier
pop
writing down everything pop pop snake
and then another P okay
[Music]
oh oh God very similar p a
and that was a
what was that
that's okay so pack
ah
p a silent snake and a k
oh I'm a genius bacon thank you
[Music]
oh it deceived me because it's turned
around oh that's it oh
wait so that would that for the example
this one would be K A and
[Music]
oh
I don't know what
must be this
I think
I think okay okay
[Music]
l or like r
gal cute girl no no
no
d
it doesn't sound like that it doesn't
even sound like okay that's a t that's a
t i just drink water oh
I'm trying to like listen to her about
the pronunciation confuses me sometimes
[Music]
no problem I got it I got it
I want to learn words I don't want to
learn letters anymore I want to learn
words can I start
oh I can complete this challenge
pass to the test to Jump Ahead let's try
to jump ahead we can do it with with
your help I can try oh god
um I learned this before
um wait a second it's a it's a it's a
it's Cali's wine glass which is pull
pull
uh-huh
Kukui okay Mama
[Music]
oh God basic
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
let's go okay
okay
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah
me me that's me no that's not me that's
me
that's me that's me oh I guess it's me
[Music]
how many
characters do you have in Korean a ton
[Music]
and
that sounds to me like g-a-l but it is
actually g-a-t right
yeah
wait
[Music]
wait for it Lee is the snake in front of
the mirror like sneaking up to the human
right this in Korean oh God
wait I don't know the word for family
though
I don't know the word for family
Duolingo
I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't
I don't know if you guys this one this
one
that's a car and that's a joke
we're cheating now
let me write it down
family
family family
[Music]
and then sure
okay
[Music]
now we go back to something so simple
okay okay fine with me oh oh oh
oh
it's with the neck
man and woman
I guess I'm not ready for this huh uh
what
oh
yeah yeah
[Music]
that's so long
foreign
[Music]
okay
does that mean Korean hunger
[Music]
what would I do without you I want to
learn way s you know
Korean newspaper
[Music]
all right I put this word in my
thumbnail Korean I asked Ina
[Music]
um
it sounds like
Japanese newspaper is uh
[Music]
I'm surprised that my super good Korean
I singer is not fun what do you mean
singing is fun
oh God
I'm not on this level yet
a singer is not what does that even mean
in English what kind of sentence is that
oh God okay singer is the
this one
okay singer not fun finger not fun is
this one singer singer
[Music]
sounds like
Japanese words
is
[Music]
not not fun right
no no
question
is
[Music]
I guess so yes sure sure
okay this my dog
uh wait if I listen to all of them maybe
I can recognize ones
[Music]
is this dog my dog no this one this is
cat
toyangi
dog is uh this one
huh my dog oh
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
what does that mean what do you mean
animals are not objects
is this
really
and I went too far with my level
apparently animals are not
objects let's see if that's really
correct
an animal is not a thing
is another correct solution
is an object not an object animal and
this is this is animal I would guess
um here I am again guessing grammar uh
the order of grammar this is the same
thing How I Learned Japanese I just
guessed it
[Music]
is
on top
I don't know
Tuesday
[Music]
y'all
okay uh
what I see I see you
uh
-huh uh wait let me find it this one
absolutely
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
how sad
song yeah yeah I agree I agree
Samsung
Channel Samsung
[Music]
television
but I have a Samsung uh Miner in front
of me wait
[Music]
that Branch what the hell is what
oh my God I thought you were teaching me
proper words
[Music]
sponsored by candy
this stream is sponsored by candy
Samsung
[Laughter]
Hyundai Samsung McDonald's
[Music]
oh my God
and
[Music]
priorities priorities guys and and is a
cook wait what was that again
give me Kimmy
can meet me that's me me me
get me Cami Cami is Aunt
hey
[Music]
kiss
foreign
[Music]
this must be it I think
I
know it
this is it this is it this is it it
sounds like it listens
[Music]
believe it
Korean it doesn't mean does it mean I
speak
Korean
[Music]
something Korean
Korean student oh cool Corey and
students
[Music]
oh
oh my God Park ah let me let me check
let me let me figure that out
um
[Music]
is it this one
oh oh I was I was thinking about Parks
as the name the pronunciation but we're
actually looking for the word ah
[Music]
um
I'm writing it down
and let's go to the park
okay
that's me at the ATM sitting at the no
that's me us
[Music]
it's me sitting sitting at the ramen
place
come on
actual
that's the actual one
going alone
but the G in Korean is pretty um strong
right it's like a k almost
give me
[Music]
can we come here
and I learned that Aunt Tokyo
okay that's Paris and Tokyo
New York London oh my
Paris New York
London don't get you
[Music]
at least I'm
gonna hear it
[Music]
New York apparently London
R is the snake
n is the swing down here long done
top
Tokyo
Paris
[Music]
Paris no I've been to Paris before I've
been to London before I've been to Tokyo
but New York and obso Nida
what
is
Park
[Music]
not Park
you don't like parks does he not like
parks there is no one at the park oh
there is no one at the park oh
I got the first part and the last part
means they're like no there's nothing
there no there is no no no
um
[Music]
also
there's no people
[Music]
you learned the skill alphabet two and
four others oh you've earned one lingard
oh start your progress with oh
that's how we skipped we skipped a lot
oh
I went down here wait did I ignore him
did I ignore
wait where did that
what does Basics one have
[Music]
nouns
wait a second
what did I just do
what if I start basic one again which I
apparently okay
[Music]
oh
this is why it would teach me about yeah
I skipped a lot apparently
this is where I would learn a few of
those words that just came to the to the
test I guess
okay you know what
um I think we will do
um one more Korean lesson sometime soon
and
yeah and now
I think
I will probably uh will I read super
chats now I don't know I don't even know
if I want to stream Minecraft tonight
I'm kind of exhausted from this week I
don't know maybe I should just read
super chats now and then take a rest the
rest of the day
I don't know
yeah
if that's okay with you guys yeah it's
been a long long week
and then I work on the schedule for next
week I'll show you that
yeah okay
um well then
um
[Music]
me football to say oh back
um
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
please help me
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
let's go to my restaurant
time
welcome welcome back to my restaurant
let me fix the chat
[Music]
yeah okay there it is
kfb and you work here now this is your
new job congratulations you have a new
job
you're checking for you chicken bucket
mmm Fried Chicken could I know chicken
inner
okay so we'll read some Super Chat
though
[Music]
now everyone will teach me bad words I I
I I I
um maybe maybe if I meet red red Nabi
but with blue Nabi I should be fine blue
Nabi Mama blue Nabi mama is safe I know
red Nabi mama is evil very evil
[Music]
okay
yesterday we
Reds until where is the end
we read until because I really need to
catch up
we read until okay here I need to read
starting from the Mario Kart uh
tournament
s stream yes yes yes
on it
[Music]
oh that's so big
I like my smug face in that thumbnail
and the hat the hat is so lovely Ina
made a beautiful hat
for all of us
yeah okay so
I will try my best to catch up today and
finish them so then I will most likely
not stream Minecraft today sorry
I I need a little break I think
[Music]
but I think today this stream was
already so much fun and uh yeah I hope I
hope it was also fun for the non-korean
viewers did you have fun did you have
fun
say yes
yes yes yes
thank you
thank you I'm glad to hear that
um
I've been I've been holding off on
learning new languages for a long time
but Korean has so far been fun and not
that difficult
like if I if I actually like learned the
letters
uh then I think I'll I will
[Music]
um be able to learn at least like basic
really basic uh daily conversation
skills
Google
[Music]
mama
foreign
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you all of you
you guys are so sweet
yeah okay now let's read some simple
chat Mr cashmere
looking for the top bankers and when
should we change the painting a little
bit
cute Patrick
[Music]
well actually you know what I don't want
this right now
yum yum yum
I want this one
so loud
okay
this is good the good old Speedy um
oh that was uh was that during the
preset
where uh I actually was uh placed above
you in in a race yeah hell yeah
thank you Judas I am so proud of myself
for
um finally beating you
but it was kind of well RNG a lot of RNG
there as well I would say but but I
really improved in Mario Kart yeah thank
you Judas
thank you for um you know helping out
like hanging out during the the pre-chat
races thank you
I hope you had fun can't believe Ina is
better than Tunas
I would I would like to see uh Judas
racing against Ina yeah because Ina was
pretty good but
I feel like maybe she would
would play a little bit differently when
against the
you know the the super skilled drivers
that are my viewers
we will see maybe one day maybe she did
she ever do a stream in Mario Kart
stream with the viewers
I wonder
[Music]
she never do that before
yes you did oh did you guys ever make it
in he should give it a try
and black kitchen thanks for the piggies
take this for Cafe pie yourself up Kiana
remember don't let us distract you from
taking the gold well I
have a gold but I got uh some really
good placements so I'm proud of myself
yeah
yeah it was very chaotic so
um maybe uh with a bit more practice I I
could have been a bit better but but
yeah
I think that was great Improvement
um
thank you for supporting me guys
the golden Gaggle up there
[Music]
from the Mario Kart tournament
he only practiced for real for one day
yeah it's true like oh every every
practice or like normal Mario Kart
stream before that was never released I
was never really trying to seriously
improve like I wanted to but I I needed
to do it differently
um
and I did finally
so now I am a decent opponent
hmm
[Music]
first of all thank you
so glad I got to got to take part in
some of your final practice races even
though I could tell I've really lost my
touch for Mario Kart there's no based
off of what I've seen you're really well
prepared for the tournament hot wings
thank you
foreign
yes
very much gamer
thank you thank you for for believing in
me
shadow thanks for the pinky believe in
the Phoenix bus yay thank you
thank you thank you very much Miguel
cfaa thank you soon Spencer and thank
you for the pinky as well this is from
my saving up to buy Nintendo fund no you
should have saved it to buy a Nintendo
what the hell you mean a switch you
don't have a switch yet priorities you
should get a switch first before before
um uh donating to me for the Korean
viewers let me explain
is German Deutsche foreign
foreign
yes
um
my name is
Jacob 47 darkest
yes we Have No Nintendo we have no
Nintendo today that's a song apparently
because there's a musical note in front
of that is that a meme
yes we Have No Nintendo we have no
Nintendo today I don't know that song if
it is a song
never heard of it
Pink Floyd
are you changing the lyrics for that
no you should really get a Nintendo
though the switch is so worth it I would
say switch
as one of the consoles in this
generation that is the most worth
getting
um
yeah
[Music]
it might not have 4K I think it doesn't
even have 1080 uh P right it's maximum
is 720 I think
doesn't even have 60 FPS
but still it makes up for it with so
many other things
yeah
it does have 1080. when docked the okay
okay okay well at least something
dunk shoot no damn kitchen
thank you
[Music]
all right
yeah yeah
well I personally don't really care that
much about those kind of things
um
like I I don't I mean I care about
graphics and all of that but
720p
1084k whatever as long as it's 7 20.
that's good enough for me
it's looking for the top fantasy
[Music]
whoa today's the sixth month anniversary
since you arrived to sideways Peru why
the were like that to say
Australia what the hell looking back you
overcome overcame many challenges yet
accomplished so much beating fans being
an ambassador cooking yummy lasagna or
getting good at Mario Kart or Minecraft
and you never stop being yourself you're
considerate playful Dr dodging self
appointment
after you arrived six months ago you
said you didn't feel at home now that
you connected with Mama
have your friends to support you or hang
out with them and your cats are there to
cuddle you I hope you are finding a
place to call home thank you
Yeah Yeah well yeah yeah I would
definitely call it home now I'm I'm I
got used to it yeah apparently it's been
six months since I came back yeah
um speaking of cats I had a dream this
night that I was uh
I went to a shelter or cell
where I saw all these cute cats and I
spontaneously decided to adopt two of
them and they look so adorable they look
so cute the kittens they were kittens
there was like one Ragdoll kitten and
one kitten was like I don't know it was
like a long fur black cat and it had
like a a round thumb around the snoot it
was a bit more gray and it looked so
cute oh it looks so fluffy that was a I
didn't bring my
the problem was I didn't bring my my my
um the the the boxes
for the cats obviously I wasn't prepared
for that so I was like yo I want to
reserve those two kittens I'll be right
back so then I went on a journey back to
where I originally came from to get
those uh boxes but but this is where my
dream kind of started going crazy
because I I kept on getting lost and off
track and I don't know it was really
weird I really just wanted to quickly
get back so I could uh capture the
kitties yeah
[Music]
but yeah I have two cats right now and
they're already like so much like work
as in they they're so attached to me
they want so much love for me and so
much attention if I were to get new cats
nah they would probably be kind of mad
so dream only I'll I will let my dreams
be dreams one day I'll get more cats but
right now is not the right time I've
been yeah they just they they need a lot
of maintenance
[Music]
I know
um
[Music]
foreign
getting worse
over these past weeks because I have
been speaking barely any Japanese oh my
God
I need to speak more Japanese but I
don't have any
any people around me to speak it with
I think if I were to spend like one week
in Japan I would immediately like pick
it up again
normally
Japanese collapse yeah into the more
Japanese collabs that's right yeah
thank you for the red super chat wake up
simple sweet I love kfp oh yeah I did I
did write something like that right
check my uniform it says kfb we love you
too
you're my first OC only Aussie and last
Oshi I'll never forget you your sweet
personality and this community will be
in my memory forever thanks for
everything you're awesome thank you
thank you thank you thank you so much
for being part of KFC yeah I was feeling
very
wholesome
on that evening I think really just
wanted to tell you guys how much I love
you
thank you for the recipe
thank you
fancy dinosaurs
Merchant thank you soon
tickets
okay now I have a Korean name
so
[Music]
um did I learn that one no
then wait I don't I don't have it
perfectly in my brain just yet
[Music]
thank you oh my god reading all these
Korean super chats later on is gonna be
tough
thank you for the pinky Pinky
so late Super Chat thanks for the name
you gave me last week oh you're your
lasagna now
um
I love lasagna too oh perfect I'm so
excited for today's stream enx ID collab
let's go hope you have lots of fun today
thank you oh this one's even before the
stream actually started still oh wow you
guys sent so many
thank you thank you very much for the
pinky and your support
and thank you for taking the name being
lasagna is very important role yeah
thank you for the red super chat I lose
my bed so here is my first red Super
Chat spending all
spending all spending spending all my
time loving you so loving you forever
you always will be my Aussie your skill
admire card becomes so much better now
thank you
you lost a bet
did you think did you think I would lose
was that it and then I actually did
quite well
never underestimated well I can I can
understand because up until that day at
that very day up until that very day I
was really at my account so it's
understandable that you guys would
underestimate me oh
ah the recipe
in case I would get some free
um but you lost it wait Did you bet that
I would get it or did you bet that I
would not get it
[Music]
if you win you were betting that I would
win top three
and I didn't and that and that's uh
moment
oh dear
but I did later on
[Music]
looking for the top down
Casino one time in Rainbow Road I
accidentally watched a VOD and I think I
fell twice
twice
not that twice
opportunity Skye thank you for the red
super chat oh what do we have here
congratulations from the 2500 kfb
Discord
and we have two things one to say ask
first is we think you practice a lot you
really become a gamer in this even in
the Rainbow Road second one of the
members
wants to be your cat can you adopt her
I just talked about this
I can adopt you in my dream
but not in reality unfortunately
I I don't have the spare space for more
cats I think
uh however let me try to read this
uh
yeah huh yeah
sorry no cannot do no can do no candle
wait can I can I check something really
quickly
really quickly really quickly
uh
oh no
oh
[Music]
uh
oh
I was checking our
um song list
of what we are allowed to sing on three
months wondering if there's any like
Korean songs because there's so many or
like basically only Japanese songs
but
um I found one from izone
it's called The Vampire but I actually
don't even know that song
foreign
oh dear
yeah I think it has to be an I want to
do an undercut karaoke stream we're
seeing some
some Korean songs we did that in a
Members Only
unarchived karaoke stream
I tried to sing some Korean songs
actually went quite well
I want to try again
I can't find
can't find any Korean songs here
what about Kara oh
of course car because karma was so
popular in Japan as well
go go summer what the what was that song
again
Kara Kara would be something that I
could sing on stream apparently but I
don't really know how to sing the song
is not here maybe maybe they have black
pink
I mean I'm not I'm not like the biggest
fan but I know like some of the songs
nope nope no black pink
[Music]
no blackpink
yeah very difficult
soon me I wish I could sing soon me
um
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no it's
all Japanese artists foreign
[Music]
yeah no
nope
[Music]
no no no no nope nope
unfortunately
Girls Generation come on you must have
Girls Generation Girls Generation come
on
GG
[Music]
baby baby no
no no
baby baby
[Music]
oh Supernova I like that one too
yeah
[Music]
ah good songs the other day what was
that song from from twice
that I kept that kept coming up in my
head
uh I
love that one
[Music]
hmm
okay
I love all their songs so much
okay I need to read super chats so
protect us
[Music]
and thank you thanks for the pinky
thank you I want to support Jacob 479
Korean name is
[Music]
no I don't know wait let me see
I have to check
yes it is
that an e let me see let me compare it
with what I learned today
yeah the second one is an e
hi
oh
yeah that's an all on top of a snake
which is the L
the snake
yeah I guess that's the E and then the S
is that the person oh
lit
[Music]
big brain
finally finally I can somewhat read your
name properly but already if you super
chat so often so I kind of already had
it in my memory
foreign
[Music]
was really fun to watch and your
practice really showed off thank you I'm
so glad I wasn't like a complete loser
I was I would have been fine with that
too to be honest but it feels so much
better to actually be good at something
yeah
thank you very much Apple for supporting
me and watching my stream
love you
you'll be first place soon yeah honestly
next time we do this uh tournament I
will practice even more and I will get
number one I promise you kfp I will get
that golden Jago for kfp again
[Music]
thanks for the pinky wanna bless you
girls that great you all did well and
the collab was fun as yeah thank
you everyone for participating and thank
you Kiana for organizing this amazing
collab much as well thank you yeah I
really had so much fun racing with the
girls
yeah so I hope we can do it more often
not be the local Merchant dungeon
science
all that work to put all this together
and also all those hours of practice to
become a threat in the races themselves
you did us all so proud Kiara we
couldn't ask for a bad attention so
please put scary TV out away
hey what's your problem with scary teeth
Kiana I it's not even that scary it just
looks funny
thank you thank you
yeah organizing these kind of
um tournaments slash events slash
collabs
and
I I
enjoyed doing it so
I don't mind doing it more often
yeah someone has to do it
thank you motion thanks also for the
pinky seeing your progress has been so
great reminds me of your ryza 2 or
Minecraft improvements but for an actual
competition
you worked really hard and it shows
happy to see you get as high as you did
proud of my gaming burp yeah with rhiza
too
like in Verizon one I I was still like a
little bit like who what am I doing but
in ryza 2 I also
um had this big Improvement Arc and it
did feel good yeah
it took me a while though
um
thank you thank you with Minecraft too
feels very good to be able to teach
others stuff and uh yeah keep up with
everyone
[Music]
yeah thank you motion use soda thank you
soon
for the red super chat golden Yago
funding thank you on the golden yellow
was sponsored by Amelia Watson
we finally found it in our basement
then dusted the yagos off
and then they were ready to be given out
to everyone
yeah that one is that one is quite dull
quite the quite the oldie yeah rare item
from back in the day yeah yeah I mean I
mean um
made it for a collaborate I think for
our first collaboration
[Music]
I don't know one of the first
collaborations Emma made this golden
yako
what my cats
are doing parkour
[Music]
don't do popcorn kitty cat
and thank you Papa
[Music]
um
it went red Red's not red I'm so
confused
foreign
[Music]
we have an interesting interesting
storyline going on again
let's read okay this is this is one of
those
special ones
listen up listen up
foreign
[Music]
wait a second before you listen up
no I'm looking for the dramatic one
where is that where is that one is this
one
no
that's not it either
I want the the one I used in Minecraft
the other day this one
oh yes this fits
oh my God okay
to her Reverend Kiana DB your vassal and
humble servant greetings
oh I wish you had witnessed the Gallant
efforts about wearing chickens against
the bamboozlers on that day
General pickled in leading the charts
with his sword Hand flanked by
by Valiant chickens whose names and
deeds precede them with great honor all
were eager to fight
entire host of KFC to exit antioxidants
gains in hopes of encircling us and
putting an end to our opposition though
we were few in comparison the bamboozles
were shocked at our defiant charge and
as we chickens barreled into the
Bamboozled lines that shock gave way to
doubt and fear
as the sun began to fall so too did the
morale of our bow and soon enough they
were chased from the field by our
chickens as they up a box of
Israel
having finally secured Angela from
Alfred's who has led us so well but
feeling the weight of his age in order
to be continued on and leave him in
Antioch to be continued
[Music]
hahaha
isn't dead
perfect
[Music]
that was quite
thrilling I must say
wow
what a cliffhanger hell yeah
that was amazing Divine Exquisite I
might even say
thank you everyone's salute salute
huh
yeah the timing of the museum was nice
too
okay
prepare for the back
of the battle
that kind of stuff always reminds me of
the times when we watched uh Lord of the
Rings
uh with the members
so so
okay
[Music]
I love this kind of super chats thank
you if there's a vault
[Music]
wow
looking forward to the continuation I
was really into it really immersed today
um
[Music]
Felix Sal thank you for the oh wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait those are uh Legend
of Zelda super chats oh
starting from one before there's a vault
starting from Patrick Chen those were uh
Legend of Zelda Super Chat
let's read these
and then after that we can finally read
the Korean super dance
so you have to wait a bit more uh Korean
friends sorry
uh we're we're getting close
to the Korean super chats I just need to
refresh this and then
wait
um
yeah it's Zelda
super chats from yesterday
oh my God oh my God so many Korean super
chats
hahaha
oh my god oh dear
this is gonna be fun to read
[Music]
let me just copy and paste the updated
version
[Music]
foreign
a friend of mine asked me why there's
only two employees working in the new
kitchen background it was a silly
question I answered because everyone
else is in the bridge too that's right
but
[Music]
eventually we are all intentious stomach
I mean heart
um
no okay no no no this this is this is
there's more first of all we have we I
have acknowledged I have told you guys
yesterday that the chicken running in
the background is not the same person
always it's always a different person
and um
it may look like there's only one
chicken cooking in the background but
this is not the whole kitchen there's
there's more to it yeah this is just one
tiny part of the kitchen
and there's way more in the background
and uh they're moving at the speed of
light so you don't see all of them
yeah they're sweet chickens
thank you Felix
skeleton chicken lives thank you also
for the red super chat what the hell it
was a double red Super Chat that just
says insert joke
though
[Music]
well are you asking me to insert a joke
I don't know any jokes
I really don't know any jokes like if
you ask me I'm really a bad uh stand up
comedian
I'm really bad at jokes man I I don't
know why I ever called myself comedian
I'm I'm a I'm an imposter
I'm a faker fake it till you make it
though right
why did the chicken cross the kfb Kiara
you didn't cross it though it got stuck
somehow it's not coming out of the kfb
anymore
that's the joke
it's kind of a dark joke
[Music]
it says insert small follow-up okay
where is the small follow-up guys
I'll leave it to you guys because I
can't think of a smart follow-up for
that one
Germany
[Music]
they always know it didn't get to cross
the road yeah is that the follow-up that
we can come up with the only one
amongus
the chicken never left yeah there can't
be a follow-up if the chicken Devil
comes out of the kfp
damn it
airmail dolphin thank you In Motion
thanks for the pinky after one month I
finally finished my Ur sentence Oh
so what you expect some kind of like
graduation ceremony or something like
that you want us to clap or what
you want us to clap for you
I know I now know to never say you can't
read
okay hell you're reading this super chat
at this very moment exactly
I am a reformed chicken never again
unless I forget which would probably
happen
yeah I guess I can't blame you for
forgetting eventually because you guys
are chickens
can't blame you that much thank you for
the pinky mouth of Phoenix foundation
and rail boy Danish and small brain
thanks for the rest of
the red zazella I haven't played all I
stand by that decision oh
are you saying that
watching my stream you you once again
affirm reaffirmed that you are not going
to play this because you don't like it
is that what you're trying to say yeah
this is the Zelda is apparently not not
the most popular one
not that bad
it's actually fun it's just a bit
difficult here and there with the
controls but I think
I think all in all it's a it's a great
Zelda oh
[Music]
well to each their own right yeah you
don't you don't have to like it I'm
playing it right now oh wow
it's not my favorite but it's an amazing
game yeah I think so too I like the
story and hey it's the it's the origin
story it's the beginning you kind of
have to play it if you're a Zelda fan
you have to
do you know about Hyperdimension
Neptunia yes I do I own uh some of the
games yes
I'm dancing
this January opportunity Duncan Ezekiel
Ramos thanks for the pinky insert I love
democracy meme good job Chad 50 50
Supremacy haha yeah every freaking poll
I was making turned out 50 50.
man can never make decisions here
lost traveler 649
mods thank you thanks for the pinky dear
tension my third Super Chat my
researchers have found some evidence
that a phoenix may go through a pupil
face what does that mean where they turn
into a bucket-like cocoon before
becoming a full-fledged Phoenix does kfb
member badge confirm that or is that
just a coincidence that is interesting
excuse calling it a cocoon
I like that way of describing it
interesting very interesting
I can neither confirm nor deny that at
this current moment
Mr Casper extension Elemental colors
looking for the top tank because thank
you for the rest of the chat
a chance because I missed the live
stream you did an incredible job setting
up the Mario Kart tournament thank you I
was glad to see everyone who had so much
fun and it was nice of the young curse
to be lenient yes yes hope to see more
events like it in the future thank you I
will do my best
to make more things like this happen so
that you guys have more exciting events
to look forward to
thank you very much because for
acknowledging it
thank you soon for your support I'm glad
you enjoyed it
ah KR
um
can I read this without
without looking it up um so this is uh
wait a second I mean looking for my for
my notes
um
[Music]
teeth
where is it is it a b b yeah that's a b
b
the first thing is bull I think because
it's made up of a b o and a l
bullet bullet and then it's uh
[Music]
so it looks like
pop pop no not pop tea
[Music]
what was the first one I said
four times time
eat for turkey why did I really
correctly correctly let's see Google
Translate
KR fire chicken
[Laughter]
[Music]
I have a Korean fan and I'm watching you
well
604 that took me so much time to read
that oh my God
I think spiders spread and zombies scene
rather than this dungeon is an homage to
the Japanese famous novel kumono Ito
if you're interested in a novel please
read it that sounds so interesting I I
would love it if that's true if they
really like implemented that yeah
thank you for the rest of
a triple round you crazy
thank you
I already reacted to you during the
stream because you crazy
Jackson FB also thank you again for
converting the Skyward Sword rupees
thank you
mango rocket function
s
for another triple red Super Chat you
are crazy crazy
thank you so much for your support
uh skipping the flush chats oh dear
there's a lot
and take a cake thank you thank you for
another red Super Chat raccoon
[Music]
um
always so supportive
price all free thank you for the pinky
got my paycheck yesterday so here's my
kfb salary
unfortunately this month will be a bit
of a high expense month for me so I will
have to leave it a bit less than usual
don't worry about it you decide yourself
you could even say zero no salary
that is fine too
thank you thank you
mad speak studios.com
[Music]
foreign
of a kitten that I had when I was
younger my first kitten
um who was called Hugo he was a black
black Kitty that we got from um
a bad one hole what was that again in
English what the hell
um h-u-g-o
[Music]
uh not a shell a farm yeah we got him
from a farm and
um it was a baby and I was so happy to
have him I was really really young but
he died like so soon like in in the
first one or two or three weeks or so
because he had
um some
um really bad illness that cats have
sometimes that you cannot really do
anything about
um
yeah something what was that again I
wonder I forgot
I think that's what it was called in
German so weird what is that what is
that naming
cup since
[Music]
veterinary medicine let's cat disease
what
[Music]
yeah it's it's some
some kind of
um
what is the word for that
cats play
apparently
apparently that's what it was so he had
basically no chance and died so soon
after we got him from the
um
respiratory virus feline leukemiah
doing very soon after after we got him
from the farm yeah that was sad yeah
very sad
but I think like like
probably all of the cats from that farm
had that probably
very sad
it's okay though it's okay it's a long
long long long long long long long long
long long
time ago
yeah foreign
[Music]
wanna go to a vacation
I want to go on a vacation but I don't
want to go alone
hopefully I can go sometime soon
Skippy one one one five two thanks
[Music]
I watch other streamers whose first
language is not English and they all say
they rarely use their home language
because everyone in Europe speaks speaks
English anyway is this true for our
Australian bird too no
no no no no we speak English uh German
here all day
[Music]
cake
I forgot how to read those
is that really is he trolling or
[Music]
is he trolling me or is it true
what's that even mean
[Music]
not true
this real yeah
let me see
who I see oh
[Music]
what
that's chicken and duck
[Music]
ah
and the pronunciation is like super
similar if not the same yeah
chicken and duck
duck duck
so so fire chicken could also be Fire
Duck
um can I eat a cookie
cookie to sale
[Music]
um
hmm
[Music]
one more
hmm
[Music]
okay
now I feel better
hmm
wait water is blue blue wasn't am I I
feel like I heard that before
[Music]
how do I say I drink water
money
[Music]
how do I say I drink water
water
um oh wait I I used to know the word for
yummy
[Music]
what was it again
what's what how do I say something
tastes good
mashi
[Music]
Master
sale
maybe it was not that my man was
thinking of a different word
I don't know
I remember like all these tiny words
from that show
[Music]
oh yeah okay
and back to Super chats so yeah no we
don't we I mean all of the I would say
like everyone almost everyone in
Australia knows basic English definitely
a lot of them know fluent English
uh but we still speak German here every
day in everyday life of course so yeah
uh Starman thanks for the pinky come on
bro stop sending super chats I thought
you said you wanted me you wanted to say
for video also me haha credit card yeah
yeah this was the Super Chat I remember
that you were you were trying to save up
for your own YouTuber model
good luck
good luck doing that
I hope I hope you can
create the model of your dreams
your ideal model that represents you
well I hope so
have fun with it go crazy with it
hi team thank you for the pinky as well
thank you
MBS 1969 looking for the top Danke
Schoen chicken says what what
I just want me to say that
oh
[Music]
um the first two letters are all
oh
[Music]
I am
what
I am Bulldogs
for Las Vegas
for the pinky
for your ground wagyu beef lasagna and
artisanal butter what is that in anyway
so some fancy butter huh for your made
from scratch bechamel sauce
if when you say made from scratch do you
even expect me to make the butter myself
please serve on some weird object that
isn't actually a plate yeah good idea
good idea I'm gonna make a fancy lasagna
restaurant
um
yeah we were talking about this uh some
um I think GD maybe in the super chats
mentioned uh about going no not GD was
it someone else someone someone
mentioned to about mention about going
to uh a restaurant where there was a 55
days it was days sorry going to a
restaurant that served 55 of lasagna
lasagna that costs 55 so this is related
to that
I'm really curious about that lasagna I
want it I wanted
is this the same guy yes
I am
Bulldog who comes at me now thank you
Patrick
thank you for the pinky everything's
based onion info short url.it
slash
you really want me to go there
[Music]
I don't know if I can trust you
can you guys go first
I mean I I mean I I know you wouldn't do
like that but
you guys gotta go first okay short
url.80 slash
do small letters in capital letters
matter and URLs I don't they don't right
slash h
j z
in small letters and on capital b
capital M
foreign
[Music]
it was just the onion thing
yeah I trust you I trust you
but I can't just go open your eyes on my
stream
[Music]
hey the audience doesn't trust you
either that's sad that's sad
[Music]
oh well we will never know
stop trying to give your viewers advice
all right all right your choice all
right
we will not go there but apparently it's
some onion info
isn't it is it about washing the onion
Kiara virus
piano virus
wasn't there something like that
like like a while ago
hatchimal virus what was that
some kind of whole live virus
what the hell was that
[Music]
Corinth
am I no I don't I'm confused there's a
lot of viruses apparently
foreign
okay
Korean super chats
let's go
isn't this thumbnail cute it's me in the
school uniform there's not much um fan
art of me in the school uniform but I
wanted something like that for this
thumbnail
so here we go okay I will probably have
to switch over to my Google translate a
million times because I'm not very
confident in my reading yet
what is this
okay
[Music]
you used to hate me but now you're my
friend I'm really happy what
don't get it wrong don't get it twisted
Duolingo verb we are not friends
we are acquaintances okay at the very
most
you are green bumps I am Orangeburg you
you taught Carrie
and kuna languages
when I could have done that and I will
never forgive you for that
Kiana is the best bourbon Town danger
soon
oh is this I am
Bulldog yes
let me put this tablet next to it so I
can always use it
I like that
this and then move this here and Yoshi
there we go okay perfect
okay
[Music]
soon oh here we go oh here we go
and
foreign
[Music]
oh dear
cookies delivered
[Music]
the chat most of the time anyway because
that I couldn't read the letters so even
if there was a lot of trolling I
couldn't have noticed so it's all good
don't worry about me I don't mind at all
it's fine it's fine but there were a lot
of you guys worried about it
which I think you guys can calm down
it's okay
thank you for the red super chat
[Music]
barley
thank you
thank you soon
um foreign
[Music]
if I were to do this all the time
looking it up by myself we will take
years
[Music]
um
Kim Kim
dog
children
a pH
ineas
[Music]
as a Korean viewer no tencha has a great
talent for learning languages I know you
will learn Korean very fast and to love
you from Korea thank you
well I I don't know about that yet but
we will see I'll do my best
don't get your hopes up just yet lucky
profit thank you
[Music]
um
thank you
for the pink Super Chat have a good time
thank you so
for watching and supporting me
[Music]
down
tickets
[Music]
two one three five
no more dance
is my new best friend
[Music]
foreign
uh-huh
[Music]
I understand
is
[Music]
peas a shrimp passing by oh
thanks for today's stream made with my
mother tongue oh I always admire your
enthusiasm and activeness I mean really
oh thank you
[Music]
Kiana fighting
makes no sense
I'm surprised that you're so good at
Korean you must have studied I'm always
watching you thanks to you I spent every
day Thrifty oh 50. thank you no I have
not studied until today but as I'm
either as I explained I learned a few
words from some some places yeah
thank you Anthony webb thank you for the
pinky hi Angel I always love watching
your last terms or at least listening
while I'm at work thank you for making
my work week more enjoyable you're
welcome
I enjoy entertaining you
yeah I'm glad I can make a tough and
annoying and exhausting work week more
worthwhile for you thank you thank you
for watching and supporting me Nam sh
kams
[Music]
hey
see this is okay I can't even laugh
about it
[Music]
um
Rachel thank you for the Super Chat for
the pinky
uh what
huh
uh fighting rots is such a good variety
show you mean you mean the one that I
mentioned Return of the Superman yeah
yeah I'm so happy to know that you
listen to Cable girl groups too but
anyway I hope you enjoy learning Korean
because I know I did your pronunciation
is already so good love you always thank
you yeah my pronunciation I just
um do it like similarly to Japanese
pronunciation and it kind of like ends
up being okay-ish so I'm glad that I
already know uh another Asian
um
language yeah that's very helpful in
this case
are you still watching The Return of
Superman no because
um
I I stopped watching it because it is so
wholesome that it makes me want to have
babies
and I don't know my mother instinct
kicks in and makes me want to have
babies it's really bad so I cannot watch
it
and they don't show though the evil the
bad sides of the kids they only show
like how cute they can be it's deceiving
it's deceiving
but maybe I'll maybe I'll check in again
to see which kids they have going on
right now I like the ones that were
there in the past
[Music]
but yeah maybe I'll check in is this
show still going on
is it still happening
could I still put out new episodes you
got Clara
there's always Clara Clara is not real
she's only in Sims
[Music]
no did the show stop
they have new episodes I'll go again
I've been missing a lot of streams but
not just yours but I'm so glad I'm still
awake for this although I'm currently
going for Japanese Duolingo still
learning the advanced hiragana there's
Advanced
it's nice to finally get a stream
Arigato you're welcome thank you good
luck studying you should um use other
studying methods as well I think
Duolingo is like a good addition to
other studying methods but you shouldn't
only rely on it yeah good luck though
[Music]
actually Korean has only 28 characters
but they combine into a syllable
oh the oh the circle refers to silent or
NG sound
and the other is blah blah blah the
tables until the walls refer to vowels
yeah if only they would have taught me
that first
um stop please start chill
watching
[Music]
what is this
happy birthday
um
[Music]
foreign
question
[Music]
and thank you for adding the English
reading to your Korean name that is very
helpful so if any of you Korean viewers
are watching here and want to make it
easier for me you could add the English
reading not the English translation but
the reading to your name to your YouTube
name and that would save me a lot of
them
so it says it's my first akaspa as a
Korean I'm so happy that Kiana is
interested in Korean thank you for
always doing a good stream I'm always
waiting for you I love you thank you
foreign
[Music]
for many many years and every every now
and then whenever I get like a like a
like a addiction to it there's always
like a face where I listen to Kpop for
days and then I stop
and into the show that I told you about
I was watching that like many many years
ago as well and I was also watching this
show where these celebrities sat in a
circle on the ground with pillows in
front of an audience and then there
would be like family members discussing
their problems like random family
members from the audience and discussing
like other family members I don't know
what that show was called but it will
happen together maybe
let me look it up
it was really dramatic
um they would not be like why the
don't you get a job and like that
uh
let me see
[Music]
doesn't no not that show no it doesn't
look like that hello counselor yeah
hello counselor I don't know why but I
watched like
30 episodes of that
hahaha
I don't know why it was so interesting
to me to hear korean's family's problems
like yeah I want to do something similar
yeah very very interesting hello
counselor
um Korean show so I was I was watching
stuff like that
but the reason why I really decided to
do a Korean language study stream
recently was because for some reason
there have been so many new Korean
viewers and when they sent super chats I
can never read their names uh because I
don't know their signs so the characters
so I wanted to learn that to make it
easier and also I was just really happy
to see like Korean uh translated clips
on YouTube and all that and so yeah
um I want to give back a little bit yeah
yeah yeah there's probably gonna be
there's this one channel that Clips me
all the time uh the like a Korean uh
translation uh Channel
who Clips me all the time I don't know
how to read the name of that channel
but uh yeah he will probably clip this
one as I found it I found it
oh that was my song
the channel is called
foreign I never knew it was called that
[Music]
is one of them at least yeah
maybe you know it if you were looking
for a Korean translated Clips then you
might know the channel
um
yeah thank you thank you for your
support one of the reasons why I wanted
to do this stream is because of uh these
these translation translation channels
yeah I'm sure they will clip this one as
well
she does really good Clips actually
I know you for that channel oh
[Music]
Korean Kitty nuker the way you write
that is
n't followed that before Kitty Nuki in
Japanese is Clipper someone wrote it
like kitty nuker wait why is that so
funny to me
they they nuked the kitty nukis
sorry that was um funny to me because
I'm stupid
um
oh man
[Music]
thank you
thank you so much for watching my
streams
[Music]
oh
sugar sugar
oh yeah milk I already forgot wait milk
was oh yeah
I learned a few useful very useful words
today
sound that cool thank you thank you soon
sick
[Music]
come on
even if you misspell Karina a little you
can understand the meaning if your
pronunciation is correct I don't mind if
you pronounce it wrong
[Music]
um bgy five six four five thumbs
foreign
[Music]
thank you
is but it sounds more like quickly
saying
o and E together
[Music]
interesting uh
um
empty you're doing really well with this
actually Duolingo is teaching you the
alphabet in the most weird way if you
watch any short YouTube video explaining
the Korean alphabet you'll get it all in
one hour I can't imagine yeah I bet you
tense like thank you I'll check some
videos out I think I'll teach myself
properly yeah
whenever I have some time thank you it
was a bit confusing but yeah I got some
some ideas from it
the whole Ninja Turtle Arc was really
funny and the Ina Ina meeting the Ninja
Turtle I think that was all quite funny
so I enjoyed it I had a fun time
hey
[Music]
um
thank you for the pinky thanks for
trying just to take care honestly
Duolingo didn't do a very good job
teaching you hunger you should look up
learn to read Korean in 15 minutes it's
a short comic strip that explains the
logic much better oh interesting
we learn to read Korean in 15 minutes
let me look it up right now so that I
don't forget it learn to read Korean in
15 minutes
[Music]
oh it has a ton of views yeah
oh wait no that one is uh in five
minutes seriously why is there bananas
in the thumbnail
learn to read Korean this must be it
from nine years ago this is probably the
one that you mean
yeah that looks like a comic strip
[Music]
Ed chicken
is that Immortal chicken
kanzanita
what is his name
you just put like you just hit your
fists on the thumbnail five times and
came to come up with that name didn't
jump
s-j-s-y-s-j w j x w h x y w j x cake
what the is that name
um but you wrote a message so I'll read
that
is
no
um
[Music]
and
I don't give some Supply comes on down
[Music]
fine fine fine
thank you now
[Music]
though
foreign
[Music]
consists of 14 consonants and 10 vowels
a letter can have up to two consonants
giving a total combination of
14 times 10 times 14 is 19
1960 letters
that are possible in Korean wow wow
wow
the paper jam comes on
James McPhee thank you for the red super
chat smart boob it's fascinating to see
your process to learn an alphabet it's
very much like a Memory Palace anyway
just rambling keep up the great work
boss I was also just rambling the things
that I came up with
Fascinate myself as well
yeah but like if you see I think like
when you learn for example kanji like
Japanese you also kind of like you have
to like do it like that like imagine
like something some situations or
stories or whatever in order to really
memorize those
um if you're not a freaking genius like
me yeah
um but with with kanji it's also
partially for some kanji it's easy
because like for example the kanji for
tree kind of looks like a tree the
country for a person who kind of looks
like a person stuff like that it does it
it there are a lot easy ones that look
like what they're supposed to represent
but not all of them obviously there's
many that are much much more difficult
and you're like you don't really know
anymore what to associate that with but
basically when you learn a language that
has a different alphabet then your own
then I think it's a good strategy to try
to associate it with something
in your brain
yeah yeah
it's also the same way like when I look
back when I think back to my time in
school
like in English classes I think other
like I I was I had an easy time with
English but I think others in my class
personally tried to make such
Association bridges in their brain as
well when it came to English even when
it came to vocabulary as well yeah
comes
[Music]
um
as always thank you for your streaming
and Duolingo has a serious problem for
learning Korean some are hard to
distinguish some were not you some are
no value but you're really good if you
say I'm a genius yes you deserve it
thank you we should not roast Duolingo
too much in this stream
because you never know that the Green
Owl might be watching
[Music]
um
I'm a bit scared because I roasted them
myself but for now I don't have any any
direct messages from manager son so
probably die jobu
probably dojo
um
foreign
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
I will try my best to study a bit more I
will never be perfectly fluent I think
but I'll try my best to get like a daily
conversation I'm actually motivated
I am motivated
Max solomonson
lullaby come send me now see me thank
you thank you soon
there was a fan-made game of you what
would you like it to be
fan made games and I think they are
really cute like because they're like
um stuff that are related to KFC you
know someone made the the loading screen
that I had in the very very very very
beginning
um made it into a game uh actually there
were like two games of that
and so I think that is like super
fitting or like you know how how there
is like these like cooking games
um or where you serve people in the
restaurant and you are under time
pressure I would love to see something
like that
like a restaurant game with with uh
where you have to remember orders and
then serve the customers
yeah something like that would be really
cool I don't know if anyone ever made
something like that with kfp I don't
think so
hmm
like overcooked yeah for example
[Music]
there was one really
yeah really
hey I want to see you guys should send
it to me on Twitter if anyone can find
it
um
[Music]
foreign
I love lips and iced tea one of my faves
they had so many different varieties of
Lipton iced tea in Japan
They Don't Really in my country but in
Japan they had all these fancy Lipton
ice teas oh man I missed them
ah okay that makes sense so basically
you're learning the value combinations
of vowels and consonants they mostly
don't have any meaning unless combined
properly though yeah maybe maybe
Duolingo you know there were a lot of
words that apparently according to the
Koreans in the chat made no sense but
maybe they were just trying to show me
that you can make all these combinations
with you know the basic parts
and
of the letters but but but then first of
all you should tell me about that like
they did it without explaining that
um
Haven Heights zero one eight XE thank
you
Korean weatherstructure left right
bottom side ah do I always read from
left to the right to the bottom to the
right again bottom is optional but
others are necessary right it's vowel
and others are consonant I want to tell
you about consonants and vowels
but I can't because of YouTube no
problem no problem I can't I kind of got
the gist of it yeah
zero one one zero
you like my thought process I'm happy
about that
oh he came down
um
the hell do you like every freaking
language just seem to speak English
Japanese
and Chinese probably two and Korean
what the hell
a scene
um wow
[Music]
amazing
I I really wonder you're you're so
mysterious you never talk much now you
finally you finally gave me a Super Chat
that is made up out of actual sentences
and you actually wrote a lot which you
never do and now it's only Korean though
and I never I didn't even know you speak
Korean what the hell you seem to speak
every language that's the longest Super
Chat I've ever seen from you normally
you're like so so quiet
you're so mysterious
[Music]
man
it's the beginning the potential in
Korean
[Music]
hell yeah
foreign
[Music]
oh
oh oh oh interesting
this person was trying to tell me some
Korean words are pretty
similar to uh Japanese words ah
it was a mixed this this superset was
mixed Korean and mixed and Japanese that
like it probably came out weird in the
translator but it says
yeah yeah cause like
sounded so similar and otherwise
apparently as well interesting
that makes it easier for me
now
[Music]
and
engages
[Music]
friends so what we learned in Duolingo
today
[Music]
was a word that I remember too yeah it's
like really what really
[Music]
you did such a great job learning Korean
today also trying to learn Korean
because there's a lot of Koreans lately
it means a lot to me
all the hard work in trying your best is
a huge reason why I love you and use
dreams thank you you're so sweet thank
you
[Music]
you're not you're not uh donating with
Korean money so thank you thank you
DT dipton oh wait no
deep Tone come send me down why do some
thank you
what is this
is
[Music]
speed freak thank you thank you
thank you
correct Super Chat even though lingo had
problems it doesn't change the fact that
Kiana is a genius how do I say it is
I am a genius
yeah I am a genius
[Music]
wow I keep on repeating the same words
I'm such a genius
thank you
[Music]
written in Korean interesting that's how
you write it huh
Cheryl
for the red super chat oh my cross
Frontier fan
I see I see
I am more on the side of rankaries
always needs a Cheryl gnome so
cute what a Super Chat thank you for
supporting me that no more normal
[Music]
GPS comes foreign
as well was that Korean too
[Music]
much
me
[Music]
it says good girl but that's that
person's name
thank you thank you
come on
love aseline
cook
come on
[Music]
wait a second
foreign
[Music]
no way
I was worried that many Korean viewers
would have put pressure on you but I'm
glad that Kiana learned it in a fun way
I'll always support your friend you know
it was really a lot of fun so don't
worry about it you guys you guys are too
worried about everything chill
okay
[Music]
Cloud S2 Luna
and as Korean thanks for streaming today
I'm gonna I'm gonna get a third language
certificate but I am not good at
speaking could you share how to practice
speaking are you are you referring to
English
well this is very simple advice but you
should really just try to imitate how
others speak
by maybe trying to sing English songs or
talking to English people and on Discord
or in like
um I'm sure that there's like uh
one-on-one English teachers in Korea as
well
[Music]
um
or watch uh watch um Netflix and stuff
in English with Korean subtitles
or maybe even with English subtitles
because you if you already have a gist
of of the English language you might
want to try to watch it in English with
English subtitles because that way even
if if you're listening is not so good
yet
um by reading it at the same time I
think it will be really really helpful
you will be able to
um pick up the the pronunciations and
accents and all that
much easier and then maybe you'll be
able to imitate it
yeah that worked perfectly for me oh
there we go there's people who who can
uh confirm that
OTL comes
down I'm I'm soon done
I see the end sometime soon
[Music]
no no no no no not yet no no but thank
you
[Music]
I will do my best fighting
you guys know why they call me Kim Ada
because Kim is such a common last name
in Korea so they call me kimara because
my Korean is good
yeah I don't think I deserve being
called bottom left anymore
they think I'm smart
I am smart
[Music]
oh
Communications
[Music]
foreign
thank you
huh
[Music]
because
password number 4867
thank you thank you very much is there a
uh like something in Korean that's like
[Music]
is there something like that's
comparable to other in Korean
um
[Music]
foreign
funny
how do I say funny Kusa
[Music]
I mean
damn
the does that mean
s
[Music]
if you can't read my name I'll come up
with a new one oh yeah I tried to choose
uh the characters that I already learned
oh sweet I'll try to I'll try to
remember but it would be even better if
you would add the English reading to it
oh wait you already uh almost hatched
chicken oh
foreign
[Music]
twice twice song
wasn't there something like that
there was a song where they sang that
[Music]
um
bigger sister right I know I know
foreign
[Music]
I love that song
baby baby
[Music]
mm-hmm
okay refresh time I am almost at the end
our girl and Tricia comes
refresh refresh
or so I thought
[Music]
oh it's so I thought
for sure
there's so much Korean today so much
I hope you guys don't miss the danke
schoon
[Music]
ER time jumped on the keyboard he was
trying to tell you something I think it
was
cat always welcome on keyboard cat
Welcome everywhere cats even welcome on
lab when on toilet no problem
good cat good cat
thank you spank happy and hun thank you
I just should call you just spanking
time whenever I I say your name normally
thank you
[Music]
for the pinky thank you for the great
stream today Duolingo
okay this is almond
and thank you for the great string to
that building it was so bad that the
Korean chat was confused if you try to
learn Korean seriously I recommend TTM
ik and lingle deer much better version
of doing oh dear oh dear oh dear I
acknowledge your recommendations but I
should probably
should not say that I look forward to
the day you can read my name for Super
Chat
actually
actually yeah I could probably already
read that now if I would actually take
some time uh and think about it for a
moment yeah
thank you so much I will do my best so
please don't give up on me
don't give up on me
[Music]
down
[Laughter]
English
kfb Korean secret menu Pride Daniel's
husband with fire chicken sauce now on
sale
thank you thank you
[Music]
that's difficult
foreign
[Music]
that's flower I learned that today
my name is pronounced everything oh
look
[Music]
I see you wrote something in Korean
there did you use uh
perhaps already in the usual room
because if not then you're going there
now
Elvis my dear Elvis You Are up
challenging me once again
yeah Gemma jenma is my manager and he
says he loves Jen ma now in Korean
one month
additionally two if you're already in
there
okay
foreign now
[Music]
pretty sure he has been in there he's
probably still in there yeah
stream Elvis challenge that y'all
garlic seasoned chicken
no not yet but that isn't that some of
the Korean special chicken that you guys
have over there I love garlic I love
chicken gotta give it a try dancing
[Music]
with the pinky I'm going to the bed
today was so funny thank you Kiara we
love you oh I'm probably too late
already you're probably already gone but
[Music]
foreign
does that make sense
good night sweet dreams dream of me
[Music]
wait wait wait
wait wait
um
[Music]
that dude's voice is so comforting
the Google translate male voice for
Korean is so comforting
I like it
[Music]
do it thank you thank you
well I speak 90 languages and bound to
make a few mistakes how many languages
can you speak how to free that's nothing
nothing oh he mad
it's okay so no I was actually I was
actually when I was talking to a
Japanese Super Chat I was actually
defending you I was saying that
I forgot what I said I was saying
something like well you know all
languages so cannot underestimate you
yes
yes and no no no no kfp is not Korea
fried Phoenix it is Kiara fried Phoenix
um
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you wait wait you don't look Santa
pinky let me read that first
I am cute when I speak Korean take me no
wait if you mean take me as an employee
okay okay I will hire you you're hired
thank you for your interest
you are now officially hired you may
work at kfbu until the rest of your life
is that what you wanted I hope I hope
that was what you wanted because now
it's too late anyway to sign the
contract officially
[Music]
for the pink Super Chat
no thank you for the pinky as well my
class is starting tomorrow so I might
not be able to catch every stream's life
anymore oh no I'll still watch all the
vods and try my best to catch you live
as much as I can though love you tencho
you will be forever my Oshi
who's coming back to grab us all
yeah unfortunate but please do your best
in your classes
and I'm glad you still want to watch my
streams in VOD form that's fine too
thank you so much for thinking of me and
continuing to support me thank you soon
good luck
and uh
um
thank you boss today very fun do it
again study yes I will do it again maybe
like privately more but also one more
stream
probably
I wanted to learn
um the letters first and when I can
properly read it I want to do another
stream where I learned some words
[Music]
foreign
thank you
now
[Music]
Patrick C turned into pet with joy
thank you soon
Young
foreign
[Music]
okay what did I say there in the
beginning though
oh my what why did I say
when
nanny
okay wait
I'm so close to being done
okay let me turn them off right now
I really need to go to an idol meeting
I don't know how much longer I can take
it so let's go speed Super Chat reading
and as we as I can be when I have to
input all these names into uh Korean or
translation
foreign
[Music]
hey me dude
chat what is this
I am more chicken
[Music]
say that
I refuse no
thank you cake I thought you were being
nice to me recently and now you want me
to say that
you've you've earned my trust and now
you destroyed it
you got a kiss though
soon
Fox spicy
foreign
[Music]
I think we're done yeah
thank you everyone for today I had a lot
of fun and
um
so the Minecraft uh sorry I will not do
it today
um
no Minecraft today mommy will be mad at
me though because she sent me a list of
what I should do in the Minecraft stream
today to prepare like resources Mommy
it's okay I can maybe do it privately
too
she wants me to get a ton of
resources for
um houses that we are gonna build for
Phoenix 10 because
um the thing is um like nothing went bad
or so during the collab that we did with
my Mommy it's all good but after we
connect the two servers which still I
think will take a while because hello
Ian we are slow
um but after that happens I was told
that my mom probably can't come onto the
server anymore
so I want to do the Phoenix 10 stuff and
all that before that
uh yeah and afterwards we can't play on
our server anymore but I mean we could
still do stuff like I don't know one
block of Minecraft and all that
um in the future
yeah yeah I think I don't know I don't
know exactly why but I was told that
probably gonna be difficult
from the side of the Japanese management
yeah after connecting the servers so
yeah we're gonna do the Phoenix and
stuff rather soon I was I wasn't
originally planning on making it so
early but
rap sooner than later
and then well we don't we can't do the
whole renovation we'll just make a few
houses and then I'll do the rest on my
own time
yeah we can still do stuff together just
not on that server but I know it was
funny because it wasn't the Halloween
server and because she could like also
meet the other girls and stuff like that
so it's a bit sad but it's okay
it's okay we're gonna do
um something together
very soon either next week or the week
after we will see
yeah
we want more Mama Tony I understand yeah
dming Omega right now
maybe in the future you can try hardcore
with Mommy on a private server that's an
interesting idea yeah
I could consider that but we will see
so I'll probably make the schedule
uh afterwards after I went to my Island
meeting and had some actual food
I hope you had fun today
um
[Music]
thank you
down
[Music]
thank you