e
[Music]
home fun no I'm all alone on the
server but I know I won't be the only
one playing today I know that I won't
be because some people already have
their streams up my server
now man these things are really
terrifying I would be scared which one
is the worst I think the corks
the cork screw seems the most gruesome
but I also feel
like it might not Pierce you well it
does Pierce you though because of my my
punching
skills all three
middle I guess there's scissors on the
inside
right they're all they're all gruesome
every time I log in I expect like the
stuff to be done cooking cuzz I forget
that the server does not run on its
own it will it will not be running while
we are not
here I'm
[Music]
hungry should I eat this old sham
sandwich somebody said that these are
not really me to be food but what what
else are they are they for if not food I
won't get
sick somebody's got to eat
them food 15 looks like food to
me that's how we all end up with dis
Terry in the in the
zombie
apocalypse kiaha
she's talking to her chat I think but
look her sock puppet is
there looks mostly
edible what was I doing I was going to
try to make duct
tape I remember now
also it's done right this is
done I said also like I had something to
say but I don't think I
do farming I
guess but like I logged off last night
and everything is exactly the same as it
as it is now none of my crops have
[Music]
grown more do collectors I'm kind of
broke well probably we'll do more quests
today
anyway I need another
Ice
Cube and whatever this is I haven't seen
that in the stores I don't
think punch some grass I
guess one my fists are for I have not
discovered anything in this world that
cannot be solved by
punching
um hook some of those
I feel like I should have more
food than what I have oh the blueberry
pies are pretty good 45
food how are these 50 wait the staked
potato meals are actually
good I don't know why I have two stacks
of them I thought they would
be much worse than the the
stew I guess they don't give you like
water
[Music]
probably but pic of find dining being
worse than stew steak and potato meal is
the Pinnacle of fine dining look these
look like like fries to
me I don't know which I guess is fine oh
hello hi hi hi again there you are hi
how you doing I'm good I'm excited for
another day you're EX
[Music]
hi I think we're
back that was weird that was the first
time that that's happened my computer is
usually so stable ever since I upgraded
it right I can't I can't recall another
time where like like YouTube has had
problems but my computer rarely
explodes like that did it blue screen
event no I think it was I don't know
what happened like OBS crashed and then
my game crashed and everything crashed
but we're back okay let me go join then
when did I last restart it's off 90% no
like 99% of the time I turn it off
whenever I'm not
streaming so it's almost always off well
I guess I stream how much do I
stream
1% is that too small why don't I sleep a
lot I don't stream I don't stream that
many hours in a
week
5% maybe so the computer is off well
does the computer even know when it's
off does it experience time passing okay
sorry we're getting we're getting too
deep now I'm just thinking like my
computer's experience it must feel like
it's always on right well I don't know
you don't feel like you're always
awake do you feel like you're always
awake cuz whenever you're experiencing
ing the world but not really cuz you
have dreams and usually when I sleep if
I sleep 8 hours I feel like I slept 8
hours you know you know it doesn't feel
like I was awake just moments ago
exactly it's not like when you're
getting a surgery and you you
go you you go completely unconscious and
then the next moment it feels like a
Time skip that's not really how sleeping
feels anyway
let's go
back hello hello the quest hello take me
with you oh okay okay we're just doing
I'm just doing one quest with bi now you
can join us but I won't be questing the
whole
time I think um there's a there's a
there's my tier three to the north
that's very close to the house if you
got to do that one to the North oh yeah
true uh we can pick fun up on the way
okay oh you're already going towards
mine huh yeah wait I think our bike
should still our mini bike should still
be there for now oh should I
bring yeah I took the wrong mini
bik I was should still be
there yeah it's okay I can pick you up
mine have the
seat oh okay so I'm trying to figure out
my
inventory D DC oh you D no oh no what's
happening today not again
[Music]
Happ nah unbelievable oh
no it better behave during the the H
night I know
yeah well well at least you girls can
hear me right now so let me actually um
bring up something for today's
raid I think one thing that would be
really good to focus on because in this
raid oh you cut out
uhoh uhoh
[Music]
uh-oh Mama I outside the door with the
seat warm and okay for you when ready
I'm trying to fix my inventory okay no
problem no oh welcome back you you cut
off ah you cut I cut off oh God I wonder
where I cut uh-oh uh-oh
uh-oh oh here oh is locked locked uh I
can't get in
uh what the bike I made is is locked oh
okay no the one sorry the one be boo
she's picking me
up kiaha
[Music]
kah
uhoh what's going on today they don't
want us to play today
[Music]
it will surely stab stabilize soon I
believe I believe I was saying I think
we should focus on Moes not on spikes
because did you see how yesterday during
the digging Quest everybody was falling
in and that was so
op that's true that is true yeah yeah
yeah and now the zombies can probably at
this level really easily destroy our
spikes especially the vomiting
guys
so you want to loot this house while we
wait for kiaha yes okay can we fight the
boar is the boar still
dead where is the Bo um I think it's in
here it's probably still dead though I
think
a are we back in stream okay okay why we
make Moes and then put spikes at the
bottom of the mo oh wait is this the is
this the quest we have a quest for the
bo oh good then will respawn when we
start the quest oh I
think okay I think it's
stabilized knocking on
wood oh there's stuff here
okay I'm coming back into the game
[Music]
hopefully I have a book for
you thank you
ooh armor piercing round thank you o you
don't use Point 44 ammo I do I willar
when I make my uh Magnum gun I just
haven't made the gun yet thank
you so the board is not down here it's
supposed to be down here oh yeah it
hasn't respawned it'll probably respawn
when I start the class
yes okay okay I'm getting in I'm getting
in I'm I'm coming okay I'm back
[Music]
toing let me
in both okay there we
go wait isn't the isn't the raid
starting like really soon no I think we
have one more day 28 it's 28 28 yeah at
10: p.m. so okay it's the divisible by
seven right so yeah but one thing in
order for the Moes to really be useful
for us we have to kind of stand behind
the modes so I know fa you like to
really go out there I'm going out there
I'm really strong I fought a
bear all on my own she's confident she's
confident yeah okay I'll stay behind and
then try to shoot them while standing
behind yeah we'll we'll cover we'll
cover your backside
okay where's my
bike where did my bike
go the poor pigs maybe it was a
mirage my bike was a mirage it's gone oh
P we didn't take it didn't we no that
was mine this is weird are you girls on
to separate bikes right now or just one
just just
boys shouldn't it show up up
there that's so weird I guess I got to
walk home and pick up another bike oh no
wait you don't see the icon anywhere no
oh
actually uhoh weird things are a foot
today yeah mhm oh conspiracy
there was another there was another
yellow bike uh at the at the mini bike
at the at the house yeah I think the
yellow one is our f a w
bike yeah I know I was driving there
but I wonder if something happened while
you DC a well chat is saying I can still
walk towards where I like got kicked out
of the game May the bike is there even
though it doesn't show up on my
navigation
okay also so fin you weren't there but
I'm going to try before the raid to get
bioo better armor and if you have some
really low level Parts ideally I'd want
to improve your armor
too my the
only are level one okay that's yeah
we'll improve that for sure especially
if you're going to go to the front front
lines I'm strong though as long as I
have beer to drink that's all I needan
just give it the beer she'll be fine
junking fist all the way exactly it
gives me 300% power woo damn and you
have that perk that negates the effect
right that's
crazy by
why doesn't it show it on the on the big
map I put a lot of resources into that
bike why does the map not show it to me
I'm so
rude I think I was already kind
of in this
area like in
between oh oh zombie hello
it was on the
road I was what do you mean it was on
the
road was I following this I wasn't
following a road I was just going
through here
[Music]
right
you okay I'll go back and look around
you want to go to the house across the
street final yeah and resty okay let's
go oh I think I I killed the Boors in
here
too yesterday
ah ah you girls are not in the party
right now oh we are I'll let me add you
you you uh left when you disconnected
[Music]
okay okay
lots of corn
seeds corn I feel like potatoes are
better you can make steak and potatoes
yeah I saw the the stack looks so good
maybe instantly
hungry I know I feel like we go through
the food so
fast I really want to level up enough
that I can make the Sham
stew I have
infinite Shams
to and not here why would it be here CH
are you one guying me not the one
guy I'm so slow my stamina
h i mean it won't re uh despawn right so
maybe just for now I'll go get the the
other bike you could put a marker on
your map where it's where it was so you
can come back later
yeah not sure where it really was but
yeah I know the rough
area okay I'm going to walk back and get
the other bike okay okay unless I
accidentally find the other
bike stamina I want more
stamina it doesn't despawn
okay yeah I was near to Burnt
Forest oh well
we'll find it one day yeah one day it
just be traveling the road and boom
there it is hopefully hopefully cuz it
was going to be someone else's
bike um by the way generally what I
think we should collect before the raid
is uh ammo and maybe more repair
kits yeah I'm going to spam while you
guys fortify or something I'm going to
spam quest for ammo for all for all of
us and ammo parts so I can make ammo
Parts yeah yeah yeah and also uh we were
thinking in my chat before we started
today uh it might be good to make
turrets and I think people weren't you
kind of like starting to learn that
stuff no I'm
explosive I think I'm learning turrets
but I'm really far off I think is that
robotics I think so I think it is
robotics yeah I need 51 and I'm at
16 oh okay all wait where am I going I'm
going to go towards you girls now okay
my quest is up only two at the quest
Point coming okay so maybe no turrets
this time then unless we find a lot more
magazines I have I have explosives
though so that will help yeah indeed
okay I have fists so that'll yeah
that'll help definitely
we'll see oh are we
doing oh B and bears BS Bob's BS yes
yeah oh we're going to fight the bo
again ah speaking of fighting fa
up there you go I got these for
you
okay is is it is the staring Point
okay oh we got to go we got to go to the
library before the rage
F the library the one I went to the
library mhm wait did you find a new one
no the one that you found oh okay we can
go I think I got well I don't know how
much is left how long does it take to
respawn probably long iawn after the
raain yeah probably over here hop the
fence I can't hop that fence oh you
can't so
easy I'm I'm chunky
okay ready I've got ammo for both of
[Music]
you thank you also have nerd
boots anyone wants nerd boots let me see
if they're better um no they're not
better I'll drop them
we could bring them home and then give
them to someone else like if somebody
joins us tomorrow also without
armor okay clay here we go slay all the
piggies oh
no po
p do we need more meat should we get
their meat well always always have more
meat handy okay I'm going to get the
meat and the lever oh yeah
lever
bacon there's a lot of
corpses in
[Music]
here make cows fat again cattle
feed why is this going so slow
oh hello piggy I'm
sorry are you already
upstairs I am in the middle
FL po
pigs
piggy defenseless pigs
oh hello
sir it's so dark but it's like not dark
enough that I want to activate my night
vision you have night vision oh night is
actually really nice here I've been
using
it yeah it's all right I just don't like
the oal
shape
ah bothers me I want to see the whole
screen
oh with my fire it's not too bad
yeah oh yeah remember curtains and stuff
curtains and
toilets everything is
important mattresses I
suppose sideways egg Vision it do be egg
Vision huh
oh wait we have to look for supplies too
yeah oh
realize ah chemistry session did
somebody open it up and was something
inside or what was inside I don't
remember I heard that the chemistry
stations they sometimes have a really
valuable item I think it was like acid
or so oh should I wrench it okay let's
Wrench It
okay ooh steel and forged ingots good
good okay
okay
oo oh
okay I can't find my
thing is it upstairs perhaps it might be
mine I think is on the third floor
oh no it says it's
downstairs oh I wonder if it's like
where the where Grace is Grace is at the
bo yeah that's the big Bo no will they
force us to go
there I say no it's easy now you want to
go there anyway huh yeah we got this she
want to test her fish I already killed
the boar One V one wow it's easy
we've grown so much
yeah ooh
ooh what is this more
Bo good
job through the wall I feel bad they run
away from me I
know it's sad but we need the food I
guess
oh there is another
[Music]
room I think my satel is in
there I haven't really paid attention to
mine um it's probably not there but I'm
going to take your
path it was an unlocked
door maybe we could have come here
without breaking the walls
maybe maybe it's on the
[Music]
Roof oh mine's here miss I I hear a his
where is
he are they on the ro oh they
there
oh maybe we yeah maybe we have to go to
Grace because yeah mine's like farther
away I'm too stupid to figure these out
where is mine does it show on the big
map um no oh is it the red dots no those
are the
zombies it's probably in the basement
huh yeah I see my compass but do you
really think I understand that when it's
moving does it have an arrow at the top
or bottom
[Music]
uh bottom and it's below you oh I didn't
realize there was an arrow
there yes oh another chemistry station
oh the super corn super yeah the super
corn is
back there I hear hising but don't see
oh yeah they're down with me
I'm busy can you guys leave me
alone stay down oh this is that type of
puzzle that I
hate there's a puzzle puzzle that you
hate it's a a light
puzzle you know the puzzles where you
push something and then like the two
buttons next to it oh I love flip on or
off you love those I love those
I hate
those I'm so bad at
them okay how to get down fa can you
show me how to get down uh down yeah I'm
not sure we can we can look
around I only know how to get to Grace
from the
outside come back where to where you
just uh the stairs look at this the just
see this picture oh my gosh the cat is
photo bombing the
dog cute so cute that's a good one the
best one yet I think so too 10 out of 10
I like this picture can relate yeah can
you get the gra
from here like this
house M well we can go from the outside
we know where the exit was yeah I think
it might be locked though
yeah it's locked oh it's locked from the
outside yeah okay wait oh wait um okay
oh what if I just dig down
ah you surprised me I'm just going to
maybe dig down from
here oh yeah my satula is right there oh
oh on the ground
ah easy yeah ah wait
spes wait is it this way oh but it's
locked I think it's oh it is it is on
this
level oh metal
spikes welcome welcome breaking the
walls there's no point putting a metal
gate if your walls are going to be so
flimsy this one isn't that flimsy a
I don't think I'll get through it what
about just next to it just goes over
here ow spikes oh wait there oh those
are
spikes yeah when the door is too much to
get through just break the wall that's
right next to
it let's you guys going down oh yeah
wait there's spikes that's scary yeah I
fell into one
Hur hi almost there almost there my
Satchel is definitely
there come
on I'm out of stamina ow
[Music]
oh the stairs are
here ah did you
[Laughter]
find it was easier like this for
me can't orientate myself all right
going to BR force it okay I found mine I
found
it mine should be I don't know where
might
is oh oh that was mine too okay I'm done
really yeah we still have to clear the
right oh does that include the bo
there's a there's a orange dot that says
to the distance that says below that
might be I'm assuming that's it we can
take her oh there's a there's a oh
there's a thing here oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah we went there
before that's where you get to the boore
oh it's kind of crazy in
here oh
yeah ammo
[Music]
fertilizer oh
nice okay I want to eat some more food
you need food I have food
H I'll survive a while longer ah I see
her I won't engage yet I'll let the Tank
come tank I'm really slow right
now I'm very
cucumber
uh-oh can't run away from the board that
fast hold on let me sneak attack her
once since she's I'll get the bonus for
that
[Music]
oh ah okay never mind she woke up she
woke
up she already dead oh no oh stealing
board easy easy
easy what's inside some knife book some
armor part I'll let you guys look at
this uh I will take the ammo I will take
knif
that's so different from before from the
first try we're strong have faith B your
outfit I might take that Medium
armor okay here you go there's some ammo
for
you yeah okay
nice well then I'm already cucumber uh
me too we should go and drop stuff off
yeah and maybe just one more Quest and
then I'll go prepare armor and stuff
yeah I guess we should reinforce the
base yeah maybe make a few more Moes if
possible let's get out of
here yeah we could go to the bookstore I
feel like I got a lot of the books
though I mean maybe there's more
in like a basement or something but it's
pretty far away is the
thing
true feel like that might lose us a lot
of time
yeah I need to craft the better shovel
go like after the raid everything will
respawn I'm so slow let's go
oh shamway foods and Savage country seal
chipping
gra come on lock do your
stuff let's see
o does somebody want to take these
things in the weapon
bag it's a scope and Knuckles
mod oh I want the knuckles I thought so
do you want night vision yes okay here
you
go thank
you where is these polymer string mode I
can only have one
my my water you're going to just switch
them out you know combat use night
vision how do you use is the night
vision
F
oh
cool thank
[Music]
you oh Chad is it better than one of
these worth
replacing
[Music]
oh let's look at it later chat okay
shall we can we go to the the one that
Wawa had uh okay it's a little bit we
drop stuff off at home first it's it's
kind of on the we can stop there for
sure okay where was the bike there
okay I'm so
full it's okay we have mini
and they don't take stamina can you
drive the bike over to me and pick me up
I'm driving
it hold on I'm coming
mama here you go thank
[Music]
you this door is a
little
thin
narrow we get let do it there we
go okay I'm heading ahead good for you
we're going home
first the Nerds the
Nerds I'm no longer nerdy my ex ping oh
no she outgrew us She nor what level are
you
anyway
I'm wait where do you see that again
level 28 28 okay yeah I'm 26 oh B's
29 wow I've been killing
things uh oh yeah I came
[Music]
for dropping
off oh I got so much meat from the pigs
I
know me
too okay maybe some
stuff what is this fort bites damage
mitigation mitigation does that mean I
get less damage yes potentially yes Fort
bite Fort bite fortnite for
night I think I'll use one of these for
the P
night sharp maybe I should make a repair
kit there there's a lot in one of the
chests there's like six yeah okay maybe
I don't need to make one then what
[Music]
okay I'm ready I think to go to the next
one okay okay
[Music]
can I use those guys to like wrench the
electrical
things seems like I might be able
to why is this stuff in here anyway
oh we have an armor chest oops I was yes
I'm not
organiz it's new it's new ah okay might
not remember cuz it's
new it's
for what uh connecting traps and turrets
to power sources is is this bottom uh
storage crate FL there's six repair kits
if you need one oh I wish just going to
bring some in case I think one is enough
for me for now
same or
two where do the bones
gol my oh
okay
okay connect lights power door okay for
now then I don't think we need
that can I wrench this
yes
oh of the
crops F farmer back farmer FAA farmer
Fara it's not much but it's honest
work I have just sold out
microwave in our um fridge online
secondhand
so we have no more of
that I'm sure we'll be fine without
yeah spending hours in front of the
microwave watching it turn my favorite
pastime it wasn't working
anyway I think we're ready I'm ready I'm
ready f
get on my bike okay you must are we
going to the tier 2 infestation one yes
it's a bit far but I want to get that
out of my
system let's go R go we still have tier
one clears too oh when will we get to
those maybe once when you're really
bored for some reason and rather do a
tier one quest which will never
happen but we so
fast I love not having to
drive can just look at my inventory
should I start an Uber business you
should what is that what do they call
your passenger princess I
am oh sorry
oops you can stay on the bike even if I
got off interesting oh am I on the bike
did you get back on I got off by
accident uh I hope this road will lead
us there sure
surely oh yeah we're
close I love how my arms are around your
waist it's
ticklish she's tickling me I can't
ah can't can't drive like that stop
tickling me f where are wait actually
this is not a good
path oh this this is not the place yeah
this kind of a dead end uh H the road
ends
here maybe we just power up the
hill I'm doing it I'm powering up the
hill Oh
oh okay I'll try to from here might be
good do your
best come on it's
working going to catch up come on come
on oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah yeah I also
there oh no oh
noch we're
vertical can you push us it worked
just just uh just trying really just
could pick up my bike for a few meters
I'm pushing get back on get back on it's
time to go
down oh gosh it's like a roller
coaster oh ow I'm hurt that's why uhoh
all right foreshadowing I'm a little
scared I'll be careful I I'll get go
I'll go off the gas now and I'll just
let it okay okay
come on come on come on come on come on
come on come on back
up all right I feel like my game wants
to crash so bad oh no it wants you to
crash with the bike or the game itself
wants to no I feel like the game itself
wants to crash so bad cuz we're doing
illegal physics things okay I made it
wao this is
spooky Oo we made it two oh
yeah does he have any
resources he does I can make some sham
out of this
sh oh this guy
too well let me just get this car
wrenched and
then we can
start yummy car materials Yum Yum Yum
Yum yippee
my inventory is already filling
up oh I've got I we brought a lot of
food just in case let's
go what do we have
here no interesting
oh
oh oh feel like I can get met from this
to a d collect yeah can we have it oh
it's destroy oh watch out behind you can
we watch out watch
out oh
nice
oh put stff in oh the mini bike has
storage
huh they have a big
maybe just a small one but better than
nothing
[Music]
yeah what is my holy hammer called I
will give it a name huh I
I
easy
stadio station
oh the keys are here keys keys we found
I've never found keys in any never
before no I didn't know there were
actual keys but makes
sense I'm rarely fighting in these
quests it seems I'm always wrenching
things there's Air Supply draw will this
hurt me no
[Music]
it's kind of
far they usually hang on the wall oh 400
me there's a roof yeah there's upstairs
there's a
ladder no you jump right on to
no no
[Applause]
you guys are so
funny zombies scare me no
more isn't spooky at
all oh did we finish it yeah oh we did I
feel like there's more to explore and
more to wrench oh I got armor crafting
kit oh god oh I think I'm done with that
level maximum level so you can use that
oh no the armor crafting kit oh that
make okay let's go let's go oh here's
here's some ammo for you and I'm going
to drop the armor crafting kids you can
hold on to them oh there's ammo for both
of you in
there invested
[Music]
cash invested cash in here too ammo
clean my cash thank you
[Music]
clear out your
cash
okay I guess if there's nothing else
interesting we could
go oh a
pumpkin pumpkin what the katana the
Callie mentioned Katana Katana Katana
saw Katana oh that thing the tempered
blad SK
itic
oh increases block
damage do the keys work only for one
specific door or for every uh lock door
cuz I had I found the key in the bo
house and it opened the board cage so I
think it
it's
okay oh do you want to get the a drop
yeah we should it's not too far right
okay oh I don't know if they're even
good I think I will go back home and see
what I can start crafting okay you guys
can go home I'll just go grab it real
fast
okay actually first I'll go to the
trader but F we can go together okay to
the trader
do you want to still like get some stuff
or uh what do you mean like from here
wrench wrench
stuff maybe
this I think I need to rep my
ties now I don't think I'm like I don't
need it that urgently
oopsie uh tires I I think yeah they can
be
crafted can I get it like
this no I just got some scraps what
World level are
we oh somehow far oh you're 93 how did
you're 95 how did we I feel like it went
way up I feel like the last time I
looked it was like 60 I think it also
depends on Armor maybe cuz you guys are
wearing like high level armor or
something or maybe it's
what's mine you're 91 f is 93 I'm 66 no
you're 95 oh I'm 955 on my screen you're
95 oh on my screen it's 66 so I thought
it would be an armor difference
[Music]
but oh what's up wrong way wrong
way oh it depends on the
biome interesting I I don't even know
what that means
all me
neither we're just living our best life
yeah does that mean the raid will be
easier if we go back to the starting
location maybe oh the supply quate gave
me a bunch of books okay oh nice books
what kind of books
I'll let me
see any bar brawler level five no
Barbara trap and
B my German brain
rot yeah you know that song it was on
Tik Tok you probably saw
it yeah did you know that was
German yeah the the whole song I mean
yeah the whole song I I was trying to
learn it but it's
you should do the dance
too I want to
see wait oh is this Quest from Trader
Jen I think any any MPC can finish the
class
right can they you have to go
back we have to go to both according to
I think we have one and one and O okay
I'll try to be fast uh we can check see
if they've got anything good for sale
although I'm kind of broke right now
same I see you have to go back to J okay
okay oh but yeah speaking of Tik Tok
people I made a Tik Tok y I saw your Tik
Tok you should follow my Tik
Tok I'll follow you do I even have a Tik
Tok online yet I don't think so maybe I
should make
one he f no you you you use Tik Tok no I
look at YouTube shorts sometimes same
but you YouTube shorts is literally Tik
Tok but a few weeks late like everything
you see on YouTube shorts is just out
put that was repost from there but late
so you guys are late to the trends I'm
fine with that I tried to watch
Minecraft Parkour civilization and I
felt like I was losing brain cells and
my bones were turning to dust and I
became 8,000 years old she was like live
tweeting it last night she was watching
saw
that who was streaming it I was was live
tweeting she was watching the parkour
civilization the movie
o oh Iris I don't get it is it how what
level of irony are we on when we say
that we like Minecraft parkour civiliz
ation do we like it ironically or
unironically we like it
unironically
yes is that like a level one unironic or
like a level three unironic oh c I don't
know can you be my
GPS I got I got a motor motorcycle part
bundle no no I'm sorry wait yeah yeah
I'm sry
I wish I could have the map open while
ring icon on my map is like backwards
it's like facing the opposite way that
you're going
confusing well everybody who has Tik Tok
please follow tasi yeah follow takanashi
she's got some cool dance things thank
you yeah thank you do you think a lot of
your viewers are are like Tik Tok
users I don't know they always seem
really mad when I mention it oh no yeah
same
same I'm personally not a big fan
of no no heck no no please no no no I
see
uhoh absolutely not I feel are lying
though just to sa
face there's nothing to be also I got I
got a my
motorcycle parts box from to give you a
job wa this is a dangerous one need some
relief Trader Jen's got what you need oh
I leveled
up
yippe she's selling have you read urban
combat volume 6
fa um let me see cuz this one says armor
doesn't slow you down when in combat and
that might be good for you oh okay I'll
use it then
[Music]
yes how much money do you have
1,000 no
2,000 can you buy the
remaining uh duct tapes that she's
selling why we have duct tape at
home but not enough we always need more
we can make more we should instead buy
do collector Parts if she has it then we
can make even more duct
tape duct tape at home how much duct
tape do we have at home we don't have
that much duct tap more duct
tape yeah we have so many we have we
have bones and we have so many bones in
water so we can make glue yes yeah it's
better to buy the the do collector parts
so that we can does she have them yes
she does okay do you want me to
get a dual collector part oh water
filter is is 7,000
yeah would be good though I'm going to
get the The Gatherer at least
okay our first get I'm going to buy tarp
our first quarrel between wives about
how to spend our money we have duct tape
at home mom she has so many BS
quantity we'll make more if we it's we
need to invest our money instead of
spending it as soon as we get it then
we'll always be broke forever child I'm
going to get trauma
[Applause]
understand she doesn't she doesn't
understand because she's not in my
position I don't I need much more duct
tape than she knows she doesn't
realize no we'll be fine wait one day
we'll have so much duct tape hopefully
looking for some
healing I literally just saw her spawn
in front of me
G yipp G my third parent is
here I'm eating right we Jo call off
okay where's my
bike over there we're going to wait
don't leave I don't have a car I just
knew you find something just trying to
find my bike and then we can go to the
other Trader wait did I sell
something
no wait did I sell
something I sold the magazine back oh my
gosh I oh
no oh my gosh she scammed
me I got so distracted looking wa did
you sell something you Wen supposed to
yeah I bought a magazine and then I
tried to use it from my inventory but
that just sold it back to her
W did did was it was it Jen did you just
you distract her by distracting I see
it's okay it happens to the best of
us
oh oh no is Gigi going to be left here
yes yes no
that's what she gets for leaving us
behind
yesterday she has to walk does she even
have a bike she doesn't even have her
bike oh doesn't CeCe have her bike wait
we should kill these zombies yeah this
is
RA Action
Baby St okay
[Music]
I got I got armor piercing CU bullets
I'm going to put it in the weapon and
ammo armor piercing can you use those
with any uh uh machine gun or does the
machine gun need any any
7.62 it's just different type of bullets
so you should be able to use it
[Music]
okay well that was easy that was
easy I think we got this yeah tonight
well actually soon wait what day is it
wait we have one more day we have one
day uh I will spam quest for
[Music]
bullets okay we're going to go through
the village here but we're not stopping
for your quest
funo that's fine or should we no we
don't have time it's almost the end of
today
we really got to get
home we got to make more
modes
no I should check out if the mailbox is
refreshed could it be could it be or is
it too
early they're empty maybe after the
raid okay
uh you
need F on you you answerer I need to
control the bike was in
my my
thing what resources do we need uh maybe
iron
oh duct tape we have duct tape at home
and suing kids so but that's just
randomly in the houses I think more
cloth would be
useful cloth is like I feel like I have
a good amount now but we always need
more and also cloth is helpful for
explosives too so always use
more more Mo molds at the base so that
they fall in so a good
shovel yeah I wonder if she can make
iron or is it iron or Steel
um wait I'm starving um I think food
don't star it's okay driving first so
much
food driving comes
first K has level you should
good I'm going to make some both good
water since we have a lot of water now
too oh yeah please
please are you where are you B boo I'm
at the house oh we should save some
water for glue though yeah I want make
so many see we have to share the water
for different things Faun well that's
that's why we need the water upgrade
parts so we could get more water I put I
put a water upgrade part in the in one
of the things so one of them has some
upgrade I'm going to make a third one
okay a third do collector
mhm okay you getting off you don't want
to give the quest back oh I guess I
do it's dangerous to get off while I'm
high speed driving F you're right you're
right my server lagged a little bit it
looked like you were slowing down no no
oh we don't have
chisan yellow ones or the red ones the
red ones we need more red ones for me to
make the
oh I can get a bunch
okay make sure to rch
cars here we
are wrecked we are so
back can you welcome us back friendly
we're still coming back to you even even
after we have other
Traders I think he'll still be
[Music]
mean I don't know about these rewards
could give these two
no I have collected 56
crysanthemum oh that's
useful what's
[\h__\h] it's a flower yeah
M I'm very
slow oh
wrong
spending all my
money not on duct tape I
hope no no he he didn't have any duct
tape
sadly food please fun
yes take take this pumpkin
pie
pie congratulations here's your reward
sucker I don't need this I would like to
confess something I actually don't like
pumpkin pie really yeah it's so good I
prefer like apple Apple's good too yeah
yeah me too weoo have you read pistol P
Volume 2 um where do I check your
inventory in the books
tab
inventory definitely that
way I think I've never had pumpkin pie
IRL before never mhm you should try
it I don't think I ever I'm not too big
on pump the pumpkin spice I'm not a
pumpkin spice girly dang me neither
really I love pumpkin
spice Pistol Pete which one volume two
no I have not okay I'll get it for you I
didn't ditch just looking for the other
bike in the meantime oh you can ditch me
I can walk home it's
fine bike bike bike bike bikee
carp but I can't afford it it can't just
be gone maybe
they glitched out my bike out of this
world and they won't give it back to me
hobo stew hobo
stew yum y I don't know what that
is oh no I should have bought here wait
I can still buy one here it shows my
bicycle on the compass but it doesn't
show the other the
[Music]
bike
rude very
rude are you still at the trador I'm
done okay I might pick you up
no I'm just going to be punching
flowers okay wait I want to Ranch car
really
quick no problem oh no ah my game
crashed I think that was just a crash
not internet oh okay that's good it was
just there oh my I passed my bike oh
really they like they don't want you to
have the
bike game boy are you doing this to
me okay well took the say
[Music]
I'll be
back in a moment I'm going to get that
bike actually fa do you see the you
don't see the bike on the map do you the
one we were driving around
with yay I don't think I see anything
okay okay no problem can you guys see my
old bike my regular bicycle
[Music]
H okay okay okay okay okay game is
opening
up got a lot of
stuff I'm going to make so much duct
tape D has three books of furious fist
by the way
I tried to buy one and I accidentally
sold it back to her oh no oh that's a
big loss of money huh I know she sold it
for me to me for 300 and bought it back
for 20 don't let her her good looks and
charm fool you she's as ruthless as all
the rest of the
traitor
ah is it possible to like K just in
theory is it possible to kill the
traitors I wonder cuz they have like a
skull rating right o the last boss are
the traitors maybe maybe when when we're
done with the tomorrow we can
check that's scary
though I don't want to ruin our our
whole game what if we can't go back
anymore because we've ruined it killing
the traitors
true okay and can I get a party invite
again oh
[Music]
yes where did you guys see
it the spike was
here we have so many bones
do we have gas cans at
home uh
uh maybe I think we out of them because
I filled all the bikes up as much as I
could I have eight of
them I found the bike oh
good oh it's not bad okay you're never
leaving me
again it's weird that the icon didn't
show up for you yeah don't know why okay
I'm coming
home preparation time oh oh we really
only have like one day left yeah 24
hours I bet I can just punch them
anyway I I'll make you better armor what
should I prioritize uh your gloves right
Bon um no no no I have good gloves it's
my oh my hat in my chest ah your hat and
your chest and you want the same set I
would assume right yes okay and then for
beo I wanted to first of all make gloves
preacher gloves I think yes please
okay well I'm going to go get cooking
going to go
cooking let her
cook we have a bit of cloth
now oh me too me too I think cloth is
like okay now in terms of yeah ever
since we started destroying everyone's
curtains yeah
[Music]
uh what was it what was it preacher
gloves preacher gloves maybe I level
[Music]
five my delicate hands full of
knives oh this despite all the punting
they're still super smooth and nonous
yes I don't know how you do it what
moisturizer do you
use I'm in BR
moisturizer what was for an infect
infections what
was honey honey and antibiotics there's
antibiotics at the house and
honey should honey only work uh uh for a
specific percentage 5% honey Works 5% at
a time awesome so it'll still work if
you're high percent it just takes away
5% at a
time
okay I need to ask KY too KY are you
coming to VC
soon he's num nomy
I want to num nom too
okay maybe I can make a Max
Level but maybe I should be more careful
oh do I have to run all the way to the
pond to drink can I just drink water at
home yeah just drink water this
expensive though I could just go to the
pond and drink
I don't
know you you've been working hard to get
us water I feel like you deserve a nice
sip
sip without making to our time is
precious okay every second wasted is a
second closer to the horde so don't
waste your
time so what about the duct tape do we
have more duct tape at
home definitely we can
yeah I appreciate a couple more duct
tapes I'm on
it wait I can make a couple
too just free yeah if we have more glue
I can do we have more
glue um we can make glue we can make
glue with the water
this how much water do we have I'll make
glue okay
I need to save some water to make
food here I'm putting another do
collector
out guys what level should I make it in
cuz that already takes even on level
five it takes five armor crafting
kits oh my internet died oh no but I
didn't get kicked oh
interesting oh we're back okay that was
just a short Maybe YouTube issue or OBS
only
okay
perhaps I'll make I'll make I'll
make I'm going to let zombies kill me
don't be alarmed I want to be full
health for my quest okay
what's doing
kids
damn um what was that uh fun uh you said
hat and
shoes no hat and
chest
[Music]
okay I'll just let's make the maximum
now
or yeah with the
materials oh I'm still infected oh wow
okay second to last it doesn't matter
we're going to do this again
sometime and then I have to continue
with the stuff I have
yeah the steel the steel I even bought
extra
[Music]
steel will
be
okay
okay uh but then I probably can't make a
new
yeah cuz I'm out of armor crafting kits
oh well for
now
seems I don't need to make I have so
many corn seeds
[Music]
already I can't make beer for a long
time cuz I need the chemistry station or
something
oh really going to be expensive
[Applause]
yeah but that's okay I have I have
enough for
now yes look at
this I'm out of armor kits
now thank you for this maximum
level so that should help I don't think
I can improve your helmet uh but that's
okay yeah and I got the gloves thank
you let me know when you're home bioo
okay I'm just doing one
class my own armor is okay it's okay oh
I can't make potato seeds
yet wish I could make a few more armor
kits she has duct
tape for
one
wow duct
tape oh the shovels are
expensive I can't too stupid to type I
can't type
H I pressed some weird stuff
again oh okay is hobo still really
good I don't know what's it made of you
don't want to know don't ask questions
you don't want to know the answer
to it's the healthiest ingredient I for
sure um what's that sound wo wo wo wo oh
was that a
tree I put some glue in your
chest oh a little bit thank you and
cloth glue
glue free glue how much I can make free
duct tip with free glue
[Music]
oh um everything needs water of course
oh but I'm lacking sewing kits
now and seing kits we can't make
ourselves
[Music]
only had s kids maybe the old house
still has some sing
kits oh can we not craft
those no I guess
[Music]
not
ah
there's some nice minor boots and gloves
for you in the armor
chest in your
house I think cuz
her her equipment is probably also not
the best so that
should I mean it's for mining but it's
um decent better than
nothing the nerd boots look
funny okay I'm going to
check out the old
house okay
okay and pray
for S
kits they will always be rare items the
rate of savage country house cuz they
usually got py yeah I did get a few ones
from the one
house oh I'm going the wrong
way maybe I'll check over
here I'm going to go raid a house okay
good
luck thank you you got it need that I'm
scared don't be scared you're strong I
don't know you're
brave
okay I believe in you in your words they
better be true if I die then I will cry
yes I got gimly and my machine
gun it's just with
gimly it's taking up my stamina so
fast it's kind of bad so I'll use my
machine gun I love how you call it gimy
yeah best dwarf
ever oh oh this doesn't really look like
it would have seing kids
face the Bears D free I don't like that
advertisement hi hi
hello I is your meal yummy it's so hard
to play and eat
though don't get don't get crumbs on
your keyboard what are you doing the
ants the
ants I'm summoning them
no please ants come eat my keyboard
it's not the place I was thinking
[Music]
of are we going to be fortifying
today well a little
bit the thing is like spikes might not
be so useful anymore because we're going
to get probably more of the vomit guys
now and they destroy the spikes
easily um so rather than that I was
thinking our strategy should be modes so
that they fall into the holes they fall
into those pretty easily and they don't
seem to be able to get out of them so we
just got to lead them into the H SP I'm
thinking we spikes yeah spikes in the
modes best
Strat um so yeah we already have some
modes but maybe adding another row would
or like filling up the areas where
there's no modes okay
[Music]
okay I'm going to see around
here maybe this
one do have a raing oh it has a rating e
PA what's your experience with two two
skulls houses easy easy easy do you need
help though I can help no all
I've got some more glue for you that's
nice good to hear not not much
H better than
nothing six Ste yeah
wow
nice G are you streaming no I'm just
here mhm taking a good time getting
trees nothing
else I can't use any of these bicycles I
can't unlock them
oh and the bicycles or the
bikes none of them none of them not a
single one but I unlocked them maybe I
have to unlock them every time the
bicycles yeah
bicycle I think they auto lock because I
had to unlock mine when I didn't
before suing kids suing
kids
um I'll unlock it for you when I'm back
you can you can use
mine my God thank you for letting me use
your bite it's so green mhm she has so
such a little quality on her she
okay do you want a repair kit I'm scared
of hurting her even further I think we
should have repair kids
somewhere think I saw you I see one I'll
repair her I'll go fix her right up she
can fix her I'll fix
her that's so nice of you to return my
bike with a full tank of
gas all by myself I feel so powerful
I knew she was alive just
sleeping but I had a
feeling yeah head shots definitely make
things
easier
microwave okay I mean we're we're
cooking we're cooking I'm got cooking
magazines I really want to get to the
Sham stew
[Music]
sounds
delicious I think I'm far though am I
far heit fish
tacos oh my God fish tacos I can't make
them yet maybe someday you wanted you
wanted seing kits right yeah okay I'll
bring them
[Music]
why so noise oh dog no not dog you
sounded like a
dog
spicy okay I'm gaining
confidence good you should be confident
yeah thank you so synced up girls
so would you guys ever possibly need
like more
wood I think okay for
now you could make more spes though the
um always good to make more spikes even
if they can be destroyed they will be a
line of defense yeah yeah yeah yeah this
stack and can I how come I can't use
armor plating
mods they I I've noticed that I cannot
use them on my chest but I can use them
on for example the feet I think oh
really yeah damn oh I can't use them on
either oh well they don't go on heavy
armor what works on heavy armor oh
probably different plating the heavy
plating I think there's particular
plating for it
oh no can't put any armor mods onto
heavy maybe
really maybe it's already strong enough
without we'll see maybe that's the
tradeoff
no I'm crafting 400 spikes don't worry
nice let's put them in that moat yeah
yeah yeah
yeah what is this okay
I never know what any of the modifiers
are
for yeah me too oh I can do customized
[Music]
spinnings I think I'll go to the next
house find n
hopefully how many swing cats are you
girls carrying around if right
now the hobo stew is good but what's it
made out of no don't worry about what
it's made
of what's inside our hobo can I have can
I have the nutritional facts please I'm
watching my
sodium B um 2,000 mg of sodium wow per
serving it's highly nutrious yeah
o machine gun
parts I don't have any
vehicles to
use can you unlock the stuff at
home
so why are they locked again I unlocked
all of them yesterday
I think I think they auto lock I think
yeah okay I I I'll come home I'm not
that
far every time you pick one up or use
them they lock
oh oh ah so each time a different person
uses it it blcks for them I
guess oh
ah they belong to the person that sets
it down makes
sense I guess today uh we have enough
bikes for everybody to have their own
maybe fauna can use the Cali bike or so
the golf bike okay golfa uses golf
bike makes sense is this one right okay
and luck try it thank you oh it has like
no fuel oh I can add some I think I have
some this person returned this car with
no
gas it has not that much fuel can you
unlock a bike I'll just take a bike and
no wait I have I have more fuel I have
more fuel a bike is good enough for me
save the environment everyone I don't
think the environment needs to be
saving we have to thank you it's about
Reviving the environment and yeah and
we'll die next if we don't save the
[Music]
environment I'm I'm
I'm come
on what am I
lacking another couple of ceing
kits I have two but I'm far away
okay still have your gloves back yeah
I'm heading back now okay
yeah when should we start
fortifying maybe around early
afternoon
okay just put these in I have time
yeah to do stuff like kill bears
yeah beep those
Bears I guess I could go back to the
bookstore
we could go after
though be going to find all the
bookstores I think they can be in in
many
biomes yeah they seem like a good find
yeah have you been in the biome with all
the
special little things the special
zombies special zombies all the throwing
up zombies spawn
in there yeah the desert the desert
spawns a lot of throw up the ones if you
want if you want a real challenge FAA go
to go north into the snow there's a lot
of yeah that's where I was scary
creatures I killed the bear that's where
the book St
is that was the Bear's bookstore well
it's my bookstore
now never learn ever again Action
[Music]
Now Finders
Keepers that bear was going after his
Masters and you just ruined his
education so be it
then okay I think I'll go back to the
house one more time
oh oh where are you guys
going is there party that I wasn't I'm
just soloing some stuff oh no no you
zombies around their house
or walking
around looking for something to
raid maybe they're telling us that we
should
not be so easygoing the day has
arrived yeah they're kind of right they
are right it's the day
do oh yeah let me unlock the other Bo
okay why am I why am I so slow okay o oh
two forg ah
heads o some
shouldn't we have
[Music]
another they're so loud
zombies someone have to keep some Manns
I know can't even get any peace and
quiet even win the zombie apocalypse I
thought that would help I
know gy if you want uh there's
an unlocked bicycle or do you at least
have a bicycle I took faas she she lent
me hers okay I thought I have another
mini bike
but I don't know where it
went but we do have some seat modifier
thingies on the on some of the mini
bikes so we can ride together
yay I they so cute I know I didn't
realize the mini bike had so much more
storage this is so good
really I got to check it out too
how about this
[Music]
house just going to raid one more house
and then I should maybe be able to
make a new armor oh yeah giggy how's uh
can you tell me what level your armor
pieces are um a bad feeling for yours I
took I have an Assassin outfit of level
one and cool sunglasses of level one but
I took the mining things that are level
four um wait your chest piece is level
one yeah what they going do kill me I'll
make you a
different is there a specific set you're
interested in no I'm just I like hitting
trees and and
Mining yeah but those things are outfits
you shouldn't really wear for fighting
but only particularly for the actions
that you're taking um um so maybe I'll
make you I'll just make you the The Meta
J trust
me I am St okay I'm ready for the h okay
I put your gloves into the armor B if
you can the K some yeah I'm coming home
right
now anyway
oh no you
guys zom no the zombies are not okay
they're stuck in the barb
wire they're no they're lowering our red
get out of
[Applause]
there no I'm fatig
[Music]
oh good job made
it Hi
friend come on down ooh water's fine
they work
out so we building an even larger
moat I mean you don't have to go
overboard but just one more row of modes
would be cool maybe with spikes filled
with
spikes Moes filled with spikes H got it
oh I have tier four
now
yeah oh here they come
oh oh the next Trader is in the ice area
oh yeah up
North I'm excited for that but I don't
know if we'll see that anymore I don't
know if we'll see it today but
yeah we need to play another week
yeah yeah I'd be up for that but a
little bit of a break would be nice I
want to play some different games too
yeah I've been itting to play games but
then I'm like this is too fun as well I
know I'm
split so true and like you get so
committed to it I think all of us are
like super committed to it so we want to
show up every day yeah I'm
committed oh wait did I do it I think I
did it we are not scared of commitment I
feel like I have to do my
part yeah me too I
know isn't there loot in this house
somewhere apparently the Japanese girls
played until day 49 or
so but they didn't play in one go they
they had like several sessions of
several
days so that's how they got so
far we should just continue at some
point yeah are we are we what it going
to do it longer
tomorrow uh yeah we started uh 1 hour
earlier though uh if everybody's okay
with it already said she's okay with it
yeah I'm totally fine okay cool and then
yeah we'll just go however long I was
wondering how long it will be maybe like
5 6
hours really depends when we end
today cuz our raid is soon
but we can still maybe yeah I want to
definitely end on a hord okay today you
mean oh I mean tomorrow like because it
we might need depending on how we end
today I don't know how close we'll be to
a hord uh tomorrow but I definitely want
to end on the H tomorrow cuz I think
that'd be like a nice Bang Yeah agreed
yeah I think that's why we're playing
like longer just to get to a hoorde on
the last day I think so
more Swing
Kids what is this house how are you
going to fix anything if you don't have
sewing kits at
home can't repair
it I feel like I'm using so much
fuel it's bad for the environment you
got to
stop it really
fuel I've been I've been ranching like
so many cars to get some more fuel but
it really is a little bit of a limited
resource so if we can use bicycles more
often or car poool we can car pool car
pool saves the environment exactly yeah
true we need the we need seed
modifications everything on everything
and I'll make a car as soon as I
can from four orbe four
people I want to be in a car so
cute family road
trip road trip to the best
bookstore
yeah and we stop at every bear we see
MH if you're feeling under the weather
good job I knew you could do it come
on oh oh but a nice
magazine if you do this for me I will
never sorry how many sing kits did you
bring again there CutiePie need a little
Healing
Touch oh she has Forge head
books oh we still need that very much
need those are the workstation books I
think so yeah oh Dan yeah she does have
them does she also sell sewing
kits we have sewing kids at home no for
real so I really need more if she sells
them please tell me we don't have so
kids at
home does she could
though she does I'll buy please thank
you thank you how how many do you have
two okay please buy both I bought both
okay thank you I love you I'm expecting
somebody's going to have to Fork up the
money for the water purifiers though
since I just bought I just spent 1,000
bucks this is a waterproof I I'll buy it
remember remember how much money I
invested in making everybody mini bikes
and stuff that's true that's for
D if you come to my to my home which
water thing do you want me to buy I'll
buy it um I what do we need I think we
need water
filters I think I can buy a
gatherer wait no I need to save money
for beer
I have $9,000 on me if someone come to
me wow in
my in my
trenches oh water filter is too
much The
Gatherer I think we need a gather The
Gatherer let me see do we need the
gatherer still do we have the tarp I
can't remember if I bought the tarp or
The Gatherer I bought the Ice Cube I
think we need the gatherer we need
another Ice Cube we need another one I
already bought one well we made a new
water purifier
oh okay I'll buy one more gatherer there
we go thank
[Music]
you thinking about what will not stack
probably well
whatever okay I'm coming home do you
want to ride home oh you have a bike too
never mind I have one wait do you want
do you want to get on so you save gas
but then how are we going to get this
one back home you'll pick it up how I
walk what what put it in your inventory
oh because first time so
smart oh you're bike is locked Oh see it
locks every
time
okay thank you
yeah I know how much you like being a
passenger princess I Do I
Do is it getting dark and scary
yes I have six Forge ah head
magazines yay
what six for head oh my God amazing
you're so
lucky it's all skill no luck 100%
skill I would say those magazines are
pretty
lucky I bought three of them will or
whatever the song
goes yeah exactly remember the name
yes F or something yeah
yeah why are they so
rare where are we where are we doing the
defense at Old House
okay oh that's that's spooked
me I just stepped on a zombie and it
woke up oh no this game was a jump scare
happy Halloween happy
Halloween God my heart I'm
old can't take this
anymore okay we're
home
yay thanks for the ride yay yeah oh you
did make another one okay I'm going to
put the thing in
here
boom making L of
food everything I just want to look for
I put the sewing kit in the in the crate
next to the thank you forge I put the
magazines in the
magazine
okay d
[Music]
damn that other house gave me false hope
I have ammo too for you kiaha I put in
the ammo
crate thank
you we're so PR short on ammo this time
than bless you thank you oh I have ammo
for you bi boo let me just drop it the
crate is full think think I'll be fine
with the
ammo last time I had to share this time
it's all mine oh yours these zombies
we're going to kill them before daytime
again yeah yeah so
easy knocking on
wood wood where
that's your favorite word
huh where is it what no wonder you like
fauna so much she's literally a tree
pulls out my axe no I'm not a tree I'm a
[Laughter]
Kieran this might be dangerous if gigy
gets drunk and cannot tell apart is that
what Tre is that why this is happening
why she that's why she punches you no
yes it's because I keep falling asleep
been punched by G that tells you
something yeah yeah sorry I have um I
have
narpy oh that's not an
excuse I just fall asleep and then I
imagine that I'm punching a tree then I
wake up and I'm hitting you I don't need
it it's
tough married life is stuff huh we're
going through counseling it's
okay hey shouldn't I be there
too yeah but I I keep beating her I
don't know
how I'm going to be so traumatized when
I grow
up aren't you already a little
bit close your eyes B boo I'm already
I'm already very murderous it's I get it
from my parents play play on your DS go
on go back to
bed sneak downstairs while you're
fighting by the staircase looking down
into the into the living room oh they're
fighting
again oh
no no don't
fight going back home
unsuccessfully should I check one last
time in here
[Music]
hello
M
zombie where are you I feel like we're
procrastinating again on the ho no no
don't worry I'm working really
hard you're going to be really impressed
when you get over here oh are you making
the modes and stuff yeah nice once again
I don't have to do anything in terms of
fortification leaving it to the others I
am the Gopher the Gopher I thought you
were a beaver right now I'm digging
through the
dirt do that doesn't that make you a mo
I'm the little mole naked mole rat
cute why is it empty was someone here
recently what
was someone in the what house is this uh
B bore barnfields recently everything's
empty yeah probably I mean it doesn't
have to be recently right it's just yeah
true I can never find any small
stones do we have them we should have a
lot I would feel like I can never find
them am I just blind
well you can always Farm them
outside hit some Stones dig for them or
do you have to just look for them no I
see rock ston yeah has five sewing kits
in her personal
storage we're taking it's should be only
F I'm taking those if she's not showing
up like two raids in a row so I'm taking
those
she doesn't know how valuable they are
it's okay it's on Z yeah no I I I think
a lot of things in the storage they
might like not need anyway
so they're just putting them there for
safekeeping but we're one big team
that's
right one dysfunctional family if she
does show up again I will make armor for
her so
exactly what comes around you three
armor crafting kits in your storage yeah
those are like you know I'm gathering
them for another piece of armor for
G and for myself maybe we'll see how far
we get I'm just looking in
everybody's now nosy yeah what is what
is going
[Music]
on
beo interesting you're very buggy for me
very glitchy yeah her shoulders are like
off her shoulders oh you see it too huh
H is that better well you're constantly
in like a shooting and walking
position um but yeah now they now the
should yeah they're floating again looks
funny looks very
funny is hoarding too I'm calling
everyone else wait no I'm I'm holding
stuff for my Magnum gun okay so that's
why there's tape in there that's the
amount of tape I need for my Magnum gun
picking it to everyone's inventory what
the hell are you doing with
this hiding stuff from
us
unbelievable all I'm going to say is I
don't even have a personal box my stuff
is everyone's
stuff oh we're getting close to the raid
so now everybody's like so 10 on edge
and everybody's fighting I don't like it
it's not good for my
development our child getting a
part-time job we like oh you're not good
I I'll keep a better job at your money
than you will no I made this money on my
own here let me put in the bank account
for you wait Mom I wanted to buy a new
game games you have to study no how will
you get to College like
this question uh the the
shieldy things that you found did you
are you still carrying them I put them
in the chest next to the forge okay
thank you I was able to make a couple
duct tapes
now
so I can make more armor crafting kits
oh oh I'm getting a good amount now
let's go
looking good oh I'm so hungry and
thirsty oh
God oh maybe it's time to eat my banana
banana don't eat the banana put it in
the chest eat the hobo
sou the banana is IRL oh
oh I'm really going to eat
it
oh I'm like I can make banana bread out
of that I don't even think there's
bananas in this game if are I'm sure I
can make
[Music]
something
oh I could place the time charges into
the into the Moes so they'll explode in
the mo
o that might do you have to activate
them I don't know it says time so maybe
it just oh it's 4 seconds okay I drop it
and then expl in 4 second
[Music]
M there's um 440 small stones in this
top chest fa what I missed
it I'm just blind I went out and
collected
some too
[Music]
bad 15 minutes before blood moon what
oh but the hord will not come yet so
oh
right um I think it starts at
22:00 yeah all right yeah
22:00 10 p.m.
yeah F what did you drop off from
sh uh sewing kits
huh you don't have it anymore right
no I put it by the unless somebody
somebody took it maybe no I think I
already took it then we should do
another sweep of everyone's chest I
think I
will someone's hiding things under their
pillow don't if my game stashes in there
don't take it away from me that's all I
have I remember grandma sent you some
money for your birthday
funo yes didn't you need bar brawler
magazines they're in the chest oh I only
need volume five
oh did anyone take the stack of forged
iron can I have like 25 a um what
um let me see uhoh there's some
outside oh
hello yay the party is starting
yeah I'll let you guys handle
that more more
okay I put some uh forg iron back in the
chest for you and I'm forging some more
you don't mean steel right you mean
forged iron just iron yeah just IR okay
okay that's good um so we're making one
Ned outfit for there more out
there a yes oh there's a lot
oh oh are they going to try to come for
the back
again maybe
let me know if you need
help I think we got it what am I oh
watch out Le it's pain being
melee okay I think we're
good
storage
more so nice when you forget you have so
many things in your
bike that will make you happy when you
see
them where does we have lever I know we
have lever somewhere oh I have it I'm
just going to make a thing real quick
and then put all the stuff back into the
chest
[Music]
okay oh the spikes hurt can I delete
these spikes that are right outside yeah
please please do I think I put those
there you mean the one spike in the back
of the house that was me cuz I was
trying to achieve something I
see and I've achieved nothing okay I'm
putting all the ingredients back in the
chest the Le's in there thank you thank
you so
[Music]
much all right then can we craft some
forged steel do we need more iron no we
need a crucible we don't have Crucible
is
15K oh wait it's money yeah you can buy
it's money or me crafting it but until I
can craft it I still need a few more
workstation magazines oh did you get the
15K did you get the six that are in the
magazine box I already read them I still
need
um 30 no four 40 more oh yeah I have 4K
40 more yeah 40 more books of
workstation but I can make a cement
mixer now which with that we could make
cement walls in
fur but my next reward that I can uh
make is a chemistry station and then a
crucible so it's very hard chemistry
station's good for yeah it will be good
let me put that in
there
and
uh oh it's loading up
slowly
okay okay not enough steel so I
[Music]
think I have to make a lower level
one which will be good
enough chemistry station will be great
to reduce material consumption
okay everyone donates you'll get to buy
the C yeah but I haven't seen a Trader
selling it yet oh maybe the one in the
in the next Zone will have it yeah
probably like I it wouldn't make sense
for them to sell it so early in the game
when wait I can't even like I'm way too
far from crafting it myself they
probably want to balance that out so
that you don't get it too
early so yeah probably in the mountain
area there's a
chance Bob usually has it Bob really Bob
got to check Bobby more often I think we
could farm that much money easily it
might be worth it y yeah the the higher
the tier Quest the more like CL we have
start getting like 2 ah 2K now and stuff
so do we have more water because I feel
like the the food chest doesn't have any
water right now um there's some in the
output let put it oh okay I'm also
cooking some uh good water that's being
cooked
currently actually keep
those hobos do also hydrates you a bit
oh really yeah this D has everything
yeah it's good uh gigy I have your uh
level five Nomad
chest okay I'll give it to you when I
meet
you um thank you if I were to make one
more
thing what could I make but I I don't
have any more steel what's the time by
the way
5:00 p.m. oh yeah 500 p.m. yeah we still
have five ingame
hours wait GG do you have a wood
splitter Mod on your axe need a hat I do
not wait you you should have this let me
bring it to you thank you more damage to
wood can I just take this bike I don't
know who this is take it if you ride
wait wait take take my bike if you want
since I have the which is yours
here pink it's locked okay it's unlocked
oh wait let me put this mini bike
back gy what's your hat again that
you're wearing cool
sunglasses remind me that that wa
where's your bike by the way don't my oh
okay it's in the hole with we're just
Trading bikes
yeah ah people your preacher gloves are
still in the armor chest don't forget
about those okay thank you should we
bring food yes I think
so I'm going to head over to the new
house okay me too I'm going to come soon
I guess I'm I think I've done enough
crap I got enough
ammo I got some let made as much armor
as I could but with the lack of Steel
it's difficult to make more good
stuff so for
now maybe we're I think we should as a
group try to get 15,000 I bet we can
yeah I 9,000 toen on me yeah we're close
then right 9 10 11 12 13 we need 2K more
that's
it 2K more yeah she has 4K I have 9k or
she has 9k I have 4K like
2K yeah I used up all my money yesterday
for something what did I buy something
really
expensive what was
that didn't I buy
it no not just steel does anyone have
bandages okay maybe I think no we are
yeah we need bandages we don't have aloe
is the
problem oh I guess it's in the desert
right dang
it have three Alo in need four to make
one bandage I have five bandaids I'll
bring those no it's okay you can you can
use them cuz you're going to be on the
field anyway I I just might have someone
kill me before the raid starts
okay I'm to go to an idle me I'll be
right back and I'm going to go to the
new house okay old house I mean be right
back okay
[Music]
actually is this
mine repair kits do we have repair kits
yes there's repair kits in the thingy
thingy new house or old house new house
there's like in one of the unnamed boxes
oh oh
okay ah saw one no threee
nice I'll just take all of them with me
for now we might need them
there make a better
Sledgehammer no it's fine do I have any
skill
points free okay
um oh I have four thank you for
reminding
[Laughter]
me
uh what's where should I I'd like more
stamina I was also working on something
previously was
I over
here stamina what was stamina again
stamina is
[Music]
is it is
fortitude and it is Rule one
cardio thank
you yeah I need more you I'm
back why is my on Fire H you're on fire
do you do you see this my bike is
smoking uhoh is it okay hold on maybe I
should better go catch it only for
running oh yeah you want to do you want
to give me my bike back and then I'll
just drive you to the place oh
okay your bike's over
here should I just get more of these
points I'll just do you want it over
here I'll just put it anywhere I'll just
pick it up I'll just put it over
here want to be something like this oh
can you unlock my bike oh
yes weapons skill thank you oh wait uh
where Ma okay
ready yes we're going to need more of
these okay I think there's North yeah
there North okay well yeah I'm then
would need skull crusher though we're
coming G okay focus on the gun anyway I
can't wait for you to see my work oh
hold on I have to take a tea break cuz I
have I have the no nose oh no what were
you eating I don't want I don't want to
be stinky you eating sham
sandwiches EA sham
sandwiches I don't because I took all
the food out of the
chest you want steak and
potatoes it's okay I still have some I
was just trying to like clear out my
inventory so I was just eating whatever
was in we don't have to live like that
anymore I wonder how long
this uh buff
stays getting
spooky oh r r feel like we're always
down to the water when we're running to
the new
house yeah I forgot I wanted to go into
the desert and punch aloe cuz I can
probably get a ton cuz I have the perk
now will this be able to go through the
river yeah wow okay wow
Easy E are you taking a mini bike to
dive into the water yeah it
was thank God this game isn't too
realistic all right I'm on my way too I
bringing some some vitamins and stuff
too do you have beer fauna yes I have
beer drink up and go crazy I am I you're
the alcoholic now I know I know I was
afraid for you to come back can realize
I've slipped into bad habits things have
changed it just makes me so
strong because you weren't around when
we needed you we we we don't have to
live like this we have a child it makes
me three times as strong I need this
about her
future she won't have a future if she
dies to
zombies these are special
circumstances I don't need to be I I
don't need bullying anymore I learn from
my mother oh my gosh this is a scary
pit does it look functional it does it
looks scary if I was a zombie I would be
very
[Laughter]
scary all
right sounds
promising
ooh yes
[Music]
I am also very scared of
accidentally did you fall
in almost almost I'm scared they have
the Alo SE here I'm Ying these oh
yeah it's so much faster with the bike
let's go
very nice wait where's Gigi in the hole
what you're in the hole I'm still
digging right digging herself a hole
where there's like my head out two
layers do you see me
yeah
here a gift for you oh I'm so excited
yay thank you
wait take some take some food take
this and take this what one more hour in
game
hour oh my
God I'm so last minute
again oh yeah g I have stuff for you too
okay where is the entrance oh wow nice
wow yeah that's uh that looks very good
the only problem will be if people
people go through these doors and then
let people in again like me last time
and you
fall don't fall down no no falling no
falling you guess we could have made
like iron doors or so to replace these
by
now um G where is gigy in the hole okay
I I'll put your uh stuff into the armor
chest thank you I will take my perch
M have some food oh thank you I did
bring a little bit for myself but that's
good have a
bandaid oh thank
you oh yes can I have one Band-Aid
maybe over here won't need
that take this and take one of these
take one of these take thank you oh
thank
you thank you wait wait wait take take
take one of these oh thank you
okay all right I'm excited let's see
what this will bring us yeah today you
think I can keep digging while they're
here you still need
more actually finally quickly kill me
that's F really yes okay are you sure
I'm sure are you going to spawn here
what yeah I'm going to spawn here
I got some
[Laughter]
XP
[Music]
ooh yeah the front and the sides are
very well protected I wonder when the
zombies come from the back if we'll have
any problems but should I take back
there too no no no no there's one one
line of mode and a line of
spikes it'll be fine we just always need
to have an eye on where they're coming
from but it won't be as many as last
time cuz we're less people so we'll be
good it's going to start
soon 20 seconds 20
seconds what do these do again damage
rication disease resist s region I see
let see if I go out I have to eat this
and this only if I go out
I'll stay up here if I shoot someone by
accident I'm sorry I'll try to not shoot
you if I set you on fire by Molotov I I
I will call out when I'm going to use
the molotov okay smart smart yeah giggy
are you coming out to fight or are you
going to keep on digging I'm going to
see if they bother me down here okay
well my bike is oh my bike is in danger
will they hit it I don't think
so [\h__\h] I'm scared to go out now they're
about to
come they could take they could take my
my bike will die oh F I'm going to go
grab my bike can you give me coverage
yeah I don't think you can pick it up so
I'll I'll cover you with shots I'll
watch you thank
you oh
god oh it's lagging got go go go go I'm
watching I'm watching
okay they're going into the
I need to drink my
beer with you I'm leaving St the P
me okay I got my bike I got my bike I'm
throwing a
mol there's a lot of them aren't
there on my way
fuing
door okay okay
ohy all right I time again
see he's
[Music]
spinning oh there there are all burning
and they're dying by the
spikes they're dying yeah they
are
fire try let's try to always prioritize
killing the police guys first yeah big
big big yeah why are they Hing the tree
that's my
job how dare they I know no stop taking
my
job like how they're all Gathering
nicely and some I'm fixing some of the
spikes that I
can that's nice so you ouch yeah they
seem to have a hot spot over there yeah
get out these spikes and the trees why
are they hitting the trees I know the
train alive is it because you have
the oh yeah they got dles
my aim is not the best cuz
I'm final watch out watch out okay
what's inside where how did they get in
just the SP oh hell no oh hell no oh my
God I'm fight over here I think one wave
is maybe over cuz the music maybe not I
hope that is the second
I'm placing more
spikes uh should we have stack them
upwards the
spikes oh it's they're coming in through
the the doors they're coming in through
the doors oh they can use those
nah
nah there's not two I don't see anyone
actually there's some in the spikes huh
in the there a few inside but they're
dying from the SP inside too that's good
all right they'll they'll die
eventually yeah let me fix some of these
spikes okay New Wave is coming new wave
is coming watch out uhoh what was that
just having a
snack ow the SP are hurting me
too oh oh oh they burn out they got
animals
uh-oh
my CH out
here I'm good
okay there's a big wolf thing or so is
there wolf
[Music]
oh God oh God I'm taking care of it
don't worry about it I'm taking care of
it I suffered a deep I'm dead I'm dead
I'm cleaning out I'm
done think my stuff fell into the spikes
and the mold I'm going to retrieve
that I already used all my heel are dead
it's fine
okay um how am I going
to get my
stuff oh gosh
oh there there okay oh gosh thank God
okay don't look at me don't look at me
oh I broke my
[Music]
leg they are punching the
trees why what's your problem I
know good life good
job get job
okay oh gosh there's a lot of them all
right I'm going to go fire again run
isn't he
running okay burd
down keep running rning
running keep running oh my God how much
fun Staying Alive well I just die
once spray and
pray come
on keep running keep running keep
running oh is that where is I can't tell
which one
where keep running keep running I'm
taking a break oh God good idea oh
no coming through
me they're kind of getting inside watch
out I'm resp
spiking I'm resp spiking him TR good
job I'm in a rough Squad right
[Music]
now don't worry they will die this
fight nice nice nice nice nice nice
we're doing good we're doing good I'm D
SP oh gosh they're about to come through
the
door I'm going to thr bom at the door
behind watch out for
the
[Music]
[Applause]
behind they're
parkouring please be over soon
civilization I need oh gosh
fix our defenses is it still is it still
it happening yes things are very much
happening here I will put another line
of oh God how are they getting in oh
it's broken in the B I see okay
okay they're hurting me I'll try to be
your uh back up here okay ow
[Music]
wa oh there a lot coming from the
goodness I'm going to throw bombs again
Watch Out does anyone have any spare
[Music]
Band-Aids with that bom I'll use my only
one oh god oh yeah we need some I'm so
I'm so
ow ow what hitting
me owie
[Music]
owie arms also sprain from all this
punching re
[Music]
spiky there are so many coming from the
hill
there okay I'm thr I'm throwing my last
bomb watch out watch out
close maybe I should have made a in the
back give me ammo oh that St someone
else's oh God okay Hammer Time
baby I'd like some free ammo please oh
Dro ammo drop ammo
the back
side I'm fresh and ready to
go no more spray
arm what the music
stop ouch are you okay this only half my
health it's
okay do you have a like a a healing
no I'll be okay though I have one okay I
I can drop it right here on the floor
right here where I'm right let me take
the
guy I'm okay I'm not going to stand in
front of
you
oh
oh wait it's not over it's not
over Hill there's more there's some down
the
hill Oh
ammo yeah if we pick some stuff up from
the map they give ammo I think it might
be over nope no there's
dogs hi
Doles love you're joining us after
all that's a is just fine she's just
fine
stop stop burning the tree taking the
tree down
please don't work for me that was is
mine dog incoming dog running F big Dogg
or small Dogg small okay more big dog
then we we scared we're very scared
why did they stop the music I think it's
over
now
ow
seems uhoh one more maybe these are just
regular zoms yeah maybe I
yeah oh it's so quiet
now wow I actually used all of my ammo
oh
God
still let's loot there's birds coming oh
Birds where can read the r from the back
from the
back yeah it's over good job girls good
job we survived we did that was
definitely the toughest one yet yeah
okay there's a few more but wait no no
there feel raid anymore L it must be
though of the dogs right oh big wolf got
I'm
sorry wolf is attacking Tre oh dear
there's a
wolf I'm scar I don't know going for oh
he's going for you
giggy something me oh hello
hello I'm so
sorry it's okay I was dying anyway from
the
spike
[Music]
really leave me alone leave me alone
leave me alone leave me alone leave me
alone near
help thank you
Father what is
this I'm exhausted
that's why I'm not a tank
usually can't deal with this
stress tank is low stress we just walk
into them and punch
no
from okay then
I kill I did not really die guys was not
a real death
M
undeserved I'm
[Applause]
practically they're still coming I know
it's okay one more hour I
guess did anyone bring any repair kids
you're getting attacked by a bird uhoh I
did but it seems like they're used ow
the dog too oh
my my gun is broken
uh-oh uhoh I don't have a parid de I'm
I'm putting spikes down watch out SE the
loot search the loot maybe the loot has
one I need I need ammo if this continues
strong strong hold strong 40
seconds I not
[Music]
die die die level
31 oh
yeah oh they really hate the Dre
do ouch I'm going to die
goodbye you have served us well
FAA alive or
dead they can't
oh God oh God good thing there's no de
right yeah thank God they took that
[Music]
out thank thank you y watch out I don't
want to stab you oh there's more
[Music]
jeez to end is over
I'm so exhausted 2 minutes actually y
two minutes 2 minutes the music stopped
though yeah stopped a long time
ago oh my mini
bike I need to make these modes
better no they were
wonderful I don't know how many fell in
I feel like they were we killed a lot of
them before they could fall in again so
I need to make a m on the back side
though yeah didn't expect them to come
from
there y we over more ammo for tomorrow I
used up all my ammo yeah I need to
prepare more ammo found a few for you
already went
collecting the when the when the
magazine has an open book that means I
read it already right yes yes okay
these are all not really for
me well is it over it's over
we we won let's go with just four of us
but that was I it didn't feel like they
sent us much less than yeah right it's a
lot they did yeah also how do we get all
the loot that is at the spike I think we
might have to break the spike yeah I
have to break this Spike
okay gy get going this door
is where do
we maybe we can burn it down with a like
Molotov cocktail or so the spikes I
don't have
anymore if I had one safe spot to get
get down there I could Hammer
them Place boxes on the BL oh
good
idea definitely don't want that to
[Music]
despawn let me I don't want I want to
ruin
it at least we got a lot of loot
yeah g do you have some
wood um I have 200 on me can you make
me a few
blocks okay just like maybe 10
oh so okay crafting right now thank you
oh I'm so full
yeah me too can't even walk through here
ouch time to get out my bike and let the
bike take things how come I'm I'm like
too too wide to fit through this door
frame you've bulked out from all your
fist training I guess so where do you
want the
blocks um I would like go uh around the
modes and place them on top of the some
of the spikes to pick up
the thank
you let's
see I don't know how that's going to
work can I really reach them from here
found a treasure map oh I got super Co
seeds more of those that's good that's
good I still can't cook anything with it
but hopefully one
day I can't reach it from
[Music]
here oh
no PE PE
PE is that the block or the
spikes it's the
spikes but that's the block
maybe ow okay I'm in the spikes oh yeah
me too they do hurt even when you just
graze them they hurt Oh no I got rid of
one one block of
spikes at what cost oh wait there's oh I
see there's like a lot of loot down
there yeah so in theen get are we going
to get them in the trenches yeah we need
to get rid of the spikes but
oh it's difficult and I don't have an
axe I don't know if we can get rid of
these we can we can ow herey I got rid
of that one block
already uhoh Goodbye
World goodbye goodbye
goodbye goodbye this SM pretty good just
don't
[Music]
panic parkour civilization flashbacks I
feel like I just missed a chicken jump a
shameful ow here I'll get rid of
some we leave it you
Eggman ow the
spikes oh no my
backpack oh no
ah oh I see it okay hold
on yeah going to be breaking a lot of
these spikes I'm
sorry my trees is it it's the blue one
down there right yeah
yeah make
yeah at least it gives me wood back so
oh oh oh oh it's two layers of spice
oh really good right yeah don't GL don't
GL no I was testing no actually this
time a building block suffocated me I
guess oh no I was testing I wasn't sure
where the damage was coming from we
might have to just say goodbye to this
room no no no no you're magin I mean
definitely the backpacks but no
I wonder is there any axes that I can
use in
here can we not set them on
fire yeah I was thinking that like
throwing in the moloto cocktail or so I
don't think the loot I have some in the
new
house but I don't know if it will really
efficiently
work Chad do you have experience with
that dig the dirt oh yeah we could use
the shovel I guess I'm dying to the [\h__\h]
no this is this is wor already learned
from this why does it keep on
happening can when we dig can we fill
the hole that we
dig I don't know whatever I'm going to
just dig any way to get F's backpack
back
ow stop touching me
[Music]
oh well well oh
Noe
goodbye an unnecessary death I died
exactly where you died to our B in the
same
place learn the schematic
oh wait didn't I already know that one
this one I
canar a it's a nerd outfit that's where
the cage comes
from are you digging naked people hello
I'm just jump for it no no give me my
bag you're going to be stuck in the
spikes Spike free are you oh no just
wait they're almost there okay you can't
take it up with spikes on top of it
anyway I tried mhm it seems like
so I can't even reach the
spikes almost there almost there it
should be pretty reachable now oh see o
that
hurts wait is this mine
this is mine
okay did it work yeah you can go get
your backpack
yay all right I I'll continue with this
then
very extremely
[Laughter]
effective this feels so
wasteful I'm going to get out of here
and then restart somewhere
else yeah I want to go home wait the
loot despawned there was loot here like
a lot of it it despawns after a few
minutes I think too long oh
well maybe mod with spikes are not the
best thing cuz we can't get the stuff
well we did it did save us probably I
mean yeah it was really effective
and getting the house anyway
so I think it was still good it but F
you can take your bike back oh is it
because there was no M here they all
went here because there was no M here oh
I was CR I was
crouching everybody check the magazine
box for ammo and magazine means cuz I
put some in there okay um here is your
bag yeah you're done with armor right y
okay work station still useful okay I'll
start learning
armor M maybe maybe the spike should be
around not in the mode even though I
like the
idea but it's not very practical when it
comes to picking up loot
what about
survival we can survive and get mot uh
mot
loot
ah
well they had so much ammo in their loot
I want that
ammo I used up
everything did you check the the
Box oh well not recently I put some in
there okay I up and there's lots of ammo
in here stacks of ammo and I used it all
up I'm also putting uh the 9 mm ammo
into the box oh thank you and some
shotgun
shells here have you learned the Pocket
Mod armor Pockets I think I did yep
how what do you need to craft
it uh let's
see
pocket armor double pocket M
um scrap polymers which we should have
plenty mechanical parts we got a few the
the materials that might be not plenty
is duct tape and sewing kit sewing I see
I see those are good apparently if you
haven't yeah
I have a couple of those too mhm two I
think I put two in my armor have
two it opens up quite a
bit but still I would like a bigger
inventory even
bigger good
job motorcycle
motorcycle oh I I just
unlocked vehicle it seems oh I I have
more motorcycle parts I got from a class
in my chest at home but I literally just
made mini bikes yesterday I'm not going
leg go make motorcycles I
think yeah and they need a lot of
Steel I'm not going get that Crucible
first I think yeah we should see if we
can buy it yeah maybe tomorrow when more
members are online we can gather all our
money yeah I bet we could get it today
you guys want
to
yeah oh yeah here take my
money good job take all of this really
yeah thank you I'm going to be digging
are you digging more yeah got to make
sure the back side and the other side is
all covered
anything from home we should take yeah
oh sorry you didn't take the nerd hat in
the end did you no I didn't take it it
was going to give you more
exp yeah I slipped my mind I was so busy
bgy oh we have more treasure maps we
should do those oh I want to go on a
treasure hunt okay I'll hold on to them
and we can go treasure hunting
[Applause]
whoa whoa whoa whoa he you think we want
to go today or tomorrow anytime I'm just
going to bring him to the new house I'm
just seeing what's here so we can move
stuff
[Music]
over people box has five suing kids I'll
take it take it really yeah did you know
that you had these over here no
a nice surprise found a couple more
sewing kits in an unnamed
chest they go to the armor because the
armor needs it most for everybody's
purpose treasure chests have money in
them that could be good yeah money is
always good mhm wait isn't everything
supposed to respawn today or no is that
not how
who is this a crony Cron's
chest okay I guess I'll go back to the
house I'm I wonder how long we should
play cuz the raid ended and tomorrow CI
wanted us to do to do like a a full
cycle more or
less wait did
she 7
hour I feel like I don't know that's
what she meant I feel like it's it's
it's honestly better if we play a little
more that way tomorrow doesn't have to
be seven six hours tomorrow yeah six is
already plenty how many how many hours
is it from now from the next
day an hour day or not not the next time
the next time so like 7 hours seven IRL
hours yeah so yeah we could we should
play a little bit more to like bring
that down down yeah I think so I don't
think I don't yeah I don't think are we
Addicted by any chance maybe just a
little bit
just I'm not sure it feels
like we just want to make sure we're
really prepared for that big final raid
yeah exactly yeah we want to make it
into a an easy fight for our girls who
haven't been here every day so the
experienced ones are preparing it for
the less experienced
ones plus it's going to get even harder
yeah yeah right I'm scared of more of
the Wolves showing up
mhm I guess it's
nice dead though the the wol wasn't
actually bad I just jumped and it
couldn't hit me and I just shot it while
jumping jumping is kind of op I see
the more Shooters the better for Wolf
yeah unless they shoot the one tank that
is tanking the
wolf oh I guess I'm the only one who can
do that to W though cuz I have
parkour I got parkour too oh ni yeah
parkour is good you jump they can't
fight you so you just keep jumping in
place and shooting them from below or
above and kill usually when I'm out
there if there's a need for me to jump
then I'm probably already using my
sledgehammer and my sledgehammer will
use up so much stamina that I'm not even
able to jump anymore most of the
[Music]
time bad weapon but I already committed
to it and it's pretty cool I like it
when I can Hammer their heads open and
[Music]
satisfying my armor is breaking huh do
you guys want to do the treasure chest
today
then yes sure okay but I mean I guess
not everybody has to go we be productive
and split it's helpful a lot of people
huh huh huh did do that did not
see I don't know how to describe what
just
happened you I got to show you a clip of
it later yeah someone clipped that I
don't know what
happened
yes uh but I I to say uh the area for
the treasure is actually quite big so
and um you know it's the same thing
where when you after you dig enemy spawn
so it would be helpful for a lot of
people to come out
okay all right I am bikeless oh no did
we leave you
there I I willingly chose to
stay I'm just saying I will need a ride
if
okay uh I'll come pick you up actually
are you ready to come back no okay let
me no let me know when you're ready to
come back and I'll come pick you up okay
I I'm I'm I'm almost done
digging now one thing I realized when we
were fighting rather than food I was
more in need of medkits yeah I want to
go get a bunch of aloe from the desert
if we can make a pit stop I can collect
a bunch really fast
probably okay that's a good thing to put
on our list tomorrow or
today yes
beer excuse me
excuse
trapped thank you
sorry it's okay small house I know
should knock down some more
walls make it a big open space I got an
Al aloe vera
seed we we have four yeah I already
we're out of a gardening
[Music]
you need to come here and bite the walls
down please
okay I'll knock all the wall in the
house
yeah yeah I I had to tear down these
walls because I was going for a much
more open kitchen and then that way it
leads into the the patio as well the
bathroom and you can see the bathroom
from the patio what I was going for
yeah I see the vision oh I don't like
the Privacy you know that's why I like
going to everyone's chest
what's yeah that's exactly what I'm
thinking we're already in the zombie
apocalypse why are you keeping secrets
you
yeah do we have any repair kits
no don't think
so okay my bike still has stuff
right what we
got
ah
magazines um pair Salvage Salvage
is anybody learning repair
tools uh how much do I have to let's see
I only have five that's more than me so
I also have a little bit round that but
I thought somebody might have
[Music]
higher stealth boots
mod don't forget to periodically check
your
challenges oh
[Music]
yeah
nothing except for
one cop zombies yeah I killed plenty of
those m
oh I need more big mama
zombies is that a thing yeah I got the
cop zombies too 10,000 XP wow wait does
it give you a rare
item rare item I thought it
said I didn't actually read it I just GL
that it said 10,000 XP and rare
item did I get something
rare items I didn't get anything where's
my rare items I from the trader oh do
you have to turn it in as
Trader hopefully any Trader not a
specific
one I'll just learn these all
I'm so smart in this game I'm so smart I
have read so many books I'm so well
read my brain is exploding and
expanding yeah more books more
knowledge knowledge is overpowered
knowledge is everything
I'm making a bunch of repair
kits for
us thank you Mommy the corn
[Music]
Ready
corn corn for
dinner it has no nutritional
[Music]
value
wait do I need to use a knife to get
corn 20 steel am I
[Music]
crazy oh it's not ready oh is did it say
growing I just can't could make a better
one of this
read maybe
five it looked ready it wasn't ready
don't want to use up do
it make steel I don't have enough steel
I'll just make this L five one first and
then in the future I'll make the best
steel Hammer I can make how about that
steel is too rare right now guys give up
you're too helpful yeah but we can go
get The Crucible
right yeah indeed generous
donation yeah for my wives do I have the
parts I think I do you have my entire
life savings in your hand I do
do you have enough I have I have some
more money I have
10,000 oh if we I have
4.6k I'll give you all my money for one
repair kit okay how about I've got a
bunch of a pair
kids where's a be boo I
see if he does sell it right now then we
should definitely get it
from Bob yeah I don't know if he always
has it but we should
check I he he
go doesn't matter where you oh I have
exactly
15,000 but I want to make it at a higher
level
chat I think I'll just make this one
first I be right but I wash my eye out
there's like a oh no a
aass in it an alley Al be right by
okay I think that's better before I'm
like wasting those
people so going to make this one
Lea
Lea should have made this before The
Horde came
but you know lots to
do oh gosh the steel Knuckles are so
expensive like the cop zombie reward
might be really good huh
really chat keeps on spaming now that I
should go get it
now so I'm going to go get
it wait take me with you
okay if you don't tickle me okay I won't
tickle you okay otherwise I'll crash
us tickle
tickle vom your Uber bike is outside can
you unlock in the doors what I have to
do that again
unbelievable you need a fob you need a
key fob maybe I should just put codes on
everything then I don't have to unlock
it right oh does that
work11 hope so yeah most common code
okay yeah that it seems like it might
work all
right here we
go oh I see yeah go to any Trader to
collect your
reward for cop Slayer
okay I'm back back are you better are
you I'm better yes I washed it
out please write me high ranking uh in
the St yeah please do D smell very good
thank
you spread the
word what he gives us water
filter I'm taking Tak
wait these are really good these are
super good he also gives legendary parts
and solar cells you didn't have to buy
it no uh it's a reward for killing 50
zomes you should conven too wow I check
I check I check did we only need one
Crucible yeah only one I bought it I'm
going to get the water filter then okay
take a look but don't expect me to hold
your hand through it nice noise you guys
can have your money your money back okay
[Music]
although
maybe he sells something nice something
else what does he
have I mean sell steel no wait we don't
need steel now I can I can forge steel
with this
Crucible
if handgun Parts I would really like
those I already what's it going to is
she selling them I don't know
um no she does not if you don't like my
food you can always go dumpster diving I
wonder how much steel I can make right
up the bat wait can I give you your
money back oh yes here take your take
your money
back it seems some of it is missing is
it it's okay it's okay just a
joke it might be it all
combined oh I can also take a water
filter and a solar cell and a
crucible what what do we what do we
need the water filter would be good but
yeah or legary parts
yeah maybe give you can also get a
reward G did you kill 50 cop zombies no
I need to kill 20 more we we have a lot
of legendary parts and we can loot those
right so I don't feel I feel like
legendary parts we could make a second
Forge we have three right
now I used some for your guys' armor and
also one for myself I think so we're
down to free what what does solar
sell it must be for some other cool
machine but I have yet to find what's
useful for yeah I guess you can get
power but I I know what it's used for
electricity okay maybe maybe I'll just
get another water filter yeah let's get
a water filter be useful yeah
okay all right steel is in the
making Ste Ste Ste ah for turrets solar
power for turrets maybe is what it's
for oh I already got the waterfilter
though
by the way people you were able uh to
make ammo right yes do you make those in
the Forge or elsewhere no the work
thingy the
work is it difficult to make big amounts
no oh I might we might need extra
tomorrow make you can make bullet
casings in the Forge and then I need
gunpowder and the the bullet
which I've been collecting a lot of so
not too bad cuz like even with four
Stacks I ran out today and
tomorrow you know a lot of people need
probably much more ammo so we might want
to make some ourselves
[Music]
tomorrow send gy to collect
gunpowder yeah gun gunpowder would be
nice where do you get that
I don't
know what rock do I hit for
that uh explosive one no iron they
they're saying you should rather collect
iron iron iron okay I have 1,000 on me
right now I can get
more more more
more after I finish this
Mo oh you're already making the next MO
yeah maybe let's not fill it with spikes
let's just put spikes around you don't
like my no I like them what about what
about one one one Spike you know instead
of double spiking what if I do one oh
okay so you mean have the path two two
Fields but only one is spikes that could
work yeah single wall spike okay ah also
they're saying make free Block tall wall
of spikes on the outside for jumpers
oh I guess we're going to get some high
jumping enemies
next
concerning there we go I wonder if we
have more I'm just not seeing
it iron iron iron iron iron
iron oh there's a bunch of gunpowder in
one of our
chests
yeah but you you can make bullet casings
in the
Forge mhm with the brass gu oh brass and
clay and we have so much of that mhm
so that's easy
so just bullet tip and gunpowder bullet
tip
uh is lead and
Clay so you can make that in the Forge
as well so basically we just need
gunpowder I think that's possible
too maybe I should put out a second
Forge good
I could maybe I will oh I have a lot
of I can make some bullets now if
anybody needs any or I'll wait
until people all on and see what people
need I mean we could already put it into
the
queue you let's throw in
some chemical St I don't chal I can't
make it yet no no not
yet oh I can make high
power ammo too and
armor I would already be happy with just
normal one I think cuz I'm guessing that
takes less resources okay I'm going to
make I'm going to make some 762 for you
first and
okay and then once we get
more materials we can yay do
collectors filters that will be
useful yay we don't have to boil the
water
anymore I also want to stock up on
explosives again because explosives were
very very useful for that mhm
mhm sounds
good okay I'm making a second Forge so
that we can um
smelt all the stuff faster the brass and
everything I'm going to put it also in
the
[Music]
kitchen may be
here where's my
wrench renovating the kitchen a little
duct tape
oh yeah just put it in put it in for now
I'm just collecting a lot of uh stuff so
that tomorrow hopefully I can make some
armor for the less covered up
girls so lot so scantily
clad I would like to go to the desert if
anybody
want we could do some quests and I want
you want get some Arrow get the treasure
chest first I have two treasure maps
on there is oh there's one by G there's
one by our old house and then there's
one in
the dead fire
area yeah let's do it okay I'm going to
go to the one by GG first now way we can
pick you up as well you're going right
away one
by where is it please bring me some food
and
water okay I thank
[Music]
you should I go tooo yeah we should we
should all do the the treasure cook
together cuz it's a big circle and
enemies will
spot okay is it digging do you have to
dig for it yes you have to dig y I know
yeah I need an iron
shovel uh I only have a stone shovel I'm
coming to pick you up GG okay let me
know when you're
here I will come out of my
[Music]
hole hobos doew take so long to cook but
it's
good got to render down all the stuff
you put in it all the mystery
meat just wonder what you're feeding us
what are you feeding
us is it worse than rotten
flesh um no it's not worse than
R
nice
nice how about bre
oh there's so much clay over there um
sand when will we need sand and
Stones is it crushed
sand for
cement I don't know should I prepare
it not don't have space
anyway trying to forge
on
ah
okay could craft another
Bellow um
[Music]
I think I'm ready to head over when you
are
kiaha
oh yeah I'm just looking for six pieces
of
wood check the check the fire the
cooking I don't think you can take it
out of there I cancel it but I I could
just yeah I'm canceling it for a moment
we cancel the water one
the water one no no I already have wood
I already have wood oh
okay um is that that's that I got it
just reach into the fire and grab the
hot hot
[Laughter]
wood as a phoenix I will be
fine I'm
here come out of your hole come out do
you like What I've Done why is there a
dead when did this dead animal get in
my oh this where did it go I didn't even
I didn't get to glut it how did it
die it just died and
disappeared it's not
fair Al are we waiting for them to
arrive are you going there keep working
on your hole here I'll give you I'll
drop some food in your home y
yummy sorry keep going drop some food
water in your hole so that way you stay
gobble gobble
yeah okay that will make me thank you
you're
[Music]
welcome okay okay okay um uh yeah I'm
just putting away a few things and
two one minute one
[Music]
minute okay okay right bless
you it's
you I can make SS potato seeds
now it feels so expensive though you
need five potatoes to make one potato
scene and I feel like I get seven
potatoes back so it's like only net two
potatoes what a waste I
know oh
okay I'll just leave it
behind ready to
go
this although I don't know where to go
oh you didn't take these five sewing
kits in my
box me uh in the old house yeah oh no oh
I'll just bring it with me just in case
okay but right now it's not too urgent
probably tomorrow I'll be making a bunch
of armor but then uh until then I don't
need it are we going towards the old
house now or where where old house
there's a I don't think you guys can see
the where the treasure is but it is by
the old house okay okay is this the
right way
no is this the right way yes okay
H
what are we going to run out of
fuel
maybe I feel like we are should we take
our
bikes we going Ranch a car on the way
and get more
fuel where's the gas station when you
need one
yeah Will is the save the environment
huh GG
I'm going to use a
plastic somebody's saying we should do
the last raid in the snow biomi because
it's more fun apparently for some reason
it's more fun you need more
more yeah she so hard on her hole Yeah I
think we should just stay there at least
for this last rid and if we do a second
season then we can resettle in the snow
biome Maybe but I mean the Wolves the
wolves from the snow biome still came
over here so but we didn't see any bears
at least yeah fauna hold your bre
okay okay there you
go if I was there I would have tickled
you that's
evil what happened to my caring husband
you just you're just so cute when you're
giggling when I'm drowning
and you hold I just want to see how well
you can hold your
breath it's very concerning I I I feel
like there's some murderous
intentions yeah but only towards fauna
like what's what's what's between you
two that I don't have with G she doesn't
want to seem to kill me yeah can you
explain
yourself lust oh
where I'm out of gas but there's some
gas in the old house I
saw I think unless I took it all uh no I
took the gas in the old house no I
already put it in my in
my bike thingy there's no gas in here
okay next car we see I'm going to wrench
okay I'll help you there there's a car
by the house you might to what that
was 6% guas
I have 15,000 clay in my inventory
everyone aw that is a lot Clay is foring
yeah that'd be good for making bullets
and stuff but we already have
several thousands of clay are you still
in your hole no yes are
you yes I like it in
here
deep come on
it's okay you for you get to dig another
hole I'm taking you somewhere you can
dig
too okay do you like it so
far it's very nice thank you I work
where where is the extra hole it's on on
this side ah oh yes you have you have
made it longer beautiful why does be
have a floating
plate do you see what I see do she has
that for a while I'm like GL something
yes oh yeah wait F do we have a to no
that's just
bio
yeah all right I'm going to come here
follow me I'm going to bring you
somewhere where you can dig more
okay favorite hobby but I like what
you've done with the place thank you
I'll put spikes outside of the hole and
little B inside you going to remove
those spikes that are there
no they can stay for now cuz we got a
little bit can we siphon gas out of mine
no no it's okay I fill this back up to
30% okay oh mine's at 30% as
well maybe if I don't step on the gas it
won't use as much huh yeah does does it
work that way I'm not sure so I'm not
stepping on it now and it doesn't go
down very slowly
maybe I step on it oh yeah it go down
right away oh but oh not that
much just we're going to have to walk
home no no no no the Traders have some
gas and we can stop
by no a or just ran more cars we'll be
fine okay it is close
by so aha okay okay G stand right here
okay stand right here I'm going to
stand right here this is the this is the
width of the thing
okay you take your money back from the
bike okay you don't want it you gave me
more than I gave
you I must have given you some of some
of B boo oh they don't give oh it's okay
I deserve my child's allowance
what nothing don't worry about
it this is
college Ive for college I'm doing I'm
getting a because of you you told me to
get a so I did that's why I'm putting in
your college fun you'll see it once you
get to College don't worry I believe
you all right F I got some money for
your alcohol
addiction what oh thank you but Papa
please oh no don't worry sweetie we'll
get it we'll get it back we'll just go
to the casino and we'll win
it how how deep is the
treasure uh if you hit rock that is yeah
that's too
far but girls I was um I wonder what you
think about this before I started the
gaming portion of the stream today I was
um discussing with my viewers how I
would love to take a like a trip with
everybody to like Las Vegas or so
[Music]
[Applause]
but we all have to set like a maximum
budget just so that we don't overspend g
g y I'm putting it all
in yeah but a maximum budget maybe maybe
like
$10 okay okay very very
controlled you can't go a sent over
$10 and then in roulette will'll always
just bet on the same thing over but if
we if we each bet on something different
then that means one of us will always
win sure for sure except when the house
wins will they kick us out is that
cheating you're outside the border now
oh no I'm just diing for fun
now oh my shovel is going to not hold up
for that long I've got repair kids M
okay there's already Stone
here oh okay
the the perimeter got
smaller okay which which way towards B
okay
yeah I'm standing pretty much in the
middle of
it do we have to dig in in the circle or
just a
line I think it's within the circle it's
somewhere within the circle perimeter oh
this better be worth it
yeah I'm enjoying this how many
Treasures do you have I have two maps so
this one and there's another one in the
okay fire fire like the fireplace but
Wen there zombies going to
spawn zombie spawn last time
huh maybe that was a natural
spawn
[Music]
maybe oh hey you wait the time when it
uh spawned are you referencing to the
time where we had the digging Quest no
it was I had another quest in the ice or
not Quest but a treasure map in the ice
place and they were spotting quite a
bit oh we already dug so much where
imagine if this was our
Mo we could just move
[Music]
here I have 200 spikes on me oh God 200
is that what all the wood was for was
this your like Grand
Design it wasn't planned to become
spikes it just so happened that they
became
spikes I have a good
plan how about you connect this time T
this way toward towards people again
face way yeah
yeah so until tomorrow's forn night
giggy I want to see a connection between
these tunnels can you do
it these are our secret
tunnels it's absolutely necessary for
our survival okay once I get an iron sh
I'll start working on it it will be our
emergency exit tunnel yeah yeah they'll
never
know yeah we can bunker up somewhere
here these are the secret Denver Airport
tunnels are you very familiar with the
Denver Airport Denver
Airport I've looked into yeah okay I
need a repair kit okay what's special
about the Denver Airport here go the
horse with the glowing eyes is very
special and
interesting the horse you could take a
field trip to Denver airport and check
out the
horse on the way to Las Vegas yeah oh
wait oh I don't need a repair kit for
this shitty shuttle nice oh I guess you
don't yeah Stones
yeah
awesome Denver is pretty close to Las
Vegas amazing let's combine the trips wo
let's go see the horse and then go
gambling yeah it did give me Las Vegas
Vibes same area I
guess are we still in the perimeter yeah
we're still in the perim it got smaller
but you're still in it
okay this is crazy this is crazy this
better be good this better be good yeah
we could be questing I could be digging
the actual
hole wa when's the next day
30 oh the the wall is right right here
oh so like fun is right on the edge of
it I see it oh you see it it's right
here oh it's locked let me no I can uh
lock pick it one
second
yippe
[Music]
yipp this better be worth
it what's
inside oh 5K okay was worth it oh 5K
money 5K money yeah that's not bad is
that it there was a lot of stuff okay
here I will drop some it gave me a lot
of materials for bullets
actually and then here's some kiaha
bullets
thanks yeah it gave me Bullet and um and
weapon parts and 5K so that was worth it
that was that was totally worth it yeah
it's all right it's all right was pretty
good pretty
good let's get out of this oh and I got
I got gold
too gold gold apparently that's worth
gold is extra money okay he more money
okay that was worth it
oo all right do you want to go to my
second one yeah yeah okay I don't know
if this thing has any fuel in it no no
it doesn't only the car
oh well but those parts are still
useful all right lead the way all right
rooll chest
G I'm
here
I sorry this U I'm on
it I'm
[Music]
on close to her face
all right
um we're
[Music]
going last for a while least
Le we could check out the bookstore too
oh yeah it's books books it's in the
snowy area it's Northwest from
here you want to lead the way um let's
go to the treasure first maybe okay and
see how close we
are wait can I share the wayo is that a
thing shared way points how
I'm going to stop by Trader wch to get
some fuel too oh okay so we're going to
head to the tra rors on the way but I
don't I don't think my mini bike is
going to make
it see
oh do you see my waste point now oh
apparently uh cuz you shared it but I
have no idea where it is yeah you scared
but I can't I don't see
North say I see it yeah I
see B north
north north of Home North of home
oh
what north of the new house oh I see it
okay I see it
I don't see it but we'll go there I
guess I want to go to the desert too
which is in the opposite
direction it's okay we need to stall for
time
anyway
yeah we do mhm you
mean we need to install longer today I
feel like we could and I'm not just
saying that cuz I'm addicted I mean does
anybody really want to do a like 7 hour
stream well it's we need day 35 for the
hord day okay we should save around at
least 4 hours is maybe for the
tomorrow so we should probably we should
probably stop at 31
[Music]
y oh I got a challenge oh we got some
gas I got some gas yeah me too me too
thank you car for your
donation free gas refuel can you refuel
it or do I have to do it let's see G can
you make us some
gas yeah creates it I think I did it
yeah make it some gas please would you
like some steroids what about the car
right there I don't have a wrench though
oh I don't have a wrench I have a hammer
does that work I don't think so does the
hammer work or does it have to be a
wrench probably a wrench oh
wow I'll gu where is the trader at a Jen
no I'm going to W cuz re am I going the
the right way F uh yes okay
I can't look at the map while I'm
driving just follow this road the
direction you're going okay and at the
fork take a
right okay nice oh you know the roads
now no I'm looking at the
map she got the map app out yeah I'm in
the the passenger seat
navigating passenger princess but we're
stopping for car
oh nothing inside okay give us the
guas fill up our tanks give it give it
you greedy little
minivan oh
wait the house is here you can grab a
bike if you
want no oops sorry I didn't mean
to yeah I like sitting here oh you know
what how how full is this one oh this
one's more full okay we're going to
we're going to swap swap we're going to
swap to swap
bikes oh hold I have to mod this one so
it has a seat hold on I'm going to drop
off all my clay okay put it uh next to
the forge
[Music]
okay so much clay my inventory is oops I
got off wa I'm sorry
oops I'm sorry dangerous can I you're
trying to become an action hero
can I Craft on the back of the bike oh I
can't I wish I could the back seat
making cloth Oh I thought maybe I can
check oh yeah let me store some stuff
to we're going to JMA right now
huh no we're going to we're going to
we're going to RX oh okay we're going to
pass by this house so we can drop stuff
off
cool right I feels close right over
there in the The Forest of
trees home sweet home the Clementine
house
yeah we have any
water we should have a lot have a little
bit oh my hammer is
ready yppe I feel like every time I come
home I just get stuck doing stuff so
it's like
dangerous be like that here I'm going to
get rid of these
walls aggressions are being let out
again
I want no privacy in our
house why are you worried about cheating
when you have two lives I'm worried
about my child hiding stuff in her room
you
not I need my door I taking your door I
need my privacy my
door door to hide stuff from I agree she
doesn't need doors yeah yeah she does
not need a door door
actually take away all of her furniture
all of the take away her bed too she
take anything you do in your room you
can do out in the living room
too I'm running away from home I'm going
to my friend's house I'm not when I turn
when I turn 18 I'm out of here dang it I
don't W what is that
screamer they're inside
so many of them give me some give me
this G we opened up the
pl good thing would have been punching
each other
yeah I love this they're breaking our
walls did you see that the
kitchen oh my God they're coming through
the
St oh she there huh in the back okay
okay W wo wo wo wo
W what's
happening maybe I should put some spikes
up by this house
too one still one
[Music]
coming like a mini horde mini wave yeah
oh there's still
I and now it's
daytime so
exciting come on come on stay stamina
please hold up hold up zombies please
wait for a
moment oh my God I have like five 10
zombies on me
help I'm dead no back the house kind of
Y back of the house
okay oh my head
hurts oh wait honestly uh I might Le do
cuz um I've been streaming for 5 hours
and my head hurts okay we have been here
for a while we we we can um stop since
it's day 30 5 hours isn't too bad and
we're ear anyway so I do want to like
give the other girls some more you know
time to play we should like do
everything for
them even though we'd love to do so many
things yeah
but surely a season two will come one of
these days and then and we can go to all
the biomes that we missed that we didn't
see
yet and go do all the things that we
still have available to
us I'm going to build a m outside this
house too
uhoh
by you just want to dig no I just I just
feel like we need the
protection that lady busted through our
wall do you see this did she did thought
they she didn't take our oven oh oh
because oh that one that's yeah there's
no window or anything
there just should Place something
there she broke
it building block you're not the beaver
anymore you're the mole
get the fixer my Mo life Mo rat once I
go back to hitting trees what am I the
beaver again yeah
yeah the Gopher now our house looks
stupid our my wall doesn't
match look at it painted
sorting I'll keep those and make things
for
[Music]
people we have a lot of forged
steel that's good can I what did it take
to make anyway oh my God uh what what
did it take to make for Ste anyway uh
just
iron as well so it's it's the same
ingredients for making forged
iron but it takes a couple more but yeah
we're making
plenty I'm going to make some more
50 too much what how many 50 50 50 sure
we'll make more we'll make more didn't
somebody have a lot of iron with them gy
um I put 1,000 in did we need
that into the forge yeah yeah it goes
into the forge that's fine oh okay okay
okay the more the
area I need five leather do we have any
we do it's in the uh next to the
forge take
I need
to careful
care sorry War
me I'm crafting an iron
shovel iron
shovel I'm making level five
Knuckles
ooh I have level one right now I'm
skipping a few
I hear something why is there another
zombie they can't get enough of them I
know alive so chill I'm busy like no one
else plays with us when you're offline
please play with us now did I not oh
right you have to use the the
bench feels good
nice
oh 50 50 stamina per
hit wow
[Music]
good stuff she dead right yeah
okay did you
upgrade yeah better Hammer
nice I didn't make a max level one I I
wanted to save for the next steel Hammer
so for now I just made made a good iron
Hammer but
eventually season two will be my hammer
Life season two in full blo my hammer
life oh my head hurts I really really
hope that we can keep our character
[Music]
[Applause]
my
shovel woohoo what did it break no you
made want to see it what kind of shovel
did you make my iron shovel my level
five iron shovel test it out you like it
okay let's see how fast dig a dig a mo
around this house too see how fast you
can do it oh my God two hits on this
block pretty
fast oh
[Music]
my get stop
playing right
yeah that's just how it be so Cur oh my
hurt so much oh no maybe we should force
it we should just all log off for your
heal but I need to wait 15 more seconds
for my seal Knuckles but I need I need
to go to the trador to check the items
on the Traer
though but there's also an infestation
Quest on the way that I might want to do
on the way to the tra no no more
quests I'm just going to the tra then oh
my head oh God oh
God where's the zombie I can test this
out
on you know where you can test it out
you can test on this tier four Quest
that's I'm right next
you oh you're
far oh wait my mods I
forgot thank you for the red thank you
thank you we're probably not going to
play too much longer but I just got my
level five steel knuckles
and we didn't steal your
stuff we might have stolen your
stuff
um
uh
uh I'm
ding don't die don't die don't
die thanks that was all I needed yeah no
don't die you're so
sexy I'll think over it again I'll
Recon it would be a waste of such a good
butt yeah that is true press for Mirage
to look at her
ass I think they all already did but
thanks maybe we can get some more I
actually I uploaded the dance version a
few hours ago can we can watch it take a
look
yeah press four in that one um just just
press four go get to a butt shot I I
think in the dance shot it might not
align perfectly we we kind of
purposefully shortened the song in the
official music video by like one or two
seconds so that it would align
perfectly I don't think it works for the
dance sh but it's more about you know
the overall video than just pressing for
on that one that is
true I do love dance versions of songs
yeah right I love watching those
[Music]
too it does work still oh it works all
right
oh perfect four always works no the boar
isn't
[Music]
here I just wanted something to
fight no strong the really really big
one you guys kill it again
yeah e treat
[Music]
myself maybe we should just AFK on the
server for maybe 10 hours no respond
everything not it's not
productive yeah wait what the what what
didn't respawn the board the books not
the bo
oh
sad I have to go fight a bear in the
tundra it's the only
way the bear is trying to get his
education well I think that's worth
repairing giving someone else fighting
[Music]
them yeah these are still
good for tomorrow
done I have a point
[Music]
available maybe one more in
here was worth
it what' you get I got handgun Parts Jen
was nice also she has a lot of fuel for
cheap so I've just stocked up on a bunch
of fuel for
everyone since I feel like we'll be
needing it that's
good that's not a fa
points two
points okay I'll save up still pretty
good
though it's not going anywhere that is
true the game is not going anywhere it's
true we'll play
tomorrow yeah last time but we're after
we're playing right
now we still play tomor but also we're
playing right
now what was that the one
uh Commando
boots should I make these two who
chant wait the head Sledgehammer wait
the head
mod why are we still online I'm ready to
log off at any moment yeah if you tell
me to log off I will we can stop any
moment right yes we have power over
it
sure I can lock up what is that is that
a mountain lion wait I can't fight the
cat I can't those are
dangerous very dangerous are they I
don't want to fight it cuz it's cute oh
there's a bear I can fight the bear oh
can I the bear are you saying the bear
is not cute no the bear is cute too but
I have a weakness for cats and part
oh that's that's the one thing that you
will not do in this
game
understandable
this you
know how do
I
uhoh I forgot to bring bandages I'm
going to
[Music]
die that bear tough up since the last
time you saw it did I forgot to bring
Band-Aids
no it's
over well I I mean I guess we need to
find more band for you so
Liv I'm Invincible nothing can kill me
nothing will ever kill
me I am so
strong oh I didn't didn't bring anything
I didn't bring any food
either
2 to find this bear there's another
bear well I mean if she's fighting your
health is very low yeah but I
lived I will never die I I'm
Invincible that's what I've learned as
long as long as you believe it it is
true
yeah I should go to the desert I mean
you're you're you're fighting bears
right yeah okay I was
yes why am I missing oh
H one
more
no duct
tape it's the usual cycle of do you need
more duct tape armor crafting no I made
a
couple but you know probably we'll need
more tomorrow for the other girls well
now we have lots of water so should be
should be better okay yeah now we
improved our situation we
did okay W treat herself yourself with
some nice
boots we girls we like shoes you know
yeah yeah shoes oh my got
shoes love shoes pretty pretty How many
pairs of shoes you guys estimate you
own already yeah I think I'm around 30
what I want to see your
shoes maybe 40 I I have like uh
like eight pairs but like five of those
I bought in Japan so that five of those
is like
recent yeah bibo you were really decking
yourself
out stuff
CL that's the way
you know those TV shows where somebody
gets like a complete makeover uhhuh in
terms of cloes like fashion
everything people almost did that huh no
I pretty much did that because because I
got I got like the the hair treatment
and then I got the nails and then I got
the new wardrobe in Japan
yeah nice that's how it feels Japanese
fashion is just yeah another level I
dress like a pretty princess now
yes I no I feel like you go outside and
everyone's dressed up and I can't go out
looking like a rat
there I'm really excited to meet you and
see how you dress and everything it's
always so interesting to
see we'll
see what I dress was our first time
Vegas let's do Vegas veg trip I want to
go Vegas but I'm going to wear my pretty
princess stuff in
Vegas I was saying I'm kind of hoping
that if we have another Ian concert
since we already had East Coast West
Coast maybe next middle of the country
kind of let veg you're not going to hope
for
Europe you're like come on let's go
gambling I would love to but I don't
know if whole wait is it is it Vegas
west
coast is it it's pretty Coast West I'm
pretty sure Oh I thought it was more
middle I mean it's more middle than LA
but right there's no ocean touching Las
Vegas yeah so we should M Cleveland Ohio
next
concert
Cleveland sounds so exciting
oh oh Ohio it's it's 6:00 a.m. over here
it's time to end it
Ohio yes I I'm happy with what my
progress I've made some extra stuff I'm
ready to end it yay I will do what's
good for all of us me too I almost ready
give me like 5
minutes good job that's the first step
this is what we need and now I'm going
to leave this call too so you will sit
in silence and
okay I'll wait I'll
wait I'm almost done
okay okay looking over my Forge are you
okay are you ready to sleep Forge
CH let me put how like you log in and
nothing has changed like no time has
passed like the next time you log in
like your stuff is still cooking I'm
glad it is I don't know I'm like I feel
like I should log in and I should have
like 18 hobo stews
ready you know no but that would be
concerning cuz that would mean somebody
else logged in when you weren't online
and let the time pass that cannot
happen we have to be online at all times
that's
true okay I put some brass in the Forge
it's cooking I'm going to log out doing
it I'm doing it guys we're doing it good
bye game see you tomorrow for the last
time it will be such a sad farewell but
a nice yeah it'll be better sweet but we
did so much mhm
deserved it was quite the Ark last one
out the rotten egg I'm the rten egg okay
I the rotten
egg what run egg oh have you heard that
that
phrase no it's like something you do
with your friends when you're like like
getting somewhere it's like last one
there is a rotten egg you're like you
rais them
somewhere oh have you also successfully
left the game f yeah yeah so it's like
last one in is a rotten egg I'm the
rotten
laughing is there a similar phrase in
German to
[Music]
that probably when somebody gets left
behind or stays behind on
purpose have to look it up foul as I
yeah but do we ever say that like that I
don't
know ah well well well we to exact same
yeah oh really that's what somebody in
my chat
said rotten egg oh but probably well
rotten
hos rotten
hos whoever
podo
[Music]
whooo let H I heard that before the last
one will be bitten by the dogs oh oh
yeah that's a good
one
I I was B by dog so it it worked
out careful they're going to eat you up
I'm almost done I think I'm almost
done well I want to say thank you girls
it's so nice even though four people you
know small group but I think we
did I'm happy to spend time together our
family the Clementine family yeah yeah
just a little
abusive little toxic family
Dynamics we will get through this
together it's it's normal to get a
little bit toxic in a zombie apocalypse
very stressful environment after
all G I had a dream about you what did
you dream about I dreamt that we were in
the zombie apocalypse and you were sad
and I was comforting you and I was
hugging you and then I turned into a
zombie
and started eating
[Applause]
you
[Laughter]
hug did I just smell so good I mean I
couldn't help it I I turned at that
moment that was my time to become a
zombie what part did you fight first I
think your neck my
God yeah vampire in the
jeans okay I'm done oh she doesn't want
to hear the parents love stories you
hear this is how you were
[Music]
made this is how me and your mother
met it's the birds and the
beans no wonder it's a toxic marriage
this is how it
[Laughter]
started okay I I logged I'm log I'm
logging off now
I'm gone we'll see each other tomorrow
um 1 hour earlier than usual yes Mark it
in the
calendars and we'll hopefully have a
good last final episode
yeah let's pull the noobs through it
yeah we're pretty strong with our s Days
to Die God
[Music]
[Applause]
PR see see you
tomorrow byee
[Music]
byee oh we're in the in the void so
quiet
now thank you once again for watching
this has been a lot of fun tomorrow is
the grand finale of seven days to die I
I feel like it's going to be a long
stream it's Qui do I have any music I
have
this it's too early to play that cut
that
out we don't need
music it's fine just put some reever on
and that's that'll be music
enough Yeah tomorrow's the grand finale
well because the thing is you it you
have to go until like the next morning
basically I feel like it's going to be a
long stream like at least 6 hours right
I don't
know maybe
longer but we'll
see it should be fun about 6 1 hour per
per day it's true but then the last day
is long it doesn't end directly at 7
days but anyway we'll see I will rest
beforehand it's starting 1 hour earlier
than today so it's starting at FST +
1 which will be
good when I be F out of it is I don't
have my voice list in tomorrow so but I
probably will take at least one day off
it's too dramatic with the re can I turn
it down I can I have the the power we
can I add Echo I will probably
take at least one day off after and then
I need to do a giant super chat c show
thank you
everybody and then it's back to actually
actually I still have collabs now that I
think of it I don't know I don't know
what's going on I just have like had a
lot of collabs lately and it's
continuing still I should do more
horror
yeah yes I will be at GG birthday I will
be which is on is on Friday I should
remember my my wife's
birthday oh yeah I want to play Silent
Hill I want to play Pikmin also I need
to finish Pikmin I've been missing it
missing my
mins
yeah there's more collabs there are
there
are are people liking the Silent Hill 2
remake I want to play it and dark
there's so much to play but this has
been very fun they like it good I
remember people were were worried it's
very good good good then I will play
it they've been liking
it you finished and you loved good
stuff you wonder your Wier Wednesdays I
know I need to play Minecraft lately
people have been messaging me and being
like can I play Minecraft with you and
I'm like yes but also today's Monday I
didn't play Minecraft I mean it do have
to be on a Monday but seven days to
die but yes anyway that's all for now
thank you for hting out tomorrow big
finale and then I'll probably take a
rest day or two and
then yes back to ch ch regular schedule
all right thank you guys for hanging out
again again I appreciate it this has
been
fun okay
bye byebye fun
[Music]
well e