[Music]
w
k k hello how are you guys oh just ended
the
video w w default outfit it yeah I don't
know I I
realized uh I don't use it that
much it's it's okay to use it every once
in a
while why you show up naked to
this because I'm trying
to get
um I'm trying to uh what's the
word bribe the game
or maybe I want to you know get uh the
this
hatama uh to be you know I I'm I'll try
I'm trying to be on its side you know I
don't want to make it feel naked all
alone yeah round and cute thank
you
oh and guys guys guys guys guys how you
doing welcome to my Holo parade
stream yesterday was kind of stressful
ending I apologize for that but it came
with some exciting news and uh let let
me just recap on that really quickly
especially because I changed one thing
in the schedule as
well
so first of
all
ta there has been an update in the
schedule I because I forgot because it
starts at midnight so when I was looking
at my
calendar uh I kind of missed out on that
because the calendar like kind of just
shows usually un unless I scroll around
it mostly just shows what's during the
day and late evening so I missed out on
the thing that I was planning all
along so on Saturday you can see
starting at midnight for me uh I am
planning to do a gartic phone with
artists yeah so I've been trying to
bring back some older stream types you
know that I've done before and that were
quite well received and GIC phone with
artists was one of them or actually yeah
I think I was like scroll for some
reason I was like on one day I was just
like scrolling through my whole YouTube
uh like stream history on my channel and
I was just like looking at thumbnails
and be like oh this one's so nostalgic
oh this one looked pretty good this one
was fun you know just like looking at
the pictures of you pictures of
me every once in a while I like looking
at those and then I got reminded of GIC
pH of artist and I was like oh I should
do one again mhm yeah hook Papa even was
in one in that one in the old
[Music]
one
yeah that must have been before my time
time oh yeah I guess
so it's a long time ago when was that
probably long time ago and it was
actually pretty fun it was quite a
spontaneous thing so some artists I even
like brought in during the stream I
think this time I'm asking them a little
bit more ahead of time and getting them
background checked so that I I won't get
bonked or
[Music]
so yeah that was good was fun oh yeah
money rushed in from the
bathtub yeah yeah yeah yeah I was like
money please join and she's like I'm I'm
on the
bath and then she quickly quickly came
over to the
PC yeah so I I got a I got a bunch of
cool artists like i' I've been trying to
like mostly go for artists that haven't
been part of it last time uh so like
first
time so there's been fan artists again
there's been artists that have already
worked for me uh and then there's some
even some more um how to
say High
[Music]
High what's the word high profile high
profile
artist so no Christina want Anita yeah
like oh man it hurts me like cuz her art
was so good if I need another one if I
feel like the ones I have lined up now
is is not enough then I might still like
ask
Christina because uh yeah the stuff that
she created was so good
Banky why are you mentioning Banky
reference to passport
two yeah some some senses yeah yeah yeah
I've been trying to get some cool people
so you guys were already excited about
the schedule before that but now it's
even more packed um yeah yeah I thought
I thought I wanted to uh bring some
exciting things this week like the
collapse too like first when I was
making the schedule I didn't really have
any collabs lined up and I was looking
at it I was like M this looks kind of
sad I should probably find a collab
partner or something and I've been
talking a lot to
crony uh recently so um I thought why
not with crony she can help me clean up
my she can help me organize my my home I
was thinking and then uh yeah we've got
something we P more rainpop because we
wanted to do a frog date frog VR date
for a long time and I said yo we can't
like keep on delaying it anymore let's
do it now now
now and I'm even like last minute uh I
wasn't really planning on it but yeah
last minute I'm getting uh like small
small additions made to the winter world
I just wanted to reuse the winter world
because I thought it's such a waste of
such a huge nice VR world and then yeah
I figured might as well use it again and
then we're adding some small things
too so yeah wedding
trample
no no just small
things relatively small
ah yeah okay um wait
so here's my
okay
uh let me ride the tangent list
[Music]
again for
today today on the menu we
have already I I already tell T tangent
tented from the get-go but you know can
never have
enough s let's use this I I rarely use
this memo thing but it's so hard to get
things to like fit into it
um kind of like what
this well that's fine or let me when I
size it down like this it get gets kind
of
[Music]
rough yeah that's that's
better more or
less H uh what else am I supposed to
talk about oh was there something
else
uh
ah my own life I guess m although not
not really not don't really want to talk
too much about it cuz I'll eventually
talk about it oh yeah Polaroids
Polaroids I guess I mean that's not
really a tangent but yeah ah sleep
talking M
[Music]
me
okay so like
this and
[Music]
okay I wish I wish I wish I could like
say that hey you're supposed to fit into
this area fit yourself suit yourself
no okay for now that's that we might
even think of uh
more later
[Music]
on
where's the game here okay all right
[Music]
oh let me resize this oh nice it resizes
itself thank you okay here we go I
noticed that in the loading screen it
shows the ones you already have cute uh
I have two scouting tickets from last
time still I guess uh where I just gave
up and
they I don't know if they did it because
of
me um maybe
partially but uh there has been made
some adjustments and everybody got some
more
tickets I feel like uh solely I should
have gotten tickets to balance it
out uh but that's okay okay so now I
have five
tickets
um with these five tickets I hope I get
someone else and also uh we are um not
going to get dupes anymore probably like
at least not as much as
before yeah it's it's the ease kata's
pain update but that doesn't undo the
pain I've suffered so
far like what am I going to do with this
account that already has free amdes on
level 12
huh wait I want to change one more
[Music]
thing but I appreciate the the the
M the thought behind
it trying to oh I hear
[Music]
myself Oh My My Stream is open on my
phone oh cuz I was on the I was chatting
on the phone sh phone wa be
[Music]
quiet let's try getting something good I
I I I
I I want to continue getting some more
myth characters but I also want to try
the others but H I got to I got to stay
loyal I have to stay loyal there will be
no more am if there was another am it
would be crazy and if anything I
probably won't even get any uh special
Ur uh Within These five tickets here
here are new ones though that's nice m
58 Long Range area attacks dealt by Abby
Fry's deep
voice oh really oh yeah I guess I'm yeah
I'm getting a a a Pity pick soon yeah
great I don't want that's that's just no
that's not how it should
be [\h__\h] gotcha medium range single
attack the slightly more damage to red
and blue Ora enemies oh and wait he has
a nice instrument meant
to
M I'll go
for I'll go
[Music]
for whatever for now I'll go for that
one the pora I like her
mascot okay Talent selection oh one wait
no how three more okay so we can choose
someone
soon huh huh huh how's the dup farming
going shut
up a these are also all new I guess the
the the change in like getting dupes
also applies to these
smaller uh characters or does it just
feel like it right
now oo short range single attack should
I go for the M
be opens uh the way in the on the the
front lines knock back blue and red Aura
close range area attacker occasionally
disables enemy
blocks 10 the cost is pretty expensive
shesh
don't you still want unique units for
trophies it's just like having everybody
gives me a trophy strong in offense and
defense against black or enemies sure
why not why
not if you get seven am maybe you can
summon her
you need for black Ora later okay
okay M I thought you got Pioneer last
time I thought so too I guess I
didn't see still nothing special cuz I
just got wasn't my last amip pole also a
Pity pole Wen both my am PO is a petty
pole besides the first
one
so I think so oh death Sensei is
new sure why
not so with this one we obtain a
selection Scout
ticket but I would like to get a UR with
this one too please
no fine oh is also new I think I had it
as a choice before but I didn't choose
it a sturdy skull-shaped metal cup that
has come to life close-range single
attacker deals double damage to blue
aura
okay my game Crash oh what the [\h__\h] why
would you capture that I don't
understand well whatever look at it then
my game has
crashed well well I am after all a game
bug
tester should come back in a second I
think
[Music]
oh yeah I [\h__\h] up the settings here
okay all right all right so what happens
to my gacha one
ticket so did I get the
do no no oh no there it is there it is
okay that has been applied did I get
my what
[Music]
is it's here okay okay okay okay
okay there It Is Well who do I choose
who's the
best let's see oh 36 24 uh 28
27 okay so the most expensive is CI is
she also the best who should I choose
guys the well
Wawa medium range area attacks by the
Flames of the Phoenix sometimes defends
enemy attacks strong in offense and
defense against black or
enemies I mean that sounds good medium
range area so
AOE long range area attacks de by froze
of the mighty Trident first
Trident deals great damage to red or
enemies while knocking them back
occasionally ignores enemy blocks now
700 170 o I'm I have quite a lot of
HP oh I have the most HP out of
everybody and oh and the most damage out
of everybody 340 and
area look look at the damage mine is the
most and my HP is the most my DPS
is my DPS is also the
highest and I'm not even the highest
cost who yeah a war yeah here it comes
in handy
[Music]
again and my instrument oh OHA and call
have the same
instrument okay let's
go I guess that's what I'm using it
[Music]
[Laughter]
for one more one more one
[Music]
more I don't know it it kind of high
bloop it kind of makes me mad that
like I have to go to these measures to
get someone besides am you
know well that's okay I of course have
to level myself myself up quite a
bit uh what level is everybody else on
here uh
eight 9 10
okay it's your fault for claiming the
number one
gos it's been a while hope you're doing
good thank you welcome to the
stream please enjoy it welcome to the
stream to W yay and maybe one more
oh black defense wait don't we
already we already have black defense
plus 30 black black attack plus 50 you
give me black defense plus six why not a
different
color why
[Music]
not what what's is this normal yeah I
guess it Stacks okay yeah but I don't
know I feel like it would have been good
uh to have something else what
uh oh we only have one so we don't
really want to do that now right
okay um then I don't know I think we can
go to the next stage to the next whole
like story thingy because we finished
these two last time was trying really
hard to finish the last one of non-stop
story and then once we figured out
what's the right way to do it it was so
easy
suddenly let's go proceed to parade uh
free one oh wait my team
oh oh I oh I didn't look at my team oh
well let's hope this is
[Music]
appropriate my formation we'll see if
this
works oh blue
blue we can deal with that the taco
dases can probably deal with
that
pun oh we need another
tank y y y y by y oh I was almost there
there we go Bubba Let's Go
Bubba yeah okay this is kind of
[\h__\h]
[Music]
okay R's level four
finally Bubba sweep
really let me get Bubba back
Bubba
ba should I spam I don't know man oh
[\h__\h] that is not good I I need I need a
different
formation
uh
forfeit what should my formation be
there were a lot of blue uh
enemies
[Music]
so oh ni ni has blue but like the cost
is still sick so getting there will take
a while but we can replace them for sure
nickel is overpowered
anyway surely the cat will help
me
um T can
[Music]
stay ah we can bring in the yukim Min
pretty low cost and uh good against
Blue then to cost
[Music]
h h I can oh yeah this is new an angel
will appear to offer a helping
hand let's go what kind of helping hand
like how how how are you going to help
me and we'll we'll find
out I'm
excited okay and then I don't think we
really want to use Wawa just yet not in
this
situation we'll we'll
find a time where it's uh
works out
[Music]
best should I level the dog
maybe do you guys think the dog is
[Music]
good got to put in the waa replace Taco
with waa I don't even we're probably not
even going to get to
28 or if we do then it's at the end of
the battle
probably
[Music]
you can have W as a trump
card not with that
attitude but do you guys generally think
this one's a good one to like level up I
I I will give it a chance because like
it's very blue focused if we have
trouble going up against blue
boys he cell I have no problem problem
summoning her well how far are you in
the
game let's bring in the dark and replace
uh with the same
instrument uh you know
what ah okay that's fine we can I don't
know if I'll really get you know time to
shine but let's
try
[Music]
W let's
go oh the duck the duck is actually
probably going to destroy the yukim
Min F yukim
in just it's just getting
drunk oh I already have easily voltage
level four that's
pretty
good keep them coming keep them coming
maybe a new one oh yeah the Cat Let's
Go destroy destroy them destroy the blue
[Music]
tachis and now
won another
one can we get to eight
perhaps
let me just summon everything again yeah
we're pushing now we are pushing
now H cat is strong but um not very
[Music]
defensive don't be mean to us what does
this
do wo I think it
missed is level
six I think it this use dog yeah yeah
yeah here we go two
dogs two dogs in the
house Bow Bow Bow Bow and we got the
shield
go now we have reached the end of the
wall uh or the beginning of the
wall I guess we still need to push a bit
more
fine
okay dogs have good HP so they can work
as tanks yeah it's still
alive oh there it is yada first clear
reward as well
well easy I mean it was not not a easy
sweep but we managed do it let's see
what the next one has to offer and we
might have to adjust our team
again we should remove the 12 and
expensive well what I wanted to it was
fine I wanted to try it out you
know wasn't even that
expensive it's probably not going to be
blue ones again right it's probably
going going to be a different color and
I'll be in
trouble nickel Army
[Music]
hey and Vol
four can we get to
six yes easy oh so far I don't they
don't even have any any like specialized
colors so
far from what I can tell this level is
easier eh this level is way easier than
the previous one I'm not
even having to
think and
you I mean okay they cleared up my line
a little bit but besides
that blue Loops are good lowc cost
tanks bloop is considered a
tank
[Music]
Nan go go can yo this time certainly it
hit
[Music]
something I don't know what to send out
this is just uh already over anyway just
give up
already you have no chance I am breaking
the wall I'm breaking all walls
especially the fourth
wall bloop has a helmet he
tank I mean bloop has a deal of G of
course he has to be tank what what what
no like if he were a good tank then I
feel like he would be able to stand his
ground against gura and so far I don't
really see that at all in
him looks so
stupid
has almost no offensive ability but very
durable thanks to its bubble barrier no
this bubble should really not be that
protective have damage from red or
enemies not all
okay might be worth leveling him for the
future
yeah if I need a cheap
uh basically a bubble wall yeah
M on that note how about we try it out
cuz they're actually the same instrument
and I want to see something new don't we
[Music]
all go next go next speaking of go next
did you guys see ena's
concert
Ena concert the
yesterday for me it was in the night of
yesterday oh my God it's blue it's blue
it's
blue yeah it was quite interesting
because like for most of it until the
very end oh God we need a lot of
Yuki
uh oh
dear until the very end uh uh uh what
was I going to say yeah it was like
grayscale pretty much but at a certain
point oh my God they brought uh oh but
gloop is really defensive they brought
in some colors back Violet
haha uh okay I'm standing my ground but
this is uh quite a lot to
handle keep on bringing in the Yuki me
let's wait a little bit for something
new
there we
go okay y y y me oh no the Y
in oh are we being raided welcome to the
stream I'm struggling a little bit right
now uh-oh uh-oh you're not standing out
ground anymore please help can thank you
uh that was uh important but uh
dying okay to this is not going to
work I like ena's new OG song oh yeah
yeah yeah she was uh performing a new
song I asked her when when released she
said not very
soon still working on it but yeah she
called it she she named it after another
flower which was spoilered I I wrote to
her while it was being like revealed I
was like hey yo he yo yo new song called
named after flower
y yo you did it didn't you you sneaky
sneaky
Taco oh thanks for the membership
[Music]
gifts yeah but it was really pretty like
the the songs she
chose damn she's so good at like singing
those type of
songs
yeah she has such a interesting type of
voice it it fits to sing like fragile
sounding songs you know what I mean it's
hard to describe
really uh blue we we are kind of like we
have what we need against Blue but I
it's it's hard for me to get to that
point do I have another blue that can
replace the crow
[Music]
maybe
no oh the taco DOI yeah let's bring in
the takachi even though it's the same
instrument as somebody else but takachi
is pretty durable so that should
help oh we could even bring the
duck duck is pretty low
cost low cost and highly mobile
m
I I will level it no
problem but
where where does it go ah ah would I
don't know if it's worth replacing but
we let's try because I do need something
low cost and it's the same instrument so
I would have to switch it out with that
I would say let's give it a
try yeah so turns out exactly one week
after ena's um stream concert
is
mine prise
surprise it actually makes so much sense
because I did um miss her in Japan like
exactly we were we were we just like
missed each other by a day or
so no pretty
sad
H we talked a little bit about it
beforehand too like we're trying to
figure out if we can see each other but
nope ain't
happening it is what it is oh this works
better this definitely works better know
[Music]
hold okay now I'll I'll try
to
wait
uh and now we're getting motivation
pretty fast anyway it's okay it's okay
oh we're already at the wall okay no
worries no worries
then yeah AOE is good
yeah
got and the pecking of the duck surely
helped as
well there we go that was easy once you
have the right team it's like night and
day very
[Music]
different NOA hint you surprised me
there I'm sure you're making good use of
the public relations department but I'd
like to share some tips with you okay
why not right in the beginning huh first
and foremost the most important part of
public relations activities is demand
research basically we look for demand
what people looking for and our
interested in from everyone's social
media post and then deciding on their
public relations policy that meets the
requirements however you should be
careful how many reactions there are
yeah okay I was already looking at that
thank you thank you yeah so new site the
M should be prioritized yep yep yep
yep pretty sure I already know that
speaking of it should we wait for one
more until it's five until it's Max I
think
so I think we
should don't like being social media
manager the flag things is are a bit
more difficult I suppose oh yeah yeah
they
are probably the next one is one of
those I wish I could see beforehand like
what awaits me so I can prepare my team
but I guess I got to fail once to
understand oh no no flag
level
[Music]
mother I'm very blue oriented right now
I wonder if that's going to be a
problem but yeah I was saying I was
talking about Ena and I want to say like
uh in case you didn't know at the very
end I I was singing together with the
other girles we were singing the
song what was it called again I don't
remember but we sang like the last
chorus which is like really
high
but no problem for me I like singing
hi good job maybe I'll sing it in K one
time because I was introduced to it
thanks to the
stream we were we were all singing at
the same time but when I was listening
to it in the Stream I feel like I heard
my voice so loudly is it just like
because I'm so familiar with my own
voice I
wonder oh they're pushing back a little
bit
heo
maybe what do I
need I stand out yeah maybe because my
my high register is like pretty strong
so you can hear it pretty clearly uh-oh
uh-oh
[Music]
uhoh save for Wawa save they
save then I wait then let me make a
little wall of
Loops okay okay little bloop wall I
don't know if I can get to 28 man
leave the bloop
[Music]
alone no no
no take blop take
blop okay here we go let's go yo it's
I'm almost dead B come on no
[Music]
wow a little bit too late
no okay there were no specific colors so
we can change our team a little bit
um maybe bring him
back and uh two
threee let's get yukim min out there and
replace
with
M replace eight and 12 of lower cost
eight and 12 no maybe the
12 12 let's replace them
with why not
Bubba because kind of expensive as well
but we can bring in Bubba to replace it
with a
[Music]
yeah right because his uh instrument
helps with the recovery
speed and
then difficult choices do I have this
instrument in right now no I
don't
I wonder if this is
better replace a tackle with
what with
what look for tanking no knif will be
fine for
[Music]
tanking ah different
instruments oh yeah I guess that's the
one that's overlapping okay yeah that
makes sense
then uh we could
[Music]
do perhaps you it's not too expensive to
Pro
no we'll also try to level them up a
little bit
okay let's
go
[Music]
the beginning was fine they only started
pushing me later on which was quite
[Music]
surprising come on come on come on come
on come on come on come on come on yep
V level
six and almost PBA
time it's almost B time there we
go show him what you
got bite them bite I saw this crazy
video today of um
a like some guy was filming his dog
getting excited about a pigeon on his
balcony the dog was like waddling his
tail and looking at the the
pigeon and then he's like oh are you
excited do you want to greet the pigeon
do you want to greet the pigeon y you
want to make friends so he opens the
door sick and bubble he opens the door
it was golden retriever by the way he
opens the door and then his golden
retriever Runs Out rushes out and
attacks the pigeon which the moment they
open the door already trying to escape
but the the the dog is really fast and
the dog like tries to bite and I like
it's hard to see in the video cuz
everything happens so fast but the dog
tries to bite
the the pigeon and like you see like
everything's so shaky cuz the owner is
also like what the [\h__\h] is going
on and then like afterwards you see like
there's like pigeon poop on the
ground and some feathers and the the
pigeon flies
away seemingly it survived but I I do
think the dog got a little a little bite
a little taste of the pigeon holy [\h__\h] I
did not
think that
dogs especially a golden retriever would
do that but in the comments it said
golden retriever are like hunting dogs
and I guess yeah I I guess I heard that
before but attacking a pigeon as a as a
like a dog who probably isn't trained as
a hunting dog yeah maybe it's in his
nature but I mean he's is a normal like
pet dog so I would think that that
instinct is being held back a little
[Music]
bit they're badly trained if they do
that yeah probably yeah I guess the
owner doesn't like train his dog much to
like you
know hold back his instincts or hold
back his excitement
but I guess not necessarily because the
owner thought the the intentions were
different so he did encourage his dog to
go outside he let his dog outside
because he thought the dog was just
trying to make
[Music]
friends Golden
Retriever
yeah hopefully the pigeon was fine it it
there was a scene at the end of it where
the pigeon flies away I I hope it's the
same pigeon and not just like him
filming a different pigeon trying to
calm the audience I would hope so hi GAA
by the
way [\h__\h] man festivals bring energy to
the city but some find them to be
[Music]
noisy that that sounds like critique
that sounds
like not necessarily like a
fan
uh that doesn't sound very
supportive like they don't it doesn't
sound like they want me to bring a
festival to their
city like stay away it's too too noisy
[Music]
Auntie h
should have done it at four was a better
prompt yeah but I don't
[Music]
know okay so is it a local
Affair
or
because or somebody said polite
inaccurate just are we trying to damage
control but then noisy I
guess
that is like hinting on the word audio
but oh I guess we'll try that
[Music]
okay it's pretty difficult to guess
what's the right
prompt what an attractive voice the
results turn out good okay really you
think so it did match to sinr okay
[Music]
oh damage control is working nicely
smoothly
oh I mean not bad we didn't
fail I would say morning Tanto good
morning social media job never easy nice
PR work thank you I'm Miss announcer
voice oh you think she voiced
it would be be nice all right go next go
[Music]
next oh it's a flag one okay so that
means I have
to
stall keep
my
uh try to get the voltage up fast but
don't spam too
much
characters don't push too much but what
if it's no
yeah probably oh we'll probably fail the
first time anyway because once they
bring
out uh oh what's so
strong that's the last one I'm summoning
don't worry what should I do Bubba to
I'm doing bubble
too okay oh we we got
[Music]
seven okay I'm holding back
now
yeah it's pretty
good and W is ready should I summon her
already wait what do I do now I forgot
what do I do in this
situation can I go
[Music]
now I can go now right
don't know what expects me though that's
the
issue yay wa what did I say something
about fire make the wa louder I want to
hear her
[Music]
more that's what I said that's what she
said
attacking pretty slowly but surely
effectively Yoo ooh
red red
oh wa wa stay strong stay strong for
me I'm counting on
you I'm going to continue summoning uh
red boys then oh another Wawa I can only
have one in the field at a time I see
okay okay but when she guys we can
summon another one
quickly are we first trying
this yes we are yes we are
mhm go go W go
go I believe in
you don't let the haters get you
down
woo
oh that's pretty tough it's pretty
tough it's pretty tough oh she's going
to die again oh and I don't have it but
but it's they're about to die too there
we go there we go there we go one more
hit come on yay I the rest is just
normal enemies okay we did it first
try
y
to keep Max Symphony I guess so yeah but
it worked it worked it was
fine
uh just got to push back
again you B when she went
down cute I look like a giant next to
these
other characters walking next to them
they must be terrified and they can all
look up my
skirt don't you
dare the duck comes running
in another W my my third my fourth
W it's fine you have spots yeah yeah I
guess I still don't want you to look at
them doesn't change
anything let's make a duck
army they run so
fast duck duck goose duck that goose
more
more keep them coming keep them coming I
like seeing an army of ducks they're so
[Music]
cute y
y woo
wait do you only get the scouting ticket
if you clear it on the first
try ah ah no it's
uh oh cuz I was wondering why I didn't
get them in the other ones but it's not
for everyone every second one is with a
first clear wward
okay
ah and there's a random chance too okay
okay no this one was like
secure okay next one I don't get one
unless it's a
random try get as next to's the only
healer in the game super op now oo
ruin also heard suicide is
op has been 3 years thank you for such a
long support I appreciate
it you also have already have three yeah
I know I'm just kind of like
waiting until I have like more maybe
five or so oh Winter Wonderland
time let's go Wawa Kelly also got Wawa
Wawa was her
first you are Talent yesterday in her
stream
if that doesn't tell you something then
I don't know oh speaking of that me and
Kelly are releasing let me talk about it
properly now we're releasing an original
song this
week so look forward to that I mean
can't say much either because she's also
keeping a bunch of things uh secret
[Music]
right here we
go oh but it it has been long awaited I
think like we started working on
it over half a year ago or like started
talking about it and then like planning
it over half a year
ago and then I I sent in my vocals ages
ago I think but
then there was no Pro progress
made for a long time and I was like M
maybe maybe we should get this out soon
and and then
suddenly everything started coming
together finally it's coming out let's
go people have been waiting for this I
mean it's it I think Callie said she
wants to make an original song with
every myth
member I think that's what she said
before so like it was bound to happen
but I think uh you know for Takami it
just makes so much sense
[Music]
let's go let's
go yeah walk into the fire yeah oh and
now I heard clearly cuz there was no bgm
yeah walk into the fire
yeah what stream was that
from do you guys
know yeah I I did a a song cover with
every myth member in the early days go
and uh Callie won want to do that was
easy Callie wants to do a original song
wow good luck with that sounds like a
lot of
[Music]
work probably
Minecraft sounds like Sims could be Sims
too
yeah was I trying to get someone to die
cuz otherwise that wouldn't make no
sense originals are incredibly hyp
mhm I mean I think covers can be just as
hype because I
mean the covers I did with myth I think
they were all really really really well
received and they were all such a a nice
surprise and a nice
present ah oh yeah I was probably trying
to get a villager to walk into the fire
that that could have been it
mhm
mhm the Classic Country Roads the
Country Roads is something else she says
there are a lot of extra Hoops for
Originals of other h of now of her being
ing yeah yeah she just can't release it
the same way I think she said something
like that but we're making it work and I
hope you guys will like the song it's
been a long time in in the in the
works and it's about time it's about
time I saw people freak out about this
like I was looking at the quote
retweets and of the first and the second
announcement and like there's some
old old H why didn't the other clicks
not work there's some old um fans Takami
fans who came back from their grave like
oh
Takami oh my God I'm not an active fan
anymore but oh this is super special and
yeah it
is it really
[Music]
is you're welcome tamole
fans haven't gotten Mone out of the
Grave yet I think I don't think she
reacted did
she oh my God let me bring out my units
for [\h__\h] sake I just want to get a
full
[Music]
Symphony I love that song Symphony from
um what's their name I sang it
before
[Music]
what do I actually need to tackle these
These are so strong the only mascots are
so strong more amas I I'll try Oh you
mean Oh you mean I thought you meant
more bubas but you meant if I got more
dupes no it shouldn't happen anymore
because they uh changed the system a
little bit dupes shouldn't be so common
anymore supposedly
[Music]
okay now we're we're making it
work we're making it work it's going to
be
fine could be better but yeah I I do
think there was uh like I I I I made
them take that step cuz I was quite
salty about
it but you know it's a it's a fan Gata
game why not
you know there's no reason for them cuz
they don't even make like extra money
with the gacha like other gacha
games there's no reason to be like
really uptight about it and and give the
worst percentages ever of pulling
something good like certain other gacha
games there's no reason to do
that make it a bit more friendly than
other gacha games out
there
not too friendly of course because then
it's doesn't feel like gotcha
[Music]
anymore not sure what to send out to be
honest no but we're we're fine we're
almost
done ah yeah look at look at them now
look at them
go maybe they fought it needed to change
I didn't here's a here's a secret I
didn't really uninstall the
game I didn't actually do
that should have taking the criticism
while ultimate the game as fun as it can
be yeah exactly I mean it's not really I
wouldn't even call it criticism just
like
ideas that I had I
lied out of nowhere a wild Anon hint
appears oh okay hooray in the next stage
there will be an army of red oh thank
you for telling me ahead of time as we
learned previously red or enemies have
double Health as well as double
attacking power right that's right def
for the next stage yep yep thank
you that's fine poo oh they mention
poo suming two or more tal yeah no
problem I know what to do thanks for
telling me what's going to happen
po no
wait
[Music]
yeah red H so we could get uh yukim Min
replaced as
[Music]
well do we have something
cheap the
W what am I going to do with the Wawa
she's the same
instrument m
upgrade yeah over overall upgrades I
could also do
[Music]
that the pirate
crew oh that's also the same instrument
what the
[Music]
hell but then my team is overall pretty
high cost one
two
[Applause]
[Music]
oh wait bloop has
uh the red defense
thingy half it by
50% I
guess this is okay I
guess don't use sh
b
m
[Music]
ah we can upgrade someone who's like
level 9 or level eight and see what they
get for level
10 maybe someone low cost because that
might help
[Music]
me I'm going to try with
obak hopefully I
get not it's
blue of course it's blue what else would
it be it's always the thing I don't need
in the moment how about we upgrade the
Knight as
well are you not feeling naked no I'm
good thank
you as long as you don't see anything
below you know my collar
bones ah we're getting red attack plus
uh% against red
okay that brings
you a little bit higher in my importance
although you have the same instrument so
I don't know what is better bringing in
bloop or bringing in the Knight what do
you think
guys bloop helps with the
defense of the red enemies and the
Knight helps with the attack they're
both tanks so the knife
okay he is a little bit
cheaper and then I can probably still
upgrade someone
else oh Neco also already has red by the
way and he gets another one let's go
let's go a
ni getting more and more
useful defense and attack m
thank you I
feel an orang bias you were surely doing
that to please
me thank
[Music]
you how about the sub duck can I get him
to 10 as
well yeah but it's going to be black
that's okay for the future I'll probably
need
[Music]
it the you came in
gold attack okay I barely have anything
against gold so that's also fine
honestly I'm running out of
money
but for now wait who I was going to who
was I going to bring is this team fine
what do you think
Guys these
are Tachi still an option I would
say how
about but T right Taki has the same
[Music]
instrument would you think do you think
we should
replace them at
least for the red coverage and cheaper
cost it's fine right it's fine to have
one less
instrument show
[Music]
let's see how it goes it's fine if we
fail but the Neco upgrade I think is
quite
op the Neo with the Knight the Knight
also got a red upgrade right
so that's pretty
[Music]
op yeah we're already
pushing pretty pretty
decent a
nice
no wait I'm I'm I'm trying to yeah there
we
[Music]
go
okay the crow can attack from behind
stay away stay distant now we're
pushing let's
go what are we lacking oh I almost hit
Bubba won't get to
[Music]
him okay well level six hey I'm waiting
for poo now wait more or less oh
actually wait I can't wait I can't
afford to wait
ah waiting soon oh wa the fist the fist
will be very
useful I think I thought so it's okay we
have
poo
po uh I would like another coron skin
and another BB then we get there we go
our maximum possible level
easy nothing gets in the way of Po here
I'll send you another one there it
[Music]
goes don't fight back just give up
already just give up oh they don't want
to give up
[Music]
H that's holy [\h__\h] that's the first time
I watched the K konus ski attacking and
with one bite it killed three
[Music]
enemies that one bite that's a powerful
bite shees e
okay let me look at let's Scout a little
[Music]
bit count to you are appearance
for
oh should I still go for the myth I
think out of loyalty I want to continue
with the myth until I have them all you
know I can't help
it
in wow she looks so nice she's
floating perfect now I got three out of
five
yay clost 27 continuous long range
tentacle attacks that has area effect
massive damage if able to inflict
multiple hits deals increased damage
towards blue and red Ora
enemies
nice thank you
tasar now we only need Calli and
goba y that was not even a Pity pool was
it oh
but oh it does reset this counter I
thought it would keep on
going
okay oh oh a new one
lunit close range single attacker
sometimes blocks enemy attacks Hales
damage from black or enemies
cost is pretty high
though now we need another am no we
don't if it reset I think it was a Pity
no but it said uh free until you are a
parent so I don't think it was a
[Music]
Pity hi okay cute the way the COI
assistant is sitting down is so adorable
oh my God I want to give it
pets I want to give it belly rubs I want
to touch the fluffy
tail so I have to I have to get the
doggle have to adopt the
doggle so cute she do a sit a good sit
who's a good
assistant o I have uh sh already so I'll
go for the Pioneer finally short range
attack that opens the way on the front
lines now expect blue and red more
enemies
okay all right all right all right uh
probably the next level isn't so focused
on red enemies so we can switch things
out
again how about this make my my team
overall cheaper oh but wait this
overlaps
[Music]
H how about this
and
and can bring in the
[Music]
Yuki then we have all the instruments
again eight instruments and pretty low
cost team besides the puyo and the
[Music]
Wawa have you looked at what Ena can do
yeah I read it out loud did I
not should I switch to Ena a level I
don't think I have I don't think I have
enough to level her to a good
level not yet let's wait a little bit
then we can switch it
[Music]
out you didn't take it in same most of
the
time can you produce a flame to warm
your hands up come here just if you type
in the chat a
lot
then I I will be able to get my my own
heat across through the keyboard just
type a lot
like and magically totally not for you
typing really fast and moving your
fingers no for you touching the keyboard
the connection let's me transmit my
heat M it's real it's
true so keep on writing comments CH
chat
it works right 10 out of 10 oh my
God I know I know it works that's why I
told you to do
[Music]
it I feel like in The Last
Story chapter thingy there were so many
flag levels like every second level was
a flag level
but this time that's not the case at
all easy easy not a single colored
enemy are you guys excited for my guest
announcements for my own life by the way
on Sunday I finally
have my birthday
life
yay I called it end of the year concert
because I just thought it's half a year
later I I don't want to call it my
birthday concert it's just
weird Ena still went through with it I
know and that's fine but for myself I I
I just thought it's kind of weird I'm my
birthday is not in the winter so I call
called the end of the year
concert yeah I'm going to announce them
beforehand I saw some Japanese Senai do
that with their own concerts and you
know you can either keep it a secret and
surprise everybody or you can announce
it beforehand and I thought I'll I'll
announce it beforehand because I want to
Hype you guys
up yeah yeah and then the the members
who I do announce can talk about it
beforehand and also promote it so
I thought that might be pretty good
when's the first announcement I think
tomorrow I will announce the first one
probably and then every day it's it's
um not all guests will be announced uh
separately if you know what I mean like
there may be like two announcements at
once on one or two days or
so yeah
[Music]
maybe so hyped just from the concert
happening yeah me
[Music]
too yeah I'm going to be announcing them
in the form of photos
screenshots from the recording
day yeah yeah
yeah
they look so
cute ah it's a flag level Maga well I
mean let's see how it
goes let's
[Music]
see that's all I'll do for
now see how good that works although
they send out quite a lot of enemies
let's send out nickel a
nickel
oh this level five is is that too
much is this too much right now too
many oh
okay stop pushing chill
out you know in Ark Knights you can like
bring back characters that you already
summoned I wish you could do that uh for
this game too that would be Tactical
[Music]
quite
big yeah the music is
Halloweeny yeah recall them bring them
back on to the
bench okay I'm collecting I'm collecting
the
motivation what going well this good
right
[Music]
H when is it time to start
pushing get want to get
uh a little bit
more I think a although yeah I'm scared
I wonder what the color will be of the
big boss
enemy okay I'm pushing a little bit
now slowly but
surely oh by the way sorry about the
time like it was really hard for me to
decide what time frame I want to go
for oh uh blue and red I think blue and
red
[Music]
oh
magikal oh okay we're holding we're
standing up
ground but yeah two are down two of the
bosses are
down W let's go come on y y indeed
it might work it might work first try
yeah so I was I was going to say um I
was I was considering doing it during na
prime time as
well um but you know it was a hard
Choice um I also don't want to
completely abandon the EU fans of course
since I do usually stream during EU time
and I thought since it's on a weekend
you guys will forgive me
right it's at least a the weekend day so
na fans I know especially PSD is kind of
[\h__\h] with 5
a.m. uh-oh I get another push if they
take down the flag so it will it should
be
okay actually I want the push
please
be oh
the push did not help so
much not sure what to do right
now a
no okay okay that's fine our our
formation wasn't really um adjusted to
this situation anyway it was blue and uh
red
though I did summon kiar but I I
couldn't just wait for her
either yeah I was outrange let's use the
flag strategy again let them take your
flag before you push your
okay wait actually Ena is kind of
perfect cuz she has blue and red and she
does AOE and there's like free bosses so
I might want to switch these out if I
have the money to level
her yeah a little bit she's she's level
nine that could be
fine letting him take your flag makes
things a lot easier okay
okay yeah she's ranged too so she'll
stay in the back and
then I mean they all have something
useful but
but do I have this instrument no okay
then I think I want the Tachi cuz Tachi
have same cost as the UB but both blue
and
red blue might be good here cat to
squishy yeah
yeah
maybe even a dog for a little bit more
like buff enemies buff uh talents
protect
me or even a c on a
skin you mean me and Ina K kiaha and
Ina don't think I can afford that and
the fan mask is oh yeah that would be
cool if there's a bonus for having a
pair like
this
Tak good combo you legit mean me and you
know
oh let's try it this way
first let's see how this
[Music]
goes so we want them to take our flag
first but I also want to
get uh enough Symphony uh enough
voltage
so maybe this much five and see how they
go I could bring out Bubba now can is
that too much if I bring out Bubba now
it will the motivation will go up faster
but no but we're already already too
strong look at
us oh now the ni died now the Niel and
the Niel died
okay
okay hands off now hands
[Music]
off I li I
lied I
lied
don't don't attack the flag guys don't
attack the
flag
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay
okay how is
[Music]
this
Bon
[Music]
okay we rolling
now T
punch Taco punch you said
cute can the tacos really punch though
because
they don't
have they don't actually have uh arms ah
youa not push back but it's okay we're
standing strong and immediately the
enemy po are almost
dead they don't stand a
chance let's go Ena stay back no don't
get
hurt even if she dies we have enough
motivation to immediately spawn a new
one ah oh but she does have a cool down
not a h all we'll support her in the
meantime five 4 a three a two a one and
let's
go so my dear na fans who are up right
now since we're up for this stream
surely you'll be up for
my
upcoming concert at 5 or 6 or 7 or a.m.
your time right right right you'll be
there for me right perfect for me really
it'll be early burbs yeah the early BBS
will catch the
worms Oh yeah and I wanted to talk about
the fact that there's a a member's only
UNC so I think it's the first time that
an member gets to do this not that it
wasn't allowed before but we just didn't
have the opportunity until now I
think um um so what that means it's not
just me from home doing a little 3D K or
whatever no no no it is an
extension a direct extension of the
concert oh oh let's go
cute it's like pretty short but it's uh
as long as I could make it with the time
constraints you know and me having to
learn so many songs and dances
already yeah but it's like basically a
little extension it's it's like from the
same recording it's also like a concert
edited in the same
quality and it's just for you just for
my members to
see yeah I I could have just said no I
don't want to do
it um and it would have been less work
for me but I I I really wanted to take
this
opportunity
yeah so it's not it's not very long it's
like just like 15
minutes probably I'm not sure I didn't
get the Final Cut yet but it's probably
just like 15 minutes which is uh
seemingly what most Japanese members go
for uh in their own an
[Music]
orders it's better than nothing you
don't even know these 15 minutes how
long that took me like IRL
to like prepare and record
that do you guys have choreography
lessons uh I I usually learn my dances
alone I hire a a choreographer to make a
video of the choreography and then I
learn it at my own on my own but in
Japan I did have a bunch of uh
choreography
dance
lessons because not really for me but
because the
guests they usually don't want or like
feel capable of learning it on their own
for a
video so in those cases we just have
dance lessons with the with a teacher
even even if the dance is not from the
teacher they the teacher learns the
dance and then teaches it it to us it's
honestly more easy for me too to learn
it with a teacher because I
mean it it gets very confusing because
like it's so much Coro at once like
packed into two hour lessons usually
learn a whole Cho in two hours um so
when I learn it with a video only at
home then I can go in my own
pacing but then I also get kind of lazy
and also like the details get lost
sometimes and some difficult moves I'm
I'm like what the [\h__\h] how do I do this
but a teacher yeah it's a lot at once
but at least it's like very concentrated
and and easier to learn because they
like show it and explain it more
professionally yeah
mhm thank you guys for the
memberships so the members Uno I will I
think I saw Japanese members have it on
public until it starts so that people
see it and maybe get motivated to join
so I'll probably be doing that too I
I'll have up to reservations just so you
guys don't get get confused I'm saying
it now it will probably be public until
the stream
starts can you rate it yeah that's the
plan I guess should be raing it
uh these are almost all the same except
for the boys at school admire the parade
is a little bit more than the
others the boys at school local affairs
Maybe
video
[Music]
maybe oh this one's pretty good the dog
wow
andon your time to shine again modern
and
[Music]
cool you think so my milkshake bring
milkshake brings all the boys in the ah
thank you for all the memberships thank
you thank you chunky
chunk I don't know I'll just try with
this it
oh second time it crashes
today what
it wait the gacha last time it worked
but what about the what about the pr
activities Oh no okay it didn't happen
okay
crashing a
lot is this what they want because I
don't know what you want I can't read
your mind
people overall it was well
made it doesn't match
[Music]
IM please do well anyway can it go viral
anyway it won't if that's even
possible have you yet to see crash I
don't
know why you think it's my PC yeah we
seem to be losing our views to a similar
r that has been posted what those
fakers
[Music]
copycats I man this is not too
bad good job you
too can't always read the mind of
everybody
yeah I don't think why how could it be
my PC I mean it has been acting a little
bit weird sometimes
but still maybe the recent patch yeah
cuz it didn't happen the last time but
who knows that's fine though that's fine
because the game starts up so fast
anyway it's okay
and did I change my
[Music]
formation um
I it's a low cost formation mostly
actually we can probably work with this
whatever
happens so yeah what else is there to
say I said we have a members
only
onore
and members uh guests will be announced
beforehand and
and I'm excited and sorry for the weird
time
slots is there something else I wanted
to say probably more tangents after it
actually happens
but oh yeah for for merchandise by the
way since I already brought out birthday
merchandise there won't be any
merchandise announced during the
stream um I was told and offered I was
told that you know because I didn't do
an outfit reveal merchandise this
year that I
could you
know use it for different merchandise
like I think last year I also didn't do
outfit merchandise but I basically used
that slot of creating merchandise for
the HP
merchandise and this year I'm not doing
that so I I don't know I was thinking
what can I do and you guys already kind
of know what I'm planning to use it
for and I was hoping that it could make
in time for the concert so I could
announce it at the concert but no
unfortunately not but that's fine that's
fine
um that merch is supposed to be for 2023
but it probably won't come out until
like
2024 end of February or
March so please be a little bit patient
until then
[Music]
green
Menace it will be so worth it I'm so
excited I'm so excited for
it still very much in the planning phase
right
now check out the tour mode oh wait
wasn't that really difficult though oh
it's blue oh [\h__\h] blue no actually I do
have a couple of
blue
[Music]
um how to say
Defenders oh this is
[Music]
fine no problem we're pushing
hey like
I'm back to back
parade until you lose one or is it not
endless in
theory was that statement too
controversial why can I not say
that three in a row
OHA too late late but I want to see you
anyway look at her floating I didn't
know you could do
that why does she get to
float it caught as off guard well I mean
aren't you used to
that yeah floating in Hol parade uh Ina
so much for being human right
aerodynamic she do be
aerodynamic okay how do you do this tour
thing switch to tour tour
Tokyo and then it it
like let's just see what
happens oh it's a flag
one is it like an existing stage being
reused or is like you know with the same
enemies
maybe not cuz this doesn't seem familiar
to me
blue it's
blue
oh colored enemies from the getg go kind
of scares
me okay but hold back chill
chill they don't they uh I'm sorry they
don't send out enough enemies to push me
back oh oh maybe maybe the boss isn't
too difficult oh it's very blue they're
all very
blue very blue so blue all I see is
blue maybe we'll
survive we can do this I Believe in
Us Care Free
superiority yeah yeah yeah look at that
oh easy oh easy No need no no need for
me giving up my flag guys not
[Music]
always punch KF
punch come on don't waste my time I know
the fight is already over do it do it do
it do it do it CH m
[Music]
next all never are they all flag
levels but this one's also with blue
enemies right away from the
getto
oh but again pretty small amount
of waves
[Music]
coming I don't know if this one's worth
waiting for let
me I will be pushing
now I'm I'm
pushing guess I'm push to
I don't I don't know if I'm ready for
this one to be
honest
y don't underestimate the need for my
low cost
tanks h
punch come out the
punch she Chad dead by the way or am I
just boring to you guys am I boring
you oh there you are there you
are chat was dead
right I take it as an insult when it
doesn't
move hello
where you guys
sleeping look at me clearing this stage
with
easea she's busy making food oh I need
to cook today D oh actually no I still
have half a pizza yesterday I was
actually
like you know kind of exhausted after
all the excitement too and the headache
and so I just ordered
pizza I still have half of the pizza
left so I don't have to cook
H
H tuna and corn h no it was uh corn and
ham and uh it said mild Peppers so I
thought I was getting Peppers but then
it turned out to be bell
peppers I wish it would have been like
uh I guess you don't call it can you
call peppers in English
uh not the pepponi
I wanted I wanted
uh no I meant the mild mild U no not
jalapenos pepperoni yep pepp pepperon
pepperoni
pepperoni in German we
say
pepperoni ah the pepperoni no got the
pepperoni
oh my God it's again of lag
level can we do it can we brute force it
again ah
Theon
[Music]
Theon there's so little output from
their
side oh a
raincloud e what can I do besides
pushing they couldn't even push me if
they
tried oh my God Hama purple
oh per
purple ooh I didn't prepare anything
purple besides the taco ah buba
too oh
[\h__\h]
and we're already doing damage on her
maybe die
trouble worst case flag goes down we get
some
more punch punch yeah have punch
time having a second support card is
really nice I wonder when I get another
one to replace the the pan
with the voice acting no you I've
noticed some people when they call cats
they go
like especially on like YouTube videos
from like people helping Stray Cats
which are really nice to watch they just
give them like big amounts of wet food
right I love watching that but they go
like and I'm like what the [\h__\h] no
that's not how you talk with
cats we do that here in no way no no way
you do that in no way you guys don't
understand cats it's supposed to go
like like Dad what do you
know ah German always works I guess
German would work too
yeah German always
works like that that's the noises I make
to my
cats not everyone can make cat noises as
well as you yeah I have to say it is a
bit difficult to do that
noise a bit difficult you can't make it
so continuously
as I don't think my cats would I I I
will try although I guess they react to
anything I do they're so
sweet they love me so
much y oh a phone do we got the no it's
not a phone I thought it was an iPhone
it's a I guess it's a cutting
board a new I was just talking about it
like getting a new support card is that
a support card
oh it's almost cool birthday yeah coall
birthday oh it's a wall summon a wall
that cannot be climbed so like a second
wall that they have to
destroy hey cool down 50 seconds 80
Seconds sheesh okay that will have to
that takes a while Aura hi
aura
[Music]
they bump into
it can they it what do you mean it can't
be
destroyed how's that
[Music]
work
sorry I was writing a message only stays
for some ah okay so it disappears after
a while oh maybe putting that up right
when the boss
spawns could be pretty good or when they
get like when I'm like in a pinch and
they get right to H or my own flag or
so
[Music]
we have a lot of money and we have three
h parade tickets let's um
[Music]
Scout believe in the Goa nope but oh new
things at least
okay I'll go with the robers because
they're low cost and might be
useful gotcha this one this one this one
this one is it
[Music]
no oh no question we always take the new
thing last
one come
on come on
ah oh another tle that you but we're
going to take the
onia cost six close range attack a half
damage from red or enemy
M
okay singing my lungs out for sleep
talking P up thank you yeah please guys
please please please please uh sleep
talking please stream the music video as
much as you can um is the last one and
it's it's out later than it should be
so that is a bit problematic for my
plans but I hope you guys can watch it
at least once daily I would appreciate
that sleep twerking
yeah I'm really glad that you guys
received it so
well that you guys um you know uh
thought it was really really good even
though it was mostly
2D U my colleagues are all talking about
the trending
parades please help me what is this if I
was wrong last time I'm not sure
what it is this
[Music]
time can we know what those PLS are yet
no not really it's kind of an
internal
[Music]
thing wait for something better but I'm
already at
5 oh this is not a
trend how do you
know you could Skip and reor for better
wait I can also grade up what does that
mean
Yi it will say trending
oh
oh what what video uh my new music video
that I put out yesterday did you not
watch it please watch it it's on my
channel sleep talking the music video
people were quite
surprised
grade up is
worth okay oh not even a confirmation
screen
okay wait so what
changed you guys said there will be more
slots I don't ah here more slots here ah
the
seats okay but let's wait until
something's trending I
guess made a bit more
twerking I'm Jelly of the white
mannequin yeah the white mannequin wow
wow wow
wow I saw I saw you guys making
[Music]
memes you
crazy chickens crazy
chickens it was quite funny oh movement
speed really okay I didn't know it could
be anything besides the the Buffs uh
against the color
enemies now you're even faster did you
really need movement speed huh I don't
think so I think I have to reset this
because the nickel certainly doesn't
need more movement
speed e
[Music]
speed don't need that oh
wait it keeps the movement speed what
what
I thought it
resets oh
[\h__\h] no I
[Music]
misunderstood what the you can you not
not reset
this I thought that was a
[Music]
recet damn it
whatever okay I guess you're now the
fastest boy in the
room or in the whole wide
world
M attack + 15 oh
[Music]
okay
dog nah come on movement speed okay I
guess the dog is pretty slow sure
[Music]
okay should I level any of these new
ones that I got
before anyone you guys really
[Music]
like the night is a good
tank which one there's these
two the lit oh level wait 10 cost
sh you're not very useful though okay
[Music]
okay movement speed okay I'm assuming
it's a really slow unit so I guess okay
I use small robot instead since it's
super cheap yeah I think that could be
an option
[Music]
too cost
to what about the
[Music]
do
basically it has a 30% chance to block
an attack oh
[Music]
nice what didn't we also want to maybe
maybe level the ssrb cuz the the blow up
is pretty strong but for them to blow up
at like impact and then cost six H they
better be blowing up really
[Music]
strong not worth
it I wonder what else we could make use
of what what else might be useful
[Music]
helpful they're not good oh okay they
die so it's a waste of motivation I
guess
yeah it prevents keeping full s true
yeah the simpon
keeps on resetting then shut up ad doe
Creative
Cloud try next level first
okay I guess I'll go with the team with
the same
[Music]
team oh yeah also we got something new
now the support card of the wall
looking forward to using
[Music]
that oh yeah let's talk a little bit
more about the MV so originally it was
supposed to be a 3D MV so I I felt very
disappointed that I had to do this but I
wanted it to be at least like more
intricate than the other couple ones
that I released
recently so you
know I mean made some sacrifices but I I
didn't want to
completely you
know go for the most lowc cost thing
ever
so
that's why I went
for a little bit more there's the wall
oh I can't can I get through oh I can
but the Wall's like only on the right
side
uh well yeah so free illustrations is
the max we could do in the time
constraint holy
[\h__\h] holy
[\h__\h] uh I would have liked to do even
more but yeah we were literally lagging
time but I was trying to get the
illustrations to be like kind of fitting
to the
lyrics and be kind of sensual too so the
one with the phone is obviously because
there's a lot of me talking through the
phone the mannequin is because I feel
like you know it's such a central song
and and and I'm talking directly to
someone more or less so I wanted
something there to interact with and I
thought I'm not going to let me justart
this I thought I thought I I wanted some
like prop I wanted a
person but I didn't want it to be like
like someone clearly I wanted to be
something vague that you can't point a
finger at and say oh this is
mean or this is that no exactly that's
the thinging you can say that's me I
guess but you can't say that's that
person or that whole life member or you
know I just wanted it to be something
that could be anything so it's a
mannequin and now you guys are meing it
into
[Music]
Oblivion it's actually me no it's
actually me
no but actually it's
me uh actually that was uh purple right
so
H
purple no purple
purple actually mean I have
proof it's me no need to hide
in you just meet need to summon Ena
lineup is fine I couldn't get to that
point they were spamming
[Music]
enemies she would be good
too let me bring
in this
one
and
[Music]
the rest is like man maybe the duck same
instrument even but the duck has at
least some a little bit against
purple HP
342 oh but the nickel has way more HP
actually
no lots of AOE on the enemy side the
small units are doing nothing when they
pile
up
a then I want AOE right I
want
okay
AOE that doesn't
overlap wait we
have Bubba does AE Pachi does
[Music]
AE the no Sagi doesn't do AOE right
yeah single single area single area but
quite high
cost yukim me does do area
damage
okay I
[Music]
can't [\h__\h] I don't know what to do maybe
these
two I know I know poo is strong as [\h__\h]
but does not necessarily help me in this
situation
[Music]
so you have some nice area just not as
many single powerful units like
Po you're good for this St should I try
like this
huh yeah I have come to a point a stage
again that troubles me a little bit but
that's
fine we don't want it to be too
[Music]
easy let's get two tanks
there and there goes the tacki with the
AOE damage
takachi versus
[Music]
takachi and here comes the cat and we're
up to vage level
[Music]
six can we get a seven can we get a
m
yes seven is there and wall is
upcoming but why is it so much on on the
side towards the
screen do I hear healing
noises they're
healing no
way oh but we're pushing more now we're
pushing
more he trying to get Ena
eventually but maybe not necessary
[Music]
cha get those healers out of there they
trigger
me come
on come
on I barely can build up the motivation
oh this will help a little bit
maybe that was really not
[Music]
top tier unit okay if I ever see it in
my gacha I'll go maybe after this map
I'll get it as an option maybe it's just
not even in the in the oh God in the
possible units I can get
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] why they're pushing so
hard I know I
lost it was going so
[Music]
well please
oh no
stop oh my God there's like a million
[\h__\h] healers oh game
crashed
10 crashing so much am I the only one
are you guys have you guys played since
the update am I the only one who's been
getting crashes since the
update did they count my
[Music]
failure
[\h__\h] man got to change if I can't get to
Ena how about a tribe of
[Music]
hotal M I will try this
strategy maybe cuz hat I can get out
earlier
[Music]
try
guys I'm waiting for you hi you
good we
good stck enough okay there's game crash
now steam crash yeah it's a weird
day
come on come on give me the flute give
me the D
flute we need more
damage so that they can't get those
millions of healers out
there why is this wall so far over here
does it always spawn like there well now
I didn't even need it there [\h__\h] I kind
of wasted
it h okay let's wait cuz hatama is ready
to go
see see there there we
are
yeah I know the wall I just wanted to
activate it um just in case I didn't
feel so secure but soon after
yeah oh I even got two
tickets
yay okay I feel like I made the right
choices somehow it was very different
even though I only switched out hatama
did I
not and she
only came in like pretty late already
when I was pushing
anyway
H it's still not trending
magal hour pass I started listening to
the Brass Band that would be
audio
[Music]
and not sure what else when to explode
from
[Music]
huging
you can add more member oh yeah right
yeah but I don't even want to like go
for it yet that's the thing I've been
waiting for something to
[Music]
Trend but it did I
think simple and catch okay let's just
let's just do it
anyway
audio
oh
oh oh we have some strong
hitters so we want a we want a full team
of audio right ooh
ooh oh that's that's incredible overall
yeah that should go
[Music]
well
oh oh should
I it it it's it it's the right way to do
it right to just get uh only members or
it doesn't match that focus on the thing
you set
right the focused
[Music]
contents oh hey that's good
16,000 the money is low but the
followers are really high
[Music]
collection for the hints on PR strategy
might be off yeah that's the thing like
maybe it's easier to understand what
they want want in Japanese H oh well
let's go
next with the current team just to see
what's going to happen I was a guy
who ah H you know oh my God generally oh
I'm I was so like flattered incredibly
flattered at the panel because several
people during the Q&A several people
besides asking a question just said
random
uh by the way k I love you or I love
your streams or so Tanto they called me
they called me
Tanto that already proves their
kfp and was like what what what that's
so random thank
[Music]
you and that came right after the meet
and G you know I know I talked a lot
about it yesterday but I really hope we
can do more interaction IR out next year
I want to go to a lot of
conventions can I just push away the
wall with another
wall
nice didn't know that
works I love you dento thank you I love
you guys
too it was so
wholesome so wholesome I live in Asia
hopefully there's one nearby soon yeah
more Asian would be nice I really was
hoping for a Korean one again this year
but I was not chosen even though I asked
so so passionately I was like please
please please let me be the Korean
conven because I studied Korean all all
year I want I want to show off my
skills yeah maybe next
year
Korea
Europe please the problem really with
European conventions is like they don't
seem to
understand
how valuable it would be to bring
vtubers as guest they might not even
really see it as an option or like as
something that could even work
logistically uh yeah and then I do think
that at ventions there would be a good
amount of YouTuber fans I do think
so but yeah they also don't want to
spend much money uh I think on on
bringing uh guests and or or maybe they
would but not on vtubers they don't
probably don't see
how like why they would should spend as
much money for a vtuber guest as like a
like a real life guest I guess I don't
know I don't really know why there's not
much more offers from European
conventions but who knows maybe there
are more offers and they're just being
turned down and I just don't hear about
it but we wouldn't turn it down if it
was like appropriate in terms of
like yeah the
offer oh it's the same multinational
company that runs half the conventions
in the US oh it
really what there's a company in the US
that runs conventions that also runs
them in Europe
really thank you Tassimo than
you every UK convention I went to last
year that was whole life fan UK was
definitely uh like a recommendation I
made personally I said like for European
conventions I would recommend like the
UK and
um uh
perhaps or Germany again but no I think
there was also uh Italy I wanted to
recommend Italy as well cuz Italy has
like two huge conventions that
uh I think are worth looking at they're
really unique though in in the way that
they
are very different from other
conventions just like Beach
Convention starts at like in the
afternoon goes through the night same in
like with their their they have like a
convention that is like
not really in a convention hall it's
like throughout a whole city literally
the whole city center is the convention
and that's that one's also like in the
night time like evening nighttime
something about Italians and their
conventions they they don't they don't
do early morning or noon
conventions yeah it's not the
traditional kind of convention I really
love that because like from my
experience going to conventions all over
the world especially es in Japan you got
to get up early and then like the time
is so limited they end it like in the
middle of the day it's already over like
after 300 p.m. like people go home or so
and it's just like so short and then in
Europe generally they start at like
maybe 10:00 and then people go home
maybe at 6 or 7 even the long the people
stay really
long and then often there's even after
parties and all that but but yeah Italy
just starts everything way ear way later
and ends it way later but for me I don't
want to wake up so early you know I like
to sleep
in and you know you got to also think
about the
cosplayers I don't think they want to
get up at 6:00 a.m. to do their wig and
makeup and all that there's this
convention in was it the Netherlands
which is being held in an indoor pool
Paradise but it's like mostly for
Photograph photographers and
cosplayers um because of the location
like it's a location focused photograph
focused
convention but yet even though that that
they don't even book out the the like
venue for the day no they basically only
book it for before the official venue
opening times and after so like you can
only really take those pictures that
you're going there
for until like what whenever the opening
time is like what 900 a.m. 8:00 a.m.
something like that so cosplayers have
to get up at like 5 and do their makeup
at
[Music]
5 and then yeah during the daytime you
not allowed to take pictures in the
pool and then in the end of the day you
can do it again but that's like what for
the amount of money you pay because in
order to get to the convention you can't
just only have a a ticket for the
convention no you need to rent one of
those little apartments like Huts like
the little little vacation homes in in
the
pool like area
yeah yeah I I mean I heard from people
they had fun there my
friends went there
too but I would not consider it because
that's just too tight too strict to
tight if it was all day [\h__\h] yeah but so
restricted yeah it's one of the bung one
of those Bungalow packs mhm like lots of
little
Bungalows that you can rent and then
like spend your time inside this
tropical
covered indoor pool area
mhm
no you're better off with anime com abai
really yeah I heard about those well I
hear a lot about European conventions I
haven't been
to that many outside of like Germany
Austria but I want to go to more anyway
uh what were we doing did we just fail
something or what happened I literally
forgot what what the parade the last
parade was
like did we fail it or did we clear it
and we're just going to the next
one no I'm not ending the gaming portion
just
chilling have you ever been to Tropical
Island you mean you mean a tropical
island or like a specific
one did we
fail oh was I swarmed and I accident
what was it
black what was the what was the color
that I was overwhelmed
[Music]
by H resources well last time I got
myself a private teacher but
H do you mean the males well I went to
the males if you mean any tropical
island
[Music]
yeah I don't know what that let's just
try it again and see what happened let's
relive you guys seemed to have forgotten
as well
Chicken brain cell memory of 5 Seconds
oh no this looks new we didn't fail this
no no no no
no what what you guys gaslighting me
into thinking I'm a
failure nice music in
here oh [\h__\h] lots of red uh red T oh
these ones are good for
red oh my God strong
stop but I should probably let them take
my flag anyway
right nice
music chill very chill
I'm at work listening to kfp
podcast oh yeah lots of people told me
in the meet and greet too that they
listen to me doing work I was surprised
like most of them said yeah they just
listen to it doing work I thought they I
thought they would all be bot gang oh
there's blue ones
too a damn it damn it I thought I could
level up the voltage there we
go well this level I probably should
switch out hatama for something more
powerful but who
knows maybe we can do
it I let them push
me can we working right now
oh
I need invisible
earbuds I mean I think they're like
quite a lot really small
ones oh
[\h__\h] let's
go I don't know if I can still win
this but I'll just spawn a million
tarantulas let's
go easy easy easy easy another one
another one another one
yeah uhoh what's that red oh [\h__\h]
hold your ground stand your ground stay
strong oh maybe the wall too early sorry
that was a reflex it's a [\h__\h]
reflex ah all the tantas are dead
no
[Music]
y no they're all one hit they're all
want it the peack of Doom
no
ah it's over let TCH
over s this
now so but the final duck was red right
it was mostly all
red definitely worth it to
bring the PO back then maybe also the
crow um
instrument these two we could
switch and died yeah enough know oh yeah
we wanted to switch out hatama for
something more
useful
okay good
coverage cuz Ena has blue as well which
is good there there were some blue
colored enemies as
well
um I could I could bring in the coron
skin if I wanted to but I do always want
to keep Bubba because the that
instrument until I have another talent
that has that I will forever keep Bubba
in we have good not
yet not
yet should we try like this maybe this
is good what
get maybe C his ski instead of C would
have been better you think
[Music]
so the only other one is OKO what
really I wonder if it's on purpose that
they
like have certain instruments that are
extremely rare and others that are very
common
is that a balancing thing I feel like
one more would be good for that
instrument give me a bit more Choice oh
they're already working the flag what
the
hell stop what the [\h__\h] is wrong with
you yum
all y it
all
stop it what the [\h__\h] I mean I'm going
to let them destroy the flag but uh this
is kind of too early for
me it was too early I I thought it was
too
early I want to build my voltage a
little bit
more all right it's already seven though
never
mind okay you can have it you can have
it I'm sorry kill
me I'm sorry please no
no Oops I did it
again okay there we go okay okay okay
okay
mhm
mhm punch
I bring out Ena
now such a wasted
[Music]
Strat bring a couple more of
these oh my motivation is so
high
Goa
go oh okay okay yeah I could have
summoned wa with this much motivation
[Music]
definitely when did Ena say
that ah no I'm trying to take Ena down
it's okay I have another one back up Ena
let's
go
yeah don't give up don't no don't attack
TOA directly no no it took them two hits
two
[\h__\h] no okay uh well very [\h__\h] now we
very [\h__\h]
now yeah that is
unfortunate
huh
huh oh [\h__\h] they're the same
instrument
no no I don't like this if I do that
then I'm lacking an instrument should I
get rid of the
taco
H
what's replace
with maybe the crow after
all I no let's try
it but that means because I won't be
able to spawn Ena and Wawa for a while
that my voltage Max will probably be
six until I spawn
[Music]
them oh yeah one thing if there's if
there is a Kevin p in the chat please
check my reply to your uh comment on the
community
post just wanted to say that is there a
Kevin p in the chat cuz I did do your
Polaroid um it wasn't missing it should
be
there it's in there and I uh just named
it a different like not I I named it
Kevin p and then blah blah blah blah
blah blah
blah cuz you asked a question in the
Super Chat and I wanted to answer it oh
[\h__\h]
don't
yeah fight back fight
back doesn't seem like they're here
either maybe they'll watch
the the uh oh
[\h__\h] I guess we're doing
it
[Music]
yes ha finally I'm using it the right
way
ah yeah the wall is down and Ena will be
down in two hits and here comes the Wawa
who probably can't protect me that well
either oh one hit and two hit and waa is
a free hit from the
duck a don't don't don't kill the W I
know it's my fault cuz I pushed to too
fast I know I know I know I know I know
I know I know I know I know oh wow oh
he's attacking the the
Poo oh he was attacking the PUO for so
long yeah okay
uh I think the team is
fine it's okay the team was
okay just got to go slower cuz they
can't they they they spawn to little
enemies in the
beginning
Ki before Ena true okay not that Ki can
take that much more hits uh
anyway
oopsy why did I spawn poo
[\h__\h] yeah not that I am that much much
more bulky you would think I'm that much
more bulky but the
duck
peck so
strongly so CL thank
you oh we're not doing Polaroids during
oh
no I you know what I I will write you
down for the Christmas ones how about
that uh but you'll have to choose a new
number once the the Christmas Polaroids
are ready to be chosen
misunderstanding oh no oh [\h__\h] I'm too
strong
again go back go
back go back you little
shits okay 40
41 43
44 okay
okay
50 just a little bit bit just a little
bit I I spawned kiata first but they're
very close is is that
y
spam little ones okay but do they
actually go past
[Music]
them okay let's go let's go
wall I wall kind of early [\h__\h] I we'll
be fine they'll do enough damage
[Music]
right
w w oh but the dog is going to go down y
do
something look at them they're so cute
they look so cute takoni
power takon is so strong at the moment
with the 3D lives showing our true
power power more strength more power I
said that I remember that I said that
before
surely
y that's the first time I had two URS I
think out on the
field it seems like it was
necessary okay time to scout a little
bit let's
go oh Udin let's go new one Udin is so
strong as an enemy I feel like I always
have trouble when I have Udin up against
[Music]
me one
more
buba
okay count to youp oh next one is the
penny ah
[Music]
I don't like that I don't like that at
all I don't want you
penny Wait this team is not going to
work is it this is not a flag
level I should have changed
it oh
no they're
blue
[Music]
die
no why you got to be blue why not
red
[Music]
why more Yuki means they seem to have
protected quite well actually
just no damage
either
Bubba can you guys
stop
I'm trying to
save oh we're almost
there we're almost there
no no no don't let her go alone don't
don't let her go alone don't let her go
alone don't let her go alone no e go
back no no no no oh but she's we're
we're kind of clearing it yeah no yes
yeah push her back that's fine with me a
she survived oh my god oh [\h__\h] the wall
[\h__\h] that
wall no oh they have AOE damage that's
why they killed all of
my uh tanks at
once yeah stay back
now just stay back okay stay back
back you not attack so slowly witch wall
yeah there were two walls
huh don't let her hear this comment I
wonder if Ena is going to play Hol
[Music]
parade this could still
work oh okay I'm sorry I'm sorry it's a
don't you guys have the same reflex you
just activate whatever you have in your
support
cards Ena takon strong
[Applause]
again just don't die
Ena yes yeah you
too you have the same
issue you've got issues I've got them
[Music]
too I no cuz I got
issues you've got them
too or is it the other way around cuz
you've got
issues I got him
[Music]
too Ena is dead in peace rest in peace
wall versus ball what you going to do
what you going to do when the wall
blocks you
too okay
guys we have a chance for the
pity is the pity for every
o should I should I
try oh wait no the next one is the pity
one right after this one but everybody
keeps on saying auki you know what I'll
go for I I I'll from now on I'll try for
the Gen zero but the chance of me
getting auki oh
ah are
low as [\h__\h] so was that the you are the
the the pity I mean it was the pity oh
okay accurate shots are easy for robots
like myself these long range rabid
attacks that occasionally passes through
enemy blocks H okay strong against
Blue relatively low
[Music]
cost
roboton I do love
roboco I love roboco
sire it was so nice like getting to know
her better in the last
trip
yeah and her cats yeah oh my
God her little
kitten oh wait my team my team I should
probably change my team right I mean
still kind of worked but I would like it
to be not too red in case what we get is
not red at
all
also level I have a lot of money ooh
gold defense M nice look at her
coverage
yo everybody's still kind of chilling on
level 10 let's get everybody one level
up
[Music]
that decreases my money a
lot me
[Music]
too and now uh
H goodbye Wawa
you will take a step
back and replace it pack with that you
cuz you guys have the same
instrument
no whatever that's fine wait what level
isi oh 10
okay and a level for you bye waa it's
okay I'm still here same person actually
I'm the better waa anyway of these
two
feel free to create more uh more of the
um mannequin memes by the way I
especially like the self sessed
ones oh this should be an easy
level or is
it but the other Wawa has a hat h
would you still love me if I got none of
my stupid
hats would you still love me if I've got
nothing but my
uniform I hope you're
well you'd be a little
sad it's
okay I'm also sad
without my hats or without my hat
singular I mean the red one the orange
red one I'm only here for the hats wow
okay I thought you Lov me for being me
you love me for my hats only
huh wall attack oh this time it didn't
work so sad I wanted to attack the wall
with the wall also where where did the
where I clicked the punch
right and it didn't
appear did
it I only heard the sound like there was
no
[Music]
punch was it because it can't do it on a
wall only because in the moment it was
only a wall
there uhoh oh why would you do that why
would you do that you stupid fake Taco
nais why are you so
mad no no why would you do that leave
her alone leave your Priestess alone why
are they
rebelling there we go that was
close almost had Ena die on
necessarily
still not trending
[Music]
right why do I not get a trophy by the
way for like this
one what did I do wrong was I not good
[Music]
enough oh it's
random
ooh flag
level
H
okay oh yeah by the way I am working on
Christmas Polaroids so just wanted to
confirm that or Duma is working on them
I should
say not going to do as many options just
because cuz I also couldn't even think
of so many Christmas related options so
not as many as before but that's going
to make it a bit easier for me
too yeah let's see but I don't know I
feel kind of bad
[Music]
because you
know H yeah I'll do them for Christmas
but I feel like December is generally
like kind of
a big spending
month uh not that you have to but like
it usually is because of New Year's and
Christmas and now there's a third thing
which is my my live concert you know so
I don't want to like tickle too many
super chats out of you ah oh wait wait I
forgot it was a flag level I was just
doing my thing but hey I did get up to
Ena uh uh oh
[\h__\h] yeah bye H youa go back I hope the
others are faster oh he's attacking her
directly I [\h__\h]
up but now we know what Aura it is it's
uh
purple oh [\h__\h] I mean we we could still
maybe do it it's halfway
down there's a there is a purple and a
blue one
actually it's not too bad not going too
bad they're not pushing that
strong Let Me Wait
actually little bit
wait
no do what you need to do I already got
the next Ena
oh never mind I
don't
soon the reach though the reach of the
enemies is pretty big they so no Ena
don't get so close you
stupid punch
punch get so
closea but this one does way less damage
than the duck that's
goodaa sorry I let you die
twice I'm not going to stop though I'm
not going to
stop
no we're so
close
no no don't give up
no
no well okay I know like I I I I did a
mistake anyway so we could have
won so same team as
it was Ina
over wait I need some
water
okay oh yeah she doesn't have the right
aura wait did kiaha have the red or I
think kiaha has
right should I
redo switch the taco for the to yes
let's switch the taco for the to but
that means I'm going to switch this one
for this
one wait what did it have
uh maybe
[Music]
not maybe this one oh no we already have
that
[Music]
one what about the duck cheap
duck but I I like the AOE you know from
the cor this SK I'll
try
yeah let's give it a try T clost
destroys Flags easily replac
Oh you mean
okay we were close to winning even with
the old team and even with me making a
mistake because I was just like Tangen
thing about
Polaroids so with me Focus
thing and kiala in the team so whole
different
story actually early on we kind of need
the blue not only
black oh
[\h__\h] so the only thing that the the the
trait that the blue ones have is their
defense being higher
right so the Yuki
mean their defense is double is it and
they bring it down to 30 uh So 20%
right ah only the HP is higher oh
okay yeah I'm letting them have it more
or less right
now oh [\h__\h] sudden angry black
duck stay back stay where you
are nice oh good damage the fist really
does good damage wow that cleaned it up
nicely the longer the time oh
really oh did I summon her to
oie oh
well let's go let's go let's go oh wait
no they still wait know what there
didn't take down my flag
ah well sorry I thought they would I
just started summoning a bit
early
no it's okay I have so much
motivation it's
okay don't let M stand there all alone
come on you slow
[\h__\h]
I can get a trophy easier this way oh
really if I don't let my flag be taken
oh let's
go okay don't use the don't use the
wall don't use the
[Music]
Wall go one one go go one one go go W go
go W go go W go go W go go W go yeah
yeah let's go we're
[Music]
winning we're winning K look at her more
strength more
power more strength more
power yeah bye she's all alone sorry
sorry wa I was focused on your
beauty why is that little hat so huge
it's not supposed to be that huge oh we
did it
n let's go let's
go oh my God I love
her a thank you I love you too yeah what
did you say what did she say I wish I
could summon another one but you
literally can't let's
go yo my motivation never been that high
and that easy
walk to the fire yeah to the fire yeah
oh sh it again oh let's
go no trophy I need a
[\h__\h] that was trophy
wory still nothing trending why is
nothing ever trending I think we should
go for it anyway H wait this but maybe
it is Trend it doesn't say trending but
this one's so much higher than the
others I don't know I'm interested in
the Brass Band I like the sounds of the
trumpet
audio but the rest I don't really
[Music]
know you help
me I missed the 2K post
ma under one over 1K is ring ah okay
okay
okay big friends are like one out of
15 15 simple and catchy
[Music]
polite trending never shows and it's not
accurate oh well they're probably trying
to fix
[Music]
it
pop okay there's a couple of popping
cute I don't see how that's cute
[Music]
but
no well if I imagine this in
yongo
then a brass band what would a brass is
a brass band considered cute I don't
think so is it considered cool
maybe
[Music]
but maybe it's a local affair because
the brass band is maybe like locally
there I don't know simple and
catchy yeah maybe maybe simple and
catchy wake up oh yeah cuz I was using
it it's on a break then uh another audio
focused
one oh
you okay let's go oh watch the
[Music]
[\h__\h] oh she's so motivated
oh oh indeed uh what was I doing PR
simple
catchy audio Brass Band let's
[Music]
go bounce bounce bounce
bounce attrac The Voice couldn't have
done any
better doesn't
match it doesn't match much maybe like
half of it matches the audio part right
that has to match but the the simple and
catchy didn't match I guess
[Music]
oh 17,000
sh my followers are doing really
[Music]
well okay go next go next go next go
next okay no
[Music]
flag let's go pity summon it wasn't the
last one of pity
summon I thought we were agreeing on
that
[Music]
M let's get to Seven come
on it was
yeah I think so
too God damn
it I'm barely holding up there we go
six
I'd like more coronis skis because
there's a red several red enemies and
koniski has
AOE but all of them are good against red
actually oh the CIS wait the CIS are
missing the the head uh
feather they're Bal just like me right
now they're twinning we're twinning
yeah they have only slight
differences it's just a random orange
bird
[Music]
now wait a second
I'm so stupid I just realized a
thing I just realized
wait I just had the most random
Epiphany
uh oh just had the most random
Epiphany you know
how I Commission members
wallpapers for each
month and uh recently like I started
planning them like a bit more ahead of
time but recently sometimes
uh even though I choose the artist quite
early they don't get contacted uh until
like right before the month switches
switches so I tell them what what to
draw basically within the month and so
we just had our December wallpaper
right which is the snowy
one and just realized for the upcoming
one that would be
[Music]
January the next one would be January
right yeah
and I because we're in December though
and my brain was so set on December I
asked the artist to draw me again in a
Santa outfit on on a
sleigh and they're already like working
on it and sent me a draft already we
like pretty deep into
it but you will get the wallpaper on the
first of
January for me I thought I don't know
why but I thought we were still in
November and you're getting this in the
beginning of December but we're already
past
that so second Christmas in
January I'm so
stupid CA I just
realized I'm so stupid you can keep
working on this but I just realized this
is is for January I I I got
confused I don't know why I made you
draw me in
s bringing presents
SL I'm so stupid Oh I was so confused I
was so confused I got really
[Music]
confused that that is a big pun from me
right
now second Christmas
y oh I'm so
stupid Oh my head hurts I even today I
have a head h guys is this starting to
be concerning I'm not even that stressed
out right now like I feel like I've been
way more stressed like two 3 four weeks
ago why do I still have this head Hort
I've been drinking water too it feels
like like a it's a weird headache too it
feels like so heavy you
know
H maybe I have like a lowkey cold but
this is the only symptom I'm feeling
[Music]
oh red
nice it keep some happening see a
doctor SW is there
maybe brain is fried like
mine has your nose pleas up yeah yeah
yeah I've been doing my best at keeping
my at least my bedroom um uh humidified
[Music]
yeah I have the humidifier on all
night even during daytime sometimes so I
have not been humidifying the other
rooms like not even this one the one I'm
working in but I I feel fine it doesn't
feel so I mean today is a bit worse than
yesterday to be honest my
throat but I'm mostly
[Music]
fine ah yeah thank you for mentioning
the blood cookies I just wanted to talk
about them I was like so proud of them
you know uh I made them one day before
the meeting great right and then uh even
when I thought they were dry the whole
evening um they were like cuz I made
such a fake layer of sugar
glazing uh like when you bite into it it
was definitely still soft on the
inside but it was still good so I waited
another day and then I ate some uh like
around the meat and greet time and I was
actually so delighted so surprised
because they were really good and they
were actually dry now and and I wanted
to share my feelings so with one of the
I don't know who it was anymore but with
one of them I felt so proud I had to
share it I was like so randomly out of
nowhere I was like by the way my cookies
are so good right now my the sugar
glazing is dry now yeah I just had to
say it and my brother got a taste
yesterday too cuz he came by to pick up
my my drill cuz he doesn't have one and
he wants to build something and uh I
gave him a a taste of one of my sugar
cookies let show you right right what I
thought they would maybe appreciate my
random tangent but they they were just
like yeah oh I see
okay cuz we were in the middle of taking
a
picture I didn't make the chocolate cup
ones yet ah I have to make them maybe
after the stream maybe I'll end it like
soon once I have this like Story 3 done
let me bite into one they're really good
and I I I I couldn't help myself but eat
a couple of the unglazed ones too yeah
but now now that these ones are dry M
they're so sweet and it kind of tastes
like even though it there's absolutely
no apricot in there it gives me lowkey
apricot
Vibes the sugar glazing
M
yummy
[Music]
M I'm so
happy you would love a random tangent
during the med and GRE
right would feel like a stream
like iron what iron
no no no no no there no blood touched
the cookies okay it's
[Music]
fine well the treadmill arrived L 2 days
ago give me some
time you almost r on a tangent during
our me and
GRE what was I about to tangent
[Music]
about was it about the
cookies no I'm going to open it okay
maybe on my day
off oh they're so good these cookies are
so good
I wish you guys
could H take a bite I forgot but you
kept going you had to stop
yourself I I was just go I'm just going
to claim that you are the reason why I
went on the tangent in the first
place it was you know fitting to the
topic I would say surely whatever we
were talking about
here we go start the
parade no time to waste you love the
anime FR P thank
you hope you're well thank you I am hope
you're well
too I've been pretty good I think like
now that all the stressful [\h__\h] is
over there's still some work I have to
do behind the scenes like small things
but I can totally keep
up more or less yeah
so it's such a big weight off of my
[Music]
shoulders yeah finally for the first
time in
months I feel somewhat balanced oh my
God the
AOE
when we bring some tanks and some
cisis was the crow the crow is not AOE
right
[Music]
quoon no maybe not this uh
no come on Punch Yeah yeah I think I
need more AOE this is
[Music]
tough they're red too though they're all
red so I feel like the cor the ski
should be good but they're not buff
enough I need like distance
Al ah [\h__\h]
this m M
[Music]
okay yukim Min is not red so let's get
rid of the yukim Min even though it has
area attack but it barely stays alive oh
the ah the taco would be
good uh place like this
yeah wait you guys kept them saying
several times don't use the shield goal
but I think I will actually use it this
time
cuz of the area attack and the shield
also staying back a little bit that's
exactly what I want I'll replace it
with maybe with the PO
o or with the ENA even no you
are I don't care I'm going to do it I'm
going to build a strong
Army even without Ena
high cost yeah but not as high as
Ena Taco
Time Taco Time Taco Time taco t t time t
t t t t t t t t t t
t t time ah who died h
huh
ah
[\h__\h] you know what I I I might let them
come for a little bit I I'll let them
kill
those and put a wall let's then I'll
wait a little
bit keep them
back can we
still doesn't really suit this
song uh yeah this this music in my
opinion H oh we were ready for the
shield
call
oh
now I just got to Stand My Ground for
the Sha is like kind of in the front
[Music]
lines
sh
no I
[Music]
can't it's still not dead though it's
quite sturdy actually surprisingly
sturdy ah now it's dead m
a
[\h__\h] what am I doing wrong here what's
wrong with my
team am I just too low
level I can try to so like level them up
a little bit oh no I can't I have no
money need a good
tank
H
oh
six I mean we can try with bloop
or yeah they have much higher numbers
[Music]
yeah strong AOE I don't have that much
more AO we
[Music]
can maybe I don't
know cuz I don't even get to summon
Shield that much so I don't think I'll
get to summon
here try doing tour a few times and
level up your
[Music]
units Callie solos levels like these
what okay let's
[Music]
replace
back to yukim because areial damage and
cheap
cost but it doesn't even have
red upgrades uh red thing
[Music]
here 36 that's why she cost so much huh
interesting
the private crew is also a relatively
good red tank
but not high highly leveled yet I'll try
again
more I want to clear this one we only
have two more I want to clear it let's
go
and inir these are all good for red like
I don't know what more I can
do oh oops no no that's good that's
fine that's
okay get the Bubba get the Bubba
oh my
God I'm waiting on
purpose give me some time to
spawn some motivation
ah we need more yeah that was good that
was pretty
good
please be nice to me what did I ever do
to you to treat me like
[Music]
that no why is this so difficult the
spam is
insane maybe my levels are just too low
honestly yeah the Udin I told you those
Udin are
cracked every time I have Udin against
me
[Music]
maybe
I focus no but I need damage output too
I can't just go for a million
tanks I can bring in the lunite though
[Music]
but it doesn't have any strength against
red but let's
let's give it a
try I
guess I really need
levels oh okay okay I have an
idea
[Music]
um give me the money give me the
money give me the
money cuz I don't use these units
at the moment at
[Music]
least sorry I'm really in a desperate
situation right now sorry C you got to
go too you're worth a lot of money
here even you yep I have enough milks to
do that so I'm going to milk it as much
as I can and then we're going to level
up
m
M oh n
what what what did I do what's happening
why am I getting a different
[Music]
one
what why do I got to
[Music]
skip
I didn't understand what was going
on what every two levels I get an option
to change
it I didn't know I didn't
[Music]
understand well this is like pretty much
like you know same but I'll keep black
for
now oh oops Yeah okay
[Music]
not like black helps us right now so
I'll I'll
skip I've never seen a
gold you don't you never know they might
spam them at us like in the next
chapter and then I'll be like what the
[\h__\h] I have no gold but I I do I do have
gold but oh I'm already out of
money
[Music]
a loop give me I'm
desperate
desperate red yes yes this one I want
right now I want
that the color of the skill shows the
Rarity I guess
[Music]
sure
gold skills are hard to
get I mean now I have plenty to be
honest yeah if this still doesn't work I
guess I'll go on a tour but they take
quite some
time I mean just these couple of levels
are probably not going to do that much
of a difference but we also don't know
yet what Lou Knight brings to the
table
ouch
[Music]
ouch come
on
[Music]
ah ah K
me I can't do
it
I can't do it I
just
uh okay now can we wait for the
lunite
no protect the
princess she may not be here but she's
here in
spirit how strong is he
really punch time punch time this could
be our comeback our great
comeback down
there bong B no he's already dead
no no
way still didn't get Bubba come
on
yeah [\h__\h] whatever get out of here it's
not
happening let me do
one tour I guess
uh ah we have to we we do the same tour
okay so I hope my team is all right
we're just strong now they send out the
same mobs right do they like adjust
their
difficulty can you tell us how long your
pretty life will be oh like all like
they all are 1 hour but then there's a
members only
[Music]
uncore for like 1 hour uh 15
minutes you're
welcome it may be short but I think the
impact is strong of the members only and
core
yeah it will be immediately
after
connecting it will be difficult to us
okay more difficult than
[Music]
me I can't
imagine W the boss is here and they're
blue that die and I have nothing against
Blue except the yukim
me but it's okay we're going to do this
no matter
what yeah we did it okay the yukin
haven't even all arrived and we're
already through
[Music]
yeah I hope you're happy as well of
course I
am I mean the process was very painful
the a I I I don't even want to like
think back on all the muscle pain muscle
sores that I had and then my neck got
really [\h__\h] up from it
too for a
while I don't even want to remember
those
times
yeah it's really stressed out and I had
to learn so many dances and even on the
actual recording day I still felt like
pretty insecure about it like still made
many
mistakes
so won't be able to watch it live oh
promise me to watch The V as soon as you
can hi hi hi
[Music]
hi I'm going to cry all of my eggs and
bacon yo full
Voltage oh it's also a
shield uh uh uh sure whatever I'll just
send out
everything keep on coming keep on
coming
Punch Yeah I got to get them all got to
catch them all it's really nice how you
rebranded it as yeah I mean I thought it
would be just weird you know as a
birthday I'm mentally way past my
birthday ouch
I've been really neat like theme play I
wonder what yours will be oh honestly
because it's my first one I didn't
really give it a theme I just wanted it
to be you know normal because it's my
first
one but that doesn't mean it's not going
to be incredibly
awesome I'm going to rock the
[Music]
stage
the theme
is let's have
fun that's the theme the theme is
Idol
idol
basically be is
Wawa exactly true yes you get
it last time we also went for the flag
immediately more or less so I I mean I'm
scared but it should be
fine
uh-oh oh
God
yab real yab
moment
the thumbnail outet is
Idol he cuz it's in my idol outfit
yeah I originally wanted to do a like an
a thumbnail art with um more than just
me
but yeah it's a little bit expensive to
have so many guests on one
thumbnail so it's just me now
oh spoilers what what do you mean did I
say
something oh really did
I I'll start spoiling the members though
from tomorrow
um rock and
roll I thought we did it return to home
so we got some money from that that was
actually pretty
[Music]
fast who needs a level up you need
one gold red
no I know I know gold is also rare but
we need red right now no no thank you
sorry doesn't even seem that rare I keep
on getting these offers ooh HP is that
pretty good cuz I never saw a HP skill
[Music]
before might be better
right okay let's go for it not like we
need the golden right now anyway the
golden
[Music]
buff that's difficult because the night
is already so slow so the speed is quite
helpful but we could give it even more
HP more is good
okay I believe
[Music]
you
1,300 HP five no
okay okay now I'm out of money again
should we try again or you think this is
still not
[Music]
enough ah this one's
trending I could give it a try all par
was fun it was so cool and the
performance was
awesome
uh performance Maybe
[Music]
video
tashar modern and cool
yeah it does say
cool and maybe a
video yeah okay uh so I'll have to
switch you guys
out
[Music]
video
video W is photo uh that's pretty
low that's oh they're all pretty low
[Music]
h
36 but they're all
photos huh they're sleeping I guess I
have no choice to but to choose the the
lower
ones
M that's fine I guess or should
I get one of the unrelated ones in for
like good
[Music]
thumnail that's so Random did you
congratulate iron Mouse by the way I
think I did I think I reacted to her
tweet but like why are you bringing this
up that is so
[Music]
Random not like I I I'm obligated to do
so for not even in the same company I
did though I did but not like I have
[Music]
to okay video good results turned out
good
M this doesn't match it doesn't
match I will never understand the
internet these tumors are so
confusing that was barely any money
[Music]
1,000 we try again we Brute Force this
[\h__\h] you guys don't have any other like
um advice to me for this stage nothing
in
particular don't lose
wow sub what Subway
Surfer just congratulate the small hat
for it new SL with cie shut
up the small hat is not involved in the
making of the
song no no
no okay good voltage level early
on
[Music]
mhm
okay B level
seven we all know small hat goes through
the
song small hat this track what the small
hat against me or me against the small
hat who's riding the diss
track oh I think we're going we're
getting there now oh I'm going get yep y
oh I'm finally doing
it pushing it
out
cool a they're still strong they don't
take this loss
easily they don't accept it so
simply summon another Knight okay
they're coming they're
coming another
one another
one I want the shield go another Shield
go to back up with some
damage if we need another one I I'm
keeping them
coming oh this will be helpful the punch
really helps me clear a lot
yeah it
it ah why did I make it so
difficult h
no do you need even more really come on
why are we so even I kept on pushing now
we're so even again just let me
throw
ah just let me
through it's
unbelievable why is this so
painful and then it probably the next
level is going to be easier than this
one again cuz it goes up and down and up
and
down oh wait we're actually finally
getting a bit closer and we're attacking
the wall and there's another
punch
oh come
on that should be it that should be
it yeah it's the last level of the
chapter but I don't it could be easier
than this one who
knows yo stop stalling let me
thr
ah I really wish I would have gotten a
ticket from that because that was a pain
in the
ass for real she
agrees okay I'll probably need something
strong so I'll bring in Ena cuz
currently she has like a lot of uh oh
sure a lot of different
strengths
um
so good but should we keep the lunai
doing maybe yeah cuz he can protect
Ena let's see what happens this is the
last one for today if I win if not then
we'll do it until I
win cool that was my goal for today
finishing at least one
chapter oh it's a FL one that we could
probably use that to our advantage and
okay red red focused again again perhaps
I have a lot of purple in here
[Music]
though they're pretty strong so they
allow me to get out quite a few units
mhm
interesting yeah I'm
holding 71 Holdings
oh oh there we
[Music]
go ooh angry black
duck back Peck Peck
Peck oh where did the ENA
go oh oh there she is well she would
have had to be summoned last anyway so
that you know everybody else is in front
of
[Music]
her enemy kot looks like a red twiter
logo yeah true
actually orange though why are you
saying red it's
orange remember my campaign to make
Twitter orange
again make Twitter orange
[Music]
again let's get her a lot of
knights so that she can stay in the back
do damage
whatever
comes we'll have to deal and handle the
knights and now we have to campaign make
X Twitter
again make Twitter Twitter again oh what
the
Shon but I already oh [\h__\h] no he hits
Ina too
a oh we can do it though he's Blue by
the
way okay that was unnecessary no don't
go so why is I I really don't like this
it's so
useless holy
[\h__\h] holy
[\h__\h] like being a a distance unit barely
helps when the the enemies hit so
far
oh I don't know about this
guys I don't
know stay back you
[\h__\h]
it looks a little bit like the mannequin
yeah he
does this is not working is
it I don't think it's
working well maybe it this I can like BR
Force stall the [\h__\h] out of
this
nah n damn
it so he's
blue surprisingly
blue
uh the en the smaller ones were still
mostly red I
think but yeah if I can't bring
down the Shang
gelon what if we bring the Ducks a duck
Army against the shubu cuz they are
focused on Blue 50% defense down we can
bring in some
[Music]
ducks maybe like
this and
then maybe replace the Sho with maybe
even a
[Music]
takachi quty versus quality
yeah cuz they have blue as well both
attack and
defense so a wall of takes and the ducks
with Ena behind and also the knights
somewhere in the
front and the tacos also have with the
red Taco to I think the Ducks won't kill
him much
really I mean I'm open to giving it a
try
but they over there's a lot of overlap
[Music]
here his attack range is big though he
will hit yeah he'll hit Ena
[Music]
anyway yeah I can't go in with s
26 how about the
[Music]
dog what was I going to do either the
ducks or or the dog or oh even the cat
is they're both squishy oh actually but
the cat is less
squishy oh but the DU does a bit more
[Music]
damage
let's try [\h__\h] it [\h__\h] it let's just do
it for the jokes and the memes kill duck
with duck
[Music]
a I need to go to Idol
meeting so please let me win
this my steel iron bladder did you say
bladder of steel or bladder of iron iron
bladder steel BL steel
right duck duck goose duck R is stuck
who's stronger oh they're stronger [\h__\h]
oh yeah I guess cuz they're
[Music]
buffed oh he saw a fast
boy
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] yeah let's stop
spawning the Ducks cuz they're not
helping
me not right now at
least oh God they're already going for
it
that was not even enough to summon
Ena this do seem
[Music]
right no that's not going to
work did you get at least a break a
break no not really I mean I talked a
little bit about it yesterday but was
like 15 minutes but that's totally fine
Ma by the way Ma I saw you
[Music]
too so
so delighted at making your
acquaintance you give in change you give
in
change you got one ticket pray for I
mean okay we can check we can check yeah
know that was the pity already
previously there's no
way
[Music]
but okay let's do
this and
you
[Music]
I'll bring back the colon no wait that's
the instrument and the
instrument the instrument for [\h__\h]
[Music]
sake I don't know anymore I don't
know I don't know anymore let's try
got to keep it low cost as well you
[Music]
know
okay four let's get up to five come on
come on come on don't die don't
die don't die I say okay
five we can more or less
stall
but ideally I would want Bubba
out
for the
buff the instrument
buff yes okay I got it I got it I got it
six okay since they're killing me anyway
I need more units
anyway seems like
it w oh my PC
lagged did you did you feel it
too did I turn into a robot again as
well
[Music]
okay oh why did I do that [\h__\h]
reflexes okay I think we're pretty
strong
now we can go all in now uh it was blue
right the H blue blue blue oh oh more
dogs more dogs more
dogs the shangan is blue
Ena you're laughing now Ena but this is
not
funny oh she didn't get damage she's
like in a good spot don't no don't get
closer Ena you were in the perfect
spot halfway
down
we could do a wall for Recovery I don't
[Music]
know now we're oh I can get
anothera maybe we're
fine do do second Ena
punch uh-oh that's uh uncomfortably
close but he's going to hit her anyway
no matter if she's standing there alone
or or not because of the AOE come on do
something Ena before you die do
something do
something no she's dead
[Music]
again I'm so
[\h__\h] I'm so [\h__\h] I'm so [\h__\h] I
don't have a I don't have a
chance
little wall
time no he can hit her anyway what what
is he
doing no they're in
[Music]
range no please no no no no no no don't
hit no
[Music]
no we need someone like oh roboco roboco
I could
do just have to level her you think
roboco would help
me let me see does she have um blue buff
oh she
[Music]
does uhhuh maybe unlevel someone
else let's
unlevel tanama for
[Music]
now just use W no no no no
no attack
okay blue
defense
Additionally you guys have to help me
choose
[Music]
that
skip e is
[Music]
fine she also a little bit
cheaper problem is just she's single
Target and also ooh same uh instrument
[Music]
H how much HP
1,600 keep Ina and add
robocall oh who do I get rid of then
uh
[Music]
maybe the
crow the
dog okay I'm
scared did I even have enough motivation
to do
that to get both
out
got to build voltage
yeah
sheh okay before tacle let's get the
[Music]
dog I'm about to find out I did you
think
[Music]
so
well the reason I'm spamming them is
because I I I thought maybe I can save
some time to get a bit more motivation
but I guess it's not really
helpful so now I definitely don't have
enough still
uh I don't know
man they're all out
now the wall they're not breaking my own
[Music]
wall but maybe I should let them all
kill me
first now and then a wall oh oh we're
pushing back
[Music]
actually no
okay hey cute I love her voice okay we
got one more higher volage level but now
I need
Ena
ASAP as s a p
[Music]
baby
don't that's another new Jean song
surprise so two you are it's like I
don't know what else you want if this
doesn't work then I can't help
you
yeah I'll try to keep all instruments up
yeah yeah yeah t
punch tacle
punch maybe a few more
tanks woohoo let's go please please
win
oh God they take so much damage but I
can send another roboco if I want
to oh that was good
damage still
alive then I'm sending
Eno stay stay back stay
back
it's possible
though not over yet especially with the
ne oh no that's still oh we're did
it
finally I needed to spawn them
twice but
there's no problem with that right no
shame in
that
Big
[Music]
D So
Long Farewell Al in
goodbye let me take a fro
candy oh what I can get
chelion all right why why am I so
surprised I know I can get all these
bosses
but that's
insane no 20 cost oh he's like a hat M
mhm thank you for your patience oh
there's a kto tour now more difficult
than the Tokyo tour whole parade is
really grown hasn't it I think we have
finally reached a major Milestone let's
show the country we're made
of H maybe another
time let just use up these oh nothing
new
okay
well that was good progress
today uh we had some good PS too we got
Ena we got ba and we got
Senpai so finally more variety on that
front healer unit would have been nice
but can't have everything in the
world and got to make it
work anyway so I think I think I did
that eventually I'll give these people
that I robbed of their levels their
levels back but not for
now thank
you I'm jled as a Healer I don't even
have that I wish I did I wish I
[Music]
did yeah but thank you for watching the
my second Holo parade stream I'm going
to read super chats but before that I'm
going to go to the idol meeting for a
moment cuz I've been drinking so much
water so please wait and I'll meet you
in my office yes uh I guess yeah why not
in the office cuz I'm in my
uniform oh not this
one
M oh don't
look that's was the wrong
one
oh
oh where is
my didn't I
have oh I guess I didn't I only have the
this one wait I need to put up my
Christmas
[Music]
office the idle
meeting but before that let me put up
the
[Music]
chat
okay what crib is time
what what MTV my crib or
what my legs why do I always sit on my
legs I can't help it see you in a moment
oh I don't Mee
with wait for
[Music]
me
oh
[Music]
e
I'm
back I missed
her ah I'm back I'm back I'm back
um where am
[Music]
I
ah
[Music]
yeah okay I'll keep the music running
cuz I really like this one for now at
least
[Music]
oh my head do be round and glossy and
shiny and
gravy okay super chats I think we are a
little bit
behind let me
see taka
Hyer love the onion thank you onion
excuse
me the Mario finale oh thank you for the
hint I finale
oh oh
why does it already feel
nostalgic it's not been that long
just you know when I went into the
bathroom chunkers was sleeping in there
so she was really surprised when I
turned on the light and walked in she
was
like and gave her some
hugs so fluffy my brother also commented
on chunky wonky yesterday being so much
more fluffy because of the winter
coat she is quite something let me tell
you
that why is it cherry
blossoms ah man do I have e an exile are
you here do you know the file name of
the winter office I surely have it
somewhere on my PC I just I just don't
know Eden are you here I can't stand
having cherry blossoms in freaking
December
what was the file name you're here of
course you are thank you so
much could it be
office oh I think I have it Christmas
update I mean it's from last year but
you didn't update it since right
[Music]
so there it
is oh it looks so nice so
festive
my so much snow snow is
falling all around me chicken
playing having
fun T the
season oh I didn't
look please
[Music]
look okay perfect now I feel like you
know this is this is how it should be I
feel more comfortable now you guys
hopefully as
[Music]
well yeah that's how fast the seasons
change one
second chicken slaying yes slay
[Music]
yes okay then here we go Hulan thanks
for the pinky greetings benevolent Tal M
I wanted to ask this since you showed
interest in cars but have you considered
trying out car racers
ah
no they drive differently from MK FZ or
GTA and genre is very Niche and
[Music]
Hol I don't even know like like there
would be nothing interesting about it
like like just racing it's like a daan
stream
[Music]
but I feel like i' rabit play like truck
simulator yeah because then there's like
an actual Target of going through a
country I guess I'm guessing I don't
know it's really rewarding to
learn how
so a set could have played one of
those
I feel like I vaguely have that in my
memory you EU TR I really should play
that as the only residing
European uh whole life
[Music]
member maybe we should play E Truck
Simulator I don't know about those
racing games though m M I'll think about
it thanks for the suggestion though I
mean it's not as
Unthinkable it's not the most
Unthinkable thing I'll just say
that finally made it to a stream welcome
thank you so
much unfortunately we just reached the
Super Chat uh portion of the stream not
the gaming gaming is over so I hope
that's okay for you Jacob 47 py I am
a can you stand D dry croset
D oh yeah yeah yeah I met you thank you
for coming so much theas
artist Mario's entire
family well this time I feel like
Mario's entire family
like we all went through the game on a
positive
note everything was wholesome and happy
I think so
oh yeah even someone I think even at the
panel at the Q&A or during the meet and
greet both actually someone yeah two
times the first I think the first
question mentioned first Q&A question
somebody was like the first thing they
said before asking the question was like
okay wow I really loved your Super Mario
RPG
playthrough like see the stuff like that
also really flattered me I was like whoa
whoa whoa whoa who who what you watch my
streams
thank
you
amazing takasi kiaa 1.5 million
subscribers is surprised people watch
her
[Music]
streams what what unbelievable I'm
shaken shooken Sky D am
d oh thank you spanking thank you for
two pinkies technically Boomers go up to
1963 and Boomer oh yeah we talked about
this on stream we talked about age I
guess well you know it's nice to have a
mix of Boomers and Zoomers in my
community I think because and in between
of course because you know the Zoomers
maybe spread some energy the Boomers
share and spread the wisdom and I I
think it's it's good to have like a good
mix because just like like I look at
YouTubers certain YouTubers famous ones
that have like that built their whole
fandom around like they have like 12
yearold fans mostly or 11 12 year old
fans uh like even D tendo I noticed when
I went to a median grade has mostly like
young Lings but yeah also other famous
[Music]
YouTubers all the the prank YouTubers
and so on
[Music]
so yeah they may be I yeah like so many
that are at the top have that kind of
fan base so maybe they're good for like
getting a lot of Subs but uh I I don't
know I I don't think I could even cater
to do even if I wanted to um you went to
meeting yeah I did
I did long time
ago yeah I think it's
like in some way it's an easy audience
easy to impress but in another way
they're a difficult audience
too and yeah I think I prefer having a
relatively mature audience so that they
understand what I'm talking about and we
can have serious conversations every
once in a while
to yeah oh yeah attention span is also a
[Music]
problem and a lot of my tastes wouldn't
match with like 12y olds either like
they would have no idea what those
animes that I like are and they would
probably not really connect with my
music taste either and probably also not
with my gaming taste cuz I don't play
fortnite
yeah so I think it's good this way so
spankenheimer
age is very much appreciated thank you
for being part of kfp and you
know making us a very
very colorful bunch of people I don't
know how to say veriable very
R ranged group of people
diverse your taste is so weird no it's
not weird you're
[Music]
weird back here's a kiss now give it to
your cat Sushi KY D boo 723 D Louis
Angeles D I'm a proud Taco that no oh I
think
I I read this this is so funny thank you
D Brandon D Theo artist thanks for the
pinky speaking of Final Fantasy 10 it
has an INF famous laughing scene that
someone autotuned for the whole
soundtrack on
YouTube
[Music]
what
what they also did other games g game
themes in it too and while F of 10 has a
sad ending X2 makes it better 10 two do
we say X2 or 10
two
10 to sounds
stupid ff9 has a happy
ending
as uh your for your
information
t 10 that sounds
stupid no but I was curious about that
like yeah which games which of the Final
Fantasy games have some Happier
Endings don't you know maybe it will
influence my my choices in the
future
no most FF have happy I was told the
opposite when we had our pretty negative
ending and I was like are all FF games
like
[Music]
this F of nine will be your favorite
based on your taste
wait let me look up I have9 what does it
look like I may recognize the characters
ah that one with the lady in the orange
jumpsuit thingy that's so cute that
outfit is so
cute wait is there a remake of
this is there remake oh yeah there
is no there isn't that's
fanade oh that was fanmade what I'm
looking at is fanade
[Music]
okay if there's ever a a remake of this
I will play this I like the the lady
she's so cute what's her
[Music]
name what's her name say her name say
her name so I can get her number and
call her um to come
over why you playing games W that
picture is
[Music]
nice hey
y doesn't need a
remake know well it would it would
motivate me in a new release is like
also as a streamer like kind of
[Music]
like how to
say so a new released
game always a good opportunity to play a
game on stream yeah the hype mhm and
it's just a
good
reason my
Thro Peak oh oh I'm glad it has really
really good reviews
then tassy M thanks for the pinky yeah I
am done with my game today to that today
today just going to restore my sanity by
watching you w I am sanity
restoring oh thank you even though I Rob
my own myself of my sanity sometimes or
the games that I play rob me of my
sanity but no I I would say Mario RPG
probably didn't do that that was pretty
nice pretty
healing sometimes I am you like Mario
Kart or Super Mario 64 those kind of
games definitely Rob my
sanity Nathan CAU them than to the pinky
congrats on finishing yet another game
unofficial game finisher of oh thank you
I did yeah man I keep on finishing those
games I can't help it I guess I do not
have commitment issues that's for sure
or do I no I don't think I
do I think on that front I'm pretty
good and you know I may be completing
games
but you complete
[Music]
me was I as smooth as my
head
that was sweet that was really sweet
what I just
[Music]
said just trying to give back to you the
way you flatter me all the time yeah
yeah a little flirt here and
there well in any case I won't be
playing any FF game anytime soon so
don't worry about it for now don't chin
D JK monkey dun alaro dun J swag
swag wait why did I never recognize the
swag in your name until now what the
hell I never like saw as its own
word did you purposefully put swag in
there
swag did you ever Super Chat Cali and if
yes did she like say like swag to
you yeah cuz I always read a j swag book
like a really clear
up so I just never heard myself saying
swag in your name no you didn't but she
didn't say it or you never super chated
it cuz I feel like if you Super Chat she
has to see the
swag she looks for the swag every day
she strives for the
swag she she is the swag you never did
okay okay yeah one day let's test it out
for
science such a fun play for with a good
game and lots of great w content thanks
for playing one of my favorites oh one
of your favorites huh I guess like the
old one right the the OG game did you
play the Remake too or did you just
enjoy me playing
[Music]
it
oh you also play the Remake okay wow
okay imagine playing a game from my
childhood that has been remade or did I
ever do that I don't know if I did like
T shonia never got
remade was there a game that I played in
my childhood that got
remade I actually can't remember you
guys would have to tell me a wind my
girl well that's not really a remake
yeah Metroid Prime that was was that a
remake or wasn't it also just like a
really good
remaster I think that was also just a
good is
a there more of a remaster though yeah
it was like something in between it
wasn't a fullon
[Music]
remake in my
opinion I don't know
[Music]
H it looked that good on the yeah I
did yeah I
did H weird
weird well those are all like kind of
like a lowkey remake I mean like a real
real real remake like this one this was
like a you know like you know what I
mean cuz like the the OG compared to the
Remake that it's just like night and
day in in terms of Graphics at
[Music]
least my favorite song on POV would
either be like from the new songs sleep
talking or pineapple probably sleep
talking
even and overall it's hard to tell
because I'm so accustomed already to the
first five
songs so used DB that I can't really
compare them with the new
ones sleep twerking in my dreams I'm
sleep twerking all these nights it's
[Music]
you sleep
twerking I should put slip twerking up
here on the uh monitors I should put new
one new stuff up
[Music]
there okay where was I oh yeah uh just
here's a kiss M another one Jim Tracy
thanks for the pinky congratulations on
beating the Super Mario RPG it was so
cool to see you play such a classic game
especially when I have fun memories of
I'm happy I could make you guys happy
because I also really enjoyed it so we
all had a good time I think and it
didn't like take too long either so it
really was well balanced good fun not
even too
easy cuz I I've experienced many easy
easy easy RPGs
so good stuff we made good memories I
think worth
it R free d blood guzzler D GD D I am a
beep D Unity chat D for the pinky the
ending was really cute but of course not
nearly as cute as you it was such a fun
and lighthearted game really enjoyed
those streams and I'm happy I got to
watch them thank you everybody had a
good time yeah I appreciate that thank
you thank you so much for watching
tasim hey congrats on beating your first
Mario game I I guess yeah that that
really surprises me every time I hear it
what a nice ending I feel a lot better
now anyway thank you for playing K it
was a lot of fun of watching thank
you I hope I hope you feel happy every
day I'm glad I could cheer you up but I
want you to just feel happy by default
if if I could make that
happen
oh ah oh you guys don't count Luigi's
Mansion
huh H yeah it says Luigi in it but they
mention Mario all the time and finding
Mario is a go and it's not like Mario is
not not existent in
there you call it a [\h__\h] Lui game you
little
shits you little
[Music]
[\h__\h] I don't know about
that you little
[\h__\h] my head
[Music]
hurts J than gamer than for the p thank
you for an amazing playr K I hope you've
enjoyed your time with one of the most
treasured RPG of the SNES area
era it's such a fun and Charming game
with a sense of humor that has H up
remarkably well over the years I know I
have and if so I would absolutely love
to see you trying out Paper Mario the
Thousand Year Door remake once it's
getting released next year you know the
funny thing is that is like d tendo's
favorite
Mario so I know it's
good I know it's
good no I'm not hating
it no I mean I don't know about taper
Mario if I run out of games maybe it
doesn't um I don't know maybe if the
Remake comes out didn't it already come
out I thought it already came out what
I'm so
confused
I guess
not okay maybe when it comes out that is
a good reason for me to play it
then perhaps if I not totally
overwhelmed with other
games oh but yeah uh what was I going to
say U oh yeah I also going to mention
again like I'm
so like confused that they never release
it in Europe if they release it I would
probably know it's better Super Mario
RPG like I legit never heard of it
before they announced the
Remake so what a waste really I'm
surprised you you're from Europe and you
know
it must have been deeper into the Mario
games than
me
no no
no it was just not a
[Music]
available oh yeah I think I heard
something like that about Mario RPG
[Music]
too you one piece it ahuh I
see uh Yumi thank you for the pinking
Mario RPG really is a lot of fun for
what it is thank you for taking the time
to enjoy it as well K thank you for
watching
yo me I think that's like the first time
I see a super chat from you Som I might
be wrong
but I'm I'm surprised you must be a huge
fan of Mario
RPG thank you for the support very much
appreciated D I'm glad you had a good
time with me and the Mario
[Music]
family the game of reduction Ray smash
br ra dun Cruz dun M eight thank you for
the red super chat so crazy you know how
you broke my mind you broke my mind
M comment your first Mario clear this is
one of those games where I only dreamed
of you playing one day so it's great the
Remake came out and what an amazing
remake it was you singing along with the
music was definitely a highlight oh
thanks for the serious Oh you mean like
ch
[Music]
no you like that huh me too
Lord about you salty piece of
chicken don't be so
salty add some pepper in there too maybe
maybe some paprika not only
salt
too
salty need some spice some Chate in your
life I'll be your CH tomato tomato
tomato flavored
chicken what do you mean polar R men I
already talked what I wanted to say I
talked about
[Music]
it Lord
EV t panto tomato it does sound like
that oh it's oh it's still pinned I
guess it
[Music]
is here I'll I'll pin you or
wait this is one thing with Hyper chat I
can't pin
[Music]
comments
it's really
[Music]
unfortunate so I pin
you so M thank
you big kiss big
big yum yum AR for D thank you I'm glad
you enjoyed it as well carp up than
pinky really glad you likeed the game it
has been an amazing playr congrats again
on your first Mario finish
y since you guys don't count luig I
guess okay wow so much for Mario's
entire family I guess Luigi is not part
of that huh space
[Music]
wonderful uh GTA has no super chats then
next is Holo parade
I'm going to r on your
parade what am I waiting
for for me to finish my super chats I
[Music]
guess you know what should get a remake
Dark
[Music]
Cloud genuinely speaking she loves you
more than her dad what what what
what thank you for reporting this to
[Music]
me let's
go oh are you guys saying yes for Dark
Cloud or yes for my win my
w oh I heard dark was good but never
played it dark was so good oh you guys
agree with me let's
go
both I won the parent
one don't tell her though that I feel
like that's not
really that's a bit hurtful don't tell
her Dark Cloud is hey I mean the thing
is I only ever played Dark Cloud when I
was like so young too young to really
enjoy and understand
games so I can't really judge if it was
a good game but I think for its time it
was
amazing
for once a b Sak you little [\h__\h] for
once what do you mean for
[Music]
once so true thank you for Ling Sparks
zly thank you oh yeah finish chickens
that's go oh where's the compliment yeah
but like kind of you know
backhanded Rock sja oh listen everybody
sit down and
listen thanks for the pinky let's
say k let's say what are we saying this
time that whole life has recently won a
battle against Great evil no
wait no I read this one before
we could to turn into blanket I yeah I
skipped previously I skipped some super
chats oh yeah the the Super Mario ones I
skipped those and just quickly went to
the Hol parade ones
no don't sit down and listen because
that was already read
before the gooda blanket made me
realize ah
Maga
oh that is
disappointing why am I so disappointed
by this cookie baking it is I found this
super old fan art of me baking really
randomly and I thought oh my God I have
to REM remember this one until I need my
my thumpnail for the baking
stream yeah lucky
lucky Miss D the gamer great D J Monkey
D unknown d
oh thanks for the r jet unknown I can't
imagine ever getting tired of your
conert I watched all your 1,000 plus
vids streams from start to finish and
almost all of them live I even rewatched
some streams many times I still think
that your content is the absolute best
and nothing can ever
compare we need a
convention or I need to be at a
convention in Australia next
year I know Australia is also really big
so if it's not in the right place it
might be a problem but I need to see my
Australian fans you too you yeah all the
Australians in the chat I need to see
you next
year let's make it happen Okay my
homeland yeah oh say can you
[Music]
see all the to around to
and the snakes slivering
around and the
crocodiles
too and the
karos are
so
cute when the
kiwis are not kiwis
but they
birps that I love
to what do you mean that's not the
[Laughter]
anthem you know I like mixing up
[Music]
anms kangaroo punch is hard have you
been punched by a kangaroo
before [\h__\h] punch
[Music]
do you know your an
uh I'm not sure on the
Melody I don't know the melody actually
something like that and then that's all
I
[Music]
remember I only know those few
words because it means land of the
mountains land of the of the uh Rivers
because we have a lot of those things
beloved
Austria and the the one I know the best
is the uh Canadian National Anthem
that's the one I know the best
surprisingly so maybe I'm
Canadian Oh
Canada Oh Canada how nice are your maple
trees Oh Canada Oh Canada we must not
fight the
pues sometimes you cross a bear on the
street sometimes it might be a little
neat Oh Canada Oh
Canada the mooses
are the
gooes
what
what anyway thank you unnown I will come
to see you in
Australia
2024 let's make it
real the mooses are the
gooses you surely have some gooses in
Canada
[Music]
right Trevor Jean thank you for the two
pinkies Alo wow hope the cookies turned
out great I finally got a notice that my
popup wa is coming home as well as the
friends with you plus waa plus a little
promotion at
work
what what oh you got a promotion what so
aside from just running sending red
supers and filling your nest with new
eggs to celebrate I have oh wait is that
why you sent so many memberships didn't
you send a lot of memberships on that
stream to celebrate I have booked myself
uh a round trip myself round a trip
round trip ticket for a free week trip
and March to a place I've never been
before where I have no clue what I'm
doing or what I'm going to do let's
fingo hope hope your actual vacation
will be fun and relaxing Trevy where are
you going in March if you go to Japan
that would be
perfect that's when the concert is
Right Trevor are you here first ofal
congratulation on your on your promotion
motion mention promotion Japan it is
Japan oh are you trying to get to the
concert I hope you can or at least the
Expo oh I wish you much luck in the in
the lottery whenever that
happens if you need help I'm sure
there's like Japanese Bros who can help
you
out nice that would be amazing
good luck I hope it works out I hope you
get your chance to watch the
waa I guess you have you have two days
that you might want a ticket for maybe
at least one of uh them
works or two concerts cuz I'm in two
concerts oh will they actually put out
official travel package wait without a
flight right you don't have to like buy
like there's no M just like a ticket for
foreigners right that you can sign up
with cuz last year I was really pushing
hard or the last last year
even because foreigners wanted to go to
Japan to get a ticket but like you know
not planning a trip when you don't know
if you get the ticket yet it's kind of
[Music]
difficult they have more news Wednesday
oh okay okay I didn't even know that
that was going
on
oh they already have the lottery for
foreigners going is that
so oh that's really interesting I
totally missed all of those
news
[Music]
nice they had to make a post to one
people about travel package scam they
were travel package scams what the
[\h__\h]
obviously try what I mean try just get
the tickets from official sources
please
eh is that why they're making their own
package cuz they saw someone else making
a
package that's
weird well yeah anyway sounds great you
got good stuff going on I'm excited for
you thank you Trevor G M for all the
support too
W so many memberships on that day that
was crazy jaob
47 as Phoenix thanks for the pinky humix
than Hilder guard thanan anime life
thanan howu thanks for the pinky three
years of being a CP and my 33d birthday
thanks to my Kam oi for the years of
entertainment and Community
oh thank you two three years sheesh
it's such a long time that we spent
together thank you for always supporting
the waa and being part of
kfp I see Ollie in your profile
picture OE is a cutie too maybe maybe we
are your two osis I don't know but but
he I'm your Kam
ooshi I guess I guess you found that
only picture was funny that's fine
that's fine oh totally fine but I just
for a moment I thought only must be y
Koshi if you have her as a picture I
guess
not it's always so sweet when somebody
says Kam ooshi to
me I love you guys thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you hard looking for the top
D I heard you were at anime Frontier did
you not get a meet and greet uh slot or
did you not even
try I need your picture for my
[Music]
collection just kidding I didn't take
any pictures last time besides those
pomu pictures for
pumu it's just a I'm taking pictures
with my head in my head it's all in my
head
head really though
really
mhm you're my Cy oie thank you you're my
Cami bus
[Music]
driver I didn't see an answer in the
chat
[Music]
h you know you have the folder well yeah
but like I don't use it I don't use
[Music]
it I did it like
once just
[Music]
once I'm not lying what do you mean
no
I would never lie to
you except
[Music]
sometimes oh I guess no it's okay I
already have you in my
brain I don't need a
[Music]
picture one of your friends moved to
Austria who she from
[Music]
where from
America
looking for
theal D it was your
birthday happy birthday to you happy
birthday to you happy birthday happy
birthday to you happy birthday
[Music]
F that how you say that
compos right yeah that sounds
[Music]
more
7 p
[Music]
W5 Sky I
Paul Sky
g
r friend Riley g d i a t d best friend
Riley D Flappy boy thank you for the red
chat thanks so much for opening
up in
the this
[Music]
super hyped for what our unofficial Holo
Christmas MC has yet in store for us
wishing you a flum blood free Advance
season and that JMA Claus will deliver
the legendary sock puppets in
time yeah otherwise 25th is
cancelled I don't know what to do
otherwise
[Music]
um
I need a backup plan early on I
[Music]
guess but it definitely can't be
something where like if I want to
include all members it definitely can't
be something where they all have to be
there at the same time at the recording
like stuff like the last sock puppet
thing um everybody could record their
lines on their own and I just acted it
out so that was that was
fine
um but it's kind of unrealistic
to get everybody all of
us at the same time now that's actually
so unrealistic at this
[Music]
point especially cuz like some people
are also on a break but I mean they
might still be open for um taking a
video but and I think they they really
mostly would be open to do that but
still it's just little bit difficult to
plan something like that um and I don't
want to annoy everybody too much either
with like forcing them to do stuff like
that
so please forgive me just in case if it
becomes something that's not all members
at least all members will and are
featured in the Advent calendar overall
but I don't know how realistic it is to
do uh the 25th with like the finale with
all
members it might be just like a grouping
mhm
[Music]
sorry hope she's okay I don't know who
you mean I was actually like mostly
talking about M for
example who is like on a break now right
but also she did take the hor video with
me so I mean
understandable thank you thank
you thank you thank you for being so
[Music]
understanding I have to think about it
soon though I have to write a script if
I wanted to something um that involves
many
[Music]
members going to try to come up with a
script on my own this time I
[Music]
think hope it won't be too cringe it
might be
cringe
yeah anyway thank you so much love
boy Christmas season tast the season
let's go thank you so much for the love
t d and Jim Tracy thank you also the
cookies did turn out
great ah I wonder how long are they
good I feel like like these kind of
cookies they're good for a long time no
I have them in a little box that I can
close so they're not like out in the
open
either
M yeah it should last a while right I
was also
thinking um I still have a bunch of the
the the just normal butter cookies I
don't even have to put the chocolate on
them what if I there's like some recipes
right that need like crumbled
cookies I could make something with
crumbled
cookies like a little dessert of like
maybe apple pie filling and and ice
cream or so that would be insane
wouldn't that be
[Music]
insane cuz my family is coming over for
Christmas so by the way just so you know
already I'm uh I think we're going to
celebrate it on the 24th so I'll be
streaming on the 23rd and the 25th uh
most likely on the at least my mom will
probably sleep over so if I stream on
the 25th it might be in the evening for
me but that would be morning Christmas
morning for you guys but in any case
24th I'll probably not be
streaming pretty sure unless we change
plans
suddenly um what was where was I going
with
this oh yeah cuz I was thinking um what
to cook this year cuz last year my
sister and her boy boyfriend cooked the
dinner
mainly and this year I don't know what
the plan is but I could make cookie
crumble desserts with those
cookies I just thought of
[Music]
that take a break for all the days no I
don't want to because I'm also uh doing
during my midnight of New Year's I'm
going to be with my friends so this year
I decided
uh cuz last year doing New Year's I
wasn't uh home so I couldn't really
celebrate with my friends and there's a
place where I want to go with them to
watch the the fireworks that I missed
out on last year so I'm hoping we can do
that this year so I I still plan to
stream on New Year's but just not my own
[Music]
midnight we do to too you know but I
want to be there for the people who
don't spend like have family around or
so who are like alone during the
holidays I want to give them you know
Joy something nice exciting to
watch during those
[Music]
holidays so I'm trying to be around but
this year is pretty IRL heavy for me
just still trying to squeeze
as much streaming time as I can
in I'm not not yeah well we're not going
partying or so
no just looking at
[Music]
fireworks okay I'll read one more the
one from the Koka I
[Music]
guess it's not that much but there's
there mostly pinkies and
[Music]
reds thank
you thank you
[Music]
guys without you I literally have nobody
to count down with for real see for
people like you I want to be there h
H I'll be there for some time zones
countdown don't know which
one
[Music]
yet oh you're going to be alone for
Christmas but Christmas for you is more
like the 25th is it or what do you see
is
[Music]
Christmas
Jacob 47 J Monkey D RS d p thanks for
the pinky a
p w I had so much fun at anime Frontier
I was so happy that I was able to ask
you and cell a question when you
remembered me and said hi in Korean it
meant so much for me I'm sure that like
some people may have been confused cuz
like all you did was like you said your
name pong and immediately I said an I
wonder if anybody in the room was like
maybe thinking I was being racist or
something just by hearing the word pong
like assuming you're Korean and so I
say but I just immediately knew you know
who you are so I I wonder what other
people were thinking that are maybe not
as knowledgeable about me and my
fandom
yeah
cuz I don't even think pong is like you
know such a clear it's not an indicator
like that is that must be Korean I don't
think you could say
that so I just really knew who you were
obviously but I wonder if other people
realized
that inside the
knowledge left side knew the left side
knew what was
up thanks for remembering me and moving
to Texas for AF was worth
it moving to you mean traveling right
you did cuz I know you're in America now
but you didn't move to Texas did
you you're not in Texas are
you you you did move to Texas
oh I see wa
okay
so it but you say moving to Texas 4 AF
was worth it did you make your decision
where to move in America based on the
anime Frontier
appearance you little
[\h__\h] no
way that's how you phrased it
so maybe you were like H I wonder where
to go I don't really have a good reason
to go anywhere in particular h I's just
say I did that okay
okay hey that's so interesting like
honestly nothing against Texas but if I
were to move to America I would not
choose
Texas definitely
not like I would probably go
for something on the on the ocean side
first and
[Music]
foremost I'm sorry but like if I got the
choice as someone from a landlocked
country I'm I'm going to pick the ocean
side yeah Texas doesn't have an ocean
you're landlock too aren't
you wait you are on the ocean really let
me look at the America map again America
car oh you are oh true quite a big
[Music]
chunk yeah but still yo but you're it no
never mind I was going to say you're
close to Hawaii but that's not true that
we just like showing like a cut out of
Hawaii on top of
[Music]
Texas nah I don't know I don't I don't
know it's I don't even know America well
enough to really you know make a a good
decision in terms of that but I feel
like I would want to go to a more chill
area cuz like parts of America can be
crazy hot
right so I would want to live in an area
that's a little bit more
balanced and I think Texas is like
pretty hot overall
right and and this is just like you know
forgive me this is just Austrian
speaking in me but I would probably go
to a state that is more politically
aligning with my
[Music]
country in terms of like all kinds of
things but yeah
anyway H where was
[Music]
I where are where is the I have so many
windows open there we are
okay state New Jersey what this new I
didn't mention New
Jersey
it was fun seeing you though yeah I hope
you're enjoying Texas I hope you're
having a good time I hope you can make
some friends too especially with the
Texas kfp that you met there I actually
that must have been a great opportunity
cuz you're like really new still right
in Texas so you surely appreciate any
any person that you can get to know and
like connect with so that was perfect
for you I hope you made friends that
live somewhat close because Texas is
huge nice nice I'm happy for
you sitan or CJ thank you for the pinky
I rarely come to your live streams
mostly B clip gang here but I just want
to say thank you for having you sleep
talking and me of course I had to that
song is a gem in your album not going to
lie it's my favorite genre too oh anyway
thanks for the hard work always y our
taste are similar then
I feel that I I appreciate
that cuz I'm I'm happy when I hear from
all kinds of people that they like all
kinds of the songs like all of them like
this one the most or this one the most
but when somebody likes the same ones as
me that feels
really like re
reassuring and and what's the word
approving
so thank you so much I'm glad you liked
it and the sleep talking and I'm really
happy you guys received it so
well I did I think some people no this I
did choose uh the MV maker because like
around the time I was like okay who can
I ask who has an interesting style and I
was watching waya sip some te music
video and I think I was like reminded of
it and I thought the style should be
pretty
good yeah so then they also asked me
like what kind of a me do you want and
all I could say was like oh something
similar to way to sip some tea I guess
with uh these illustrations and like
fitting the vibe of the lyrics and yeah
and then I provided the illustrations
that were supposed to fit certain parts
of the
lyrics um by the way the
illustrations I
requested uh or like in my mind the vibe
I was going for because like they gave
me a lot of options for outfits and and
hairstyles and all that but uh basically
what I went
for I wanted Ariana granded Vibes now
that I say it can you see
[Music]
it cuz the song gave me lowkey Ariana
Grande vibes
the ponytail is 100% reference to
that and the the style of the outfit
somewhat as
well yeah dangerous woman Vibes yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah you get
[Music]
it I love dangerous
women you don't have enough Ariana
knowledge but I think for the ones who
saw some Ariana mvs or sell they they
would understand
mhm I need to sing Ariana in my next col
[Music]
okay yeah so that's the direction I was
going for and I think we we nailed it
[Music]
m I love dangerous K Taki K Takashi
aggressively gay doesn't like Sushi I
guess that's
okay also
like I I was like lowkey thinking to be
more inclusive to do a female mannequin
too but that would have been another
extra illustration and then people would
make such a big deal out of it I didn't
want everybody to make such a big deal
out of it like read too much into it you
know like oh my God famous male
mannequin oh male mannequin no that's
not like I just really
wanted like to tell a story and like
um I wanted it to be like a like a real
artist MB where they you know have like
maybe some abstract objects or whatever
and and some some actors to act
something out with and I can't really
have an actor in my music
videos so you
know this is my my way of uh handling
that
mhm but I like the memes I like the
memes the mannequin replacement
[Music]
memes would have still been hot either
way maybe it what if it was a mannequin
but like basically
like a mannequin version of myself in
the same
pose that could have been
cool like just the same art flipped and
then in the white mannequin
[Music]
look that could have worked yeah but I
only thought of it
[Music]
now self love is important exactly that
would be the
lesson yeah wholesome lesson of love
yourself
appreciate yourself treat
yourself your body is a
[Music]
temple no but I think the the song was
obviously like kind of flirty song
flirty towards someone a love interest
so couldn't have really been me could
it okay next one Dragon CR say thank you
for the pinky hi T I'm the new fan with
the love life fure that you met
yesterday oh yeah yeah thank you for
connecting the dots again with me like I
was aware but you know like I need I
need I need to be
reminded it was nice to meet you
currently in the middle of my 6-hour
drive back home oh sheh I'll be
listening to the stream in the
background looking forward to being part
of
C I'm so happy thank you I I really I
really like
I'm so so so so happy when new kfp
joined us welcome welcome I hope you'll
have a good time I hope you'll enjoy the
games that I play and the music that I
put out and you're joining at an
exciting time where finally the tree
that we have been nurturing will bear
fruits in the form of a fre D
concert Sun
TM
[Music]
are you in the chat even now while I'm
saying these big words I'm really proud
of my words right
[Music]
now nurturing a tree bearing
fruits I'm so proud of
[Music]
that now that was not from today so
should be home by now I'm the my speaker
of Y
[Music]
yeah they're not long words but they're
interesting words my vocabulary you know
it's like I feel very insecure about my
vocabulary ah you are here you're still
driving what the [\h__\h] oh yeah no ah you
are home now okay all get all get so I
was your radio
basically well then welcome home and I
hope you had a good time nice to meet
you Spang thanks for the red super chat
M bring back to dancing pineapple
chickens oh I did bring them back
eventually a few times now they had
their time to
shine I love those
chickens I'm also bouncing this whole
time in my
[Music]
chair I don't think so
DC no way no way I wish I
wish thank you spank
time
pineapple Unwritten D Al D Jacob 47 D
moral imoral D mod arade D I can't stop
bouncing it's the music Cruz d g d it's
such a pickle
music six D Bruce D thank
you I was not I was on the not so
outside but I tried to make up oh thank
you six by the way I just read that
now thank you I did see a few people you
know cheering in between the more quiet
people but I think it's like difficult
um when you're on the quiet
side I get it I get it I would probably
be a little bit more shy too if everyone
around me is like quiet that's
[Music]
difficult I do not not have my feet on
the ground I have them lifted in front
of
me they're not a
[Music]
pretzel I can't stop
bouncing bounce bounce bounce bounce
bounce in the Bounce House bounce
everybody Bounce With Me bounce and
ounce bounce bounce bounce bounce bounce
bounce bounce in ounce in the bounce
house bounce like a mouse and bounce and
bounce and bounce and bounce bounce and
bounce and bounce
[Music]
and you're walking with a
bounce you're walking while listening to
[Music]
me you hit the ceiling o o I'm sorry H I
do not take responsibility
you or nor will I pay for your hospital
bills not my
[Music]
fault let's finish this Super Chat uh
rench cool Mo and another a pinky you're
sending so many pinkies these days thank
you it's awesome to hear that everything
went well in the convention I sadly
couldn't be there still stuck in Europe
what do you mean stuck but I am happy
all of you had such a great time should
you not be in
Europe or is it more like like a general
saying like I'm stuck nothing's
happening here in the future I might be
able to attend the next one the next
anime Frontier or the next convention
cuz I don't know I probably won't be an
anime Frontier again usually they don't
bring the same people to the same
convention
[Music]
it's still bouncing me
too but you're donating in Europe so I'm
like assuming you're actually like from
Europe no am I wrong I love sleep
talking thank you I love sleep talking
too is a general convention okay I'll
try my best to be all over the place
like I'm on I'm on a convention high
right now still you know M so next year
I want to be
everywhere please event
department but usually it's like the
event that like makes a suggestion of
who they want and then our team may also
make a suggestion if if they don't know
who they want but you know usually it's
like them choosing
so I'm actually honored I get chosen so
much
[Music]
yeah uh Amilia Paladin of the Bri Shield
thank you for the rest ofe chat hey K
congrats on the album I had some really
rough freaks leading up to the release
but listening to your album made me feel
like I could take on the world like
every hardship was to be overcome wow
not to trip me up thank you K thank you
for all you do wow what damn like I feel
like music doesn't even have that effect
on me
so I'm it's just
like crazy to me that it can have such
an impact on someone else thank you so
much I'm happy to hear that yeah it's
great I wish you all the best thank you
for all the love please continue
listening to PO and the waa music thank
you so much I wish you all the best
things in the
world I'm glad you like it so much it's
an honor to
me Nagel thanks for the pinky oh another
name you don't hear so much these days
thank you hey K it's great to hear you
enjoying meeting new fans and older ones
as well I wish I could go to one of the
Mee and greets but sadly missed all the
doomies one day yeah doomi would have
been the chance that's the closest I've
ever been to you but yeah one
day there must be at least one European
convention this year right I mean the
coming year we we'll get something going
for
sure we'll make it happen thank you Nago
for saying hi nice to see you around
nice that you didn't forget about me cuz
I didn't forget about
you JP r snsr y d thank you it was so
cute thank you chocolate insomnia thanks
for the pranky K it was so fun talking
to you I think you were already tearing
up when you got to me yeah
like in between when people left the
room and the new ones came in it took a
moment and I was
like like
sobbing forgot to mention at the meet if
you have a nickname for me let me know
since I know my name is a mouthful to
say oh I mean it's not difficult to
say how
about um how
about
M ch
ch ch
ch that's
so thank you for
[Music]
that
ch ch ch it's pretty
[Music]
similar maybe something like that but
you can keep your current name too it's
fine cuz I didn't come up with anything
interesting
really thank you though for being there
at the Mee and gr it was great meeting
you
too yay was a
[Music]
pleasure
forever it's B thanks for the pinky
thank you for the wonderful K looking
forward to the 3D celebration let's go
you're
welcome I'm also excited for it w wow I
mean you guys know it's pre-recorded
right I haven't seen the final product
yet
but I probably will see it like sometime
before yeah but I think it will be great
cuz I trust the director as well the
director also did my my
3D
um uh debut I was actually quite
surprised because I feel like he did
such a good job at my fredd debut and I
thought like oh he must be like doing
this these 3D things all the time but I
was told he told me that he doesn't
actually uh like normally do these more
like
live
like how to say life focused like
dancing singing performance focused uh
3D programs like usually he does more of
the like bangam me like program
comedy uh
variety
programs you
know and he told me that besides me he
only does one other whole life members
uh birthday anniversary
Etc so like just in charge of two people
basically
y not like they like once you have one
3D thing with one director you always
get stuck with them I don't think that's
the case but like since I was pretty uh
satisfied I just like requested the same
director I don't know if that even had
any influence or if it was just assigned
because of the scheduling thing but yeah
yeah yeah
I just thought he's really good so let's
go with the same person cuz I don't I
can rely on
[Music]
that yeah yeah yeah I I wanted to work
with the same person cuz I don't know
like he also has like a lot of
experience with these uh
programs so even if it's not just like
uh these dancing singing things
usually even then um I trust the
experience cuz there's a lot of new
directors too
apparently so I don't
know better stay with what I
know
[Music]
yeah especially cuz I'm like
pretty uh not like picky but like I have
I have certain like special
requests for like how to do the
recording like certain things I'm kind
of like partic about and like he already
knew it from the first time we work
[Music]
together and then because I already knew
him from before I didn't even feel bad
like uh you know there's a thing that
happened like it was a two-day recording
right and that you know you guys know I
had one day in between where I wasn't
recording but I was still like
practicing and you know how I was like
pretty until last minute I was still
practicing even at the recording so
there were certain songs that I was more
more um uh confident about and certain
things I was less confident about and
then there was like a schedule of which
songs to record on which day
and
I uh first I was like trying my best to
go with that but then I
noticed on on the on the morning of the
first day when I arrived I I went in
there already with with like a lot of
nervousness nervosity so I I I asked
please please please can we change this
and this and this and I don't think I
would have been able to ask for that
confidently uh really uh if it wasn't
for that
director
cuz I felt comfortable enough to say to
speak about my troubles of
like being um in pain and being stressed
out and not having enough time not being
able to sleep and all that cuz that was
a big issue during the time
yeah so it all worked out in the end
thankfully team work
guys
teamwork yes
yes the thing is like it's not so easy
to change these things because um like I
don't want to you know speak too much in
detail but they prepare a lot of stuff
depending on the song for like how how
the
light and the
like the camera angles and all that they
they prepare all of that beforehand and
like changing it doesn't work with like
one finger
snap it's not like
that
so it all takes time yeah technical
[Music]
stuff hold this
now so this n anyway that was another
tangent while bouncing
how many finger snaps oh a lot of finger
snaps a lot of have you guys seen that
like Zoomers like the cool kids on the
blog when they're like I saw I saw this
in like YouTube videos and I was so
confused they go like they go like
snapping when they like something
instead of clapping they snap and I'm
like what the [\h__\h] I can't even snap
that fast like they snap out of
excitement what what
why they're like yes yes let's go I
can't even my fingers it
hurts I could not show my excitement
like that do you guys have you not seen
it I've only seen it in the Poetry SLS
oh that's that's different I
think that's different that's different
it wasn't the poetry slam at
[Music]
all let's beat
thanks a classy form of
clapping that's like so difficult to
clap like that and like very unefficient
The Poets from the 50s no but it was it
was definitely not like
that it's more like young kids
appreciate each other like
yes maybe yeah maybe people gets
[Music]
it clapping is triggering and too loud
oh yeah I guess clapping can be pretty
loud but I can I can clap rather quietly
too but then it just doesn't seem right
does it like you're not that excited if
you clap like this is so half
[Music]
F Jazz head
what what do you mean Tri it's
triggering these days no way no way no
no don't say
[Music]
that I can't keep up with that I will
continue to
clap I just hum quiet just hum quietly
to express press approval approval
mhm mhm like
that anyway rud rules thank you for the
rest of the chat I love fredine I love k
y let's go I love fredine and I love
kfp this kind of
matching you love kiata I love
kfp so I'm assuming rude rules you're
going to be there right it's a promise
I'll see you there first row
you're just
cool ziply D and Fafa thanks for the
pinky sticker wow wait I feel like I had
stickers off for a while maybe that's
why I didn't see you around for a little
bit
fa thank you d Everybody for the support
D had a lot of fun reading the super
chats and playing the game although
playing the game was kind of chill today
wasn't it more the chill side
I'm going
to warm up the
pizza
and uh do I have something to
do I don't know can't think
straight I want
to I want
[Music]
to I want to eat
first then think eat first then think oh
I have one more thing to
[Music]
say oh no no no thank
you
fighting fighting
fighting I feel bad I can imagine work
being really bad for you
[Music]
f you can do it Hulu do it for m
a better
[Music]
future no go to
sleep you're staying up all night for me
and then you go to work tired no no no
no yeah I wanted to say something about
tomorrow's
[Music]
stream it has been br brought to my
attention that may be the game I was
excited about in my childhood was not
snowboarding but 1080
Avalanche we told you that what do you
mean I don't know I don't remember that
when did you tell me that why did you
let me have a excitement
for this game that is a [\h__\h] stranger
to me probably
possibly for so many like a whole year I
was excited for this whole year yeah the
the Avalanche one is the GameCube one
and I feel like when I saw in a direct I
was like
gastl naturally to think that because it
it looks pretty
similar they both have like El squiggle
maps on the Bott
right they both Zoom through the snow
but if I think back I think games that I
played on the N64 were really limited I
did have an
N64 uh like early ear like it was like
uh I was really young and I think it was
already like close to the end of the era
of the N64 because I feel like soon
after I got the
GameCube um is a
sequel yeah but uh yeah
well I don't know I watched videos of
the gam playay of both and first I
watched the 1080 snowboarding one and I
was like yep yep yep that should be it
but then after I watched the 1080
Avalanche one and then I was
like wait I feel like this is a bit more
familiar but I'm really not sure but it
makes more sense if the one that I
played was the GameCube one because I
definitely spent more time with a
[Music]
GameCube yeah and the oh like from at
least from the game footage that I saw
1080 snowboarding didn't have uh like
those stunts on like rails and all
that but Avalanche has them and I feel
like I experienced that those rails the
stunts
[Music]
maybe oh yeah I don't know so I realized
that and I was
like do I even still want to play it
then I guess I will because surprisingly
you guys are excited for it aren't you
like for some people it's nostalgic um
we'll just imagine we'll just pretend
can we
pretend that it was the game from my
childhood long long time
ago we're just going to
pretend that this is the one it's pretty
similar
[Music]
anyway so with
that I'll see you tomorrow to go
snowboarding I wonder if there is that
even like
like how much content is there anyway in
that game can I play it for more than an
hour I
[Music]
wonder can't imagine a game like that
being that like grasping for several
hours we'll find out
yeah if not then it'll just be a short
stream and that's fine too because I
have so many streams this week anyway
right oh that reminded me I have
something oh yeah don't forget
wa so yeah goodbye guys I think I'll
take a
shower oh [\h__\h] my headache what is it
with this headache I I need to go I need
to get away from this PC German we
[Music]
say
bye-bye guys snowboarding
tomorrow
hey
bye-bye oh almost 6 hours
well see
y stream uh sleep talking please after
this would you kindly go over to sleep
talking the music video and give it one
View and don't tap out
please cuz that might influence
it negatively maybe leave some likes on
the comments to show YouTube that you
are interacting with the
video thank
you thank
you
thank fine I will consider
it thank you thank
you I am so
[Music]
hungry is is is no one streaming right
now oh no one is streaming according to
[Music]
hyzer a CO is starting in in a
while but yeah
okay I'll just end it
then you see a Pomo
stream oh what is she
streaming Metal Gear
Solid yeah no raid you guys are just
going to listen to sleep
talking go go go