[Music]
welcome
to
ollie's deadly fun
[Music]
can i get a clap
thank you thank you very much
thank you
hello everyone
welcome welcome welcome to my
birthday
orino
can i get another hand please
[Applause]
i i found this free clapping um
effect and i'm in love with it
yes
so
um actually
we're not going to call anyone until
another 15 minutes
[Music]
like we're going to start calling
at uh
5 p.m gmt plus 7 we're not going to call
anyone yet why because i'm way too
nervous right now i want some time i
want to warm up a little bit my hands
are shaking my knees are weak mama
spaghetti i don't even remember to rap
there's going to be a lot of people
coming to the
i'm super excited
around around did i give you guys
spoilers on how many people
happy birthday
thank you
you guys you guys want to know how many
people are coming
it's probably like 50 people
wow
a lot
yeah and i'm very very excited i i uh
yeah that's a lot right and i'm very
very excited because they're all
really nice friends of mine
i can't wait to call them
so anyways before we start did you guys
heard my new cover
thank you so
much did you guys did you guys hear my
cover did you guys did you guys uh
heard following
me
yeah even the fanfare channel is here hi
yeah so um you know how the original
um the original song is actually
jazz pop pop jazz
originally
did such a great job
with uh but with the arrangement like i
literally told reynard reynard i want
this cover to be jazzy and boza nova i
want it to be chill something that you
you'd usually listen to when while
you're sipping coffee and then art was
like say no more i got this ali what do
you mean
hmm
is so so nice because uh i know i i
didn't say anything like here of us was
like what kind of illustration do you
want and i'm like
make it cozy begin cozy there
and boom
like like did you guys even see the
encounter in the city did you guys see
that there was encounter in the city in
the illustration
that was how like like i told you it was
oh can you put an encounter in the city
and then he of us was like oh all right
if that's what you want
and so here was put encounter in the
city right right then right there
it was also a 301
an r301 carbine in a music video i'm
sure you guys saw
for example i have the soundproof walls
and they're black and white and he has
actually put that into illustration also
i have a guitar and he has in here wasp
actually put that in too so it was it
was very very nice i liked the little
details that he was put in there
here
[Music]
uh i don't want it to be too flashy i
want it to be simple but stylish i want
lots of smoothing some
and guess what
delivered
and i became really good friends with
because
we have we have quite the interest right
[Music]
i love how clean everything was and you
know
isn't actually indonesia
but
she put all of the lyrics in the right
places
right
i'm really happy i worked with really
really great people for this uh
cupboard and it's my very first ever
indonesian cover
indonesia
[Music]
it's not an official translation
like uh i had a team that helped me
with the translations because i want
everyone to know the meaning behind the
songs
hey
isn't it early
early at your place i love you no i love
you
i love you
love you
thank you
man we have seven more minutes i gotta
get ready
i don't want to miss a thing oh shush oh
sister making me happy
making me really happy no you
we might get into another one-hour
argument
last time i had to collab with it iron
mouse asks what happened also before we
get to anything else huh do you guys
you bit
yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh no no now that's some spoilers
hmm
[Music]
uh you guys see this new setup this
layout was made by omorphia
yes omorphia
so uh i want to have a stage thank you
for my thoughtsumachi so i commissioned
on
uh omur omorphia to make me one
hmm
you see all of these audience and
morphia also do it himself
and the lights look look look it's it's
dimming and it's lighting up again and
it seems again then it lights up again
and i even have my very own led screen
i prepared a question deck for my guest
for example
[Music]
and then last but not least
what was your first impression of ali
eating
yes i i prepared everything so that i
can have a proper conversation with
everyone but
uh all of the all of my conversations
won't last too long i want everyone to
have like a turn
and a call
so we'll be limiting their time
there will also be a very important
announcement on this on on on 6 pm the
gmt plus 7.
[Music]
um
three more minutes until we call our
first
yes
very excited
[Music]
by the way i'm showing everyone's fan
art on the led thank you so much
everyone for the fan night uh i couldn't
put every single fan art in because
there was like 200 fan arts
and i don't think my obs can handle
more
but i hope you guys enjoyed this little
slideshow of fahrenheit
i used uh i used the hashtag
holiday
2021 to to
save them
please uh enjoy them
yesterday
i'm so nervous
can you guess
who will be the first one
[Music]
i'm sure you guys would know
i'm sure
you guys have any guesses
oh thank you
[Music]
[Laughter]
this is
yes
the first one is going to be my first oh
oh my god
they're already standing by
bye
[Music]
let's call them
[Laughter]
this this is after a great start indeed
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
one night
[Music]
do
bye bye
that's one way to open my birthday
that that is one way
open my birthday indeed
getting called out
in front of 4 000 no 5 000 in front of 5
000 people
but but i love my
man how do i even react
how how do i react everyone
she's like don't don't love any other
women but me love only me okay
hmm
um
[Laughter]
we just started
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
is
a
um
what do you know
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
hey
what is it with everyone exposing the
first time they get into the car
but hey i got a shogi date
ma senpai won't be so happy about this
yet
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
okay
hmm
[Laughter]
m
[Music]
um
my
[Music]
yay
definitely
of course
yes
[Music]
give a round of applause everybody
i should have done that
uh
i keep forgetting i have this
oh
are they here
thank you
[Laughter]
everyone this is
i get boing boing
boing boing happy birthday yeah thank
you
[Music]
hi
like
the uh
[Music]
um
i'm blessing
[Music]
[Laughter]
so
[Music]
foreign
thank you
huh
i'll put it where should i put it
put it here
[Music]
then bye
oh
[Music]
um
me
[Music]
baby
hawaii
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
um
hmm
[Music]
bye
yes
[Music]
um
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
me
foreign
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
come on
foreign
uh
[Music]
thank you
yeah yeah
i give you i want to
give you presents
today
oh
[Music]
i saw that creep
and ori talking
3d uh coming japan because 3d
they worried
speaking
japanese
[Laughter]
yes
okay come on come on
very very crazy so
crazy
at first
at first i saw the greeting so
[Laughter]
thank you
sorry ori i delete apex so
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you
everyone i got i got it i got a date
ticket
with about a senpai if i come to japan i
can ask her
attitude to guide me that that is so
nice
of course it'll only be the two of us
like i love muna senpai
but
but i want to have my own date with
subaru senpai
sharing sharing is caring am i right yo
am i right
[Music]
huh
this is
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
foreign
um
is
foreign
yo
[Music]
foreign
hey
[Music]
what a special date yet another day that
you have uh evaded my chase that's fine
though okay because you're cool i will
allow it
i mean
i i just called arusha senpai the other
minute
listening
listening you guys are you guys are real
buddy buddy are you now
yes it makes sense you know she's a
necromancer i'm machinigami i get it
yeah
don't you worry though i'm still going
to wish you a happy birthday thank you
because yeah i'm not bitter i'm not
jealous don't you worry about it oh i
wrote you a wrap you did
wait i want to hear it
i kind of forget the flow i wrote it uh
in the past 15 minutes but let me put it
down for you okay yes please
let me let me turn down the bdm there we
go
oh you betcha and i'm gonna send you the
lyrics too
because uh
i i rap like it's like kind of hard to
understand sometimes
um so i'm just gonna i'm gonna put it
here for you and you can you can read
the lyrics as i go okay here we are
okay
yeah i got this friend her name is ollie
to the crazy try to play it cool [\h__\h]
gummy but she plays me like like a
fiddle talking hey diddle diddle between
russia and ollie wanna always be the
middle tried to kill me yesterday i
cannot hate you though that face is so
perfect like the golden ratio and not to
mention that her cooking is fly because
ollie is the best when it comes to pie
that's pizza the i counting 3.14 you've
made so many cakes are you down for one
more you make everybody's birthdays so
bright so i'm saying that it's your turn
now enjoy this party night i made you a
cake
yeah i know everyone can make me
i did you made me a cake before too so i
made you one i'm gonna make you look
creepy you're always making people cakes
so i thought
well i should make you one
oh it's so cool there there's there's
wait let me sell everyone
yeah
don't worry it's definitely safe to eat
the eye isn't very convincing though
uh yeah it's um it's a k it's a candy
eye maybe possibly i don't know i didn't
check i didn't check underworld
supermarket kind of sketchy
a new supermarket
i hope you enjoy it though
oh i will i'll enjoy it deliciously
sorry that was cracking me up yesterday
i i love how we actually share the same
brain still when it comes to fishes and
like people selling stuffs right
very very lucky it's like we connect on
a spiritual level i like it i mean i am
dead and you are death so it makes sense
it does make sense that we are we are
connected deep inside please enjoy this
delicious tasty cake oh i surely will
other than this cake i kind of i kind of
want
more cake from you if you get what i
mean wink wink funk
oh you mean wait
huh
why are you winking at me i'm i'm
confused i'm scared
i'm gonna pick me up i feel strange
right now
it feels strange always making me feel
strange
oh god
enjoy the birthday cake that i gave you
okay listen i i i i will okay then time
for some questions senpai
all right hit me i'm ready i'll hit you
boom
right no
oh maybe not this one what was your
first impression of me
oh
good question
um
i think everyone's gonna say the usual
uh like crazy like everyone thinks
you're crazy and whatever uh but for me
i just thought you seemed really
passionate like i'm not trying to be a
contrarian or like a hipster or anything
like that but like it felt really cool
to see you like bust onto the scene and
just like have so much love for everyone
already and um i kind of like wasn't
like that i was the opposite i was super
confused and afraid and like didn't have
a ton of love for everyone right off the
bat so i just really admired that you
know
it took a while for for some folks to
grow on me but you were just so positive
and cool from the very beginning and uh
i really admire that about you you know
you just you just are yourself and i
really i respect that a lot
yeah you're awesome dude you're awesome
man look at the look at the red hearts
in the chat senpai you're so wholesome i
love you so much thank you
of course no problem i can't wait to do
more collabs with you
yeah like
mario party or or
more apex with lucia senpai holograms
apex oh my god if you two are there with
me i'll do my best
[Music]
got him yay
oh god i feel like i'm being roped into
something
but it's okay you guys will make it fun
i just know it like when we did it with
uh when we did apex with um with mel it
was super fun so i just yeah i know it's
gonna be a blast again with you guys so
i'm looking forward to it ollie you have
yourself a great birthday okay i will
thank you so much
of course i'm gonna go cook spaghetti
now you take care of yourself ooh mama
spaghetti
yeah my spaghetti oh by the way um i'm
uh i'm wearing pants right now goodbye
goodbye
why did she say she was wearing pants
she got me a cake and wrote me a wrap
that's mori senpai for you
yeah next is actually um
uh
this next person
she she was about to come but uh she had
other schedules
and so she decided to send me a video so
let's go go go and watch together
i'm gonna turn this down everybody ready
one two three
[Music]
i just wanted to quickly say happy
birthday to you i'm sorry i couldn't be
there live on the call but
i am thinking about you
i just couldn't be here today but but
still i hope you're celebrating a lot to
help your partying as you always do and
that's what we love about you your
energy
and your your vibes and your motivation
it's very inspirational and
you kind of just give up i just hit it
on her
lives to everyone in the video so i hope
i hope you can continue doing what you
do
because you bring a lot of joy
to whole life
the first time i saw you
and when i saw that you were debuting
i was like
i was so excited because the moment i
saw you i kind of like i was like so
hyped up because i was like this girl
this girl
yeah she must have something special
because she already looks like extremely
special oh you're special so from the
first moment i saw you i was very very
excited and you definitely lived up to
that excitement yeah
so happy happy birthday once again
please
have an amazing day
and i hope to see you soon
[Music]
bye oh
so sweet of her i literally was just
hitting on morrison pie
she gave me such a wholesome video i
feel bad now
feel pretty bad not gonna lie
oh i got a present from nelson pie it's
a little bit late a bit
better late than never right look look
look nelson if i drew me something
before we
go on to the next i guess i want to show
you guys this
thank you nelson my mom's in my
honeycomb oh i'll oh where should i put
it i'll put it
here
yes
we'll wait for the next a dialer
oh why is it happening
[Applause]
i'm doing great everyone's everyone's
greeting me everyone's wishing me a
happy birthday i got some cake it's
amazing
oh wait wait uh oh your voice wasn't in
i'm so sorry
i forgot to admit i'm so sorry
me bob this is the answering machine
i'm so sorry thank you
happy birthday
thank you
[Music]
how are you doing
i'm i'm
i'm doing great
i got lots of presents and it's a fun
day
oh i guess i should uh add on to the
pile of presents then huh
[Laughter]
[Music]
i can find it i can find it i can find
it that's okay take your time
[Music]
i love it is it to be me
let me show everybody
[Music]
that's big
oh yeah it's big
baby i i love it i'll put it here thank
you
okay it does kind of look like you thank
goodness
wait did did
did you have doubts
uh yeah cause i i
i started it around when um when metal
supply was called
with that speed what the heck
need
so speedy what the thank you
sorry it's not it's not very fancy but
what no i don't want it
it's everything
look look look i'll make it my face
oh
that's so cute
yes
it it'll be my new face because it's
just very very
yeah i hope you um i hope you have a
really really good day today with lots
of cake
let's just delicious
uh yeah
yep
send by can i ask you some questions
maybe
of course
what was your first impression of me
senpai
uh first impression of ollie i thought
she was a very calm and uh so
uh kohai
with the name crazy ali
no but you know
people
people see you know the crazy part of
you at first but one is supposed to get
to know you you know you have a lot of
care for everyone around you and you're
very
kind a sincere person and i
i uh i like that about you hmm
yes
like like everyone would say you're very
energetic you're a very brave like like
hearing some wholesome compliments makes
me all jiggly inside
oh
let me give you a headpiece
yeah you're like like basically if i had
a younger sister i would like her to be
you
can i be your younger sister
of course
yep
[Music]
boom
basically yeah
kind of close in that ballpark
thank you
thank you for coming soon bye
y'all happy birthday
love you
let me
get a chew on my cheek
did you get it
i got it i got it
it's kind of cold but
zombie lips really be cool
[Music]
and next right off the bat
hello
happy birthday
thank you
say bye
i have a present for you presents
give them to me
this is for you
is wait
the the shape oh never mind
no no no no no no no no no i had i had
indecent thoughts when i saw this thing
i'm so sorry for you
look everyone's spaghetti
oh yeah i'm not that great at drawing
but i wanted to make you something uh
that reminded me of you
oh
i i remind you of spaghetti
yeah
spaghetti meatballs
why
with your meatball buns
it's spaghetti sauce
and spaghetti sauce
yeah
oh i love it
there's like a hidden ollie over there
like three circles all together
oh yeah except you have i don't know the
candle sticking out of your mouth you're
like
[Laughter]
i can see
and that's something
i love it
thank you
a happy birthday did you eat something
tasty today like spaghetti
oh actually
since you asked i actually had this
really delicious
um full meal it's like a full breakfast
with hash brown and sausages and
scrambled eggs oh
yes
i'm gonna eat that i'm gonna eat that
when i wake up for real because
all right i just love the earth
yeah but it's totally worth it now i get
to be the last person right before oh
you know oh yeah
thanks i'm excited to see hmm
please dude anticipate it
and oh well i'd like to ask you a few
questions if that's okay
sure
uh what do you wish for ali's birthday
like
oh
well
what do i wish for ellie's birthday i
wish that you continue having the
amazing collabs you've been doing lately
i mean since you were able to collab
you've been doing some pretty awesome
ones uh so i uh i hope
that keeps on going well and
i hope that uh you know you feel good
for the for the rest of the year well
not just for the rest of year you know
but yeah i hope you have a good time
in uh
in a hollow life with everyone
[Music]
stay over there
i guess i'll make an exception since
it's your birthday
i'll allow it just because it's your
birthday
thank you oh senpai we said um
you know
we played apex
so i thought mimi and next time we
should play something else like maybe
sure chess ah
okay okay
yeah we can play chess i'm ready you
know i've had a long break since the
last time i've played and i really
needed that mental you know release
i think i'm prepared
yeah
let's do it let's do it thank you
goodbye
yeah you're welcome
thank you
yes i'm looking forward to it
me too i i know you've been studying a
lot i haven't
uh i don't really know anything about uh
strategies and stuff like i know kind of
but i i've never like looked anything up
so i'm i'm excited to see what you do
i'll be sure to give you some tips too
while we play it'll it'll be awesome
it'll be like a learning play
oh okay oh that's so useful thank you
i'm gonna kick your ass
[Laughter]
that was muted for them okay yeah you
couldn't hear what she said it was
really bad oh my god
thank you
okay senpai
uh you're welcome thank you for
having me and uh good luck on the rest
of your stream and by the way i am not
wearing pants
okay bye
why aren't the young girls wearing pants
why are they not wearing pants
okay
man i i love everyone yeah before we
move on everyone
what
my man maurice and bye wha
what what have you been
what have you been
uh telling the girls to do
legend
that's the gum worries inside okay time
for announcements everybody ready
do this real quick
okay
we're clearing everything up first
announcement times announcement times
happy b day thank you
well then
it is time
for
the real deal
oh wait no
wait no
there we go
everyone
the birthday merch is finally out i
wonder if i can pause this yes the
birthday march for ollie there will be
four special of voice and one special
item wonder what it is it's an odin plus
check this out
this is the japanese version this isn't
it we didn't flush wait
is that it gotta
and four special voices wonder what it
is also a bonus if you buy the full
package then you will get a bonus
postcard with my signature on it it's
super super cool i'm going to put the
link in the description below there we
go so you guys can start ordering from
now
pretty dope pretty awesome right
yeah the wooden plush will be 45
centimeters tall
centimeters so it's pretty big the
wooden plush is going to be as big as
the
the illustration that you see on the
postcard yeah it's super huggable and
and not to mention this wooden can sits
visa beside
you
pretty cool right and you guys can get
it now
take my money
amelia senpai would you like an udin
yeah see that that's just how big the
odin is it's quite big
very big only with the highest quality
of material
there's also a bonus short voice if you
buy the full pack this is
or as we say in english meanwhile in
another universe
[Music]
you're buying
oh you you also have the taco that you
plus right maybe takodachis and and and
they can meet up
and then and become friends that would
be so
cool
yeah
super big
so if you guys want to buy it it's
available if you guys want to i want to
if you guys want more details it's
hosted in a hollow life indonesia's
official twitter account
you guys can check it out right now
the twitter official hololive indonesia
uh
wait let me drink a little
yes there will be one olivia voice but
that's only a bonus voice it won't be as
long also ah there we go thank you ram
chan
di
[Music]
special voice if you guys buy this
little set you guys can also get the
scripts for the iden and japanese of
special voices
yes there will be three scenarios i'm
not going to give you guys spoilers
every
uh storyline in every um
language is different
how different is it well one way to find
out mudas kali as i learned from renee
all you need to do is go to the link in
the description below or check the link
on the pinned comment and check out this
toy
boom boom boom
why isn't it looping please there we go
or special voices one special item put
in
oh
yes
very
easy
in the midst of promotion i got it i got
a gift
while i'm promoting i got a gift
everybody from
from
oh wait wait i'm going to show you guys
after the promotion
oh
after after after the promotion and uh
give me give me two more minutes
so what else should i say about this
notification
for whenever you guys get a message
official
voice notification what happened
thank you so much for coming
thank you
ringtone yes ringtone ringtone that
that's what i meant
there's an english version an indonesian
version and a japanese version
of
[Laughter]
hey oh thank you for coming
so anyways we have a few minutes to
spare i want to show you guys the gift
that mama gave me
you guys didn't see anything yet
you guys didn't see anything
i'm
i'm i'm i'm a i'm not
yeah
present
okay
i got i want to show you guys
this
is going very well everyone
um
this cake looks like a hat it does
doesn't it wait let me wear it actually
wait wait wait this one
oh yes this one
i'll wear it
as a hat
here this is this is the present that i
got from mama
but mama gave me a present anyways
mama
thank you
thank you so much i will i will where
should i put it can can i put it here i
don't want to block everyone's fan art
but but i need a place to to
to put the dilemma down i don't know
where
high and mighty
nice uh uh
molly okay then let's get ready for the
next color shall we
next color is everybody ready
hello
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
hmm
foreign
[Music]
birthday present
so cute
thank you i like horizon who is always
happy to talk so i'm better talking the
original gif
oh
very very talkative
very
what was your first impression of ollie
nice
and my percy pleasure wally is that she
is crazy
i know
foreign
[Music]
which made me very happy
i wanted to talk to only chance so i
started studying
[Music]
even
zombies
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you
foreign
bye bye
thank you
oh that was so sweet
nathan
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
and that
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
um
foreign
[Music]
what is it
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
it
foreign
um
thank you
[Music]
um
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
my
foreign
[Music]
hmm
bye
great
and that has been my two twin sisters
from the lamale
yes so there was and babanetan and
shizukunichan and homura
now before we go to the next guest i
wanna
i kinda wanna
um tidy up my obs real quick um
if you guys don't mind let me let me
where should i put this
look at this here yes oh the spaghetti
stays and then uh
it should be close to llamas darling i
believe
hmm uh for this one you can put it over
here
it's not blocking anything because so
that would be good and then
should also be close to the lamily
[Music]
over here
okay that's a lot more tidier did the
cake place on top of my head yes so
anyways we're going to move on the next
one i'll be calling a very good friend
of mine you guys ready
[Music]
[Laughter]
we're born
[Music]
good morning there for you there who's
having a good day
lift your arms to the skies
and stretch all your troubles
away
[Music]
we were born onto this world we shall
ventured at all
with all the good times
or even sad times we're born today
[Music]
you may say it's just like any other day
be a downer and sad like any other day
but listen here my friend
everything is going to be
all right
zombres are here with you
and that's the song
for you
today
now put a smile cause
you're born today
[Music]
okay
okay let's go
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
my
happy birthday
[Music]
yes
wow
i never expected that i'd sing on my
torso
next
[Music]
happy birthday
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
me
foreign
[Music]
hmm
[Laughter]
[Music]
m
[Applause]
[Music]
you make our golden week
we make our own golden week
[Music]
only a week let's go
let's go
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh thank you
thank you have a great day have a great
[Laughter]
[Music]
my
but she couldn't come today so she sent
me a video so let's
move to a different overlay
[Music]
happy birthday
foreign
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
you're so well loved i'm not well loved
i'm just lucky to meet so many nice
people and so many kind people in my
life i'm forever grateful that i'm
always surrounded by them anyways next
caller i wonder if they're ready
ethan
[Laughter]
working that etanke
hmm
panda
[Music]
hmm
[Laughter]
it
[Music]
huh
oh
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
[Laughter]
um blue yansky you can speak english
indonesia and also
great japanese but not only language
skills you are
um you have a very clear and
heartwarming her is your strongest point
i think so um
[Music]
thank you so much
i'm very sorry everyone for for i forgot
to turn the door
off
um uh uh
i'll make sure that the next guest
doesn't experience anything like the
dumpsters
[Music]
i feel so bad
okay don't overwork eitan you are cool
thank you so much i love the cupcake
cupcake
[Music]
how's your birthday olly
man my birthday has been so good so many
people wish me a happy birthday it feels
good man
yeah nice happy birthday to you
[Music]
thank you so much
yeah thank you for inviting me too
i'm glad to i'm i'm glad to see you're
having a lot of fun
yeah
it's it's making me happy too just by
watching
oh you are watching
yeah
yes
[Music]
okay
happy birthday
to you
happy birthday to you
happy birthday
fear only
to
you
yes
[Applause]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
you live up to your name
i do
you do
like
you live up to your name i like it oh
you know it's funny i live up when i'm
actually dead
you did up
there
easy
[Music]
and then
um
you're fun to talk to
up yeah uh
i like that you're really easy to get
along with
[Laughter]
like hell yeah one brave cell let's go
let's go
apex brain rot
literally when you don't know what to
say just say apex
yeah all right
roger roger
thank you for coming
yeah thank you for inviting me as well
and have fun for the rest of the night
okay
i will thank you
thank you bye bye
bye bye
from me
our other friend the leader
mio savia
last time we uh we played together
okay
our next
[Music]
hello
hello hello
happy birthday
thank you
thank you for coming i love you mandela
okay i i just i just finished a bake a
cookie for you so so i i was running i
was running so i'm sorry for my frantic
voice but here here you go i bake a
cookie cookie i like okay
[Laughter]
it's so it's so cute it's so gimping
yeah it's skipping like us of course
like us
[Laughter]
the skipping of
this is a fringe
[Music]
uh
yeah this is this is our first time
talking to each other
yeah i guess so
hello
happy birthday oli and thank you so much
for inviting me to your party
thank you for coming
like uh like you might be wondering why
i invited you it's because uh
oh
oh right like like you're a historian
right
and and you you teach history to your
listeners i teach math and i thought
it'd be cool if i'd had a fellow teacher
with me
uh yeah yeah technically yes i am a
teacher
technically
technically on stream yeah
[Music]
hello everyone i love his story
she loves history
what other things do you love other than
history
animals
cookings bakings i don't know
also you missed the opportunity to say
oh i love ollie
of course
i love you too
i've been wanting my topic
for quite a while
oh thank you ali and yeah here i am now
thank you for inviting me so we can talk
together now
[Music]
so yay about some questions and answers
please
yes
i'm not i'm still not ready
a pop quiz for fellow teachers on them
what do you wish for ollie's birthday
my wishes
[Music]
can't hmm awesome you i love you forever
you are and please keep being awesome
you did a very great job
oh so please always be awesome
i think you didn't i guess oh i guess
i'll continue being awesome then
yay
yeah hi chad okay awesome
but listen
let's make a teacher union sometime
of course hit me ahead of time
[Music]
yeah it is
okay so
should i sing a birthday song for you
will you
[Music]
yes please
don't mind i don't mind at all the time
is yours
madam
okay thank you princess zombie princess
[Laughter]
okay one two three
happy birthday
happy birthday happy birthday
[Music]
oh
lydia our precious and awesome zombie
princess you are always
i will always love you
[Music]
i
love you too thank you so much for
coming to the colin
[Music]
lila i i
i still don't know how to say her last
name
everyone from ninja sanji id a historian
dope
yes thank you so much for coming
next up
next will be our guest
she should be coming
in a minute
is he here he's here everybody you guys
know
moss moss
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
that was my attempt to sound like crazy
ollie did you like it that i drive my
breath that was your impression of me
[Laughter]
oh yeah
hi
how you doing
i'm doing great oh what a lovely weather
we're having
yeah the weather's
real nice so
cloudy
[Laughter]
we're inside a studio though
oh oh
your studio you're still so well
decorated oh my god there's so many
proteins thank you yes
[Laughter]
happy birthday i i i have a gift for you
oh
give me
please
wait i thought about saying this but i
got embarrassed
okay i got a gift for you and the gift
is a
um
me
you're doing it
[Laughter]
[Music]
not a dork i'm very cool
a very cool dork yes very very cute
but yes the gift is me so uh yeah feel
free to take me out anytime take me one
thing with
my wording
i'm sorry
this is why i love you thank you
so um uh so um
we're kind of limited on time so i just
want to ask you a question what are your
wishes for my birthday
my wishes for for the birthday uh
hmm let me think
i
i wish
i wish ollie was mine
am i not
excuse me
or something
[Laughter]
[Music]
today but also at the same time i really
really do hope you have a great day
today and i hope this opened your eyes
to how much
everyone loves you everyone loves you
look at everybody who came look at all
the gifts you got today everybody loves
you so much please don't under
appreciate yourself and i love you so so
much and i really really do hope you
have a lovely
lovely year and then we can celebrate
another birthday
more birthdays to come
[Music]
is already waiting
okay
i'll be going then thank you so much for
inviting me i love you i love you
[Music]
let's meet up after stream
okay
bye bye
[Music]
and that has been
hanamakia from
meeting sanji id as well
all three ladies from nikki sanji id
next one is also a very very cute lady
let's meet up with her
come on
[Music]
[Laughter]
i'll send you something to fill your obs
with
the first one
[Music]
that is from
me
and from my staff
we drew it together for you because we
all love you
shut up oh
that's so cute look everyone
golden daisy oh yeah
um yeah i mean what if my staff really
uh
love your love your
oh
yeah yeah
then uh and i don't think he likes math
but
he's not handled
[Applause]
another one
made by my own mouse
my own hand it's very beautiful i'm
proud of this one
it's a mini alley
oh nominee on
[Music]
my
do not be afraid my child
it's okay what was your first impression
of ollie
my first impression
i
i i really like you like
your energy
it was
i love your streams
[Music]
i watched your first debut until the end
it was you did
yes
you often come to my streams and i'm
really grateful for that
you're welcome i really like your
content i like when you play apex i like
to see you having fun
and i hope one day we can have fun
together too
yeah let let's play more apex in the
future i must just play e6
okay
thank you for coming
thank you for inviting me i hope you
have a wonderful day
i hope you have a lot of fun today
uh
yes
i'm not good at saying words
but happy birthday thank you
i love you
i love you too step on me i mean no i
mean have have a nice day
[Laughter]
it's okay
uh mommy i'm sorry mommy i'm sorry
i'm
i'm sorry
bye bye
thank you goodbye have a nice day
uh video bear pants thank you so much
and the next is we have uh i have
someone
um i invited them but they said that
they're a bit too busy so they can't
come but they did send us a video so you
know what that means we're going to move
to another
uh what is this called again
to another overlay yeah let's go
hi
we are here
everyone ready
you guys know who it is
[Music]
i know a little english so
i'll speak to you in english
it's very powerful powerful
[Music]
today i'm going to
teach you
one japanese what that
the highest level of awesome
you know the best
[Music]
if you
like this video
try saying
han panel
[Applause]
i'm happy i'm happy
hi
i'll be
happy
if you use it
okay okay have a great day let's
collaborate again
sometimes
bye-bye
bye-bye thank you to my senpai
oh that's so sweet he he taught me a
japanese word
huh he even spoke in english that was
very very nice of him like i'm not very
good at my i'm i'm not very good like
when it comes to like japanese
yeah
i'm very very grateful that i have such
a an understanding and a hard-working
senpai thank you so much senpai
oh
[Music]
happy
present
[Music]
okay
ah
[Laughter]
yes
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
and
zombies
yay
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
no no i i know he didn't mean it in a in
a bad way but it just
it it talked me weed how did i how did
okay
[Music]
foreign
um
hmm
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
nice
foreign
um
[Music]
is
hmm
okay
foreign
did someone clip that please clip that
please clip it
i i need it
oh
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
foreign
it's
[Music]
thank you
for helping
foreign
sorry there's a lot of things in my obs
it's kind of hard to find
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
um
one day
is
five minutes five minutes
15 minutes songwriter
so don't panic
okay
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
happy birthday
to
[Music]
you
foreign
crazy
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
foreign
for you
[Music]
puppy bastard
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
just
foreign
[Laughter]
um
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
collaboration
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
i mean
[Laughter]
huh
gracie
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
hmm
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh people stay
tuned
my
happy birthday
[Music]
[Applause]
happy birthday to
you
[Applause]
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
um to be honest they were about to come
to the stream but then again it turns
out that they have another schedule and
um
they couldn't come
so they sent me a video
[Music]
i'm so happy that you and ori are
friends
i hope we can be friends forever
i'm not
getting
married
i'm not getting married
happy birthday
she says i love you but she says she's
not getting married
what
just a minute man my my obese is messed
up really bad i can't see anything wait
uh
i'll be going into the
wait
maybe maybe i should get rid of the
questions first
okay there we go
[Music]
so i had to look for everything now
like
don't get me wrong i named all of them
but i just can't
find uh
[Music]
no i i was sure that you'd come i'm just
really happy that you're here
you were
you were like even before we started
even in the pre-chat i saw and i was
like wait wait your turn isn't until
like two more hours what are you doing
oh wait wait i'm sorry i accidentally
muted you again um
i'm so sorry they didn't get here okay
it's okay it's okay it's okay don't
worry he was using the echo
thank you
i was so happy for you i'm happy that
today is your special day
oh
i'm i'm i'm kind of overwhelmed i don't
i don't know what to say i'm just ah
it's really nice to see everybody come
together to wish you happy birthday and
to give you all these nice presents i
couldn't make anything because uh uh i'm
not good at making things but but i
think everybody's saying to you in
english so maybe i could sing happy
birthday in spanish
[Music]
oh god i'm so nervous now i forgot how
to sing it
take a deep breath let it out
you're good
[Music]
um i'm honored that you asked me to be
here
well duh why would i not invite you
you're like my bestie
yeah yeah yeah i'm just really happy i
i'm just
it's it's so nice to see like uh i
remember i i watched your debut and i've
been here since the first day that you
came on and i just i'm just so
overwhelmed and overjoyed to see how
much you've grown and to see all these
people coming together to celebrate how
amazing you are because you truly are an
amazing person uh well amazing zombie
and you are a light in this world to so
many people and i just want to thank you
for being a shining light to everyone
and to me too
why are you so awesome i just want to
gobble you up
okay but maybe later
maybe later wink wink
so while we're at it let me ask you a
question
what do you think is my strongest point
mousey
oh your strongest point your strongest
point is that uh you never give up
you're very determined and you're very
uh creative that's like two points but
that's okay i can make a million points
because you have so many strong points
but i think uh your your strongest point
would have to be uh the perseverance
that you have and the fact that you just
want to make everybody smile like
when you start your stream
it's like almost as if everybody gets
all of your light energy shot into them
and it's just an electrifying event and
i'm just really uh
excited and really honored to be able to
share
that with you and to be able to witness
your glory because you're just truly an
amazing person and uh i know this is
gonna sound kind of like uh
corny
but uh i want to say uh thank you to
your uh to your mama and papa and thank
you to hello life for bringing you in
this world so that we can all be here to
experience you and to be with you on
your special day and all your days
because every day is special you know
that was corny a.m but i loved it i know
i'm sorry i have a lot of feelings
you do and
i really do
you know what they say elsie you're
you're a precious friend and i'm i just
want to let you know that i'm never
going to give you up i'm never going to
let you down i'm never going to run
around and desert you
[Music]
oh
i just want to give you a big hug
i mean me too man if if only we could
like maybe we could hug and get on the
bed and cuddle then
[Music]
maybe maybe we could maybe we could hug
an in minecraft yeah yeah yeah
minecraft
yeah yeah yeah my pencils i'm not very
good at apex
you have to teach me i could teach you
so many things oh i will anytime you're
down
anytime
i will take that open invitation
yeah thank you so much for coming mousy
thank you thank you for having me i wish
i could be here talk to you all day but
i know you have a lot of people that
want to wish you happy birthday so i'm
going to run away now
please be careful don't don't get run
over
i will i will i won't get run over i'll
run away and i'll hide in a nice little
corner so i can watch you have fun
okay take care now love you
[Music]
i over so much hi
mossy if you're in the chat please take
care i love you you're great you're
amazing
[Music]
i'll be waiting for my guest over here
hello
my sweet little white prince says hello
oh hi
birthday girl
no no birthday wife birthday wife lily i
you got it wrong you're so cute
[Music]
a gift
what the heck that is so cute wait wait
wait let
this just let me let me download real
quick so that i can tell everyone this
masterpiece
you created
hi
that is pretty putting his heart and
love into this so that you know we'll
take it
super cute
friendship is the purest love
yes is this your way of um
of a friend zoning
[Laughter]
hi happy birthday
really oh gosh well i i i you know what
that's okay because at least you still
love me
that's the most important part
yes of course nina were
anyways let me ask you a question lily
what was your very first impression of
me
is very very um already very active it's
like
hey
[Music]
[Laughter]
another first impression
sasuke or they must have been like a top
student back in when she was still alive
or something oh she's super smart
um
[Music]
wow
yeah how did you know
is it true
it is
oh because only only streams chest which
is like a very big brain
game
wait wait wait wait people people
sometimes get the wrong idea just
because i seem just doesn't mean that
i'm good at it
i don't even know what
[Laughter]
thank you for coming have a
oh i will
i'm having the greatest day now that
you're here
thank you
thank you so much for the invitation
you're welcome
jillian will give you a few papers later
to sign
for our friendship
[Laughter]
i'll be sure to burn them later
[Music]
how dare she
she's referring to the divorce papers
how dare she he's mine he's not going
anywhere we're not getting a divorce
we're going to stay married until the
end of time
mali
um
[Music]
i'm hmm happy
okay
hello
[Music]
ah
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you for sticking to the gimmick
yes of course maybe anything for you
watch much
oh my god ollie hello happy birthday for
you baby girl and
i have something for you too
pretty much i will turn it quick for you
yes it's bad but i hope you like it
nothing is bad from you apple
[Laughter]
it's not bad i i was just taken aback
gorilla gorilla gorilla pose like that
[Music]
[Laughter]
you're a very very beautiful monkey the
beautiful monkey in the universe
beautiful monkey
of course your happiness
your your your uh
what is it called
uh your life become better and better
you have great friends
more more great friends on your life
and
a lot of opportunity come to you like
like like
uh
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
yes
let's play together
[Music]
bye
literally the only one
who sticks to the gimmick
on apple i i literally wrote down a
guys please pretend like you're being
kidnapped and that you
and please scream every time i try to
close a call
ah
[\h__\h] the muscles
[Music]
huh
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
what is it
[Music]
[Applause]
night
[Music]
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
hi oh
man really it's a fun time so i couldn't
talk with her
i'm sad
this is one of the most wholesome
zombies i've ever seen and and you know
it feels good to have like a zombie
friend you know
yeah
oh the next one is not in the in the
server uh oh oh
no
oh no i also don't have
i also don't have their
png
wait wait wait wait wait wait oh no oh
no
okay
hello
happy birthday
[Music]
oh wait i'm so sorry i don't have your
pnp
oh it's okay it's okay it's like i um my
head is very big so that's all you can
see
i'm about to leave earth
she said you see me from the sky
i see you there you are
how how's the weather up
there oh it's very sunny will you be
okay
aren't you don't you like burn from this
one
i know
those are like
those are weak zombies i'm i'm a strong
man
yeah
hi do you want
do you want any souvenirs from space
before
when i come back
yes please
yes would you
like let's see what would i like uh how
it is is there any water in space
um there's quite a few water planets so
they're quite big though oh i can bring
yeah i'd i'd love to drink some um space
water that sounds amazing
oh nice nice nice i'm pretty good at
collecting space water
um
it might flood the earth but it'll be
okay
well we'll figure out we'll figure out
what to do afterwards
thank you man this is our first time
talking to each other
yes yes this is our first time talking
to each other this um my first time
talking to anyone from hollow id
actually oh
i'm your friend yes that's all right you
are my first
i'm glad oh i'm i'm sana's first whole
idea
yes
is it okay if i ask you some questions
oh yeah go ahead
oh uh
i uh have you ever seen my debut
yes it says i was watching it live
you were
i was from space
yes yes yes yes of course i would whoa
oh
[Music]
that's so sweet well i'd like to ask you
your first impression of me
very loud
you're saying the same thing orgasm i
said
um but full of energy and like so warm
and definitely definitely loved by
everyone you'll definitely be loved by
everyone and hey that proves um well
today we've seen proof of it right
you've been showered in so much love
you've been crushed under all your
presents
um yeah extend a piece of yourself to
everybody warmly
and that's so funny because you're a
zombie
you can like give a piece of you to
everyone
[Laughter]
everybody loves you because um
yeah you're so approachable
and then you just ruin it all all that
buildup of being approachable just by
asking people to play apex
oh speaking of apex
how about some epic sometimes
if it's you if it's you he can he can
teach me
yeah sometime
so that's a promise to your senpai
back from when i'm back from my planet
when i'm back on planet earth
we should definitely eat because that's
that should be the first thing on your
priority list when you come back to
earth you got an apex well what about
the water the space water that doesn't
matter anymore
are we not are we not flooding the earth
anymore
we'll we'll flood the earth with the
blood of our enemies
that sounds exciting
thank you so much sana for coming
remember when you once came to one of my
streams and you were so horrified you
talked to me in small caps
oh the
navy
that was scary like like i was like
is it scarier than a zombie okay you're
not scared at all you're adorable ah
thank you
but i think damian is pretty adorable
too
like i heard that they actually showed
it to jago
oh i do i don't have a reaction from him
but um that will be from when i come
back i'll show you when i come back okay
well thank you so much for calling it it
was it's a pleasure to meet you sana
you too thank you for inviting me i'm so
happy to be able to talk to you
and ah it isn't much ben
um i wish you i wish you a lot of love
and
happy birthday
thank you take care
thank you bye-bye bye-bye
that ladies and gentlemen was a michael
high the first goal high that i called
tonight
the next one is also a very very
precious goal hi wait wait just a minute
let me let me let me let me uh
i i gotta i i'm i'm a seven pineapple i
gotta look good and for the michael hi
hello hi
happy birthday
hello
it's very early in the morning for me
are you okay a little sleepy i'm sorry
no no no no
that's okay i'm sorry to it's kali it's
so early in the morning no it's it's the
best way to wake up in the morning oh
shush
i do have
a little gift for you
i brought this with me
i mean this myself
wait what you're kidding this is
adorable
fun
i wanted to draw you something cute for
your birthday so happy birthday birthday
thank you oh wait wait let me share with
everyone where is it i
wanna do this herself guys
how are you
yeah it got big
i sent you the full size you can exist
in all your stories
super cute thank you
um
uh
fauna may i
ask you a few questions
oh sure
tell them
i am
i'm a person who really likes to get
compliments so i'd like to ask you what
is my strongest point in your opinion
to me it is your crazy energy
i think you have so much energy and
you're so friendly and welcoming
and
just like
the essence of ollie
it's very strong
and very good
[Music]
no you really want to switch your cheeks
no you're just so precious
no you no you
precious zombie
everyone's uh typing plants versus
zombie in the
chat
maybe we should be
uh when you're doing that game you shoot
guns on each other
apex i mean
if we played apex together it would be
ant versus zombie it would wind it
sounds interesting isn't it so um ivana
i actually asked sana earlier would you
like to play apex with me
well in general i would not like to play
it is your birthday so i think that
entitles you to um
asking requests that normally would not
be fulfilled so today yes
thank you so much
you're adorable i love you mwah
thank you for inviting me happy birthday
thank you for coming take care okay
yeah you too you too
bye bye
bye bye i'm supposed to scream right ah
i'm falling
she she sucked with a gimmick
oh wait
that is so adorable wait wait where's
fawn now wait i can't find fawn anywhere
wait wait wait wait wait
but
there's still so many people that i want
to call wait where's swana like
[Music]
oh
oh oh
where's swana
wait wait wait i can't find her anywhere
lately i'm so sorry no i'm making i'm
making i'm making one of myself i'm i'm
making one of my what is it
oh here it is i'm making one of mine
go highest wait that's not that's not a
very senpai thing to do okay i'm ready
next up in the list
[Music]
hello
happy birthday
is that a valley accent
a happy birthday
ali senpai you deserve
the best
ice cream
oh oh that's not a valley accident
you're just sleepy hi
it's pretty early at your place huh
no oh no i still have no concept just
like that is not the main point the main
point is that you are the spotlight and
you are the best
zombie
[Laughter]
you're good you want me to get a glass
of water
oh i have glass of water don't worry
about it
she's actually drinking
i'm so sorry
no no i wanted to be awake for your
birthday so i set an alarm
oh so sweet
i'm i'm not really good with drawing or
anything so the least i could do is wish
you a happy birthday
thank you
should i sing a happy birthday that
would be wonderful
happy birthday
to you
happy birthday dear
ollie senpai
dear crazy ollie
a happy birthday to you
oh yay thank you
yeah
so crony i know i know you're kind of
asleep right now but can i ask you a
question maybe
oh yeah ask away
yeah so um
what was your very first impression of
me
um
when i first saw
wait uh when we first interacted or just
overall overall
overall
uh you seem very energetic and
you talk
really fast
it was quite amazing i really can't
talk that fast and
um oh i saw your
uh
weave
ring ring fit trainer yes
i saw you struggling and i thought to
myself
wow that must be a really tough guy
out of all the streams
i don't even do rings with them
oh my goodness uh thank you
oh that's that that's sweet
it's um anyways um we have
a test appointment
yes
oh and then i noticed that you seem to
be very uh
into chess and apex and
for me i really like chess and you like
chess
and i can't wait for our battle once you
are you are you better now
i'm i'm i'm
i think i don't know i'm kind of scared
oh no i never i never saw a stream of
you playing this i don't know just how
horrifying he could be on the board
i know don't worry about it what's the
worst that could happen
yeah the worst thing that could happen
is
what is it
like maybe i could start begging for you
to turn back time that's one
thing and that's good
no no no as long as
son doesn't come out oh no
oh no
you know that is the scariest move i've
ever seen in this
me too i actually want to see it in
action one day yeah
i can't wait our battle will be glorious
it will be
thank you for
waking up for me cronie
of course
of course i would wake up for you
any time
and
time has no concept of anything besides
time
i can wake up any time
i don't sleep
thank you so much for coming
yeah
happy birthday once again and
everyone please
love our
uh crazy and sweet zombie senpai
and
across me um
i'm going to do it with dubai
happy birthday
bye take it
next guest is here hello hello
hello
what's up
oh oh wait the wrong person what's up
happy birthday
thank you they bae i was
i i suddenly got a dm from rainey while
i was setting up my obs she was like hey
i'm going to be
your um
i'm going to be your uber
turkey
and i'm going to send you something from
a certain someone i was like
what
you mean
you yourself and she's like nah you got
a present
all the way
from upside down world
you little
sweet
thank you by the way happy birthday it
really it
it encompasses
um your birthday with me yes
[Music]
i'm sorry about the drawing i i can't i
i drew with a mouse i drew with mr
squeaks
but mr squeak
no this is adorable guys look at this
little masterpiece oh
and with with a with a strawberry
cheesecake and donuts
yay
they got me
a cake and and donuts and rainy senses
[Music]
i had this thought literally 24 hours
ago and i was like
let's just do it
this
this zombie spoils everyone with her
kindness with you know her incredible
energy and
oh yes
she needs to be spoiled too you're nice
so
no no wait bae
but
i'm
i am a zombie i'm already i'm already
spoiled i'm rotten
i'm i'm spoiled already
well he is more to add to
this
spoiledness
who doesn't like spoiled cake amazing
[Music]
thank you i did man everyone is just so
sweet you especially man you you took me
by surprise i still can't believe that
you sent me hey man the strawberry pig
died
yeah i somehow knew that you liked
strawberry and then i checked and i was
like oh yeah she likes strawberry meals
i had a i had a feeling i had a feeling
it is
we asked the fellow chaos crazy unity
so okay let me ask you a question
okay
i am
i am a
spoiled little zombie and i like
compliments so i'd like to know
what is my strongest point in your
opinion
oh
definitely
well i kind of said it but definitely
ali is just
so nice she's just so kind to people and
i also feel like your other strong point
is your perseverance you have such an
enthusiasm for you know what you do and
i feel like that's really infectious and
i'm sure a lot of people draw
inspiration from you and i definitely do
so
thank you for everything that you do
that really is
you know
it's really amazing
no
man why is your birthday on the 29th of
february
why not why
but like we won't be getting it until
another three
[Music]
do got time years outside just saying
you're right
you're absolutely right
looking forward to it then you better be
ready
oh no oh no
thank you thank you for coming i will
take it easy though i'm sure birthday is
also very stressful even though it's
very exciting so please make sure you
take care of yourself
i will thank you
[Music]
like did you guys i i i still can't
grasp why she's actually chaos how is
she chaos when she's this that hold them
doesn't make sense
yes
good morning
hello
hi where am i
you forgot
i i just woke up
hello
[Music]
hello it's your birthday you remember
oh i i could not forget that hello happy
birthday hello thank you and nice to
meet you hello yeah hi nice to meet you
you're the first person i'm meeting out
of ian i'm nervous hello which really
yeah
score another one on the list everyone
[Music]
i have hey i have a gift for you i made
it before i went to bed oh oh once one
second i'm gonna get it for you
i hope it's okay i had trouble with your
hair
so i replaced it with other things to
make it a little easier
[Music]
it's adorable
let me say that it looks like
is that olives or is it grapes or is it
oh berries actually
i i figured
oh i don't know i wasn't sure if you
were oh i see
yeah
yeah it's just so i i thought it would
fit with the the sword thing too you
know ah
you see you have you're like very known
to
i think they're pretty nice yeah
well i love you very much
oh gosh
thank you
i i think you're very very cool
thank you so much
um
um is it okay if i ask you a question
yeah
yeah so um do you have any wishes for me
on my birthday
what what do you wish for no i won't ask
you i want i wish i wish that you get
what you wish for
and
i i just woke up but i think you've been
going for quite a while and you seem to
have a lot more to go so i also hope you
rest very well
and have lots of fun on your birthday i
certainly will
yay
yes all i could wish for for you and i
wish we i would this is maybe my own
wish i wish we talked more too nice to
meet you hi
nice to meet you hi so have we added
each other on discord actually
yeah
yeah i'm going to spam you with messages
if you don't mind
of course please do i'm very scared to
message anybody
[Music]
and maybe you know we could your collab
pen is over so maybe we could also
collab
yeah
yeah yes please i'll play anything
apex
okay you so much for coming earlier man
thanks for having me i am honored to be
here happy birthday
thank you have a have a wonderful day
thank you
i'm so excited thank you
bye bye
goodbye
[Music]
okay
happy birthday
[Music]
thank you thank you
i was really surprised you literally
have a lot of friends
[Music]
yeah we are friends we are friends
sisters
yeah
yeah you already received so many
birthday gifts is there enough space for
mine oh
i
[Applause]
[Music]
he
oh
[Music]
hmm
for everyone so many friends are
celebrating your birthday
[Music]
me too
thank you
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you
[Music]
thank you bye-bye
wow
[Music]
hi nephew
i need you
no no no hi
i'm what this is in real life friend but
no doubt absolutely definitely
neighbourhood
yay
yeah
i'm so happy to be able to talk to you
on this special day
thank you
i loved wonderful english culture and
chess from you you're a great teacher or
a gto
yeah
don't do too much okay i have a present
for you presents yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
me as a brave man
very brave i am very proud of you
[Laughter]
i adore you this illustration with image
of a cute door
ah i hope you like it
you know
i i like it a lot thank you
thank you
[Music]
are very very energetic yes
yeah
but not not only not only in general
zombie bodies are cold
but
you have a warm heart that cares for
someone
and that warm heart is also compared to
your viewers
yeah your kindness viewers
yeah
all right
[Music]
thank you for always playing with me
what
is it
um
[Laughter]
that has been
this stuff
foreign
hi
[Laughter]
[Music]
uh
um
[Laughter]
foreign
that has been
[Music]
it was funny how he was actually
very what is it hot it was nervous
he wasn't that nervous when we were
playing apex like every time he gets
killed he's like nice good
nice kid
um
you guess who's next
can you guys see this next
hello
hi can you hear me i can are you in the
bathroom right now
no i am yeah
beautiful time to call how are you doing
[Laughter]
what
what what's timing
i'm doing great how are you
i'm good happy birthday by the way thank
you
i've seen you've had like a million
guests on
no it's only like what 30. it's only 30
people only three
you've got more than the hunger games
but anyways let's not talk about that
let's talk about
my birthday
i know i feel woefully unprepared
everyone else brought you a birthday
present
a terrible friend
no you're not don't say that
yeah
i'll get one that's amazing next time
next time okay how about you get me to a
diamond in apex
happy something you know um
i'm pretty sure
dreams are meant to be hard to achieve
um that is one that is uh very difficult
um
maybe you can ask an apex predator to
help you out
well that is that that is true
one day one day one day anyways connor i
have a question for you
okay
so um
what do you think is my strongest point
connor
i thought about this question a lot
i think
i think as a voice actor i admire a lot
that somehow your throat
is able to keep up with how much you
scream i don't understand how that
happens i don't scream that much
you don't what are you serious
i don't
i i think there needs to be like a ton
of exes in your chat right now um that
is
you you are you scream more than anyone
i know
you lie it has not true right chad
good
they're calling you a bathroom va right
now
the echo must make me sound godly
you sound gnarly that's okay
i'm sorry i want to fire it
so yeah um
i'm sorry to bother you when you're
doing such an important business i'm i'm
just so so so busy right now on in the
bathroom but what is your next question
ollie what is my next question let's see
um
[Music]
oh do you have
like any expectations for me like do you
have any wishes for me on my birthday
i guess other than you getting to
diamond and apex
i want to see you become
a giant chess next that's my that's my
wish
dms yes well we'll have to call anna
back
yeah i need we need a gmall gm kroger
that's an arc that i can get behind like
like he imagined a tournament and
they're like damn ali steps up
when's the world
i think you can do it and then the
viewers can see your your progress from
day one to year
it's funny how you're very optimistic
about me turning into a dm but like i'm
in a gm but you're kind of pessimistic
about me getting a diamond in apex
well i i think you know maybe sometimes
you panic a little too much from gaming
you know maybe that that is true
but i mean you are good at apex though
you've gotten a lot better when i first
started playing with you you were you
were not rich
it's okay it's okay he can say it out
loud it's okay but i wasn't very good i
know when i started so
thank you for being on connor
oh no it was a pleasure i'm sorry i wish
i could have prepared more but thank you
so much for having me
yeah
i hope you have an amazing birthday and
i'll have a great time with the rest of
your guests
thank you
all right well i'll leave you to it all
right molly thanks for having me bye and
thank you for coming
bye
and there goes connor sea dog va
everybody
in the next on the list we have
another friend from a different part of
the world can you guys guess who
i just don't want to wait wait
let me prepare for a sec just just a
minute
hi wait wait
where did i put them oh here it is
yo
yay
oh you remembered how to say it
yeah
that means merry christmas right wow
you're so smart moon
thank you thank you
so i have a
two birthday present today you have
yes
so first one is picture i saw your
stream today so everyone just give you
the the drawing the
picture thing so
i think i thought just
you know
drawing the picture and give you so i
just
write
in when you're streaming
i'm starting to question your aesthetics
moon i i
why is beautiful
beautiful if you see it from mars
no no thank you
it's a wonderful wait let me let me show
everyone the masterpiece that you
brought upon this world
yeah
wow so beautiful it looks just like yeah
guys so beautiful oh my god i proud
myself
you can't tell us apart
wow
thank you guys thank you thank you
[Music]
everyone can buy that like
ten thousand dollars something
this is ten thousand dollars
yeah
wow
okay so
you need to ask to me right
yes a question so so moon
i'm ready
i am a great friend don't you think so
ah
right yeah right so i want to ask you
what is my strongest point
your point
ah
you have so many points so but the best
is the
tension you know
when i just first collaboration when i
see the first time i just told oh when i
just
uh
first
talking with you
i just
think
oh
this weekend nice collaboration
hell yeah
so another is a one question on this
only
you want more questions okay another
question uh what are your wishes for me
on my birthday
wish wish uh
i just um
i just wanna just you just keep going
you know just like streaming good
streaming that's all
that's i wish to you
and be my
uh still be my friends you know it's
weird
[Music]
[Laughter]
that
okay as a last thing
i have the
good one so can i screen share
are you on the screens here oh yeah yeah
yeah
oh wait just a minute
thank you okay so
yeah yeah so
anywhere so what i do uh just i'm just
making meme
so
this time
uh i just
i just make meme
uh off yours
oh okay uh
not yet
oh wait
oh please please oh come on
come on i'm so sorry it's taking quite a
while
my obs is filled with a lot of stuff
that is kind of lagging i'm so sorry oh
oh oh
i'm sorry oh i didn't know that no no no
no no it's fine
um
and
this
and then this okay i think we're ready
okay okay okay
just a minute let me transition real
quick
um
sorry guys it's taking quite a while obs
is a pretty heavy
oh my god
oh no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no
[Laughter]
oh wait no that's that's not um
ah
wait
why must you do this to me obvious
or i can or i can give some video later
or something yeah that would be nice
yeah
sorry about that i but it's kind of
really
cool meme so
after the stream or something i just
showed my
um twitter or something okay thank you
i'm sorry about it yeah guys
i swear i swear but then obvious just
decides to f up on me i'm so sorry
there was nothing
i didn't see anything right like nothing
but me
that was
that was something hopefully we don't
have to cut that out because this is a
very long stream i'm very sorry moon for
this i don't think we can see yeah it's
okay yeah nice it's nice really nice no
no problem
anyway salama ulang town only thank you
man i want to see like he had a vr chat
and everything
it was like you guys didn't see my
servers or anything right
you guys just saw my chap and moon
that's okay if you guys only saw my chat
with me it's all good
wait who's next like one day
oh wait moon is still here i need i need
a simon
okay sorry obviously very heavy
next is
hello
[Music]
wait wait let me let me show you guys on
screen i'm so sorry
it's completely fine you have a lot of
fan out on the screen i think
quite a lot
yes
hello
it's been so hard
yeah
thank you very much for inviting us on
and thank you thank you for coming
hi how are you guys
i am good
yes
how's your birthday so far my birthday
has been fun it's been wonderful and it
got even more wonderful with you guys
here
you feel like my gift for you i did wait
let's show everyone your gift
she spent all day yesterday
she did
no don't say that
you knew wait wait wait wait wait let's
let's show it to everyone shall we boom
is so cute
thank you
oh
despise or something
i love
crying
thank you
i'm glad you like it
i'm so excited i love it
i'm so excited thank you very excited to
be on thank you for inviting us
thank you
so guys man when was last time we talked
on the on the on the dog a dog talk show
the talking house
so much time ago
thank you for coming on then
yeah it was my biggest
i miss you too
i have to buy a new ring for you
very soon
that'd be so wonderful yes oh
can i ask you guys a question
yeah absolutely yeah yeah
what was your very first impression of
me guys
i shall let unique go fast
i go first okay so
when i saw your first your design for
the very first time i was so shocked
like i have never seen a zombie girl
but
to be honest i immediately fell in love
with you
oh no
you're my wife yes oh thanks
we don't want to third wheel you but
we're wives though
sorry well she has a lot of wives are
surprising about him
a rather large amount
you get used to it
i hear you only
yeah
my first impression was that you were
incredibly nice and welcoming to
everyone and i was very surprised to
hear when i followed you and you
followed me back that you actually had
read one of my comics which was very
nice one of your comics man i followed
almost every single
one of your comics seriously
how do you have time to do that on top
of streaming
uh it takes quite a lot of a lot of
effort yeah
i can imagine
well thank you very much
and your streams are always so
entertaining and i i've your design
especially is quite nice it's uh it's
it's it's lovely it's very unique i'd
say especially the sword i love the
sword the sword you like the
love the sword if i throw my sword will
you guys go run for it
you guys adorable i love you
guys no you thank you for inviting me
and mary
thank you
bye
you're you're most welcome let's play
again soon
yes please whenever you want sure
and there we go
until then my friend
ah
is it goodbye
is it not goodbye
and let's talk a little bit more let's
how about i ask you guys one more
question hmm
yes
yes what do you guys think is my
strongest point
compliment me hmm
i shall let juni go fast
oh no funny okay uh
my my
my opinion is i i feel like
your strongest point is your energy
every single time i watch your stream i
feel so energetic as well and also
your your source stuck in in your hand
[Laughter]
you guys really like my sword wow
i think it's very powerful yeah yes
i would say that your strongest point in
my opinion is in fact your very very
powerful voice
during our stream together at one point
you screamed so loudly in an attempt to
express how excited you were over apex
legends that the discord force muted you
they did didn't they
that happened
i have never let i have never had that
happen with any person
ever
no matter how loud they were only you
which just goes to show a testament to
your voice's power so yes
woof wow yes right
i wanna i wanna join your club chris i i
kind of wanna be a dog too now
can you back with us zombie dog
i love it
i love it it should be a thing
ollie i wish you a very happy day it is
clear that many people really care for
you considering how many other people
are coming and going constantly you
deserve nothing but a very good and fun
birthday ali
thank you
have a very nice birthday ollie thank
you
thank you for having
me and thank you for coming please take
care
i love you bye bye bye i love you
yep
that ass three person who sticks to the
gimmick
next on our list yes we're still going
everyone
a very very lovely
yes
um
has hope descended
iris
and hope this is coming for you
man
that gets me every time every time you
say hope is coming for you that gets me
i can feel it in my bones
[Laughter]
oh and there's nothing to be afraid of
it's just hope it's just how
hope yes and you need a lot of hope for
your birthday obviously right because
it's a great
day
[Music]
i i drew you something i drew you
something beautiful absolute masterpiece
where is it i promise
thee
absolute masterpiece
i i um
like
wait i'm going
let me you have do you have anything to
say
i love this santa hat
yeah merry christmas everybody
no i mean you know you seem to really
really like to push the santa
especially in minecraft yeah i think oh
yeah i haven't i haven't mentioned but
thank you so much for that second round
of surprises you you know prepared for
me
in my lovely abode
the other day i i haven't seen actually
haven't seen your reaction i mean
[Laughter]
oh it was it was it was a shocker yeah
surprise a very nice wonderful wonderful
surprise yes
with a bunch of signs and a bunch of
uh
leather armor yes glitter armor yeah
did you like the signs
oh yes yes
i i loved it you know never
never gonna let you down either ollie
yeah
that just goes to show that i
i constantly remember you like you're
always in my mind
oh really
always in your mind all
aliens in your mind
i'm really happy to hear that it's
flattering absolutely flattering i hope
i'm in your mind in a very positive
light yes
of course you would hope after all my
dear mm-hmm uh-huh yes of course
so iris time for some questions you're
ready yeah
i'm absolutely
ready ready
so
what was your very first impression of
me
ah first impression
ah
just so energetic
and like
you can
basically make anyone your friend like
you're just you you oh my god you're
just so friendly like you you can always
make the first action and especially
like you know you can you can propose to
someone on twitter on their very first
twitter conversation
to everyone you have so many rings
opposed to people
uh i'm sure you're not using the same
ring right
of course not i'm filthy rich i'm ready
to have
as many as life as possible yes yes i'm
sure you have a treasure load of those
proposal rings
to every single one
of those you know lovely lovely people
that you propose to yes
including one yes
exactly
also um iris we have a very delayed apex
collapse
oh yeah
oh yes we do
like we keep on saying to each other oh
my god we should apex yeah i'll be your
first ever apex but it never came to be
yeah oh my god we really do need to do
apex though we did get champion ones
with with eofy too and we did oh yeah
we did do it we did we did we did do
like a three-way
yeah a three-way apex collab so if you
if you to you know um play apex with me
you know alone with hope alone
i'm i'm i'm down anytime
let's go
yes everybody give it up for iris
yes i'll get champion for you just for
you another birthday present for me for
just for you yes thank you
[Applause]
but yes i hope you have a great
great birthday
yes with lots of
cake lots of soda did you notice there
was a cherry on that cake
there was wait let me let let's zoom in
there's not a strawberry they're
strawberry it's strawberry filling in
the middle but but at the top there's a
there's a tiny little cherry on it
i i love how flirty you are
oh
you have a fabulous zombie day
i'm sorry sorry for the for the scuff on
that but
everything else is is filled with love
yes
it's wonderful
thank you yes i'm i i really feel
the appreciation
appreciation in your tone
i know that i i really like it thank you
so much
no no thank you thank you so much for
inviting me
i'm really glad to be here
and yeah like there's so many people so
many people in line to to wish you happy
birthday seems like all those proposals
are working
they are aren't they it's amazing
yes
what
i hope you have a wonderful day iris
yes i will i just had i just went to the
dentist and my top uh lip is is
is numb right now so i'm glad that i
might i'm not am i not talking weirdly
i'm okay no you're you're you're
actually talking really nicely i'm
surprised you actually went to this
dentist yeah yeah my teeth was hurting
and i went to the dentist they gave me
the numb shot and i'm just like am i i
can't feel my top lips i'm just like oh
i might sound
on the stream
yes yes
awesome
okay but yes i should probably be going
since you still have more people in line
yes
yeah well we'll talk again soon okay yes
let's do that apex yes yeah
and teach me chess by the way i will
definitely you've been going on a lot of
test dates
you know i didn't i didn't
yeah accidental test dates yeah i didn't
expect chess to be there but it just
happened to be there and i now know that
it's important to have chess skills
especially losing to bae was
very
very um
clear
yes teach me
i will that's a promise
okay but have a wonderful birthday eat
lots of cake drink lots of soda i will
yes
for my share too especially since i have
a uh ouchie teeth now virus fires bye
bye
and there she goes
hope has ascended once again
next man i really after after these two
calls i might have to go to the bathroom
or can i go to the bathroom right now
real quick i'm so sorry wait i need to
stay sorry first i'm
[Music]
bathroom break
sorry guys just a minute
i can't hold it anymore
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
that was a lot of pee
quite a lot
man
i'm back everyone okay it is time to
commence the next yes let's call them in
up
i've been tired everyone
hey
yes let's wait a little bit
so hmm
i think they're coming
they're coming everyone
up hello
hi
[Music]
oh
give you a present but hey happy
birthday
[Music]
he didn't only target
oh
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
i'm in danger
[Music]
[Laughter]
a
oh
me
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
oh
[Music]
foreign
yay
[Music]
[Laughter]
huh
[Music]
is
um
[Music]
bye-bye
maybe i'll do this while i snack a
little
i don't eat anything really
i ate something uh i i ate uh i ate
lunch but it was like at 11 a.m
if you guys don't mind i'm going to
snack on a pie
um
[Music]
special guest because we'll see it later
oh
i mean
[Music]
i like pie
okay
hello
hello crazy over here
[Music]
hi
thank you thank you
a special day
for our wobblies on week aways we only
how was your place
wow are we
have been going fine
it was really really nice everyone was
really really really nice
that's good to hear
yes i have something for you oh you do
i also have something for you
cute wait
mine is cool as well mine is cute as
well just wait for it
mine is cute too
i also have
i i believe i believe
that's cute
[Music]
[Laughter]
let me show everyone everyone
this is the
the one from rainey boom
oh cute and this is from anya boom oh so
cute
[Laughter]
picnic
[Music]
did you enjoy follow me
i did actually not not yet but i'm
eating the other snacks that you gave me
oh
no so uh today rainey not only did she
become
uber turkey for a base cake but she also
sent me a whole lot of snacks like
it's live
i'm opening one right now
snacking
nice
which one i'm eating the the pies and
also the
the sticks
the spice
the i'm eating
[Music]
pie um why were you on it
it was i on eagle
uh yeah there was a reverb
oh
rainy just sending stuff she can't eat
anymore
like this really spicy holo me which i
really really like
yeah yeah like i know you like that one
so oh i wish that were me like i don't
even i don't even eat follow me lately
oh you want me to spend your holidays
myself i will send you some halloumi
that is despair how are you not eating
halloween
yeah i don't know
i don't know both of us are on the whole
on me detox yeah
and i'm slowly i'm slowly losing my
identity
i know
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes
[Music]
[Laughter]
what
thank you so much for your gift guys so
um i kind of don't want to use the
question deck on you guys i'm just going
to ask uh how's your day so
wait wait wait what
how's your day so far like i've been
streaming for five hours i know i i
haven't checked on anyone yet
oh
um
me um i had i had a dvd collect before
this and it was so much fun oh
all right both of you right
yeah both of us what's that
dvd column yeah it was so much fun it
was my first time doing custom
[Music]
is
if we were put into the format i would
be the one who'd constantly abuse the
emojis like i would use all different
kinds of emojis just to say good morning
anya would be a simple good morning well
renee would be that type that says
them
[Laughter]
always becomes like this at this hour i
know it's like at this hour
yeah this hour you always become like
this i'm slowly getting used to it
who are you talking about
you
me
yeah you
saw it
[Music]
please do you see what i'm talking about
anyway what i'm talking about i hope you
are having a very great birthday huh
i'm having a
blast yeah
yeah
we can't wait until you know we can play
what what time is it
good
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh yeah i love your cover by the way oh
thank you
[Laughter]
okay
okay see you guys all right okay
bye bye bye
fun good luck thank you
hello
man you know talking with them is so fun
and uh
i lost my track of time sometimes
now we're going to move on
this one this person is the last one
last one and then we'll be watching a
few more videos
okay and then i'm going to get ready
this is a very unexpected guess i i bet
you guys wouldn't know
you guys would not expect it
hello
hi
how are you i'm good how are you
i'm good how are you happy birthday
thank you thank you and and thanks for
accepting my invitation
no no i'm sorry i uh sorrow's a bit late
i i mean like a i feel a lot of pressure
because you said i was the last one and
i was like oh god
i have i hope i'm okay for that no no
you're fine everyone's happy look
everyone's everyone's saying joey
everyone's greeting you
hello
so yeah um
this is our first call i believe
yeah i think so i think so i i harass
you a lot in your chat
i'm probably calling you yeah
yeah
i think thank you for coming to my
dreams like uh
he surprised me a lot
and i surprised you yeah it still feels
surreal for me to be talking with you
that's all good it's all good i i like
supporting people i like so ah
i have a question for you if you don't
mind
of course
so um what was your first impression of
me
first impression of you
well i i i saw you and i was like oh
that's a
that's an adorable little zombie goal
and then i watched streams and i was
like oh it's it's an adorable
loud zombie gun
loud
emphasis
yeah like loud in like like bold letters
underlined like three times wow
loud
yeah
yeah but i don't know like i don't know
i saw you playing a bunch of games and i
was like oh man you you know she plays
games like she's really having fun and
you know that's that's fun to watch so
that's why i keep coming back yeah
[Music]
first time i am
oh when was the first time you came to
my stream
first time came to your stream
donation reading
yeah that's the one where you like broke
down crying or something
that happened
yeah but when i got clipped like crazy i
was like oh i just said hi i'm like i
didn't mean to make you cry i felt so
i mean
wouldn't anything i don't know if you
actually cried but all the clips were
like
ollie cries over joey i'm like oh what
i didn't mean to do that i said hi
um
the clips are showing the truth billy
that happened
okay well
sorry they don't need to be i was crying
tears of happiness
okay okay i'm glad
i never thought me saying hi would you
know
make someone burst into tears but you
know what i'll take that
it's a it's a trait it's a unique treat
uh so i don't really have like a
physical present for you
but um i hope i'm the first one to give
you a present like this
uh
when
and not if when
you come to japan
uh i will
treat you out to a dinner of your choice
you're kidding
no you're sick
wait i'm actually a big eater you sure
yeah yeah
anything you want like when and and when
not if when you come to japan
i'll take you out wherever you want
one time
one time and you'll take aki with me so
that you can wang you won't get her and
do your weird stuff
man
zoey you are the man you should know
that
a dinner and donkey
man here you're spoiling me you're right
in here
yeah so wherever you want to go well you
me and aki three of us will go out
and go eat somewhere
sounds
so good i'll look forward please please
wait until i get to japan i'll be sure
to contact you guys
and i will you know let's let's play
like i i know i've been uh asking you to
play eve until like i i never really
give you any
sure yeah right
yeah i feel like i feel like we're in
due time to hang out on stream sometime
like play games together something i
don't know just just hang out yeah
yeah so whenev whenever whenever you're
okay with that i'm i'm i'm down whenever
so just let me know thank you
i'm just happy
that you became the last person that i
called
oh thank you i felt a lot of pressure
but i'm i'm glad i could make you happy
this is this is my first like totsamachi
of like any kind so it's like
yeah it's it's weird is this is this how
you're supposed to do it yes it is
you're doing great don't worry okay okay
cool cool i'll take that
all right awesome well i i hope you've
had a lovely birthday you too have a
wonderful day
i will oh i'm about to go to sleep
actually
a wonderful day i'll have a wonderful
sleep yeah
yeah
all right um yeah happy birthday and uh
i'll uh i'll talk to you soon i guess
talk to you soon yeah
yeah all right bye-bye bye
zoey the enemy man the last person
that we called now next up we'll be
watching some videos like um
i put them last
because they are special
yes
so we watch rin and mustang by lumi ah
we have
two videos before we end the stream
you guys ready
okay
three
two
one happy birthday
happy birthday
thank you something
you did close your eyes
yeah
it's a
it's a delicious fruit
fresh from my garden
it's a fruit oh
young young
young
senpai i i don't think that's it
perfectly in your mouth wow
if she says it's the fruit
everywhere
yeah i'll take a bite yeah take a bite
ah
actually you know what it's your
birthday
happy birthday ollie i if you have a
fantastic day
and i hope you eat lots of cake and
stuff like that birthday stuff
what do zombies do for their birthday
zombies
we release a cover
we do thoughts
no no no we don't do that pancake oh
regardless happy birthday
happy happy birthday
thank you
she's adorable
she sounds sleep deprived well she she
is a busy woman
a very very busy woman that's why she
can't come to the totsumachi
way
way too busy and she's uh overworking
herself
that's what i believe
so
it makes sense but you know this video
is just so cute
yeah thank you so much for sending and
last but not least
it's the fruit
the fruit indeed
last one you guys know who it is
[Music]
a happy birthday
i i did i got best girl
and then i i wonder if you can hear it
here i'll stay silent and i want you
guys to listen carefully okay
breathing heavily
did you guys hear it
was recording yago
and you know uh the the reason why she
was out of breath was because she was
laughing because yago took so many takes
just to send me a happy birthday because
he says it's a little bit too
embarrassing
to say it out loud
here's some bloopers
[Laughter]
i mean
it is cute best girl a best girl
i have yago and emchan with me
yes wanna see it again
[Laughter]
best girl is being so shy
and bloopers yeah so we have this
like like did you see the yaga was
actually holding back his laughter like
[Laughter]
like it was
earth and not to laugh because they've
been i heard that this took like six
takes just for him to wish me a happy
birthday
[Laughter]
yes this is diamond you're welcome
she loves it so much
when else are you getting a birthday
wish from yagos
this is a rare footage of best girl
so yeah that is everyone
to be honest uh
i invited a lot more people
back to the totsumachi stage
hi
i'm going to uh
sorry everyone
off so that i can talk properly to
everyone there's there's quite a lot of
things here
i don't wanna
put them away just for a little bit so
that i can talk with you guys
is a lot
not gonna lie this is this is quite a
lot
light i must say
um
yeah this is a lot
but but that makes me really happy
because everyone is thinking about me
and everyone gave me presents
i can't find it my obvious is all
vocabulary
[Music]
that was everyone can i get a handful of
clap please
thank you yeah it was a five hours and
20 minutes and it was really really fun
having everyone giving me a happy
birthday means a lot and not only for my
friends but also from you guys having
you guys here was a blast
i hope you guys enjoyed the kotsumati
we'll definitely do it again next year
and i will be sure to invite a whole lot
people
there's actually quite a lot of people
that i actually invited but they're like
sorry we can't come because um we're
busy or sorry
i'm kind of
under the weather right now so i can't
come
for example uh i'm sure you guys noticed
i invite
almost the whole holostars the only one
who didn't come was easily senpai that
was because he was sick
and he couldn't come
he actually came to the countdown stream
which is very very nice of him even
though he's really sticky so me time
comment
and uh i wanted to invite the whole
hello uh whole life members too like the
others
but my managers were like ollie this is
already a lot of people you won't have
time you're planning on doing this and
that and this and that so you can't do
that
yep even sarah sarah sarah
but what if
what if i actually
i kind of don't want to and what if i
open a totsumati
for the whole members i don't think
they'll see you though
we'll just open it until i end the
stream so before we end the stream i
want to remind you guys once again about
oh my goodness where is it
oh here it is found it
just want to remind you guys again that
the ollie birthday merchandise is up you
guys can get it to the link in the
description below or by the
there's going to be four different
special voices voiced by yours truly
all in id en and jp
mama
you know
come on
everyone calm down
foreign
mama
hello
[Laughter]
oh
[Applause]
nice to meet you my name is
to meet you
yes
[Music]
mama
thank you
sounds okay
[Music]
foreign
some people didn't come
um
hmm
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
and thank you for always supporting gory
and please continue to suffer
oh don't cry
[Music]
um
kindness
genius hyper cutie
strong zombie idol
danny
[Music]
ultimate cuteness kind of
genius
[Laughter]
um
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
my
crazy
[Music]
everyone that was my mother my loving
loving mother
and just because
mama is a dude does not make ma la mama
less of a mother
i'm so happy because you know my mama is
always continuously supporting me behind
the scenes like the llama man is always
on the comments sometimes when well
sometimes when i'm streaming and
something goes wrong like let let's say
that i'm muted like llama would dm me on
the squad and say hey
you're muted
you gotta unmute yourself
mommy is always looking out for me and
and you know i never asked for a present
from mama ma but here i am but with with
this with such a wonderful illustration
also the
the the merchandise was also made by
llama
oh man if if if i were to round about
llama i could go on forever
forever um
dude
where a woman i'm a minister
yes
wait wait where's where's the picture
that mama uh sends me i want to show it
on stream i wanna you know what i'm
going to make in my profile picture
later
this is the best
birthday gift that i could ever
get
best mama ever you
we're going to end it on this note you
know what i'm going i'm just going to do
this
in honor of llama my mama isn't dead but
like like i'm just i just wanna wanna
show you guys
my mom is the best
hi
thank you so much everyone for coming to
the stream
later i'll be having a collaboration
with rainey and anya it's pretty late so
i i wouldn't i i wouldn't recommend you
guys to go to my stream after um five
hours and what almost 40 minutes
it's really late i hope you guys can
rest up after this i'm going to wrestle
have some dinner then maybe uh play with
anya and rainy after this nick
it was a really really fun birthday
again i want to thank everyone again for
all of the love support
and for all of the birthday wishes and
the comments and chat and twitter
and in in
youtube communities and and other social
medias i i thank you all so much there's
so many presents that i got
and i am planning on doing a presence
opening stream somewhere uh tomorrow
sometime tomorrow
please look forward to it
yeah i'll be sure that i'll be reviewing
each and every one of them
yeah having llama and the stream
it's the best
it is like the best way possible for me
to end the stream
thank you so much everyone i hope you
guys had fun
thank you so much for wishing me happy
birthday i certainly did have a
wonderful birthday i'll i'll still check
out the gifts
the hashtags and everything else so i
hope
guys
oh i'm getting brain dead i don't know
what to say but anyways seriously thank
you from the bottom of my heart i love
you all so much i wouldn't be here
without all of you
and i'm glad that i got to celebrate my
birthday with so many people
including you guys
this has been crazy
thank you so much for coming
[Music]
bye
you