[Music]
a
n
[Music]
PA
n
[Music]
a
n
[Music]
a
the
[Music]
n
a oh my God
sorry I'm so
full I'm so full
Chate wasn't even that much but I was
like I was stop I was I was pushing it
in so that I could yeah I'm stuffed I
was stuffing it in stuffed
Phoenix so that I could be done
faster okay chat is there
wa
Ah Ah that's uh not not not uh such your
comfortable feeling stuffing yourself
really
fast
but my application has been sent in what
did you eat crispy
chicken crispy chickens are pretty small
anyway
but let me open the COC Cola zero that
came with
it I like how they don't deliver the
like normal cup containers anymore but
just the bottles like the plastic
bottles because that way I can like also
decide to just drink it on a different
day if I don't want it right
away
genius ah
okay W I'm a bit like like
um how to
say brain brain needs to calm down first
because I I don't know I was trying to
do everything really fast I I
underestimated uh by the way talking
about your origion song contest
application I underestimated even though
I did it last year I forgot how how many
questions there are once you are in the
real application cuz first you send in
just like really basic stuff then they
send you an email to like to to go to
the actual application process and
there's a lot more fill out then it
first looks
like yeah like over stimulated
like writing fast trying to get it fast
done before the
stream I don't even know what I was what
I wrote last
year um but this year I I made sure to
also explain in my application how we
could possibly do it because after
talking to the the Austrian
representation people seems like that is
their first
concern so I was like okay let's let's
explain all the ways that we could do
it a bit early to think about stage um
presentation for normal applications but
I am not a normal
applicant as we all know
eh it was in the thumbnail what
what oh oh the stream wasn't starting
well sometimes that happens
yeah sometimes always make sure to to
reload refresh abnormal that's me I am
abnormal but I always think like why
turn someone immediately down ask
questions ask questions if you need more
answers ask more question
questions uh this PS5 screen yeah my
PS5 yeah let's
go
[Laughter]
a always rely on red yelling let's go
and then red says anytime I say let's go
that's when the stream
starts seems like there's a somebody who
announces the stream start in the
chat
[Music]
what's 200 million
in in Japanese numbers Japanese numbers
always confuse me so much I always have
to think about it what the conversion is
I mean if numbers are still numbers it's
not like you know a currency but the the
way they um number the
numbers it's
confusing uh
[Music]
no no no
no
huh wa I'm so
confused it's it's 6 + 4 wait 200 no 6 +
uh a million is a million
is
man I
can't two I mean two million is but
let's say one million 1 million wait 1
1,000 is uh
e
uh uh 10,000 is
ichim 100,000 is n man a a million is
niak man
so
[Music]
uhak NIU or niak no but it's not Haku
it's it's more than it's more than 1
million it's 200 million
so
M if but if OK is a
million then I guess no wait I no wait
oku is fine oku is 100 million yeah yeah
okay okay
okay so yeah okay yeah
yeah brain brain
H the biggest freaking event in in
Austria H Europe being led by 200
million people at least like I mean it's
probably still growing who
knows okay enough of
that I was trying to charge my
controller um by just uh connecting it
with a shitty cable to the PC but it
didn't work it didn't charge it all so
now I'm just connecting it to the
PlayStation and hoping it will catch up
and charge ing
uh you guys hear the audio right I might
have to turn it up or down again
who oh the screen is so so
fancy let's do
it I I I I I am excited to play
more um but at the same
time this is the teleportation thing
right can
I this isn't the first time I've seen
one of these perhaps I can use them as
way
marks louder or what do you
think can I uh okay I have to go from
here huh uh I want
to go to where I can practice oh I can't
go anywhere
now
I wanted to practice the CH perfect the
fighting again I wanted to practice like
the
combos H wait uh [\h__\h] how do fight how
uh focus and
then uh
okay okay uh yeah okay that's fine
that's fine not not the worst not the
wor I remember
roughly one day passes
one night passes and Wawa already
confused about
controls no I didn't forget it's in my
blood oh level up 16 already
sheesh wait let me like the
audio bit louder for
[Music]
me ah also
apparently
would you guys agree
that uh the audio is just
generally too loud only during the
fights because of all the special
effects in that case cuz that's what I
heard uh we'll turn it down a little bit
more a little bit
more I would say only the special
effects need to be turned down cuz all
the all of the slash slash slash had
that problem it t of arise too games
just get too loud in battles
which is generally fine if you just play
it for
yourself but if you play on the stream
then you want your audio to be
balanced I want to explore let me run
around look look at the map we're going
here huh okay but I want to look around
why it looks so
realistic Hi boss sorry for being late
don't worry I was also late so you're
not really that late well looks so
cool smaller smaller baby
tree is this like going to lead a
different place sometime yeah it does
see I stopped running so now my my speed
buff is gone so lame come this might
take a
while get him get him get him get him
get him get down here you little
[\h__\h] there boy
yeah get
so I ate some Burger King before the
stream I still have some fries next to
me but I'm so
full did you guys
eat
get you can use I yeah right Garuda
Garuda wait I have like Garuda activated
right now oh
[Music]
oh oh wait these things are different
too right
W oh I love it I love the bringing
enemies to metrick but with bigger
enemies I think they said it's only like
a little bit uh like not as effective
right that's so cool I like
it yeah cycling with L2 okay okay for
now I'm F of Garuda it's kind of fun
don't have to move too much just for
lazy
people I might not do side quest but I'm
definitely doing side tracking by
running around everywhere where I
shouldn't
be can I cross this can I walk in the
river no well that's
disappointing am I late yeah but I was
late too so together we're we we even
each other
out
romantic oh the bridge is closed
they okay what was that what did I do
that was not deadly Embrace in my
opinion sick
tole sick him tole oh my
Gody what what am I doing
get him whoa whoa whoa whoa oh did I
Parry I can't believe
it
get why is everybody so close together
my god oh this one's a strong one
actually I just
realized I'm not doing so
well oh is that attack
like does it always let make you go up
in the air
s to or is it just a coincidence that
I'm going up in the
air yeah
okay get if they're not up going up with
me that's kind of
stupid hey don't hurt
me oh also okay deadly Embrace doesn't
work on this enemy for example it does
some weird what is that was that what is
that supposed to be
doing oh wait is it h no why does it not
do my deadly embrace it's too big so
what what is it doing instead it's not
even like oh God I'm going to die it's
not even roughly bringing him to me over
here sick
tole mommy
mommy over here there boy sick of tole
get him I'm D get him boy I'm waiting
for my treat to go back up sick to thank
you too get
him 185 HP in the
dream
[Music]
in that case
uh the other
skill uh from um my fire my fire skill
would be
better because that way that one doesn't
get like debuffed just because an enemy
is too too big I still get closer the
same amount get as I
do oh [\h__\h] 6 hp in the dream get him boy
sick of
tole you know what to do
boy 18
HP I don't want to switch though because
now well I guess in my brain I didn't
want to switch because fire versus fire
but I guess it didn't matter in this
game over here there
boy that's not fair I barely had potions
to begin with was the checkpoint in this
battle
or I was still I was still warming
up I was trying my best to not die okay
okay nice this is how you get back all
your potions without having to spend any
money
y
a [\h__\h] they're all in the
way get him
boy flashing what you guys say the game
is still too loud I think it's generally
quieter than I had it
yesterday you to do
boy get
him
get him boy sick
tole I feel like when I do that since
I'm above the enemy I'm not really doing
damage but maybe I
am
oh deadly Embrace do well it doesn't
make sense on this
eneme not too loud might be a bit too
quiet okay one second
over
[Music]
here there
boy not this
time there
boy over
here also I need to stay with this right
now with Garuda because we want to
practice using
her you little
[\h__\h]
oh you know what to do
fory oh did I just
cancel
that why are these like mini mob fights
so long so unnecessarily long get him
boy I heard that's quite the
um common
critique sick of
tole over
here D
boy get
him d boy get him
boy what do you mean I'm using half my
skills I'm using everything I
can sick
tole get him boy at least within my own
capacity
[Music]
ouch
sick of
tole not this
time there
boy over
here what the [\h__\h] man that should keep
on my
[Music]
feet
sick of tole do you mean these with with
the other half is that what you meant
get him boy just like constantly
switching in between sick of
tole you know what to do
boy W
okay well I didn't realize that that's
what you're supposed to do constantly
switch get up boy how the [\h__\h] would I
know that that's the strategy that's
normal I just got guda I just just
received
Garuda I thought You' just like chill
with the one that you you want to use
until you don't want to use
it they said it it tells
you
okay
not effective as a general speed
increase on the
map she mocks us she mocks
us oh it's only
me how G are you trying to get yourself
killed killed it's not me who's been
playing with
fire you don't do things by half Ste you
ooh is this what the explosions were
that we see saw in the
background at the end last
time is this what what that
was
probably so if it wasn't you or him who
freed the Bears who was it good question
you someone who didn't have their hands
full F bloody har raise the volume here
a bit more but what matters is they're
safe something they wouldn't be had it
not been for you g a just doing the
job so uh what about his dominant gone
and after we were so
[Music]
close well I can track him it do be like
that so close but not close enough
s told us about your
family lost me own to Imperial
steel sometimes venance is the only
thing that keeps you
going thank
you go safely
Brothers I reckon he likes
you what's with that
tongue the detail in facial
Expressions she's gone she's gone oh my
lady you have to walk
on in the crisis and not what's her name
what am I going to do
Barnabas Barnabas Barnabas sounds like
some tropical how long to the coastal
Road Island at this pace we won't make
it by
Sunset he'll know he'll cast me out like
all the others benedicta what am I going
to do
going to
do holy [\h__\h] here we go
again who was
that g is that the big guy or who what
holy
[\h__\h] oh my
god oh what do we have here what do we
have be here that's a good price I
reckon but we'd be doing the slavers of
disservice if we didn't price her wor
stay
away okay sorry I should I want to feel
bad for
her M it's all
right they can't hurt you
anymore come on let's go
home is this it at
office my punishment for not listening
to you
[Music]
H this wretched
world like she still has something in
her doesn't
she is this the
remaining deserves to die it all
deserves to Die the remain G power die
die there it
is oh she still have gud
right oh I didn't steal
Garuda okay that's her primed completely
right now
she's she is she is the icon
well she still looks pretty powerful
what the [\h__\h] they made it out to be
like she's completely lost until this
point do you feel it too she's fine
guda I'm like a
bear
[Music]
oh
fine into control she can't control
it isn't stopped that Vex will swallow
this whole forest and another along with
it should have finished her off I'll
stop her this is what happens this game
is already so brutal why why why did we
not finish her off dummy lad that
doesn't mean you have to
listen I should have gone with g
always finish your opponent off make
sure they're dead Clyde I don't think
you understand that's not just windy
weather you're wondering into Benedict's
rage knows no bounds and that's on a
good day I don't want to know what's
weighing inside down you know what if I
do your I have to find out you will help
me back calm her down with your love
and we'll see how deep is your love is
it like the
ocean
the how your
love
how there are so
many for every fragment
of
ow
ow first time I'm actually running away
from these
enemies should I I guess I got to fight
them how strong are they those [\h__\h]
they I feel like she might be pretty
strong no
yeah no actually no never mind not that
bad
too
[Music]
slow yeah still a little bit bulky but
not as bulky as that weird baby
dragon
ouch
sick
tole
get you know what to do I hate that
skills sick
of deathly Embrace is cool though but
like I'm always in the
air you want some
okay doesn't work on them
either get
him keep your distance
boy
ca
ca give them all you've got
for get
him over
[Music]
here there boy
camera get him there boy don't let them
get
away get them boy boy give them all
you've got
boy
uh by the way how was dead do fre I
didn't watch it I was trying my best to
like sleep a
lot be before this stream cuz I was so
tired yesterday without the um energy
drink was it
good
man man I need to watch the
V legs
she's so
cute I don't want to fight
you can I if I run far enough does it
like leave me
alone I'm thinking when there stagger
bars ah when the Stagger bar is full it
works
not a
potion but still two two I don't know if
I can really fight Garuda with that uh
whatever she
is at 50% now hold yeah I think I
remember seeing something like that in
the he's in there
he did he say
he
oh now hold now I could
travel I guess I
will let's go to the Hideway
first does he mean the man in the Rob
[Music]
okay I want to
try something I want
to m
re
rearn you guys have to help me if you
played the game
before
so the ideal
way oh uh wait how do you
do let's have him not
[Music]
fight so the ideal way of fighting how
to do a good combo do I go round round
round like do I go the full four normal
or do I have to stop at
three to then finish off properly but
what's what's what's the perfect way of
comboing do a magic for after each swing
wait after
each after
each
wait you mean after like the the fourth
or fifth right try four squares one
squares one triangle and deadly Embrace
okay
well um 1 2 three 4
oh
oh one 2 three
aha oh wait that was it's over was that
uh does that magic burst only work when
I use it after the fourth
one every
time right let's
try one one
two I don't think that worked one two
three
wait one two a but it's just smaller
three one two
three one 2 three
4 okay he died
[Music]
um and then you press square again to
continue to come one two
three one two
three okay
sometimes I can't get it in
but sometimes it just uh ignores my
input I
think okay I see that's like one way of
comboing but I want to use these fancy
things too it's over this especially
this one
Yoo square triangle it's not working
square triangle square Tri it's stupid I
don't like the rhythm of
that that's oh wait okay I see like it
gets
like some kind of a
boost I don't know what's going on I
just something's
happening charge SW sword jump release
sword
oh
what
uh charge jump ooh aial burning strike
sexy M it's
over
moral double jump I don't have double
jump
[Music]
yet can't press it too fast it's like
difficult to figure
out uh the when to press triangle
sometimes it's too fast sometimes it's
too
slow how
[Music]
fun after you do like the fourth magic
burst he flies away
Noob trap is wanting to spam all you
mean
this doesn't even do
damage wait I have an idea
ah well now it's now it's on uh re
charging but I wonder if I get him up
with the AR Ariel thingy that I just
did if I can activate the Wicked
[Music]
Wheel well this works
too
[Music]
it will okay my combos I'm going to try
to make this work I don't know it's not
always like consistently
working
somebody somebody just said I can spam
uh
Square uh when I have gosh happening
that attack in the air that I just did
to get more hits in
hold
n is that only for
[Music]
gosh now that missed oh is it because he
died how far can we go
he's way too
far uh big enemy
where
how
ah
um anything
medium
Maybe
oo
Hello nice to see you again for now on
you this doesn't work
[Music]
okay get him down to 50 oh he's he's
pretty much now he's now he's at
oh
okay only that in that moment I I did
it but I I took a few steps away so that
I could see how
it how it affects him when I'm further
[Music]
away
bring him down get a lot of time to hit
of a Spam
of no I won't be in the in the
tournament no
no
he won't he won't do like he won't move
when I do
the magic first so I don't know if it's
really
working
oh oh yeah
right
doesn't feel as intuitive on big
[Music]
enemies
see like him not moving do I'm like
unsure if it
worked but it says Times Free and I
think when it's Times Free that means it
works uh
ah one two three no one two three 4
huh why is it not doing it one two three
oh
shush uh I forgot what I was supposed to
do this this this is this what you want
me to
do oh 40K
[Music]
yeah against prob won have time to do a
magic first Bo I'll hit you before so
just focus on Square four times in
Triangle at the end but it's not working
I can't do it 1 2 3 4 and that would
worked one two three four is that now
now I feel like that that's like too
little stuff in my reper that's all I'm
doing that's kind of boring too I got to
mix in some fancy cool stuff like this
but that just doesn't mix into my combos
that
well how do I how do I mix the other
things
in tining
so
I'm it may not count as a combo but
[Music]
still yeah I have vibration
on yeah
who even I don't know how I'll be able
to use every stupid
ability especially later we'll probably
be switching even
more
ah
[\h__\h] uh ah confuses
me I don't even get my magic burst in if
I don't like really focus on the timing
on the
[Music]
Rhythm
like I can do it but I have to really
focus on the
timing then even then I miss it
sometimes like
now wake
winds
now that doesn't really do anything when
he's on the
grounds well I mean it's better than
before at
least wouldn't use the wheel no not when
he's on the ground at least still does
damage
[Music]
then
also what was it the upgrade
for the
dodging here wait I already did it oh
it's mastered wait what was I supposed
to get
additionally ah at this one I
think
um no wait this is also already mastered
or
so well let's learn this I don't know if
I'll be using it I don't think I'll
remember to press R1 to get up uh R2 to
pull the attention away of an enemy to
pull the attention of an enemy Target
taunting what who wants that I don't
care about
that Swift recover is nice h use X1 in
the air to kick off a nearby
enemy a increasing jump height and
duration
Nar probably another thing that I won't
remember increases maximum kicks to
two
well and what's
this
ah ah this is the one I was thinking
about cuz it extends the trigger window
there we go so now when I
dodge m counter attacks okay let's have
him uh attack me
uh I don't like this
menu okay come at me
bro not this time oh see I can do it
after all why did I like forget how to
do
that okay that was not dodging that was
already too far I
guess
ow okay one more come
on too
early ow too
[Music]
late
look at all
[Music]
that
pretty good pretty good pretty good no
what why is what
what uh I think there will still be many
times where I'm messing everything up
though cuz
it's
difficult difficult
this
time wait do one again I want to trve
with X instead didn't it say x works
too oh no h that was a stump maybe they
meant
triangle h no wait wa wa What
triangle not this time oh it's a like a
bigger
kaboom
oh I
buried okay enough of
that don't want to tire out my fingers
too much right away in the beginning hey
I want to leave I want to
leave
leaving okay by the way did I get any
important drops
from
fighting uh benedicta that time cuz I
heard that you can get like strong
weapons from the bosses all the
times but did I get anything
cool
no oh my access I got an accessory
though um
which
one this one the rising Flames
one
probably I don't care which one we're
using need to craft do you think we
should go and
help uh wait where was
the blacksmith
[Music]
again was he here probably
not
and not here all the way on the other
side okay let's check if we can make
anything useful right now if not I'm not
using right
oh then we'll keep the other
one was that the
one
probably let so I was say see I'm busy
here can we we make something useful
otherwise I'm out oh Bastard Sword
what o should I make
this I have the materials for it I
switched the wrong one okay okay okay
just one
moment yes bastards let's
[Music]
go
proudly
bastard and one of these should I make
this too a nice new belt that's a big
Improvement sure should last you a good
while
[Music]
and this one could also be
good not bad if I do say so myself uh we
could reinforce them
yeah
meteorite yeah that should do you that
should make me stronger
okay best work these better be worth it
ooh another 20 or 10 I
guess yeah that should do you okay
hopefully I'm using up all those
materials I won't regret it
hopefully so this
one and this
one and this one is all upgraded
nice should be much stronger
now then let's
teleport can I teleport from here
yeah to the Dragon's
Ary also really close to this
place the eye of the Tempest that's
where you want to go wait maybe I should
have bought potions oh well we'll die at
least once
anyway probably no side quest no Fox
side quest we're not doing them cuz I
heard they're not worth it unless
there's one with um about uh the cute
girl
[Music]
oh wait
live what's that the dominant the man
who killed my brother are you absolutely
certain I've seen him every night for
the past 13
years watched as the flam his ey
Joshua
out thanks bro
it I'm here and so's
too don't worry about us oh I'm left
behind you beting left left of front see
I got to go alone as if you couldn't
climb
that as
if that looks very
climbable the dude is still there I
thought he walked
away that's [\h__\h]
creepy why
not and there he goes where did he go
[Music]
that's so
creepy Who's Laughing I'm freaking out
that was [\h__\h]
terrifying [\h__\h] jump scare of my life
you literally had to hold on to the
table I'm so scary I'm going to Su
Square Enix for that the
[\h__\h]
you won't stop me
garuna oh we're still calling it's gitaa
okay yeah now I see you coming hi she's
toing with
me I don't know if she's thinking so
deeply about that
man why are we so slow
now Mama Mia
go go
go that's a bait that is such a
bait this thing isn't really there is it
you why why then just it just makes no
sense you called
me why
so that you can die
here oops wrong
number stop
bang wee
[Music]
yes
Lasher a nice
start for our
fight I thought it was over I thought we
were done with her for
now where is he but see I already I
already feel like I don't know what I'm
doing anymore more even though I just
practiced what the [\h__\h] she so
[Music]
big ow she
sh guda lend me off she's so big n take
down large enemies will become partially
staggered when the will go will reduce
to 50% ah you teaching me that what I
already learned just now thank
you uh so when they're 50 I shall use
garuda's deadly Embrace
quickly will topple it leaving it
vulnerable to followup attacks okay
uh is that what you
mean not what what what what is that
[Music]
what hey I can counter properly now
let's go let's
go
oh
[Music]
ouch
oh ah [\h__\h] I missed the
[Music]
timing damn I'm in between her legs I
have a special angle let's
go wo wo wo wo wo wo wo wo wo wo wo wo
wo wo wo wo
two
wo oh can't touch
her okay just just uh wait wait it out I
guess I can PE PE PE PE can
I
ah
ah hey W I'm trying to
dodge I'm in
between you calm down now this
time
yeah I have to redo this but I got
pretty far just trying to use my new
tricks you
[Music]
know and I'm using my counter let's
go oh I didn't use the there you go it
was not too late it was not too late go
go go go I don't know what I need to do
in that moment gu nothing
wait oh oh I thought she was just
bagg okay perfect perfect perfect I
already used up everything except that
so thank God that was still
[Music]
there oh actually that came
back
all right hey I'm actually doing it
but with
no no healings left I don't know
man
[Music]
give me
fire uh sorry I forgot how to do
things
oh I got better for sure I got so far
without using a potion without getting
really
hit that one hurricane moment was so
confusing though I didn't know how to
really Dodge her so that did a lot of
damage
man maybe we can do it just got to be
careful
now
oh cinematic
Clash dude you got to fight faster
where's the combos there's no combos oh
we cut off something
there oh oh oh that was it oh Oh I
thought we had to do it a little bit
ourself
okay
my
oh oh oh all right a first try I didn't
think at all I would do it first
try wow all these new like strategies
that I just uh practiced really paid
off I don't know if that would have gone
so well if I didn't use all the counters
and all that it's good that we practiced
that
that was a solid run and the only moment
was really that those weird hurricanes
cuz I was standing in the middle of them
and it still hit me what where do you
want me to
go here we go t you get ready is your
face
five I feel like she's done
oh there is phase
two I mean if you combine it with all
the phases in the previous
fight this is this is just phase four
and now phase
five there's
more there is
[Music]
more there's
more can we
not well with no potions this one I'm
certainly failing don't eat me you're
nothing you're
monster just like you I will
not let you stand in my
way oh oh oh interesting we had that
before
Oh
that's what I'm
saying
that's it's
us that's what I was saying it's
us what was I
right
but what about the P the cloaked
prisoners that we saw in completely
different
scenes holy [\h__\h] I was
right I was like N I can't be because of
they were like actual people that I mean
the other things they really seemed like
you could say that was just Le fata
Morana or like an imagination in my head
me trying to cope that it's not me
thinking it's someone else trying to
tell myself it's someone else it's
really
not
hallucinating it's just a
Coke but those two cloaked people they
still exist
though they still certainly exist and if
they really exist then the one cloaked
person that was there at the time when
our brother died makes me wonder if
maybe they were
there but me thinking it was them is
just a cul they were just like
coincidentally there or whatever but I
still was the one that turned into eph
is what I think I don't know I don't
know just my
explanation okay controls for eph are
mely ranged evade
uh-huh okay basically
same uh Circle can used to charge an
enemy charge charge at charge and enemy
covering great distances in short period
of time as well as dealing damage if the
enemy is
struck okay so this time Circle does do
damage all abilities available while
bodying can be confirmed on the abil
[Music]
okay
okay well there's not even potions I
feel like this is like a short certain
win oh the combo still works I
think
oh I was pressing R1 in the moment but
it didn't matter cuz there was a
cinematic strike or did I activate it
this
R1 oh I I went into that oops see yeah b
y b what the [\h__\h] is going
on oh I can stop her when I do that okay
okay right now I'm losing so let's uh
should we not let her do
it I say
no no
[Music]
no stop
it there we go there we go let me let me
do my thing you
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oh Skyfall let the
sky
[Music]
oh
it hey she's killing me wait wa wa wa
hey that's not fair this [\h__\h] this
[\h__\h]
M
[Music]
yes no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no please
let me win
please no no I don't want to okay okay
okay
She's So Mean She's So
Mean oh she's so
mean let me f [\h__\h] she won't let me
[Music]
in
I'm like a dinosaur I fight like a
dinosaur what the
[\h__\h] wow if only I had wings I want
wings
too
no no let me do something cinematic
too oh
wow me
platforming I literally I I wrote this
in the members chat
but part of my dream last night
was um I was in a Super Mario a Mario
maker game
like versus like three other people
playing the same map at the same time I
was doing without practice without
anything I was doing so well just
naturally holy
[\h__\h] and I
won I
won winning Mario maker in a
dream only in a
dream W oh she stopping me Mommy Mommy
stop I'm sorry
Mommy insane cinematics though
insane absolutely
insane now oh I grew a new arm oh almost
like a
phoenix that's a long long cinematic
scene finally not a nightmare well yeah
no this time no nightmare but I've been
having a lot of nightmares
[Music]
lot of weird
dreams
punch [\h__\h] punch oh okay more more
more more more more how long is
this ah
stop she I call for it I that I mean I'm
barely doing
anything
but a
sick sick and
thle
wow we're not doing this until until
she's at zero right but it kind of feels
like it actually so long also am I
done am I actually done fighting for
real now there's no way to they're
bringing me back into a a battle portion
for like 5% of her HP at the end after
this badass Cinema
Scene okay wow that was a big chunk of
her
HP actually without all the Cinematic
scenes I would have maybe
died and couldn't have done it first
try slain for real for real are you sure
is it really for real for
real yeah the
last I don't know if I would say fourth
maybe fifth was all
movie
Tas was actually big
[Music]
TASC
I did do both first try
now oh
time standing still almost but not
really so do we have this realization
moment
now control it Clive I
can't it is you isn't it Clive yeah it's
[\h__\h]
me St this
now we didn't get a last chitchat
between benedicta and
Sid
oh
oh wow it looks like a great God but I
guess kamu is not a great God that is
thatu is that like something that
actually like out of Final Fantasy also
is the
[Music]
thing sounds kind of Indian I don't
know
[Music]
he's very
choicy or I guess in English you would
say
Zeus nice is your problem like is he is
ramu part of some mythology IRL or
bloody mess
this which one
no yes
no oh chist based off of so
Choice okay well Clive the ghosts you've
been
chasing it was inside you that's an
early Revelation I thought if they would
reveal that I thought it would be later
they'll be damned if I know what that
means that's pretty
early oh tiny tiny SM
SM
bro
I didn't look at promo promotional
material I didn't never even look at the
trailer I
think I don't even watch the trailers of
a lot of the games that I play but I'm
glad I didn't cuz this way I was still
questioning
it turns out trailers can be pretty
spoilery
too
why why did you have to listen to him
is she dead b or just
Garuda this can't be you wanted can
I
[Music]
a is she dead for real for real but guda
is a God so like guda is still like
somewhere
right just the carrier is dead but if
she dies will Garuda be given to like
someone else besides me and I still only
have half of the power or do I get the
full power now or or or or or questions
questions
questions Gara will be reborn right like
like a phoenix dominant basically okay
that's what I
thought a new dominant will be chosen
hopefully someone on our
side new someday not right
away sometime
Le
Majesty
je what a hair do for the horse
desperate that's a
king she will you engage him personally
your
highness of that's like gond dorf's
horse way bigger than the
others G's breath really he called
Odin
[Music]
n wait is this
his icon whatever Prime whatever
version it's for har I'm so confused
us B is this F
thing yes yes both fully primed okay oh
so like the voice is part of his
[Music]
thing sexy
violin
oh
interesting interesting form to take
on you can
fly my e can't really fly you can only
Fly With
[Music]
Me
true let's
go the warden of Darkness oh I was going
to ask what's his element who rides into
battle at top his spectral Ste and whose
Black Blade is set to be sharp enough to
split the very season Wayne his latest
dominant King Barnabas h barados of
valud
wow Bahamut the warden of light whose
power dwells within Dion Odin and Deon
Las Prince of
s I don't [\h__\h] know how to say that
in the Holy Empire the GRE Gregorian
faithful hold
dragons to be sacred creatures and baham
the most sacred of them all because of
this as well as the protection it grants
them the icon is loved and rever rever
what by the Imperial
populace Dion Dion
Dion
now
[Music]
okay
R is that him he's done being a dragon
for
[Music]
now well very pretty Prince reform the
cohorts at
once
[Music]
yourness water break me too me too me
too me
too
saurs their attacks are frequent and
widespread even in the Holy Capital the
capital what of my father is Radiance is
safe but he has ordered the city guard
strengthened we can expect no
reinforcements why why does everybody
look like a super model the emperor's
safety is
[Music]
Paramount I shall deal with our enemies
here cuz Final Fantasy
so
true
Me Oh Me In
Chains yeah it was me yep it was
you I killed Joshua it's pretty [\h__\h]
up why did you do
that what made you do
that ah you're
awake you're just full of surprises
first that trick with guda then whatever
the hell that other thing was yeah I'm a
[\h__\h] weirdo know you had it in
you do
it hey but it makes so much sense
because kill me he's the brother of
Joshua it was me and they're both I
killed him fire Dom I killed Joshua I
killed them all I'm a
monster and I deserve to
die so ended anyone would be another
fire dominant it would be
somebody by Blood oh she
NY
I reckon I can take you if that's what
you
want but first I thought I'd give you
the benefit of my Timeless
wisdom I'm timeless it seems to me you
see that since you're still breathing
you might as well make yourself
useful yeah cover yourself up please get
dressed pretty as you are you're not my
type um what the [\h__\h] didn't need that
comment I'll uh see you in
all
booty cutie
booty booty
PTI booty
nudy
why was I naked and if he had my cloth
well when if I was naked because I
turned into eph that means that all my
clothes are like fallen on the ground so
he picked up every single piece of every
belt do every every every little single
piece of this detailed armor and brought
it
here like sorry I'm I'm questioning
logic
again
made sure to have every single
piece he just took it why why would he
take it
off Quest lock there are certain times
during the game that side quest will
become temporarily available until
progress has been made for the main
scenario such times Quest givers will be
indicated with
a may as well hear what he has to say
don't go makeing me throw you back in
there doy dog hi you still like me
H you do don't you you understand me
you're the only one who gets me brought
back with him I did girl poor thing all
dressed in dirty rags have to make a new
dress for her
benedicta is she down here too I guess
not probably
not wait does she get something better
than the cell wait is that her no
as a
dude a Jill
oh dead for real for real well maybe he
wanted you know to bring her and make
her a grave that's that's totally
it finally crawled out of the cryp eh
you look like it although I thank you
for doing us the courtesy of covering up
don't well still have a bit of fight
left in you then listen I've arranged a
meeting with gav in case you've
forgotten you're the one he's been
putting his nose to work
for for nothing
mhm oh we're really just listen really
down you've been relaxing in your cell
gav's been busy sniffing out your
dominance and according to his last
report he's picked up a sent gav's gone
to a fair bit of trouble for you the
least you can do is hear the poor booger
out he's going to meet us at the king
for pack your stuff we'll leave as soon
as you're
ready my
dominant but now we know if it is me so
are we still looking for the cloak
people h of course we are I would be
curious
too
I upgraded my gear just like right
before the big
[Music]
fight oh well it's fine it's fine it's
fine not so long ago this here was a
thriving trade
route then the blight came the people
left and just like that it was
deserted making it the perfect little
shortcut Dab's waiting for us up ah come
on still feeling sorry for
yourself don't please think about it
Clive the rumors all point
to that was an imperial
signal they shouldn't be here the old
for's been abandoned for
years our little chat can wait I need to
see what the bastards are up to you go
on ahead and meet up with G but we both
know that no buts about
it what's that
song
what was
that got to ask
Google what's this
song this is stupid I'm the dominant of
fire yeah we sent galin a wild goose
chase yeah but I'm the one
F he ate it but there was a ball that
he'd have to bring back to
me he just eats
[Music]
it
nice
ouch oh speed
us you catch the VOD all right
what keep your
[Music]
distance get him
get him get him get him get him get him
get
him set the spiders on
fire oh new enemies
approach jez this attack is just
endless sick
tole you know what to do
boy
get
him that's enough it's
over it's over now you know what to do
boy get
[Music]
up level up I forgot to buy potions no
no no no no no my strategy is spend no
money on potions just die and get free
ones what the [\h__\h] why would I spend
money
no no
no I am stingy when it comes to RP
games what
now if the game is so willing to give me
all this stuff for freed and oh it's a
minur Min Tower Beast man where are you
going yeah I thought
so you know what to do
boy too
slow oh the window is pretty
big
ouch ouch oh I'm stupid ah sa for coming
see I actually I'm actually
remembering how to do it you first time
I'm doing
it too
slow get him boy go this time [\h__\h] I'm
doing everything that I need to
do so proud of
myself you know what's
BO oh wait I should have done deadly
Embrace right
right I don't know should
I sick tole in that moment or in a
moment ouch sometimes I'm too
slow
get him
boy oh my
[Music]
God maybe I'm doing this on purpose
because I want the potions H maybe I
just want a potion refill get
him sicker
tole King your distance
boy
get him
boy sick of
[Music]
tole see my pump is already
hurting come on thank God there's so
much
story to
[Music]
the you like recover from all the
fights
but it's still not enough there
boy get
him ouch I'm going to
die I'm sorry it's okay I wanted to
die the B button mashing Jo but my
mostly like yesterday both my hands
were hting a lot
oopsy
but it's both it's both now it's mostly
my like the the meat in
between my thumb and my R you know get
the chunky meat over
here get them all you've got
boy
[\h__\h] sick tole I legit forgot there boy
deadly
sick I know it's just circle I realize
now get him boy get him sometimes
forgetting the most basic things you
know it is what it is also I should have
I know I should used this and
but especially when God Is So
endless you just want to bring in as
many hits as possible sick of
[Music]
tole get
him you know what to do
boy
[Music]
give them all you've got
for get
him sick of
tole precision sick over
here too
slow somehow I can't do the counter
anymore what what's wrong with me what's
wrong with
me there we go there we
go sick
tole get him ah my
B just it's such a workout though
switching all the
buttons not this time
like try going
between
uh square and triangle for like five
minutes however long this fight takes
five sometimes 10 with it's a bigger
fight oh my
God it's such a
[Music]
workout I can change the control so that
magic is on ah yeah yeah yeah I've been
told somebody else told me also they
were doing that but then what do you put
where do you put um Dodge H not Dodge uh
Focus where do you put dad
then yeah going to have shortcut said
stret to a nest of bloodthirsty beasts
kill me more Heal Me heal
me why you not heal me outside of
[Music]
battle I can change to try it that's so
complicated thinking of better
[Music]
setup now I'm like getting used to this
can't be much further
[Music]
now
I don't I don't
know wait I want this
too did I just take the
wrong
[Music]
shortcut give all you've got
boy over
here get
him you know what to do
boy sick of
tole get
him over
here H that was also some kind of deadly
Embrace get him boy did you guys see it
for the
Minecraft sports festival today was the
like team
[Music]
decision like who gets into what
team I think don't they do it like
randomly I wasn't watching it I just saw
the outcome but I know that it's random
cuz I didn't have a say in
it
but oh yeah I find my team
interesting for
sure can I not get back I want the
item
uh there's like a team a and Team B
within our
team I don't know how what that means so
that if if that means we're like split
then I don't really get to do anything
with Kyla and Amilia it seems cuz
they're also in Fury in my
theme oh oh my God not enough one let me
through get him boy uh but my team is
like um
basically uh clo no not what's it called
uh uh
uhai
[Music]
uh uh
Nissa get him boy auk sire G from the
the new
people get
him SI
to keep your distance
boy yeah get him boy an interesting team
and we're like in the meal
te there
boy sick of
tole
ouch get him do you know the games we
play no not yet I don't know did they
say anything on
stream not this time
boy
get him
boy get
him yeah I wonder
what get him boy uh what game maybe
there will be some new ones maybe
they'll redo reuse some old ones but
generally I think in the past we kind of
at least got to choose like if there was
something we felt not too confident
about could switch
team maybe there's an initial team that
they put us in maybe I don't remember so
well but I don't have to necessarily
stay in uh in the when I say team I mean
game actually in that
game
why are they fight so
[Music]
long my
God too much HP maybe I should switch to
easy mode so just so that the fights are
shorter I'm sorry but my
God it's just unnecessary long I I can
totally handle this action mode I think
it's called
but it won't help as far as I know
[Music]
really I don't think upgrading my weapon
is going to make such a huge difference
in
time
they get very fast later really it
doesn't lower the HP but does it
heighten my damage what is it
boy after him don't let him Escape oh
Gap g that one just fall
down you get much more DPS later
okay who goes
there this one's a desert take his head
desert out of my way why am I desert you
made oh they have a
Healer what or I don't know if the
astrologer can heal but let's take him
down
anyway wake
winds oh the captain is a
medium
enemy I'm getting all fre of them let's
go and S
[Music]
to all right all right all right all
right all right all right all right oh
hello wait aren't you the the Dron oh
and a dragon a Dron and a dragon you're
so funny there he is don't let him
Escape kill the
deserter the
fu you want to test my skills with this
Dron bring it on
oh hi s what's the situation you're late
get in trouble I'm in a situation the
Imperials are his tail we have to get to
him before they do understood
I'm here to even the odds any
objections I honestly forgot if I was
partaking
the in the Minecraft sports festival
this
time because it was a long time ago when
they asked me and I
remember I turned down some stuff
recently because I
thought I don't want to like you
know I don't want to force myself to be
in all these like tournaments where
number one I have to wake up a two times
probably number two I have to be on a
lot of pressure I'm really bad
especially in Minecraft one though like
I feel even more pressure than with
other tournaments also Mario Kart Mario
Kart are turned down I
think because some like it's with
Japanese viewers and and the Japanese
members partaking in
it keep your distance point I just feel
like I got to do well I got to practice
really hard and that much more of it you
know Dron already dead not this
time don't let them get away
there boy hey I wasn't hitting get
up still not really hitting
sick for Mario Kart especially though I
thought that oh my
God I'm going
to have
to work under so much pressure and then
for such a short amount of time if I
[\h__\h] it
up then all of that will be so
wasted I like playing Mario Kart but I
feel
[Applause]
like that will just not being quite
worth it unless I'm already skilled in
Mario Kart and have hopes of winning
what the
[\h__\h]
there
boy oh my God he's so he's so
strong sick tole you know what to do
boy oh I'm so bad too
slow there
[Music]
boy
not this
time go
[Music]
bad get him
boy there boy
give them all you've got
boy
oh Mirage died
oh oh how is you doing
that why is the real one going to
drop since when could these bastards fly
but what goes up yeah let's go come
down
bloody GI W literally playing hard mode
finish him off by not using the upgraded
weapons I see I see I
see you know no go down go
down
[Music]
no
get him
[Music]
boy critically claimed every ah you
can't even write the full
paragraph the full critically acclaimed
paragraph but yeah thank you for the
advertisement Imperial link
well where's Imperial
Zelda Dev Dono please play our game
please please play our game please
please play our game please play our
game please please play FFX if F I
played it been there
done hard to get in there it's like a
click
you saw it
coming oh thank you yes what what made
you say
that it just feels like I can't take a
break because I just went to
Japan and that meant I couldn't stream
as much as y Joel and now I'm going
again soon and I know there are certain
people
who
um really need me to stream at least uh
five if not six days a
week and I don't want to be affected by
that but it it certainly puts a lot of
pressure on
me I know I'm doing my best that I can
come on G come
on well I think Cliff could also do a
bit better
here Cliff CLI help me my my God help
me I've got you yeah you could have done
that like 5 Seconds 10 seconds
ago C with the
cliff um but yeah I I constantly feel
this pressure of delivering and so I
can't take a
break but I know I need one mentally
too
um but for now it's not not possible
maybe in January February maybe sometime
there
yeah got to got to hold on a little bit
more because now I need to focus also
on like preparing for
the 3D concert what a doesn't have your
nose I said he'd stumble off a cliff I
said that's a trouble with a nose like
mine can't help sticking it where it's
not wanted but if it wasn't for you to
cuz if I take
I want to be able to also take a break
from behind the scenes work at least for
a
week so I got to find a good moment
where I can do that as
well well uh found out now the heading
for one
thing I him and his mate are on their
way to your old stomping ground Ros area
the Coca-Cola just came up you should
have seen what they did to the Imperials
who tried to stop
them
there's no question about it he's a
dominant fire all right he can't be huh
I saw you turn into an icon before my
very eyes yeah and yes there's a good
chance it was you who killed the Phoenix
yeah or
maybe that other guy is also one it was
the fellow you saw enter the Whirlwind I
I saw him too you saw him too you didn't
dream it Clive he's out there okay so
it's not a
hallucination don't ask me I don't
bloody
know but I do know one thing you're
going to find him and find out after all
you swore
enough
what you swore you'd avenge your
brother's death that you'd never rest
until you'd hunted down the man
responsible but what if it's me find out
if this man's responsible and kill
yourself if he's not okay okay thanks
for the great
suggestion kill yourself if it's not
make sure however first that it's not
the other one either before killing
yourself now just make 100% sure before
regretting it that is actually I mean so
logically
pleasing he's not wrong it's important
it could still I guess in some way maybe
be
him no birds returning this year no B bu
no bird the deadlands have swallowed
their roosts like us not what they ate
them we're running out of
time we'll be in Rosaria in a day or
two
ooh Back to Where it All
Began he's got blonde hair that
is pretty long is it is it Joshua I was
going to say I was going to
say w w
[Laughter]
i
s who who wo wo wo hold up hold up hold
up like I was literally just before he
revealed that I was thinking wait let me
see his hair color let me let me let me
see let me see cuz that's that maybe
could be a hint and then and then and
then and then cuz I was for a moment I
was thinking what if it's somebody from
the past or from from the future like
time traveling but then what if what if
what if let me see let me see what who
could he be if he was traveling from a
different time um let me check the hair
could it be Clive from the future or the
past I don't [\h__\h] know uh but then
then then I saw the blonde hair so I was
like wait a second wait but it's just
like him but he just survived I guess
and and and I was like wait but if in
that Split Second I was like w his voice
though like could it be his like
grown-up voice I mean it could it could
and oh my God may maybe oh my God so
that that makes sense though because
like we're still insisting on him being
a fire fire dominant and and I mean
there can't be a thir fire dominant no
okay okay okay okay okay oh yeah Phoenix
well yeah yeah yeah yeah you can't just
die like we saw the Phoenix survive
already before like why why would he die
that one time just because eph was
killing him no no no no no can't take
down uh Phoenix no it's impossible you
can't but I guess if you do it like
benedicta died if you kill the the the
person then the Phoenix will just switch
bodies but I don't know I don't know how
that works like can you really take down
Joshua how how would that work but also
why does he why does he want to take me
down now why why what what problem does
he have with me oh my God like like
what's what's his issue I I I maybe he's
mad because I was trying to hurt him but
I don't even understand why I'm trying
to hurt him I would like to understand
that so many questions can we just
[Laughter]
talk
oh spit out of fire you was like a
bleeding volcano oh is that where we
wanted to go anyway never seen a volcano
I just wanted to go upgrade you think
I'm having you up
cve your friend she's awake ah
Shea
right oh
um I am
not mentally capable go to her you fool
right
now no I
can't I can't right you lot enough
slacking goats come with
me go and get those wounds seen please
remember to
breathe oh give it to me straight have I
got so fun all in good time let's make
ourselves
scar
yil they're revealing everything so
early is the game just short or is there
still so many other plot twists to come
I wonder what it's trying to
say
well if I would have
known that I would get a new weapon
right away so what it
be oh but I can make it just from the
wind Shard okay cuz I was going to say
like I used up so many materials for
what I made the Bastard
Sword no scratches right but I would
like to upgrade it can I no can't
upgrade
the that one anymore
storm cry oh I could but I need another
wind chard well where the [\h__\h] do I get
another wind chard
from I no that's just crafting it again
so you just can't upgrade
[Music]
it okay so now I have everything
fine oh it has a feather on it a
turquoise feather or several turquoise
[Music]
feathers Phoenix col kind of but it's
from mix before someone
doesn't
anyway
um yeah I'm fine guys I just uh keep on
pushing myself because of work and
because of the pressure
from some people I know most of you guys
don't mind me taking a few more days off
I
know um but it's really difficult to
please
everybody and
so
yeah but when the time is
right probably January or February I'll
take a proper break uh may it would be
cool if I could like take a like one or
two week break properly and then go to
the males but in the MDES I would still
stream or do the break after the mold
something like
that I don't
[Music]
know maybe I probably for the sake of
myself should do at least two weeks
yeah I feel like one month I would feel
too too much like
y I'm gone for too long I would feel
guilty but I'll force myself to do at
least two weeks watch out for wobbly
water I can't I wish I could stay that
long in the moldes but it's really
expensive so just like a week or so in
the moldes with streaming and then two
weeks maybe one week at home and another
week some in some Resort in Europe or
Austria even just
Austria and just ignore the
world
yeah sounds good right oh I
basically I don't know how much I told
you so far I I told you guys right that
I want to go back to the
MS
did I tell you who was going to be there
cuz things changed a little
bit but if I never told you who it was
going to be with that's fine
then things
changed but basically plans that I have
now so many plans for this part of the
Year fell for because I just felt like I
don't have time after
all um but I I want to make sure some
trips are happening next year so I want
to go to Bali next year for
sure we want to make a a big trip with
ID Girls whoever wants to come whoever
open invite and me and probably
cie
uh but that will be sometime next year I
don't I have no idea what time frame and
then
moldes I'm planning with one person just
one person again first we were like
considering okay what if we do like a
bigger group like four
people but it was hard to find a good
combination of people who would go there
also
with um being open to streaming while
being there cuz some some girls I asked
they said like they would go but they
wouldn't really want to stream or so you
know um and I want to go with someone
who's open to stream while being there
create content cuz then you can ride it
off too let's
go yeah well I'll keep the the secret
still with whom I'm going to the mes
let's keep it the secret it's not Raina
again
[Music]
though
it's someone
[Music]
new it's someone
new and waya uh is going to visit me in
Austria uh in this winter
mhm okay so just a little little tangent
break break in between the
story and weisa
WEA weisa
waya Bali no waya just going to come
here Bali though I don't know she can go
to Bali too cuz it's like open
invite whoever wants to come to
Bali it's WIA is it
WIA I don't
know I have to watch this s sorry guys
oh my God she's so
pretty
[Music]
a it's true
then it really is
you it
is CLI
a nice nice reunion you're
alive everybody's reuniting now even
Josh so are
you I still can't believe it
are your wounds
healed yes T told me what happened you
saved my
life after nearly taking it I had no
idea stupid forgive me but how did you
ever come to be there
Jill stupid protagonist fighting for
them how can you not see it IMM the iron
blood they invaded not long after the
news
arrived about Phoenix
gate Rosaria had lost her leaders the
duche was in chaos the iron Kingdom saw
our weakness and pounced upon it they
killed the
men and captured the
[Music]
wom and took you back to iron home
I thought they meant to have their fun
with me before the
end but the end never
came my Powers awoke
and everything changed
oh it all happened so
fast we were told that the iron blood
had captured a dominant and plan to
bring her on their latest
Crusade h
they gave me a
choice to fight for them on the
battlefield
[Music]
or see my country women
slaughtered now on and they call us
dominants
what what happened to Clive what
happened at Phoenix
gate in the end she's still killing
people but it's hard to choose it was
me I killed josua you kill if you're
being put in that situation no that's
not true I know you you wouldn't do
that it's the
truth I changed into him again not long
ago the second icon of
fire the one
responsible
CLI when I think back to that
night
mhm oh yeah
but oh man he was oh he spoke to me
already at the time he was the same form
maybe he was traveling traveling from
the
future all I don't know cuz like how can
he we have found
you what did he
mean
Clive we should go back there to Phoenix
gate do they like to do time know what
really happened and so do you you need
to know for certain and if what you told
me is true and you did what you said you
did then we will face it
together Jil
sometimes okay so it's a
possibility but no spoilers all
right you'll be needing a change of
clothes then H out you go your lordship
we wouldn't want you getting over
excited
sorry
what I'll see you soon then Clive what
are all these
like unnecessary comments we have a long
journey ahead of
us let's get this fixed before everybody
horny what do you want I don't know to
say
farewell we're leaving
okay good decision better that them
buried out there in the black you've got
a lot to thank that girl for you know I
know the production team take away from
Game of Thrones what do you really want
brutality and hor you don't come here
forers
ation a now a [\h__\h] sword but it's
like so similar in damage but this one I
guess I could
upgrade I don't need it
[Music]
right
more love scenes than all the ffs games
[Music]
combined five isn't much because yeah
but how high does it go after upgrading
it
h you not find a better price than
that why did I just make a different
sword I guess that item I wasn't going
to use it for anything else
anyway also this is like also new and
it's weaker but only because it's not
upgraded I
guess
well off you go
then I should probably say thank you to
gav
[Music]
too make it quick you so
sword not worth fiveing if it's weaker
really okay but how strong does this guy
another another 10
should last you a good
while okay that's 15 points stronger at
least anything
else wait
what
what who
who what I craft it
oh so
confusing but okay was already one
that's why it was 10 not
five oh well I just lost a little bit of
money no no no
matter we just don't have enough teams
to follow every lead I have plenty of
money
now
yeah can you sell old
stuff yes let's going Pur weighing you
down I'll be thankful you got that much
wait where's my special I guess I can't
sell it that's why it's not there you
got out
else I reckon I can find a
buer is that
all who
sells potions do you what do you want if
you're going to buy some be quick about
it m
I guess I'll buy some prob me blind you
know you not find a better price than
that you're rubbing me blind you
know it better I'll be I know I just I
just have so much money so why not I
guess so your mind's made up is it we'll
be leaving for roseria as soon as we're
were able Back Down Memory Lan
eh character development area Ain what
you used to be c not since the Imperials
moved in first sign of trouble you make
straight for Martha's rest and ask for
the land lady she's a friend of the
cause tell you with Sid and she'll help
you
out understood stupid
[Music]
hayle thank you gal I'd be lost with
without you yeah I'm just doing my job
no need to make such a
fuss he like no
homo you take care all
right oh I'm crap it goodbyes where's
Sid when you need him give him my
regards when he gets back I
will don't touch me don't get too close
oh oh waiting I've seen that outfit
before not hold ready my lady
pretty
ready that is her proper
outfit looks good I like it where are we
going
free reads I thought we were going to
like go here but I guess
not
okay thank you
my yeah two dominants together freaking
strong
a look at us
Rosaria it's been 13 years but this
Breeze the smell of the grass it's just
as I remember it you haven't been back
either well the new sword is pretty
broad I
couldn't brandid keep a close watch on
each other in the Imperial Army you'd
get beheaded just for knowing a
deserter the only way out was on a
mission
[Music]
I
see Tiny Dela you horny little [\h__\h] but
mostly I was
afraid afraid to go
back there I say a bro
sword might be it might
be but I'm here now me why do fries get
so bad after they get
[Music]
cold thanks to
you oh
[Music]
man
romantic we should Press On
[Music]
yeah I clearly do own an air fryer but
I'm not I'm clearly not using it that in
at the top of the hill must be Martha's
rest gav said the land lady's a friend
but can we say the same for her patrons
Imperials don't tend to take well to
those with my Mark if anyone asks I'm a
branded
Soldier to protect my Noble
mistress I thought it was an item
cuz I saw the Sparkles of that in the
background of the
cutscene I thought I I should go back to
get the
item
same oh hello look at thees on
this explains why there's a premium on
Imperials oh look at
that monster big horn shall we fight it
or just take the item it's protected
[Music]
let's make this
quick yo I swear to God you know what to
do
boy it's
over over
here get
him you know what to do
boy over here
you know what to do
boy I get jump scared so
much so easily it's spooky time by the
way I should play at least one spooky
game I know I know I
know maybe we can revive the idea I was
literally waiting for the next
Halloween last year we wanted to do you
what was it
called get Fatal
Frame with way mental support get him
boy over here not bad
onwards yeah I even have a thumbnail
from last year I just got to use the
same thumbnail
at least
one
oh also we're not as all ASM currently
not planning unless there's anything
last minute not planning any kind of
like big thing right now for Halloween
[Music]
at least I mean not on
the big scale of all of Ian I don't know
if promise or Advent are doing
something on their
own uh myth isn't doing
anything and as a whole we're not doing
Bridge there after what happened at
Phoenix gate it didn't oh yeah they've
been doing something in Minecraft though
a few people
[Music]
mhm but I don't
know maybe I should try to get a big
collab going I don't know what though uh
what what would I be
doing what would I get us to
do we could do that Halloween version of
that neighbor game
again that we did like with myth only
but I guess the maximum players might be
a
[Music]
problem it's Callen bus time of Oh you
mean wait is it a joke like
uh a joke about her
being
de or do you mean she's actually like
busy aren't we
all aren't we all always
busy get
Bo okay I used all four of them get him
boy if you use all four of them while
using
the full potential of g
gold then it takes up the whole stagger
time
frame look at me look at
me
sorry I have to like adjust my hand for
a
[Music]
moment you know what to do
boy sick of
[Music]
tole get him
boy there
boy let's
go
sick of tole
6,700 you know what to do
boy so difficult to figure out the
timing for that cuz he's like swing
swinging for so
long oh but if you got a Precision Dodge
and
then uh counter during that it turns out
as a Parry cuz like he's still
you know what she's still continuing to
swirl and swirl like a pretty
princess nice too nice paries right yeah
it's pretty easy when he does that kind
of happens
automatically I would say my
combat has
reached really good level wouldn't you
agree yeah
I got
good TS it's a side quest I want to help
them cuz they're cute
but no time I'm not going to fight those
no medium enemies are so
annoying but those are just small ones
hey what's that heyo hey there's an item
there I'm going to run to the
item oh I have points to spend on the
abilities
oh MAA there's a new one
[Music]
here one what oh in order to learn that
I need a lot
more oh wait also these
[Music]
HTS oh but these also this one costs a
lot jump
back then deliver a punishing
counter instead of one of these maybe
instead of the Wicked
Wheel have to jump AES and attack
counter potency is
increased so if it's kind of a Dodge
kind of and if it's really used as a
Dodge it's even
stronger you don't like go it it does
I've noticed that
yeah if it leaves you
vulnerable it's like
Heatwave oh
true I
guess
oh we can upgrade it wait we can upgrade
these ones too I
forgot Mama
Mia now I know where all my money is
going ah I can almost afford this okay
we have to save I have to save some
points wait did I get the item
[Music]
yeah there's there's another thing there
though the
[Music]
no
ooh do we have to fight the Big
Horn I guess we we skip the other one
maybe I'll fight it because I want to
see it maybe it drops an item that I
need
for get him
d
boy I waited for it this time I was
literally looking at the trigger
counter waiting for that to
happen get
him yeah I'm so good actually I have it
down get
him
I have upgraded I know I know I know I
know
chill wait I'm too strong St
Boy Can't oh there we go now we use it
all sick
tole over
here oh oh I was going to I remember
those that attack from Shiva I was like
okay something's attacking me just is
giving me
ttsd but no it's it's on my side helping
me
now oh wait
oh there we go there it is I thought it
was already
[Music]
ready sick of
tole
you know what to do
[Music]
boy get him you know what to do
boy give them all you've got
[Music]
boy sick of to um I would say I'm pretty
much using the full potential now of
what I can
do but it's still such a [\h__\h] lengthy
fight
man it's still long as
[\h__\h] now let me switch
um which one was going to was I going to
switch this
one it doesn't look as
powerful but
yeah you
know it might be easier to use cuz I
don't have to be in the the
air turn based fights were even
longer I guess they definitely can
be I upgraded the wrong ability one that
I don't
use what really whatever maybe I'll use
it again in the
future maybe I will here we are oh okay
Martha's
rest Martha
Martha
Marfa reminds me
of handmaid's
[Music]
tail I can refund I am
right
company no
[Music]
mistakes why what are you guys okay what
meme is that why why did you say that
name what
[Music]
meme I want to see what's hidden here
where does that lead oh it's like a
[Music]
circle Batman versus
Superman
uhhuh another thing
that I can't really really late
[Music]
too can I get up from
here oh
yes I got
to no worries it's a terrible
movie my
really oh music I don't care what your
orders are branded you keep that sword
in its
sheath okay I'll
try I wonder if Marthur is as friendly
as G claims let's go and find out shall
we you know in
German which stuff was for especially
kids are I think teenagers are
embarrassed to say
sheep
I was oh Callie is she
done did she
get
3,000 or why else would she uh end so
early Callie you did it oh my God
[Music]
Callie was it worth it also Cy you need
to stay a little bit and watch my combat
cuz it's like legit it's legit I figured
everything out I'm doing everything so
good right now chat is so proud of
me we're both winning we're winning
[Music]
Callie
3,200 girl you [\h__\h] did it in your
last sua stream and it didn't even take
you 8 hours it only took you free hours
free hours for
3,200
noise oh it was a second
try didn't you start your stream 3 hours
ago good on his work building the
aqueduct i w that problem ah super chats
tra
oh oh she's pretty too everybody's so
pretty
excuse me would you happen to be the
land
lady depends who's asking and why they
have an imperial Bearer with
them we don't only have an imperial
Bearer with us which hopefully won't be
needed we have two do me on the safest
route to the west but let's not say that
it's your friend here I'd be worried
about about beas don't have an easy time
of it in Rose area even a strat and lad
like tra kind of
attention if he gets snapped to end well
for you either then we'll just have to
stay out of the malitia
way gav said you might be able to help
us let's
go she's been enlightened follow
me she did the exact opposite of what
she was doing before oh sorry for before
can't be too wary of strangers asking
questions in our game I Marthur an old
friend of s she's also green he said he
had high hopes for a
bearer handmaid's tail I expect that's
you are also green so where is it you're
headed oh wait are they for Phoenix gate
I think they we have questions that need
answering really is that
so all right well if you want to avoid
the Garrison the road through East
pool's your best bet or it would be
if the bridge hadn't
collapsed a right blooming nuisance it
is we've had no trade with the village
for weeks yeah they were well kind of
did ask our Carpenter to take a look at
it grayish green but he went out on
another job what you asked your
Carpenter to fix a wooden bridge do you
think something might have happened to
him
what fingers crossed he's just taking
his time the alternative don't be
thinking
about we'll find him sense we just put
the car on top make sure he's safe just
cover the whole Bridge with a carpet
need that bridge repaired your carpet
sounds like the man to do it I see why
Sid's got such a soft spot for you are
you sure if you could I'd be in your
debt you said that he went out on a job
right he went down into the to check on
another Bridge the one by the Fallen
Gate what the marshes were dangerous at
the best of times we should
hurry
carpet gas me for Heights his name is
should you find him well tell him
mared at the bridge to East
pool is this a side quest oh I'm not
doing side quest what the [\h__\h] I thought
that was a main quest why did she give
side let's find that
ladder or should I do this one cuz it's
special oh there's a main quest
okay no no you guys are stupid you don't
know the English
language English language literally so
unlogical he goes to east pool here's
the
gate and that must be the
ladder this
[Music]
one I was I thought we were going to
zoom down the ladder kind of lame I
don't care what what your orders are
bran get away from me what was that the
carpenter the bridge whoes the carpet
for the
bridge hold on with com oh yeah okay now
look I mean with this this
enemy I can show up better with a medium
enemy you know what to do boy cuz these
ones don't
even get staggered
there
boy that's enough you're
finished what did what wait say you guys
are saying
same you know what to do
boy get him boy
carpets They just added the end because
it it sounds better you
know
carpenter carpenter carpenter carpenter
carp carp
car you want me to meet
someone can't wait for her to meet you
know
who home combo's on point right right
right right I'm really good at like save
my life countering and even parrying
you're burned the carpenter yes I am got
it all down I didn't realize my name was
known so widely I'm a friend of Martha's
she asked us to come and find you well
I'm very grateful for it I just finished
checking these piles when I turn around
I see a gang of slaving monsters looking
to to Feast on my flesh if you hadn't
come when you did I'd have been snipped
into strips by now oh don't worry about
I'm just glad you're safe could can you
make me my regards to the land lady then
hey actually she asked that if we found
you we should beg you make haste to
repair the bridge to East pool of course
I said I'd take the look at it but it
clean slit my mind I was all good
yesterday straight
away but yesterday I was like mixing I
was trying my best to mix all these
like skills and there was no good combo
coming up most of the
time yeah today you guys taught me about
Square thees are still sturdy it's just
a matter of replacing the stringers and
reining the deck so now that's all I do
time thank you burnard we were hoping to
take the road to Eastport all ourselves
we're very grateful for your help and
sorry for asking this of you after what
you've been
through gives you more options brid is
the least I can do that as well thank
you my lady so I also do the thing when
he's
half me and him triggered I do the not
as far
as far enough with
Garuda to well I just get crack and then
you go and let Martha know I'm all right
and she'll have her Bridge back soon
enough you guys you don't get me to
agree why is the carpenter fixing
Bridges that's exactly my question but I
mean I guess they don't have any a
bridge person the bridge will be fixed
when it's fixed right oh my God that
kind of answer it's done when it's done
we'll get there when we get
there what are they called in German
what the which one the car making person
would be um
[Music]
um carpet maker and then the the uh
person who makes something with wood
probably a simam or
uh or I don't [\h__\h] know I don't
[\h__\h] know TLA TLA a Tesla makes stuff
with wood uh like a desk table
uh I I don't
know doesn't
matter ah you're back what happened did
you find Bernard we did he's fine and
he'll have the bridge to East poool
repaired soon a bridge the founder for
that I don't think he would make it was
lucky we found him when we did the
creatur out there are not to be trifled
with capability it's the bl's fault they
nothing to eat in the north so they come
down here hunting for
food he can't keep going out alone I'll
have to arrange a guard for
him oh you anyway thank you just give up
I don't have a lot to offer in return
but you're welcome to rest here until
the repairs are finished agree with me
or
else usual room be delighted getting a
unusual spike in you
visitors it's been a
while
yes you agree can I get you a drink or
anything while you wait no thanks flagon
of imperial gold perhaps tastes like
swill but it'll slake a thirst no thank
you I prefer the
truth about why there are so few bearers
around
here yes there were more of them when we
were young far
more is this the Empire is
doing have they been sent away
[Music]
wow wow second one was my finger either
to theion or oriflam call did your seem
Min head having a hard time keeping up
with demand of late so the be make up
the shortfall super tired and ex used to
do crystals like sugar plums even down
here in the provinces thanks to the
battles nowadays they'll jump at any
excuse to confiscate our bearers so they
can be put to work
elsewhere I always knew the Empire
treated their branded like [\h__\h] but
after seeing it with my own eyes
[Music]
well she's more used to
controllers ah
the congratulations on the new
arrival and you got the little lad with
you it was a bearer the boy I carried
for nine long moons
a bloody Bearer oh you poor thing you
gave it to the constables then just left
it at the Garrison I let them deal with
it are they treating couldn't wait to be
rid of the Blasted thing been wanting it
gone since the moment I found out well
it's all dealt with now there no harm
done
eh mom you weren't my brother was he
they're treating newborn bearers like
you'll have one soon enough you just
have to be patient
in medieval times how they would treat
anybody who wasn't born like
normal unbelievable Ain
it bearers may have been looked down on
back in Arch Duke elwin's day but they
were still human beings but bears are
powerful no they've fallen so far a
beggar wouldn't spit on
them
they should appreciate
them but well well since you're not
drinking do me a favor and take that to
the Abby there's a Darkness at the heart
of this world and I'd have you see
it and we'll see it at an ABY Glade on
Abby on the shore of sorise bay the
Abbot there is a friend tell him Martha
sent you
and he'll show you what I mean
understood hey why do these quests show
up like this now it was good on his
work is there a blacksmith in here
should I check it out if yes
um I don't see one unless I have to make
sure you're aiming that at the F it have
a look don't be
shy so green Fresh Cuts Fresh Cuts get
your Fresh Cuts
here food but a lot of food that I don't
like like big ass
mushrooms look at that bacon and that
pork and all
that what the [\h__\h] is that tongues is
that
tongues cuz Japanese people made this
game and they love
eating
tongues from
cows I
guess grilling them in Yakiniku children
were tested that a bearer's fate was
decided at Birth and assumed it was best
for all
concerned I know but for a child to be
blamed to be hated by its parents
through no fault of its own we knew
nothing of what it meant to be born that
way not a
crab new name for a crab I didn't
recognize it as a crab but a crab is
basically just a turtle
spider wow wow that's
cute turtle dinosaur oh no okay this
actually a a a
turtoise a big ass
turtoise not wrong Turtle
spider everything's a turtle let's fight
it I'm sure it gives
a
a decent
drop too SL you know what to do I wish C
would still watching you would see me
being freaking
good with
everything see deadly take
down to to the house small small to to
the house why
[Music]
get him boy yes prob is sleeping now
going to going to
sleep it's so
cute aggressive tural
cute
who almost
triggered sick of tole over here get him
boy over
here come
on
number
one get him number don't get away number
three number
four and smash him with the burning
strike a little
[Music]
bit wow it's got quite a hard shell to
break you know what to do boy
get
him
o did I just add a b to my
B yeah the head have to attack from the
front oh my
God sick of
tole sick of
tole you L
it there boy
get
[Music]
him you know what to do for
me get
him sick of
tole over here D
boy
can I attack him from the back on Tail
as
well oh my God why is so
annoying you know what to do boy oh
there we
go oh [\h__\h] I I wasted it the got I
canceled
it sick
to oh well sick of tole still got
8K how much did I get before that when I
had all four of
them get
him okay okay okay you know what to do
boy oh my Precision counter goes for the
shell sick
tole
8.6 black blood that better have been
worth
it cuz that was so off my actual path
[Music]
anyway
careful there's the
bees was not worth it oh well but
hopefully at least we got some good XP
from it right
right oh I skill
points do I get skill points it's only
from Level UPS or from each
fight no holding
[Music]
back my skills oh yeah oh my God there's
a colorful
choco interesting why are most
choos that color and then there's a few
that are different it's like a pile chle
B we're completing Quest also
for using the
skill
chest Cal
[Music]
chest okay they're protecting it for
real for
[Music]
real keep your
distance sick of
tole special bre yeah it's a way CH B
different
attribute
oh oh that's the the new
on the new
[Music]
skill e it's fast don't know if it does
much more damage than the other one but
probably only if you used as a
counter but s using as a counter by like
switching
over you got to be ready for
that I so pretty
Bluebird should I fight it these ones
aren't meant to be F fought but this one
this one is actually an enemy so get him
boy he just see those
magic burst combos oh my God it's it's
it it's got literally zero point this
thing I feel bad for the to you know
what to do a perplexing amount of
a call the others into fight I'm killing
Twitter don't worry Elon Musk already
killed Twitter it's not
me I'm not at
fault
is there any item here I don't like the
camera it's like hard to see when I when
I move the
camera I don't know if it's as hard to
see for you guys but it's not so nice on
my
eyes I wish there was like a like a
quick adjust you know what I mean like
uh I think they had that inails of a
rise you just press like L L2 or or R2
company
ah the motion
blur and then when you press that you
would quickly have it
refocused but yeah
um so we lower it you guys were saying
something about motion blur blur since
the
beginning wait uh wait I'm in a
[Music]
fight all right Wawa does not stay from
a
fight this is
fine I wonder I should tell you a
tangent what could I tell you
about it's over you know
what's keep your distance
[Music]
boy oh this
is this is a million times better I
think or is it oh yeah it's a bit
better what was
that
see still not ideal I know I mean yeah
it's mostly better mostly easier on my
eyes no l free R free doesn't do
anything to send to the
camera there's there doesn't seem to be
a button for
that any updates on your vision I sent
in my application
today I hope they at least don't
completely ignore it and give it a
chance and I hope they check out the
YouTube
channel I'm afraid the Abby is not open
for public prayer
M gger go with you to look at the other
things turns out I could have just
auditioned came to offer a donation
without a song from
Mara and just say I audition with my
voice and just put in a cover or
something
else I
yeah last year it wasn't possible then
please they changed the rules this
year but it's okay it's okay
okay it's okay this at least I think
impresses and also now I have my next
single I want done really
early so I can father work on Coro com
for the pain and stuff for a long time
hi narissa
if I don't want to die
alone it's all right I'm here
who are these
people Martha's
bearers she entrusted them to my care
that I might ease their
suffering to the extent that I
can for the time they have
left today
Sunday I'll I'll put up my schedule
after the stream cuz I already have it
ready
mhm the curse has taken
them all of
them as it does every Bearer forced to
use their gift with each draw on The
Ether their bodies petrify oh till All
That Remains is Stone and pain and so
they are cast
aside there is nothing either Martha or
I can do to change that but we can at
least strive to make their final hours a
little more
barable it's a [\h__\h]
pun have faith my son for you shall rise
again and find the happiness denied you
in this
life I'm sorry thank you Father it's
their fault for saying beable to a
bearer oh he's turned into a statue
completely
I must offer you my own thanks for the
medicine you so kindly
brought now their final moments maybe
moments of
peace I have to wor
the price bearers and dominance pay for
channeling a through their bodies the
gradual petrification of their flesh it
does not affect those who use a crystal
to cast Magics beginning with a
stiffness and ache in the
extremities as the curse progresses
limbs are rendered immobile immobile and
the pain
unbearable at last the victim turns
completely into stone and their body
crumbles into
dust when when does it happen like why
does why does it not happen to us right
now are we channeling it
differently a person with the power to
cast Magics without a crystal inv Val on
men and women who awaken as bearers are
enslaved oh they are marked with a brand
upon their cheek and used as tools a
cheaper alternative to the scars and
precious shards this system of slavery
has persisted for centuries and has
become so ingrained in valan life that
few take pity upon the bearer's plight
interesting we were we became a bearer
by being
blessed though
right we got the mark
afterwards after the whole Joshua
thing
and but these people just that are born
like that just randomly doesn't have to
do with their parents just
random not exactly the same thing when
next you see a dominant not a but wasn't
I first a
dominant first
be now I'm a dominant I mean I guess I
was always a dominant but I was
considered to be a barer
first but also didn't it say baras and
dominance are affected by this
we should get back to Martha's rest yeah
yes we
should well not
a basically it's what I'm saying so yeah
I'm
special yeah cuz I'm a noble that's why
I didn't become a slave
but they marked me because of that of me
being captured m
s this
s still don't like the camera
movement turns out I'm special I was
special all
[Music]
along they they underestimated me and my
power yep yep
yep they Channel a better and
bar let me
go item item item item there item to get
the
[Music]
item I don't like it when the when I put
the camera somewhere and then it goes
like back you
see it's freaking M me out of my ey
[Music]
guys turn
off what
what oh shut up I'm not looking at that
[Music]
now is
it one of
these
M
okay I think I
think but then I got to do all the work
with the camera that's fine for
[Music]
now
ah you're back thanks for taking care of
that the Abbott had a message for you
thanks for taking care of that two more
have
succumbed dominating the
camera come
upstairs stairs stairs come
upstairs so now you know eh
I've seen plenty of bearers die on the
battlefield was my training partner but
never like that and all because they
were born different the powers that be
can't take away their gift so they strip
them of their Humanity instead what do
you mean oh there's plenty who p a
bear's plight but so long as we're
content to sit around weeping for those
on Whose Broken Backs were carried we
ain't going to Chang
nothing and so you l s your strength
what little of it I have use profits
from this place to buy the poor boogers
so when the abber told us the bearers
were yours I they're my property at
least by law property any still fit to
work fetch a price beyond my means all I
can do is care for those who are past
manding
manding but it's not all doom and gloom
Bon's finished fixing that bridge for
you you can carry on to East pool now
you got questions that need answering
ain't you well I wish you luck thank you
Martha oh I almost forgot Sid and I have
other friends in resera wear this and
they'll know you for one of
us mm slumbering to I know that you will
always be welcome
here slobbering like those choco that I
slaughtered
outside you were right
said it really is them Lord rosfield and
Lady Warick have come back to us yes and
long may they stay it to be us thank you
thank
you welcome to the
cult yay
oo level up again let's
go mhm
okay so motion were you saying that
because you wanting me to promote what
I'm uploading
[Music]
tomorrow or
what first plus side quest okay
Sid ah Clive you're not where I left you
hurt your
hand I did
I with a thousand little lightning bolts
oh [\h__\h] can't fling them around the way
I used to
[\h__\h] is he being
petrified think of it as my decoration
for long service and exemplary
misconduct
but you didn't come here to compare War
wounds we
didn't thank you Sid for
everything if you want to leave that's
your Lookout I'm sure you'll have a long
and happy life together if you stay out
of my way
Sid
hold
on I knew a girl back in the day uh-huh
she was a slave to her fight just like
you I wanted to save
her we're talking about the bee
girl for a while I even thought I
couldn't
but just cuz you think something doesn't
make it
true
Sid I'm no savior just a conceited old
fool I talk about people forging their
own
Futures but instead of handing them the
hammer I beat them with my
own and if no booger wants to listen to
what you've got to to say you might as
well keep your Gob
shut but Clive I will say
this you're not a monster you're the
same man you've always been accept that
and you may yet Escape your
fate my
fate
[Music]
look L you've had a hard
life and I don't see it getting much
[Music]
easier you might not be able to save
anyone
else but at the very least you can save
yourself I'll
try and Jill
I'm sorry we didn't get a chance to talk
but I trust you'll take good care of the
boy yes I
[Music]
will is that the last of it hey we best
head back then wouldn't want to keep n
waiting all
that no stay with
us
holding
[Music]
on
okay where is this side quest with the
excl uh no it wasn't an exclamation mark
what was
it I don't see
one the plus I hear the L you
[Music]
go they're just normal
ones should promote that thing I don't
know like the reason why I'm not making
a big deal out of it is
because well it's a released song If it
was a song that I haven't released yet
Martha said the blight it's PR even
further south you know that you guys
haven't heard yet monsters done with it
then I would make a bigger deal out of
it along the way it's okay guys have to
keep don't worry so much about
it I'm not stealth dropping it I'm
uploading the schedule today and I'm
making reservation
for the music video right after the
stream wor don't worry don't worry
people will see that it's going
up they will see it don't worry don't
worry
[Music]
well not
as I wouldn't make more hype out of
sleeptalking
MV and pineapple MV you know those are
like proper
M this is more like a lyric
video yeah oh but it's tgw next is still
not retrospective I'm waiting for the
8bit drummer to do
[Music]
retrospective oh
yeah interesting wait I have a chest I
think they have a chest oh yeah okay
that's fine that's fine
and there
boy give me
fire don't let them get
away give them all you've got for
you you know what to
goling get him PGW is an amazing song I
agree with that
to and I wish I had the budget to do
something greater but I have literally
no budget by the way my the this the the
motion capture suit that I was trying to
get I'm still trying to get
it m we're getting there finally closer
and
closer um today I got the billes that
was
thankfully thankfully I say because uh
yeah well that was a mistake in the
bill
thankfully
because the price was insane
16,000 no 17 16 or
177,000 I was like wait it wasn't
supposed to be that
expensive so I looked at it and I was
like wait wait wait wait wait one thing
that we can
still change here to get a little bit
lower is because they um gave me the
they put the year subscription of the uh
there's like a cloud that you have to
use if you want to do like streaming I
think was for
streaming and there's a yearly or a
monthly one and I was thinking I don't
need the yearly one I'm just
anyway and the yearly one is 2,500 well
the monthly one is working now oh 250
just in the month where you actually use
it you have to like renew your
subscription but you
know but then still it's still [\h__\h]
expensive the one thing that's like the
most expensive is the gloves those are
7,000 bucks it's cheaper than the
suit which isn't really really a proper
suit
but the the gloves are
insane but they're pretty good gloves
for what they
do there but I'm like you know I I I I'm
if I wasn't in a difficult position
right now financially then I wouldn't
you know worry so much about it but um
I'm worried that if I buy this now then
I maybe can't pay my next um
um uh uh taxes that I'll I have upcoming
in
November I don't know it should be fine
I
think oh yeah can you spread it out I
don't know it will be um taken from
my um Sal monthly salary
from cover cuz I made it so that it goes
for cover instead of going for me
will be deducted so if you think about
it I'll be paying less
taxes in a way
but yeah I was able to arrange it I kind
of had to because they made it so
complicated if I were to buy it on my
own
ooh I'm not going to fight you
bro oh those five kills are not wor come
in
here oh
lag actual FPS drop I think for a
second oh interesting that one is
interesting because they have a chest
there I don't see one here let's go over
there fight that
thing yeah it's basically this is one
thing I was questioning in my head like
trying to grasp the logic of
it is it
here am
I if I if I buy it myself and then ride
it off versus if I buy it through cover
and it's taken off my
salary in the end am I paying the same
amount of taxes or am I paying less in
one
way uh doing it one way what the [\h__\h]
what what what the
[\h__\h] will will it get come down to the
same there boy you're making me second
guess if the suit is wor it I'm also
second guessing
actually but I need it uh because that
was the plan of what I was going to use
for uh sleep
[Music]
talking [\h__\h]
man you know what to do boy
don't let them get
away I don't know if it's really wor
honestly only if I'm going to
do be for a long long time I
guess for now it will take a while for
me
to make it worth it know what to do boys
get back
[Music]
to wait I wanted to use the rip scam but
that was too get him
boy give them all you've got
boy you know what to do
[Music]
boy weekly for you scam but then the
problem with that is this honestly it
really loses this time it's um novelty
get and people will end up not really
caring about it and not coming to it
just because it's
a 3D stream especially cuz I can't even
even even when you say 3D I can't even
do like special stuff like 3D concerts
like the cover Studio does on my own I
could do like stuff like ringfit stream
and really really good tracking I could
do some kok streams with really really
good tracking but that's the extent I
can't change angles I can't do like all
that kind of fancy
[Music]
[\h__\h]
training it's not an issue but I think
it it's better to space it out don't
make that's why that's why I will do a
monthly subscription cuz I don't want to
do it too often but at the same time I
need to get my money's worth it's
difficult but for for me it's mostly for
making more 3D music
videos um I could make 3D music videos
without choreographies but I see it as
one of my specialties to have 3D music
videos with proper dancing in
it and I don't want to let someone else
do it I want to do it
myself I was here
already and for that I will make this
purchase I
guess simply also just because of my
principles yeah so for example the
windmills I would probably renew my
subscription when I am making a music
video and then for that month I will
also plan some fry k or something like
that I guess and then there might be
like one or two months without oh
sorry without fre the
[Music]
streams I remember coming here with
hopefully we'll
get a very different place about
then oh thank you
guys thank you yeah I remember coming
here
too
oh 10 bloody Heights mate HIDs mate I
want to go up
there good
plan epic music for bumping some
goats oh hello think up now my
darling um this lady thinks that she can
talk to her
[Music]
plants we better think of more
ideas well
I can do more stuff
like uh I can do like dance shots
choreography like dance practice videos
ah I can do I can do a lot of things I
can do the thing that I was planning to
do a while ago but I ended up not doing
because
the the way my current motion capture
Solutions at home work are not as good
um I wanted to do
like try to make a Coro graphy for whole
life member songs that aren't my own
that don't have a choreo yet for example
also I could do a lot more shorts yeah
yeah I was just about to say yeah yeah
yeah in one of those months where I have
the subscription I can focus and make a
lot of uh YouTube shorts to upload later
on dancing YouTube
shorts the gloves are very precise you
may do some pretty magic too oh I wonder
what I could do with that I I should
talk to Amy maybe she has some ideas too
me and Amy could somehow maybe maybe I
can stream my motion to her I wonder if
we could do something together with our
high high
quality motion capture things quiet
isn't it she even mentioned before that
she could do
something um remotely you you're Clive
rossfield
it's me Hannah Rodney Murdoch's wife
lady
[Music]
Hanna oh I knew it was you you haven't
changed at all guy was Rodney again
Maris what does he look like it's so
good to see you both
again oh
she's it's good to see you guy who
trained
me
M
A she recognized us immediately I did
not recognize my childhood bestie girl
if you have time you simply must come
back to the house I haven't much to
offer but what is mine is
[Music]
yours we should be
delighted skill issue
no I don't think those those are
wondering the world ever since I don't
think any of those excuses that you guys
are coming up with work I can well
understand fleeing from those iron blood
brots but oh to take to the road at such
a tender
age yeah it is what it is oh how he's so
conscious
self-conscious it uh wasn't easy but we
survived and and now we're
back it it's wonderful to see you great
tldr we survived and now we're
back
wow so Much Death in those
words
I guess we did it we just we're
alive do you think you will stay here in
East pool we did something now we're
here still enjoys the mother Crystal's
blessing does it not you could always
move this house holds a lot of memories
for
me so long as I can live here in peace
here I shall
stay
not that it matters the capital is
closed to civilians by order of The
Duchess or should I say her Imperial
Majesty annabella's marriage to the
Emperor of SRE heralded a great many
changes
here yes of course oh forgive me I I
didn't mean
to
please there is nothing to
forgive
oh that [\h__\h] would my mother not make
an exception for you and your
husband surely she would not refuse the
Lord
Commander
ah you haven't heard
then Rodney passed away on the night of
the
fire he never returned from Phoenix
gate oh
I I'm
sorry
Clive
Cliff hangry my poor child you look pale
all this traveling must have taken its
toll I insist you rest we can talk
later
C
we killed all that was here are you sure
you don't want to sleep
inside but not all I
can't not after what I
did Lady Hannah said she would prepare a
change of clothes for you in the
morning she really has been very
kind
13 years of
killing 13
years without the faintest glimmer of
hope
oh
[Music]
he it was only Joshua that kept me
going
I swore that I would avenge his
death that I would kill his
killer that was the only thing that gave
my life any
meaning but if it was me who killed
Joshua and Murdoch and all the
others then why the hell am I still
breathing
I ask myself the
same when I
fought hundreds
died there were so many
bodies so many lives cut short in their
Prime that day in Delia
I I wanted to join them I wanted it all
to
end I I couldn't bear it anymore if
living meant being that better to be
just another
[Music]
body I'm
sorry do you remember that night on the
balcony when we looked up at the the
moon I said a prayer to mea and that
prayer was
answered what was
it you came back to
me the heavens must have a plan for
us
close close so
close
oh this is I was hoping that there would
be explanation for that now the burning
red star that sits beneath the moon
folklore ascribes to Mia the role of
message Bearer to the moon so this
common common custom across Vala to wish
upon a star that once heartfelt desires
might be conveyed to the heavens and
Beyond
H but what what if it's not a
star what if
it's something
else we should get some
rest an
LED good night
Clive sleep well
what what happened what happened to C
thank you lady Hanna perhaps now people
will not flee at the sight of
me you look just like elwin did when he
was your
age how did you come to have some of my
father's old
wow well before elwin became Arch duuke
our families would often summer together
he and me were like brothers tripping
these clothes have been in a wardrobe
for years collecting cobwebs along with
everything
else is this like a uniform why does it
why would this I'm very grateful for
them and sorry for depriving you of your
memories not at all why would this help
it's what your father would have wanted
they suit you
well but why would it help to make
people not so scared of me or what yes
thank you you've been most kind no I
should thank you I know it's from the
father been for a short while but seeing
you again took me back to happier times
[Music]
fair you oh cuz Okay my Lord the
previous one was in parallel okay see
that's what I wanted to
[Music]
know all right we both are in our proper
drip now character appearance oh can
change the outbut appearance
not if we follow the road to the North
she it should take us all the way to
Phoenix gate let's go
[Music]
sheesh
she I'm not sure this arice will see us
through
winter maybe I got a phoenix Haw eye
anywhere else to Goblin
[Music]
coin this
chest side of chest Mooky
Mooky Mooky mie
Cliff I'll just call him
Cliff open the gate
you those are
elins by the
Flames you're his
firstborn Clive rosfield you're
mistaken no it's right it's
correct oh you can't fool me my Lord
you're the very image of your father and
that would be true even if you weren't
wearing his clothes the selfsame
garments Hannah was keeping for you if
I'm not mistaken she always swore that
she would never part with them until the
day elwin's Sons returned a and now that
day has
come why you'll be able to take your
bearers back as
well let Baris
what
talk talk forgive me master may I was a
child when last I came to East pool I
didn't recognize you oh I'd be surprised
if you recognized anything at all much
has changed since Rosaria fell to the
Empire not least for the bearers who
once served her noble
[Music]
families when the iron blood sacked
Rosel 13 years back many who lost their
masters fled here in search of sanctuary
and never
returned I the plan was to send them
home once we won back the capital but
then the Imperials are arrived roseria
became a province of sanre are they
looking for the they no longer had any
home to
return like what are they doing back in
your father's day any Bearer who lost
their Master became a ward of the duche
we'd hand them over to the sheriffs and
they'd be assigned a new position but
when we saw how The Empire treated their
branded we knew that wasn't an
option so they've been here ever since
and now you want to give them to me give
them to me like how they're yours by
right Lord rosfield bequeathed you by
your late father on paper and they'd be
better off serving you than hiding here
indeed many of them used to serve your
house and still considered the Ros
Fields their masters I'm no one's Master
yeah let them be free
[Music]
we don't need they wouldn't be safe with
me
slaves I
understand you'll forgive an old man his
fanciful Notions been daydreaming for
too long but still I would ask a favor
of you a small
Mercy if it is within my power one of
the bearers is an elderly fellow who
still swears absolute loyalty to Arch
duuke elwin I don't ask that you take
him into your service only that you meet
with him let him see that elwin's son
still lives and that he's as fine a man
as his father ever was it would be my
honor you can't say that thank you my
Lord he sits by the well most days
watching the people go about their
business if you could show him your face
I would be most grateful
[Music]
okay a fine as in my beauty as fine a
man as my father in my booty you're not
so very different you know especially
dressed like that come on let's go and
meet that Bearer b b
to if you're buying I'm
selling you're buying I'm
selling where should my we only had one
safe
travels or did I sell
one if you're buying I'm
shallon I sold
it so confused I thought I was in the
right
window oh Mama Mia here you
go safe
travels sure this AR
[Music]
he's not
here well I can't leave without meeting
him I've led the mayor down once already
it would be cruel to disappoint him
again all right let's ask
around someone must have seen him okay
about I'll grab a rank or maybe actually
let me wrapped socks my feces are
[Music]
cold
I didn't I didn't touch any cats I I
totally
[Music]
didn't L not roasted anymore from the
summer
yeah I it still gets weirdly um warm in
my apartment so I turned on like some
cooling system let me get
[Music]
Chunky
cute
soft she is the epit of
[Music]
softness oh my God no I did touch
smoothie before now I'm bringing chunky
wonky over she was sleeping on a pile of
clothes from
[Music]
me
hello my chunky you're so so
[Music]
happy oh cat break have
Heavenly Heavenly cat
break oh okay bye-bye there's so much to
grab so much to touch so much chunk to
squeeze
[Music]
okay they do clearly love me but that
was um he was making like kind of like m
uncomfortable
noises just a little bit of
complaining well now unfamiliar
faces what brings you to East pole
Travelers I'm hand me for an elderly
Bearer let me go you wouldn't happen to
have seen him would you ah you mean the
old boy who always waits by the well yes
that's
him what business do you have with him
if you don't mind me
asking you're not from the capital too
are you we are yeah in a way so cute
when they well then it's a pleasure to
meet I was born and raised down Market
Street and never would have left if Arch
Duke elwin had survived the fire it
weren't the same when The Duchess took
over though all the beatings the
evictions going up and up and up even as
the blight took half the
Harvest oh listen to me telling you what
you already know I'm sorry I'm afraid I
can't help you with your Bearer either
though I doubt you'll have gone far he
comes there every day almost as if he's
waiting for something we'll keep asking
around then thank
[Music]
you well she doesn't like hate me
holding her she's just impatient and I
was holding her up to the microphone so
I was like what you
doing good day my
lady what can I do for you are you I'm
looking for a bearer an elderly fellow
who used to serve the Ros Fields have
you seen him ah that old Lon gry no no
sign of him today funny he's usually
down by the well at this hour cooking up
his fantasy Feast fantasy Feast I'm
sorry oh he worked in the kitchens at
roset Castle back in the day still
thinks he's there now it often hear the
poor fool chatting away to the arch
duuke Living in a Dream he is but better
there than here I suppose can't imagine
the vicine stopping to trade tales with
a bearer can you
no anyway you'll be around here
somewhere thank you well thank you
byebye
um don't you guys also when you play
these games privately Mo am Mo young
Patrick the choc ball keeper might know
just skip through it like this like
that's I rarely play games privately
anymore making you do this I feel bad
for not listening to dialogue fully if
we're to keep up the stream come on
let's head for the Stables a lot yes
sometimes sometimes but at least like
this kind of side talk main
conversations maybe not so much but like
like the wonder if Martha could these
kind of things where you just have to
talk to like five
villagers
yeah where the bloody El also cuz like
the the voice acting will be often much
longer is something the matter than the
time Bearer I've been minding Take My
Eyes Off him for one minute and he he's
not in his usual spot by the well nor
anywhere else in the village
you must be Patrick I am but and this
Bearer you're looking for he's an
elderly man who used to work in the
roosth castle kitchens yes that's a fell
yeah okay how you know all this I've
never seen you in East pool before but
you seem to know the place better than I
do
myself we're from
here
N N I see fu fu wow interesting go ah so
that's how it is well then if you're
acting under orders of the mayor you're
on a bound to help me find him he's been
losing what little sense he had left of
late saying the sheriffs are coming to
collect him and that he needs to go back
to the castle I was supposed to watch
over him keep him out of trouble
understood you keep searching here we'll
look for him outside
thank you I'm in your okay he's gone
insane no but I generally like listening
to dialog hased into trouble in my
stream let's just concentrate on finding
him especially in a game like this where
everything's like acted out
properly there's like motions for
everything it's just so even further
detailed oh wa it's over here
yeah it's not just like for example like
some games just have a picture
PNG for
dialogues but okay that's like their
style and how they do it sure but this
is like more interesting to look
at it's pretty it's like a
movie look at the
Scarecrow look and now I'm here there's
someone over
there
it might be him we should
hurry did he give
up after all these years we can't lead
them to the old man they need to die
we'll fight and then he'll be like oh
this style of fighting I recognize it
you are you
are yes I am get
him it's over
stay
down over
here don't let them get
away ability finish oh wait what I
here
boy King your distance
boy
get him
boy I think especially cuz he seems to
be
like senile maybe he'll think I'm I am
my father
yeah
farewell you're slow paced
gamer well then you have so much to
enjoy
that's nice you can take your
time he didn't watch he didn't notice
what's been not going on behind him my
friend come on let's go
home Lord Lord Ross you came for me I
waited for you so long but you finally
came I'm not who you
think Clive close enough
yes pray forgive my long delay it's
nothing Your
Grace I prayed to the founder that you
would come and at long last he answered
will we be returning to the castle
then there is still a place for me in
the kitchen no my friend a we will not
be returning to the castle not yet man
I'm on a very important Expedition one
which may take some
time could
you wait for me in East pool until my
journey is complete I will come back for
you
then I
promise of course your grace for you I
would gladly wait until my dying
day this is how old kfp was will be
a
no I'd rather have you guys Forget Me by
that
time thank you both of you you've been
most kind the memory of serving the late
Arch Chief was this one light in the
darkness God and now that light burns a
little more brightly it's nothing but a
fantasy of course but it's better than
the truth of the matter a damn sight
better the blight is on our doorstep our
harvests are failing the people are
leaving in
droves if it weren't for Lady Hannah
selling half her worldly Goods to
provide for the few of us who stayed
behind we would long since have
starved we want to keep the bearer safe
here we really do
but unless a miracle happens we won't be
able to spare a crust of bread to share
between them soon enough let them just
eat cake is it really that bad so bad I
even petitioned the Imperial Garrison to
take them but when they found out where
they'd come from they damed near spat in
our faces jcal dogs they called them
enemies of the Empire I know a man named
Sid who would gladly give a home to any
Bearer in need of one leave this with
me as soon as I return from Phoenix gate
I'll speak with him thank you my
Lord will you be passing through East
pool on your way back I should very much
like to speak with you again if you have
the time regarding the future of the
village and what might be done for Lady
Hannah after all she's done down for us
yes of
course I'll be back on Fair you well my
Lord my lady I wish you a safe
journey thank you long time no
see a I I appreciate that hearing that I
was more like thinking of you know but
generally I want I would of course
appreciate you guys following me as long
as you can but I was talking about a
very
very um long to go scenario
where maybe you guys are seeing all and
don't you you you're confused and you're
like keep asking oh but where's where
where is the
WWA when does Wawa stream start even
though you know it's like in 50 years 60
years I she she hasn't said k a key to
me in a
[Music]
while
oh watching if you guys have like kids
and then your kids will turn on one of
my bods and and you'll be like oh oh
she's live again honey she's live again
my
wow key she said There She
Goes
a thinking it's
live oh
man but you
know that's why I said maybe I'd prefer
you guys to forget
me instead of Clinging On to a long gone
past oh she's still the
same after all these years streaming for
60 70 years I've been watching her every
day and she's still the
same that I actually in my like family I
haven't experienced any like that I just
see it
in videos TV shows or YouTube videos and
stuff and it just seems like really hard
to deal with and like
sad you
know when
some when when age makes
you yeah what's it called what's it
called the Deads are rly named Alzheimer
I didn't realized they were this close
no wonder their crops are failing the
blight is leading the ether from and
when the last drop is drain their fields
will turn to this I remember this path
no plants no animals no life yeah you
monsters recognize that's one small
Mercy people you should recognize or
when
you when
you
when you forget things all the time
what's this another relic of the
Fallen there's a crystal in there and it
seems just really really difficult to
deal with
no
heartbreaking we won't be able to use
any magic here another thing to worry
about as if the absence of ether didn't
cause enough problems no take away the
land's life force and problems are all
this
left everything's dead I can hardly
imagine what this place used to look
like before the blight took it I
remember it
was no info about the blight okay the
blight I would have liked to a refresher
on like how how the blight is caused
maybe you guys can give it to me
dead
no I don't know yet oh okay well
then there it
is Phoenix
gate sometimes when I don't know
something I feel like I must have missed
something
wrong I feel bad for admitting
it
come on Clive but then it turns out I
shouldn't have known it
anyway it's time to discover the
truth cuz when I do already when I
should already have the knowledge and
then I ask you you guys are some of you
guys are like I already told you oh my
God she forgot she's not
listening I'm
trying you guys already always should
consider
that when you stream a
game it's hard to take some things in
all the
time you
know difficult Phoenix gate
ruins that's why I like the low button
in this game you it's
helpful to burn the details into my
brain
[Music]
H maybe I have dementia
already no no I I'm I'm
certain it's almost as if time has stood
still I want to play a bit
longer we're not at 5 hours even
yet I suppose no one had any cause to
return
here
my hands are really recovered right now
they don't feel
exhausted yesterday was so many battles
Like A Rush of
battles today's not so
bad let's have a look
around oh I got a long part coming up
oh okay you mean after that long
part could I have done this break could
anyone just walking
now oh oh
sheesh
um you're saying this crater was caused
by
me
I'm a
meteor well me and Joshua right Y what
is it
to
K
no that's him if it's really Joshua why
is he B anyone who can tell me what
happened I have to
know uh dude that that's the only person
here
where is he nowhere to be
seen damn it he's like a bloody
eel what is this place anyway some sort
of
shrine sorry you've never been been here
before this is the Hall of the gate the
gate it's a relic of the Fallen only the
Phoenix's dominant can open it maybe we
can do hence the Castle's
name this was where Joshua was supposed
to do
what yes he would have stepped through
this door the next morning and listened
to the words of our like that too that
we found the side would you have gone
with him side path thing no the otry is
Holy Ground none but the dominant may
enter would have stood guard and prayed
for my brother's safe
return we did go
there where the hell did he
go perhaps he went
inside he couldn't have he'd need the
power of the Phoenix
well he's lacking critical
information if we think he could could
not be in there why are we now trying to
get in
there okay let's give it a
try show
yourself it
works
all
right thank you
Joshua are you sure about
this never more maybe Joshua is evil
because he's like
more like his mother his hair
color this General
visuals another
gate let's see if this one opens it
takes after his new
mom since I was always more like my dad
could this place really be a fallen ruin
who hardly call it a
ruin it's perfect like it was built
yesterday looks insane
that's not why we were
fighting looks so
cool what it has an opening
there maybe we can go up there
too have you ever seen anything like
this
it will come to life won't
it like protecting this
place good morning
[\h__\h] ohuh what elevator
oh
ah oh
speeda or
crap
speeda what do we do fight the
usual what kind of question
[Music]
them get him get him get him get him get
him get him get him get him get him get
him get him get
him oh they're
easy get
him sick of tole
oh don't let them get
[Music]
away I like this battle
music oh I don't think Joshua would have
had
trouble more
trouble speaking of trouble it's
the defense not Death Star in
miniature get
him give them all you've got
boy hey what sick of
tole guda lend me your strength get him
boy keep your distance
[Music]
boy sick of
tole there
boy get them boy Star Wars lightsabers
oh yeah they do how can these things
light How can any of
this this must be what the Fallen ruins
were like before they
fell
cool looks
insane so pretty this game is so
pretty yeah I know Final Fantasy usually
also has uh some like cool modern
stuff mixed in to their medieval looking
fantasy
[Music]
world SciFi
St
boy get them all you've got
[Music]
boy
eh yeah tailes off games also do that a
lot
but not always I
think like adding sci-fi
elements it's not a
must
wow
this this section reminds me of one
section in near
tomata I don't know if you guys know
which one I'm talking about but that was
just a very specific one I think wrong
direction or
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah I think it was
right before meeting the the red
ladies
maybe oh thank
you MH
mhm people like to
say I
didn't what what's the critique I didn't
take in the story properly or something
like
that and have the the right
reaction I don't [\h__\h] know what
that's about looks like it can take a
beat oh big fight and let's give it
one
oh oh two times
oh see you know what to do
boy
sick also seems like I missed the 50%
window let me switch
[Music]
to okay lots of new cool
stuff keep a distance Bo wake
win let's
go you know what to do for me oh get out
of there too
late try to get out of there with
dodging but probably easier to
it to though get out of there with just
normal
walking
a no I'm I'm dodging too late not this
time no [\h__\h] oh his timing is
r no no no no
no y b get him boy he's got
me he's got me
good
not this
time get him
boy oh thank God
okay you know what to do
fory how do you make it out of there
quickly
give them all you've got
boy sick of
[Music]
tole over here do backwards
well trying get him boy need to end this
quickly just what I okay he's almost
dead I don't know why I just took the
pic but
oh
keep your distance
boy [\h__\h]
me there's a
good sick of tole there boy oh oh take
this you know what to do
does any of this make sense to
you let's find the hooded man and leave
[Music]
she he's
got uh very very many Qui fancy attacks
the favor of wind oh forgot go gosh gosh
go go
gosh I want to use that cuz I use go a
lot go go 15%
so
you wait a second actually let me check
how many points 890
890 I could upgrade Scarlet Cyclone or
actually while we're at it let me
upgrade
goou increases followup strike
speed followup strike
speed refund Rising Flame
uh should we just unlearn it
completely no I guess I still have it
right
okay
then let me put one in scared
cyclone
and okay that's it that's it for
now
I don't think we really say
that I potion oh thanks for the potions
I used up so many give me more give me
more
yikes bomb what the hell are they
whatever they are I don't think they're
friendly uh how long until they explode
or do they explode when they
die not this
time over
here okay okay okay okay okay I think
it's
exploding
ah so that wasn't even so close
to uh give them all you've
got sick tole it's
death quite
early get him
boy you know what to do boy get him
boy over here not
mother there it
is oh wait
attack I was trying to get away but I
was confused why this bomb is even still
alive huh why did that one not explode
like the
others had the lock
on [\h__\h] the lock on
man is it this door
no thank you
dog oh it's
random
oh so this one just didn't want
to would Joshua have had to run this
Gauntlet too
no at least not that I ever heard about
I imagine the Phoenix would receive a
warmer welcome
so I see this more as a
test I feel like Joshua could have here
we go again where will we end up this
time surrounded by Contraptions held
bent on murdering her
wory could the hooded man really have
taken this path we won't know until we
followed it all the way to the end o
1,200 let's keep
looking
uh that looks like another big one this
won't be
easy and small one small small small
small small it's already starting with
low HP what what you know what to do
boy
what I know this are the not the not the
not the same bombs but uh okay you know
what to
de
no leave me alone leave me alone leave
me
alone there boy no leave me
alone no leave me
alone get
him I need
that not this time indeed not this
time sh
to I hate
you
oh ah
[Music]
hey oh I really hate this
enemy get
him it's not this time nice
nice uh
give them all you've got for
it nice nice nice nice nice nice nice
nice nice nice nice nice nice ni
ni sick of
to enemies a [\h__\h] you enemies all my
homies hate you what mean sick of
tole
smaller smaller enemies first
maybe but my my focus just goes on the
big
one uhoh I'm out of
ption not this
time I'm glad you're
here I'm going to
die get
him you know what what to do
boy get him
boy taking a bit of a distance to chill
for a little
bit and maybe focus on these
ones he
coming I'm die
[Music]
out get him boy get him that's it I'm
going down s tole get him sick him tole
over
here not this
time you know what to do boy oh
oh I was trying get
out get him boy you know what to do boy
sick him
tole you know what to do boy not this
time
oh don't let them get
away oh my God that was that was a good
good momentum that I had
there there boy hey but I want my
potions though I want my potions
though I want my potions
though
man I don't know I I just get good at
the end I got too good
[Music]
well okay would you guys like to kill
me not going to let it happen easily but
then but then if I get to the bus and I
have no
potion then it's not going to be first
try better get killed by these on so I
can have a first try TI to kill
me thank
[Music]
you is the is the boss soon though what
if I lose even more potions until then
is it
soon look out there's more of them
they'll full like the not that soon oh
well then we can do it twice maybe can't
do
it only 50% through okay then 50%
halftime is a good timing to get me some
potions get to restart before The Battle
Before the room
entering wait am I not getting potions
because I didn't go through the battle
that much oh we're being
welcomed oh no they are potion being
welcomed with the bomb already get
him give them all you've got
boy you know what to do
boy get him oh [\h__\h]
wait
[Music]
over here stay
down this one doesn't want to explode
okay
fine fine we
have
uh what do you call it again when you
make a bomb not
explode
oh Rooks Gambit oh but I'm going to stay
with the G diffused yes we have diffused
the p
with with
pure aggression for our
hands and
swords keep talking and nobody
explodes ooh
o
huh has narissa played that before I
wonder like this if not she should play
with
me keep talking with me Nissa and nobody
explodes oh
W seems to feelings Mutual what uh
design all right bring it on good that I
got some
potions get
him don't let them get
away
ni wow
sexy simply too sexy for this game not
this
time get him
boy get them all you've got
[Music]
boy deadly T
down there boy
not this time sick tole where's my
counter get
[Music]
him
oh King a distance
Point look at all that damage look at it
look at it look at
it and look at it
more
you know what to do boy how much was
that I didn't look at the final number
there boy what what what do it mean
press what does that mean what does that
mean what thaty what does that mean what
does that mean press the attack 12K okay
what does that mean I don't
understand why is it purple do it all
okay long it isn't with
[Music]
me don't let them get away oh perfect
time for
B get up
boy sick up
too get
him keep your distance boy okay I did it
I did
it this is our chance yeah well I
already used like
everything little
[\h__\h] maybe it wasn't necessary to go so
[Music]
hard get
him there boy not this time where's my
coun
I mean that one I understand but before
when I'm actually doing the do there
boy sick
tole you know what to do
boy
oh don't let them get
away I don't have my go ready there it
is go go go go go go go go go
go get
him
easy I'm doing really well with this
one there is there's my counter there
was my
counter get
[Music]
him this
time you know what to
do I think I I definitely prefer bulky
big slow enemies over the fast
ones that's more my
style I like to have some time there we
go
easy
yay easier to read yeah easier to
prepare and
counter I'm in the groove baby
that was the
50% boss it
[Music]
seems seriously good thank
you feels good to really grasp the
combat it's good that I took some time
to understand it what are these
creatures my hands no they didn't hurt
attack us not really I mean they feel
kind of tense
but they don't H
yet not right now at
least they're probably asking themselves
the same
thing we're the ones trespassing here
they're just protecting their
home oh N N N Jill n look I'm
looking camera
change what am I looking at is that some
kind of mural it's worth a closer look
whatever it
is
that thing in the very back under the
glowing Stones looks more like I don't
know Garuda or so to me
oh
[Music]
potions
right I didn't even use so many
potions oh there's still chest I could
have like totally missed it just
now Wicked Wheel the one that I don't
wait do I use Wicked Wheel I don't think
I do
is this the way there's two ways I
think
I open the door
please the one that goes up in there
yeah totally not a ballerina no no no
circle shaped things that doesn't mean
battle no not at all
no oh we just finished a battle you're
throwing another one right away at
me didn't expect it that
fast what the [\h__\h] is
dead all right
then she like the Boss
[Music]
Rush
lit it looks like a fast one but
actually
no
get him
boy sick him tole sick
tole keep your distance
[Music]
boy oh
wa get
him ow oh that one
hurt sick of
tole get him oh okay okay okay focus
focus
let's let's Focus ST
boy oh I staggered him
uh give them all you've got
for let's
go combo combo one more one
more he almost 10
okay
OU oh I kind of saw that one coming as a
finishing move he wasn't quite done I
saw it coming and yet ah [\h__\h] I took two
potions I didn't want to take two
potions two high potions
[Music]
even nice
get him
oh he doesn't have that much HP actually
and another trigger
to give them all you've got for but I
guess it's because we're probably going
to have more
visitors T nice
finish it wasn't like the others it
would seem this place holds even more
secrets than we
thought
okay we opened this
door there's potion there
too not a lot of Health just likes to be
annoying it wasn't even that annoying
that was
fine
so we can go for this door but it felt
like I could also go for that
door maybe it doesn't
matter maybe it isn't that it doesn't
have a lot of HP maybe I'm doing more
damage look
out give them all you've got
[Music]
for that's
enough these ones are
weak as
[\h__\h] was that chunks of
w guys give me something what should I
tangent about I feel like wait let me
look at my do I have some
[Music]
notes now that we're constantly just
fighting and there's
no no
dialogue ah actually uh I guess I
started this tangent in
my um member
stream uh but just again for the people
who are not members so before I went to
Japan recently well that did something I
went to like
uh not stay over Resort right where I
went swimming they had like salt water
warm water Etc all kinds of cool stuff
oh new fight new big
fight
no
and what I'm confused and uh yeah so
when swimming I tried to learn a little
bit more um how to breathe properly when
going with my head on water while
swimming it's all practicing right one
weird thing
that
happened on that
day I noticed get
boy at some point like pretty late in
the
day there was like a group of people
where at least two people of the group
their face looked so similar to me uh
familiar not
similar familiar and what Happ here like
especially with one of fall actually
both I was like so sure that I know them
from like Anime
conventions and so I was like staring at
them hoping for them to
realize that it's me notice me what the
[\h__\h] is
that but they didn't they didn't get it
and so I was like hey maybe it's not
them but I can't help they look so
familiar
so shortly after I noticed what they
were talking about was anime convention
related and then I was like okay it's
them for sure I'm like 100% sure they're
like I know them from seeing them from
conventions but I don't think we really
talked much but I still think they
should recognize me too if I recognize
them it isn't a dead end after all
oh apparent but I stared at the directly
so much and our eyes
met and I ended up feeling like such a
creep I was I was like hoping for them
to like smile or something and be like
oh like have like a oh
moment but instead I just came across as
like a real creep I think staring at
them
endlessly like smiling
too I didn't want to I tried for like at
one moment I was like okay whatever I'm
just going to go there and like instead
of being a creep I'm just going to say
hi do you recognize me but
like I went there and then I couldn't
get
the like I swam over and I couldn't get
the the the courage I was like swimming
at them staring at one of them making ey
contact and then I then I was like right
next to them and then I lost the courage
and I was like I just looked
elsewhere and it was like awkward and
and they were probably thinking what the
[\h__\h] is up with this this girl why is
she staring at us for this whole
time but if I see them again uh at a
convention cuz I I later on I was so
bothered by this I was like looking
up uh on social media if I could find
them cuz I couldn't remember the name
either of yeah what their names were I
was looking it up and I found them but
the account was private so I couldn't
message them my plan was to apologize
and be like hey I was the the weirdo
that
was yeah looking at you hoping for a
reaction I guess you didn't recognize me
sorry for being a creep I couldn't say
that so instead uh next time I see them
at a convention I'm going to say hi that
was me you found
them yeah that's not the scary part I
was like 100% sure and I was right that
I know know them from conventions I know
that but
yeah relatable right like if you stare
at people I mean sometimes it's also the
other way around people will like stare
at me and be like hi and I'm like oh
wait who the [\h__\h] was
that but I will still like act as if I
know them all seems to lead to this room
like yeah hi what's in it it's been a
while put this time I was the other
party how old do you suppose this is
okay now it doesn't look like thousand
years more I don't know I've never seen
anything like it
before who is that in the middle do you
think you would have avoided
me
Tinus
that
again tiny
tussy
bro you you're
him the second dominant of Fire
who are
you yeah yeah but
just was
me there's like more than
one more than one cloaked
person yeah so the one that was standing
there when I first saw them that was
me
what the one that's always like
whispering to
me but why must it be so similar with
the way Joshua is running around right
now I'm
back
oh oh we're watching as it happened
we're watch watching it Joshua reliving
it but from a different POV which will
maybe tell us something about what
Happ please stop
Brom poor
[Music]
Phoenix oh is this where I learned time
travel
I did it I stopped
it I I did
this I killed him no he's not dead he
said Phoenix don't you get
it Joshua chose me to be his
shield he gave me his
Blessing and asked me to keep him
safe I should have protected him that
day o it was my
duty all the versions of
me
c yeah you get
[Music]
it I'm
sorry I failed you
[Music]
H Joshua
died I killed him and I blamed another
for what I did to spare myself the
guilt I feared to BU accepting it I
would lose what what was left of
me so I
ran from
everything and
now are you ready to accept the truth oh
that's like I
am I know it won't be easy but it's he's
brainwashing brainwashing myself Soul so
that Joshua's
Soul can finally rest in
peace
o he's judging
me oh
n Fire
handshake
what what's going
on
the [\h__\h] he's gone what the
[\h__\h] am I letting it kill
me remember to how bit to the truth that
awaits
me I will Press
On Come iFit show me who you truly are
[Music]
uh either their
demons have to fight my inner
demon
what I'm sorry but this just seems a
little bit absurd to
[Music]
me
I don't know if I want to be
[Music]
here bam yeah I have waited for it wait
for it wait for
itam
time can't see
[Music]
nice
ow couldn't get out of
[Music]
it that's fine though easy easy easy
easy easy easy so far but I'm expecting
some fun cinematic scenes
again that will help
[Music]
us too close for my own
good oh and I missed this
one going to get out here
[Music]
this
time
there we go even on this big fat monster
I can do a deadly Tak down
he
SC confus
you he where attacking the head no
o ah
wait
oh ah
uh did I did he just stay in the same
place and did I dodge it though I think
I
did I guess I'm still attacking the
leg
I dodged by standing still making him
not move much
either ouch ouch ouch hey hey hey hey
hey let's talk this out
oh
[\h__\h] this
[Music]
leg
come
[Music]
on there we go
finally yeah he's almost dead that went
pretty
well 12,000 without the the four ability
cuz I used it before he was
staggered go this
[Music]
time sh ah
I Wrong bad
[Music]
timing oh
uh
[Music]
oh there we
go don't let first try the times of
second tries are long
gone this
Phoenix has no time to waste I shall
first try it
all no match for
me
[Music]
but wait there's
more Dark Link style dark me
shadow
Cliff still you deny
it even when the truth's staring right
at
you come on
Clive face your fears you're crazy
crazy man oh man it's not going to mirr
on me though
[Music]
I too
slow not this time I know myself too
well even though he has attack I don't
[Music]
know
you want some you oh potion oh wait wait
wait I I I I'm good but uh I'm running
out of potions already
so
concerning
[Music]
concerning yeah we got to probably do it
redo it at least
once too far too far to
counter do be stagger is he a considered
a lightweight
enemy I
wonder guess I shall try it
out no he medium oh how did I do
[Music]
that
oo heavy heavy
heavy perfect
watch cuz I don't think I was attacking
in the moment I was like readjusting my
hand
what I know it was a Parry but I didn't
feel like I was
you'd help me learn my example doing it
right
[Music]
oh he's very
predictable I st say and then get [\h__\h]
but he is
[Music]
predictable oh oh stay in air should
have stayed in the air longer I
[Music]
couldn't was
that hummus and
Anvil
[Music]
humus
oh sometimes I forget what is
what uh thing I'm in and I try to get
closer to him with Phoenix ship FL to me
I
can't die a
hammer makes
sense okay that's fine that's fine
that's
fine sometimes you got to do this to get
some potions back I see molten me that
my example
wait didn't we get reset by a lot how
far not this time I feel like I was
already halfway
through
[Music]
oh too
slow too
[Music]
slow just got to get behind him and then
you get some free time to attack him
pretty
[Music]
noise uh there it
is nice Dodge R thank
[Music]
you you got me this
one not that I wasn't trying to dodge
but hey Counter
Strike I'm his favorite game
how are you letting me do this wait oh I
forgot I think did he just did he just
give me an opening Hellfire did he just
give me an opening
for the the green thing the circle
thing oh [\h__\h] I I was looking at the
chest
not this
[Music]
time got to D much more of
it this
[Music]
time
one more back cuz now it's reloaded so I
switched like two times this
[Music]
time
noce
oh very Dynamic we both
[Music]
are
there wait how does he still have so
much HP did he
heal I feel like I saw him at left I
need the
[\h__\h]
[Music]
let me let me attack
you what button do we need to
press 10 billion
HP Edy gives you more HP being my inner
demon
oh no escap eh me me it's all right I'm
done running from you get ready Chad
Here Comes
Peak give me more
power
me what's going on this is all in my
head
together it's all in my head
am I strong now it's time to find out
who we are once and for
all
oh
uh accepting the
TR had to think for a moment what that
was I'm you show yourself
fre oh I'm priming is this
priming
ouch
uh I feel faster and
[Music]
stronger sadly I already used two with
my
skills this we'll have to
[Music]
do everything's burning let's
go I'm so much
faster
yeah get down on your knees kneel in
front of me who is
you and so
[Music]
on
ooh time I'm so good I'm so good
I'm sorry guys you probably are like oh
my God it's such a queen yay like oh my
God you're so impressed by me and you're
probably like how can we ever
compare
yes she's too good for us
Queen become at
if
noow well me
too
[Music]
enough TR
now I am well we
are so
far
this dude is so
confused but he's got the
spirit
oh
Pro oh I don't have to
anything
[Music]
luxury
yes let's
go I love
my love my references to Tang top of
good and Lagan because if I think of
somebody using all their [\h__\h] power
what I think of is
that shadow Vanquish what do I leave no
more shadow on the floor
now pierce the
heavens
[Music]
yay oh epic epic
amazing wowy
togy we got a fire
Shard and
[Music]
Ashes so can I like
Prime at a certain point in battle now
like if I fill up the
bar limit
breaker
nice another way of getting
stronger
Limitless
power
acceptance Clive are you all right
no I guess
yes am I evil it's nothing seems kind of
evil I'll be
fine think I'm the
villain oh how was the bit rate in that
firefight huh can't couldn't have been
too
good no more chasing
Shadows the hooded man isn't
here we should go he isn't here cuz I am
the hood of man
no questions
asked
okay is
that is that representing
me instead of the Phoenix it's
representing me
actually
interestingly what fight couldn't see
anything
Clive it was
representing whatever it is you can tell
me wait a second do we learn something
new
[Music]
here uh it's just saying that it's me
now shocking
[Music]
revelation
no
no I had a hard enough time telling
myself I awakened as a dominant of fire
right here in this castle and I've been
running from it ever
since but now I know for
certain Who I Really
Am the second icon of fire who killed my
brother and burned this Castle to the
ground was me but if but why did you
kill my
brother why did you do that though I
took so many lives that night and
destroyed so many more including yours
we need to find
out and I must atone for the crimes I've
committed but not before I learn the
whole
truth
second I could a fire even exist I guess
that's and why was I chosen as its
dominant enough of a
reason who is the hooded man who brought
us here and what does he
want I need to
know and since I'm still
breathing I might as well make myself
useful I can't R we'll find answers
together present I want to learn the
truth too to
truth there'll be time enough for
atonement when we're
done I was hoping you'd say that I don't
think I could do this without you you
never were want to hide from the truth
he talks funny even when we were
young and you haven't changed a
[Music]
bit you're wrong
I have
changed but I don't want to be that
person
anymore the things she did were
unforgivable Unforgiven I'm a villain
I'm a and
yet they're what brought us back
[Music]
together thank you
Jill
hey oh if he is here
then the disturbance I felt at the care
must have
been confounded the hour is later than I
thought let's confound
it put it aside
or
meanwhile this looks more
deserty no blasted dang
[Music]
on
E is this the big guy who was into tell
me who did this or I'll see you suffer
the same fate yeah
okay the man who delivered who who
delivered the coffin said he said
sit it's a oh her her
coffin and why is she in such a small
cop and ised her
ashes I let you R A marck with the rest
of your rats and this is how you repay
me find out where he
is I'll crush him slay him rip out his
heart ultimate rage and all his filthy
brute and send every last one of them
to bring it
on no Bring It
[Music]
On inhale
it inhale
it
angrily oh he going to
cry
no
oh oh it's her head o oh
wow that
that's that's a
bit
evil
she was Sid's lover
too
Benedict
damn oh yes it didn't do it probably but
could have at
least fixed it by sending the whole body
or burning it and sending the ashes I
don't
[Music]
know oh someone's a someone else sent it
and framed him
us
oh did we just leave the body behind
like that
then maybe was
Joshua never mind oh IFH awoken CLI has
gained
control uh of the icon
in allowing access to new iconic iconic
Divine abilities such as ignition
of
fear fire Fury launch that drives back
enemies while dealing continuous damage
as well as unlocking a limit breakage
yay slots for if abilities are shared
with those for the Phoenix and can be
confirmed via the ability
stab located beneath C's HP bar release
CS in OB beast and semi Prime into
effort by
pressing except the truth when this go
is full the G fills and b battle both by
taking damage as well as by successfully
performing offensive and defensive
Maneuvers semi- priming temporary grants
increased attack potency and speed
gradual HP regeneration and Guard
breaking stes
oh so what next well next Super Chat
reading I promise the mayor I'd talk to
him again about Lady Hannah amongst
other things she may be loed to leave an
hour ago you guys told me oh there's a
good good point to stop soon
introduction then soon TM
if for channeled wow okay we'll look at
that next
time next
time yeah it was longer than
expected you
lied
[Music]
uh uh yeah the meaning of life oh is
Final Fantasy 16 the game which will
tell me the meaning of
life I save once per stream and that is
at the end of
it
w today felt less painful for my
fingers oh and easier to process
everything
nice good good good day now we'll read
super
chats yeah my fingers are getting strong
getting used to it I don't know it was
less fighting in general I
think and now I just
know I feel like button mashing randomly
aggressively probably took more out of
my Thum too than having a
system my fingers except the
truth gamer muscles yeah that was that
was fun hope you guys enjoyed it too um
the game by the way without side quests
is like 30 hours 30ish
hours and with today we have uh like
passed the 10hour mark so we're
definitely 13
in and I'm planning one stream next
week uh and then the week after
two
so yeah well get there maybe the one I
do next week I'll do an extra long one
not just 5 and a half like today but
more like eight hours yeah yeah
yeah want to do a long
one yeah exactly one3
noise if not longer I would do longer if
if if I will be feeling well
enough having a blast yeah I love it
like it's it's great game uh grasping
the combat feels really good too
so s is
[Music]
n oh my God I have like a million
DMS my
mom my mom is mommmy do do do
yeah this is AB my mom wrote to me uh
after
I after I spent a few hours watching
those extremely L dragged out fights in
Final Fantasy in my stream uh I noticed
that they didn't only
steal from Game of Thrones and Lord of
the Rings but also uh in in terms of uh
Movie music such as mass effect she sent
me links Mass Effect 2 soundtrack combat
theme Overlord DLC Mass Effect 2 OST
suicide mission Mass Effect 3 soundtrack
leaving Earth no she didn't say this one
that she says this is game music while
we're at
it mommy mommy they didn't steal it they
literally like admit or not admit but
they say they took inspiration they um
they made as I learned
too while developing this the like lead
developer or whatever project leader or
whatever told the whole team to watch
Game of Thrones Lord of the Rings and
Wheel of
Time so it's it's very much on purpose
mommy but I agree the fight are dragged
out
although no the the these last boss
fights I think were
fine they were
fine to
me hopefully it was read not watch Wheel
of
Time Well there wasn't much to watch cuz
it was only one season at that point
yeah yeah yeah
yeah
uh
[Music]
oh oh sorry I'm checking my
DMS
H
not oh well okay we are going to go to
my ah to my RPG office right I forgot
that
existed I forgot I had
that chat come on come on come on come
on come on come on come on
[Music]
baby for
cookie eat in
shambles perfect background for Final
Fantasy [\h__\h] yeah I am the dominant of
the Phoenix no one else is so call me
tits Mr cliff and Mr Joshua and stop
impersonating me at once or else I shall
put you into my usual room and you are
not getting out until you nail in front
of your dominant
Queen understand
okay I sue Joshua for identity fraud yes
yes
yes I am yeah I guess I'm not dominant I
am the
Phoenix that you guys try to
be I am better than
you nice nice nice yeah I I I love how
there is just so much Phoenix stuff in
here in this game and I know that you
guys told me that Final Fantasy
generally often has a lot of Phoenix
references but this time it's like
taking up a
notch in terms of
Phoenix playing a huge
[Music]
role is this playing automatically yeah
okay
k k
on let's play some music oh we should
play RPG themed music I think I have
something
in my audio stock library
library
R this one I
think the
[\h__\h] I cannot hear
it I can I
cannot and I have some must have some
sound things messed
up
there it is uh for you there it
is
[Music]
yay I'm feeling good I'm feeling way
better than yesterday so we shall Read
Super Chat
those Yumi
muscle Tavern
music
am I the only Holo streaming right
now oh I
am many
times is the
case dominating I am the dominant of all
life literally The Only One Prime real
estate solo
hours
but soon there's uh morning streams from
Japanese members
starting all right
uh
[Music]
Hyer
uh which
ones
and ah
sua sua game
right I'm
[Applause]
horse it's difficult to do them so
fast toon it's the toon
sound it did both like
ear AOE then
okay
right
[Music]
okay by the way I started
signing um the
oh if good good that I pointed out and I
started signing
the limited
edition things for Anniversary
merchandise
and I actually I asked for my deadline
and it's like pretty far like I have
like until end of November I think so
plenty of
time
um but so I think tomorrow is the the
16th I think 600 p.m. jst is the
deadline for buying the anniversary
merch so just a little reminder in case
you didn't get it here is Yago wearing
the backpack here is the inside of the
backpack with it has a little
rubber uh charm on the
zipper and here is a another view that I
haven't uploaded I think of the backpack
I think I want to make a community post
also before before the time is up and
show these because um this is also this
is the on the right side is the uh
luggage tag that's also Rubber and
inside on the other side there's a paper
where you can fill out your address and
your name Etc and put it on your luggage
then there's this little memo with a pen
looks like this I love that they using
they're really upping their game in
presentation here cuz they're using a
orange wallpaper that looks so clean
um yeah it's a has a little calendar
inside uh I asked for that I wanted to
make it a bit more useful besides just
taking
notes
um you could use like in order to read
it you could use
a erasable pen
actually and this is the the normal
Pages extra photo that I also didn't
upload on
Twitter
yeah so I'm going to probably make
another post on the community board to
remind but I think you guys everybody
who wanted it probably got it by
[Music]
now the Links are in the description in
case you still need to buy it
just as a little
reminder M you ordered day one thank
you thank you very
much yeah if you were hesitant at first
look at the nice quality I really like
the inner
lining I chose all of these for you guys
there's some inner B like how to say bag
not really bag uh uh compartments as
well and on the side is like a I think
it should probably be stretchy
stretchy net for putting a bottle BT
water
maybe finally got limited edition me
releasing it outside of a stream
definitely made it easier for everybody
to get limited
edition happy for you
guys I am going to request that next
time they make the percentage of like
how many are being sold
by geek Jack a bit higher for my
European fans cuz I noticed even when it
went this
slow it was immediately sold out on geek
Jack I don't even know how much it is
but it must be
[Music]
tiny I will inquire that I already kind
of did but I'll remind them to do it for
the next time I release
merch
yeah
[Music]
it's just too little two minutes for
Geek Jack but then it took like what
three hours
for for the other one and it really made
me doubt myself like what the [\h__\h]
what's going
on I was
like
panicking I was p e 90 minutes it felt
like 3
hours I was like not sure if I should
doubt myself or if I should doubt the
system but in the end I think the system
didn't do anything
[Music]
wrong
man
[Music]
sheesh but in the end we sold them and
once again I'm signing
them uh so let's read super chatos
[Music]
[Laughter]
ah I've got the
power to sneeze in your
ears
[Music]
okay my
AO
thumbnail
uh where is
it feel like recently I've been
accidentally saving my thumbnails in the
wrong folders all the
[Music]
time
uh what's my which one is this the
just I'll take it from here from
[Music]
hyzer there it
is
[Music]
okay here we
go a good night yo oh I see you got your
membership
back
[Music]
noise
py thanks for the pinky T if you forgot
about A2 you can practice for something
in the Art of War campaign or search
Spirit of law on YouTube and find
tutorial for beginners his pronunciation
and a lot of thinging will be nice for
you but the emotions arrived yay yay I
did try
both uh
honestly Art of War campaign for being a
tutorial I guess it does say Advanced
but still I I wasn't even able to clear
all of
them especially the ship one the one
where you you have to control the right
warships you get like three different
warships and you have to kill several
rounds of other ships I tried like three
times I couldn't I couldn't uh
win H yeah but I thought it it won't
matter so much because we're probably
not going to fight much on
water and I was right would I I really
wonder like how much different the
tournament would have been if we
wouldn't have gotten such
a
clear
prepared map you know with walls already
there and no no weird Terrain in there
everything like
empty everybody in the corner was a very
I guess
tournament focused
map so I wonder how it would have been
if it was a more natural map cuz I think
didn't MAA ended up putting only three
Maps into
the uh
randomizer I was
like but it happened so fast I couldn't
stop
[Music]
her yeah like we were looking at so many
and
that then she only ended up putting in
free so the chances of getting this one
was so
high I mean I I appreciated it because
then I didn't really need to uh create
walls but there already being walls
meant that you know everybody was
already well protected except crony
uh but who knows how well their
protection would have been if they had
to create it
themselves
I didn't need a Navy either Mauna was
going to go for Vikings right so she
should have preferred a a water
[Music]
map I'd have done better without
walls yeah the walls were [\h__\h]
annoying later on in the beginning not
so much cuz I was aiming at
crony she had an opening
anyway yeah yeah yeah like because of
the harvesting of the wood but that was
really early on and I really wonder how
she didn't know but now you guys were
saying oh she probably knows but she
can't get there because of my
castle she can't fix it I'm sorry sorry
sorry I'm
sorry I honestly didn't expect that my
castle would even though I know about
the tuttons bonuses and all that but I
didn't like really when I placed it
there I didn't realize it would have
such a big
impact and be able to destroy even the
building that was across of
it I didn't think that
much but yeah it was well
placed I honestly every time I placed a
a castle so close to someone else's
walls I didn't think they would let me I
thought they would just uh stop it
I was scared every time I would place it
I was like oh this is like me asking
them to attack
me my Builders were fast yeah I always
sent a lot of Builders to be quick and
efficient
[Music]
yeah so I think I did really well in the
I may not have won but I saw a lot of
people also saying that like um
skill-wise
and I may have been the best and that is
satisfying for me to hear cuz I tried
really hard to play well I totally
messed up the beginning cuz I was
nervous my efficiency in the beginning
was [\h__\h] the first like
villagers
but then I got into the groove I was
always trying to stay efficient also
telling waya what to
[Music]
do always create something always
reproduce and then I had like always at
some point I always had like 15 people
out of of a job cuz they just finished
working on a castle and I was like okay
well what do we do with all these people
I guess just make another
castle Yeah reproduced new new
humans exactly that's what I'm saying
anyway thank you R for the pinky so The
Art of War campaign was only partially
helpful cuz I was struggling a lot with
it yeah but I watched a bunch of videos
on YouTube
too um Flappy Boy Thanks for the red
super chat once more I'm delightfully
criis that you would do the honor to
this living fossil of a game to see you
participate in the tournament is a dream
come true even if it means rooting for
the underdog thank you for this absolute
yet highly unexpected blessing
oh I I was the
underdog to
you yeah what Underdog I am the
overdog I have I I I was also yeah
expecting we were all expecting Muna to
be
like absolutely
overpowered by
far
yeah
[Music]
but what's up
dog I need to watch ID tournament I
wonder what happened there but they
probably didn't speak much
English well well Flappy boy thank you
so much now you know I'm not the
underdog
anymore um yeah but who knows maybe
maybe if there is a next time maybe they
will have caught up so much in
skill Studio Rob thanks for the pinky
t
wait I've got the kiss for Flappy
[Music]
boy Kyla has bad memories about it
a also CU
of same
reasons as me like people being shitty
in the
chat what why what did Kyla do
was she too good
or oh they bulli her for being a noob
what man hey that's so
sad cuz I feel like she would have had
great potential she would have played it
endlessly and probably turned into one
of those micromanaging
people
now hold
na yeah so this is kind of like making
me feel like I don't want to be part of
tournaments like
this there like at the end there's often
such
a bitter feeling to uh walk away from it
[Music]
yeah it's
unfortunate I don't think it was that
much of a tunnel vision for me like
only three bad comments versus 300 good
good ones to me it felt like it was a
lot
of like
taunting taunting and riling up
but yes mostly
non-members seemingly people who don't
ever watch My
Stream uh
normally but I also saw some members
comments that also made me feel like
that added on top of it that weren't as
bad as others but still kind of added to
it
[Music]
uh so it just it just felt like wow even
like everybody's like hating on me now
and even a few of my own people seem
like not hating on me but I don't know
it wasn't that bad for my own people but
it still felt like you know it adds on
to it it's just to never punch in my
face but I'm it's okay you guys didn't
do anything bad
you guys are
fine no I don't think it was you telling
me to close the
hole
no yeah it's never everybody but um I
just it's just a it's just such a
stressful situation and then when people
come into my chat just for the sake of
riling me
up in a moment that is like you know
so uh I don't know
tense yeah and
and nerve nerve
wrecking and you guys trying to tell me
about Pikeman or whatever that's totally
fine that's not what I
mean that's not what I
mean
it's okay though and like
yeah it's what comes with these kind of
competitive
situations I just wish
like yeah maybe next time I'll do
members only at least chat members
only
because it definitely feels like I have
a Target on my back in these
situations
[Music]
and uh yeah it's hard
to to not react to that when when I feel
[Music]
it yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
whatever let's leave that aside but just
so you
know no chat night I don't know I don't
even know if I'm participating next time
I I like the game and I will play it
again but also
like uh I have to learn a lot of dances
I'll be kind of busy in the next
weeks for that purpose and so I don't
really know if I could even if I wanted
to I don't know if I want
to
yeah which is sad because I want to get
good at the game and and if there's a
tournament you know shouldn't I be
there but I don't know I'll think about
it depends maybe if some time
passes maybe if some time passes but if
too much time passes maybe everybody
gets so
skilled uh giving them too much time to
get
better I can't give them too much
time or everybody forgets everything who
knows who
knows
it's hard to
[Music]
tell play without your PV well yeah that
could
[Music]
also work but then again like I
I hopefully I wouldn't need it again in
another time but you're I I had like you
know generally a good idea of what to do
but every once in a while having a nice
reminder from you guys like oh by the
way you should do this again and you
should upgrade this again it was very
helpful without that what am I going to
do I will feel so
lost yeah members only is the way to
go so er
mon
ering D ER ding Ringo Le G thank you for
the red super
chat yay you got to let us go the
accident wasn't your
fault you can manage on your own but I
like to be able I want to be able to
manage on my own next time I want to get
to a point where I'm very confident in
what I'm doing and be able to use a few
um hot Keys macros like I tried and I I
I learned like three before the Stream
but in that like stressful situation I I
I couldn't use
them even pinned a comment for
that sometimes I used some of them but
not not effective not efficient but as
long as the others aren't using them you
know then there's no need for me to go
that
hard yeah Town Center hot
very good very
good yeah so easy to forget everything
in the moment where you really need
[Music]
it yeah one or two hot keys at a time
when it's really in your blood move on
to the next one I wonder how long it
takes to like get it really down like
all those AO AOE streamers and
tournament
participators have it down how long does
it take to get
good I want to get
good want be
[Music]
efficient
it's like you can't even tell what the
hell they're doing cuz they're so fast
they switch between
things so fast they do five things in 2
seconds it's
[Music]
insane
she like watching on fast forward so
true anyway she the thank you Ki is so
cool you'll be a tactical genius in no
time thank you it turned out I was quite
a genius thank you thank
you D for the support I'm glad you were
there chainsaw lizard D mon
P fantasma thank you for the red super
chat hey girl love the look today M I
was wearing the same as I am now thank
you I appreciate it this I'm getting a
lot of mileage out of this
[Music]
outfit I think it was a great choice
going for
this yeah the pathing of the troops
individually that's insane like how do
you have time to do that
while still man managing your whole
town
shees sheesh
fantasma black d EAD art D looking for
the top D I am a te oh my beep is gone
cuz somehow the buttons for a reset beep
than Captain coconut than so is killer
Productions
than oh you going to play the campaigns
this time no maybe I'll play campaigns
again in the future but
M I had so much more fun with the
skirmishes man and I want to try online
playing some ranked games at some point
when I feel a bit more
confident CH Channel D Stone yellow D
scar D andet Lee danash clear ey
danash multiple buildings at one set
path for unit to follow I I learned
about the the the shift like giving
people follow up things to do I learned
I think I learned that in the middle of
the
tournament that was
[Music]
helpful or did I do it before did I
learn it before maybe but I learned it
recently the queuing take for
the the
speech I did practice the counters
but of course like in first of all in a
situation like this
forget and I also like I didn't know
that she was going to like be fully
going
into
um elephants until it was too late and
then the production was too slow and
then me not being able to control them
like separately
properly I did people pointed it out and
I that's what I was feeling at the time
time I was trying to attack things and
they were just running around
stupidly I don't get it so stuff like
that should be improved was tough they
were not
efficient yeah and monk
conversions not efficient enough either
never worked never ended up
working need more monks or
else but first got to really learn how
to properly control everything cuz
otherwise monkss may be too expensive to
really
spam mhm they're I think they're hard to
micro cuz like that was that was my
issue like they don't even do it
automatically you have to tell them and
then select what you want to
convert
o
oof
not really
my play style Brutus salad D Cy d n d
gamer SL Dan cie cie D Fred pen Dan
David
internet gang Dan 3,000
ER T talk thanks for the pinky well this
will be my last stream for a month ah
this was the one that made me so
sad I'm going to the middle of nowhere
after that maybe I will no longer be a
kfp how can you say that so if that
happens say hi to froggy waa that she's
my only true o
she why why why is this serious also T
is cool I guess I'll miss being a kfp
what
what what is this is this a jork it must
be a jerk now that I realized you were
mentioning froggy waa and putting a frog
emot and sounding kind of tnd at the end
maybe it was
jork it better have
been but I hope you're coming
back everybody who leaves at some point
for a while I hope they all come
back
fall
and
[Music]
no I
won't you're here right
now you can't make me I should start
work next month
oh but you still have the time to be
fulltime kfp
wow wow I guess you just will stop
sleeping syy does seem to love AOE
[Music]
oh
kind okay that was a practice round
now AOE not practice
[Music]
round check J thanks fored super CH it's
nice to see a of Empire streams again
after a while have nice and good luck
thank
you yeah oh was was happy with my
team and we did so well I think we did
way better than people expected of
us I feel like probably if people see me
in any tournament really involved they
don't expect much from me they
underestimate me that's why I want to do
even
better and surprise people and like
change their
mind show them what I can do it doesn't
always work but this time I mean it kind
of worked unfortun I I couldn't take the
title of the winner which would have
proven it even clear even more
clearer but still I think I've I've
shown that I'm good at age of vampires
decently and not good compared to pros
of
course but I also improved so much for
that one practice stream that was a lot
of
[Music]
potential yeah Pokemon Unity tournament
un Unity
unite is also like something that stayed
like left a bad aftertaste I think for
me just because I couldn't we couldn't
perform as well I was with am am was
lagging we were
being like constantly
targeted over the others
I was trying to tell myself well in the
end that was good because that helped
the the others of our team to you know
do their thing but still yeah I really
couldn't do anything there and that
really bothered
me yeah it helped the team but still
frustrating
exactly
yeah that was rough it's not fun being
targeted like that but it doesn't mean
you're bad thank you
yeah we really just want you guys to
have fun so we can have fun alongside
you yeah I know I
know I know I
know oh good night thank you for
watching maybe see you again
soon thank you J swb Jim
Tracy the
gamer andless thanks for the r Super
Chat oh New Zealand wow
fancy I know the time sucks for almost
everyone else but I'm going to relish
every
moment Mor Mor moment I don't know where
else to put New Zealand accent in of
this rare prime time collab
well speaking of New Zealand you
[Music]
know
H prime it was prime time for
you isn't New Zealand Time Zone close to
Japanese time zone how is it prime time
for you or or it prime time it was prime
time for na isn't New Zealand like more
like on the Australian
side did you just mean prime time in
general for englishspeaking
Market cuz they say I know the time
sucks for almost everyone else but I'm
going to relish every moment of this
rare prime time
[Music]
collab it was late for n 12 hours ahead
of au well okay that's way more than
Japan oh
oh
W wasn't it like seven for me so that's
like 1 18 19 700
p.m. ooh that is prime time
oh
wow ah
Kate
9:30 in the morning now she's good
[Music]
morning
wow but is it really 12 hours ahead are
you
[Music]
sure
late morning K do you hear the birds
chirping do you hear the roosters Kik
kicking
so funny at my my mom's place like cuz
I'm I usually don't hear that kind of
stuff but my mom's place I heard so much
nature so many like especially
roosters kiky
kicking in the morning but also during
the
day it's so wow stuff that
I stupidly only hear in
games real
nature
what isn't it shameful of
this
society that you hear something like
that more in like movies and
games than in
reality if you're like in a city at
least guess if you live on the
countryside you get n nature Ambience
but besides that it's so
sad that's just City Life yeah but like
never get out of there where is
nature I'm
ashamed cuz it felt so wo whoo to
me oh my God there's an actual rooster
going KY
ke
wa
it's
real real life
[Music]
sfx I am not a rooster I'm the
Wawa nature is
real oh there's five people who have
chickens in the rooster then you you
must be hearing it all the
[Music]
time wow sound team did a great job in
this Ambience feels so
real so thank you
endless I hope I hope you can watch my
other streams too I'm sorry I normally
can't provide streams in around the time
it's really like the shittiest time for
me if I were to stream during that time
I wonder how my viewership would be but
it's not worth it to me to
ruin
everything I prefer it this way even if
I must accept lower
numbers it's
okay it's
okay g d Ben D ta D random person d d
boo D Ferris GT
d c I'm so sorry I never saw your super
chats Unity chat
than yeah I would have to
sleep like if I want to stream any prime
time i' even have to get up like super
early but then even then if I get up at
600 and start streaming at 700 or
so then I can't really do like I
wouldn't be in prime time for long cuz
like
uh if I do a longer stream it will go
through the night yeah cuz that's
already 1:00 a.m. you see that's not
really prime time so in order to be in
prime time I'd have to start at like 300
a.m. or so 2 between 2: and and 500
a.m. basically for me it's not worth
it not I don't want to live my life like
this especially not long term cuz I know
how it is for people who do like normal
jobs working night shifts and often
often though night shifts at least like
it's already tiring but at least a lot
of night shifts are like in terms of how
much is going on or at least usually
like more chill like in a hotel for
example at least there's like not
many stressful
situations um but if I were to stream
that is a stressful situation cuz like
I'm still using all my
energy and yeah that's just not
not healthy for
me yeah I'll continue like this
sometimes I do feel like man I wish I
would have done it
[Music]
differently but yeah I would probably
fall apart soon and
[Music]
crumble
I could stream for sea and Japan and so
on that's still like realistic but na
unfortunately not where where the
biggest potential for a big fan bases
but I'm so so so so so thankful for you
guys being so
dedicated all of you but you know now
especially talk about na people who
watch me sa too though yeah na and sea
sea not sa
sea Asia viewers who still watch me
live even when it's really
rough for you guys to
adjust thank you you try your best to be
here for
me thank
you thank you thank you thank you
H
H thank you I'm glad I can you know be
alongside you during your early mornings
and daytime and
for sea Asia Etc
[Music]
I I I don't know how the [\h__\h] you do
it I don't know you must be
sacrificing so much to watch
me I don't know how you do
it sleep during day and then your job
must be like late shift or something
like that something really Dynamic
flexible don't know how the [\h__\h] you do
it South American fans
too
wait ah South South for some reason my
brain was like South Africa AFA
[Music]
huh where are the South African
fans maybe North maybe North
Africa
there were at least
two
really
really yeah
like North Africa isn't even far in
terms of time
[Music]
zones saw them in disc oh
really yeah yeah yeah similar time
zones yeah going vertically okay okay
okay okay chill chill chill chill ch ch
no need to make me feel stupid
now no um where was I F
GT Unity M 101 Mac 4906 I onction C
thanks for the r chat that's a good GG K
do you did great ah c will you do me the
honor and play uh when if I do online
tournaments try to get into the queue
and play against
me don't forget that un feel of both MAA
and crony kind of on you too K is proud
of you of our Warrior Phoenix thank you
thank you you very you but I guess you
would be you would probably be too
powerful for me to go against against
you especially if it's ranked I don't
think they would match us
ever yeah you're probably too
good so you shall continue to watch over
me and judge me and tell me what to do
instead until I get good enough so that
I can match with you in a ranked
one oh May a Smurf account could you
host matches with us I probably could
probably could Smurfs but who else who
else here actually plays it and uh or or
played it before and would play it
again no matter the
rank for playing against
me me
me oh oh there's a couple
[Music]
there's a
couple
n that's
noise is AOE like
a popular category on
[Music]
Twitch
uh
I wanted to open twitch and see like go
into AOE
category RTS aren't popular
anymore well yeah not popular but like I
don't know if it would be better to be
popular or not popular as a category but
um well 3.3k right
now
ooh
cuz yeah so that's a thing um I talked
about with am
recently one of the
things uh
like I wasn't like planning on trying it
anytime soon but
um I asked her like how how her twitch
streams were like received in terms of
how how well the viewership was and
stuff and we talked about how you know
it's an as a content creator when this
is your job especially for a long time
you want to make sure that you're like
growing or at least staying
stable uh and not like uh declining is
the
word and YouTube is just generally not
the best market for live streaming right
we know that and I have noticed a while
ago that the especially the European
market for streaming they're all on
Twitch
yeah there's a big potential
viewership to snag on Twitch for
European time zones and
yeah I I'm thinking that I'll eventually
have to give it a
try not like
the like all of my streams moving over
there but like partially trying it out
like once a week or so I don't
[Music]
know yeah so I know it's a different
culture and I know that some people have
like negative feelings about the idea of
that but uh I have to think of it from
the POV as a content creator and
somebody who relies on this as my
livelihood
and I
mean yeah I can do this even if I don't
know a thousand people or less 500 or
even though only five people watch me
but
um
for you know I talked about it in my
member stream how I'm doing mentally
and
it's also for the sake of my me mental
health
to make things go up again
uh cuz if it's only going down it if if
you if you work really hard and you
experience a big high and then
everything just keeps on going down you
know that just doesn't feel good and you
try everything you can to bring on uh
keep on bringing interesting
content within my
limits you try and try and try you try
with music you try with streams you try
with collabs and this and
that and if it then still doesn't look
good it's it for streamer or any
YouTuber any content
creator can tell you that
it it definitely in in in affects them
yeah
so if you're just like if you start out
small then of course it's also difficult
um to become something in the first
place but when when you then reach
something big a big big
hype time and
then it fades
away it when you peek and then it fades
away yeah it makes you question
yourself obviously it's like it's not
only got to do with yourself of course
but then you you still question it you
[Music]
know it's hard to not question yourself
and and and try your best
to fight against
it so I'm not saying I'm doing it like
right away anytime soon but at some
point where I feel like now is the right
moment or good timing or I really need
to do it Now or Never then I might try
it out to mix a few twitch streams in
there yeah so I hope that's okay for you
guys but you I hope you can understand
the
[Music]
reasoning
I think I talked about that before geie
um a long time ago that
like when you get like so and so many
subscribers you then you aim for the
next milestone in the next Milestone and
you think you'll be satisfied with that
one you'll H you'll be happy with that
Milestone but turns out once you reach
it it's never enough It's never enough
you always want to get more reach the
next milestone
that's just that's just how it
is that's just how it is but yeah you
could see it as it's good to have
ambition something has to give you a
drive it's an endless grind that is just
how it
is but that's also the thing that kind
of destroys
you the the
greed it's exhausting yeah you're always
running you always you always feel like
it's not enough you're always
running to reach bigger things and when
it doesn't work out and it goes even
like backwards that that's
o
[Music]
o German channel should have been a
twitch Channel
yeah but then again I don't really see
how me streaming on in German on Twitch
would be the solution to my
problems yeah I mean
[Music]
it I do know that there's plenty of
German streamers on Twitch and also
German viewers
but you you want to see
it hm
[Music]
not a lot of holos on Twitch yeah like
I I think like I like that we are on
YouTube I like that it's our place you
know and I don't really want that to
[Music]
change but just reaching out a little
bit
more to try a few other
things I think it's it's fine to give it
a
try
[Music]
virtual YouTuber vtuber the ver the word
comes from YouTube so got to be on
YouTube v v
twitcher but if you take part of it away
like with
vtuber
f
F fer
F
no
Witcher
wicher
[Music]
weird V streamer I got to generalize it
but V streamer sounds stupid V tuber is
cooler V
Boer no I'm I haven't been a we boober
for a
while the chat will be fine because I
will bring you guys over and you guys
are going
to bless the chat with your
existence and you
know we're going to going to make the
chat a comfy place a good
place I don't what we we'll have to
try oh but the potential for more and
cute emotes and moving animated emotes
oh one good
[Music]
thing and bigger ones too easier to
see oh chicken twerk chicken
[Music]
twerk yeah but anyway it's a thing for
the
future I don't even have the mental
capacity to do something like that
now I'm
busy so um I tangent it so much thank
you C for the red
chat Josh L I am a
che
sick them too not this time give them
all
you sick too get him that'll help over
here there boy not this time give them
all you got boy sck him togle get them
that'll
help wow that is so true so deep and so
profound and
helpful how do you do it
krono how do you
become so wise my wounds
boy how how do I become more like
you thank you for the red super chat
giving you an early
kiss Thank You cor that was indeed
uplifting accept the
truth have you
someone knocks on your door turn turn
turn turn you open it it's two people
standing in front of you in a robe
cloaked with a hood over your head
asking you have you accepted the truth
yet are you ready to accept the
truth they hand you a
controller if you are ready to accept
the
truth press L free and L free
if you accept the truth we will accept
you welcome to our Cult of
acceptance which is all about the truth
and accepting
it I will not accept the little chef
head cow
carrot you usual room three months for
that
misdemeanor of the second
degree I was a bit late
to let down my
judgment but here it is goodbye my
hero the
bond the wait you were never in the
usual
the bond there's no bond you have to
stay but uh you will be given a a PC to
work continue working while in the usual
room that is not something you
can take a vacation from so
[Music]
easily okay
his first usual room
[Music]
oh they grow up so
fast
H six St Flappy boy thank you for the r
Super Chat expected expectedly that was
a
massively this was massively fun to
watch
as can't speak everything else I did not
see coming should have had faith in the
H might you were that close to Total
Victory very proud of my boss would be
wild if someday you found the Muse to
further
peruse your RTS career I don't need a
muse I am the
Muse my RTS career shall
continue
H are you preparing something for
Halloween no no I'm not sorry I'm
busy I mean I I'll probably play a few
scary games but I'm not preparing
anything big no song covers
either cuz I'm still putting out all the
other things from my
[Music]
album a FAL frame yeah horror watch
along I don't want to watch a horror
movie nah
no not
[Music]
really no
no no they're not enjoyable for me no
nothing fun about
that if they bring out a Luigi's Mansion
movie we can we can watch
that no they're not that scary
lies some are surely very scary some are
maybe decent but I don't care that's
that's not the kind of movie that I want
to
watch
Ghostbusters okay maybe
Ghostbusters anyway thank you Flappy bom
look forward to more AOE in the coming
week actually you probably already saw
the
schedule GD D pill comes on me down my
Korean bro who really loves me playing
AOE even if elephants trample us they
cannot break the will of our
nights I I want to try playing Koreans
too
sometime they seem they seem
special they seem to have something
special about
them so thank you for watching I'm glad
I could you know make you happy again
with a AOE stream thank you so much for
being there and
supporting more waa AOE fan
art Sky Al's Channel C and H B
[Music]
okay Final Fantasy from
yesterday uh
[Music]
thumbnail there it
is
oh actually I guess there's member super
chats that I should be
reading
oh
[Music]
oh oh I just
realized save them for a member
stream can
I I mean judging by the capacity
that
uh that the YouTube Super Chat reading
thingy can actually take it will
probably be
fine should still be
there they're a bit heavy oh
[Music]
probably yeah I could probably keep it
for next time I might I might also save
them put them
[Music]
aside
okay then we continue with this
one ja
47 moral
immoral Theo
arst oh your friend is getting this for
your birthday you've been avoiding
spoilers oh when is your birthday when
are you going to play it h be fast speed
Sky D Looney
D oh yeah active time L very cool Jeff
star thanks for the pinky good luck
thank
you m didn't need
it but I appreciate it py d t thanks for
the pinky hello K today's my birthday
and I wanted to leave a Super Chat as is
customary unfortunately due to my family
obligations I won't be able to watch the
rest of your life live stream I'll be
sure to watch the vult later stay
amazing and have fun are you here
now that was in dollars so you could be
watching now happy belated
birthday and it's not that belated let's
go
congratulations don't think you're here
now but I hope you get to watch the
V hope you had a wonderful day I wish
you all the health and love and
success everything you need in your life
to go
well and thank you for being you than
soon
congratulations red Jack 271 dection
spank andham thanks for the red chat
you're our Phoenix he's an emo game kid
the power is yours thank you I am the
Phoenix the one and only true
[Music]
Phoenix thank you
for understanding the truth and
accepting the
truth you get it you just get it you
guys you all get it you know it I don't
know why the Final Fantasy peeps don't
get it but you guys get
[Music]
it thank you you some guy thank you also
for red super chat but no message what
and just calling himself just some
guy understand statement of the century
oh my God he just he just wants to be
unnoticed maybe it's some guy in the
hooded cloak being
mysterious and later on revealing it's
me it was
me and I will accept the
truth tin foil hat on thank you some
guy it's me I am my own biggest
enemy and my own biggest
supporter stud thanks for the
p
[Music]
accept the
truth with the Bas profile picture Chris
plemons thank you for the r and another
new name at least for super chats hello
K soon I will be
embarking on my first trip to Japan may
I receive a blessing from the Phoenix
and hopes for a smooth Journey thank you
for being such an inspiration for Travel
and Adventure hope you enjoy your first
non mmrpg Final Fantasy thank you
oh how long are you going to be there I
wish you good good luck and
blessings I hope you're going to have
fun so many people are going to
Japan it's
tourist country once again no more empty
Cal or anything like that oh there you
are here at a time like this must mean
you're not quite in Japan
yet
I
[Music]
think yeah of course it was tourist
packed again I wouldn't imagine it any
other
way which is good for kilo cuz I'm sure
like kilo always has been relying uh on
the
tourists
income it's good for them but surely
they also in some way at least at least
the normal people living there not the
people who like are relying on their
shops for tourists or whatever but
surely they also in some way
enjoyed the emptiness for a while for
change but yeah have fun I hope you can
see everything you want to
see and I hope everything will go well
and
safely and that you'll have lots of fun
and lots of of good food
M yeah enjoy oh and find you have to go
out and look for all the whole life
merch that you can
get I
think there's a lot of stuff out there
you can get you just have to look in in
in several different small
places and collect it
all take this
[Music]
opportunity
go to
awon convenience
store you're going to go to kyota
university
shees I think that's a good
one well asking for tips like that it's
hard to really say I don't know what I
supposed to say you know you're going to
figure it out you seem like a smart
person if you're going for PhD you'll
figure it out
it's really hard to say anything now
that won't just be a really vague and
general
comment but damn good luck and
congratulations Chris
plem Choo
[Music]
CH shadow soldier dun eating my Tyson's
ass
dun oh my God yeah yesterday yesterday
some of the Dodge comments really for a
moment made me think oh no is it going
to get really [\h__\h] annoying again
like an Elden
ring
but I think today there could possibly
have been such complaints cuz I
immediately figured it out today not
only dodging more efficiently but also
countering
so there was no over rolling rolling but
I think I was like um
I did not shut up you can't tell me I
didn't I I parried plenty you're not
serious are
[Music]
you you make me
angry I'm waiting for an answer
tell
me game
8 910 or something like
that tell me there you are she's priming
why will you ignore my
questions why won't you tell me you must
have been
joking right right right please tell me
you we joking please tell
me Point gun at you do you were joking
right you were joking
right oh my god there you go giving me
more things to fix you're never going to
be happy with me I'm never going to be
good enough for
[Music]
you you hate
me
just kidding I'm
I'm just
acting this whole time
but I don't know if you're trying to
taunt
[Music]
me an the Oscar goes to I'm better than
other streamers that you watched let's
go
ah feels
[Music]
good
satisfying I shall bathe in this
[Music]
[Laughter]
comment um
[Music]
uh what do you mean stop using Goose
during staggered enemy States what why
I'm using everything I'm using the full
potential why would I not use G that's
like so good
or do you mean because it uh is too long
it is too
long it's not effective it does less
damage how why the [\h__\h] would it do less
damage than regular attack what the [\h__\h]
it feels like I'm doing a lot but then I
mean if I use all the other free
skills at that point you know why not
use gu
to oh yeah ramping up the
multiplayer
I move to get them to get them
[Music]
staggered but most animes they won't
even give me that much time to stagger
them with
goou like in one
[Music]
go okay I'll think about
it how dare you how dare you come at me
with some actual
good advice and logic and and factual
facts how dare
[Music]
you I guess I must accept the
truth
Goose
[Music]
goose
I saw you do it a lot after the 50%
Embrace yeah yeah yeah yeah you mean the
yeah yeah
yeah felt like it was a good
time they are down for not too long as
as in the staggered state but
long enough to do one full
goou
go to gouge well I thought so I expected
that much gouge yeah well [\h__\h] you it's
[Laughter]
sco if it was gou wouldn't it be G8 oh g
g a u g
e gagee what what the [\h__\h] is that
microphone to gagee Gage I guess that
was Gage [\h__\h] to gauge but if it was
Gage wouldn't it be g a y g
e okay I don't think I can find find
and uh but I mean there there's gauge
with without this y to gauge something
see see g a g e is the same as g a u c a
what what g a u g e makes no sense
should be G A if you're going to
pronounce it like that should be g a g e
see
hia I I have obliterated the English
language once
again and proven it wrong
[Music]
[Laughter]
carpenter
carpenter Carpenters make
[Music]
carpet there's not even a prople word
fora in English it's just carpet layer
ridiculous who stole this word from the
carpet layer who was like uh who had a
personal Vendetta against the carpet L
was like [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] carpets people
should walk on bare wood thus I steal
your carpet by stealing your Carpenter
name and now you're naked and now all
you have is the name carpet layer which
doesn't sound cool at all which doesn't
sound even like a specific word just for
your job I shall take it and you shall
never have it back now I'm the Carpenter
and people will be confused cuz they
think I lay carpets but in reality I
don't and then I transform them from
carpet lovers into wood bare wood lovers
and they will walk on the wood they will
ignore carpets forever they will hate
carpets they will burn carpets they will
rip out the carpets of their homes and
then burn them and say [\h__\h]
[Music]
carpet that's HP that's what
[Laughter]
happened superiority to hardwood
floors I'm not
okay it's getting late for you hey hey
don't you don't you put me on the
wheelchair and roll me to my bed don't
you don't you give me my mids against my
[Music]
will
M I will choose when I go to
bed Twilight hour it's time for bed
keep do that scream it's too late for
the
[Music]
scamble they're just vitamins oh yeah oh
yeah like in the chest show yeah yeah
yeah sure just vitamins
M I watched the chess
show mm- I don't believe
you Queen's
Gambit okay back to Super chats come on
Focus guys focus
focus so thank you Chris plem shadow
soldier wait I was already past it
J game 891 oh D boo 73 Tracy D thanks
for the chat now finally say congrats on
getting to stream an FF game by the way
this was the point where you would have
stopped if you had played that day your
time was limited ah also feel free to
use any wait what what what point was
that you guys did say like ah something
like I ah would it have been after the
teenager time cuz you guys did say oh
there's something that's perfect for
like fre hours B blah
blue
m i don't hold on a oh but that would
have been such a Clive
hanger feel free to use any of the
timely accessories if you want fubuki
use the used the focus one yeah I I'll
be using the the
healing one for the dog as long as I
have him in the team I don't know if I
ever will replace him if that's going to
happen but for
now I don't want I do not want to
control all the dog so thank you
m finally
finally let's
[Music]
go oh I'm still using the dog one in
fights without the dog well I'm not
going to like micromanage that [\h__\h]
no it's
fine can say did I give M A
[Music]
Kiss M AR res thanks for the r Chad glad
to see you enjoying the game T about
abilities you want to master basic ones
like process Precision Dodge Swift
recovery Etc ASAP it's how you get a
bigger Dodge recovery faster shoot
damage better and shoot man magic better
so everything you've been doing already
will get a boost thank you the Swift
recovery was surprisingly
effective I feel like it even works if
you if you're like being flung over a
big distance and you already press it
early it's already like registering it
early and immediately bringing you back
up really
[Music]
nice manual dog combo extender I don't
care
[Music]
most people also ignore tole yeah it's
just I don't even want to get into
it he can spein all he wants
oh okay well sounds really
good I don't need
[Music]
it wow wow I had some even though I
didn't drink Red Bull today I had some
crazy moments today didn't
i w w
[Applause]
[Music]
w and the carpets the
carpets I was the Red Bull I am Red
Bull sorry I need
to punch
myself oh thank you
rine I hope you'll enjoy the rest of my
playthrough too cuz I'm having a great
time thank
you g Tracy fire M Legato Sky
hard resine another red Super Chat
what's
up what's up
braine sheesh the side quest involving
the main character later I read this
like Jill 100% worth it and add to the
store you might actually want to do
those on streams the side quest that you
want to ignore are those from some
random passor by NPCs that are not times
yeah I will try that but so far I didn't
see
any important looking
ones we'll do them if we find them feel
free to remind me
when such uh a a quest shows up you've
been killing us boss thank you I've been
having
[Music]
fun
yay um well within the year I don't see
any more FF games coming up for me uh
next year for sure we can play another
FF game next
year I'll I might make a poll like with
GTA and have you guys choose which one
[Music]
I don't know we'll see which perms I
have next year I already have a couple
this year
[Music]
already oh seems people want seven a lot
it's a remake so it will be beautiful I
I think that's a good
idea H oh oh oh wait it's coming out
next
year ah the rebirth one but there's also
a remake of the normal
ff7 there's a remake of both ff7 and the
the the sequel she they are they're
really on it aren't they I wish I wish
Bai namle would remake more tales off
games please
please
please oh yeah Yakuza in January yeah
yeah yeah maybe we can play the normal
ff7 before the rebirth one comes out and
then time it to then continue with
rebirth but I have no idea when it's
coming
out
February oh yeah I that's
o no I
don't
tight on leap day oh
funny never mind J I'll try to like do
it close to that at least but we'll see
how it goes lots of RPGs going to be on
my channel
[Music]
the game play is dated even though it's
remade Super
Mario yeah I think
so I think I want to play that
[Music]
raeline
D for two pinkies AKA one red hey ten I
have a little story from my work I'd
like to share with you I work as an
Rehabilitation educator and an youth
welfare hi
smoothie youth wal for institution
recently a little girl moved to our
Residential Group as it turns out she's
a little
weep wait Residential Group can you tell
me this with German terms
there's smooy under my chair why is she
under my chair hello
[Music]
hi okay
oh did
did I understand I understand I
understand she's wet she went to the
toilet and then went to
me it's like I I was on her
[Laughter]
path uh it didn't go on my hand start
went on my pajama
pants okay
um today I met her for the first time
and at some point I had to Google
something so I took out my phone
naturally I have wa is my background so
when I take on my phone this good SE my
background and goes like who is she
she's so pretty oh what did you tell
her what did you tell
[Music]
her is she so she's one of the
people that you are
rehabilitating what Rehabilitation
educator so she's
like something you are educating
[Music]
what are you here to answer my
question join
that oh you're supposed to do that are
they like really young you say little
girl so probably pretty
young a little
weeb tell her about
kfp does she know about
vtubers might be interesting for her
feel like um weeps are like would be
obviously receptive to
[Music]
that keep her the full rown yeah yeah I
showed her your first performance
a oh isn't is it because that one was
the the one that was oh wait aren't they
like removing it after a certain time is
it still up the summer first
day isn't that from Summer First Day
concert I think it's gone oh man ah it's
gone ooh okay MAA
W it went down a month ago who a the Lou
Lou birthday one
ah oh did she like it what did she
say I wonder you answer me I'll continue
reading thanks for the two
pinkies i
a she liked it all right hope she she
should listen to my music she should
listen to pineapple and sleep talking
and all that and love rush I'm sure
she'll like
[Music]
it I think I'll leave the Super Chat at
that I
[Music]
can't so I will now upload
my schedule and prepare
tgw and try to do a few more other
things I
guess
yeah tomorrow no stream just tgw going
up yeah yeah merch merch I want to put
up the merch let's let's do it now
before I forget
[Music]
it let me just copy paste what I wrote
on
[Music]
Twitter the links probably won't be
properly copy
pasted no it works okay
and then I think YouTube also has a
maximum of four
pictures U but I'll I'll bait them with
Yago and this one
oh
uh on this one
and this one and this one
ah doesn't work like
that and this one and this one oh
there's one more okay M maybe this
one
okay
um un
go
okay it is now in the community
post possibly one of Yo's last
jobs as a
[Music]
model so sad he's
graduating what an honor
[Music]
yeah and I asked like because it's
actually really helpful to have not just
pictures of the product but also a
person carrying or wearing them
Etc um I asked if there will still like
be someone else maybe who can do it and
I was
told yeah possibly just someone
from the merch department or whatever is
probably going to do
it don't know who but just somebody
who's open for doing it
yeah they might not show the face though
for Anon
[Music]
anonymity okay guys oh they used the
mannequin
already for for whose merch a
mannequin that's so stiff and like
unrelatable we need a real
person for
[Music]
stuff I hope they will use the
person well maybe that was special
because those were concert merchandisers
and they wanted to present it in a more
professional
way I don't know okay thank you guys for
watching today see you on
Tuesday uh members already saw the
schedule the rest of them if you guys
should check it on my community board or
on Twitter in a little moment I'll check
again did I have any mistakes on there I
don't think so just the the one
collab Mark I could add that but the
time zones I think were all
[Music]
correct
yeah I think I can upload it just like
that okay and in German we say I'll Fe
in thank you for watching
[Music]
bye-bye
bye-bye let this time bye-bye
[Music]
does anding go anding go anding go
anding
go anding
go time bye-bye anding go I need to
practice it's been a
while
thank you C absur that's just absurd
you're randomly sending a red super chat
at the
end thank
[Music]
you
that's absurd Carpenter
[Music]
absurdum the
absurdness of the carpet
[Music]
scandal
oh movie movie rubbing herself against
my
leg hi she should be dry by
now
[Music]
hi a
baby
[Music]
e
sorry I was
cuddling okay