[Music]
n
a
okay K KY
key hi hello
everyone
[Music]
is everything normal now I think this
the stream is kind of a little bit have
a
lagging let's hope better now yeah okay
so this is the first time that I am uh
asking uh some Ian member Kon Kiara and
FAA to join the uh Age of Empire 2 uh
but we also have
Ana and rainy to play
[Music]
again
yay so uh this time this time um we put
it into a team um since me Ana and rainy
already playing this game before so we
put I think it's wisely to put uh two
versus two versus kind of thing
yes um every team have I and and
ID yes yes International Teams let's
go
yeah
yeah like a like a game setting with a
random map a normal six player and the
location actually right now is randomly
choose Coastal but I actually have no
idea about
it I don't have any idea about the maps
it's yeah I don't have idea the
map are you sure it's random Mrs Mauna
who's playing Vikings are you sure that
was not on purpose cuz you're playing
[Applause]
Vikings I I put like game modes and
random M and they put Coastal
okay I I me Co is fine right it doesn't
really mean that the whole map is
covered with ocean right it's just that
there is a host right
chat
[Music]
right custom map
Pool yeah there there you can just
choose like 10 or 15 maps that you want
to be in the pool oh oh so you can
choose everything that looks good to you
for a big
match okay mostly oh maybe I just choose
the one that have like maybe six with
mostly
[Music]
the choose Arena too Arena and black
forest in the uh in the top uh two top
top two row Black Forest yummy black
forest in Arena Black Forest
yummy oh yummy with
chries which one in the top row there
should be black forest and Arena it's
alphabetic anyway Black Forest yeah I
heard that I never played it but it's
very popular I think for big
matches what do you want to
request Arena I don't know I up to you
you almost chose everyone it you
anything's
fine it'll be fine oh you chose so many
fine how bad can it be all right you
chose so SRA oh my God no no no no no
the one that is on
Orum Black
Forest um one but there's so much green
I
[Music]
want look at that V majapahit Empire oh
my God wait can I see a custom map Pool
oh I can't oh I can are there there's so
many oh wait is it like standard
there
gy where's the big
mapish
they have like a how many Maps there's a
map called Mega random like is there
really like a question mark shadeed
water on it Mega random is just super
random has
everything I it's going to be heavily
stylist like everything is going to be
random it's not always going to be the
same I'm looking at four people yeah but
like the thing is I can't select see
like I
I can't see the six people maps how do I
see the six people Maps I don't know
these four people map there
four how
mostly how old I mean it's just a map
size and these are just map Styles right
there 83 maps in the
game automatically adjusted it says oh
look at this oh now this is huge adjust
it ah you went to you real real world
Indonesia oh my God so much water in
Indonesia not real world there's so much
water in real world so much water in the
real world go back to random Indonesia
too random Black
Forest it's
fine black
forest know I put it on random Black
Forest Black Forest Arena and V Empire
that's the tree random that I choose
okay oh it tastes Black Forest here but
I guess when you get to the game it's
going to be
randomized yeah I
guess we'll see it's not bad if we go
eat cake
right cake is good let them have cake
yum let them have
cake okay um well I think it's time to
start okay guys ready good luck
good luck everyone ma don't kill us all
have mercy
MAA okay
byebye what is up let's go way let's
focus on our economy okay first okay
first let's go wait so where are you oh
you're like over
there let's uh uh wait I'm I'm confused
I don't know how to play the game
anymore I don't know I forgot I know I
know I know I know like wait like I
don't even oh can I can I just like um
do this and you you you are supposed to
do
this I don't
know um you are going why is there big
walls around me wait there's already
walls around us yeah that's why I'm I'm
like so
confused actually a [\h__\h] I don't know
I'm so
confused wait okay there's Stones here
and there's wood here wood is so
far all right oh but the wood is like if
it's gone I have to build a wall wait
can I cancel
it oh no guys how do you oh my God got
this o I don't know guys double Raina oh
because oh
wait
what uh never mind I had like double
Raina on my OBS he was delete
okay okay well it's just still there how
do you um you know like uh how do you
look for idle villagers what's the
shortcut I forgot uh uh I I don't know
if it's the same for you cuz I changed
it sh SH now I'm behind
sh oh
no oh no he's Idol go
here it's done okay there's no Idol
villagers sorry I just woke up oh my
God I'm forgetting everything I learned
me too it's
okay oh my God many many people
so [\h__\h] many many people they are um hey
unemployed
that's fine no that's not fine it's not
fine wait you go here
first okay let's just get this one down
until I have enough for the lumber Camp
okay are there any unemployed
people there must always on the you know
you know even if you don't know the
hotkey on the top top you can see the
next to the Dark Age thingy you can see
all your idol villagers okay I see I
see
okay oh my god oh it's it's chat chat is
fine okay okay you guys you guys chat
don't make me nervous yo yo yo what the
freak yo yo what the
freak who is this e who FAS Cavalry
she's here oh well don't worry about the
Cavalry scouting wait how do I Scout
anywhere
actually H you have to press you click
click on your scout and then press G
then he starts walking automatically to
wherever so
annoying I can't kill it for I wanted to
kill it but can't whatever what what are
you trying to
killas uh Cavalry yeah because we did we
made a treaty Raina remember oh okay
damn sorry I
forgot sorry I forgot about it what are
these people
doing oh what these people are
unemployed oh wait wait the goats are
um no no no no no no
go also it's never worth it killing the
the Scout because he always moves so
fast so you just like you'll just be
following him
endlessly yeah yeah I guess so and he
just runs away and runs HT it HT it HT
it just going to build houses just
because I can okay okay make sure to
build everything else for your economy
get food food is most important in the
beginning
waya there's so many unemployed people
in
here
yeah oh oh my
God so many Idol people Idols where are
Idols what should I build I should make
a mill for some reason maybe
here
wa it's all right well as long as the
others are you know as chill as
you it's all
right
uh go go go well then if everybody's
like you then I'm I'm more concern more
more relieved and concerned but also
relieved also
[Music]
relieved oh not enough
wood H so many unemployed people what
are the unemployed people going to do
hey
Kara what are you doing with your
unemployed people yeah I make them work
on wood I make them work on food I make
them work on Stones uh like everything
all the resources most important in the
beginning is food and wood I would say
gold is not not gold is not the priority
right now okay I'm going to tell all the
unemployed people to work on stuff
okay make sure my God so many unemployed
people make sure to always have your
town center be building uh some new
villagers
okay wow I'm afraid of the goats are the
goats
aggressive h no the goats you can just
you you have to shoot them twice but
they don't fight
back
okay wood is also very important yeah
wood and um food so you can go to
berries or go kill
animals okay good good good I would I
would recommend to have at least two
people working on one animal because um
if you're not fast enough the animal
will Decay before you can get all of the
meat out of it you know okay
[Music]
okay okay okay I think uh everybody's
not
unemployed okay good oh I should uh
yeah I did my
homework I did I did
um I'm like
okay come on actually they're like so
far away I should build a
mill really really yeah you should
minimize the paths that they have to
walk as much as possible I I guess yeah
because that's like that's like the key
to becoming successful in your
economy okay I see I
[Music]
see I I see I
see what do I build
next cron is fast castling
NY
n but she doesn't have a castle yet
right
NY we don't have any unemployed people
here it's
fine
she's it's going to be fine it's going
to be fine also ma said I can look at
chat we can all look at chat she said so
yeah we can mhm it's it's a chill
tournament okay it's not like like a
stuck up tense oh my God I have to win
tournament yeah we're just chilling well
actually there's no unemployed people
here
H I'm so far from my
Town Center oh
well oh
well oh well but how much oh make sure
to get to feudal age Advance as fast as
possible but for that you need a lot of
food okay so food really
important okay we want upgrade to how do
we upgrade to when you click on the town
center on the bottom left it will tell
you how much you need like 500
food okay
two dark aged buildings so I already
have a Mill and I already have a
what I already have a house do I need
something else you need a lumber camp
and the mining
camp Oh I guess
so
wait I heard I heard before when there
was an ID tournament that you were like
not too
bad really yeah I'm just doing my thing
I am just doing my thing hello Bo I'm
going to C
you I'm going to kill you
dead R is so chill that's fine that's
fine we don't need to be try hard I'm I
don't
worry
I'm not even using my shortcuts
meat we need
[Music]
meat yeah yeah we need
meat okay we need meat and we need
houses I guess
so
[Music]
okay okay
now
more okay now oh God I want to I need to
save food now I want to get to feudal
H yeah I want to get to feudal as fast
as possible but you always have to
continue creating villagers very
important um yes yes okay okay
okay
yes okay
okay hey you I want you to make a
house how to make a house I
forgot eh uh in the buildings the first
one there's actually a hotkey queue for
it maybe I can remember try hotkey
Q I forgot how to build a house hoty key
q q press
Q yeah I
did I did oh wait I need to select the
Villager let okay there's so many
unemployed people actually oh
[\h__\h] how
do
why do I hear double oh my
phone my phone was playing the stream
okay I want this oh do I need to be
feudal in order to activate this chat
this unemployed rate is too
high the rate of unemployment is too
high that that doesn't sound
good yes F okay
okay okay let's get enough wood so that
when waya asks me for wood I can give
her wood yo literally don't rely on me
though try to get your own wood there's
no there's no more animals what the hell
well then you have to you surely have a
berries and then um you can put Farms
right next to the mill attached to the
Mill
Farms
yeah
yes uh wait oh oh I need houses now
[Music]
what do I have to
do excuse me I don't understand
though I
don't wait the rate of unemployment is
so
high I can advance let's go he it tells
the others when you advance right yeah
how do you advance I already click
advance but it's not you don't have
enough food probably oh I already not
builds subtracted my food uh then it
takes some time you
know oh you need to build more houses it
says I'll build a
house I'm being attacked by fauna is
that her it's just her Scout probably
has it already 20 minutes
really I don't think
so why can't I do it now
Hey cuz I'm not people yeah many many
unemployed
people
I and they can work on this house if
they're
unemployed m
I don't know oh oh thank you for the
raid hopefully it's not a AOE
raid these people I also don't know
these people are so
unemployed okay there're still creating
villagers
mhm hey don't be unemployed don't be
unemployed yo don't be unemploy I don't
want to build this
now make new
[Music]
Farms what short wait what shortcut
for
hey okay and then they're still queuing
villager still giving birth doesn't
work okay what is this placement my
Farms are so badly placed M me too me
too don't worry don't
worry me too me
too unemployed
people fear of being
unemployed oh it's researching
now
birth into
unemployment okay are we still it's
still researching
y well well that's fine that's fine
that's fine that's fine come on
faster ah finally am I the first sir uh
no F's already cast AG ah huh excuse me
what for real what um what yes you're
lying no no way I'm for
real
nah I'm being for real oh my
God
what I'm being for real then we need to
gal we need to
Gar guess
[Music]
so we need to
G okay but now I can do this now I can
uh I mean there's nobody that's
unemployed here
so he sir nobody's
unemployed oh I found where the other
people are f is the closest to me okay
you're Canan right yeah I'm
Canan yeah well where can I build
stuff there's so much
space there's a relic here ooh
ooh really yeah and there's probably one
right at your doorstep too A
Relic
really wow let's give birth to more
people inside M I want some protection
outside too before they arrive but
okay treaty is
over no treaty no more over no treaty so
sad just building a very peaceful
[Music]
Village how do I build the um Cavalry
and
stuff
Cavalry yeah well you need a once you're
in feudal age you can build
barracks and then you can start uh also
building the Archer range and everything
else MAA Advanced to feudal age Barracks
where M so you need also stable for
Knights you need
Stables where is it oh here it is let's
build a
Barack okay there's unemployed
people going to build this anyway cuz I
like it
um many many unemployed
people and what do we need for Castle
age let's let's
see um cost is meat and 200 gold
improves your civilization more powerful
military
units okay well can we research this
archery range stable blacksmith or
Market well I already have oh two feudal
wait I have two feudal age buildings
what do you
mean what's the like whatever is red
will tell you you don't have enough of
so it's maybe food if you already have
all the feudal buildings
not
sure says I need
to just trying to use the houses as a
wall Stables to stabilize the villagers
mentality so
true oh I can go to Castle
age let's go military buildings out let
[\h__\h] go how good right I know oh here
it is build stable let's build
it
actually I want many
many there's many unemployment
people oh wait there's already
one no
[Laughter]
no I'm just that didn't happen
okay now will we be able to advance okay
thank you combat
unemployment what is one
villager we need to broo broo broo broo
broo and then how how to focus
on which
one can we help why can't we upgrade
this I don't know is night starting from
Castle age I don't holy [\h__\h]
uh oh so many
unemployment many many
unemployment
uh no why so many unemployment guys
please give them
jobs I don't know why they're so
unemployed Castle soon Castle soon there
we go Let There we go Castle
baby let's
go spamming the knights wait that means
that I can also build a
castle should I build one inside and
then some outside to like you know close
get closer to them oh is crony the
closest to me on the left side seems
like it yeah I guess
so p Ah P you Advanced to Castle AG
winner
yeah and then I'm
researching and there's still
unemployment here which is good I think
hey upstairs and then now what should I
make I don't
know what should I
make I think is that all I need that one
spot there should I research
[Music]
this
upgrade Pik men but I guess
no zero unemployment rate
H should I build
[Music]
something okay okay
okay should I which one should I get
guys maybe these
ones I don't know I don't know Siege so
this
no Siege order
order why no Siege
order why can I not build
Siege ton archers are bad oh okay how to
scout scout what else then the
skirmishers scouts are generally not too
bad for raiding oh I need a black oh
[\h__\h] uh that was
here m
yo where's your
kingdom uh uh left side of the map
kingom oh [\h__\h] this is the wrong
one I'm like
H okay no unemployment here which is
good but also I don't know I'm not sure
what I'm supposed to do
two Castle age
buildings or Castle how do I build a
castle you have to become I think you're
already Castle age right so then you go
to the military buildings or whatever
they're called there's a castle there
around the where the where you can also
build the walls it's on the first
page some has Mar
shoot these people aren't mining stone
they're mining gold
oh yeah you need
both especially now that you Advanced so
much you really need like
everything
whoops oh you that was your trading
center ah well maybe I need a market
too let's build a house oh maybe I
should have made it further apart wait
where's my Trading Card wait how do I do
this where's your Market uh I'm building
it
now okay it's it will be in the
like back like behind side of my Camp
next to the town
center
okay oh it's kind of close to my farm up
soon
okay oh I can go to Imperial age the
[\h__\h] do I really want that I guess so oh
look at my Army I don't guys did you
agree that I should do skirmishes
instead or what wait I need a sieg
Workshop uh wait hold on um yeah how to
build I
forgot um University
or monk go go go go go monk go yo what
the hell she's building a Wonder cron
well then I will build one
too soon
soon the thing is like she gets auto win
if the wander survives for uh 200 years
or
so what is
this I'm going to
sell
wood I don't
[Music]
know oh okay um
near the barracks how to build
blacksmith guys I want to build stuff
but I forgot the
menu like a lot of this is just me
looking for the
[Music]
menu ah here it
is more more wood more just more more
more wood always need more
wood build Monastery University
hey can we build University I think we
can build a university hell
yeah reduce unemployment by building
university see we even have unemployed
people already
yo where's your Market is oh I'm going
to send mine my card now to you um
there
okay my market looks like the same as
yours
so yeah
yeah wait and then what okay I'm
bringing
gold so is that it so is that what I do
wait uh
okay and
then oh there's another
one oh no that's a
night uh monk monk haak haak [\h__\h] monk
faster murder
holes
okay
[Music]
nice I got one Relic oh and I'm at
Imperial H let's go oh let's go let's go
um what are you doing
now Elite toonic Knight yo my stones are
gone where do I look for
stone oh they're
outside there's like stones
outside where's um the I'm going to
build a mining camp here fortify my
house
walls okay upgrade blacksmith Knights uh
blacksmith blacksmith
blacksmith uh I don't
know wait Cavalry was the people on
horses right infantry is the bow
shooters
what ouch yeah okay something like that
okay yes okay okay okay okay oh
sir nice nice nice nice nice oh no more
unemployment okay then I will go
proel don't tell her guys if somebody
goes over to crony's chat and tells her
that I will be mad oh they're out of
stone
uh what was I going to
do let's build
stuff how do I build stuff again no the
menu is
gone what do you click first if you want
to build
something
yeah uh
I'll select a villager
right okay
okay they already told her
great
faster okay no unemployed people
here this
okay let's go and
go no unemployed people yes unemployed
people can I not go
[Music]
inside how do I send them
inside wait how do I have
Garrison wow these people are so
unemployed
[\h__\h] I'm getting scared cuz now it's
getting serious like yeah bye uh really
did he get the Relic I think he did
um
uh oh wait I should I get
crenelations there we go if I get
crenelations on one Castle it gets it
for every Castle yeah okay okay okay
okay okay okay
ah
we can't let crony win with the Wonder
no wa we will have to eventually attack
crony for real for real because
otherwise she gets an automatic win if
her wonder that she's building survives
more than what was it 200 years or
so okay
yeah oh wait isn't the aren't the other
team thinking the same thing too I don't
know if they why is her wall open here
oh is my castle shooting
at why is her oh it's because
her whatever it's just open she farmed
the trees right she doesn't know that
she has an open
wall okay um what are we
[Music]
doing should I make walls how do I make
walls um it's also in the military
buildings menu
is it this one not stone wall
right palisade Wall oh [\h__\h] my castle is
attacking crony's
thing oh whoops she'll be mad he
doio my Castle's range is just too big I
can't help it crony I'm sorry I'm not
even trying to do that oh oops oops oops
oops
hey I'm not ready to attack I want to
play defensive I don't want to be
offensive I'm scared she doesn't even
notice that I keep on like killing her
villagers does
she I don't rush before walls
up but I there's no way that I can
really do anything
right there's no way that I'll succeed
also she'll send like she'll get maa's
help
uh um
I'm being attacked
by the
gate what about the gate what is the is
this attacking me ah this
thing why is the light why is this
only wait I don't know if they're
ready
no don't kill my
castle
Okay okay something like that I guess yo
you're unemployed go help
build
what is
on
fight what is going
on build a
gate we're having a a nice battle right
now
what you
guys you guys said you can Team the
thingy oh like this like this uh oh like
this okay nice nice
nice they're so slow though they're so
slow wait two doors here okay
fine Abby
Abby okay okay oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] I'm kind
of doing
it oh really wait I no wait am I orange
I'm orange I'm orange yes I'm doing
it chill chill chill chill chill
chill where's her wonder is this the
Wonder nah her is there is that
Wonder y nice okay
okay where are my other other there they
[Applause]
are why can't I upgrade to
Paladin sorry I'm going to I'm losing it
I'm absolutely losing it are you having
fun shaking I'm
shaking yo let's support you okay her
Wonder's dead I killed her Wonder yo
let's go
girl oh I what's wor what do I destroy
next I don't
know you can destroy anything that you
want wait I'm just making farms and
stuff I need stones y I need stones
Stones you need
stones yeah but it's okay oh my God I'm
out of stones that's so
crazy maybe I can trade or not sure are
we dying should I
Retreat who the [\h__\h] is
green green is faer is FAA helping crony
or is she joining the attack
is she joining the attack yeah trying
probably trying to like a third uh what
you call it oh take advantage of all
right are wean like for this moment a
team yeah trying to find an opportunity
oh no this okay she's attacking my
castle no I will not accept that girl
you have to control your things if you
want to work together
FAA no no girl no you can't do that mm
I'm just going to build another
one uh what was
all F see see was a bad
decision bad decision anybody
unemployed okay I don't want to deal
with the elephants though [\h__\h]
no elephants you should attacking this
thing
okay go away are her elephants
retreating
too okay anybody
[Music]
unemployed what's
Loom
hey oh they're still going oh they're
still going cron isn't even trying to
defend herself n while Kiara is fighting
crony Raina is fighting unemployment
yeah sorry way I'm like so focused on
this hey her
stupid you
no it's okay I'm com I'm combating
unemployment
sck how dare she how dare
she
okay unemploy what could help
me it seems that unemployment is going
to be defeated she's
retreating she's retreating okay I'll
Retreat
too nice nice nice nice nice nice
[Music]
nice I'm being attacked by MAA really
really I don't think so I don't think
[Music]
actively
hey shut up
chunky sh
sh um let me look for a moment at
everything else okay
Stone I'm going to run out of stone
too
H okay oh also I guess I need I just
need more trade cards okay going to
rebuild my
Army okay chill guys chill guys chill
stop attacking
them Garrison in here whoa is that a
tiger tiger oh yeah that's a wild animal
I think will the tiger attack
me my bottom well they won't know
this oh my God no gold are you serious
we have fallen into
poverty those
shal I guess can join the Gold when in
doubt get gold fall into poty where's
our
Market yo yo little shits you really
think this is you really think you
really
[Music]
think how do I get my two tonic Knights
out on
Garrison yo look for gold my
homies look for
gold where's my market I don't know
where my market is oh here it
is I'm going to say
okay I don't think I'm ready to go like
that deeply
in sir I'm I'm on my way I have like
some cavalries I invent I I gave birth
for you
okay together we shall kill
crony yay m
but I'm kind of poor right
now I need to look for
gold need to
dig for gold what else could I
do oh my gosh this person unemployed oh
she's a builder
though blacksmith blacksmith uh
blacksmith so much unemployment in
here why why are you you all
unemployed everybody's
unemployed wait is there no mining spots
here I still researching hings okay
thank you Kelly thank you
Kelly I'm actually doing it man I'm
actually my my practice was actually
kind of worth it yo let's go I want to
make some I don't know should I make
a where
is where is just
thing that is it the mango now the thing
that you place and then it goes boom
boom boom but then it has to like it
always has to place itself which one was
that do you get what I'm talking what
are you talking about I have no idea
the yeah where is the cuz I I'm blind ah
here this
one let's make a
few okay oh shift dot to select all gabo
people at once holy [\h__\h] that's game
changing
should I research con
conscription I'll just keep on making my
Army bigger oh hey girls you're done
[\h__\h] there's some more gold here I don't
really need the
gold hey how many paladins do you want
me to you know come
over uh
all no what do you mean all 15 20 wait
you know what I'll just Build Another
Castle she won't see that
coming kind of close to the other one I
guess
but just to keep a chain going I I'll
just surround everyone of
Castle what was it I'm shaking by the
way guys this whole time I'm shaking I'm
just oh the
no can they kill it yeah by oh yes they
[Music]
can okay creating wait you know what I
really want to do put the experiments
still you're still fighting uh no I'm
preparing Another Castle oh my my castle
is like shooting on the archery the
whole time did she give up her
archery okay okay I wonder if I should
Build Another
[Music]
Castle I wonder what else I should
research ah [\h__\h] should I research on
Pikeman I'm not
sure okay what's going on what's going
on what's this cart doing
here
okay do people need to be also in the TR
no they're
packed
siret more
people they're on they're on okay monks
for the elephants what what I don't have
oh to
convert
okay
and then what do we
research do they do they do that
automatically cuz I don't really have
the time to micromanage that conversion
stuff I'll build another unemployment
rate looking good we don't have anybody
unemployed yes everybody's busy will
they stop me from building another
Castle
[Laughter]
h
uh 0% unemployment in the Pavia rain
Empire wait so what what was the answer
chat about the monks do I have to
micromanage the
monks am I actually winning holy [\h__\h]
yes I don't think I can do
that you guys have to remind me
so when I have uh crony has like really
strong um elephants as her units yeah
and I'm going to try to convert them
with my monks but I'm personally not so
confident about it how has she by the
way still not made a wall here when she
knows I'm constantly intruding on her
wall like she has an open wall and I
keep on coming through but she doesn't
care against elephants M I don't know
what's good against elephants are the
elephants employed though I don't think
so your Castle won't let her true oh I
made another
Castle oh she wants to maybe do
something about oh but my castle is too
strong
so yeah you know what oh there's
unemployment here unfor am I dominating
this unforgivable I'll make another
Castle here I don't think I can actually
really manage so many castles
though uh what else could
I oh we need to build more
houses oh nice one
nice okay is there anybody hello you can
make a
house okay [\h__\h] I'm so nervous like my
[Music]
God AOE age of
employment yeah we have houses here nice
how many villagers do you have in your
city e uh 142 what about you nice I'm
only 125 M oh that's fine I I got to
give birth to more
people hey
people oh they're done they just let me
do this why don't they stop
me I don't know is there any resources
oh yeah Lena do you need the
stones not really
okay but I guess I do but also not
really I don't know we can
share yeah okay I don't know how to
share
I think my Army is like ready but I'm
I'm mentally not
ready
yeah yeah yeah so is does yo what the
[\h__\h]
bro oh it's Kiara never mind yeah that's
just me don't
worry orange is friendly color yeah yeah
yeah good good
thanks let me prep some people to
Garrison
inside hear some people
more holy [\h__\h] my Army is going to be
huge coroni can't stop you just wipe I
was so ready to throw down oh I'm going
to go
soon I'm I'm going to go to cron in very
soon do you want to you probably don't
have to join me I can probably do it
alone yo I'm being attacked by fa
e she maybe she sees you as a weak
person attack her back but maybe maybe
don't worry maybe it's just her Scout
like just one make sure it's a real
Attack might not be a real Attack no I'm
dying I
think upgrade units where how what what
should I upgrade what
else
this infantry was it Cavalry
cavalry
[Music]
my castle
castle there's
create R do you need help yeah I do uh
fun is attacking my base from the East
side her
elephants yeah
her so
annoying do I
have should I send my whole army or just
half of
it do we need to repair or maybe we
build another
one anybody
unemployed I'll just put a castle here
they destroyed your
Castle yeah
no I'll send some people I'll send some
people to make
it they're so mean to me I'm going to
give birth to
is she still attacking you or did she
Retreat uh she already retreated oh okay
wait then I'll go attack crony
now we're full
force nice we're going to let her go to
sleep IRL because I'm sure it's late at
her
place why is FAA attacking me all the
time
crony just accept it just accept
it why are you attacking the fields
don't do that yeah like why what is this
sparkly sound it's my monks right
okay it's so annoying why where's her
Town s where she's harassing
me what fauna is still harassing you
yeah she is she cannot do that she will
she will feel
karmer oh she killed did she kill my
villagers uh she killed my villagers I'm
so sad oh cuz I thought I was sending
them wait I'll don't worry don't worry
just stay strong I'll take down crony
and then I'll take down everybody who
hurts
you okay which one is the Town Center
this no wait what's the Town Center is
this the Town Center I don't know what
the Town Center looks like that's a
mill monaster no we're jobless now her
place is empty did she move in with Muno
or something her place is literally
empty H wow
really she doesn't have one where did
she go what is going
on is she even using this
place she did move in with
MAA okay do I need to like kill this
place to officially let her and I have
to kill her Town Center or what h
H well I guess some population cut would
be fine oh there's actually unemployment
here
unforgivable can you guys not go for the
gate like what the
[\h__\h] um I'm apparently now going to
attack MAA just so you know okay because
they're where is is crony cuz she moved
out of her place a while
ago oh her castle is here all right all
right um where are I me where do we
meet uh maa's
Corner oh muna's
Corner Hey sir here oh I see it
yeah hey sir I need to gather all my
people first come on come on faster
faster yo the horse is being chased
by
dude they're being chased
by they're being freaking chased with
stuff is there a shortcut to get all of
all all all of
all all of uh my
Army Hey
sir
okay I'm going to build a castle to
protect
you nice thank
you that's so nice of
[Music]
you oh
girl I'm going to make my tripet are
very um is that you is you are you
helping me at maa's Place yeah yeah I am
a wait we need to take care of this
unemployment though
unemploy probably going to be too
late uh wa can you send your horses to
uh help me uh cuz MAA is kind of
destroying me oh sorry sorry
they the ones that you already have here
okay
okay she isn't I destroyed her really I
need I need to get rid of this [\h__\h]
pisses me
[Music]
off never
Castle here
what's this oh you sent you sent some
Tes can you uh make them attack um like
anything at the walls
yeah of course of
course thank you thank you we're we're
going in we're going in oh she's she has
some people Yeah
by what's the shortcut for uh uh Army
please guys I'm I I'm not looking I'm so
sorry tell me tell
me oh we your backup is is so helpful
right now
Raina
ctrl1
ctrl1 uh that's not really all of them
is it is
it yeah you're going to
build build I can't believe I'm kill
killing ma let's
go yay let's go let's go let's
go Rams
[Music]
attack
attack attack oh my god oh my
god let's go R we're winning we're
[\h__\h]
winning and they don't stop coming and
they don't stop coming I keep on
creating my two tonic
kns
[Music]
yay wait is her Town Center down so why
am I not winning she needs to resign
now now now now now what do I attack
next I don't
know does she have a another town center
German
engineering German engineering let's
freaking
go
German
engineering so I'm like a little scared
actually of like fauna and Ana because
uh they're oh don't worry about
Ana don't worry about don't Faun
maybe fauna
maybe so I need something to counter
fauna's elephants that's the thing so
Pikeman for elephant or something eh I'm
still not sure about that
I'm going to give birth to more Pik
men I think you can move your tet that
are outside to go more inside okay sure
oh wait she has castles here I didn't
see let's go
Tres let's go
TR maybe monks monks for what oh yeah I
don't even know where my monks are like
I have no idea that I was never going to
really use
them what's going on here how to make
how to give birth to
monks she's going down she's going
down I'm not even using my full power
because I don't know
how me too I'm just like randomly you
know doing
this
okay MAA Castle all down I think unless
she has something hidden somewhere oh
you're building near Red okay yeah
yeah I am are they stopping
me well then I'm going to separate the
attention to I'm on my way to Red then
after this
okay uh red red red yeah uh we're going
to just quickly kill Cron's
Castle all right gosh tushes have a huge
reach what was it ctrl1 but that's not
all wait there's unemployment here it's
not
right get down go down I'm being
attacked by fauna really is it the
castle oh don't worry FAA I'll just
build another
one um are you on on your way to um red
now uh almost yeah she's she's killing
my villagers in my castle that's okay I
make
more oh Fun's coming F Fun's coming to
help elephants are coming by the way
well now now Wawa is
[Music]
coming how do I choose
everybody ter repairing stuff
here should I pull
back see you are they not Retreat like
re resigning like why I
mean what do they nobody I think like
nobody knows how I think nobody nobody
knows resign here no no as in like
nobody knows resign
like I'm not going to Res design for
sure FAA probably
has yeah built an army this whole time
so to to
retreat yeah I see Fun's Army in the
middle oh my God she has a lot of
elephants
yeah she has a
lot of
elephants what's all this fighting still
oh your horses are still trying to
destroy things you do know you have a
lot of units on the top left of muna's
uh area they're just doing nothing
yeah they're just doing nothing it's to
micro
that's fine I totally get
that is this Fest
stff she's not my T are kind of um she
doesn't
know no my
tush oh Ana
St oh Ana coming mhm but just with a
little
bit like in this time what is what is
MAA and crony even going to
do what are are they trying to like
recreate
or not sure
[Music]
actually stop that stop
it what is happening she is destroying
the castle as I build
it who oh
FAA
mhm oh I hear
something I hear
something oh where am I creating Scout
Cavalry oh my God please
great
Paladin and I'll create the
Pikeman more
Pikeman is my monk here how do I find
there he is I don't
know oh wait that's you that's you oh I
was worried about it what what what's
going on
uh what is going on everyone all the
enemies are keeping me so busy that I'm
like losing track of of my things right
of of my resources I know I'm just like
I'm looking for like these Lost Child
lost children you know
he where are my lost children they're on
the
way okay
okay are they doing anything here at all
oh my God they're these guys literally
doing
nothing H are they um are Mauna and and
crony just sitting back and chilling now
I don't know on people coming Ona people
coming oh
okay Ah that's that's just that's
nothing but okay let's attack I guess we
can attack
now we you know assert our dominance
mhm let's
go let's go let's freaking go
oh together pavi
strong
yes are these oh you still have some
things in maa's Camp by the way oh
really oh my God
these these little
thingies what are these guys doing I
don't even
know what's going on what's her Town
Center that's a castle that's a town
[Music]
Center yeah straight pieces everywhere
like yo what are you doing oh elephants
are coming elephants are coming oh no
careful care where is my
monk I don't
know where the [\h__\h] is my
monk what's with the
blacksmith
elephants
coming y
y
ah okay it's okay it's
okay uh my city my peaceful City why can
I not sell more at
once
what are you doing move sorry I'm
talking to my own people I'm getting
very very very very
very
excited can you aim wait that's that's
not
you yeah like the people aren't like
attacking I'm just like please can you
attack you
know okay well I it's it's not the best
way of doing things but we are currently
destroying Anya just fine and we're
keeping fauna busy for that
[Music]
too you had the [\h__\h] elephants like I
don't
know yeah I don't know where all my
monks are they're probably dead by now
yeah I'm going to make more hell Birds
what was I going to do oh
yeah
my units are too used to the peaceful
life you
know yeah B the [\h__\h] elephants the
[\h__\h]
elephants the [\h__\h] elephants she just
has a million of
them it's okay I'll make more I'll make
more that's not really worth it is it
that's not worth
it there will be peace once the
elephants are gone
yeah B it's killing all my units yeah
yeah it's okay it's killing mine
too let's just um let's just I'm going
to rebuild stuff basically
okay mhm nobody cares about our empty
our wall our walls that are broken
that's
good yeah my whole Army is being SW
let's regroup let's regroup
M no I don't want to give
up stupid elep costly it's going to be
costly it's okay just regroup
[Music]
okay
oh it's too late it's too
late
NY too late
give me
a okay okay I'm going to go to your
place we will attack uh FAA cuz she's
more dangerous I'm building I'm building
a castle on her side right now
Pikeman
Pikeman can I upgrade them them to H
deers yes you can apparently uh Pikeman
are good for um elephants anything with
a spare or a pike or H actually also
archers
apparently sorry guys I'm saw to late
cuz I'm like so I'm trying to multitask
and multitasking is the thing I do the
worst I literally can't it's okay it's
okay I mean we did some action yeah I
think it's
nice also this whole map is running out
of resources is what I'm
feeling you're being attacked by wild
animals I mean I don't know
oh just destroy everyone like you did
recently okay yeah I just need to
rebuild I guess did I build a castle uh
didn't I build a castle just now
somewhere no okay you have like so many
castles there it's
cute yeah baby castles I need
Stone yeah the map is just out of stone
all we have is
wood
okay [\h__\h] I hope this game is ending
soon I
know kiah was
Enterprise yes get some from crony's old
base that's gold U gold I only say
gold oh I need Stone pH me too but worst
case you can buy it for your Trade
Center
yeah what's happening right now what am
I doing I'm like I am I'm building an
[Music]
army
um do you want to attack fauna from um
the right
side
yeah I'm I'm making a castle I want to
um get rid of that that um her castles
you
[Music]
know where the Pik
man oh she's coming she's coming she's
coming she's already coming she's
already
yeah yeah she's already coming uh uh I
think somebody's just straight up uh
telling her that I'm doing this and that
you know
probably uh wait I'm not somebody's
definitely just straight up telling her
that I'm doing this and that I'm not
quite
ready I'll send some people but it's
probably not that much wait oh yeah
she's attacking my uh
vill it's a lot of
elephants this one
going to try focus on my mocks now and
get the
elephants do I have to do it one by one
do you have monks yeah only a
few yeah like for elephant on my um
walls
literally crazy
I'm coming I'm
coming I'm
thaning yeah they're coming in my
Village my Village has no
defense I'm
coming no F you cannot hurt my
wife
no no no no where where are the monks
where are the monks
he Yeah by my to my the thing is with my
Knights they're so
slow she's killing your town center you
should build another one if it goes down
I think
mhm I'm going to build a town center how
do I build a town center again uh here
I'm going to move with you
actually I'm going to move to your place
wait are my monks dead they're
dead you you could do that yeah I guess
yeah
[Music]
um yeah I'm just going to build a town
they are doing it do you have some
Pikeman to attack the elephants it was
they were kind of doing
it yeah hold
on
but yeah she's destroying you I can't
stop her yeah it's okay it's okay let's
just uh focus on other
things let's
build shift
Dot
yo the trade card just doing nothing we
yeah we can't trade anymore cuz your
Trade Center is
dead yeah it's okay it's okay you you
could build one like like really far
away yeah I'm I'm I'm building right
now building the houses wait what's
going on
he Hey sir
yeah let's make elephant I mean let's
make elephant let's make
Pikeman okay um yeah I I'm also creating
like millions of them
mhm I I'm
so
okay
wait he still on that
[Music]
dying want to make it here
actually [\h__\h]
[Music]
sake okay we have to
attack Yeah by she's attacking my pretty
castle ah she has millions of [\h__\h]
stupid
elephants yeah I guess that's like the
reality of 2v2 V2 you know yeah while
while we were killing killing crony and
everything else she was preparing
millions of elephants and then like cuz
we're already like hurt from like
attacking MAA she makes the final sweep
it's all right though
[Music]
no oh I think she's coming from my
place she is
uhoh she
is for Real yeah we let her prepare for
too
long
no stupid [\h__\h] elephants I swear to
God yeah do you have enough Pikeman cuz
I no like I mean I thought I had but
she's like swiping wiping
them yeah the thing is like as as long
as we're not attacking her at all she's
going to keep generating those elephants
you know mhm well she I think she
brought probably most of them to me
they're like at my walls
now but she can create more where is she
going that's the thing where is she
going
yeah
later where is she
going what
see I don't know where she's going she's
leading me
away B you maybe
yeah elephant
[Music]
parade let's make
walls
oh you're making walls you're so
cute baby
walls they're coming back though she
lost the elephants oh there they
are
give
birth the house like
this damn it takes a long time to
convert them
yeah
yeah attack them oh my God those are
look the elephants too
oh oh what's that fighting
sound oh I don't
know I'm just going to give birth to
Pikeman it's not over yet it's not
over
I don't have stone do you have stone
nearby no I keep on selling my other
resources to get stone and gold cuz like
this map is
empty oh my but I forgot to do
this going to take crony's
resources
yes we're getting ready waa we're not
not going to let them have this
okay
okay what are they doing for real for
real like are they just
waiting oh ah they're trying to destroy
your castles
but as long as they're busy with it with
[Music]
something what was that
fauna well yeah fauna is going to be
coming soon so if you have Barracks
create some more Hal deers and Pikeman
or
whatever she's on her way we need to be
ready I'm going to I'm going to
[Music]
make it's the end of the game probably
so just going to use all my
resources okay I want to make Market
we need to build more houses damn
it can you build priests you mean
monks yeah yeah yeah I've been I've been
doing that yeah okay good but it's it
just takes endless time
to do something yeah I need to build
more
houses
fa incoming uhoh
oh she's going there she's at Elena
attack attack attack time to
attack oh she's attacking from
here
a I don't have Tre that's the
thing
sorry Where's My Town Center
uh-oh uh-oh I'm too
slow they're too
slow this is not
happening what are they
doing taking
advantage yeah
I can't build
houses yeah my uh my Pike men are gone
because they're
outnumbered oh
no so sad what do we
do I can't make a castle cuz I don't
have enough Stone I don't have a market
either
no my
relics my beautiful beautiful
relics I'm at the level while I actually
need to build
houses yeah it's it's kind of over but
like if I resign now does it
automatically put me on the last spot
just because I resigned first yeah
that's the thing cuz like um we already
destroyed the others like um we already
destroyed the other
uh thing but they wouldn't reside yeah
it
does then I won't give up maybe it will
give me credit for the things I
did thund Z croni and MOA didn't well
then how do we know it's over when do we
decide it's
over chat how do you open I don't know I
don't know how to control
this I don't know what to do to end this
nobody's resigning
ever
last place is always lowest score not
first to
resign
really but if you resign that means
um stupid
ass I hate elephants
[Music]
forever I know [\h__\h]
elephants sh B Be Be Bel low profile be
low profile
what do you mean don't don't don't
engage unless they engage it's too late
anyway I guess
so yeah the thing is last what does Last
Man Standing
mean I don't even
know how many villages do I have one
let's take Cron's place let's seek
Refuge refuge
on
place no it's
[Music]
over it's over my last uh dude is
dying oh okay my last villager
dead but we need to keep building so our
score stays
up
uh well we are not last waya that's for
sure that's for sure I guess we were
dominating for the longest
time but in that time FAA was building
her elephant
Army elephant Army El
elepant well where are my
villagers I don't see them are they
working on
something oh they are working on
something I don't want to retreat and
rebuild I'm done I'm I want to
sleep this is so if like it makes no
sense to do that now in my opinion
because like it's already decided like
there's no use but at the same time it's
uh it's XI but at the same time it's
like you know I'm going to resign cuz
this is so stupid you want resign
yeah it's [\h__\h] this I did
enough yeah me too I think I did enough
you should resign too it's under
Escape okay the second
one I guess so but what happens when you
resign I hope that the one person who
said that the score matters more than
the resign uh was right cuz then we
would be ranked
higher m i I guess so but the thing is
if Muna and crony is not resigning and
they keep building and building we're
going to
lose I don't think they're building oh
wait they
are they are they cover wait I I've been
telling you that I didn't see
that wait there's so much trees here
what the [\h__\h]
mhm well what the
[\h__\h] yo like fauna like can you like go
to like Moon and CR and check out if
they're like building yeah she shouldn't
waste her time with my castles fauna you
can go I
resigned go to crony uh MAA
whatever yeah I don't know the rules but
they should have retired they should
like normally when you're playing this
game in normal online they would have
resigned ages
ago
yeah wait
what um
um can I just leave they're rebuilding
look at this why don't they just attack
these people before they grow too
big yeah why are they attacking my dead
castles and muna's dead walls yeah oh by
the way I'm uh I'm
dead cuz I have like zero people I
think I have zero houses or something
H I want to see like what's going on
though what's on your screen right now
uh I I went back to the map and I'm just
watching what's going on but okay okay
okay she stopped her elephant's
movement well yeah we'll see
though so do I do we just wait another
five years
or maybe I'm uh let's try let's try
resign okay
yeah you have you you have common
sense uh yeah they need to destroy all
the production buildings Last Man
Standing literally means that I don't
know how long this will end it didn't
even but even when like all my villagers
and stuff were in my town center and
everything were dead even de I don't
know there's the walls or something no
more fog of war ah true true true let's
see what they're
[Music]
doing yeah I guess they take they take
Last Man Standing very
literally yeah a walls don't count if
when you lose all production buildings
well Kiara still has a castle Yeah Yeah
but it's not can you move to my
castle what I
resigned I'm no longer available for
giving
birth like FAS fauna's just scouting
Cron's place now yeah they should go
straight to there in the
[Music]
corner oh thank you
guys I did my
best yeah I did my best I feel like you
know like even though we lost L I think
we did okay you know like we're
literally we're literally the one who
started attacking and stuff yeah we made
we made coron move into MAA and we made
Ana move into FAA so we were dominating
strong it's just like you know I was
doing the piece I was doing the piece
and then I helped you out I played
enough it was a
good and like I think you know
it's fine we didn't really have a
counter for this either but to be fair
they started late as well so I think
it's nice fauna has nice
3,100 power I mean three
3,000 oh my God I can't
English yeah my overconfidence was my
downfall I wouldn't say so my downfall
was just people not resigning when
they're already
dead
but here here we see the final
finale The
Showdown fauna is attacking the
kingdom I like the the
wall uh ar ar architecture that they
have going on so many walls mixed and
entangled it's
beautiful oo they have like several
layers like a like an onion she got
archers they're
rumbling this is so fun to
see oh there's so manying oh I see you
guys in the chat waiting on me I see
you go back the city is like an onion so
like a double they're making like a
double layer thing
mhm it will take a while to destroy
people are coming our elephants are
glitching let's
go historically accurate walls
really it almost looks like a
city yeah like a proper City with like
two layered walls that's pretty cool I
think yo yo yo the invasion of f land
let's
go you're not coming to see an elephant
parade then the elephant parade is
coming to see you did you read that from
chat or yeah
chat
yo wait what's going on in oh fauna
place is pretty well symbolized I need
to copy her building Strat okay like
this Farms yeah pretty much oh she made
double
walls yeah she made double walls which
is pretty good I guess but only on one
side oh yeah cuz the other the one has
Forest right
very orderly
yep even though I resigned my resources
are still like our resources together
are still like Place third and
fourth yeah at least in the in that
ranking there I guess MAA didn't know
how to resign
either
L I didn't
know ah P
comes you were in a hard spot I was
trying my best Under
Pressure nice but I mean also I was
having a lot lot of issues as well you
know I tried my best but also it was
also like obviously the lack of
experience in playing the game even
though you play like once or twice I
think most of us didn't have much
experience so yeah I think like chat was
like oh my God we told you it's this you
know at some point and I'm like I don't
know I forget it's fine to
forget it's fine there's so many things
to remember if you want to play
well so many things to manage like
upgrade this build this make your army
make your villagers make your
resources at the beginning like um I
made too many cavalries and I think
that's why like we could like do um
munai and crony fairly uh nicely but
that's the thing I didn't build enough
crony resign I didn't build enough um
Pikeman
Moon never is that it's over oh it's
over time has
stopped time has stopped I guess we
joined them in the VC I guess
so I'll join yeah me
too
G Dam GG
G damn you're military economic oh my
God FAA is really
great yeah she was building she was
building building yeah is still strong
the mother
of that was really
nice I enjoyed that yeah that was fun I
I was so scared with Cara at first like
K put Castle
everywhere Castle I was minding my own
business and here was like yo yo yo yo
Raina can you send some help I'm going
to attack Cronin I'm like
what I was minding my own business and I
was minding my own business too like
everyone was minding their own
business damn Kar was out for blind I
mean I was just trying to get the game
the ball
rolling I guess so before someone rolls
it on me yeah I guess otherwise you know
people would be just like build like me
like
me well me and Anya I feel like we're
playing like a farming simulator me that
was me that was me before Kiara was like
yo help me out I'm like huh what oh yeah
actually the reason I attacked crony was
because she was building the wonderand
and I you know when you build a wonder
you target for
everybody well she building the wonder
she was building Wonder yeah and that
gives you automatic win if you keep it
for a very long time and as we see this
game was going to go on for a long time
so the Wonder could have
won that would have been a good Strat
found I was about to attack but then I
was like if they're fighting each other
then let them
be I just did elephant strategy just
build a million elephants and hope for
the
best wait can we see the I think MAA has
to maybe somebody has to press something
so we can see the the the stats or
something oh yeah stats already here I
say it is it quit current game yeah do
you Do You Really Turn to map go oh nice
nice nice
nice wait where do you see it oh my
Society hi Society statistics we're
living in the
society I click return to
map Co okay
Society a
lot yeah
uhhuh interesting cool cool cool cool
cool a very nice oh when come back to
economy I sent a lot to crony oh oh you
were
trading t t trading oh I had 11 castles
it was good it was good oh I killed
people yay oh
no M very cool o our numbers are
actually not bad yeah nice food
collected
yummy wood collected very cool
oh oh very nice if you look at timeline
you see like the graph of how things are
changing ooh
oh
oh my
god wow just like going up yeah the
tables are turning the elephants all
about the
elephants
yeah let me see I want to see attacking
first was a good strategy
though cuz like we could
focus chilling at
the I was like if they're fighting each
other then let them
be yeah I mean why not that's probably
what you should do let the others fight
but sometimes the intrusive
thoughts
them the intrusive thoughts are just I
understand in my chat people say like
nobody stands in that
way what whatever we do now Alice
SW uh well normally I would have liked
to play defensive too but I don't know I
had to kill the Wonder and then from the
Wonder everything was just like rolling
and I it just happened it just happened
feel like aggression is good it that's
the spice you know yeah I think I
underestimated you guys honestly I
thought maybe you guys didn't practice
enough so you guys wouldn't know what a
Wonder sneaky Wonder out yo
well I streamed it a couple times guys
how do I build the
bar when was constantly
asking yeah don't remember almost how do
I do this how do I do that why are
people
unemployed if if I want to ask for
rematch again would you want to but not
now not now but I'm
totally nice yeah um maybe this time is
uh we we make it pretty pretty easy
because we have a cheating seat in in
our live chat but the next time how
about no cheating [\h__\h] on live
chat yeah pleas sure if you can really
control that and we could we could
randomize the Cs so that everybody gets
something unexpected mons from it's not
months from now cuz by then I'll I
forget about the game
[Music]
already we it just the date immediately
before we forgot how to play again yeah
what I'm
saying what I'm
saying
MH maybe after this I will put another
date yeah so but overall this this seems
fun like like I I'm pretty pretty I
think I understand at a lot of you guys
yeah oh my God that is
crazy again I was scared of you Luna I
was so scared of you no I I told you I'm
not really good at this game you didn't
believe me just because I BL skin
doesn't mean I'm good at it even the
chat said that MAA is good everybody
said you are good it's just that you
were trying to save me and I'm
[Laughter]
sorry I think everyone need a practice
them after
all
no but yeah thank you so much everyone
for playing this game with me uh it's
been fun thank you for organizing yeah
thank you I'm glad it happened
finally it was super fun thank you thank
you it's been we almost doing this like
for like two hours I to leave yeah wow I
know flew by that was a long one like I
the game is going to be two hours oh
perfect perfect timing yeah well um for
this one actually I have a lot of uh
strategy game
um uh each of Empire is like one of them
while the others uh there is another
game called Starcraft Starcraft you guys
interested Starcraft it's another
building game another starting game if
you guys interest I would love to make
another one I'll try it yeah I'd love to
but I need to learn about the game yeah
I need to learn to yeah yeah more more
learning more learning let's
go my brain is going to
explode what it is what it is thank you
so much um I we need to end guys have
any uh maybe information for the
viewers I don't know I'm good no no I
just want to say thank you thank you way
for being a great
teammate thank youa for bringing out the
aggressor
in N
strong for being a really good team like
we we're actually pretty working good
together yeah next time I won't build
the
Wonder
no no you need to build a wonder you
just have to figure out when you're
building the Wonder is your military
already finish also weren't you building
it like at least when I arrived you only
had one person working on the Wonder but
the Wonder takes like so much more time
than other buildings you need to build
with like 20 people at once yeah it need
you need a lot of people and make sure
that uh your military is ready to you
know
why the Wonder I wanted to build one too
someday someday someday
somay that's all everyone thank you so
much I'm going to end the stream then oh
okay yeah thanks
guys let's play
again bye bye membership later bye-bye
[Music]
bye-bye