[Music]
hmm
my
[Music]
good
hello how are you guys doing welcome
welcome welcome
hello what what what did you see what
what what oh but no no i i just
this doesn't mean anything wait how do
you see i'm using swordcraft i i
how do you see that just because of the
cards that happen here you automatically
know
what what that is oh my god you're
amazing
i see there's some people in the chat
already who already played the game
or are still playing the game which is
amazing because you guys can help me
the cards in the main menu is the last
deck yeah yeah i know that i know that
but i i'm surprised you guys recognize
that so
so like instantly oh thank you for the
super chat thank you
so yeah um uh first of all welcome
welcome
we are today playing shadow days
jennifer's uh it was so kind to sponsor
today's
stream yay thank you shadow verse thank
you thank you
everyone thanks shadow fairies for
sponsoring
us
[Music]
so happy yay
um so since uh
we wanna do this right i will explain to
you
what kind of game this is i mean uh
looking at the screen i think it's
already kind of obvious
but it is a card game
[Music]
and it is mobile on mobile and on
computer i'm playing it on pc right now
and i'm actually really grateful
that you can play this on both
mobile and pc without like emulating
anything because
i used to do that for other uh
phone games but here you don't have to
do that because you can just go into
steam and open it up there it's so much
easier yay
also as you can see it has really really
cute
lovely uh anime style artwork which i
really enjoy you guys know
i like games and anime style way too
much i like my games to look
cute so
i'm really i really appreciate the art
style it's like i i really like the
the anime aesthetic and i i really like
some good art in my games
and it has plenty of that like all the
cards look so gorgeous
i love it uh and
since it is a card game it is also kind
of
strategic highly strategic
uh you can't play in your style because
there is um
if you have no idea what this game is
let me tell you
there is like um eight like classes
and each class can like play specific
cards and use specific cards in their
decks some cards cannot be
in certain decks yeah
and the latest card expansion actually
came out yesterday
so this is just in time
you see it right now because the card i
have opened right now on purpose
is a granblue fantasy related card uh
and i have to say i did i don't i don't
play grandpa fantasy
but i've seen it all over the place
everywhere and i really like the style
as well from that game
so uh that just started yesterday
yesterday so with that uh apparently
there came like a bunch of new cards
um i personally played a little bit uh
yesterday and
the day before yesterday i played the
game and practiced
and i got really hooked i have to say
because i actually
in the past when i was younger i played
a bunch of card games
and ever since then i didn't really have
time or interest to play any new or
old card games again um but now
[Music]
but now thankfully to being sponsored by
shadowverse i got into this card game
and i love it i love it
it's really great so let me show you
today
how this game works uh i'm i'm obviously
not a professional yet
but i am hooked i had to stop myself
yesterday to stop playing
i had to stop myself yesterday from
playing because i just
i just i wanted to give you guys more
content
so yeah the crossover with granville
fans let me see okay so
i i already used up like when you start
the game
you get 50 free card packs
uh for the shop just for
like uh completing the tutorial um
so i already because i love gaza i
or i couldn't stop myself and already um
wait a second i already uh used up a
bunch of that
wait a second how about i still have
some left so i think we start
the game by using up a few of those
by the way so i guess that is the
is that that's the grand blue fantasy uh
thing i think
i think because i can recognize the the
art style and maybe that character i
think i've seen her before
[Music]
oh yeah one more thing um if you log
into the game
after this expansion pack came out
then you get number 10 card packs for
that which i have apparently already
used
i already used them so
i used i used those i i had something
for all of those oh i can do a little
more little more of those i can do
a little a little more of those and it
does okay so we'll do that
but the other ones are already used
because you know it's just so much fun
to open up new packs okay but
we still have a few so let's roll a
little bit and then we play
maximum yes please
show me some sexy cards please
let's see what do we got i like how you
like open these and you go like boom
pew pew pew when something special comes
up oh they look so fancy
she looks cute hello i actually also got
some kind of phoenix related cards uh uh
yesterday
one one phoenix related card i think
there's a bunch of oh princess
oh wait isn't that isn't isn't that dude
from
okay i don't want to say anything wrong
but
you guys tell me isn't am i am i going
crazy or
yes princess connect right okay okay i
wasn't going crazy
it's so nice to see like um familiar
characters in this game
what's that it's gold so there's like
bronze cards there's silver cards
and there's gold cards and you know
obviously the gold cards are
the bestest i suppose but um
wait she also looks like she's from
princess connect am i
am i am i wrong because the art style
kind of reminds me of that
what do you guys say so uh let me
oh wait a second that one looks that
won't that one looks
dope oh kelly would like that card
because of the
skulls she is wow that's so recognizable
so yeah um basically if you if you look
at one of these cards let me explain to
everyone who doesn't know the game
uh did the the this part with the with
the six that means you need like six
points to play the card
um you will see that later when i when i
played it play play a battle
and the five is the
wait which one was that this the shield
it has a shield so it should be the the
block how much they can
block and the blue with the uh the blue
one that looks like a sword is how much
they can attack i suppose
i hope i can mix it up
yeah it's defense and attack
but there's also as you can see there's
cards that don't have those two because
they're like either
they're like spells or amulets it's
etcetera
cute i have like four
four more packs
[Music]
[Laughter]
yay
wow come on
hmm we got another cylinder or two
silver ones
and some of them look like fancy some of
them have like fancy effects that's
really cool
oh what's that oh that one that one's
bronze but it still looks fancy see even
though even the
the wink cheap ones um look fancy and
beautiful
there's so much effort put into all that
artwork
done oh there you go now we have another
one of those uh princess connect
characters yay
that was that uh i think can we not into
five more
of course we can do five more of course
we can
let's go oh yeah i did check the
yeah you can evolve cards while you
battle and then they change their
appearance a little bit and they get
sometimes they get extra effects not
every card does that but
some cards gets get extra effects after
you evolve them
so that is her battle though not forever
you cannot evolve them forever
ooh pretty they look so nice
[Music]
that one was huge what's what's up
what's wrong well wow
that's not that's not even gold that's
like rainbow colored
it's a legendary animated legendary
fantasmal fairy dragon ooh that's forest
crap that's perfect because uh
the first deck that the game teaches you
to use is forest craft so
i'm already a little bit familiar with
forest craft
forest craft uh swordcraft etc those are
the eight different classes that you can
use that i told you
oh dansu that's a golden one
legendary is better than gold yeah yeah
i know
obviously legendary is better than gold
is that my i think that
is that my first legendary i wonder
maybe i don't know
okay then we can do this one 15.
i want to do
[Music]
come on show me what you got done
wait we should have checked out the
evolved one from the legendary
guys it's another legendary holy
macaroni i'm telling you
my account has not been changed or
anything
this is normal oh she looks so cute
cowardly
she's a bunny i both oh
she gets like she turns into a fiery
bunny
whenever cars refuse to discard restore
one defense to your leader
using fusing you confuse cards if this
card is first of all this one
card gain bane then if it is fused with
always two cards in word so yeah
since it is a card game you should read
what the cards do
because it is uh quite important oh
golden one
wasn't there a dragon craft too or
something like
oh never that that's another card that
callie would like can i send the card to
kelly
oh that looks wow wow wow
shadowcraft is definitely something for
kelly
well i'm actually not showing it i
played yesterday i played with uh
swordcraft forest craft and havencraft i
tried those three
um deck types wow
wow
holy croo wow wow
wow while it's eating the ship don't eat
the ship now
so yeah yesterday i tried free uh
different
um uh crap
deck types wow oh my god there's so many
gold
golden cards um i'm not sure
which well which one
i like the most yet uh because they're
all so different they do so many
different things
it's like it really
like matters uh like what kind of
playstyle you want to go for
wow we got two legendaries you know
would be proud
oh we got five more though come on what
can we get from that
oh my god one legendary in the other one
and two legendaries in this one
what's what what
i tell you shadow birds didn't even ask
for my account so i i don't think they
did anything to my account
i don't think they did anything this is
natural okay
sugoku named i got this one before
yeah yeah yeah come on give me more
legendaries don't let me
there you go yes i
when this is how you play the game you
tell you tell the game what you want and
the game will give it to you
you tell them don't let the game tell
you what you want you tell the game what
you want that's how it works
oh my god nice
can we get one more
now that was the last one okay that's
weird that's good so we got
three legendaries out of 15 packs and
one legendary
in the other in the other one that we
played as well we have five more for
that one let's go
we're almost done we're almost done
this is not right she's getting so lucky
oh you're just jealous
cute but that one is moving a lot i like
these moving effects there's really so
much effort in this game
oh that looks so fancy
everything's so sparkly makes it look
much much more
interesting whoa
ghostly made it cute this this girl is
cute too
hmm this is the last one
four out of five so there's one more see
that one looks like me
almost i already had that one though
last night oh wow wow
yes okay
well let's see how do we do we have
everything
[Music]
oh no we used it i wanna gotta do more
oh i got that more i want more
can i buy something here so apparently
you can buy sleeves which is really huge
um and you can buy oh yeah you can buy
new leaders so as i told you there's
eight liters but
apparently you can get more leaders
i didn't really oh there's granblue
fantasy leaders
did it looks so cute i want
i want i want
oh oh
ah there's skins for the actual already
existing
ones
so what would that be covering up i
wonder
[Music]
dark huntress oh
skins it's skins for cards
wait does so does she like would she
replace all my cards in one deck oh
well that's that's pretty dope what what
is all that
ah uh uh i see i've seen those before
what's that four thrifted leaders you
can change leaders on the profile screen
oh ah do you look different
no wait no they don't what is that
oh no they do look different is that
just like updated skins i wonder
oh look princess connect
oh man i didn't know you could do that
you could like
yeah i didn't know you could yeah that's
so cool
oh oh my god she's so cute
she's so cute street fighter day oh
wow there's so many it's so good
what okay okay okay and then um so we
did that mm-hmm
yeah i'm not gonna do that on stream
right now but maybe after this stream
so i have played the tutorial actually
let me show you one more thing um
so i think can i sort that obscene scene
i can i
can i sort uh for the granblue cards is
it promo i wonder
no well i wonder what i have to how do i
find them eat the easiest
maybe there's no way to find them uh
wait is it eternal
no there it is
eternal those are the granblue cards
oh and that girl looks like she's from
granville fantasy
oh so see i already got what is that oh
my god
those i got uh for from the grandpa
packs i suppose see this one
this is interesting like when you play
that card you can choose
between having uh gran or sorry i don't
know how to pronounce that is it
or dida um i know yeah i got a phoenix
empress card too yeah i think so
oh oh i didn't know those were granble
fantasy cards
[Music]
oh dj eat up
oh they look fancy wait do i let me see
phoenix oops
oh yeah see i got this feelings guys
it's so cute
[Music]
it's so cute look at it
i got that in my second pool or
something
so adorable i love the art style too
oh man it's so cute this is how is this
a phoenix card
ah at the end of your turn randomly put
one of the following cards into your
hand venus pollock star phoenix
pinteresting now this is runecraft oh
star phoenix what card is that
alright so anyway as i told you um
i already played the oh there's a quest
i already played the tutorial and i
practiced a few
uh battles in the practice thingy but
let's continue with the story i think
the one thing i had um i have
experienced is
when you lose a story battle
two times then the game will offer you
kindly to um
uh help me out and give you a a a
special pre-built deck
and i have made use of that many many
times
but every time i would play the
pre-built back a deck
because it gives you a choice of money
but every time i would use that i would
instantly win
um so i guess i i still don't have the
skills
for building a proper deck just yet oh
wait what
dragon craft on blood craft in this
battle
i can only use dragon club dragon craft
oh my god mr
the tongue twisters dragon craft and
blood craft
uh i don't have such a
i made a few decks okay um oh yeah i did
swordcraft rumcraft and havencraft and
forestcraft
okay what do we do what blackcraft and
what was the other one dragon craft
didn't we have a legendary for the
dragoncraft one
let's uh actually wait wait should maybe
we just make an
automatic one and then we can replace
some cards
uh deck codes what what are the
codes dragon craft or blood craft
this class has cards that can give you
extra play point orbs
in the beginning of a matches oh this
lets you play powerful cards before the
opponent ah in your opening hand it's
best to have cards that give you extra
play point orbs
interesting this class has cards that
lower your leader's defense oh once
selena has 10 defense or less
vengeance will activate strengthening
many other cards pay attention to the
remaining defense of both leaders in
order to take advantage i think i like
this one
bloodcraft is hard to use really okay i
don't know
let's try dragon let's try this one
okay uh the deck has been randomly
generated so you can make it yourself or
you can have it randomly generated or
you can buy pre-built bags
decks however you want i can obviously
not speak
and here at the top you see the balance
of your deck
yeah you see um in the beginning you
start with only
one point to play a card so if you are
if you have
too many cards in your deck that are
like that need five points or eight
points or whatever
then you're gonna have a problem in the
beginning and this one has
uh four cards with one point
eight cards with two points and so on so
that is
all right i guess although we could use
some more i think what is that card
see this is gonna take some time so that
i i find the
the kind of card that i uh the cards
that i want with that
and do you two damage an enemy follower
okay check it oops
wait did i just replace something oh ah
i know it those are the cards i already
have
sorry the upper one is the car the cars
i already have
wait my phoenix is in there my feelings
was dragon craft oh yay
oh i'm happy about that that's great
well anyway
let me put in maybe maybe one yeah so i
want i want i want this one
and i feel like
[Music]
maybe should we put in more with one
one point as i don't know what is this
card once each turn whenever allied
followers destroyed put a copy of that
follower into your hand
ah i mean i mean
sorry not quite sure about the controls
yet i don't want that i put some i will
put something else in there
we have a lot of actually i really like
this card
i do enjoy that card and
[Music]
let's see princess knight
oh we should we should put him in the
deck if he's not in the deck yet
she has to be in the deck come go in
there
you're welcome instead we will get rid
of whatever
that one i don't have so much time to
off screen i
i took a lot of time to look a look at
the cards
but i did not expect us to have a have
to make a dragon
yes i did throw random cats together
because otherwise it would take me a
long time to
figure out which ones are uh the good
ones
[Music]
award whenever another allied follower
comes into play give it a ward
disaster dragon
the good thing is if we lose two times
we get a good deck from the game
[Laughter]
this one looks fancy it should be in the
deck shouldn't it
put it in there let's see
[Music]
deal free damage to a random enemy
follower
it has storm is storm the one that they
can uh that they can attack right away
when they
uh you can actually just grab that
pre-made deck what
how oh wait a second i want to see how
sure what sure how do i
eh how do i get the is it is it the deck
code
can attack leader followers to turn it
back
oh okay okay the arrow
huh go to
go to stop let's go to top left go to
story
next
i need to buy pre-made decks so at the
deck selection screen
select the third tab on the top left of
your screen what
is this the direct selection screen oh
probably rotation
what's the third tab
wait i think i'm getting a screenshot
right now in the quest oh
main story
[Music]
and you sell them okay sorry
okay
[Music]
aha probably here ah
ah ah this one
[Music]
is it this one
is it this one is it this one
yes okay so i guess we're playing blood
craft
i don't get some blood crab okay all
right let's go
hello yes but now
oh well we can do it we can do it with
this one
i turned on japanese voice by the way
but there is an english voicing as well
[Music]
hmm
[Applause]
am i scary
pretty
[Music]
you don't know me
this is the battle between the guys
foreign
[Music]
we've got one imposter among us
i like the background music it's very
very tense
thank you for the red super chat thank
you
yes let's get started
the battle is starting okay so i'm
playing with with a with a deck and with
a leader that i've never played before
um blood craft i the only thing i know
is it it helps me to lower the defense
wait was that the other one
was that the one okay so in the
beginning you get three cards and you
drag
you can drag out the cards that you
don't want in the beginning and i want
some with one cost please
ah i got one perfect okay i got the
rogue vampire that can play in the first
turn that's perfect
wonderful but let me take a look i mean
it doesn't matter that much for the
first card i suppose if rap is not
activated for you what uh
do one damage to your leader authorized
game plus two plus two and rush okay
cool
so on the right for the people who don't
know the game on the right side of the
screen
you see here now i have two points so
every turn you get one more point
and you can use those to play cards so
now i have two points so i can only play
the cards with two points
eventually it will go up to 10 points i
think
also one more thing um here in the
uh left side next to the character you
see my mouse don't you
um there's like these diamonds that are
not
activated right now but with this these
diamonds one diamond
you can evolve a card understand though
yeah and i think it gets activated in
what in nine turns or is that in three
turns i'm not sure
which one that was
uh no no i think it is in three turns
yes okay so now we have two points we
can even play that card with that card
uh if rap is
but she's cute wait she looks cute let's
play her
logic the kiara theory play a cute card
oh we can directly attack the leader
sometimes you cannot ouch
there's some cards that uh will block
you from attacking the leader directly
and when your leaders hp go to zero you
lose
okay now we have three points we could
play the tyrant of the mayhem
card the vengeance is not activated okay
okay okay
let's go with that one
and then what does his car do earth
right put a condor garden
how about
we kill her and we of course also kill
us but that's okay
no problem see we're doing well actually
[Laughter]
oh no chiara is a sexy vampire do you
have a problem with that
next time we have four points so we
could play two
um cards with two points or one with
three and one with one
um what is this one doing some in the
fourth bath ooh
if raf is actually do we want a forest
bat
i think i want to see that forest bat
where is that now
wow this is uh i see is blood crabs
a masochist masochistic type of gameplay
where you hurt yourself but you also
hurt the enemy is that the
the style of playing is it is
interesting
yeah i noticed i've been taking a lot of
damage here and there
oh i i have to say i have some
masochistic tendencies
anyway let's play uh doze
what oh my god am i not going to kill
myself
we will see where this goes okay so i
say
we get rid of this dude bye bye
and then once again we attack the leader
and oh see i recover
do i recover as a vampire do i recover
every time
i put i i damaged a leader is that the
thing with bloodcraft
or am i going crazy or is it only that
uh is it because of the mark that that
card has
drain effect oh interest
it's that car oh good and i want to keep
that card on here because i'm
i'm losing a lot of hp
oh he see we can evolve cards now he
used up one of these uh diamond thingies
to evolve his heart and i have two
i can involve two cards but i'm not
gonna do that right away i think
so first of all bye-bye by the way these
are amulets i cannot attack those
unfortunately so i just attack you
directly
okay and then we play
where should we play
[Music]
let's play this one wow
and this one do you tweet me oh wait no
ah free damage to myself uh no two
damage to myself and free to him
i don't know i don't know man i don't
know that's so dangerous no no no
maybe not right now so
instead we will do do it worth it
okay
he died that hurts
wait oh good night
[Music]
can i know player one wait a second what
i have one more point
[Music]
huh
huh is it because i already no targets
ah because i already attacked elena or
i know it has to be uh enemy followers
ah not the leader okay okay
okay okay well in that case
should i should i evolve
him and then i can attack right away
tactical thinking yes
no
well it's okay we will win this battle
i'm sure oh wait i oh oh a cat oh yeah
right
yeah uh-huh i understand i understand
why you hurt me why are you hurting me
he's only playing amulets what the hell
[Music]
well okay then it means you can't
protect yourself okay you can protect
yourself a bad
little girl or boy it looks like a girl
oh he evolves his apprentice
well both down i don't mind that
wait is this one getting more and more
expensive or am i going crazy
[Music]
[Laughter]
should we play this one
[Music]
oh this is another one of those cards
that gives me hp
nice okay so i think oh we have to
attack that dude
[Music]
and we're back to 20 hp guys we are back
my friends
and you okay
oh my god we're winning guys
what
okay so some cards produce other cards
by the way this is probably why that
card suddenly
uh appeared i i'm not about quite
familiar with this leader so i'm not
sure what's happening that much
[Applause]
[Music]
what is that at the end of your turn if
rap is activated for you invoke
uh this card then banish all nights of
purgatory from your deck
pull by the way do you see this uh
shield mark it means that the
the enemy followers cannot attack me
directly they first have to kill this
one
in order to attack me you want to stand
up
should we use some of these uh right
actually wait wait a second
jump to my damn ah
we have to get rid of that we have that
one first
[Music]
[Applause]
i should have used to raise a claw
oh i see okay
okay when we first get ouch you out of
the way
and then we attack with her
nice he's almost dead and now we play
this one
i have a wolf meow senpai okay
uh yep that's that's my turn that's my
turn
what i missed lethal what
what sorry i don't understand
[Music]
i'll win anyway next turn i'm winning
unbelievable winning on the first try
no he's wiping out my team
how dare you how dare you
i did wait i might it does free damage
right
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
you
[Laughter]
okay
please keep playing my favorite card
game oh it's your favorite
let me see in the chat who here um has
played or does play shadow ways
raise your hands of hands
what so many oh my god have i been
have i been missing out on something i
seem so
what there's so many oh my god
just science playing what beta tester
what what
oh my god so many
five thousand hours
[Music]
so i saw one feature in the game you can
like take part
in tournaments and join gills
i i guess those guilds uh make the
tournaments
that's really interesting i guess i
guess tournaments just belong
to a card game what would you do like a
card game without a tournament isn't
is just impossible we'll try later it
looks great
do you guys want to read
[Music]
sorry guys sorry guys sorry guys i i
actually also really want to play more
i want to play more what's next room
crafter
i think i have a runecraft deck
but it's not particularly good
so how about we try one of the pre-made
ones
but i do want to kind of trace you no no
no okay we're going for runecraft
because
i'm already used to it a little a little
bit
let's go
okay it does have a nice story now
that i like to read when i'm not
streaming but for streaming purpose i am
not going to spoil you because i i'm not
starting from the beginning after all
and i will just play we're in the middle
of some lava
dungeon oh i
probably should get rid of at least two
maybe even all of them
yeah because i can't play okay we got
one
that we can play from the beginning but
it's uh it's an amulet or what was that
again
uh it's a spell it's a spell draw a card
well okay
well okay that's the only thing we can
play so i'm doing it oh we got one
another one what is that put oh the
great tree okay
okay and we got this fancy card already
which we can't use for a long time
anyway it's fun to have an audience uh
like of so many who already played the
game that's nice
nice starting hand really is it
let's see now i have two points now i
can bring you this one uh
yeah i am going with this one
card advantage do i miss salad oh god
damn it
i thought it would be better to have
someone here who can protect me
but i guess the missile could have wiped
out uh this girl right away
oh well we're fine
pot of greed use it what where is the
pot of greed
[Music]
how dare you attack me
now we have frame
if any allied amulets are in play return
one to your hand and do one damage to
all followers
oh wait a second let's play a tree
i need a tree and then
we have two more so
[Music]
oh
magic myself okay
bye bye bye
[Laughter]
[Music]
see we got we got two of the fiery
embrace
cards but one cost six and one costs
eight
i think this has something to do with
just the leader gradually uh
lowering the cost or so i think
okay next stop um um
[Music]
return one to hand and do one damage to
all followers
maybe not right now maybe instead i
would go for this one
guy what oh this one
returned an allied amulet to your hand
wait isn't that the one i just tried
i'm confused but he looks uh
crazy
you guys want me to evolve already
i don't i don't want to involve him
though
should i involve this dude no right i
don't want to involve him
oh yeah
oh dragon eggs can i can i hatch those
eggs i i can hatch those for you you
just gotta hire me cost a bit of money
but
i'm a good hatchery i've been hired for
hatching eggs before
i like to hatch my my adopted eggs
from my team from my employees i like to
do that
who is she who is she
okay what's up we got okay focus yeah i
really have a lot of cards right now
so i should probably play a few
of those um okay let me get back the
tree
i want the tree again and then
[Music]
extreme carrot
put an extreme carrot
what
and we got two more
when did you generally recover one
player point then if this is your oh
wait i think it is my fifth turn or
later
oh
[Music]
i was wondering if if i if it's bad to
play another tree but i guess it's
always good
oh wait oh yeah oh yeah yeah it does uh
get rid of the other tree ah
okay i have one more should i use that
one what is that
let's just keep on doing that let's just
keep on doing that bye bye tree new tree
okay
nana yeah what else what else could we
do
oh my trees give the trees the power
oh my god there they're really building
up their defense right now
[Music]
okay now's the time guys we gotta we
gotta do something we gotta do something
okay uh oh my god so many cards uh
damage to all followers yes yes yes yes
[Music]
bye bye carrots okay three more
we we completely wiped out his team
[Music]
we can put the wait we can put them all
back again
[Music]
i have still not evolved anything
kind of lame oh no
he still has 20 hp i have 15.
phoenix
[Music]
he played phoenix how dare he play a
phoenix i'm the only phoenix here
okay let's play some strong cards um
oh my god
[Music]
i have seven points guys
let's try this one
a tree come on give me a treat
give me a new tree bye tree
[Music]
another dream
i kind of want to play strong cards but
cute look at the princess connect
character goddammit i kind of
um should have played different cards
okay this is not so good should i evolve
him
[Music]
or vote for you
um well you know what i will evolve
her or him because the other one can
already attack anyway
[Music]
bye bye number one
bye bye number two
[Music]
yep it it just sometimes you have to
lose some and win some
because the phoenix
[Music]
where did she come from um okay
why does the enemy lose their maximum
defense by five oh
deal one damage
to a random enemy
you go you go girl
cute okay nice
nice not bad
[Music]
then by the way oh i can't even attack
that follower but that's good
we're the enemy has
more uh less less hp than me
i have two more two more let's play the
card again
now it looks good i thought i was losing
but there we go
the game changes suddenly
my carrot is back on my hands don't
worry about my carrots
actually no not yeah bye
[Music]
we
[Laughter]
[Music]
sorry i'm really enjoying dragon craft
or shadowcraft oh
i want to play shadow dragon craft
i want to play dragon ground
that's dragon craft right i didn't yeah
is that
that must be dragon craft right okay
should we just use the recommended one
there's a armor armageddon though
wrath of the empress that's that sounds
like it has the phoenix empress in it
[Music]
is there any anyone that you uh guys
uh recommend preview
i mean there must be a reason wow they
look she looks pretty
there must be a reason why i recommend
the the one that looks like a
that looks like a phoenix
what wait wait what what i wanna i'm
just gonna go for the
no okay raph is fun
that's just fire well fire is phoenix
phoenix is fire
same thing
[Music]
let's go guys we are in the castle
playing once again against this shade
dude
and i don't think
[Applause]
no thank you not right now also no thank
you
actually also no thank you
what do you got oh my gosh
[Music]
oh wait a second so this basically
uh the dragon craft was that the one
that lets me play uh stronger cards in
the beginning already
if i have those points
or something like that or am i mixing up
something
well there we go we have a treat
but not in this bag oh okay
um okay that deck is not for that okay
enemy follower means that i can't play
it right now because he has no followers
i can't detect the leader okay smite i
have learned something
oh how cute he did the one one
she did a one one one one one one
sorry i didn't read what that does oh
randomly destroy one
it destroyed my tree and gain an empty
play point orb oh
i swear
nice i ate the tree the trees are
i feel sorry for the trees the trees are
just sacrifices here
hey the tree's back oh
okay we got dragon shafts we can play
this one
always how about we play we play blazing
breath
and one of the four cards children
oh
[Music]
which one newlyweds
ward drain evolve my train
i wanna go for this
[Music]
nice one blazing breath bye-bye
okay not quite bye-bye but close enough
can i no i cannot attack it okay
that's for the enemy what ah you mean
that dragon the other choice i had i got
the newlyweds
i wonder if they went on their honeymoon
already or if this is their honeymoon
oh she looks cute she looks like an idol
no you didn't did you just kill
the newlyweds no i needed them
i needed them how dare you
uh
it's okay here i'm recovering one very
nice
shouldn't i no i'm not involving anyone
yet
um
okay okay wrong order
[Music]
oh my god oh my gosh
what is going on oh
how do we how did we turn this one
around
okay first of all first of all
if there's a new island okay okay we
need we need the tree we need
give me a treat nice and now i play the
dragon chefs
right smart smart smart kiana
i've learned something and i can
what do you mean i can win can i win
really
what what's the orca run do free damage
and enemies
okay free damage
ah look at those cute fishes
okay but i did i did a smart thing
didn't i do a smart thing with the
dragon chefs
should i evolve those
it says vote no no no he doesn't know
ah no no don't kill me please don't kill
me don't kill me please don't kill me
don't kill me don't kill me don't kill
me
oh my god oh my god oh my god okay
and he has a ward
[Music]
oh what about this one this is good it
doesn't
randomly destroy one and destroy an
enemy follower
ah should i go for the this one it
summons two basilisks
it's not over yet it's not over it's not
over yet guys
how about yeah we play this one and then
we got rid of that one
yes attack him
don't ride with believe in me come on
believe in me
wait if i involve him did that count as
an attack if i evolve him can he
can he attack again i want them
[Music]
it's over no
no you can okay
let's go there there's no no time to
think about anything anymore
oh oh oh oh i have to attack one of
these
bye bye
okay yeah i guess it is bye-bye after
all
we will get there in the next round
it's okay that's that is okay it was my
first time playing with my dragons
so we'll just do it again
[Laughter]
should we should we use a different deck
i wonder
let's try this one
different deck but may
might be fun we will see we want to get
to know all the
all the cards and all that so
i'll go first again
okay wow she's pretty but i don't need
her right now
oh i'll keep that there that one
yes yes yes yes yes yes
we got two of one okay
oh well i just wanted to play something
yeah
oh god he's roaring why
why shouldn't i have
[Music]
why does that does the fun father
effect only uh coming action on the
first
turn
rory xd
[Music]
oh she's back once again she only costs
two now
oh it only works when
when you play the card
okay we don't want to use
she's she's so amazing yeah she's
legendary wait a second she's a
legendary okay
if we would play her now we would lose
her too early we don't want to do that
we don't want to lose her yet right
i know i can read i am reading the
effects my friend
you can click to read the effect but am
i not reading those facts the whole time
i am it's just still i am a beginner at
the game so chill guys i know some of
you know the game very well
i know i know that's amazing but i am
obviously
reading the effects because i'm opening
the menu here do you see what i'm doing
do you see it
all right three point i think we want to
play
has been damaged summon the serpent
drake oh that sounds good to me
yay and once again he's only playing
amulets so i can directly
attack him well i think we're only doing
better than before
oh a holy falcon yo bird buddy
how's it going
[Music]
knowing you
what's overflow overall effects activate
when you have at least seven playpoint
orbs
i don't have i don't have i don't have
i don't have
but i play anyway
wait a second what does this one do
again what does this one do again
do you want damage to an allied follower
deal free damage to an enemy follower
[Music]
no i can't because he doesn't have a
follower okay
well that's just how it goes sometime
just gotta hurt myself very misogynistic
game i see
this get this deck is hard to use really
let's see if we can do it anyway
we are in the lead right now if you look
at the hp
points you uh you could see i think i
think we have a chance
don't give up yet oh no
i can't evolve yeah oh poseidon ooh
[Music]
summon a positive guard and what does
the dragon and this one
restore true defense really oh
draw a card and destroy this amulet if
overflow
is active for you do i want to play that
later when i already have some damage
hey i could i could kill the other card
or i could damage this one
should i i could
[Applause]
let's damage her because at least she
stays alive
and ooh we got her again
do i still not want to play them
[Music]
is full and area can hold five cards oh
interesting
[Music]
ah that's on seven ah okay okay
okay his word is gone that's that's good
now please don't play any more words so
that i can
uh attack you directly please
wow he has evolved his rental card
and doing some damage on my own now
oh no you didn't
oh see who we have here
500 hands still one damage to all
followers
[Music]
oh
i guess i'll wait for her as well
[Music]
oh wait a second
two down actually um
[Music]
can i is it no what
why are you guys so why are you guys
panicking so much
[Music]
okay i don't care if you guys say i
shouldn't play her i don't care
[Music]
not allowed to get too attached to your
cards because soon enough
they will they will all be gone and die
in the first turn
[Music]
there we go here's my army i waited
for this here's my army
bye bye bye bye well i already i'm
getting rid of my army as we can see
that's okay that's okay
i can't detect the later okay
the useless army excuse me don't call
them useless
they protect me
[Music]
i should have evolved should i have
evolved
uh-huh
ah i'm gonna go
for
nice okay so
[Music]
uh i can already attack nice and i'm
involved
yay we can do this guys we can use what
is blazing
ah they would have to have an enemy
follower and
this is fun it's very um strategical and
obviously i'm a beginner so i i'm not
doing
uh the best moves just yet but it's
going well anyway i would say
well you know what you got yourself into
you got yourself into
a little bit of a mess uh first of all
first of all i play this one can i get
rid of
this one
and then i play my my snake
here comes my snake
[Music]
should i involve nah tonight
it doesn't and then it's it excludes
fanfare
yes evolve okay
got even bigger huge snacks
strong snack big snack your turn try to
get my snack down
[Laughter]
oh he's also having a little party of
his own
i got rid of my snack how dare you
alright we have 10 points we're just
gonna play everything and i tell you
that
[Music]
so first i say bye bye to you then i
play this one
and then i i i just play everything
yes
[Music]
oh i got another legendary
if you have 10 playpoint orbs give alec
okay then we should probably play this
one next time
[Music]
oh what play now i have to
oh
[Music]
don't they have to be full oh well you
know what we're
already winning anyway
[Music]
it's a game over what
[Laughter]
counts the orbs that's what what
it comes to orbs that what what where
did that come and go
you have not the full point oh
i see no no no we're not game over what
the hell are you talking about
[Music]
we just play him now what
we just play him now
wait a second what what exactly does
that do
if you have to know your uh-huh
[Music]
wind blast dragon and the dragon to your
hand restores it
yes yes it's not over yet guys
it's not over
there we go
[Music]
what do you mean wrong no but i wanted
to i i did that on purpose
wait who'd i attack
[Music]
[Laughter]
nice uh i mean some people already said
gingy but i don't think it's over yet we
can do it
you guys are saying gg2l you give up
oh he's gone he gone he's also gone
i got a dragon nest oh he got a little a
little doggy
his hand is empty now but his her
playground is full famine okay
we play the nest
okay so you guys probably think this is
better
let's go for that one
[Music]
and play this one as well
oh
do i go directly for the enemy now but
what what do you mean go face does that
mean go directly to him you're using
you're using shadow various terms that i
don't quite understand
all right come at me bro
okay okay okay that's fine as long as
you don't all
attack my leader directly can some of
you attack like my my dudes
no oh
thank you dragon nest good eggs very
good eggs
wait why did that do zero
why did they do zero
is that like um
[Music]
blast dragon he has storms so
i'm just gonna
[Music]
go right there and then i shall play and
wait what does blazing graph do again d2
dominant
[Music]
another defense
the healing but okay
you guys also don't seem to be
completely decided on that one
i'm still winning guys i'm still winning
who knows for how long but okay okay you
choose to
attack my my commanders okay you too all
right no problem no problem
easy peasy
[Music]
what ah some of them
we almost done here guys
said that i was losing who said that
we did it yay a challenge ticket what is
a challenge ticket
[Music]
you got no chance because it's you're
not only fighting against me you're also
fighting against my chat
next one next one first grab the
handcraft oh that's good okay because
those at least i have a little bit of
practice
[Music]
uh i do kinda to
use a a pre-built one though because
i the ones i created i i didn't really
know what i was doing i
grow forest craft pure devotion high
born lady
i like i do like havencraft i did like
that one
let's go for four icecraft
aggro should we go aggro
i where did that go
i don't know where it is anymore
where is where did the aggro deck go
oh well let's go for this one
the basic one let me show you what i can
do with my fairies
is that cali's home
see it's me again i am first again
ask for usual oh
no actually it doesn't look so bad i
i mean i guess we couldn't
huh yeah okay yep
looking good already a good starting
hand
let's start with a fairy
okay
let me and
kind of foreign elves and and fairies
let's play a tree
and then no mercy guys no mercy
we will not let him win
under any circumstances
don't don't don't do nice battle music
[Music]
down down
i don't think i have let's play the tree
again
treat
[Music]
it's going well though it's going well
okay what are we doing what do we do we
playing
huh
and we play
it's a legendary and it's a medusa you
got some snacks
oh there we go and they're here you show
me those snacks
oh that's a dope ass character
oh i also oh yes i like that oh comic
card i played it before
well you show me those snacks i show you
something else my friend
[Music]
but you know what i want to wipe you out
as as fast as possible
what oh wait i can't
wait what
[Music]
back again okay okay okay
okay bye bye snake we want those snakes
here
i don't like snakes i play my fairies
and my trees and we're all happy
together
the forest craft is actually kind of
easy to play
oh now oh no
oh the snack is attacking my fairy are
you sure about that my friend oh no
another fairy down no
don't kill my fairies dare to attack my
fairies i will come with you
at you with my wolf soon look it's coco
it's so cute let's play some fairies
shall we
[Music]
can never have enough trees right let's
give me that oxygen
give it to me
[Music]
i guess that's all i can do right now i
don't i don't want to involve them i
want to evolve my
my other stronger cards should i have
evolved kokoro
oh no oh no
wow i think uh cocodol might die
oh
that's okay that's okay it's okay it's
okay it's okay
i think we're going straight for the
ukami
or are we oh
you will protect me
[Music]
let's get rid of you
okay new girl
where she can attack twice what what
oh no no
okay yeah that was a mistake that was a
mistake i i agree with that
calm down guys calm down
[Music]
bow
if you have a fairy in hand means just
in head not on the field right
so you don't have to be on the field yet
damage
looks good we cleared the field a little
bit
yay fairies oh
i want to get rid of that that one
oh ascend and packing
yes give it to me
[Music]
yes we cleared the field again
looks good looks good looks good that
did sound a little bit
like okay okay senpai's
why you keep on doing that oh my god
thank you for the red super chat oh my
god
uh oh my god wow uh
wow uh
i wanna uh i wanna give you
uh like uh i wanna read your super chat
carefully in a super chat reading if
that's okay
well thank you so much
now let's take a look at my little
origamis
i hope i didn't do anything bad um
should we evolve my my dogo
let's get the ferry too
stupid go away go away ship
we don't want any of you here
evolve the ferry really
above the ferry you want me to above the
ferry
what what that was my
my my version of okami howl
oh no
um oh wow
i'm just gonna play everything
happy birthday oh
birthday
oh oh damn wait it's your birthday
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you happy birthday dear darren
happy birthday to you
[Music]
wait
oh wait oopsie oh wow that's okay
well we're pretty much winning it now
okay and i want to evolve her irene
[Music]
oh no i can't attack him
goddammit
[Music]
one
[Applause]
[Music]
this is so much fun
damn forest craft is fun because i
understand it
but i think um each each
uh leader and each deck can be a lot of
fun
uh once you uh practice with a little
bit let's see what do we have next
sword craft and blood craft oof all
right sword craft is fine i have some
practice of sword crafts
i made a swordcraft deck it's probably
not the bestest so we're gonna know once
again
ooh walford swordcraft
but let's uh just go with the
recommended one
[Music]
bloodcraft is good um but i
i have uh a feeling that i might be
playing swordcraft better than i'm
playing
bloodcraft
i know second alrighty
oh
do we want to keep him
i i wouldn't mind redrawing him
[Music]
keep keep cheap
okay then actually i mean i can play
these jojo that's fine
[Music]
a good hand and good hand
good hand to start well meet 11 sisters
oh hello
hmm
maybe i want to go with her first
[Music]
order
mage i probably want to go with the mage
the two costs oh
okay
oh if you guys say so i shall trust you
i played the card before and i used the
mage at that time but if you guys say
you should use that one you probably
have a reason for that
[Music]
all right you go
i mean my turn again
trust the chat okay i will i'm actually
like surprised that so many of you
already knew and played a game why did
you guys never tell me about it why did
you guys never i mean i heard of the
game before
but why did you guys not tell me to play
the game
fine
[Music]
oh
she just told you to not call her small
it's not for everyone i guess yeah
probably many of you didn't know that i
actually
played card games in uh my childhood and
in my in my past i actually really like
card games
i just didn't have the opportunity to
play
any in the recent years
and the thing is i also like gotcha
games so
it is quite a good combination
someone me some nights yeah
[Music]
that's okay i'll take it
but it has been such a long time since
i've played uh uh since i play a card
game so it is very
nostalgic to me
i like this i like it
i'm not the best at using my brain
it works somehow anyway
oh i can play should i play albert
oh should i wait for until i have nine
points
when you put different eleven followers
from your deck until play until the area
is full
nine points okay and
then i will go far
let's play one of those
and then oh oh yeah he he was pretty
nice i played him before
and the fact restores your play points
put the knight king's mind into your
hand
sure
[Music]
there we go i has a word
should i evolve i want to evolve
[Music]
try to attack me try try it
wait what what does that do
oh oh we made him super super super
strong
super botan senpai
you placed your potential oh egyptian
pharaoh in your past life are you sure
about that
thank you for the red super chat all
right um
well
i say goodbye
[Music]
and now it's your turn
super strong epic lion
no no he killed my super epic
oh my god could you stop could you just
stop there what is going on you think
you think this is over yet it is not
over yet
[Applause]
[Music]
yes
i am i'm not happy that my lion is down
i'm gonna be honest there
what does she do
i don't know he has too many
enemies on the field so i'm going to say
goodbye to you
[Music]
stop it with the skeleton stop it
that's the ring that i'm gonna use when
i propose to a certain someone
oh elegance in action we got mates
um
[Music]
hell yeah oh yes we got a whole army now
okay should i involve one of them
[Music]
and then go straight into his face
no i can't
[Music]
god's sake i have a feeling this is
gonna be
a little bit of a close battle
oh dear lord what is that what is that
oh no no no
no no no no no no no no no
you are making me very angry right now
you are making me
very very angry
[Music]
ugh
what do we do
am i am i dead in the next turn
yes
[Music]
trees okay maybe we get a miracle
give me a miracle i need a miracle
okay i need another miracle
hey i would say we banished the
10-6 right
right or that amila what is that i'm
[Music]
[Applause]
the battle is never over
what does that one do though oh okay
i'll thank him
well that was fun oh
[Music]
should we wolf yeah it's that's of wolf
and bye bye
another friend goes bye bye bye bye bye
we're turning this battle around he did
not expect it
he did not think this was gonna come
i still only have six health points
though and he has 18 but
we'll get there we will get there oh no
i i hope he doesn't get a miracle now he
doesn't need a miracle please don't
oh my god once well stop it just stop
is it pickle time is it pickle time
he has five damage
[Music]
wait which one is the most
a scary one
[Music]
i'm dead
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
keep clearing the field
wait i have a full field now anyway god
damn it nah
live on the edge yep okay well i mean
okay okay okay no
[Music]
skeletons
but should i play albert
should i play album randomly put
different 11 followers
from your deck into into play until your
area is full
wait a second
[Applause]
trade your board clear board what do you
mean with that
[Music]
ah to make way for him oh what do you
mean clear can i get rid of them
all right
[Music]
wow
okay guys we can still do it
um
[Music]
gg
he has five damage
but maybe he will not go for me maybe he
will
go for someone else on the field
right right oh no no
[Applause]
[Music]
it was that was a tough battle that was
a tough battle oh
wow okay well um
ah that was a tough one wow okay
um however
we are now at the two-hour mark
i i really want to play more
[Music]
but
what did you guys think i mean um the
people who
didn't know the game before are there
any of you in the in the chat
what what did you guys think i thought
it was really fun it probably if you
haven't played it yourself it might be a
little bit confusing while you're just
watching it but
i really recommend it it's a lot of fun
if you like card games and you were
waiting for
something to get it to play then i
definitely
think you should play it
yeah also since uh if if you like
gramble fantasy
now you have the advantage that uh since
yesterday
gramble fantasy is an expansion in there
[Music]
i might i might if you guys wants to see
it i might want to play this again on
stream because i don't
i don't want to accept this defeat
and i want to practice more and i want
to do like big battles because like as
you can see here multi
um you can play multiplayer as well and
then there's uh
tournament modes that's really really
cool
really cool features that this game has
so much more
to explore
wait can i did i got anything new to
roll with by the way
just checking the second you know um
[Music]
can i can i roll a little bit no
oh wait i can i can buy with rupees
can buy one pack yay
just give me something new
i'm not addicted i'm not addicted to
that
no no no
[Music]
oh
i'm not addicted i can stop anytime i
want
i can stop any time i want don't get
just to make it clear
all right guys that was it for today
i'll be reading the super chats in the
separate stream also
tonight um in in six hours from now we
moved to the next stream to one hour
later but in six hours from now i have a
collab with
uh some other senpai's on aki senpai's
channel so you might want to check that
out it's at 9pm japanese center time
anyway i want to thank one more time i
want to thank shadowverse for sponsoring
the game thank you so much i i
will play this probably because i
genuinely enjoyed that
and i want to play more and then i don't
i don't want to accept defeat and i
missed
i really miss playing card games
so yeah thank you so so much for tuning
in guys
i hope you enjoyed it i hope you might
want to pick it up
there's a link in my description uh that
leads to the game on steam
if you want to get it use that link it
would make me very happy
if you would use the kiara link
yeah is there anything else to say did i
forget anything did i forget anything i
hope i didn't forget anything to say i
i don't think so
by the way there's over a thousand five
hundred cards
over five thousand no no sorry thousand
five hundred not thousand
not five thousand there's over 1
500 cards did i say that correctly
over 9000 no over 1 500.
that's more than enough oh my god
i think i i got everything
[Music]
uh so yeah just
to repeat one more time the game is free
to play on
phone and computer when you start
and by completing this material you get
it you get a ton of free packs you get
50 food packs so
if you want to get started don't worry i
already used up all the gacha stuff so
that's why i couldn't get so much right
now but you get so much free gotcha
uh packs right in the beginning
um i was like fully voiced in english
and japanese
and there's eight different distinct
glitter classes that you can use and
find your own style that you want to go
for as
you saw i played a bunch of them and
they're all really really different
i think my favorite i'm not sure yet i
have to have to play a bit more with
them
thank you for yep today i'll see you
soon
thank you and in german we say au vida
zayn thanks shadow face for sponsoring
today's stream
thank you bye-bye
[Music]
you