[Music]
flying down
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
keep your
feet
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
what's up
[Music]
and never be afraid again
going so fast
[Music]
a little bit move it everybody
we are friends with your heart
[Music]
never be afraid
let's go
let's go tonight
[Music]
Papa
those times
[Music]
follow me
do do
foreign
[Music]
what's up oh no my attention hands do
not exist anymore Nani
and Joe
and doko
Kiki
gentle hands tense your hands don't go
turn your hands up gentle hands
what the [\h__\h] why are these here
turn your hands dot Jeff
why are you so far away
I have to read color correct
oh no wait chroma key yeah
wow look at those Nails yo this thing is
all this is an old asset
I think that actually did look perfectly
wonderful
perfect
easily amused
big hands
and Yahweh
Yahweh comes with big hands oh wait that
makes that thing see-through when I get
rid of the green oh well
style points stop points you have my
friends I'm from
did you not notice in the Advent
calendar
I thought it was so genius though
don't you think it's so genius
because you did you noticed I didn't
notice oh my God you didn't notice what
the [\h__\h]
I know this I guess you were too focused
on the sweater
yeah because I was like I want to use
this outfit to represent the sweater but
um I don't want my braids to disappear
underneath
so I took the time to make pngs out of
my braids and then tried my best to
place them on top accordingly
oh my God devotion hell yeah
do you see it now
[Laughter]
it's like I guess it looks good if you
if you focus on another part of the
screen or maybe add the burp on top of
my head
then it won't stand out so much um
yeah I'm sick and tired of
my hair
beneath clothes that I put on top of
myself
spoof yeah because I was able to attach
it to the hair Parts but it doesn't it's
not you know it as you see here it
wobbles outside of where it should be
though but yo
it does move along nicely I ordered a
sweater mine should also be here
tomorrow I think
Amazon
I wonder if you can order it in Japan
but in case you haven't watched the
Advent calendar video and in case you're
also not on Twitter
we have new merchandise Christmas
sweaters for whole life English on
Amazon if you type in whole life English
oh and I did ask by the way uh can we
not make it available in Canada and
Australia and it's not that we don't
like you guys I love you guys I wish you
would love me as much as I love you but
um it's because we already have uh like
chosen everything that like we selected
every country that
um Amazon on Demand I think it's called
is able to make it available too
um
yeah for some reason I honestly don't
get it like I understand that for some
smaller countries it wouldn't work but I
don't understand why it doesn't exist
for Canada and Australia it's an Amazon
research and yeah but maybe it's I don't
know I honest I heard that Canada uses
American Amazon is that right but still
they cannot use the Amazon on Demand
from
um from America so well that's that
sucks which is it's weird because
Austria uses Germany Amazon but I can
order uh
the Amazon on Demand from Germany
we don't even have our own Amazon and I
can still do it even with Prime
so while
it's not our fault though that's what I
want to tell you no sweater for
Switzerland really because it even
worked for me in Austria
I'm actually so relieved I thought it
wouldn't and yeah a lot of surprised
actually
um but I guess okay Switzerland could
have its own Amazon because well you're
not even
you're not even part of us love
Switzerland though
um
living American I still can't get it but
that's probably just because stock
problem I've seen though it's stocks
restocks like every [\h__\h] day though
so you just get go and have to check in
I heard you know that in America sold
out really fast on the first couple
hours but then on the next day it there
was a restock and then maybe it sold out
again but there's a restock all the time
um
um the black sweater is bugged are you
sure
are you sure about that I didn't get the
black spot on purpose anyway because I
thought my word that the black clothes
that I have
are impossible to ever wear outside
again because even if I roll something
on top to get rid of the cat hair it
will never be
cat free enough ever again there's just
some hairs that stick on there for
forever as if it's glued onto the
clothes
yeah got the gray one yeah I kind of I
don't know I I I'll be honest I don't
like the like gray with this design that
much but maybe it will look nice in
reality
um mini green dark green would have been
nice but that doesn't quite work with
this
but there's dark green elements there
but anyway
can I just say
that I
I I recommended this artist Olivia's I
don't know if Olivia's nose
but you know my husband was like okay
let's make ugly Christmas sweaters do
you guys have any uh pixel artists that
you recommend and I recommended a couple
uh like two or three and one of them was
Olivia's I figured as much see this is
another case where someone some artist
some fan artist of mine gets the bag
because of me
[Laughter]
yeah
another case
I wonder Olivia's
if you if if you know
it was of course your one and only boss
which hopefully will remind you
as to who your boss is
yeah yeah it was me deal
um yeah my loading screens yeah I showed
my loading screens I was like yeah this
person does this kind of stuff
um
I should run the next gen auditions
ain't got time for that but no actually
I feel like it would be cool if if I
could be part of the uh choosing uh
committee but no
they will be available for a while
they're available now and if there's um
something if you can't choose a certain
size or color or so that means it's
currently out of stock but you should
just check back one or two days later
High chance that it's restocked again
since it all runs through Amazon
um that means that they take care of the
restructance pretty fast with Amazon on
Demand because it's basically like from
how I understand it works they have
certain types of items that you can Slap
Your Design on
um what's kind of limited to like where
it's placed and so on but you know then
yeah so it's like existing clothes and
they just print it freshly I guess and
then it comes over to your place it's so
cool that it works so fast like
we already had this with Halloween merch
and I guess also with
um uh like whole Stars Ian I saw some
stuff
yeah yeah they have some T-shirts and so
on
um but yeah this I think it's so cool
that we can do this I know I know
there's still some countries who can't
reach it and that sucks but
um
well
it's it's I think it's an improvement
but did we also put this up on somewhere
else so only on Amazon this time I think
it's only on Amazon huh well Canadian
friends I'm sure you have an American
friend or family member and Australian
friends I'm sure you have an Austrian
friend or family member
to ask
if they can get you the good stuff
[Laughter]
come on even if
a friend
then wear off you can still make a
friend maybe
I don't know
make a Tinder account or
or yeah ask a fellow fan that you may be
on good terms with her so I don't know
um
my DMs are not opening I'm not
um I'm not ordering [\h__\h] for you
no no but but there might be another
person who might do that for you
yeah and just tell Canada to do freaking
Amazon on Demand like I don't get it
like so unfortunately it won't happen
before you guys but there's uh there is
other other ways of doing these things
yeah make it happen yeah yeah make it
happen
um
[Laughter]
cries in the maple soup yeah your tears
are weird
anyway have you missed messages
I haven't um I kind of kind of I'm gonna
be honest I kind of forgot about this
kotori's existence because I've been
using the dientele kotoris so much
um
I kind of forgot that I had another one
in a different outfit
I'm so sorry Kotori
I'm so sorry
ah
anyway
yeah no it's not forgotten he's back I
remembered Kotori I remember them he's
back on my head [\h__\h] on my head like
a burp does
when he's above my head
like it's supposed to be
right
oh shh
wait what
he forgives you yeah in form of [\h__\h]
on me
um
is that what that happened yeah I was
thinking the same thing because it's
white but no I would be too perfect ah
oh my God oh my God
oh oh thank you I hope I can catch up
with super chat soon because once I
catch up I'll do my my special Super
Chat thing that I prepared
chunkers
it's just sitting outside the room
um like I see her half of her body
at the door frame just being a chunky
loaf of bread she's so cute
can I just say
I wasn't here for two days so or three
days almost so I have so much to talk
about I just want to say this happened
just today but what the actual fox movie
I just can't with smoothie right now
like what's the [\h__\h] problem with her
what is her problem my my turquoise cat
yeah my turquoise radioactive cat
I swear to God this cheeky little brat
will get herself
I don't even want to say it but someday
she might die on by her own fault
she [\h__\h] brat
she's misbehaving and rebelling and
she's such a stupid cat I ca I can't
with her I love her so much but I can't
move her right now
no what she did this time is is
unbelievable it's I was in shock and I I
I
okay
it's actually
incredible
and
so cheeky this little [\h__\h] you know how
I always give her only her because
chunkers doesn't like it uh wet food in
the morning half
usually half because if I give her full
um like a whole um thingy package then
she
um can't eat it all at once and then
after a few hours it's like dry you know
disgusting
so
uh I give her half and then I give her
the next half the next morning and in
the meantime I sometimes put it in the
fridge and sometimes I don't
um because I forgot and but it's still
good the next day so
um
what's that sound
I heard a loud sound a donk what
happened
did you hear that let me
what the [\h__\h] was that huh
little shits you little [\h__\h]
I think they knocked over my empty
um suitcase my small one yeah yeah my
stupid cats
[\h__\h] problem
so okay so a wet food yeah and um
so today was one of those days where I I
I I didn't put it in the fridge but I've
done this times before
and she never attempted anything stupid
but you know at this point it's already
open right but but but it's not like she
can just with without a thumb and so on
it's impossible to reach in and get the
food through the opening no anyway so I
I gave her breakfast and then I left to
meet um Nabi
again
um we did a little a bit more before she
left and
um
I come home
to
smoothie
viciously like a werewolf or so
feasting
on the ripped apart
cat wet food package
square right and it had another opening
that was obviously ripped apart
viciously
aggressively in the middle
and
there were some pieces of plastic lying
around it
because it's my cat is an old time
really what
what the [\h__\h] she never did this before
like up like like she's a werewolf I
can't
Earl this is the first time
[Music]
I I'm like what the [\h__\h] you stupid cat
because number one I'm worried that she
eats any of that plastic
and number two how dare she how
disrespectful
was she hungry it's it hasn't been that
long since the breakfast it was like two
or three hours
since I gave her the breakfast and she
while I was gone I guess she immediately
lost it turned into a werewolf and
attacked the [\h__\h] wet food bag
oh my gosh you fought on Earth
before a man has torn them apart when
I've not put them in a Cupboard even
within 10 minutes unbelievable
[Music]
found that bread is something she can
eat and has a tight half of bread in the
packaging destroying the plastic
[\h__\h] cats
oh my God
jeans are Snickers she would probably
rip the whole packaging of the Snickers
apart yes
I promise I won't go feral in front of
you
okay I hope so
my cat spine holes and stuff all the
time they like plastic touch mine like
plastic texture too but this was not for
the sake of the plastic texture like
sometimes she will try to chew on on
plastic you know like bubble wrap or
whatever and then I immediately take it
away and I'm I've been you know noticing
that for a long time so I try to keep
plastic away at all times
um but yeah this time she didn't do it
for the plastic she did do it for the
food
and I I
was so
angry so I took away but this is a pic
I'm gonna post a picture maybe on
Twitter later but
it's
it's saying it looks like like you know
a human's body that was attacked by a
feral animal monster
yeah
it's like a horror movie
of a wet food plastic bag
um
hahaha
I can't with her she was so aggressive
too about the food
that like a toy so ripped open yes
that's what I was thinking of
ah
I can't
did you Grant's move for a misbehavior
well she's already grounded she's a
she's a house cat
you know I was thinking
um as a as a child as a teenager
you know I was always a hiki comedy I
was always someone who didn't like going
outside that much so well thankfully I
never really did much of stuff things
that I would get grounded for ever I
don't think I ever got grounded ever
before
but partially probably it's also because
my mom realized that grounding me or my
brother would make absolutely no sense
because we like being at home and the
only way to ground us effectively would
be by sending us outside the opposite
right
computer or Internet
yeah cables and [\h__\h] that would work but
I don't think she ever did that on me
either
yes
[Laughter]
sometimes though why am I just doing
something sometimes
um
I had those days where I was playing an
MMORPG until like 3 AM or so and and
then oh no actually no wait like five or
six a.m because I remember it was like
time where my mom would wake up and go
make herself some coffee and that's when
I realized okay okay yeah but if my mom
notices that I played mmrpgs for the
whole night then
um
it's gonna be a little bit bad even
though it means it's my decision but
it's gonna be a bit mad so let's quickly
um turn off the monitor not not the PC
because it would be too um slow
to turn off the whole
um PC so just turn off the monitor turn
off the room light and quickly climb up
my bed because I had like a bunk bed
with empty space underneath where my PC
was and I climbed up quickly and then I
act as if I'm sleeping and that within
like 30 seconds
[Laughter]
yeah
but sometimes she would still notice if
ah sometimes you know I wouldn't have
time
um to turn up the light or so so I was I
would just act as if uh I fell asleep
with my lights on so I'm I'm just like
acting as if I'm sleeping with the light
on at like 5 a.m 6 a.m and then she's
like hmm
she's like
yeah yes I'm sleeping
oh what oh oops I forgot to turn my PC
off huh no I've been sleeping I've been
totally sleeping
funny
yeah
[Laughter]
use my ideas to hide my desk on my pill
and pretend to sleep yeah I think I did
stuff like that too yeah yeah with
smaller devices that that at least Works
faster
um
[Music]
no I don't think she's watching this
she likes watching my streams but I
don't think she likes watching uh my
Mario Kart streams
you know nothing nothing so far
okay anyway we're here to play some
[Music]
ah yeah old TVs I had an old TV like
that too when we moved and I had a
different type of room set up
where I had my own room at some point
anyway
mm-hmm grab my butt what
Mario is 64 yes what is that
64 DS and Mario screens bye bye when you
close your day when my
Mario
how come link was invited but not canon
I was gonna say why do you care so much
but I see your name makes sense
[Music]
ah
ah it got ported to the DS uh-huh
it's like a cocktail
a good mix of two things two good things
[Music]
probably watching the stream and like
girl when the [\h__\h] is she gonna start
playing I'm I woke up early for this so
I can
um you know ride against her like I
always do
what's up
[Music]
[Laughter]
tonight
huh
because there's certain Japanese uh
Mario Kart fans who are at every Mario
Kart stream after all no matter what
time it is I don't know why
foreign
[Music]
hot
and place only join once
please use new maps when possible
okay so I know I heard there's a new map
right
not new map like four new courses or so
whatever right for like it's the third
wave right
um
[Music]
I'm gonna hide this we wanna have it
typed out all at once which one which
one
this one Kana
it's
okay
[Music]
please try to choose new map eight new
courses okay and when I mean new then
the newest if possible and if there's if
there's
um only first wave or second wave then
choose one of those priority
I sounded like a character just no I
didn't know mm-hmm
okay let me join first
[Music]
hello from Singapore hello good morning
it's good morning isn't it
easy
Daisy Daisy here there it is there it is
there it is Daisy has been
not treated well in terms of
you know the movie why is everybody in
the Super Mario movie but Daisy they why
not Daisy cute
okay I'm just gonna leave that there and
see wait Skye
I got some second wave or so I assume so
in this case we don't have anything
really new but I would choose one of
this
Justin for Daisy yes please maybe in the
sequel
don't worry overall Luigi but like so
hello everybody but so many versions or
like um friends Companions of uh Donkey
Kong right they have like kitty Kong and
[\h__\h]
how can they prioritize
[Music]
for Daisy I don't [\h__\h] understand
this was originally a color swap of
peach yeah but she isn't anymore even if
she was nice I see a little [\h__\h]
too but you usually like so so so bad
these days so so bad
hello everybody oh Switzerland
um
no we need a Switzerland map
there's no Switzerland course yet is
there
how come let's see if I remember how to
play this game
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh
ah beautiful music
why am I 12 sorry
have you guys been warming up behind the
scenes
it's not fair
[Music]
okay [\h__\h] off [\h__\h] off
oh it's already over
um
[Music]
oh yeah oh yeah there you go eat that
[\h__\h]
okay
can someone take that [\h__\h] banana
oh my God
[Music]
Get Wrecked
not not so bad not so bad not so bad
that's a bad not too bad
what the actual [\h__\h]
no you even saw the [\h__\h] coin from me
um
oh oh number one be careful
hey
come on come on come on come on come on
[Applause]
all right all right
where's the goal
let's go Chihuahua
or double item
goal is not there yet oh [\h__\h] I didn't
want to do that
oh
six
six I warm up round what what's up
let's go didn't look so good at times
but there it is yo yo yo where are the
new maps
it should have downloaded them
automatically right because I have the
premium whatever
my guest would go for Coconut Mall that
looks the newest to me
um I should have had okay pixel sweater
and then I'm wearing it what do you mean
did someone tell you you can mess around
with items what do you mean
you can change the rules of items now
well like what what can I change it to
hello oh hello
okay
you just got coconut milk
laughs
you can toggle individual items yeah I
don't care about I think we can just all
keep keep them all
I don't know why I would change any of
them
I mean I guess you could
in a tournament or so
if you for some reason don't want
something specific
liar even I know that name
it's truly the real Markiplier right
right
could be who knows
not that I watch his videos though I'm
not here to stroke his ego let's go
ah [\h__\h] I'm on the wrong side
I see that as a win because this means I
can see the future
it's another Talent we all didn't know I
had
finally I got committed timing too
and never star
Go game ah [\h__\h] why do I always choose
the wrong one
wait you can go for the gift shop or so
my name is
oh my God
[Music]
I'm surprised I'm still eight with this
oh oh okay stay sweeped away the banana
nuts
coconut milk hey
so sad
so sad I am already being and the others
weren't
hmm
okay here we go this time I'm on the
right side
okay let's try this oh oh
wow
[Music]
[Applause]
wow it took me so far I feel like
let's go get
it
[Music]
hey there I'm 16 in the last six stars
six stars
why is there so many freaking Splatoon
people
how many squids
sixth show oh yeah
what's the newest one here Mario circuit
free
or none of them thank you guys
thank you
don't like squids well I definitely
don't like eating them
free is popular uh-huh
Splatoon free one best multiplayer game
and I haven't played Splatoon 3 and I
haven't played any of the other games I
think that were on the list
but what do you think about that well
deserved really I heard it's not so good
in terms of multiplayer
for what reason I don't know
I mean it's surely fun
but
wait what were the other ones again
who did I hear it from well from the one
other YouTuber that I watched
who is who played all of Splatoon
everything and deemed it to be Unworthy
of online uh multiplayer award and and
was like absolutely losing it when it
actually was splatoon's win
[Laughter]
[Music]
like Nintendo online has its issues
in terms of connectivity or maybe it's
not I don't know I don't know what the
actual like criticism is there but I
think we know oopsie
uh holy [\h__\h]
I'm winning
[Music]
okay let's get them with that shitty ass
banana
I don't give a [\h__\h] about that's the
Banana's banana
wait I'm I'm doing such a shitty job and
I'm still number one what's going on
yeah Korean Anya no no no it was such a
happy time oh
also Markiplier you have to leave the
game you don't understand
after this one you're out
yeah well I mean this this number is a
bit more realistic
I think I just used someone else's
a mushroom
[Applause]
s
oh
hey payback [\h__\h]
I hope that when that person gets out of
the the shell
let's get him let's get him come on tops
my British friend
oh I had a funny thing in terms of
British with Navi Chun
we're talking about like British accent
she told me that like she has a British
friend
who's
whose accent she just doesn't understand
[Laughter]
yeah yeah I I was on together with Navi
Chan for the weekend Amelia's artist
mama in case you don't know who that is
the the person who drew Amelia
um who I I also already hung out with in
Korea anyway so she was like making an
example she was saying something like
uh do you know
and I'm like what
oh here there it is online Nintendo
online perfect example wait for me guys
and I'm like what do you want what you
want me
you have a real times and and and and so
yeah it turns out what she meant was
a bottle of water which is so funny
because in theory I understand like the
joke but
she her but what uh was very unclear was
more like blah blah blah
yeah she says her friend speaks like
that anyway and then I said ah Navidad
that's so funny it's supposed to be oh
is that one also new I wanted to marry
Mountain I think that looks so
Christmassy
oh my God everybody chose it oh no
except for one thank you
are they both new
um
[Music]
it's Chris Christmas
oh yeah oh that's supposed to be chicken
I thought it was like a a punk music fan
[Laughter]
well no
where are the famous snow song is
also that that car that that other days
is riding is cool so many go round
let me look at this beautiful place oh
whoa
oh [\h__\h] where did that go
oh
it's so beautiful here
[Music]
who the [\h__\h] just bumped me
archive Watchers tell me who the [\h__\h]
that was
go back in time and check please
because that was not okay
oh no what the [\h__\h] is going on
give me item
s
oh
I could I didn't do it right
[Music]
wow
it's really pretty is this supposed to
be just a Christmas Village or is it
supposed to be some special
um City
like Finland or okay it's not a city I
know blah blah blah blah blah blah
[Music]
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] everywhere
you can't oh everybody's in the star wow
amazing
Christmas week
free of fear I before
I think I used five
actually [\h__\h] incredible
that's my karma that's my karma
what is this race it's a [\h__\h] mess
oh
it's a freaking mess oh my God
like so much is going on right
it's fun how did I get no eyes
ah
all right
that's it
I think they're I think there were times
where
I was doing pretty well there
[Music]
don't get too close to me guys when you
got mushrooms surrounding you all right
thanks thanks
just got buried by every single item I
think yeah some good items and some bad
items when there's nothing really new
here I think but uh oh sit
you're late
famous snow sang in
you're late let's go
ah I was waiting for you
[Music]
two players haven't left who
I felt like everybody left
well what's their names
George
and Jonah no no maybe not well whoever
it is please leave after this one for
real girls is that a Sanic
right in front of me
a Sanic oh you know what you know I I
didn't watch the game awards
um completely uh on the first time it
was uh uh running
because it was in the middle of the
night and at some point I just had sleep
but I called up
afterwards
watched the rest of it
and one trailer that I saw that I really
liked
um was this um I swear if you're gonna
hit me with that
was that GTA looking game if I think I
saw
a makers logo
but it wasn't labeled as GTA
but I wanna
[Music]
uh something about the crime again uh
Krampus
is that the one
but it looks really cool
I like that one
gets wrecked I'm doing that on purpose
now
[\h__\h]
yeah it looked like it was from the same
makers what the [\h__\h]
I want to play it
what's up
yeah
but even if it comes out it won't come
out on until
a long long time later right
okay I guess I'm switching to go over
here
I just go Cuba
you're cuter than Daisy koala thank you
but that's impossible I love Daisy
don't undermine her cuteness
more like payday than GTA uh-huh
I know it looked pretty good what else
impressed me the the Bayonetta Origins
came I never played a Bayonetta game and
honestly I mean they're the characters
are hot and so on but I don't quite like
the style of the artistic Direction
trying to speak in fancy terms
um but the origins one is like way more
my kind of thing you know
actually
[Music]
I feel like since it's the the original
story of Bayonetta
I mean ideally you would play it um with
some very little knowledge but it's a
completely different game anyway so I
think I want to play that one as my
first Bayonetta game when it comes out
oh
that's new that looks cool the bull egg
okay right guys thank you thank you
[Music]
what what placement was that no sorry I
don't I don't see
interesting starting point yeah but I
don't know it's my style I think you
guys understand I don't I'm not saying I
want to stream it I don't know about
that but I want to play it
um
third
[Laughter]
hahaha
oh
he's just playing games on the board
what's up what what are you gonna do
about it
what are you gonna do about it remind me
of Alice yeah I guess so a little bit it
reminded me of several things all kinds
of things
um
you can put it on easy yeah
no no no no as I said I mean yeah
they're hot but I don't really like the
art style that much of the normal
Bayonetta games actually I know it might
come as a surprise to some of you but uh
yeah
16 trailer was really sick too and of
course I want to play it but uh
I'm guessing it's connected to other
Final Fantasy games and I haven't played
a single one except for 14 in the online
one and I would have played
if if I could have in my two and a half
years or so in whole life which sounds
crazy that I've been here for so long
um I would have already played like five
Final Fantasy games if I could have but
I couldn't
that's the standalone
they're awesome
[Music]
like re
um appearing characters before
Sweden hmm
oh
well well done okay well who knows if
until Final Fantasy 16 maybe finally
finally
um
those are spin-offs
okay let me look at this it reminds me
wait I know this map no it from
no no it just looks um from like the
style of how the
roads are a bit similar to a different
one
[Music]
we're on the water now
okay come on hit someone but not me
I don't think it hit anyone and I didn't
get an item of course not
oh spooky
wow okay interesting
[Music]
I really wanted that double item ghost
fish
I can't fight that one
okay I I hate
I hate this track
[Music]
but I like the visuals of it okay
let's let's try to save this [\h__\h]
oh yeah
come on get me further that was nothing
oh
foreign
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] was that
oh
cute is that new
I remember circuits but I don't remember
this yellow toad circuit
yeah I am I mean
I would I would hope that that's wave
one oh I would hope that the other
people aren't used to it either but
everybody did better than me
huh
I'm tired I want to play this one anyway
because there's nothing else that's
really new here unless DK jungle
that's old right
hello hello
[Music]
that dude on the left looks like
he's trying to be someone the smaller
one
some some famous person
no no not the one without the hair and
without the face
the one in the bag
I didn't mean to
um
light blue
I want to say their username because it
might give me a hint and I think I I
think
I have a feeling
no that maybe it's just themselves it
didn't give me a hint at all
maybe it's just themselves
ah did you see the new trailer of Super
Mario movie
it was pretty good the toads are so cute
we could see like um
[Music]
you could see it
like toad Market or something like that
code city it was pretty cute
yeah Phoenix ladies
give me the win oh
what
oh there was a girl so far there was a
bug was it a ghost
and suddenly I am 11.
surprise surprise surprise but I'm not
giving up yet
shuts up
here we go only phones only fans
you wish
no no don't get me
[Music]
come on
but everyone's so far behind we're
actually pretty close to each other so I
see that as a win
[Music]
and still I could have
been far why would you take that away
from me
[Music]
Savage looks like a tea
oh that's New London love hey
you know I didn't spoil myself at all
about what the new courses are so I
didn't know
London Loop it looks cool from the
thumbnail
oh
tell me tell me once we have tried all
of them
I think this is maybe the third one or
so
I'm real Rusty at all America me too
me too me too
looking pretty nice yeah British accent
only all right yeah no problem
Oh I um not be Nabi
um will not be able to understand this
so well though we'll say
I'm sorry now bye
yeah this is how they speak over there
but honestly it's no joke like for real
I'm not even trying to make fun of them
it's beautiful
just let go of the tea
let go of the day
it could show everybody
who the [\h__\h] is P1 player one
get yourself a pro a name
all right we're here in Lawton today
it's Tuesday in it
there's a UK resident it is
discrimination I'm not playing this map
how is this map discrimination
how are you oh
beautiful looks exactly like
the place
what left or right what the [\h__\h]
oh backwind
the big dog
nice
awesome
all right
oh
wow wow
I think I used his uh
it's mushroom again
yummy this is the only
time when I like mushrooms
only if it's in Mario Kart
I I [\h__\h] right well I forgot about the
the accent
I totally forgot I'm so sorry
yo this item is so useless because say
they can all Drive absolutely normally
it's absolutely no Advantage given to me
oh but that's this was so many [\h__\h]
washrooms
[Applause]
[Music]
what the actual Fork
[\h__\h] hell mate
everybody got so many mushrooms give me
one yeah thank you thanks mate Cheerios
I don't know when I try to speak like
this in an accent my whole voice changes
have you noticed
I it just it's connected you know
bye
oh wait I feel like I'm somewhere else
now wait I [\h__\h] shy
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
go get him go eat him I know what the
[\h__\h] what are you doing I mean is this
okay I feel like I'm slower
ah [\h__\h]
my only savior
then oh oh wait we could get six shows
oh this could still be something
let's go let's [\h__\h] go
yeah eat them up beat them up beat them
up
hey that's right that's right that's
right oh my God not even sixth show I'm
[\h__\h] fourth child
let's go
yes so good that was one of my best ones
today how I did so badly
okay nothing new here
we should do big blue
but I'll wait for you guys
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
I say
actually you know I was talking with
oh wait sorry
Ian Advent
video coming in right now I have to send
it
to the person in charge
please put this into that
exhale shade thanks mate
all right perfect beautiful
I thought she wouldn't deliver I was
worried but here he is of course so
reliable
black out guy been in the game for three
months
what the [\h__\h] are you thinking can't you
read it's down there on the bottom left
it says please only join once I mean
that okay I guess you only joint once
but then you stay forever don't you
understand you're supposed to leave I'm
sorry then Wanna Be So Rude
um please leave after this one for sure
I know I know you want to win and all
that but this is not the place go
somewhere else
okay let's stop
oh God
I saw the texian
[Music]
oh shh
choose the one that I said I wanted to
just face guys you guys are so
considerate today in terms of choosing
the right tracks what the hell
and no rainbow road so far but it also
hasn't been offered to us has it
[Music]
yeah yeah and that's it
is that a saxophone or something like
that in the music
[Music]
I have zero music so [\h__\h] good
no no no
body
[Music]
I take it I remembered it was like a
but okay actually the timing of the
Thunder was pretty good
[Music]
because yeah
anyway
let's try to be what the [\h__\h] a bit
better now
[Music]
the two items I wanted to use it up
right before Oh well
no more British yet does this look like
England to you
bro
this time it worked oh but it's already
the end
what you guys are such losers
chill are you guys even trying all right
black out with you
[Music]
guys
live live
some people waited but not all of them
no you can't keep on making excuses like
that
is he not leaving
okay then I'm leaving you little [\h__\h]
how dare you now leave I do not listen
to my command
all right
I'm joining the same one again though
there's always two running at the same
time right
let's see
I don't want to be spectating no
hmm
yes you have to follow my order
yes there's always multiple ones
um
here we go okay
[Music]
little knife cutlery
thank you for nothing all right here how
about this one I have to change it don't
don't go in yet guys I get into you know
you won't get anything out of it by
going in early because I won't be in you
know understand
uh six seven six eight two three four
seven okay
ow
I hit my face so hard
I think that was also
what is this is this New York
[Music]
one
oh wow
[Music]
thanks thanks you get it
very unhinged today
New York accent I don't know how to do
in New York what is the New York oh mine
got chosen but that's not what I wanted
um what
only pull tuck
nice tribe hello
kim chicken
what's what's how do you say
hey I'm walking here oh
do they say that all the time hey I'm
walking I'm waddling
yeah well I don't like it when people
bump into me either I hate someone
it's wrong with people like I'm I'm the
type of why am I driving so slow I'm the
type of person who moves out of the way
people a lot because for some reason
everybody is so [\h__\h] ignorant out
there
like no one cares about how much space
they take on on the sidewalk
what is the matter with people
um
right like what the [\h__\h]
please think about it especially if
you're in a big group with like five
people like usually there's also a lot
of people who in in your own group who
don't get it but then usually I'm the
one trying to control it a little bit
and I'm like Yo dude can you move a
little bit over there there's like other
people who are trying to pass it
I gotta say though Nabi Chan
is not very good at this either
not the best at that
[Music]
okay
I am so lucky
I wanna ask you with nice rival action
yeah
oh right before the end getting a star
and a
bullet but I wasn't even on such a low
placement oh my God
let's go
come on
bacon do a good New York accent really
thank you oh my God stop
I want to do the electrodome
you had to know sucky sweating I was so
close I don't think I was ever so close
to nosagi before
no
by the way I was practicing my pecora
recently
I think I already forgot everything I
practiced though
[Laughter]
[Music]
how's that
yeah right I mean that was spot on
I can do her morning voice
[Music]
oh
not not that was on it
um what What's um I forgot some more
phrases what does she say
s
no not almond almond is that all you
[\h__\h] know about her
give me some phrases
I'm not even looking at the game
yeah is so cute I like sleepy pecora's
Empire
um
[Music]
I'm cute
I said that already
[Laughter]
well that lap at the end was me though
stupid girl who's
called that's not an amiibo what are
they called looks freaking cute that
Swedish person or whatever
I can't do that
I like just can't do the r
so I can't impersonate that either
oh
how am I four when I wasn't looking I'm
not oh there we go but that's so good
okay oh thank you
guys do so well when I was looking at
the chat for half of this tree
oh
good you said it
oh shush shush
ah
um
she says it a lot
oh
where's Daisy Gardens
[Music]
hey hey
hey Mom
hey Mom hey Mom
hey mother
oh my God I'm so good I'm so good at
holy [\h__\h] come on
[Laughter]
this
you know her voice I'm so [\h__\h] at
impersonating literally every anything
but pecula is so easy for me to
impersonate
I don't know
it's like
um
you make the voice really high and you
you you tighten your throat oh why the
[\h__\h] is blackout back
what the [\h__\h] is you back like I'm
getting angry now
are you not listening to the Stream
that won't be stupid
so I stand on in German anyway what the
[\h__\h]
probably just really needs some wins in
life
I'm sorry for the roast but they're
they're actually a good Mario card
player
seems like
wow it's beautiful here oh yeah
I just want to do some side thing here
guys
imagine just someone streaming Mario
Kart new tracks and just like slowly
driving looking at every corner of the
new map and taking some snapshots of the
snapshot shot function
like oh this part is real this this wow
these flowers they smell so nice
like really inspecting everything in
detail
anyway another thing I wanted to say is
I make my voice very scratchy
like almost like how I do obachian voice
or Grandma boys
yeah it's so easy
I'm so happy I can recreate my own she's
voice so well
um
all right
not that I can make much use of it here
[Music]
let's go
I can talk to myself and pick whatever
it's like talking to my OC
so the snare
mama
I was practicing by watching this one
video uh on YouTube it's a a clip of
pecula senpai's most famous and repeated
uh
like phrases oh [\h__\h]
it was even moved when I flew through
his hand
I don't care about my placement here
because the map is beautiful and I'm
just like chilling
boys was great thank you did you guys
watch kova's birthday Colin stream I
called in
and I I gave her and one day horse
riding coupon
okay blackout if you're not leaving I'm
gonna have to like block you forever or
something
please
oh I think he left
finally
now I'm all alone
foreign
[Laughter]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
haha
you don't know anymore which one it is
ah
[Laughter]
I should do a whole stream where I just
become peculus
if you want to go on a break for one day
but you're worried about your algorithm
your YouTube algorithm you don't wanna
you know is this a new map
don't want to be worried about not
streaming
you'll call me
no it's not okay
oh I like the music here though
um
and I also
yeah
oh my God I sound exactly
like here
oh my God
[Laughter]
I'm blessed with a good bass voice
I do sound like her
Nikki kitten
[Laughter]
come on come on
[\h__\h] what oh
I keep on trying to get over there but
it's not gonna happen
oh
Mamma Mia
[Music]
why am I singing that now
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
what is that
I love when she says that
is
[Music]
no I'm just randomly saying [\h__\h] now
I'll explain Mario Kart in that one
ah
oh she just loves
I'm gonna [\h__\h] kill my throat
okay okay it's over now I can't do it
anymore
we have to go back to smooth kiwawa
voice
uh hort
ons
laughs
you certainly do a good impression but
thank you
I understand oh
we're back in London mate
nice it's beautiful I want to go back to
London but not when it's cold the one
time I went it was cold as [\h__\h]
but also right now it's cold but it's
also cold here in Austria the past few
days holy [\h__\h] I've been outside
in the past three days every day
and oh my God I froze my butt off I even
um wore my skiing jacket
for most of the things
skin jacket very useful it did
definitely work quite much better than a
normal
word better than the normal uh like the
winter coat or so because it protects
you quite well from the wind as well
especially did you little [\h__\h] use my
mushroom
you better not
yeah yeah I recommend you guys don't get
a normal winter jacket if your country
gets really cold get a skin jacket
the best you can get and the ski jacket
comes with a lot of pockets too it's
really handy inside Pockets outside
Pockets everything
do you do alpino cross country skiing I
don't do any of that I I'm Australian
and I have a skiing jacket but I don't
really ski much at all
um I went skiing last winter and I I
just have some skiing trauma
uh and I haven't done it overall very
much in my life so I'm not very good at
it but I I do wanna
I do want to be good at skiing
I'm just not good at it though
I'm so scared especially like I don't
think I can even really improve now
because ah
I just
just I'm scared mommy
okay I'm so far behind
uh thank you for waiting thank you thank
you
let's take a fruit candy to fix all the
damage that has been done by
impersonating
[Music]
oh nothing new but let's do Tokyo blur
um
also I have like so many stories to tell
from
my my
adventure with navy Chan but I'm
thinking I want to tell most of it
tomorrow during Pokemon
um
I literally crashed into a tree's kit
yeah something like that happened to me
I crashed into
a fence
yeah yeah well documented story
happened with Cowie can we have been
very sweet
recently we have been talking more
um
I would say
we are getting along better
than before
which is good makes me happy
um
Callie asked me for one-on-one collab
and I'm like you know totally up for it
but at the same time I've been feeling
so uninspired by one-on-one collab games
like like collab games for like four
plus people
I I I like them and I think there's
plenty good ones
but one of one is like really difficult
in my opinion
uh
a lot of them are [\h__\h] or we already
played them because we both we played a
way out and the other one uh together
what the [\h__\h]
and if it's like more about one stream
only kind of game there's I feel like
there's not much good stuff out there
[Music]
but I told Cali uh let's wait
until I'm in Japan soon anyway
because then in terms of off collab we
can do a bunch more fun things I could
think of Plenty we can do a cooking
collab together at her place
because
she has done that uh cooking streams
just like me a couple times before so it
makes sense
um
what you can do karaoke again and
actually I actually I have one more idea
since she also has that suit that I have
I wasn't originally planning on bringing
it to Japan but now I'm thinking of
bringing it to Japan and we'd ring fit
together
I don't know though if I have space in
my suitcase we'll see because the winter
clothes take up so much space in
suitcase for Fox's sake
um
yeah I was making ring fit off collab
yeah
in full 3d
[Laughter]
would you be able to send it in advance
I don't wanna because I'm not sure about
sending things to Japan right now I
don't want to risk it that it doesn't
come there in time and [\h__\h] I don't know
how it is currently has anyone tried
that before
already over I felt like one minute or
less
yo what's up with today's web We're
Gonna Miss This did you guys wait for me
or are you guys just [\h__\h]
what happened
hmm
you beat me by one place again let's go
custom items I mean custom items
oh maybe disconnected
harsh words
thank you guys though thank you for
driving with me
um
Smash Bros are fighting game collab yeah
I guess so yeah yeah
but again I feel like I'm I'm gonna be
over there soon anyway so no rush to do
it right now
um
a lot more couch go up to play games
yeah that's true too
what are we gonna do I don't care Hyrule
circuit I don't care
I have seven mentions what's happening
again
she couldn't do it with me ah
oh I'm sure Callie would be up for it
maybe we can have one more person join
I only have a couple of collabs um
planned
off collabs
um
I'm planning is so difficult though uh
figuring out dates and [\h__\h]
but I think we'll have a live collabs
and
also they'll be able to
stream solo normally I think no problem
I am keeping some days empty so that I
can just do a normal solo stream or just
chill a little bit
actually I don't know if I told you yet
but the first couple of days
I'm gonna be staying with uh General
it it was actually
why that is happening is
don't be so close to me with the banana
oh God this thing makes me dizzy this
map makes me dizzy so I booked a hotel
yeah and
um I was I was looking for hotels
but over the course of like
what three weeks or so
it's actually pretty hard to find
um
something decent that's not totally
overpriced but still has thick walls
oh here's Eve
over New Years where a lot of hotels
were already booked out
um
so what I did was I just
made a reservation
a couple days after New Year's at a
hotel until the end of my trip and I was
like I'm gonna look at something cheap
some cheap Airbnb also and book that
later
um for the rest of the oh God oh God
for the rest of the trip but then
eventually
I was like discussing the trip of Jen
mark
and then General was so sweet to offer
me to stay in those days and her place
yay which saves me a lot of money
yay
then my Denmark best
than mine's best
pascado
best manager
now I don't have to buy a book and
overpriced
hotel for New Year's
my nose is itching
way too late why are these items so late
hope you'll have a good Channel thank
you
laser Sushi has been on four races now
[\h__\h] off
I'm so aggressive today
get out of here
please leave after one time thank you
thank you for following the rules this
one I'll give it my best shot no please
don't give it your best shot leave leave
leave leave
go away
[Music]
how do I kick him out I know you can't
kick people out right not good game
boom
go home
please
what what's what's their country flag
full I think they're taunting me now
they have to have a way to kick randoms
out it's so stupid
do I have to speak German
[Music]
why
who the [\h__\h] is this
yeah if he doesn't leave next time I'm
leaving
so what flag what flag
United States
[Laughter]
what the [\h__\h]
being as well they have points okay Bean
my British friends please after this
leave
let's see
if they understand my request
I'm still nice to Bean because I don't
think Bean hasn't been has been been in
there as long
sometimes you just forget the spaghetti
why did I get so slow there for a moment
what
ah the crony virus too really
are you guys all just [\h__\h] with me
like what the [\h__\h]
it started so well everyone was
following rules everyone was picking the
right tracks what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
it do be like that sometimes you just
speed off the track
right
sometimes it do be like that I I I
mean you called oh yes new code yeah but
I changed it
release the rage I haven't read
oh [\h__\h] oh my God
so fast just now
wait wait wait
no no no no no no no no no even if you
don't have the premium thing you will
still get it as a choice
as long as I guess I'm in there or so I
don't know
star will not protect me from falling
off the cliff I guess
useless
[Music]
okay I'm I'm
really bad this time I'm sorry I'll do
better next time
okay or maybe not
maybe not let's stop
why you guys never learned
oh
wasn't I like 13th just a second ago
please leave after participating once
let's see who gets it who gets it
I want to see a full sweep
a full swing
I see you with a crown
I swear to God if you're not leaving now
I will block you
okay
how do I block people
this has to have consequences
how do I know that
um
gotta go to profile
okay I'm kind of alert let me uh hide
this
um
uh
manage blocked user list
about blocking you so you can you cancel
out users to block from the list of
users you played with yeah where's that
list
game
ah there it is
or what there's a big list of people
here
so now that you know I'm serious
let's see
something with sushi
that
if you want
to redeem yourself and want me to
unblock you for future games you may
apologize on Twitter as a reply
and tell me that you understood
the rules and next time will not do it
I just have no patience but
foreign
all right everybody let's go back into
the game
consequences
there must be consequences
yes
I think it's still the same room right I
joined the same room
but I think it closed while I was gone
maybe
yes
[Music]
all right time to take off the omo cat
sweater
getting a bit hot
I feel like this is gonna fail
Nintendo online is gonna fail on me
again I feel it I feel it
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
bridge is it new or maybe Second Life
I use your usual stuff
oh that's wave one oh
um well let's go with it
are we full one two three four five six
seven eight nine not quite
come on come
on come on
[Music]
yes I will not accept your friend
requests
understand all
okay who what is that
oh
um
oh they're everywhere
wow
I'm all this nice
I like those people who play around with
their avatars to make them look like
something make them look funny
good effort
I wait for next race okay okay yeah
sometimes that happens or you get into a
different like
different version
of my
tournament because there's like parallel
universes
um
all right
[Music]
the music here oh
Mario Kart soundtrack [\h__\h] Banger
let's go
oh look how good I'm drifting I'm ready
to go on the highway
[Music]
why must you ruin my mood
rye bread why why why
why a YouTuber listener why
why must you hurt me
that was not on you
why everyone why
my
mind
[Music]
star absolutely useless
oh
could have been useful now
[Music]
okay well anyway guys let's talk a
little bit about this and that have you
seen whole talk is coming back with
this weekend
I wanted to squeeze in one more before
uh I get like really [\h__\h] busy
yeah and that will be him you know after
that there won't be a break I think
until
after I'm back from Japan
because I don't think I want to do it
while I'm in Japan I just don't feel in
control when
I'm not in my usual setup you know
it's kind of just as a streamer when you
stream every day with the same setup
it's just not it doesn't feel right
yeah anyway and then I'm also appearing
in a Malaysian convention comic Fiesta
with almond
makes sense right um
[Music]
yeah yeah we're doing a panel it's the
last convention that I'm appearing in
for this year
unfortunately it was once again one of
those cases where our appearance gets
announced after the tickets are already
sold out and this was our appearance was
announced not even a week
before the event
uh
this happens too often in my opinion so
that will definitely
be a feedback for me for next year or
like a condition
for me next year like
we
we want you guys I want you guys to come
to see me
and this is just like I see you guys
being frustrated about it and it
frustrates me too
[Music]
um
we'll do more episodes of shows an
official Channel no that doesn't
influence it at all no no no no
me being on Japan makes no difference
[Music]
yum
it's weird because I also then it also
worries me if we can even fill a panel
room because
we can't assume that the ones that
already bought tickets all really like
us enough to come to a panel now I'm
worried that we can fill the room but
I really don't know if we have so many
fans in Malaysia I mean I would like to
be surprised
positively surprised in America it might
not be so much of an issue even if it
gets announced after tickets are sold
out
but in Malaysia I'm not sure
um
definitely really
be more popular yeah that makes sense
the ID is also appearing there uh two
two ID members I think
um
um a lot of friends in Malay don't worry
really really Malaysian fan here oh wow
thank you
in New York you guys can almost get line
took so much space alone
makes me so happy oh
nobody's joining the room and no new no
no new tracks what the hell let's go
yoshido probably join yeah
sorry to the people who were in there
shinda
oh my cat line and NYC was crazy wait
wait wait wait wait the recent one
yeah the NYC where I did VR chant
that one you had to pack in tight in new
packing tight does that mean you had to
like be really close to each other
oh you beat the hardness dance with the
fact with my own oh cool
what defect
effect
can do that wait oh do you think
I'm confused
but good job the orb dude oh okay yeah I
did the the loopy deck of the orbitude
as well no or did I do it did I do it
with the ninja lady
not that kind of convention
ah don't worry about picking cheese land
we have we have had London Loop like
five times now it feels like
um we can do something else I don't even
I don't even mind
what what is left that I haven't seen
yet
from the new tracks
are there any left
foreign
Berlin
Maple Rainbow Road
really Berlin oh okay cool Berlin oh
what the [\h__\h]
well I've seen Berlin and Rand left
before hey
let's go
Maple Tree Way rock Rock Mountain Alpine
pass rainbow look at look how deep thing
without even looking at the game
[Music]
why
[\h__\h]
ah I thought I still had the fire flower
God damn it kind of
misused it
yo what the [\h__\h]
I'm gonna use that
oh
[Music]
I'm sure it's got Queen
this map shortcuts are easy to see
and make good use of
course
oh
[\h__\h] go
ah [\h__\h]
a shite
[Music]
this is rough I've been doing so well I
think but this is rough
oh I could have been farts
oh
[Music]
that was my best friend I took a
mountain
mmm
Mario card is
whoa what is that
Pokemon
[Music]
no I didn't choke I got Mario karted
no you're forgetting the first one let
Keanu win you get it you just get it
it's a digimon damn
or Digimon
wanted chocolate no
targeted by others obviously I'm not
gonna go so far to say that but it was
[\h__\h]
anyway let's go chocolate mountain
please thank you I haven't done this one
yet I think
[Music]
um
that's how we say it in German
by the way I saw Pokemon in real life
today
it was
fading
so
um
I was mine uh one thing that I wanted to
do with navitan and I wanted to show her
Hello everybody Draco too it was um
because Nabi you know she's you know
about butterflies right butterflies
butterflies so and also it's [\h__\h]
cold outside these days so I wanted to
do one thing where it's kind of warm
and there's a a Butterfly House
and
which is like like super tropical inside
tropical weather kind of very warm
and inside our like tropical plants We
performed palm trees and and there's a
lot of butterflies they mostly look the
same all of them it's like it feels like
there's only two or three types and a
lot of them are dead on the ground
or or dead on the walls and so on
because I just realized today when I
Googled it they have a very short
lifespan of 15 to 30 days yo
it's very Grim yeah we saw a lot of dead
ones we're like oh now you tell me eat
it look look oh but well when this one's
dead oh this one's dead too oh this
one's dead oh but this one
's a lot I've been to this place before
but this time I saw something that I
didn't notice last time or I didn't have
it at the time
um
they set up like some some kind of like
glass cages
where uh you could see like a lot of
butterflies coming out of their cocoons
is that how you say it
oh not paying any attention to this map
um and they were at different stages and
different looking cocoons and so on
really cool and one of them looked
exactly like Deadpool on the green one
the green cocoon Pokemon thingy
I don't know what it's called anymore
but it looked exactly like that I took a
photo too
I dodged it that one because I saw it
coming yes
yes like that
um that was actually
[Music]
what
the most
um fascinating part of the Butterfly
House for me today because I mean I've
been there a couple times
you guys so much
I hate you guys
[Music]
ah whatever
um anyway
[Music]
not so bad I hate Patrol
sorry for joined two times oh don't
worry about it you don't seem to like
want to trigger me
it's cute
it's the the what is it called
Wiggly
Wiggly thing
maybe this map oh
Wiggler
anyway
I think nabijan liked it also what the
[\h__\h] is that face what is that
allenanda not the good old face the
other one obviously
[Laughter]
the pink one none the level
who is the one who cannot read the room
and chose Luigi's pinball or Warriors
pin one
Luigi's pinball
I messed up I'm sorry it wasn't you
at least it didn't get chosen
um
oh
[Music]
no
comment
and topic change okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm gonna strike I'm gonna strike I'm so
close to [\h__\h] striking wow a tree
foreign
[Music]
but I'm fascinated
it's gone
I didn't go
is it always a mushroom comes out of
there
is that an invisible wall
felt like a skateboarder just a Tony
Hawk Tony Hawk
oh
when you're too Speedy that place is
rough because you like bump against [\h__\h]
but it's something
I'm
not Tony Hawks Pro Skater yeah I played
that back in the day
okay
Revenge
it's what you get that's what you
[\h__\h] get
oh
what what is that spawn huh
[Music]
oh ghostly made it back into after the
crash good job good for you
no no no no no no no
[Music]
safe safe
that's their payback for me saying I
don't believe in them
oh see right
I'm not gonna accept a loss against this
person
I beg you
your boss begs you
no I hate ghosts
no no
[Music]
nice sick jump sick moves
second time I fall off there
no I'm so far behind
[Music]
no
Spanish
[Music]
no play one round as
I kind of already did that though I was
model money in her a lot oh
Alpine pass guys please marymountain we
already did before
Alpine Alpine Alpine pass please
where's the snow if that's Alpine Alpine
pass
I think the gouda needs to leave
and the
trimmed deck as well thank you
oh yeah using Sun thank you but thank
you
hi wait there's two
did you guys coordinate that
how the [\h__\h] is there two of you
Peters two [\h__\h] Peters
how is that true penis
oh my God he looked to the side of this
the chin stands out that's fascinating
conspiracy are you guys friends
one is fatter and bigger than the other
dough so I know which one is the real
one
what do they call Peter and
[Laughter]
burp hello hello everybody let's go
please let me win please please please
please please please please
my first time on this map though so
don't expect any skills
any showcasing of skills
is optional
hehe
is this how he lost it
I forgot but I do like Family Guy
you know what Nabi is really into these
days
so weird and cute
speaking of Family Guy
she told me she just recently got into
um Rick and Morty
[Music]
yeah she's binge watching it and she
loves it
so
actually
as I said I don't want to tell too much
of our adventures yet but
yesterday
you know it got really [\h__\h] cold so
at some point we went to my place
[Music]
um
and I
I why am I invisible
oh
was that ghost
I was like I just want to go to my place
wants to change into some even warmer
clothes because I guess this wasn't
enough
oh
uh so I showed her my tattoos
and
um
then however
we both
kind of
I mean this may sound weird but we ended
up in my bed
watching Netflix watching Rick and Morty
a little bit
uh double star
uh and then falling asleep side by side
together
yeah we fell asleep watching Rick and
Morty it got really cozy and warm in my
bed you know
[Music]
but literally like literally literally
not not whatever it implies literally we
just did Netflix and chill
and then we went outside again after a
while
yeah
what is it with those bullets
bullet overload
[Music]
um
I ate eight was not so bad
not so bad right
oh but they're also were only 10 people
participating
glad you guys are really close I wasn't
sure we were that close but you know you
know I I actually at the moment I'm
using a single blanket on my big double
bed
um
and uh I don't know Nabi Chan was
laughing about it I said well I do have
a big blanket too but I don't use it at
the moment because it's such a [\h__\h]
hassle to change the sheets of the big
one and I sleep alone anyway so what the
[\h__\h] why would I use the big blanket
it's such a hassle kind of single blank
is kind of more comfortable too because
I can like I can wrap it around my body
easier you know stuff like that and it's
just more comfortable and and also it's
a bit more warm because my my single
blanket is thicker than my big double
blanket so anyway easier burrito yes oh
that's another thing
she kept on talking about burritos for
the whole weekend
so I only had to say a blanket and we
actually kind of fit on the one single
plank yeah
[Music]
and then at the end she complete
complaint complained that it wasn't so
warm as I would have promised because
yeah like I said well that's uh
I'll press the leave I said well that's
probably because
you were half of your body was outside
of the blanket
and she said yeah
no well
[Music]
he's acting all innocent look at him
with the feetsies
if you don't leave after this one
I'm gonna stop watching Family Guy
forever forever
no
Santos
please leave afterwards
whose Hank Hill is that a an actor
what who is that
I can't watch punishers what why
do you need him to stay for that
cartoon kid ah
yeah yeah Captain before
I shouldn't move forward but I don't
watch that show
yeah burritos that was another thing
has a big
interest in burritos right now
like she ate a burrito for breakfast
day when we met up
and
she kept on mentioning burritos every
day she said I want to eat a burrito
all the time
I mean burritos are good but what what
is that
obsession with burritos it's not healthy
it's not healthy Nabi Chan ah
I like burritos I do like them I guess
that was a breakfast burrito huh
[Music]
in general
it's I guess more spicy food
for breakfast while I like to eat like
super sweet stuff
um
you should try tacos though yeah I still
haven't really tried tacos before it's
weird
oh was that a shortcut I just I just
hope for it to be
something there it looked like an
opening and I was like well I have a
star nothing can go wrong right
oh oh the Chris oh I hate someone yeah
I'm better than Hank Hill
all right
which track haven't we seen yet the rock
rock something right
and Berlin
I'm still not here ah okay Peter bye bye
thank you thank you at least he listens
one time uh admittance only
yeah Berlin is a track apparently
thank you
thank you are these guys
oh yeah that one looks new with that
name looks new to me
foreign
's back
oh
is LP ah it's a different name and
different region okay wait so then only
Berlin
we're only missing Berlin or so
oh yeah that's the Spy X family Anya I
was thinking so and we're not enough
fault and why does this dude have the
crown he just came in
why don't I have the crown
why are we only like five people
okay it's seven is it oh it's eight
oh wait the audio sounds a bit crackly
okay I fixed it
uh-huh okay
yes I need my crown
well now we have a higher chance for a
higher placement don't we
so I'm gonna do my best let's go
that didn't seem to have hurt him
no double item
I don't know the shortcuts of this map
either though
although wait somewhere around
here there is one
I am okay well that one no I wouldn't
even attempt that one that needs good
aim
no
no no no oh
[Music]
at least I got a coin better than
nothing
if we don't get Berlin soon I'm just
gonna give up though
just saying
Berlin is a track right
oh
mud
we know mine off
[Music]
but I didn't
oh just need some some confidence
I'm actually really impressed by myself
just now
oh no
okay okay okay okay
let's go
[Music]
not bad
so it takes that to you because
it was pretty good she
oh
come on I'm so excited like Arena doll
um
Shrek cute hat I think it's supposed to
be a Shrek hat
kill on
you are a good driver thank you you if
you account for the fact that you're
only
no
chunky monkey outside of the room hello
anyway
yeah there's still not a full room again
also the old man I think was here before
and is not leaving but okay we're not
enough people anyway
are you guys still trying to get in or
what
oh
are there any new people who haven't
raced against me yet were trying to get
in did now we get along with your cats
yeah she did and she said they were
really cute and you know she likes them
but she wasn't as attached to them as
other people I think
like
her she wasn't as young impressed by
that oh my gosh
I expected a bit more excitement
she was like ah cute but
why the [\h__\h] are we on Rainbow Road
I can do it
I'll do my best I'll try my best
in my face
tournament called uh I think I still the
same is it not
it wrecked
she was after a different type of cattle
or oh what
what
yeah bottom left
the code is on the bottom left of the
screen
oh I don't want to use my mushrooms now
it's dangerous oh
okay now
now
what the [\h__\h]
is that control
huh
what the [\h__\h] was that
different color no if you can't read it
you need glasses it's that simple
[Music]
sounds like a you problem
s
Anthony beat zooming it's time for me to
zoom to the where's my Bullet Bill
where's my bowl
do I jump here no that wasn't it I was I
was hoping for a shortcut
oh [\h__\h] this
ah
how how are you still here I've been
wasting so much time with falling off
twice
[Music]
what Thunder and banana at the same time
uh here's the shortcut I think yeah
[Music]
falling off is what we're doing yeah
maybe I wasn't the only one
I got funded in blue shells oh wait
uh all right Mary Mountain we've only
had it once so I don't mind repeating it
thank you
the painting painting thank you thank
you
have you noticed Improvement in your
Mario Kart skills since you first played
you mean since I oh SpongeBob disgusting
looking SpongeBob
compared to the first time I ever played
it yeah yeah of course
yeah well hi talking
standing there so cute boy
but probably not
significant Improvement within the whole
year
this whole year there's um
up and downs and mostly Downs
and the SpongeBob looks ugly
maybe that's on purpose
come on must be on purpose
ho ho ho
I went shopping for some supplies for
the members crafting stream today
but I decided to buy things a few things
off of Amazon after all
because
I wasn't quite happy with what I was
seeing in the shops
I hate you
you know you knew I was right there with
me and you did not want me to find
happiness in Mario Kart
you want it
okay well [\h__\h] all of you I hate all of
you
the Christmas isn't Christmas and this
whole season about loving and giving
love and being nice and being polite and
giving presents and [\h__\h] where's my
present huh
where is my present
oh
where is my bread
[Music]
can't take much more of this game it's
triggering me
[Music]
what are you doing
huh
oh that's pretty
[\h__\h]
would you like a book for Christmas did
you watch the video
my my Advent video of Cali did you watch
it
I said what did I say did I say no or
yes because honestly now that I think
about it I mean I wouldn't be completely
unhappy it depends on the book
now
whoever's in front of me is eating this
I guess that's
they must have dodged it or something no
no
[Music]
I don't
put the very next
I lost anyway thank you Tommy
Tom what a gentleman
that gentleman
who was waiting for me there
[Music]
oh okay that's the bootleg only had it
once
is there really a Berlin
does Berlin exist
oh is Berlin just a pigmentation of my
imagination
so does that make sense is that is that
how you say a figmentation oh
pigment
s
[Laughter]
figment
pigmentation of my of my imagination no
I think
okay okay
what is the pigmentation
uh
let's go wow wow
oh
okay
that person looks familiar the one
next to Peach
but maybe they all look the same with
their knees
let's see oh
let's see if I will do better this time
than I did last time on those Maps
[Music]
it was a risky move
oh I actually got him but
I dodged my own
shell
sick
eat must consume mass consume eat it
I hate this game I hate this game I love
this game and I hate this game at the
same time
yeah you better be giving me an item
a good one a good one
look at those sick tricks you
play
I'm like getting really serious about
this I'm so I feel so competitive
it's way to go
please pull it bullet bullet no why no
bullet
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] edges
[Music]
yeah it didn't help me though
they gave it to me way too late
hell
sure no
oh maple
Maple Maple Maple Maple Maple Maple
maple
Maple Maple maple
where can
The Canyons
Oh Canada
Oh Canada how pretty are you maple
leaves
you eat them on some pancakes
and you eat them just Raw in a shake Oh
Canada Oh Canada how pretty are your
maple leaves
why you guys
not leaving are they leaving
are the people who should be leaving
leaving
that is not your national anthem well
why not it should be
hmm
well Vamp otaku has been here before I
know that
please leave after this one
then they left and came back
and maple syrup yeah it's the same thing
but you make maple syrup out of a maple
tree no
um
don't you
[Music]
know right
you believe is the symbol of Canada
so I don't see anything wrong with my
song lyrics
[Music]
I ruined my Boost
I didn't get a night oh
what is that man
at least for once I was able to go
straight here
damn oh shortcut there
[Music]
so many mushrooms
okay I got a little bit lucky there by
at least picking up some mushrooms
uh in the tunnel right in front of the
tunnel
[Music]
difficult
some edges are kind of weird
I don't know
it's a nice map but something's about a
little weird
[Music]
go go go go go
look at me no no no
[Music]
show what you got
oh let's go
[Music]
riveting content you are seeing here
from your local Phoenix
oh she's giving it all at all and this
all of this without a license can you
believe it
well people do say
the best drivers have no license don't
they yeah I hear it a lot
fascinating inspiring
she believes in herself she has
confidence
oh and she tries to stay away from the
red shells which eventually will
probably
really [\h__\h] up her score in the end game
but can she fix it with the few
mushrooms that she has catchy oh yes she
[Music]
super safe
oh [\h__\h] and Santa Claus right above me
Santa Claus tried to
give me a Christmas present my best
scores today is second and third let's
go
well oh there's this Rick or a Morty uh
one of those Rick okay is Rick hey Navi
really likes you
okay please please leave thank you thank
you
and Santa Claus unfortunately you must
also leave even though thank you I enjoy
your presence but your presence and your
presence oh
my Rick left what was Rick already here
but that dude is also from some kind of
uh animation I think the what's it
called
Adventure Time yeah that's it
didn't watch that ever
hello
oh that face I know that face oh
a Chihuahua but I didn't mean the
Chihuahua I mean the the one with the
yellow hat looks familiar to me too me
uh
been driving what
stream is over to 32 hours 46 minutes
[Music]
oh it's almost midnight
and how come how come there has been no
no
Berlin
I don't think Berlin exists
I've been having a lot of fun driving I
guess but uh what the [\h__\h] I
started late yeah but I thought it was
maybe two hours at the most
by now I lost track of time
hmm
freaky Wawas oh let's go which Cuba will
win this gives me higher chances of
winning
even if it's a different kilala that
still means I get the win
my game my rules
[Music]
oh yeah yeah
thank you guys
finally I got someone
oh my God that was a ghost
No my only a coin why why
this might be my my last race Maybe
[Music]
it was starting so well
oh
let's go no time to waste [\h__\h] the star
I don't need to start
I don't want it
this is my chance for Redemption
nice nice nice thank you whoever sent
that
stupid ass [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] you
okay [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you
oh man
[Music]
okay if there's no Berlin now I'm ending
it
what the [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
no better quinoa was not better
all right I'm out of here
it's over
Berlin canceled
Germany canceled
nope ah
Berlin is not the capital of Germany
anymore it is now colon or Munich or
handbook whatever I don't care
Berlin Capital perms revoked
oriented love this love would be good
[Music]
that's what you get for not showing
yourself to me you were you were too
scared foreign
[Music]
how
do I have to leave now I'm confused no
thank you
thank you soon check it out the offline
instead oh
I could I could good idea oh uh Grand
Prix
but wait can I do a single one
I thought
time Trail trial
okay
oh
ah cute is it good
it looks cute
where is Neil
but that doesn't look new oh
Berlin by the ways it's the first one
and the other ones the other ones we've
seen
um
oh wait no there's a new Rainbow Road oh
seeing the new Rainbow Road there's
really a new Rainbow Road
why do they have to keep on making new
Rainbow roads
okay
um there's no NPC it's kind of sad but
let's go let's go
turn up the music for Berlin
so good
wow
why
what
like Paris you know has a fitting bgm
how is this fitting to Berlin what the
[\h__\h] what is that
[Music]
what's going on why are we in the subway
oh
oh you guys barely hear it
I'm alone anyway so
wow well this part
Maybe is a bit
boring German is it they shouldn't I
don't know what I expected but
when this was
[Music]
this sounds like a morning
2022 track
foreign
you know what I'm talking about
this sounds like they're gonna start
singing um
[Music]
that song that song
not anymore now this part not so much
because of that extra instrument
[Music]
but anyway yeah looks exactly like
Berlin 10 out of 10.
no honestly Berlin
was giving me more scary Vibes than this
I'm sorry but
okay okay
it's sped up
it's sped up let's go
oh [\h__\h]
okay okay the soundtrack is
amazing but I don't see any connection
to Berlin
[Music]
cool
what city would have been better I don't
know it's not about the city it's about
uh
on the music
and no and uh
I want to also see the new Rainbow round
first so shut up guys
I don't
it's not funny
[Music]
um
whoa
whoa the floor holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh
wait this this boy looks like something
um
I can create in real life whoa where in
the [\h__\h] Universe oh my God what is
that
blasphemy
oh doing pretty good so far
oh
oh don't look at the chat Jupiter Uranus
but wait which one you guys don't know
your planets oh [\h__\h] wow
this is pretty cute
it has a the surrounding Circle thingy
drip let's go that was Saturn which one
is that one over there
bye
is that the Moon down there on the left
is that the Moon
whoa whoa
the mall's gonna be rescued
[Music]
it's not Rainbow Road anymore this is a
small crater Paradise
[Music]
I mean honestly it's spitting because I
think the other rainbow roads were also
uh often
in kind of in space
and this time you actually get to walk
on the moon
and I'm the only one racing here so I
was the first to be on the bus
sorry Americans or whoever
hey was the first
there's actual video proof right here
first first speaks on the moon okay well
that's that's for sure you can give me
that title I'm
on the phone
[Music]
okay okay okay
I actually took a little nap before the
stream so I'm still fine I I I don't
want to cook after this but I do want to
also read some super chats so let's do
that
oh
yummy Moss
Cuba on the moon fan art
[Music]
oh
yes for racing with me today
[Music]
um
and once in the menu good question what
is on the menu my I'm like my my voice
is a bit exhausted I I I feel like in
these three hours I let out so much
energy so many screams and [\h__\h]
that now I'm like drained a little bit
where am I
ah
I left that way in the previous stream
[Music]
okay
oh
this is cool whole eyes there
brights on like the upcoming streams
when they're late for the stream they
write nibble question mark
sleeper
sleeping sleeping in question mark
what's up
call him out call him out
um where
where have we stopped reading super
chats previously do you know
um
I don't know when this one is really
restocked you should just check every
day because Amazon is very fast with
restocking
NASA already put a phoenix on Mars what
[Laughter]
how when who
and need to read Minecraft thank you
is it up there's a phoenix Rover
they call it Phoenix
I've actually seen a lot of Phoenix
named things over the weekend too there
was a phoenix tree there's there's a
like a palm tree kind of thing that's a
that where the Latin name has the name
Phoenix or so in it
that was one of the things the other
things I forgot
hmm I helped work on it
[\h__\h]
I wanna believe you
did you really
I mean who knows we have like some
impressive people in kfp but
yes boss really how
how
I will believe you if you can tell me
[Music]
not a full detail explanation
and one small step for thinking kind
why can't the major contract that I
built the mats or one Lander that became
it
oh
sounds legit now
who literally wants him to explain
rocket science nah
hmm
[Music]
oh
hmm
I don't believe it I believe it
oh
wow
[Music]
oh gray sweater back in stock oh
okay okay
oh did you guys hear what I announced
today randomly in kobo's stream
and
I have a song
coming out
for Christmas
um
yes with coupon
I I wanted it to be all three branches
so I invited a couple who I wanted to do
a song collab with anyone
and then I was thinking
could I get it from Japan who I want to
sing with and yeah I thought about that
myself
um would be a good combination
um especially for this song
um it's a it's a very fun song
I hope you guys will like it it's
Japanese though but it's very fun
and um I'm telling you now this is by
far not the only thing uh
so there's a bunch of other things
coming out around the same time
uh
let me just say in total
there will probably be free
musical things that I am involved in
[Laughter]
and in hindsight I feel
like I shouldn't have planned for a
Christmas song cover
because obviously it's gonna be
overlapping with a lot of other things
free Jesus shut up
uh especially since they're all gonna be
probably within the span of the same two
days
um
it's
quite a lot and you know in hindsight I
feel like it's very stupid but just kind
of happened like this
uh and I think two of them will be on my
channel the one with Kubo and watama
and another one
and the last one will I think at least
not be on my channel so at least there's
not too much competition within my own
channel
yeah but that's um some things that I've
been recording recently I told you I've
been recording a lot and that's um some
of the things not all of it some things
are for more in the future
uh but yeah
no nothing with Cali
that's um
that has been delayed many times and
there is no lyrics yet
can't record it yet
Canada Lane the other one no the thing
is they're all Chris's themed kind of
they all have to come out at that time
there's one that maybe isn't so
Christmas themed but there's a reason
why it has to come out at that time
anyway
[Laughter]
so yeah
yeah
it's a little bit stupid but at the same
time I'm thinking
it actually would be fine because I will
I don't know if I can stream
the days after Christmas
because my family
uh or at least my brother and my mom are
sleeping over
from 24th to 26 two nights
and I don't think I will be uh
able to stream really so instead you can
at least stream the songs
um
yeah
okay okay and I I wanna stream
definitely on the 23rd and if possible
maybe on the 24th before my family comes
but they might come kind of early
yeah sorry
and then when they leave I'll stream
again of course
but while they're here I don't know yeah
difficult and feels awkward anyway
oh
but yeah at least then you can stream
the songs for a while I'll try to at
least
have them be on different days
maybe 23 24 25 impossible
uh actually one of the songs
um the one that's not not gonna be on my
channel probably
um yeah we'll probably not make it for
the 24th or 25th anyway because
there has been some delay in
uh
certain
things
whatever works yeah well a delay would
work better for me actually for that
situation
um
yeah yeah
I wonder if the chicken that I have in
my fridge is still good
um
[Music]
why are you so surprised what
what you guys it's been two and a half
years by now you must have come to the
realization
that I cook with chicken
[Laughter]
okay
accept it accept it
Nani
how brutal
you what you guys
oh man
have you guys seen fauna's new outfit
it's cute
I hope that the other
uh members will be able to reveal
their own outfits
sooner rather than later hmm
very cute it's girly yeah yeah and it
reminds me of Tola senpai's
casual outfit they can like partner look
and I think Thomas isn't the only one
ever like that that kind of like
combination of a high-waisted short
skirt with a blouse underneath and a
fluffy knitted sweater with some ribbons
on it it on top I think I've seen that
combination quite a lot it's a it's a
very popular girly choice for
a casual outfits it's such a class to
come actually the um kind of as a like a
summer version of it without a sweater
because she has a high-waisted black
skirt with a white blouse as well
I'm a two
I think she even mentioned it's
mainstream like that it isn't for real
yeah
well then she can match with tula's
Empire
um
all right did I have a cardigan for that
yeah did she
she had I completely forgot about it
what does it look like oh
it's not knitted though is it
what I forgot what did I forget I
remember the underneath part so well uh
Amelia Watson casual
ah okay at least this one looks very
different from the other uh like
sweaters
because it has that
um that pattern
um
but the skirt that Emma has in that
outfit
is
uh a fashion item that's been
sold a lot in the past two or three
years in actual real life
it's kind of a kind of A J Fashion thing
that got really popular and ended up
being everywhere
even I I had a skirt like that I think
[Music]
a chicken
who knows nose
all our outfits could work IRL
yeah
yeah of course even even our default one
I mean
I feel like you could make a RL wearable
version of her default outfit quite
easily without making it look too much
like a cosplay thing
I mean she has of course the whole
Sherlock Holmes thing going on but still
maybe without the coat
would look more
suitable for wearing outside yeah yeah
yeah yeah
fish on head what
have you never seen someone with a fish
on their head before
what and your basic you're too basic
yo I got no energy
trying but my energy is gone thank you
Mario Kart for killing my energy but
I'll try my best to read now
[Music]
this one
we're doing the Wither fight this week
so far we're still only four people no
one replied to my shout out if anyone
wants to participate
but fauna said she wants more than one
Beacon anyway so maybe she'll do it
again with a different group at some
point
yeah it's 12 a.m I know but I had a nap
anyway and I don't wanna I don't want to
leave you guys hanging without reading
some stupid chat so
it's okay I'll do a little bit uh Patsy
Duncan Mr can't speak Spanish for the
pinky oh sorry about the shiny Frost
move potential uh but I'm sure you'll
find another shiny soon will I will I
don't if you really want one you would
you could set up a link called to trade
with viewers have fun in Minecraft fun I
worked pretty hard on a lot of new Farms
I saw
pretty impressive like I was surprised
how much she got going there
um
mostly on her own I assume
with some help here and there
um
she's like like you know back in the day
when it was just myth uh I was like
I don't know kind of the the engine of
our server and now it's fauna you know
what I mean
but anyway thank you don't worry about
it I don't wanna get Chinese for mothers
because it just doesn't feel like it
doesn't feel the same way as finding it
yourself so it's okay but thank you I
know I know you guys would want to give
them to me and you offered and it's very
sweet but yeah I'm not that crazy about
Chinese that I would just
that I feel like I needed from you guys
and also tomorrow's Pokemon stream might
be the last one because I think we're
definitely finishing the story tomorrow
right
um
actually well if it's about Minecraft
cow carrot I will take your actually and
accept it
and
there's post game
uh well if it's story I want to do that
too but uh
anyway let's see my my face feels so
tired you know how that feels guys
my face is tired I can't feel my face
when I'm with you
no no no no no
and I have done a lot what what is that
like it's not that like I didn't get
enough sleep
after talking all day I feel like that
is that one where it comes from
because I have that a lot when I stream
my face and my jaw and everything will
just get really tired
um
talking a lot does that to me
smiling a lot oh yeah I do smile a lot
when I stream
um
which should be a positive thing
yeah okay
um makes sense
it actually really feels exhausting
ah take a place
thank you
oh it was like what calendar Facebook
account thank you it's such a nice idea
of a small Christmas gifts for the
Halloween event it makes me so I just
thinking about it also can't wait for
phonical others so thank you I hope I'm
not like annoying the other en Girls Too
Much by making them participate
but I think it's worth it and it's a
cute project and we needed something
like this I don't think we're doing
anything like big in terms of like VR
um this time
I remember like I'm uh saying a while
ago that like she's not gonna be
planning anything
um this year
uh and then that somebody else could
like plan something if they wanted to
and I was thinking about it but then I
don't know I didn't know what and then
in the end
I guess I did end up doing something
um
it's it gets you hyped for each day
until Christmas and so on no I don't
know if it's about being burned out I
honestly think it's like totally
understandable and acceptable and to be
expected at some point we can't expect
from Ahmed to do to be the one in charge
to get us our get our [\h__\h] butts off
of our chairs and do something special
but for every special you know occasion
so when she wrote that I 100 agreed and
understood
um
and organizing VR stuff VR events and so
on is very very stressful
especially if you try to include all of
the members
yeah so
anyway
um I hope that the Ian advent calendar
is some kind of a small way of making up
for there not being
some kind of big VR Christmas collab
okay
um
but there might be uh as I said in the
sweater reveal
that was
not
revealed correctly because I messed up
with time zones I felt so [\h__\h] stupid
I I I I for the full hour after that I
kept on face palming I face palmed
myself to sleep you know other people
cry themselves to sleep I face palmed
myself to sleep on that night
um there's a whole life calendar
that's about it what the [\h__\h]
type in
on your browser
Holo en minus or that Dash
advent.com
and then you'll see what I'm talking
about
you have a lot to catch up on what was I
saying oh yeah oh yeah in the review for
this weather I said um
that this is not the only thing
that we have
and in
a petal we say in German do you say that
in English probably not right
hopefully that should be this
expectation for Big Bear stuff all the
time yeah
I feel like we accidentally created
Expectations by doing it for such a long
time every time
for all the big occasions and
um it shouldn't become the norm because
it is difficult especially if you try to
include everyone so I think it's okay
um
and an ace up my sleeve yeah that was
that's what I mean basically
so there's another thing uh coming up
it's not a VR collab but it's you know
something at least for Christmas
not by me
though
but as I said I hope the Advent calendar
makes up a bit for
those things yeah
but I'll try I eventually I want to also
organize some kind of big VR thing
eventually
I hope I can or it doesn't have to be VR
though but um there's so many worlds
that we have that I feel like they
deserve to be reused
um
and the game and create dungeon might be
danishes
GM let me thank you for the pinky
it's wonderful to see my two favorite
YouTubers together thank you all for the
fun streams oh thank you for liking both
of us and supporting both of us thank
you soon
I'm happy to hear that very sweet thank
Grace wanted back on Amazon there you go
guys Go Get It Go Get It
you can match with me
okay regards that thank you for the
pinky attention help funnel trapped me
with other librarians
I remember that one
oh no yeah it was some shocking
terrifying to see
how she
kept her Librarians literally kept as if
they were animals
[Music]
they're like animals like animals like
animals balls
[Music]
ah terrifying yeah scary scary
[Laughter]
amazing sky thank you
wrestling thank you for the pinky well
and final gift of such modeling Vibes
such a comfy stream we do
really
Dwayne
I feel like like separately there's
times where people see both of us with
modeling Vibes but I didn't quite see it
when we were together
oh
interesting
[Music]
which is Mom friends then
[Laughter]
Mr empty block dangers and hype Urban
dangerson
these are like rare by all means you
should find a giant tree by Omi have I
not found that before is that a by all
me I haven't seen before is it new
giant tree biome
I mean I feel like I've seen some big
trees
like in jungles and so on
shut up
the dark oak forest oh I've seen that
one before
[Music]
you want it for the rest of your gems oh
yeah I still want to do the book club
I'm working on it
no then
kind of
hey I don't care Brandon I'm doing it on
purpose I prefer this way
girl talk as well I um I was kind of
like thinking of doing it this week at
first but then I thought I already have
the weather collab
um this week so I wanted to keep it for
another week
it might happen next week
but I didn't forget it I'm just trying
to spread things out like that
oh
the girls the girls talk
yeah throw toward Jacob 47 out thank you
and this is just Rachel just Terraria
no
I'm sorry
I'm sorry yes mirror I don't want to
play Terraria
there was this one time where money and
Senpai was like hey this was back when I
was still in Japan she was like hey
let's play Terraria together
and then we tested it out we played
privately for like a really short time
because I guess mine is that by test
sound games beforehand to see if they're
worthy of being on a stream
did I never tell you the details of this
no don't just never never happened but
she wanted me to be part of a group to
play Terraria with I guess
and it never happened I I guess you
didn't deem with Murphy and to be honest
I mean I guess I'm kind of relieved
it's fun
I would have done it if she would have
wanted to do it I would have done it
yeah
yeah after that some members played
Terraria but I also didn't want to join
because I wasn't interested in it
it's not my thing
[Laughter]
it's interesting but you know
yeah this is the graphics mostly
tell me yeah
all right
[Music]
I fell into an AOE
kind of addiction after that and
watching a lot of videos and like even a
tournament
[Laughter]
uh an AOE tournament
very interesting
um
yeah kind of rabbit hole
[Laughter]
is
yeah she learned some crazy strategy
not crazy I guess but um it was
interesting to see
like the insane amount of multitasking
in tournaments
yeah and I kept on rooting for the one
that was always losing for some reason I
I really wanted him to win
but he didn't was sad
apparently the finale of that tournament
was going is going to or or did happen
already maybe in Germany
I was like oh I could go
yeah highest APM they both had really
good APM but I guess that one dude was
just like not even human it was like
alien level APM
crazy
I can't I literally can't
but if Muna really eventually like I
haven't heard from this since ages ago
but if she really eventually ends up
planning that AOE tournament
oh I'll get so deep into this [\h__\h]
I'll play AOE for a whole [\h__\h] week
[Laughter]
but hey I've at least already getting
kind of a head start because I do like
the game
and then getting a head start of
practice by being the only one streaming
it a little bit
recently at least
when there was in that tournament there
was one commentator
cool was a woman and I was thinking of
maybe asking her to teach me AOE
but that wasn't sure if I wanted to get
that serious about it just yet and if it
would even be fair if I if I get a pro I
mean she's she's uh I think she's pretty
good like she knew what she was talking
about as she was commentating it which
is definitely more knowledgeable than me
I don't know I just don't know if it's
fair to get me a trainer
why don't you shout a woman because it
was kind of the only woman the only
woman I've ever seen who plays AOE like
uh in on YouTube and so on than twitch
because I was looking for videos right
like guides and so on and they were all
buying guys so
forget about Fair think of the content
I mean what's up it doesn't mean that
you're good at that though well but
but for sure
yeah yeah yeah but she's better than me
it's definitely stuff she can teach me
the only woman I've ever seen
[Music]
um
teaches some I always like oh I think
there was something about castling
I think one one AOE slang was castling I
think
which I guess is like really quickly
building a castle in front of the enemy
and trying to get him with that or using
a lot of Castle so I don't know
oh that's also in chess
[Laughter]
slang to us is beautiful oh it turns you
on doesn't talk and talk Ali to me
I'm sexy spicy
and where was I uh taking some
connection thank you for the pinky yo
mama how are you doing lately uh I can't
get streams because of my because of my
position in the organization is being at
the side of the CEO CFO and my internet
is firewalled what the
what the soap on your streams is
impossible but I listen to your music
always
you know oh well it's time to become the
CEO then
you can't possibly be firewalled right
no that's sad
when your job is promoting you and
treating you well but you get [\h__\h]
firewalled as if you're in school
what the hell
as if you're in school
like back in the day
ah well I hope you can come back to me
but at least you didn't forget about me
thank you so much thank you
[Music]
um I'm waiting for you Jeff the Phoenix
Sony and packaging for brief moments
that I felt a presence once one that
reminded me of my faith I've held on to
all those years despite being called
obsolete because I hope again so again
witness the holy bird Jeff Jeff listen
listen listen you must at least know
that I still believe in Phoenix Sun in
Phoenix and Supremacy at least in terms
of Human Rights
and I will never
turn phoenixson into such a horror movie
scene as what fauna created is it has
and and that should make you happy and
proud forever
even if I'm gone for a while at least
at least
at least 10 is still
a safe
City for the phoenicstonians
yeah organic beautiful
and people can make love with who they
want to make love with not forced to
make love in in one tiny Square cell
to breed
until you are something worthy of
keeping
yeah it's just not no no no
so don't worry Jeff I'm on your side
Jacob 47 out thanks
giving red ones oh
it's my birthday today for December oh
it's been 10 days I can't believe this
is already my third birthday is kfb
thank you for always being the best
honestly anyone could ever ask for
attention
it would just make me so proud and happy
to be your fan love you forever Kiana
[Music]
happy birthday
your shoes to a happy birthday
[Music]
you've been so loyal
while being respectful
[Music]
happy birthday
to you unknown
such a good chicken
perfect for fried chicken
I'm gonna make nuggets
with your beautiful face
happy birthday
[Music]
to you too
speaking of ears of verbs they really
freak me out
so please make sure to always cover your
ears
congratulations thank you for supporting
me for such a long time and happy
birthday hope you had a lovely birthday
it's kind of late now but you know I
know you don't mind
thank you soon
hope you had some good birthday cake
oh
[Music]
no add to the calendar video in 20
minutes burp ears do before you they
really are awesome
nice so several ones even they're
awesome
[Music]
so we have no peanut what's the peanut
is it the thing around the ears that I
have
what about yours my ears are fixed now
by the way thank God that was terrifying
I was like oops I Did It Again I clocked
up my ear and I can't [\h__\h] here I
[\h__\h] hate it
yeah I barely couldn't hear Mommy John
on that one day I think it was yesterday
or the day yeah yesterday and today
uh I was like oh my ear you know what
I'm gonna clean it I don't do it that
often
but
I just felt like you know and I didn't
even go in that deep
didn't go in that deep
because I didn't want another
thing like that happening again
but yeah apparently a little tiny bit
was already too deep and then I was like
we can't hear [\h__\h]
you had an ear infection oh no oh
I hope it gets better for you soon
I caught some stuff yes
a cotton stabbed myself but
um yeah it was funny eventually uh
at like
late lunch or so I was able to like move
my ear a little bit around and open it
up
hmm I I know I know the doctor can rinse
it out I did that before when it was
really bad
but this time it kind of fixed itself
Hallelujah
[Music]
baking soda water drop it in and rinse
another [\h__\h] baking soda life hack
that's insane
can baking soda do anything
baking soda like [\h__\h] op we need a
baking soda beetuber or something like
that
oh my God
[Music]
incredible
whoa
it sounds like it might not be good for
your ears so check with your doctor
first please
anyway thank you so much Pepsi thank you
students
for the pinky yeah
and all armed and ready to go to battle
I see rocket Dear Santa thank you for
the pinky okay let's say babe wants to
come ah I know one of those okay let's
see wait once you do come with her on
the international adventure and ride a
donkey through a country the size of
Slovakia what does that matter
she wants one more person to come even
another en member or olly Orlando or
Kobo who should it be
a donkey
through a country the size of Slovakia
[Music]
I think I would go with Kobo because I
could probably convince Kobo that that
is a horse
and then she will probably enjoy it
quite a lot
[Music]
practically a horse
horse
thank you for watching me since my debut
thank you soon
kitchen
um
thank you
you give me the hand of your firstborn
child
[Music]
gaslighting okay
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's just because of AOE I wonder
I would probably play more AOE if I
didn't need to
requested one week in advance I I
because normally I make my schedule on
Sunday and then
yeah well
I would have to plan it on a Sunday
[Music]
morning
and then I don't know do I Really Wanna
[Music]
it's not like this for every game but no
and Anthony
thank you for the pinky this reminds me
of playing the game in my childhood for
sure glad to sell it cheat left with
your mood you will get the win properly
next time for sure but for now let's
enjoy it car mania
I knew the game from my channel but I
never knew about those cheat codes so
that was really fun
thanks guys for telling me about it and
it's really fun it lifted my mood I mean
I enjoyed the playing a game normally
but at some point when things just don't
go well
I was
just okay Angel
almost close enough
[Music]
oh foreign
it's a publisher thing
a developer
connections
[Music]
oh by the way since I saw Trevor G's
profile picture above Tales of her eyes
I could totally finish it within this
year but now you know you guys kind of
gave me the idea that I could possibly
finish it on stream now and now I'm
waiting for perms like I just want to
make sure like I'm I'm trying to get it
uh
um
like confirmed
I haven't gotten uh info back from it
it's probably it probably would be fine
in that case I think I want to stream it
but yeah
it's gonna be lots of action and yeah
yeah I'm not the Ambassador would be
nice if I could
finish it off
why the sudden change it's not really a
sudden change apparently it's been like
this the whole year and I just didn't
notice
[Music]
might need to pre-record it
you know but that's lame I want you guys
to be able to give me like help
[Music]
it's ready yeah I can use my sash again
wait this time
by attaching it to me right I couldn't
do that before I think
what why does she have to record it
foreign
[Music]
can't be a [\h__\h] chicken forever when
when you go skydiving
because the pro will just force you huh
I mean there's obviously as long as the
pros with me I don't think I would be
too scared but it's still [\h__\h] scary
angry ghost thank you for the rest of
the chat though Piada halo jump one
Halo junk
not Halo when but halo jump when what
I don't get it
I'm getting angry ghost I don't get it
oh because we were talking about jumps
huh like bungee jumping and stuff ah
high altitude low opening is that what
Halo stands for what
[Music]
drop at 20K feet
but like skydiving
[Music]
pull
you're super dangerous oh this is
without like like some kind of safety
thingy
oh oh no okay you do have a shield but
you open it really low
[Music]
military skydiving
it's kind of everybody from so up high
you need to wear oxygen what
crazy
basically a spacesuit what I didn't know
that exists that's crazy
[Music]
you don't have a chance to open the
secondary oh that's terrifying
didn't rental sponsor jumped like that
oh they should sponsored me yo I'm I'm
Austrian
Red Bull is Austrian
why don't I not have a sponsorship with
Red Bull though
like what the [\h__\h] they sponsor like
everything in Austria they sponsor like
every freaking athlete in Austria
how come they're not sponsoring me
hello red ball hello
[Music]
uh so I'm Austrian and I do things on
the internet I have I have many
subscribers I think you should respond
to me I don't like
uh energy drinks so I will not endorse
your English drinks
um at least not for myself but I don't
think
um you should probably invest in me okay
thanks
all right guys
um I I think I um that was muted so you
couldn't hear it but um I am gonna be
sponsored by Red Bull
hell yeah
we'll get there Japanese members have
been sponsored by Red Bull so
[Music]
and austrians should be able to do it
right
anyway anchor girls here's a kiss for
you
again thank you thank you
thank you thank you for the pinky the
Cardinal Park I really cheered you up
today speaking of watch lungs making
Luma and fauna watch Lord of the Rings
when collab with Fonda was great looking
forward to the Wither attempt and of
course Congress on having two
appearances for those yams
[Music]
I have to practice though
um
yeah I have to practice
dances
so overall gonna be some busy months I
think
in the coming months oh well
[Music]
yeah I can just refill the Red Bull or
something else
hoping to win ticket lottery ah good
luck are you trying out good luck
it must been a year since the kicking
again yeah
so this one
that goes for the next question is
okay
I'm so so far [\h__\h] behind
[Music]
I'm hungry
but
this one doesn't have many super chats I
think so I'll write them
because I [\h__\h] tangent so much can I
put once just not tangent no I can't
take his [\h__\h] Edition language
thank you for two years of my ships
oh you want to become a doctor yo good
luck maybe you can be my doctor please I
think you will take me seriously Anton M
thank you for the race
[Music]
hi this today's
oh my God another birthday but this was
a different day obviously on these days
the same day
I read this before on the same day a
year ago you also fought for the title
of champion you defeated Cynthia with
the power of the Phoenix good luck on
becoming a champion of Paul there too
love you stay safe and don't forget to
grab some revivals
hahaha well I did not end up fighting uh
for the time of champion that day after
all
um but still a funny coincidence because
like I couldn't if I really wanted to if
I really tried but yeah
[Music]
um
I didn't finish for part four after the
Popeyes what
happy birthday
[Music]
around the birds
on this day one year ago you watched me
fight Pokemon
[Music]
she deserves
and wow yeah
thank you for supporting me
[Music]
when you
[Applause]
see
[Music]
happy birthday
I'm even here
you better catch up with this archive if
you're not
open the door
[Music]
foreign
definition
[Music]
thank you
who said he might stop you I'm happy to
eat my words
I mean I thought you meant yourself you
meant the the what's his name Alfred uh
is it Alfred
happy to eat my words good job while
I've been enjoying the Pokemon flavor so
far also Congress and Sparks hitting 5
million and how to tell you hitting two
melons yeah
until you hit 2 million yes they are but
not Alfred
and do you lead into the house is super
close to big muscles yeah so many
Muslims
how many miles Downs yeah also yeah you
underestimated me no no no
underestimating Chihuahua
oh no no no no
unacceptable well thank you
[Music]
yeah I hope for blood gets a milestone
too so please continue streaming for
blood please thank you
[Music]
mp153 Edition mp153
I was driving to have dinner with Papa
parked heading aside Joe the Watson was
really great oh enjoyed it if you ever
want to do Gilmore Girls watching I will
advices in one would be great to see
things to enjoy oh I think I saw you
super chatting your impressions of
watching gamer girls now
eh what do you mean I read this today oh
I mean I guess on stream yeah but but
now you're watching it are you enjoying
it I think it's a very girly show
obviously but
um I also recommend it to recommended
it's Nabi I think she will like it but
um uh please don't force yourself if you
don't like it that much up to episode 5
just for you
I think it's very cute
I've seen most of it with my mom is good
wow
I feel um a little bit
um
relieved hearing that feedback from a
seemingly male person
now I don't feel too stupid camera girls
is honestly legendary yeah my oh
you want to watch it let's react to
advent calendar
day 14.99
it is me
and I just wanted to say
[Music]
Happy New Year two times
she's literally Pentatonix
nice
cute
it would be good background music maybe
I can run it as
Loops I said there we go
I just wanted to say without
introduction would be better
all right all right we're almost done
I'm gonna end it here um thank you thank
you thank you what what seven thank you
soon
foreign
[Music]
if you guys are wondering what I'm
listening to you perhaps should go here
Halloween minister.com
okay apparently I haven't finished
reading super chats from part four is
that true
no I have to
oh no
good luck reminding me next time
I'm reading them and I can't tell oh
why did I why did I break it off why did
I not finish it oh well I'm gonna end it
out uh um
probably not gonna end up actually
cooking am I
yeah I'm not in the mood
but yeah thank you for the fun times
today I'm back and uh tomorrow Pokemon
finish
the fun level yeah that happens
sometimes for some people oh but it will
update eventually probably
um
yeah yeah
you guys when you guys do you have any
leftovers no but I think I have Lazada
hmm
I love you guys thank you
um I'm exhausted but hell yeah thank you
bye-bye and in Germany
[Music]
is there some Pokemon kiwawa fan art
that I haven't used yet
something good
I wonder
bye-bye
[Music]
you're eating Pop-Tarts for dinner I
cannot allow that
that's not okay eat something proper
oh you have to tweet the calendar video
[Music]
foreign
thank you
blood
[Music]
also um go check out that Sparks remix
that I played in the beginning of the
stream
um
d-y-a-k-o
check it out on their channel so they
get a view okay
thank you thank you
[Music]
foreign