[Music]
all right
so we have multiple perspectives yay
[Music]
okay sorry for the delay everyone sorry
happy halloween
[Music]
there's i think there's a little bit
all right so we're here and we have a
halloween special we have some
activities planned uh but for now as you
can see we have some new costumes so i
guess we'll start all the way at cali
jamming out over there and we'll do uh
introductions
you guys are watching yes we were
watching you oh gosh
you're watching me the whole time hey
guys
i have some things to show you
hold on you guys you can change this
[Music]
i don't think you could kill a vampire
with a chest
[Music]
are you good
i'm genuinely i'm worried
she's good
vampires are awesome
for a grim reaper i think
uh obviously i should be the opposite
yeah
that makes sense because you give life
and
yeah
yeah i'm a life giver
taker
has officially become canon
yeah that's what you say right it's real
now
that makes sense that it is a good
person
i just have to fix something really cool
i think it's a lot of people's fantasies
oh i could yeah i can totally understand
that
getting some good close-ups ma'am
yes ma'am
oh oh
oh yeah
wait
wait i swear
[Laughter]
[Music]
behaved
having fun i always have fun with you
guys how about next up we do kiara kiara
self introduction and tell us about your
outfit
i
chose i originally wanted to do so many
other things but i chose to be a vampire
today because today i released my
vampire shankara
yeah it goes like that you're welcome
you have an earworm you warm now by me
yes
dress do i look like a vampire i hope i
do
a cute vampire
yeah my cuteness is blood sucking
oh
[Laughter]
well i turn into a pumpkin it takes a
couple it takes some time
[Music]
some changes too okay
so i expect from you that you're gonna
sing a vampire in your next karaoke
stream
uh
okay
i'll think of that
well i just automatically learn it when
they come out turns into a vampire oh
that's what they know i don't know
all right i'll think about it
i haven't had a chance to listen to the
cover yet but i will 100 listen to it
after the stream and you guys
yeah that's okay i've been setting up
some things but i will listen to it i'm
so excited you guys are releasing so
many covers callie uh also announced the
new song huh coming out tomorrow
today
today oh yeah
yeah it's coming out after the stream
actually
you guys are interested in a race i hope
you guys like it it's not really it's
like a halloween song it was a song that
works for halloween so it's not
necessarily a halloween song but it
works for halloween
[Music]
thank you
all right well i guess
and i was thinking that costume it must
be an orange isn't it um well it is
orange physics
it does
that's it
just kidding
oh
pumpkin witch and i can bring pumpkins
to life
yeah
i guess something nice
actually this outfit um i chose this one
because somebody had drawn this but
actually this is an outfit i wore when i
was a kid i remember like uh there's
like small ame pictures small baby on my
pictures where i'm wearing uh this this
like pumpkin outfit with like a little
witch hat so i really like this outfit
yeah
oh and thank you seafoam for actually
getting dressed
i feel like pumpkin would also match you
because you have the hair to match
should be like a whole pumpkin yeah
yeah
oh the blue pumpkin is that real like a
blue banana
is that a thing it's a thing i never
heard of them
[Music]
hello oh my god help sorry i am mad
scientist
[Music]
yeah that's it
it's really cute yeah it's like yule
like doesn't you'll wear a a doctor's
coat
like a
lab coat by daytime i'm just a normal
student okay
perfect for you
you have some vials here maybe i can
by
[Music]
wait really you don't have it
hold on what
oh i asked for no no
i think they're tight it technically
doesn't count as pants okay they're
tight it's okay
technically yeah
all right how about we do as good as
introduction as you could tell you could
probably tell me
yeah whereas
cameras there we go
[Music]
is
oh yeah technically yeah look at those
yeah
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
want to touch tummy it's so round look
at this around yeah
humans
yeah
good luck and good halloween candy
pictures
oh yeah
you say that now i'm coming for you
after the stream
i love to see like a fight in that
costume like just
fisticuffs
yeah the the the default
wait what is it
oh that it's like the dancing
what is the idol
i don't like not idle but idle you know
oh yeah
oh i want to see like a video of you
doing like the godzilla
so as you guys know this is a costume
party so since it's a party we did
invite some extra guests that are here i
think they should be arriving in the
elevator at some point let's i think
let's go check on them they might be
here already how about we i'm gonna take
the camera with me
[Music]
oh hi
let me switch this
there we go okay let's go
it might be stuck in the elevator the
elevator's been having some maintenance
issues i think there was a maintenance
ahmed that was here
um
that was here uh looking at it so
[Music]
are you guys okay
are you guys all right
guys
all right i'm gonna let you out i have a
master button here i'm letting you guys
out of the elevator
oh god the door stuck i think something
went wrong
i think something went wrong in there
i'm worried because the timeline
fluctuation
oh wait
it's closed again sorry
hello are you guys okay
what happened to you guys what happened
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
oh since you're the head of the branch
that makes sense
she's a big head yes
oh for some reason your mouth isn't
moving that's weird uh-oh
really yeah it should be i think it's
just a problem with my head earlier
my
[Music]
oh it's soft your hairs feel so
okay
[Music]
a giraffe is part of nature so i guess
that makes sense
[Music]
i know
is
[Applause]
wait i can't
[Music]
outside i wanted to get a good shot hold
on i gotta watch something really quick
uh i just gotta check something you guys
do whatever i gotta
say so then i gotta check
something
um
[Music]
right
very nice just like you in the real
world give me that little button
[Music]
what are you is over here
what you doing i was showing everybody
my model oh yeah it's so good i'm glad
okay i thought you're stuck in the death
animation it seems like you fixed it
nice so cute
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh it's like you're petting here
[Music]
[Laughter]
hey kelly's a nurse maybe you can revive
her that'd be funny
oh what's up uh-oh
[Music]
thank you i'll take
it looks comfortable
[Music]
maybe there's a portal under me inside
thank you
all right if if you guys are good with
it oh everyone we can do a tour is
everybody ready to do a tour
okay let's let's start um
let's go this way okay so
if you guys all gather here in the main
reception area we're gonna be doing a
tour you guys ready if you're here for
the museum tour you can nobody's
listening
thank you
we're doing a tour you guys want to do a
tour where i'll get together like a
field trip it's like we have some kids
here
[Music]
thank you
all right everybody we're doing a tour
you guys kiara we're doing a killer cali
we're doing a tour even though you guys
have seen the building before but
all right iris are you stuck in the dead
are you stuck
all right if you guys want to gather
do you guys want to gather over here to
begin the tour
what do you think
okay so
you guys are all listening up
okay okay okay all right so this is uh
pretty much like our terminal here at
the time headquarters as you guys know
cronie over there is the head of the
branch as you can tell um so these are
our time terminals which uh amis the all
bunch of amis run them and uh recently
we did have a zombie outbreak a zombie
ahmed outbreak so we had to close off
this section here but uh i'm hoping we
can uh unclog that soon yeah so zom
zombie on it
and uh we also have a few different uh
reception desks here we do have a small
one like usually i would be here and uh
i would help you guys uh you know if you
had like some issues you know if you
guys
wanted to know what timeline to go to i
could help you with that uh today we
will be traveling to another timeline
and as you guys know council came from
another timeline which was in another
dimension and you guys got all messed up
in the elevator somehow um it has been
having some issues so
all right so i'm broken
as you guys see here we have
concierge as well which is currently
closed as uh it is a holiday
um but we also have the elevator which
you guys have seen awesome awesome tunes
in there don't make me go
we won't be using it today do not press
the second button we'll be using that
later and over here we have the bar
which you guys are welcome to help
yourselves to some drinks if you get
thirsty
um
i'll have to see we might have to make
the intern go get some chocolate i'm
sick
don't press the button no no pressing
the buttons back there
okay so as you guys saw the seating ear
area over here
and now moving into the main lobby over
here is the main lobby we have the
golden yago statue crying over here his
fountain of tears they are salt water we
were thinking about adding some fish but
uh yeah some salt water uh found it in
here
yeah okay fine here we go
and this is the original seating it
happened yeah
yes
am i allowed to take a piece of candy
from the table yeah you can have candy
that's for you guys there's so many pups
and there's uh chips over there on the
table if you guys get hungry
yeah
um oh yeah iris
lollipop
um okay so i guess that's a huge piece
of candy this lobby uh has a lot of
timelines attached but we do have
portals specifically for all of the
small myth members here i'd love to add
some more uh areas for you guys too in
the future that'd be awesome
uh so first up we're gonna go into
cali's portal let's go to the timeline
portal yay
[Music]
i guess cardboard cali has been moved we
used to have a cardboard color here you
guys are welcome to take a seat you can
step up on the stage
a syringe
[Music]
she's got a weapon
take a breather i'm gonna drink some
water really quick you guys just
relax
oh thank you for the candy i'm just
drinking water really quick i'm going to
say
i'm going to try farming
yeah let's go
i'll give you i'll give you candy there
we
go no
i need candy to give to bed that's my
bargaining [\h__\h]
oh
no
[Music]
thank you
okay
how about we go over to the next area
now let's go over to the next portal to
the next portal this way guys
follow me
all right next up we will be going into
the small kiara timeline let's go check
out kiara's portal
i don't think everybody was on board
with us we're leaving some people behind
all right here comes everybody
oh my gosh
this umbrella is cute
[Music]
um
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
watch out
[Music]
to tell you guys a little bit about this
map i forgot to do in the last one but
this is actually uh australia yeah it's
really pretty around this time of year
as you can see the trees have been
changed we have some pumpkins for
decoration and this is like the uh main
town plaza it's really nice kind of
reminds me of like animal crossing or
something that's really cute
it's my first time in australia
[Music]
yeah
with the big snowy
australia
helicopter pumpkin
patch
uh you guys are welcome to uh take as
much candy or uh pumpkins as you want
you can take them with us if you want
all right you guys take whatever you
like we're now going to be moving over
to the next portal
let's go everybody
all right
next up we're gonna skip the auditorium
for now but let's go on into gooda's
portal yay
we're gonna see the ancient ruins of
atlantis
[Music]
is there candy oh yeah there's candy in
the chat
[Music]
can we get some cool i want to get like
some cool screenshots
oh you guys are having a fight i
challenge you
oh yeah
is gonna hurt my
my
really pointy object from the different
dimensions
i think not
[Music]
[Applause]
oh the 360 god damn
[Music]
oh
all right so a little bit about this uh
i believe these are the ancient ruins of
atlantis which we could go back in time
and bring atlantis back in its full
glory if you guys would like to see that
at another time but today this is the
timeline that we are in and it's quite
beautiful here under the water yeah
how deep would you say we are gonna how
how many uh like meters are we down
below the surface
what do you think
[Music]
um don't worry it's just a refraction
yeah sometimes the light reaches some
pretty far deaths maybe
okay
it's magic no it's sci-fi destruction
huh
yeah oh yeah technically
[Music]
all right let's move on to the next
portal i believe we are now going to go
to ina's portal so let's go through the
tunnel yay
come on everybody
[Music]
uh ina you know this way let's see wait
for everybody
all right into inna's portal
[Music]
reena's portal
i think there's some we left this oh
they're coming they're coming all right
let's go into this portal
let's help
let's see
exquisite
a cookie there's a painting
where's kiara
let's look for kiara
was she in here oh
jarrah
come on
oh my bad my batteries ran out oh no
did you i thought you charged
i did i'm trying to charge my my my hip
uh oh okay it still works with just the
feet but uh we can always bring it back
later yeah all right okay
we're going into inaudible
[Music]
and i cannot touch your multi-tasker
uh
[Music]
oh as you can see the uh trees outside
are also changing colors for fall
uh-oh
[Applause]
[Music]
oh it's this one
i'm not sure what that one does ina
would know
it looks like soda pops
yeah i'll take that
all the lines
oh it made a new flip holy [\h__\h] i can't
wait
she's like an upper bachelor's perpetual
promotion
[Music]
oh god it's spreading it
it's spreading the flip syndrome is oh
my god
[Music]
is
oh
all right just to tell you guys about
this area i believe this is inna's
retreat uh a cabin in the woods with
inna's uh lab also here nice relaxing
tea area as well as some nice open
windows with a bookshelf and of course
some painting equipment as you guys can
see up here these uh canvases that is
painted are actually from her first uh
how do you say the game pass apart out i
don't know how to say it properly
this is her first from her first stream
of that yeah yeah a nice little easter
egg there
look at the camera
oh yeah
[Music]
all right everybody we're now gonna go
over to the last portal which is the
small ami portal in the desert oh god
i've fallen out of the map don't worry
guys i'm fine
okay well i teleported here fast
don't worry we'll get there i saw
everything from the bottom i don't think
you guys saw that
all right yeah thank you guys for coming
on over you guys can move on over to the
small ami portal
we do have to go through the reception
area to get there
do not press any buttons on the way
there please
buttons are very sensitive the way the
pumpkin you gotta go the dinosaurs
motion sick
sorry
you could take a seat
all right here we are
all right who are we missing cali coming
santa's here
i'm sweating the eternal day
oh yeah so uh this is uh the desert uh
some small ames uh end up here
after some time maybe some crimes
you guys could have a syringe battle
we can you know
oh
[Music]
i didn't know that this was a deadly
concoction it was an accident
and we have the antidote we have the
antidote
injector
all right
is it working
[Laughter]
[Music]
lose it for a while yeah just sit just
relax
we're gonna we're gonna take a break and
sit down in a little bit when we go to
the next area
um oh yeah okay yeah just to tell you
guys a little bit about this area this
is where some small amis come to rest
whether it's due to
time or crimes uh it's a bit of a prison
it's a bit of a resting place it's a bit
of everything for each amex
um
so
we're gonna go back to the reception
area in front of the elevator and we're
gonna have a little chit chat really
quick yes
okay
all right i got this one we're gonna go
sit down
[Music]
uh we're just going to wait here for a
second
everybody's here
[Music]
okay
attention everybody we will now begin
the second portion of the field trip as
today is halloween so we have some
spooky activities planned and we are now
going to go into the spooky halloween
timeline
iris what the hell
all right so if you guys would please
press the second button here the instant
teleport button let's go
[Music]
it was really bad
now just as a rule do not enter the maze
at the moment please do not enter the
maze you guys are welcome to explore
this area or this area to your right and
left that's you iris
[Music]
that was even more instant than instant
noodles
well it is instant teleport
everybody's here right everybody made it
last dream i couldn't make it i couldn't
make it was too much
oh yes we have pumpkins
[Music]
[Applause]
but a pumpkin
[Music]
shaving off
cute all right so i'll uh we're gonna do
a little tour of this area let's start
over here first
um i actually believe this might be what
caused
your guys's
uh
deformities of sorts
i think there's been some
messing around going on here
uh but as you can see there's actually a
spot for each council remember there's
we have the time
this is for crony oh maybe
brownies
yeah that sounds tasty
oh you eat those no i think there's base
let's see
uh santa sleeping come again oh
[Music]
i think her vampire powers have been
activated
[Music]
so i thought i thought it'd be cool
if we got some
[Music]
maybe we could get some screenshots like
callie like with her chainsaw maybe
cutting sand in half or something i
don't know
that's a great idea i like that it's
time to get over here
yeah let's take some screenshots
[Music]
i got to do my own sound effects
[Applause]
i'm beginning i feel like a rat god
right god
[Music]
this is like the setting for my music
videos
[Music]
oh
ice creams
[Music]
[Laughter]
all right everybody we can move on over
to the other side over here if you guys
want to check out the other section
follow me
let's go
oh
and we also have the yago the great
yellow pumpkin
[Music]
oh no
i've never played this before and i
don't i want to keep it that way
oh you guys are welcome to take a seat
we do have chairs scattered all around
this area if you'd like to sit let's
take a look though
and we also have this mirror i'm gonna
trigger
now you guys can see yourselves if you
want to take some
[Music]
i'm going to set the camera to be world
view one second challenge
she has nothing to do with this
spirits
[Music]
from the mario franchise huh all right
let's go what's your favorite
put you
[Music]
all right if you guys want to all take a
seat i thought it'd be fun to tell
cover my ears no all right if you guys
wanna i'll take a seat
everybody take a seat uh in the chairs
oh my god what was that
can i ask you guys to please take a seat
in the couch or one of the chairs we
have a rocking chair over here
uh there should be a chair for everybody
i think oh let me zoom out a little bit
on the camera sandwich
yes
in between in a sandwich everywhere oh
my god
we gotta put ourselves
[Music]
a little bit closer
mm-hmm
[Music]
yeah i was thinking we could tell some
ghost stories but i don't think we have
anything um there's a magnifying glass
that we can use but it's in the other
map and pretty you're watching
[Music]
this
wait let me make sure everybody is
[Music]
all right if you guys could take a seat
please you guys i like you too i see it
could you guys sit down with the going
ghost stories
[Music]
[Applause]
all right everybody take a seat you guys
sit down on the couch or in the chair
uh there's also a seat
here
seats
you can stand if you like especially
since chairs don't really work well for
you iris there's a chair here um
yeah you can sit down here then yeah it
sounds like a ghost all right you know
there's a chair there too
i could sit uh i guess i'll sit here
chilling honda's head is so wide that
it's just like cutting in between
everyone
why are you wrong
quite funny
it's like my mom's so fat do you fight
with your neck like other giraffes like
yeah
[Music]
this
has seen things
[Music]
[Applause]
is like grinding into me oh no i can't
start
camera
i'm being sliced into people i'm gonna
say cronie
okay all right
um okay everybody welcome to the spooky
spooky timeline as you can see we have a
big yago here and we could uh actually
this ouija board is used to talk to the
great spirit of yago but unfortunately
it seems like we've misplaced a little
planchette i believe it's called uh so
it's not here but
i thought instead of talking to the
spirits we could tell some ghost stories
do you guys know any ghost stories
anybody
have you ever seen a ghost before
yeah you want to hear the story yeah i
want to hear
yes
okay once i was driving down a winding
dark road
and i saw a lady and she had no face oh
so i hit her and she turned into a ghost
what
i thought you were supposed to be like
the protectors of humans
turned and then you're talking about why
she had no
faith yeah
yeah sometimes in the dark like faces
disappear yeah
are we sure
yeah do you have any
[Music]
i was also in the car i wasn't driving
enough because i can't reach the pedals
oh and uh i think it was with my mom we
were coming home from somewhere it was
really really dark and then all of a
sudden across the road there was this
like mist
of some sort that had no beginning and
end it was just in the center of the
road and we drove right through it and
we tried really hard
to will you ever see something and it it
takes you by such surprise that it
leaves you spaceless for a little while
yes
well like that that's what happened it
was it was it was kind of genuine fear
for a second uh but we're trying to
think of what it could have been and
there's no way it could have been
smoke right because smoke
doesn't you would have seen it fizzle or
how would it have traveled out into the
road like that without any
well how would it have lived that long
you know it was really scary and i don't
know how to just put in it or i don't
have any other way to
explain what it could have been
that is scary that's spooky
like a kind of spooky story but it's
like from a thing it's like a book i'm
not gonna read it but like i can recount
it to you
oh yeah tell us tell us like are we
allowed to do that you get in trouble i
think it's okay
change some details all right yeah
okay gotcha
so basically here's how it goes
sorry
here's how are you okay kiara
i looked at the chat for one second i
just had to left
all right
so
there's this girl right
and she's at a gas station
she's filling up the gas in a car it's
just a normal day getting off of work
you know the usual
and then she decides it's time to go
home as any other sane human would you
go to work you go to home just a typical
day
right
so she finishes getting the gas in her
car
well settles down in her little seat
gets ready to drive away yeah i hear it
too it gets ready to drive away
i don't know
i hear it coming from your area it's
fixed she gets what she takes a little
seat gets ready to drive away and she
heads off down
excuse me
i'm sorry
you're good you're fine you're fine
[Laughter]
[Music]
musty and spooky road and she's on like
a countryside roads there's no one
around until she realizes that she's
being followed stop oh my god no way
someone is following her you know
someone is following her yeah that's
right there's a car that's hot on her
tail and it's been following her in fact
for a while she realizes that it's been
following them
ever since the gas station oh my god and
what's your weirder about this car
yeah that's right if you remember the
gas station there was a dude and he
followed followed there's a car there's
a vision in your head now there's
another car there's one car here there's
a car here and they're going down the
road and it's dark outside and then the
car behind her this innocent victim
starts flashing his lights flash flash
flash over and over again over and over
again oh man body motions for flash what
what could it mean
she doesn't know but i started
another 30 minutes left to drive all the
way home so she keeps driving and the
the dude just keeps flashing the lights
flash flash flash what does it mean
i don't know
she gets very scared and decides i need
to call the police i need to call them
so they'll be ready when i get to my
house this dude's gonna kill me he's
gonna jump out of his car and and then
and then hold on i got i got my effect
my special effect he's gonna come out of
the car
and and stabby stabs
no it's too scared of that happening
right
not you can stab with a chainsaw yeah
so so she decides she didn't just beat
him with the car like you know beep beep
oh no she did she gets pretty mad at him
but he like doesn't care and so and so
she keeps going and he keeps flashing
eventually she gets home she runs out of
her car the police are there they all
pull up and she runs out of her car and
the guy pulls up in his car
and he comes out and he's just a normal
dude
and he says ma'am are you okay she says
what are you talking about
my man says
there's a dude in the back seat of your
car
[Music]
oh
does anybody else
does anybody else know a ghost story
oh we'll do sana and then cronies
sana do you have a ghost story well i
guess i guess it's a tree story it's
about living in space australia oh okay
do you have any do you have any sort of
scary bug stories
hugs oh okay that i mean that counts
you're scared yeah
hey
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
encounters um [\h__\h] counties
i was thinking you would have some as
well
anyway uh i did but they're not like
scary i mean they're scary it's like
this that song that's like my life
um you accidentally you accidentally
step step on the floor and you
accidentally step on the center feet
on a slug
like
a furry spider like a furry spider
oh
that's
[Music]
anyone saw it i can
my
bedroom
and then
um i had i was doing something but i had
correct vision into my bedroom
and then i was just staring at the
ground and then suddenly out of nowhere
a huge like black fighter it crawled
under my bed and then
i didn't do anything
you just left it there do anything
behind it that is scary i never found it
oh god yeah it was scary
it disappeared
you know what it went inside your
because it's inside you there's no other
way to get it
oh yeah i feel like that's bs they do
say that yeah this must be bs i don't i
do know that we probably definitely
swallow some ads without
[Music]
yeah i'm only showing does anybody else
have a scary story
yeah i did
yeah you got a scary story
juicy meat um
my my
chickens
oh okay i was um
i was living in japan until a while ago
and um i i moved after after joining
whole life uh uh i moved into a big big
house
but the house was very very
uh
old
it was that when you walked on the wood
it would make sounds like
wait wait
wait
oh no oh spooky yeah so it was really
really old that it had a lot of
it had a lot of issues to it but well it
was a big two-story house all to myself
so i was like i'm just gonna try my best
to ignore that that it's uh looking
really old so
the first night arrives and
i'm i'm like yeah i got this whole house
to myself and i was trying to chill but
i was hearing noises
from the ceiling it was like
[Laughter]
i immediately contacted my my landlord
and he was like yeah there
there might be some history of ghosts in
this house but please don't worry about
it we'll send you some ghost
exterminators what
a few days
a few days later and the the
ghostbusters came by and all those days
i i heard the ghosts like continuously
not only in the night but also during
the day and was kind of freaking me out
because i was also trying to stream but
it was i was hearing it on the first
floor and on the second floor and on the
in the side of the walls and the bottom
and on the top everywhere so
uh the ghost extremely is they came and
they looked into the ceiling and they
they saw
the ghosts they saw the goal really they
did they said that it's like they saw
like about like
three ghosts three ghosting no no no go
[Music]
and go actually had ghost poison with
them
and they pushed that crazy ass that's
right girl they got the saltiness they
put that the they put the ghost poison
in the ceiling and then they closed it
and they they were like okay kiara you
call us and tell us call the
ghostbusters and tell us how the poison
worked
and then a few days later i did start
hearing less
but it was still oh a little bit a
little bit
so i called again and i was like yo
ghostbusters i'm calling you because who
who else would i call
right
girl so they say all right you're still
here exactly
[Music]
they said they were gonna come back and
they opened the ceiling again and they
looked inside and they found the ghost
of two ghosts the ghosts the two ghosts
oh
god
[Music]
apparently those two ghosts of the
ghosts where um the parent ghosts of the
ghosts that survived uh and it was weird
because they added they kept on trying
to add poison for the last surviving
ghost but it seemed like that ghost has
started to form some kind of immunity
and uh we tried many times but it didn't
didn't work and then one time for
example i was sick
with the door open because i had it it
was like such a tiny idol meeting room
that it's like almost impossible to
close the door and i saw it again
oh
my god
the ghost like ate your food once
it ate your food
that's terrific i don't know if you've
heard of it but ghosts are apparently um
uh uh not they don't like to be tougher
because they will kill them
so in the end i decided to accept the
fact that i'm living with a ghost and
actually we're best friends now and the
ghost's name is casper
[Music]
i think crony said she had a ghost story
oh my god
[Music]
does anybody know any chance to exercise
her
spirit begun
i know
[Music]
okay so the ghosts are in too much
control okay good actually a little bit
it might help um purge the ghost if you
want to play on desktop that's okay too
because i know you're feeling a little
sick so if you want i will reinvite you
okay if you're feeling too sick
okay
all right okay
we'll wait for you it should be really
easy just get comfy yeah
we need to purge the spirits from her
just kept pumping
sit down relax
[Music]
maybe we should go to the summoning
circle to summon her
a shark
there's a baby
[Music]
why is the rat pretending to be like an
owl
why are you pretending
[Music]
oh
yeah she can totally hear her
[Music]
what
my precious
[Music]
yes i'm kneeling at the moment
you're comfortable i'm just wanting to
make sure that you're not
prone is floating also possessed by a
ghost
why is everyone getting possessed we are
in a spooky area
[Music]
you know yeah i play dead you guys want
to hear another story
i guess yes
yeah
[Music]
have you guys heard the story of the
crunch bird
crunch my grandfather told me the story
of the crunch bird long ago yeah i
remember it was an old people my
grandfather told him
i know it sounds like that right like
kfc right exactly like you can imagine a
big scary phoenix yeah so basically the
crunch bird my grandfather told me this
story it's been passed down in reaper
legends for generations so basically
there's this couple and they decide that
they want to have a pet right they
decide it's finally time to get
themselves um a pet of their own because
you know they've been living alone can't
have kids that kind of thing so uh so
they've decided okay we're gonna go you
know off to the pet shop so the
husband's really busy he's working and
so he tells his wife go ahead and get us
a pet he doesn't care what it is he says
whatever is fine right so the wife goes
to the pet store and uh is kind of
talking with the pet clerk and she's
like i wonder what would be good you
know a dog a cat hamster all very cute
but
hear me out how about a bird and so the
shop clear because all right i got some
birds i'll show you some birds takes her
to the back starts showing other birds
and she's like oh these are all very
fine birds but what's that one in the
back there's this big cage in the back
it's got this huge foul beast of a
creature inside of it he says oh that's
the crunch that thing's way too
dangerous yeah crunch bird is what it's
called you can call it whatever you want
but i call it the crunch bird and she
says well why do you call it the crunch
bird he's like do you really want to
know she says
yeah i really want to know he's like do
you really want to know she's like yeah
i really want to know show me the bird
really really no
exactly
[Music]
he takes the bird from the cage
all right and and he says crunch bird
take people and the crunch bird goes
and it destroys the table
just messes and destroys it all right
exactly that's why it's called crush
bird iris i can see your pantsuit all
right
um
so next he says
next he says crunch bird crushed bird
chair the crunch bird goes
and it destroys the chair
all right so now the chair is destroyed
and so the wife says you know what this
is a dangerous animal but i think it's
got i think it's got potential you know
it's got like
it's different you know it's not just
like your run of the mil usual uh pet
and i think my husband might like this
exactly it's got that potential real
special potential try saying that ten
times fast real special pet potential
special pet it's probably not that hard
so so she says you know what fine i'll
take the crunch bird and um and he he
they do the exchange she gives them the
money he gives the bird right she takes
the bird back home sets up the cage gets
it all nice for her husband to come back
home
now husband walks through the door and
he sees this foul beast in the corner
and he says what the f word is that
can't say that f we have children
watching possibly so she says let me
show you she opens the door lets the
crunch bird out
and she and he says what can you tell me
what on earth is this thing she says oh
it's a crunch bird he says crunch bird
my ass
[Music]
at the window for a little bit that's
okay i'm glad you're back into the storm
[Music]
welcome back
we're talking about a bird it's the
crunch bird just don't worry about it
[Music]
i thought cronie had a spooky story do
you have one cronie i want to hear
cronies oh can you sit in the rocking
chair when you tell us sit in the rocky
chair
yeah yeah yeah sit in the rocking but
not dead
yeah but not dead there we go yeah there
we go okay
tell us the story cody
oh crony is that a story
[Music]
it's actually not that good
beautiful this
is i've experienced
oh no
so a family member and i were just you
know chilling out in our room and at
exactly 12 a.m uh
the phone started ringing so i said oh
wow
why would friends call you at this hour
that's really disrespectful
and then
and then she looked at me and said that
that's not my ringtone
and
the the song that was playing uh was
pretty much all about
uh like i've been everywhere searching
for you
where have you been because i see you
like
are you hiding somewhere in the crowd
and
and then we got kind of creeped out we
uh picked up the phone
and
it stopped playing and then suddenly at
every night
exactly at 12
that same ringtone was happening
and that was that was not the ringtone
that she said and later on she decided
to delete the song
from her phone
and it still kept playing
and
and then we had some
interesting events taking place such as
how when i was all alone in the house i
would hear
a piano key
a single
oh
just going ding ding and
i would go and check it out nobody's
there or
i'd be all alone in my room and my dog
uh who's in the same room would
look at whatever's at the end of the
hallway
and i keep trying to call their call ty
mutt's name and
they won't
they won't turn their head it's fixated
at whatever is at the end of the hallway
everything was pitch black
yeah
um
that that phone kept ringing
and maybe something about that house was
weird
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
and that same family member had
some other experience where
they would have nightmares
about how they can't move but they would
be in a fire where they would get shot
so a lot of nightmares every single day
hey that can't be a prank
or sometimes
a woman like crawling over the ceiling
really fast just to look at
[Music]
everything that's on the ceiling is
haunted
yeah like development i believe like a
ceiling fan
yeah
that was when she was living alone and
when she decided to live with
her family again
this time she couldn't move again in the
dream
but
uh at her bedside she saw
a woman with all her face covered
and
[Music]
and you know with the hair and
everything and she said oh you know what
i see that you're with your family now
and
because of then
i won't bother you again
i hope you haven't talked to you like
that oh
yeah yeah
yeah after that she never had those
dreams where she's paralyzed in her
sleep oh that's good she's lonely
she's scary that's yeah she's
demon
[Music]
sleep
paralysis
take the chair
oh does anybody else have another story
they could sit in the chair
but
my brain is dead right now
[Music]
thank you
all right well
if that's all we have for scary stories
we can now move on to the next activity
so if you guys listen up
you guys listen up i'm gonna tell you
about the next activity um yes ma'am the
next activity is a maze
so
uh we're going to split into groups and
the senpai's will be scaring the koh
hais so the way it's going to work is
we're going to have group a and group b
so if group a is going to be canceled
you guys just step on over here for a
moment all the way over here to the left
or to your right
thank you and we have miss and iris over
here uh
yeah but she's your guys's senpai
yes
the way this is gonna work is um i'm
gonna send you guys council don't go
into the maze yet but i want you guys to
go all the way over there to the other
side um where the summoning circle is
and if you guys could wait over there
uh that'd be great thank you guys thank
you guys i will come get you in a little
bit
and then face it face away from
we'll figure that out
okay so let's move over here towards the
end so they can't hear us you guys come
over here
this purple is this hold on let me yeah
i'm gonna die
one of their demise oh my god let me try
to different people
i'm sorry i didn't mean to do that be
terrifying are we also going to go
through the maze too yeah so we're going
to switch um but uh so uh you guys if
you go to your avatars that you can
select you have a few different options
you have two different options um of
what you can be you guys are going to be
monsters and you're going to hide in the
maze
as they enter in and try to spook them
just don't go too far into the maze we
don't want you to complete it just pick
a corner once you get in there and then
you can surprise them there are some
little hidden alcoves in the maze as
well that you guys can um you mean like
this yes
i like that oh my gosh
all right you guys have some options
i want to be shark
not anything in public just the two that
you have so you have to pick between um
so you could be a frog or a shark look
at this oh i gotta recalibrate that is
disturbing a predator apex
if you guys could just stay here uh
momentarily do not go past up the bridge
okay
all right you guys stay here okay don't
don't follow me just uh stay here
momentarily i'm gonna go check on cancer
really quick oh god and knock them [\h__\h]
down
all right
if you guys
hello everybody again if you guys could
just face the uh gravestone over there
face the gravestone and uh do not look
it's not it's to not spoil you guys okay
i will come back back and get you
i can die
[Music]
all right now
we are now we are now ready to enter
into the map like i said in the maze
don't go too far just pick a corner pick
a corridor and uh try not to go too far
into the maze and we can get you out
easily when it's your guys's turn to
switch okay you guys are there to scare
them so you know use your scary voices
so okay we're gonna go
uh
you can explore the maze but not too
deep okay
don't go past the uh i guess we'll say
the black section don't go past the
black section you guys will see what i
mean
[Music]
and then we just enter in here
okay wait we're missing okay
good good good okay you guys don't don't
go past the dark part don't go past the
black section okay
okay all right i'm going to give you
guys if you guys can hear me i'm going
to give you 30 seconds and then i'm
going to release them into the maze
all right one two three four five six
seven eight nine 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17
18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25 26 27 28 29 30.
all right you guys the maze is now ready
for you to explore you guys can turn
around and uh
we can get going um yes no no i went to
an i know meeting oh okay okay we'll
wait no worries yeah yeah i still can't
say anything you're so big i'm gonna um
i'll tell you guys in discord when to go
okay just give me one moment and um
okay
if you guys if movement is not ready but
oh she's back
all right all right all right just wait
uh i will tell you guys in discord when
to go into the maze okay
i'm gonna go hide too in an area
spoilers if you guys are watching uh
it's just ahmed coming through ame
coming through
uh ame coming through
mommy coming through
[Music]
all right let's wait
okay i'm gonna wait here for everybody
wait here in this corner all right now
we'll wait here there's not much uh you
guys definitely go check out the others
perspectives because um yeah they're
gonna be playing the mace okay let me
tell them what that they're ready one
second
all right council uh you guys can go
ahead and enter the maze
i hope they heard that
oh
i'm gonna take a break while we wait for
them
maybe it's not that scary but at least
i'm having fun
see who the first one through will be
hello
all right it might be coming soon i
gotta look spooky
i just like hearing them
oh my god
hey wait a minute
because you're a black shadow i can't
tell if you're naked
no i'm a scary monster all right um
let me see if you want to get past
[Music]
to show you myself
come on come here
all right
maybe if i put my scary voice on
oh i can't use my scary voice i forgot
i'm using a different microphone
oh
[Music]
we're
if you guys have seen a council member
you may now exit the maze you guys
council members may now exit the maze oh
god
do not go into the mausoleum
[Music]
there she goes
i don't know how to get back here
[Music]
oh you're not supposed to say who you
are you're supposed to say ah
there you go
[Music]
shark gang myth please go back the way
you came and exit the maze yes
what do we do
miss get out go deeper in the maze i'm
gonna get lost cali
i think
this cali defined herself in discord so
[Music]
nobody made it to the end of the maze
they were so close
council there's still more of the maze
you guys can uh
keep going
let's
go
and iris
[Music]
oh my god
where are you
guys
[Music]
iris you may take the exit
oh okay go back to the vicky and then
you guys can continue on into the
haunted house
you guys can go in
a sound change is here what are you
uh i'm a frogs
[Music]
all right uh who is this
tiara and cali follow me
follow me okay
and then uh miss and iris you guys can
follow me this way
okay
uh so i think this is a shortcut so you
guys go back to the beginning yeah and
i'll i'll meet you guys
yeah wait in here yeah go on
um
looks so pretty
[Music]
i'm
hey which way do you guys want to go
this way or this way
oh maybe this
is what do you see
you good i don't see anything
what what do you mean
is that what you saw
wait where
if you guys want to exit it can go this
way
wait wait there's something
um
do you like it
come here
[Music]
i'm here to escort you back
oh
we could go this way i think crony
and fauna know the way on the other side
now
you guys follow the footsteps
i think you guys went the wrong way no
it's this way wait
wait
oh oh
all right this way this way if you guys
follow the sign okay
this will take you back to the beginning
it doesn't really work yes
what if we're looking at the other side
um nothing happens i think
[Music]
everybody's back okay we're gonna split
up in groups again but this time
opposite so uh if council could go to
the mirror area
and uh yeah
we're just gonna do a quick one doing
what she was doing
it was worth it
[Laughter]
i'm gonna kick you if you don't wake up
[Music]
if you uh the rest of council can go
over here in this area with the mirror
my boss
you guys could gather over here
yeah yes
okay
i think it's iris uh i will tell them
[Music]
we have the summoner
foreign
[Music]
okay okay if i can just get your
attention for one moment uh iris
if you could go into your ui settings
and turn off name plates if you guys
don't if it's only for inna and iris
because you guys are streaming it's
already off oh okay you know your names
are off too yeah yeah it's already okay
okay i don't know ask me to tell you
guys okay now you guys switch back to
your normal avatars please
[Music]
there's no mirror here but you uh i
guess you could go over there really
quickly if you'd like to recalibrate
there we go there she is
okay she's back
oh wait they left us behind oh uh noah
callie just went kylie just won
nope yeah i'm sorry kelly just went
somewhere yeah she'll be back
all right uh you guys stay here and face
uh the crony grave and i will come back
and get you when we're ready
all
right all right face the cronie grape
when you get over there callie
all right you guys can now change into
the avatars that you guys have the
monsters that you have
oh
yeah and you guys now it's your turn to
try to spook them yeah you guys have
monsters too
oh okay i don't know
oh you can show it now it's okay
oh okay um
well i'll hide it
i'm i don't see myself
yeah that one's pretty dark
yeah yes
yes
oh i like this one oh it's really dark
here but if you stand by the light here
yeah
oh fake
face me oh god it looks
like they're cute
nice
yeah
[Music]
all right just wait one second um okay
let me make sure that there they're i'll
be right back do you guys wait here
they're all facing okay
all right shh
you guys froze so quiet
all right you guys got a chance this
mouse doesn't have a tail
this house just looks like a really
loose one oh my gosh the mouse does have
nipples
no it doesn't it doesn't have no there's
no nipples
no it don't know
[Laughter]
come on you guys we can go into the maze
now and just you know hide wherever you
like okay
okay
i'll give you guys 30 seconds and i'm
going to send them in okay
one two three
four five six seven eight
nine
and 11
12 13 14
thank you all right oh my god
we're now ready you guys can uh come
with me and enter the maze and get all
the way to the end okay
he's good out here yeah okay all right
enjoy
yes yes
go all the way to the end you guys
okay cool let's do it where it is
it's stuck wait where is
bye
[Music]
maybe there is one here
oh my god where am i uh
[Music]
i have a crazy laugh but i'm just too
shy to do it it's okay it'll sound
awesome i bet okay i believe in you okay
[Music]
oh my god
yeah no problem
yeah i got it i got it all right
here we go
[Music]
it's you guys
have you not seen like all the
documentaries that was just uh just a
myth bro
you gotta you gotta check out those
documents
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you thank you for
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
what about you you should have fun too
um
[Music]
i'm going with you guys i'm waiting for
you guys to go forward
[Music]
come here it's just come
here i can't take it i can't jump
anymore
i'm so scared what are we doing oh no my
battery
[Music]
oh my god is this all movies movies
this is my tiara this way
kiara you gotta come to the end it's
almost over kiara come back come on come
back let's go to the end you have to
come to the end
follow me the end yeah yeah it's not
scary try again i already got a couple
of licenses
pass the berries
[Music]
is she wants your sacrifice of a big red
heart
a big red heart
red heart biggest red heart
what is that pineapple oh we can give
her a heart oh yeah give her your hearts
i want to do that come on
[Music]
red hearts
i'll give her my bigger heart here you
go for you i can all subscribe
um
[Music]
come here
oh
oh my
come give me a kiss
[Music]
oh my gosh
right up to my face
with the mushrooms
[Music]
oh
if you guys would like to exit the maze
the exit can be found here
if you guys would like to exit over here
cali mushrooms i can't tell you guys
apart yeah
you guys can change back to
yes
you guys can change back now
by the way
yeah all right come on the exits this
way
[Music]
this way
freedom you guys can follow the blood
steps to the exit you guys can follow
the blood steps to the exit
[Music]
look there's something above us oh yeah
i can't see it it's gone
oh it's because the camera is hold on
let me fix it
okay
all right do it again
oh there you are
oh no it's not hold on one more hold on
wait no yes
oh god
[Music]
wait has everybody let me just make sure
everybody's exited the maze everybody's
out nobody's stuck in the maze right
nobody's stuck here anybody stuck in the
maze nobody's stuck okay nobody's stuck
oh big takodachi
nobody's stuck in the maze
nobody's stuck here nobody's in the maze
okay good
okay now it's time is everybody back let
me do a head count you guys can switch
off being mushrooms now
i know
no that is actually pretty scary
all right one two three four five six
seven eight nine ten
all right everybody's here
i do have an announcement for you guys
if y'all switch back
yes we have a special premiere that we
are going to be watching in the
auditorium and we're going to go back
there now
uh so if you guys if you guys could
follow me and switch back to your normal
avatars you guys can press the button
here on the gate
let's go let's go come on let's go okay
everybody's here everybody's going
all
[Music]
all right is everybody here let's do a
head count one two
[Music]
is everybody here everybody's here right
one two three four five six seven
okay i think we're all here if you guys
could follow me into the auditorium do
not press any buttons in the auditorium
please and thank you
no buttons
you guys yeah
you guys are welcome to grab as many
props as you like
[Music]
no idea how this looks like
all right
now i think originally i'll wait till
everybody's here i'll get up on the
stage really quick to make a quick
announcement
all right oh [\h__\h] i fell off the stage
no oh you guys are welcome to take a
seat you can stand if you like um okay
so originally we were gonna have some
performances but uh it looks like it
didn't work out in time if anybody does
want to perform now is your chance you
could do show and tell you maybe you
want to show us you can juggle or maybe
you want to sing an acapella tune does
anybody want to come up anybody any
volunteers
no volunteers stage fright i'm okay okay
well we do have uh for chat and for you
guys here in the crowd we have a special
music video premiere for
a myth original song
that's right a myth original song
yeah and we're gonna watch it together
here
in uh
here and uh so if you guys want to get a
good view a good seat now's a good time
i'm gonna turn on the back screen
[Music]
it's a well-kept secret
all right if you guys are ready you guys
are all ready we're getting we might
watch it a few times all right chat you
guys ready
all right i'm going to start the movie
all right
here we go
oh then any second
let me highlight the button
there we go
[Music]
he's waiting in the closet tonight
is
[Music]
you're terrified
hungry dinosaur just one tiny bite
[Music]
ladies
[Applause]
[Music]
happy
myth halloween treat i just want to say
quickly that that video will premiere um
it will premiere on my channel so you
guys after the stream if you want to
rewatch it you can go there and rewatch
it as many times as you'd like and uh
yeah big shout out to cali who wrote the
lyrics callie wrote the lyrics uh farah
wrote the music and also kanaroo the
music video animator made such good use
of everybody's models made by seafoam
hasksoff and also twilight 3d it's so
awesome so many people worked on it so
thank you everybody that worked on it
thank you so much and thank you guys for
watching with us and experiencing it
with us thank you
yeah
[Music]
do you guys maybe maybe we should watch
it one more time
one more time you guys want to watch it
again
okay one more time
one more
i'm trying to press the button i can't
reach it hold on
all right here we go again round two
[Music]
[Applause]
tonight no
way you a fright trick-or-treater
[Music]
is
oh
[Music]
is
i am a hungry
[Music]
[Applause]
watch it again
[Music]
thank you everybody thank you all the
people who worked on it too cali with
the amazing lyrics yeah it gets stuck
it's been stuck in all of our heads for
like the past
all right so we are reaching the end of
the stream but i have some i have one
last activity planned um if you guys
want to follow me to the reception area
let's go
yeah let's take some pictures together
i just noticed their mic
okay
here yeah
[Music]
hi
all right now just like a real party
we're gonna jam out a little bit and
then we'll say goodbye to everybody you
guys i'd love to see some cool
screenshots so dance together waltz
together hold each other's hands hug
each other whatever you want to do dance
on the tables dance on the chairs all
right let's get this party started we
press the button
[Music]
um
oh is somebody gonna drop a beat
we get
am i dancing you're dancing you're
dancing
sort of yeah
[Music]
i just want to say thank you guys for
watching thank you council and iris for
attending in myth 2 for putting in the
extra vr
thank you everybody
hold on let me pin the i want to join
you guys hold on i'm gonna pin it here
[Music]
i'm trying to fix it
i'm just like
that work yes oh it works okay now i can
join you guys i just need to i fail
[Music]
one more time i think this song will
play again
there we go i don't know how to get up
there how'd you guys get up there
oh i see don't jump
okay
where can i go or not anybody yay oh it
fell off the scary oh my god i can see
the aisles
i don't want to see it here yeah i keep
jumping on it
wait
there's so many people
his head is so like
baby
i'm here i'm here
yeah
oh my god
all right thank you guys for watching
the halloween stream i hope you guys
have a safe fun halloween yay
happy halloween
thank you guys for watching
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you for watching
give me a second
[Music]
my
you