[Music]
so
hello
do you also wait this is so weird what's
going on
i feel like my my left ear i feel like
my left ear is kind of
weird
[Music]
let me put the logo there
today is minecraft day
hell yeah i just woke up
i'm still tired i want to go back to bed
no thank you for the pink super job
what
if a powerful god cursed callie with
eternal sleep
and the only way to save him was a spell
that would also make it so that piccolo
could never speak again
would you accept that callie was lost to
you or would you save callie by hurting
piccolo
i will not answer that question i will
not answer that question you cannot put
me in such a situation
to make such a decision no
but thank you for the pinky
all right everyone let's turn on some
music we
first of all don't take the title to
literal
uh it's not supposed to be
taken literally i
just met like because last time we
didn't really get lost but
um i made this home safely and i didn't
lose anything
so today i want to
go back to okinawa i think
i think it's okinawa where i want to go
by the way maybe let's take a saddle
in case we find a horse again or a
donkey
yeah i remember there was a donkey
before
do you guys you guys hear the music
right is it too loud
thank you for the membership
music is okay a little little loud but
good enough okay
okay okay um well so what will we bring
we have established a safe path
to where i want to go at least like in
never outside not really and
so oh wait okay so we don't we let's
let's
bring back the
the rails wow looking beautiful today
wonderful although i mean it's still
kind of tiny it's like a messier
uh wait uh here i don't need the rails
anymore where are they again
here oh it added to
i mean i i watched your stream so i know
that this is untouchable
can't touch this damn dad and them found
them concept
it
[Music]
and i'll keep
i'll keep we need some
torches yeah very desperately we need
some torches
let's see if i i feel like i have like
no
yeah no almost almost no coal
but there you go i found some uh
and you you may take this and this
and as always i'm all over the place i
should be more organized like inna
nina's like chests are so organized
this is almost breaking but i'll take it
anyway
so organization
you're organizing your own way oh well
thank you
the crossbow yeah let's take it with us
as well oh we have a lot of sticks hey
a fan snow we don't need the fence we
don't need the gun powder
we can bring cooked chicken we don't
need the lever we don't need this
we definitely don't need the rotten
flesh we don't need those
eggs actually you know what i bring
those eggs
i'll bring them i need more food
oh
i know where food is hehe
i know where to find my food
many sticks i need a lot of hello
good morning are you working are you
working properly
huh yes
say
[Music]
are you working wake up
okay i saw some food here oh so much
though
oh yeah do we need all of it
probably not but let's bring it all over
oh actually yeah let me take that
let me take that too okay
bye guys have fun with the night shift
bye bye working hard boss friendly game
audio seems very low
that is wait i don't think you guys have
any
yeah you didn't even have any game audio
wait you didn't hear the ding dong
hey let me redo that okay one more time
hello everyone good good evening
how are you doing are you working
i need to annoy my employees a little
bit
eh of course you're here you didn't go
what do you mean you don't hear it
[Music]
no sound at all or too low you guys are
being very
vague it's definitely there
okay okay
so
okay you guys i can see you from my
house okay
i can see you how do you zoom again
what's the zoom button again
what's the zoom button
what's the zoom zoom zoom zoom zoom zoom
button
see i can say
oh guys actually i should lift my house
a little bit higher
so that i can actually see the chickens
because the chickens are so small
i actually i cannot see them
i should lift my house up higher so i
can really see them
okay let's make some torches
torches oops
oh that's a lot of torches that's a lot
of torches also where did the seats come
from
when did i when did i get myself some
seats
um
all right uh ah you know what i'll bring
some iron
how much
let's bring this much uh i guess yeah
since we're first gonna go to our base
anyway let's bring some stuff there
i barely have wood though um
i really ran out of wood after all this
time i finally ran out of wood
really ah there's a little bit
a little bit wood and uh i guess we
could bring a little bit of
[Music]
i think we should sleep
flip-faced we did we have um
made uh a little bit of a
of a base before
where i recently set up my my camp
so let's go there today
um if you guys remember i actually
do i have my boats down there i think i
do if you guys remember i
have um found
several of these
uh navigates in my island
and i want to go to the last one that we
found
if i find it i i should have the
coordinates
so wait i'm more okay
[Music]
type
let's see girl
yeah in japan too but i don't i i'm
pretty sure i took some
coordinates
did you turn your uh fov
all the way up uh not all the way but a
little bit because i
i like to see a little bit more
i would i want my point of view to be a
bit a little bit bigger
you know okay
oh wait wait why am i walking no walking
here
gosh now oh i hope my path
is i i think i repaired it last time
oh did i make that for me or you know
yeah kfb is on fire
why
oh someone repaired this i think
but no rails now to hold off should have
brought some rails
you guys doing fine they keep on opening
the doors
i'm watching you also there's how are
you doing you sure you don't want to go
inside it seems kind of
unsafe here are you okay
come on come with me come let's go
inside it's not safe outside
oh god oh god oh god oh god how did they
how did they
open up
okay don't look at me no no wait wait
wait look
wasn't that just open how was it opened
up oh because
because i opened it up for the pressure
plate you come inside come on
come on nice
okay we rescued one
chicken
bye bye
[Music]
hey oh yeah i was where do we where do
we continue
do you reckon this will work oh yes
now don't stop me anymore please
wee roller coaster wow
hey a lot of dudes there
loot from they alert me here there's
nothing rude about that
but it's beautiful isn't it a lot of you
guys wear
a bit shook about
the thumbnail there's nothing wrong with
the thumbnail
i just have to use good art you know it
has to be appreciated good heart a good
art has to be appreciated
didn't i do a great job of this rail
took me a long time to make
this path and then the rail
i was always very scared of the lava and
we several times we're very close to
to dying but i have managed to not die
wow so much lava wow
somehow it's beautiful
uh-oh i hear the ghast
hello and we are
oh and now we are here yes
okay and there is my nava porter this is
really scary
why am i walking like this
really really scary here
um i know i'mma have visited last time
but she just went out of the
portal and out of the water but then she
didn't find
my oh yeah that's right that's normal
that's just normal
she didn't find my
ah you didn't find my island
unfortunately or she found the wrong
island
let's go outside to japan
and my boat is here wonderful
now i think so the one that you
see right away is not the one where we
want to go we have to go in the exact
opposite
direction right i think
let's see
i think yeah i just still didn't put up
a sign
wait did i did i name the first one
okinawa or the second one okinawa
i think the first one this is japan one
and this is okinawa
okinawa is this really my island
what is that
what's that
oh it's just one of you never mind then
the second one is okinawa oh and that
makes sense because i was like hmm
wait what should i name you
i think oh this should be right
this should be correct
uh somewhere over there should be my
house
right
what was that what was that sound
yeah what
i'm not wrong right guys
wait it shouldn't have been so far away
shouldn't have been so far around the
corner or did someone destroy my house
no way
why not build some kind of lighthouse
yeah that would have been smart wait
wait
what the hint
wait i'm not lost no no no no
we are far from being lost ichigo
maybe it was not exactly
maybe it was not not exactly like
but i remember it being they exact
opposite direction
uh the boats yeah it's just a graphic
bug
now i told you guys to not take the
title uh literally i don't plan
to end the stream when i get lost not
necessarily
okay we're going back though on
there was a torch at the beginning
really
what happened did i come
go on the boat what the hell oh there we
go
oh man did i never realize that i can go
faster with the boat too
maybe i didn't maybe maybe maybe i went
past my house and i didn't realize
nah no way
i think we need to go back to the tower
and
reposition ourselves maybe this is where
i started right this
this is
do i really have to go get my
coordinates
i think i think here somewhere should be
my
tower
ah there we go okay
where is okinawa torch by the side
you pass it again what
i passed my house
[Music]
i see the torch i think
but this is not how i remember it looked
like
what
wait is that a trident again is that
dude throwing a trident on me again
every goddamn time
oh thank you
oh my god why is
why is he is he always there
[Music]
where is my house though did someone
destroy my house
but he didn't he didn't he wasn't able
to attach me
where is he i want to kill him
i mean i've had this before i it you
know
last time oh i also couldn't find you
[Music]
okay i found him i found him i found him
i
oh god okay okay it's um this is bad
this is bad
did he come out of the water is that a
thing they do
no that's not a thing they do
oh my god
[Music]
did he come out of the water did he come
out of the water
hello chicken please protect me
she's there okay okay no panic
i didn't even
wait a second i
i i watched pekuda
senpai's trident stream where she was
looking for
trident for for
like 10 12 hours she killed
5 million dudes with a trident and she
didn't get it until like 12 hours later
and i get it with one [\h__\h] china not
even trying
what
oh my god
is it really that easy
do you guys remember the last time we we
went to this island
the first time actually the first time
we went to this island
the first time we went to this island we
um
we were attacked by this i'm pretty sure
it was the same dude
the same dude and and i i wanted to kill
him i wanted to find him but i went into
the water and i just could not locate
him
uh and now we're finally back and he's
still there
and we just got the trident what
i i did not expect that to happen uh i
want to bring it back
uh not back but to the to the middle
chest where's my boat
wait wait my boat oh my god
trident speed one okay oh my god
oh my god where's my boat where's my
uh wait i have to bulge
[Music]
oh my god this is unbelievable well how
how long i i watched tekura's
whole stream uh rta of getting the
trident
wait where is my where is my tower
oh there uh but how long did it take
gura
how long did it take good huh
okay now get back in there safely come
on
okay okay what the hell okay okay okay
okay
this is really this is really bad
what's a zombie doing there
you're gonna come down or what are you
wait what are you doing there oh damn
okay he's not gonna come down
i think okay trident
safe okay that was not really what i
came for
three streams 12 hours
12 hours in total wait oh wait let me
sleep let me sleep
now
oh my god trident rta
uh if this if only this was a trident
rta stream
then i could have made a record in her
life
of being the fastest one to get a
trident
oh
i didn't even want one i didn't even
i didn't even ask for one now but i'm so
confused where my house is
is it am i getting crazy and it's
actually on this side no it's not there
is it or maybe it is
i'm getting really confused
oh my god what is that
is that a bug is my house here
isn't it more right i i know that's
definitely like when you're in front of
the island then you have to go to the
right side
no but it's not it's it can't be there
opposite side of japan then go left left
i thought it was i'm pretty sure uh
it was uh go to the right
way i'm still not over the fact that i
got a goddamn trident
like the chance of first of all the
chance of finding
a zombie uh drowned
who has a trident first of all that
those chances are
well well well and then the chances of
them dropping it those chances are hella
low
as far as i know okay let's try to go
left if you guys really uh
think i i um if you guys
uh insist and then go left
ah i see it oh it was left
okay my house
yo but this is it's good that we didn't
find it right away because if we would
have found it right away i wouldn't
probably wouldn't have met the the dude
oh my god
[Music]
hello you guys
wait you guys remember i also have um
uh some kind of what was it i have some
really good
enchantment for the trident that when i
got it i was like who is this useful and
you guys said yeah it's useful
or tried and then i'm like oh well i
don't have one i don't i don't know but
okay i guess it's good that i have it
what was it
what was that i wonder a riptide oh yeah
what does that do again
riptide oh yeah i got riptide
riptide yeah i got ripped out free is
there even a roadside one
uh fly it makes you fly in water fly in
water
you can fly when it's raining oh what
mexico blue and water
wait hold on can i i want to try it out
guys
okay change my mission play with a
trident but i also want something
okay we're changing the the theme of the
stream
you must wait let me close the door i
think i can close the door and
let's uh i want to uh
i wanna find out how to uh
enchant i never enchanted someone before
something before
also i wanted to be um repaired
yeah i need to i need to repair it you
guys got to teach me
please teach me where's my towel and
where's my tower
[Music]
enchantment what can't repair it at the
moment
need bending and but even if it uh loses
all durability
i can still repair it afterwards right
it will not just disappear right that's
that's not a thing it will just be
red and then and then yeah
nope it breaks what
oh i guess oh i guess uh weapons do that
game is that
okay well okay hmm
oh wait a second
ah this is so difficult here
breathe uh okay
okay well what was that
what was that trident
rails let's bring let's bring a few
rails
okay now kiara the mission is
to not die when you go back home because
you'll never get a trident
ever again monitor
monday ah no
i want to enchant it and uh
why did you guys say i cannot repair it
right now
need mending that's another enchantment
is that one easy to get
yes
[Laughter]
you're in the way
[Music]
this should i try to kill him
what are these sounds so creepy
don't kill him i don't want him but like
he's in the way you know what i'll bring
the
i'll burn the card and then i start
behind him
fishing can make you get it
you can fish enchantments what
you can fish enchantments
you can fish books oh
what are you all doing there go
i think there's a gas here oh quicker
come on oh god i need to
um make this area gas proof as well
uh ina has tons of books from fishing oh
do you think she has a mending book
remaining mending repairs it one time or
and then what does it do doesn't chapman
disappear
if it only repairs it one time
portraying the librarians well i don't
think we have a librarian landing
repairs when you gain xp
oh so it will stay there forever and i
can repair it again and again whenever i
gain experience
[Music]
i kind of tried and i got it right and
without even trying without even trying
life comes too easy
for these lucky phoenix hey hey hey hey
hey
watch me
i got it tried and i got it right and
without even trying
why is it not working now it worked
before well i guess uh is that the part
that broke once and i repaired it and
now it's not working why is it not
working
how come it's not working anymore
oh my god thank you for the membership
thank you
oh my god oh my god okay i brought some
you guys all right your boss got to try
and yo
hello how did you get outside
probably i probably needed a power drill
there but oh well
he's walking the the rail path
ah
girl
he broke the rails you think that
employee broke the rails
to manipulate me maybe maybe that's one
of the
members from the resistance
you never know you never know who are
the
the real i mean i i think i have a
feeling for it
i think i have a feeling for who is
actually
a good member
and is not thinking about manipulating
or sabotaging
or resisting or opposing
i have a good feeling when it comes to
that
i gotta try that what the hell ha ha
ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
yay
okay so um first of all i need exp
right uh so
we should maybe put oh hello enderman
maybe we should put the
trident away for now to keep it safe
so we go to that tower that ame built
get
exp and get a mending
thingy right no it's when you what
yeah yeah i know it's when you gain xp
but i don't have the mending book
yet where do i get them
let me see if ah inna isn't online
too bad
i don't want to just take it yeah so
we'll try to get it ourselves
um oh what's what's this here
what happened here
wow who's is this
all the kitty cats i want a kitty cat
too
you look like my baby
oh are those innas
good ass good as barn oh
maybe i can adopt one of her kitty cats
uh i want one of the kitty cats
i want one okay where is the
uh at the end of our tunnel is the
xp farm right
hello my friend hello darkness my old
friend
don't worry i'm not here to hurt you
oh i brought my saddle but i didn't i
didn't saddle anything
oh there we go
what stole gouda's trident thunder now
you want to steal her
cat what do you mean i stole grass
trident thunder
what the hell are you talking about
is that am i not allowed to have a
trident
what i didn't even try to get one's not
my fault
am i going the right way
ah
oh enderman
[Music]
don't look outside when you're traveling
it's just a big fork for kfb purpose
yeah who knows what i'll use my dragon
for who knows
i just i just hope i'll never lose it
and isn't there an enchantment that it
always comes back to you i want that
wait isn't that isn't that what it does
anyway
i don't understand ah that's loyalty ah
so i have riptide and it would be nice
to have loyalty
and then we put on landing as well um
you can is it
can you only have three enchantments
maximum
riptide won't be thrown at all oh wait
you mean i just hold it and i fly around
with it and
like i i i'm the i'm the
like i'm i become the trident i become
the trident
what oh we will see how that goes
it was enchantment this could have on
her trident
they aren't compatible oh oh i see
we see
uh nothing yet oh she has loyalty oh
see we will have different kinds of
tridents she has the loyal one i have
the riptide one
it won't be the same dragon will be a
different trident
it will be the phoenix trident
gosh let's get some exp and maybe a book
oh but wait i don't have a is there a
fishing rod up there
hello hello
yeah okay hello
this looks really impressive
i can't go straight what the hell is so
wobbly
for your fish here fishing beer
is it in here oh curse of vanishing i'm
breaking mending i want the mending
can i take it off of the of the fishing
rod
i never fished before
no you can't oh well okay how do i
how do i fish how do i know i fished
someone does it just go into my
inventory directly
zoom in
what am i supposed to see
go get xp before it's gonna break ah
hey hi okay okay
uh okay this is also i haven't used this
one either
as well do i just do that
wow
okay i you need me to go over it now you
moved over there okay
okay you will die for that
oh i hold i am in my other hand to
repair it ah
okay okay okay come on guys
come
taking them a lot of time i should
probably wait a little bit
and uh oh wait there's a oh there's a
thing for enchantments here
good night everyone
you guys need a cactus one what why
wha what what's good about
good about a cactus fan
oh no oh no
oops no i don't want to face you
i keep on fishing guys cactus gave lots
of exp when turned
into die hey
rod is fixed oh
that was quick that was very quick wow
okay okay okay okay
well okay so
how do we do this
when do i know i have to pull it out
wait a minute before trying again to let
enemies spawn
okay
you look you wait for fish to bite
and do i see it a wave comes under it
bubbles there's bubbles now
oh oh ah
oh no
fishy business oh
this will take a long time joe
this uh hey how often oops
how long does it take to get a book
out of that
do i have to be all the way up there
ah why can't i go straight
okay now we're going straight
pretty hard there are also other books
oh okay
you need
you need luck of the sea ah you mean
those those those pearls oh i have a
bunch of them
i actually do have a bunch of them
uh okay
improve your chances oh wait i have to
wha what
wait what ah that that not hard enough
to see ah
okay oh it's coming it's coming it's
coming
yo what was that
it's an enchantment
ah to get like better stuff from fishing
not exactly what i imagined to do today
i mean we can i guess we can get the
mending later on
how much exp do i need to um
give it the the the riptide
better rod and chest really
look of the sea
um okay and i don't even have to repair
it
is it does does it make a big difference
we will see
oh it's called amelia rodson
wait did something just already
something bad
no that was just my imagination
it's still a very low chance oh man
i know i can make a villager fun but i'm
not gonna make that now because i don't
even know how to do it
i don't know how to do that kind of
stuff
huh
i missed something
oh there we go here's something
come on fishy cece
it's the gotcha stream not a very
exciting gotcha stream though
you get a villager for mending
enchantment book it's faster than
fishing
are you sure about that it has to be
someone who
who has books like where am i where am i
gonna find
that like there's a village close by to
our village but i don't think
i think most of them died and i don't
know
i've never seen a live even in my
travels where i've
seen a lot of a lot of villages
i've never seen one with a librarian i
think
you can breed them ah by giving them
bread
[Music]
make them a librarian use lectern to
turn them into librarians what
user what i don't understand anything
you guys are saying and
fishing just for me is easier to
understand
fishing is more fun anyway i'm not sure
about that part
it seems more fun to do the villager
thing you
need like one book to make collecting
like a normal book
to any villager any any
villager at all
and then i just what do i do i just wait
what if he only has [\h__\h] though
was that a golden fish
uh i'm trying to read the messages but
oh my god i also need to fish
nope no golden fish
you can enchant books at the enchantment
table you get random enchantments
and use an animal to transfer many to
the trident oh
i can just get random enchantments and
hope that
one of them will be mending
uh
oh that
that seems
you can't get mending from enchantment
table aha
oops ah it's early
the villager weighs easier
i'm too stupid to fish anyway
okay let me let me give this back and
i mean we will come back here
anyway to get exp
uh maybe
jump okay
let's try i guess
i are you a donkey or a host
a horse or a donkey
wait what am i doing is that a donkey
if yes i i think i want to bring you
back home boy
is that a horse or donkey
no you're not are you pretty
is that a horse yeah it's a horse i
think
what about you you're a horse too a cute
horse there's a lot of horses here i
should get myself a horse finally
i want a pretty horizontal
wait i can't move anymore my game
crashed
i think wait a second
my game crashed
you see that in the in the background it
looks like an edm festival
yeah is it coming back or like my my
mouth says it's loading
game crashed
omata all right guys
one second let me restart the game
java platform se binary is not
responding
i see
okay
i'm gonna be right back
i wanted to see it really look like some
edm festival damn
okay i'm getting back in there whoopsie
circles that was not that was not
circles guys
you guys have no idea circles is way
more beautiful than that
okay
we are back yes
what the [\h__\h] man
i was just trying to check out the
horses that's a pretty horse
oh my god
that's a that's an interesting horse
no you're not the one though oh isn't
there a village over there
wait but i don't have a book when there
are books
up there like are there also normal
books
uh i wonder if they have and they have a
book up there also this is a cake
interesting
it was lever i don't i want to go all
the way back home
maybe don't you think they have
something up there
bring the villager home first just any
villager
do i need a lead for that
let me go up and find if there's
something uh useful
you also need emeralds to trade i have a
bunch of mmos yeah but
probably not enough which is why i was
thinking that
yeah this is probably what
what what do i what
you