[Music]
so
foreign
[Music]
so
i'm home
[Music]
people here what happened what happened
i guess it's still um a good and okay
time before bedtime in korea
different
oh i
i
are you hearing me from
are you hearing me
oh
it's picking up my
vr chat um
[Laughter]
it's the way to delay
um
oh [\h__\h] no no it was a
webcam microphone
ah here it is this is this one this one
is
[Music]
a little bit of a pawn moment a little
bit
the more pun moment was
me realizing i turned off the super
chats a little bit too late
still before the stream but
um a little bit scuffed
sorry i had to make a new stream um
otherwise we would have waited
quite some time until yeah
you know
mistakes have been made
i've i kind of suspected this to happen
uh loki
no don't worry about it you don't have
to apologize what the hell don't
apologize for supporting
thank you for waiting uh i'm back
did you miss me
[Music]
i was gone for like what three days
three days yeah
uh doesn't happen so often
uh in in the kfp world
uh oh wait i should change my outfit i'm
still in my traveling clothes
if still in my traveling club
[Music]
i need my alden ring clothes oh here
there we go
eleven ring clothes
um my mask there we go
oh yeah my fancy
accessories there we go i got it all got
it all got it all yeah
who this new phone who this the [\h__\h] who
the who is this
who is this
looks so unfamiliar doesn't it
it is me i know it's like unrecognizable
with my mask but i am takana
you're your tencho
so we're going to play ellen rain today
um i was thinking between yakuza and
elden ring but we already played yakuza
uh on monday so i was like okay i want
to play along however now uh i've seen
that everyone else is playing all the
ring on sundays
of a whole live myth literally everyone
except kelly i guess so it's um sorry
sorry to fill up fill up your um youtube
timeline with
even more ellen ring
uh i hope that's okay
where did where did keanu go you mean
right now or you mean three days ago
[Laughter]
i'm a i'm a yeah we played it too a
little bit uh i wonder if she enjoyed it
uh did she enjoy it
did she enjoy it did you guys watch her
play it
she liked it
she did
she did she did she's making this series
oh really
did she say that
i mean she she likes
i feel like it's like
kind of low-key low-key similar
in like i don't know visuals and genre
no
um
yeah
yeah yeah she likes exploring yeah
not at all
complete
[Music]
throughout the stream today i will show
you pictures of
where i was and what i was doing
um
she likes collecting moss
you can collect moss in the game
it seems like
some of you kind of know but i mean
that's not any surprise because i kind
of told you guys a while ago that i was
planning on doing this um
just collecting bones in caves ah
uh okay well let's get into the game
first um i have a vision
uh
[Music]
that i i will explore today as well lots
of exploring hopefully
um
yeah
so social media
we're not gonna rush to the next bus
we're gonna
go in some caves and stuff
hope that's okay for you guys
eldon ring hey oh wait the desktop audio
is wrong too um
[Music]
what
[\h__\h] you no
no i'm not gonna pay that
music is so dramatic
pay playstation plus do it or your life
is gonna end
you have to do it everything's counting
on it dramatic music
no
shut up
shut up i don't i'm not not paying you
money
uh continue load game what's the
difference
oh [\h__\h] yeah this is where we ended uh
after finally being the ass of margin
i'm not part of your system
i'm gonna take your subscription and i'm
going to front right on the ground
yeah
what is that over there
oh uh
what was that again isn't that uh my
body
oh yeah but there's nothing in there
my dad is not a phone
that's funny um
okay wait so we're not gonna go there
because that would be i suppose
exploring the castle which looks pretty
cool damn
i never really took a moment to look at
it because margie was like kicking my
ass
[Music]
yeah yeah we're not going there i think
uh never getting a costume um i mean i
would i would i would i guess wait you
have to get a subscription to play co-op
that's
um if i have to i would do it for
whoever would play with me but our
problem is anyway we're playing on
playstation and the only other one
playing playstation
is cali
um
but anyway so we're going somewhere
why is it why is is this just a i hear
some like crackling noises is this just
uh
here
is it supposed to what it's gonna what
it's supposed to be is this what what
wait a second um i have a map that i'm
gonna be looking at
uh
we're gonna go
we're gonna
go is that the area yeah it's in-game
okay sometimes it's confusing yeah some
japanese girls are playing um
[Music]
ps52 yeah uh we're gonna
start where the frick is that uh one two
three
uh
we're gonna start by
[Music]
someone sent me some places i could go
we're gonna start there's like one here
and one
here that i haven't even seen yet
apparently let's go to the church
[Music]
um i need to
oh
can we fight him
i need to figure out how to play this
game again and i need to uh figure out
where the hell i am who am i what am i
what am i doing here where am i
i need to figure out some things first
um
i'll need a moment
and
uh you have anything useful i need right
now ah i want the the thing the light
thing the
light give me light uh uh purchase do
you have the light thing yes
a torch does that work like forever
we got the torch guys we got the torch
going
lantern wait was i supposed to get a
lantern [\h__\h]
is the torch okay too
it runs out
what is it in here i was just in the car
with lena we uh
we finally um we fought we took some
time to think about uh where we wanted
to stay
um you can attack with it lantern is
better than torch um twitch okay too
okay i didn't see it when there's never
lantern
we'll get a lantern once i see where i
can buy one um
yes
uh but with reyna a while ago we were
looking for hotels to stay at uh
and where where we wanted to go and then
we had some options but we're both not
100 sure what's the best option
and
well and then
just now before the stream
um we booked the hotel we finally
decided and we also booked flights
yeah
use grace for levels wait what does that
mean what does that mean
what does that mean
oh god he's coming
oh lord he coming
hide
how close is he gonna come
ah
didn't i already level up
that's what you meant i forgot what that
meant
that did not already do that i wouldn't
level up with grace
wait why did so many people say level up
with grace
i did that at the end of the last stream
did you guys not watch the end of my
last stream huh did you guys not watch
the end of my last stream where i beat
marget
the emotional moment of me beating
marget after so much work
and you didn't watch it
what she's got to pop from wind zip shut
up
shake my head
shake my head somehow shake my head
[Laughter]
yes well how do i turn on the thing at
all times can i have this at all times i
want this on at all times
i forgot how to play this game
oh
uh wait i know how to get on the horse
in options
no no no system
hud
okay
finally one problem solved
uh
okay we're gonna go
we're gonna go
which one is easier
the one that's here limb grave tunnels i
think it's called
or the one that's here which one is
easier
we can also go to one on the beaches one
on the beach here
i heard i think there's something at on
the beach
is helpful for me
second one
tunnels is better
okay sorry third option third option
what about the beach
beach is easy both are easier they're
all easy
each is good
tunnel
beach
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] last go for any
each
[Music]
go to the beach beach
check i'm putting you here is that okay
do you feel comfortable there
you good
you're good chad
coco cuckoo i mean
sorry i'm like uh i'm like a
amateur
make myself smaller to
make my hands smaller too
okay
you can see so much from up here yeah my
mommy gave you lift
so you can see everything wow you're so
tall jimmy you're so tall aren't you
i can show you
oh
where is my mark right there over there
how do i even how do i get to the beach
safely wasn't there like a freaking huge
cliff
let's go
let's go to the beach ah i told i told
reina to bring her cutest swimsuit
i gotta go
i have like a lot of how many swimsuits
do i have i have like um
eight i think about approximately eight
swimsuits
maybe i need to get new ones for for
dana
not for her to wear but for me to wear
for her
yeah bikinis and and one-piece swimsuits
what is that over there
uh
no plan no plan to oh
oh big boy but he's okay here i i i
killed him before i'll kill him before i
fight like this a fat like this
oh he's so big [\h__\h]
[Music]
swimsuit i'll be the one looking at it
was there a way to lock on enemies again
wow he's really climbing that mountain
here he's like on a
on a on a little walk
oh yeah this is it yeah yeah okay
oh god he's looking for some herbs
some berries mummy is that you you
looking for berries
oh
you found berries
[Music]
[\h__\h]
i need to warm up
[Laughter]
everything's cool every school
everyone's cool
need to warm up man
ah dashing is okay and jump is it okay
okay okay
okay okay why do i have two markers what
the hell
why do i have two markers where's the
other one
okay
[Laughter]
monkeys
i don't know what you're talking about
there ain't no monkey business in here
no monkey's here no no no no where is
big man hello big man where's my body
okay
wasn't even that much um okay now
oh
yeah
um i mean i'm getting a lot of fantasy
oh [\h__\h]
oh
beautiful no damage run
no damage run
yo that's a lot of exp does he respond
can i
farm exp with him
i did a bleed yes
he responds oh you can totally farm exp
with him holy [\h__\h]
today
is
give me your meat mmm bones um
all right all right i'm i'm not sure
what exactly i'm coming to the beach for
is there like a cave here
um
[Music]
at those mobs
these are huge
a cave
okay
uh okay okay
is this the cave no
uh yeah corrupted
it looks it reminds me of uh
pirates of the caribbean
okay my light leads me to nowhere
oh
is it is it that way though
um
yeah it should be that way
um do you guys want to fight
they're so weak
oh [\h__\h]
my friends
oh you're using a sword that's not very
unga bungalow
yeah
hey
rainbow stones and string and more
rainbow stones nice
thank you thank you
thank you thank you all right should let
me knee by the way where was that goes
this past three days days well here it
is here is the
the the the that's the cave i suppose
here it is
i'm telling you now listen up
oh
is that a merchant
i was
at
uh
drum drum roll please please
[Music]
posting drums nice
isn't there like there should be a
a thing a thing where i can save my soul
no
maybe inside the cave
i went to germany for a food trip that's
right baby
i
went to
eat food
in germany
and spent
a lot of money on uber and food
[Laughter]
yep yep
um
yes dusseldorf uh it was two nights
i wrapped uh i wrapped the
um
yeah food is good food make happy
food very good
uh
yeah i was on i was on kind of a
vacation mini vacation but it was a food
vacation and uh
it's funny because like
after we arrived at um
at the airport uh not at the airport at
the because we had to take a train to at
the train station
um
we took an uber to our hotel and
they asked us why did you come here
oh [\h__\h] up
oh wow
and we said oh we came here to eat food
and he was like what
what
what are you talking about
what are you talking about what do you
mean you came here for food they
everyone who we told about that they
they did not understand the concept of
going on a food trip i don't know i
don't know why
why are they so
strong damn there we go there we go
there we go so you go to that
oh they run
um
it's not exactly common
it should be more common
it should be
but i mean
we went to a different country just to
eat food so that is uh probably a little
bit
don't go crazy calm down
i'm gonna kill this one too
don't get dizzy chad don't get dizzy
yeah
i downed him
i think
i'm really busy oh my god
what did he just heal himself what just
happened
he's faster
ew what are those disgusting eggs
i just realized
oh
hit him
the [\h__\h] didn't know you had to move
like that
go
finally
in case you didn't know dusseldorf is in
germany and is the location where
um
i went for dokomi uh the like a really
really awesome
um
convention in germany anime convention
japan convention what is that
what's that
and in
[Music]
in all of germany it has the most
what is that
uh
it has the biggest amount of uh japanese
people living there
invisible sky ah
[Music]
and one of the uber drivers even told me
um
from all over the world
this little dog in germany is the uh
second
[Music]
the country of the second most japanese
people
outside of japan the other one being la
apparently
i didn't know it was the second most in
all over the world
[Applause]
i know there's a path i know
what
that's your voice stamp sweep oh i
didn't know you would give me that
is that another merchant but where is uh
uh
a grace looking for grace i thought it
was brazil i don't know probably not
uber driver talk [\h__\h] yeah because uh
now that you say it i remember when i
was in brazil there were a lot of
japanese people too
inside inside the cave another huddle
okay oh [\h__\h] oh i thought you were
merchant um
i thought you were a merchant
oh god
it's insane
okay we can beat him we can beat him
though
[Music]
beat him beat him
if i don't miss him 100 times
[\h__\h] you
yeah keep on running after me buddy i
have a horse
it's not gonna be
so much fun for you
oh yelling at me
there's no damage uh-uh
[\h__\h] bastard
[Laughter]
okay back to my chit chat
so yeah do so love and because of this
sort of having so many japanese people
there they have so much great authentic
japanese food
[Music]
foreign
yeah
and that's why i went there because
yes blade buddy
yeah
remember when i went to dokomi last time
i think i complained that my favorite
restaurant at dukami was closed
and it was actually
just closed
up
because dopamine was happening at a in a
different time than usual
oh god don't fall down
don't get yourself killed now
yeah
[Music]
thousands
yeah my favorite restaurant was closed
because they were all on a vacation door
i don't know and just
just during that time i was looking
forward to eating there so much and i
couldn't eat there
and it felt i felt so sad i was so
regretful about that i was like i'm
gonna come back here just to eat here
again
um
yes
it's called
tonkatsukonta
my favorite food is my favorite japanese
food is hirakatsu which is a under
a category
of
tonkatsu
i could level up i think almost
is it could we um
secretly stab his back
um
[\h__\h]
how do you how do you
okay will he notice me wait can i even
stab his back with uh this weapon
ah
he's sleeping
[Laughter]
why are you leaving me horse
invincible frames
what
[\h__\h]
leave leave
yeah
baby
i mean it's not so difficult when you're
on a horse we got gauntlets some cool
gauntlets
got him i got him
i got him
nice
city
all right let's go into the cave
with my
ex-roommate i used to live with her and
uh we already traveled to a lot of
different places we traveled to london
before we traveled to greece
together
before
we traveled to
wait there was one more place
oh yeah we went uh skiing together she
was the one i went skating with
yeah and um after
we
um went to buy
uh
my skiing equipment we were like sitting
in a restaurant and just chit-chatting
and i i told her that i want to go like
on a food trip to dusseldorf at some
point
um
because i really want to eat japanese
authentic food i want to get that
tonkatsu and so on
and she was like mmm that sounds good i
explained to her that there's like a lot
of great japanese restaurants there and
then she actually got interested and
said that she wants to
she she wouldn't mind joining me on on
that trip
[Music]
you're following me
ooh what's this
am i in the dungeon now
where is my save point
i don't like this
where's my save point where's my grace
i don't want to go in here when this
hallelujah okay
we're going through here ah wait but i
don't have a
lantern where do you get the lantern
guys
when do you get the lantern
i could buy it first and come back here
uh yeah but the torch runs out right how
fast does it run out
oh so close let me kill the buddies
outside
uh oh oh god
it doesn't didn't someone tell me it
runs out
i guess the lantern is just better
because it makes more light
hello
what
okay
[Music]
how do i block again
uh huh what's that what's that
kik
i'm gonna block uh uh i'm too handing my
weapon so i can't hold up come here
you're gonna drown in the water
be careful
okay i can level up now
geek
i have to hold the target's lantern you
can't you don't oh
oh i want i don't want to hold it can
you guys tell me where i can get a
lantern
i don't want to hold it but then i need
money and i'm and now i'm going to use
all my money on my level up
ki kitty kick
uh
santa merchant in the south okay
merchant in the south
[Music]
vigor or strength what's endurance
how much is the lantern thousand eight
hundred
[Music]
and damn i should um but wait if i kill
that big dude uh two times then they
have two
okay
stamina and equipment endurance is a
green ball
[Music]
oh i have golden runs too yeah that's
right
[Music]
let me see how many i have
uh
inventory
oh
nine
that's exactly what i need for the
lantern
that's exactly what i mean
[Music]
one sec i'm just gonna go a little
bigger
and then
um how do i what's it ashes of war
does it go in here ah it does
stamp this is the new one
we're using which one
nothing are we using nothing can i even
use it
we have storm stomp stamp and wild
strikes
which one should i do
this one is plus 40.
uh fp clause six and five minus eight
five two eight
one strikes one strikes
eight thirty eight
okay i'm gonna trust you i'm heavy
or on standard because
it would make my morning star heavy i
don't know if i want that
um
stand it okay
can't do something on the shell no okay
ah
okay now
why can i not teleport
because i'm in here
can i not tell one
south merchant do you mean this one
i can't
okay no problem
no problem
i like this for you
okay
so hopefully this is the one oopsie
someone told me to
work on the weeping peninsula peninsula
peninsula unusually this agent
yes
you have the lantern
[Music]
so how does that work have a safe
journey yeah thank you
[Music]
how does that work
um
equipment maybe and then put it
somewhere
yep
is it like a flask
but then i have to uh
switch it huh um
oh wait no [\h__\h]
i like this
oh ah can i put it on the top one
uh
equipment
the top one is supposedly empty right
now where does it need to go tap is for
spells
you know what we can do though we can
remove that so we don't have to move
around so much anymore
um
but could i and theory also put it here
i guess i could
probably
okay so when i do this
how do i
use it like that
and then what if i heal
oh does it not go away
it's a cute little lantern on my hip so
if i drink
it's still there
oh okay
ben lirana
it's like a buff
okay
cute
okay we have our little lamp
now we can go
into caves i don't like caves but i
guess we're gonna go
um
so
i hope i can tangent properly in here um
lantern
here we go
and let's go is this is this a scary
place
wait i'm not too handing my weapon
uh
yes
i know how to do it now
hello
i'm scared
i'm glowing really
how so
there's something going there too
i'm just oh i see you
i see you come fight me
oh
you don't even notice me
okay okay
oh
nice bleed
[Music]
nice bleed what is this jubilee jubilee
paper ah that's what anime was
collecting keith moss
shall we go this way ah confusing i
could go down
also
ah i guess i'm gonna go that way
hello
one after another please
thank you oh they're weak thank god
thank god they're suing you back to you
know
what am i hearing what am i hearing
i'm hearing zombie noises
coming from somewhere else that just is
hauling through the holes
it didn't work that's okay that's okay
scary scary scary scary scary scary
scary scary quiet cool eye color i need
more light i need more moo moo moo moo
at least this actually likes look even
if you still don't know
what's there because you can't see it
you can kind of
sometimes see the enemy quite early
yeah
yeah shut up no yelling the other people
are gonna find out i'm here
is there like a
lamp upgrade at some point
to get a bigger lamp
torches give more light oh
yeah but i want to two-hand my weapon
i wanted to hand my weapon you know oh
isn't this an indicator that there is
like a
boss
oh yeah
old night i can summon someone
um
should i
well let's do it
i should
is it for the whole dungeon this time or
for only one flight
welcome
you're on school well he has a big sword
he looks he looks pretty experienced
there's a bus right here that's so fast
okay move
you can come with me
okay okay
i thought we were gonna be stuck there
okay
oh he has some little friends too i
guess this is the boss oh god
dude dude are you with me
wait i can uh summon my friends too
take care of the small ones first maybe
um
what should i do
[Music]
okay i'm in the game i'm in the game
i'm in the game
it's good the dogs are taking care of
the small ones properly i think yeah
there we go
enemy filled
dude
are you guys so busy there
mosh pit yeah
did i not get any exp from that now
cause you killed them alone
but there's still another one no okay
first try atta
what is this sparkly silver firefly
well now believe your eyes oh they don't
want to fight anymore because i killed
the boss
you have exp for me though don't you
they don't
you don't have to make the kill for
runes not a hurdle but things don't even
give room snow
um
just i just forgot something that i was
supposed to do
i think
i have something here to put on my arms
which one is the new one
was this one
it's
wait the only ones that are really
somewhat better are these ones though
because
yeah there's so much
that although it's magic fire lightning
holy which i'm not using
then only strike going down matters
maybe
it's weaker and heavier
i know bluer is higher i don't know
yeah but i see more red than blue
maybe it doesn't matter
maybe it's not that much better
okay
why why do they sound like monkeys
wait was this it because i already
killed a boss is this the dungeon is are
we done
oh return to entrance
why would i return to entrance is this
the end
that's it
is there a treasure
oh i thought things would be longer now
if they're so short that's actually good
continue forward to find more keep going
ah okay okay
i hear something
it's sleeping or feasting i'm not sure
it's feasting
dad's hit from behind just feels so good
oh
come at me bro
backstabbing
don't do it in real life though it's not
very nice
to do it in real life
only in games feels good
oh a lot of bones here
who's been eating these chicken wings
huh
a lot of grass here
and light oh
where am i
i'm leaving the cave
wait is this
where i entered no where where am i
cool i'm on the island that i saw
i was wondering how to get there
oh
i'm so bloody can i uh wash it off
if i just uh
don't go too deep into the water
wash it off
wash it up
[\h__\h]
drank it by accident
roll roll
i i think this works
um if you're like poisoned and you roll
in poison and you get poisoned faster
but i guess it doesn't work for washing
with some blood up okay
it stains really badly apparently
a little bird bath yeah
and bird brain moments with me drinking
my potion when i don't need it
anyway anyway sorry it's i'm i'm really
i'm really not much of a multitasker i
can't
tell my stories properly
but i didn't want to do a stream this
time where i just come here talk about
my trip and then say goodbye because
it's not it's not as much to talk about
as it usually is i just have a lot of
photos of my food
and since i was gone for three days i
thought you guys want to see me for a
little bit longer today
so so either yakuza or ellen ring would
be good for a long stream i thought
so okay let's see let's start from the
top um
so
i
[Music]
uh
i did
i did fly uh
[Music]
wait
what what was i supposed to i think i'm
mixing up things
huh
yeah i think i just
did i not play mario kart before flying
no i didn't that was another trip
mixing up things i did and
i did not
uh play mario kart before my flight
no i i i did fly and take a train both
of it because
um
there was like an expensive flight and
rmt was like girl
na um
that's crazy
no no need to pay so much for
that flight we'll we'll fly to a city
close by and then go with the train
um so we actually flew to um what's it
called in english
curtain in english it had a specific
name
once again
uh
colon column like the
male perfume
right yeah yeah okay i figured it out
right before you guys were telling me oh
wait there it is there it is
oh it's a church it's is it a church
yeah um with the plane to colon and then
dragon communion
uh and then we took a train
thankfully rmt
don't tell me i can
summon the dragon here you learn dragon
spells uh okay
i'm scared to
say examine altar
thankfully rnt took care of like most of
the bookings
and looking up which terrain to use and
all that it's safe okay
thankfully
cause my mind
i had no time for that
bling bling bing bing bing bling what
did that was that doing was that doing
it it did nothing
i hear
i hear a
shiny shiny sound sparkly sound
you need to do it at night
another hotel
what does it do
i can actually learn a dragon skill
okay then we shall sleep until night
time
okay or run around a little bit more
is there anything else up here
okay
sorry i need some meat
need a dragon heart
i need a dragon heart
great dragonfly head oh it was on the
body oh
what
uh
anything else here
the water looks so nice
i don't want to jump into it
music
on me
i i do a flip i can't help
my character
it's even it's a girl i keep on saying
he my character will drown in there
i hear the sparkly sound again
[Music]
sparkling sound tuckle
it's gonna [\h__\h] roll over the cliff i
already know it
oh it won't
oh i thought it would roll away from me
[Music]
no we're good we're
good all right it's getting night time
uh uh uh so uh where was i oh yeah so we
flew to
uh
call lon and we you know what was
funny about that flight it was one of
those cheap ass uh ryan air flights
all right
um
and and and we were about to land like
literally i could see the ground it was
like five
five seconds away from landing or three
seconds
and then he suddenly took off again but
right before touching a ground he went
fuel up again i was like was happening
i still don't know what happened but he
apparently needed to circle around a
little bit longer
this is gonna be a tangent again for cow
carrots to cut together into one proper
story
um
yes only tolerable for very very short
flies that is very true
um
landing failed the trial again next time
yeah and he flew all the way up in the
in the air again and then circled around
and then after a few minutes he tried to
land again and then everything was okay
the pilot eventually figured out a way
to land um
it's very noisy here
let's go what does it do
ritual of dragon communion oh well i
don't have what you need apparently okay
well why did we even wait then
so there's nothing here left for me to
do right am i correct with that
assumption
[Music]
slay dragons oh
i i guess so um i think we entered these
before but we never finished them
is that the one with the fire and the
goblins
i'll go to a different one
um i would like it to be daytime i
really prefer games more when it's
bright
and i can actually see [\h__\h]
check out that lake bed eh you mean what
what do you mean like bed
like bed
you got this
it had so many jump scares too i don't
like all those jump scares
i'll go here
is it there
it should be there i don't like
jumpscares isn't it morning time why is
it so freaking dark
um
those [\h__\h] goblins kept on leaving me
jumpscares anyway so we landed okay and
then we went for the absolutely dead
cologne airport both on our arrival and
on our departure the airport was so
empty and
dead lifeless
really weird
there was
yeah not much going on there oh oh it's
you again buddy
he's probably like that [\h__\h]
oh she followed the wrong lights
that [\h__\h] keeps on stalking me
wrong light wrong beacon yes it always
happens to me
i wanted to deactivate the other beacons
once i made a new one that would be good
um
we landed and we went for the empty
alpha and now we took a train
and uh whoa
see how the light shines through the
trees whoa
and through my body
whoa
oh hello sorry i'm just admiring this
beautiful beautiful scenery
you can't hurt me no more
nah
what
animals be yelling
i'm so useless man i'm so useless
where's my light right
there here here here
what
doesn't it doesn't
okay
i don't know what i was talking about
maybe i should just give up on talking
[Laughter]
uh
i need to get up there i need to go from
the side no i think how about
i go from now huh
what if i go from
i need to go like for the side right
around it
i
think wait what is that
no that's it that's what i was looking
for
ah-ha
okay we found it we found the touch
oh
good touch good thoughts
[Music]
what was that okay so uh how about home
how about we take a sit
and i talk for five minutes straight
okay
okay okay okay because otherwise we
ain't getting nowhere
um
an uber and uber was weird because um
like i don't know i had so many
talkative ubers recently um but i'm a
nice person and i was in a good mood so
i was talkative back and i guess i kind
of made him talk more and more but he
was kind of weird because he was kind of
flirty like in the in the weird way
um me and my my friend r t we were
laughing our butt stuff because he was
saying stuff like he had a car where
there's a window on the top like of the
ceiling of the car
and and i i got in and i was like oh
look aren't he in the window up there
can look at the stars with this car and
then he was oh shall i take you
looking look at the stars anytime and i
was like
um
and then he said um
weird stuff that i don't even remember
um
like what was it something about
uh
the beauty
what was she talking about
i barely remember
cause i was i was like cringing and hold
i was like please stop talking
um
who's he talking about
i legit forgot
but he was kind of weirdly flirty and
weird and and and and and yeah and so um
finally we arrived at the hotel and we
were like bye-bye
uh
and then and we checked into the hotel
and we had a nice talk with the
receptionist and receptionist was really
nice um
and i took a photo of her name oh let me
send that to rmt because i we took a
photo of the name so that we remember it
and then are able to um
like uh you know write a good review
about her because she was so sweet uh i
forgot to send the name to rmt like i
literally i i took out my phone and i
was like pointing it at her chest
because that's where the name tag was
and we all just started laughing
but she realizes that she has a
very difficult name
it's a name that's really hard to
remember because it's really difficult
to write it out you know
okay
she was not from here so she had like a
foreign very foreign name
um
and we talked and then oh we got like uh
some kind of uh upgrade because we're
cool and didn't really make use of the
upgrade but still uh and then
and then we checked into the room and we
chilled a little bit and i think and and
then and then
actually not much um we didn't chill
much i did my makeup and then i called
an uber and we went to the first
restaurant that i picked out i planned i
planned the restaurants i had auntie did
like she trav she planned to travel
roots and all that and i planned the
restaurant where we were going where
some places i went to before and some
places i didn't um so let me show you
let me show you let me show you sate
mission
we don't have young ki niko anywhere in
austria i think like typical japanese
yakiniku
um
and and i heard about this place before
in dusseldorf and and i kind of wanted
to go before when i was there for dokomi
but they were all like fully booked and
so on um
and and it looked already really
authentic from the outside uh both like
pretty much all of the japanese
restaurants in in dusseldorf are really
um being um
or
run run by japanese people so it's
really authentic and and and then and
then i i was ordering the meat so i
ordered let me show you
i was like arm tea you're gonna love
this i miss yakiniku they even gave us
you know those little aprons because if
you go to yakiniku um you're gonna take
a lot of the smell
with you
uh in your clothes like it's really it
really
like um
it enters the fabric of your clothes
this place was really proper they had a
big menu with lots of meat lots of uh
wagyu and oops that's the wrong picture
on the same picture uh and here it is
and they wrote they write everything in
japanese and german and so that was nice
of them there there's a lot of japanese
people living in dusseldorf so it's it's
good for them to also have the japanese
uh writing there so we have a
karubi and rosa
and carlo bean i really like carduby
many many kadu beans
[Laughter]
and good stuff so we started out with
this
and
[Music]
we started out like that
and then
i also ordered some
garlic rice which was cool like it came
in a really hot
bowl and and the guy he kind of um
prepared it in front of us like he was
like
smooshing the rice while it was still
you cooking basically
grilling
and then and then i i also ordered a
salad because of course of course you
gotta have a salad because because if
you only only eat the
uh the meat it's just you need something
to change the
um the taste in your mouth every once in
a while
and then um after eating that big plate
of meat uh i ordered another one
cause we didn't have uh
harami this is harami we didn't have
harami at on that plate
and this was so good i think my um rnt
said she liked the marinated ones the
most
um
i liked them all but yeah the marinated
ones are really good so this is like
this was like five no this was
seven pieces wait let me see i took a
photo of them on the grill
i was five pieces so we had to share one
piece
because of course it has to be even when
you eat yakiniku no no there's there is
no nothing like oh you can have that one
no no it has to be evenly shared because
the meat is so [\h__\h] good and
it is a little bit expensive especially
considering that it's um
yakiniku um
outside of japan so they charge a bit
more than if you would eat it in japan
i know
[Music]
the good stuff the good stuff man
yeah it was fascinating um for rmt um i
don't think she ever
had like i mean we like to grill
barbecue whatever in our country but
this is special
and you know it was really cute like in
the restaurant there was um
and there was this like family with a
little little baby girl um like a
toddler
and and and she was like hanging around
her mommy's arms the whole time and like
going like
and then
once our eyes met one time she kept on
waving at me and it was so cute because
i kept on raving back and then five
seconds later she would like happily
with a smile wave at me again and i
would wave back again but she kept on
initiating initiating it it was so cute
and for a while i would focus on eating
and i would look back at her and she
would wave at me and she would laugh and
be like
and i went way back
it was so cute and the mom noticed of
course and she was also laughing and and
like oh look at her look at her
pointing at me yeah it was really
adorable
and and and and and i talked in japanese
to the staff and they were
impressed but
even though my japanese was kind of
um
uh yeah
getting a little bit rusty
um
stop someone
getting rusty oh and then and then we
had a dessert uh i liked the
the choice of desserts that they had
uh
this was this was the dessert it was uh
tomato
and rare cheese i don't think you
actually say rare cheese in english do
you
they say they are cheese
in japanese but do you say that in
english
yeah it's like a cheese cheesecake cream
um
uh
yeah
with matcha on the bottom matcha cream
on the bottom and then some berries and
cookie crumbles cookie crown balls
mmm
so so so honestly
it was called rare cheese rare cheese in
japanese they used an english word in
japanese to describe it but i think it's
not how you would say it in actual
english
um anyway it was yummy it was yummy
yummy yummy i was so happy to eat jackie
nicole again cause i like the the whole
grill grilling it yourself aspect of it
um unfortunately they ran out of chateau
bruno i wanted to eat that again i ate
that once before it was [\h__\h] amazing
it's a very very specific part of um
the
of of beef of the body
um it's very specific part or fillet
part that is really really really really
nice
um
sounds french yeah the name is french
chateau
bryan or something like that
c-h-a-t-e-e-u
[Music]
and then b-r-i-a-n-d
t-e-a
check if they have that because it's
really good
um
good stuff good stuff
so yeah and then we left the the
restaurant happily
ever after
and it was it was cold but we took an
uber and we drove back to the um hotel
actually rmt was so [\h__\h] tired
because she at that point she hadn't
slept for like
oh about 24 hours
um
due to work and stuff like she was busy
so we uh went to bed quite early or at
least she did and and i was watching the
netflix and then yeah first evening done
those and now we do the cave
now we do the cave and then later i tell
you more
ah she was fine she at least she drinks
coffee um and that helps her i don't
drink coffee so when i don't sleep i'm
kind of [\h__\h]
when did you record the
the video oh i recorded the voicing for
it before i got the video itself um last
week on
friday
or
yeah something like that it was kind of
last minute this one that's why this one
was kind of shorter
uh
wait a second
there we go okay
oh can you
can you like um if you have a torch can
you turn on this little candle
that would be a nice detail
i do have a torch i could try
maybe you guys know no oh okay
oh there's another one it would be so
nice if you could do that
he would scare out a nine a girl
is that a wolf from far away i thought
it was a cat
oh [\h__\h] okay
okay i hope this is gonna be as easy as
the other one was
the wolves [\h__\h] killed the night holy
[\h__\h] did they come too late
is the party over here
sorry that's actually good that i missed
because they would have heard that
probably if i break that or would they
wait i can't
oh they heard me now well they heard me
now oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
he's so big he's so big he's so big
oh [\h__\h]
i think i can use it for crafting
um those thingies that you can throw
there we go
okay
okay okay boss
like kate moss
[Music]
scary scary scary it's cool
okay okay
okay
me or senpai no don't hurt me me or
senpai please uh
um
anyway we went uh we slept and now we
went for breakfast and the next morning
mmm breakfast yum yum yum yum yum
and
then
uh
the first thing oh yeah right we went
back into the room and chilled a little
bit because honestly i planned like a
lot of places where we should eat food
but
i didn't really plan
for activities in between
so in between
there were sometimes when we were a
little bit bored um
so we um went back into the room after
breakfast and watched some tv which is
which was kind of funny in itself
because i haven't watched actual tv in
such a long time
um so i found it to be interesting
to see what's um happening even the
commercials were interesting to me to
just to see what's being advertised
recently
um
and uh
yeah then um
the the both the yakiniku place and the
place that we went to on the uh
second day
uh for lunch were places that i haven't
been to before
oh wait that's a boss there's a boss
again isn't it is it a big wolf
i can't summon anyone here can i
wait wait this is a bigger boston isn't
it cause this mist is different than the
other thing
yeah
i need to concentrate now okay okay okay
okay but but let me just tell you let me
just tell you wha what we ate for lunch
for lunch for lunch
uh i thought because
we wouldn't have so much time until
um dinner there should be something
that's a bit more light-weighted
and it's easy okay okay
something that's a little bit more
lightweighted
and
so i chose a soba place
and but i kind of already
uh guessed um that
rmt
probably
wouldn't i mean she probably wouldn't
dislike it but probably wouldn't like
classical soba that much like just with
the
just the cold soba for example
um it's it's very very simple so i
recommend it to her to eat uh
this
uh curry version of it that they
[Music]
but it was so good because it was like
um like a soupy a soupy curry it was so
hot and warm and and really spicy
actually so both of our noses were
running and running and running
now the kickoff
and and actually we were both really
slow at eating because we don't
slurp the food so the noodles ended up
being pretty soggy at some point
so
it is true you should eat your noodles
quicker
but it was so good the curry mmm
japanese curry i feel like this was
perfect because um one one restaurant uh
one one cuisine that i didn't plan for
us to eat was curry a japanese curry
because i thought we could eat more
special things than that even though i
love curry japanese curry
but i did want her to experience it so
it was a combination of soba which which
she never ate before and curry japanese
curry which she also never ate before a
good combination two birds with one
stone you know what i'm talking about
you know what i'm talking about talking
about
um
it's
she liked it yeah i told her that like i
wasn't sure if she would like it because
i remember when i first ate japanese
curry i didn't like it now i love it but
back then i didn't like it
um
she actually
please please don't be mad but i have a
really small stomach and um i didn't
quite finish my food even though i
really enjoyed it um but she did she
finished her food
it was a huge you don't even see it here
but it was a huge amount of noodles
it was a huge amount of noodles and
not much time has passed since our
breakfast
so
i was not that hungry and i have a small
uh stomach in general
that those are a lot of soba noodles you
have no idea
damn but it was really good and uh it
was a small small relatively small place
um but it felt like
cold still it felt cool it felt like
familia not familiar but i don't know it
felt like the smallness of it made it
feel kind of cozy
um
[Music]
stomach understandable thank you
did she end up eating leftovers no no
she was absolutely overfilled over
killed
herself so
yeah but it was really good i i it made
me wanna um it made me wanna try making
a
soup japanese soup curry at home as well
with my curry cubes that i have
anyway
let's kill the boss and then i'll tell
you more
ah cow carrot be like this [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
can't you just tell one tangent at once
please
oh i shall
i'm scared i'm scared i'm gone
basement basement
okay
[Music]
uh
oh
i'm focused sorry guys
okay someone out i forgot but you know
what we're gonna do it without summoning
no give me some time to no please please
okay
talisman
flame drake talisman
[Applause]
well return tensions but there's so is
there again is there uh more
is that where it came from
what is that
nice jump dodgy i don't know why but
today i've been jumping
uh in order to dodge because i felt like
that's where i need to roll i thought
that was the button so automatically
press jumping all the time
even though that's not it okay no that's
really the end of it apparently okay
okay
it worked out yeah for his hits it
actually worked quite well because he
was trying to sweep my feet away
uh he can't do that
mama mama mama
it does work and yeah it saves actually
it saves time rowing takes more time
than jumping
and it takes no stamina maybe i should
jump more often
hello
you know the sound
um in in the woods here when there's
like a horn or something that goes like
you know what that reminds me of it
reminds me so much of world of warcraft
stormwind
i think
i think that's what it reminds me of
so much you know what i mean
how's my maiden oh no i'm the maid in
here
oh
kill him
yummy blood
oh oh hello
wild boar
ah more more blood give me exp
give me how do you not notice that i'm
walking right at you
yokumo kizuka nina
oh hello
oh hello you
let me kill you too
i hear sparkle
yeah sounds probably just thinks i'm a
turtle yeah cause it was my turtle shell
oh wait it's up there
the sparkling sound is up here somewhere
is it
oh no it's there
[\h__\h]
[Music]
no no they think i'm a turtle and you
know what maybe i am a turtle
maybe i am so what where are we now
we did that one we did that one we're
gonna do the next one which is
somewhere here i think
somewhere there should be another cave
in the lake
noise
get me those golden ruins thank you
you attacked me really okay follow me
oh he was probably just protecting his
family
hello
coming for you
looking for berries
not today
no no no no
uh where's where's my light with my
light
okay here
ninja turtle
if you were to die would you want it to
be by my hands of course that's why you
signed up for kfb didn't you guys
what am i even asking is an obvious
question
what else would be the answer
absolutely of course right i know i know
sorry
[Music]
y'all remember when those burps will
always fly away from me i'm such a good
sneaker now that i can kill them before
they fly away
this was by the way an example of um how
you guys are going down
i wasn't i was doing it subconsciously
but it's a great example i guess
all right how do i how do i go there
damn it i have to walk around
i think i have to walk around
i missed your lucky birds next time i'll
get
you we'll get them next time
down here
what is what are those people over there
on the bonfire
they're burning people
they're burning others can i kill all of
them
i didn't expect that
um
thank you for killing them i guess that
was my goal you took away my job
i guess we're fighting you now
oh
i feel like i'm in the middle of game of
thrones y'all
drogo drogon
[Music]
okay i'm gonna slay a [\h__\h] dragon now
oh never mind i'm not sliding a dragon
the fire is no the fire's not one hit is
it i was just already at half
[Music]
think america
do i have a chance i feel like i have a
chance though
oh he's already here
can i can i get my body
are you feasting on my body
oh dear uh
oh god
uh where's where oh there it is
okay
where are you
burb
where is you
ah okay
wait i can summon
step by step which one is better this
one right
for this oh god run run run one
[Music]
oh
okay
[Music]
instantly kills my jelly
oh god three [\h__\h] off trace [\h__\h] off all
of you
i don't know if i can do this
it will take a lot of time and being
very careful
nice
she's she's
oh [\h__\h]
i missed i missed
yes
oh
okay
fire
phoenix versus dragon
eagle dog
easy
yo what a weakest dragon man
okay let's go dragon oh but probably
phase two and so on will probably be
really tough i can see it
catch me if you can
i'm here
damn it
he was about to take off i saw it though
hmm
oh
i can take his head now oh wait there's
several parts
i didn't realize i could take the head i
ran right into it
can i go back on my horse
invincibility
i am too careless now
never face uh your back to the dragon
oh
oh [\h__\h] i was running so slow
now
oh
you can roll dodge his slam mm-hmm
nice try we're going to like to 50 do
you guys think i can do it
more like migraine i said that before i
think
where is body
i think where is dragon oh here's dragon
easy
easy it feels so impossible one one
thing i was thinking about eldon ring is
how like
um
uh
the enemies even like right in the
beginning of the game like honestly it
doesn't matter where like at any given
point of the game
the enemies are huge like there's so
many huge
giant enemies
that if you're not used to these kind of
games so like me
you're like
you wouldn't expect to be able
to kill them
oh
um because it just looks so
ridiculous like
no [\h__\h] way yeah
like i would never imagine that i would
be able to even do like some decent
damage on a dragon
it's crazy
hey what what what does that mean what
does that mean
where's summon steed because why why
why do i need
what
my horse died oh
yeah
that never happened before
jellyfish still alive i'm surprised
no no no [\h__\h]
dragon
it's getting hot in here so take a bow
i am feeling so hot i'm gonna jump off
my horse
i don't know if i know if i want to
waste all my time today on this one uh
where is that dungeon let's try to get
to the dungeon after getting my body
where where is it i need to find a plan
there it is okay
first get body then get dungeon
then get good
oh
body body buddy
all kind of
is like right on it
[Applause]
[Music]
hi uncle hi i'm cool bye bye dragon i'll
kill you one day
you can stop the
godly music now
you can stop it now
oh it's one of these elevators again
kiwawa remembers how to use elevator
um
[Music]
no
dragon slay
one day it will be my name one day
we can do it
oh really close two two runes um less
than a three-run lesson i wouldn't have
been able to do it let's do strength
i think
what does dex do again dex makes me
faster
um
i think we need strength
we need strength
dex is damaged too that's from phosphate
okay let's do strength for now
strength strength
um
anything else no
good we used up our
uh our runes so we're good to go oh
this isn't mine
and they're mining
they're just mining and minding their
own business huh
okay
oh
wait what if i what happens if i just
kill him
will the others be uh
thankful
oh no
no no no
hmm
i can't walk oh well i guess i can fall
down
hoping there's nothing here
let's attack him from behind
oh
hi
what happens now
sorry sorry sorry sorry what happens now
you're free i think no
okay
am i supposed to the madness won't mind
you oh
not even the leader
oh
okay
[Music]
i'll go this way first
well
well he cares he cares
oh oh oh you do care
yo i like your weapon
no [\h__\h] rats
oh [\h__\h] oh oh oh oh my [\h__\h] rats i
hate them
[\h__\h] bastard rats
i hate them they got me before in a
totally different place
um
they got me out of nowhere i was
surprised
so the the ones that are mining they
don't care
but the ones that are not mining they
might care and have one or two things to
say hello
i'll get the first hit
stupid rats
[Applause]
[\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you
[\h__\h] you
[\h__\h]
[Music]
what is this
you can roll the center quickly oh
really
oh i was a dead end
okay good that i went here before before
going the other way
beethoven go man i think bae wouldn't
like these ones either though i think
you would agree with me she doesn't see
these people as family i'm pretty sure
about it
another elevator are we going deeper
oh yes apparently we are going deeper
was i supposed to jump there
deeper and deeper and deeper
is there a secret there
well i don't care enough right now
oh [\h__\h]
dog
how many
okay nice
large glintstone scrap
what
what's going on
here i am
and they are so like
i don't know
focused on their work that they notice
nothing what's going on around them
it's kind of freaky um
is there something there
no
okay
huh what's there
nothing
okay
nice work ethic i don't know man
i don't know
dead end oh no i don't have to go higher
huh
this is this level is now a dead end but
i have to go
the one floor higher that we skipped one
going down
there's mats on the miners oh
i don't know
i feel sorry but
not really
smoothing stuff oh yeah we do need those
smithing stones
ah
all right i gotta start killing them
there's your boss on this level you mean
on this
height of the cave
my hair whispers
no
okay
jump off what you're also on the jump of
not ah
[Music]
okay
so we're going one up
uh
i guess
am i looking the right way
oh god wait i'm not am i [\h__\h]
is that it did it stop properly when
um is it stopping or i wanted to stop
or is this where i came from
that looks like where it came from okay
i missed it
is it this way am i looking this way
we're this way
maybe this way
[\h__\h]
hello
parkour this is called parkour guys
nice parkour
are you gonna turn around yeah
okay
[Music]
time to take you down
it's the end of your shift oh it's
called
buddy
you can go home now
honestly you guys look like you're
literally dead anyway so
home is heaven for you
or yeah this is hell
i think you should go to heaven and i'm
giving you the ticket for that
the entrance ticket am i nice or what
i think i'm nice
can we go home too no i
hey you missed me didn't you be honest
you missed me i was gone for three days
you should be happy
oh he called his buddies ow
i didn't know they were able to do that
when they noticed me before me killing
them
i missed you guys too
i wasn't so active this time on twitter
because i didn't know what to say
without spoiling what i'm doing you know
i didn't want you guys to know because
also just considering my safety um i
didn't want you guys to know that i'm in
dusseldorf
if i said i was eating japanese food i
feel like it would have been kind of
um it could have been obvious um
so i was trying to
keep it secret until afterwards uh where
did i come from
we came from there okay
we're going down the wrap now
it's like a dungeon crawler now
oh oh
is that boston
no
it's something
behind there something big
oh yeah there's something big there
eh
but i have one
really
oh
free flasks i wonder if free flasks will
be enough
no summoning and no friend either so it
must be a weak one right
[Music]
or summoning us afterwards maybe
we have the
time to learn how to fight yeah
refill
you can summon inside
okay
never right it was a week one early
edocio
somebody wants to enter
ah
is there more than one
i think i only see one
uh quite
there's a statue here you'll sprawl not
before okay
hello
where are we going to spawn maybe wolves
yes since the wolves
oh god oh god
easy
easy peasy lemon squeezy
wow
big book
be careful we're about to kill him
yeah baby
[Music]
is that his golden poop
[Laughter]
that was fun
that was fun okay we're done there's
nothing else right return
and you guys scared me your guys were
like get back and go go back to the
grace and get your flasks i was like
yeah
then he must be strong
check out what he dropped what did he
drop uh
i had the the the the something
something something what was it i
literally already forgot
what did he drop
daniel
medallion where are the medallions
here enhances rounds and breath attacks
i don't
i don't use that huh
i remember that i have that though and
also this one boots boost fire damage
negation
uh explain please jack
is this so that fire damage won't hit me
much
resistance
how do i use uh i'm using this one right
now and that's the final head of
training ah
i'll keep this one for now because i
don't have many enemies that fight me
with fire if i fight the dragon again i
could use that
how's dragon doing is he just gonna
chill there for now
uh he's just surviving chilling there
that's cute though
that's cute
you're welcome to chill there it's in
your home
cooling off in in the little
swamp is your swamp no that's okay
it's your swamp there's no donkey here
but um
[Music]
if i find a donkey i'll send it to you
okay and you can marry the donkey
uh i can equip two
huh
oh
ah i do have two slots okay
all right
uh
okay we did those three caves now
don't
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] okay i guess we're doing
we're doing
i'm doing the jump scare goblin
one
[Music]
when i first came here
that won't change my reaction to jump
scares
but it might change um
at least my my fighting skills
okay
i know there's one over there
but i feel like if i'm gonna
i'm probably gonna end up losing
my 2 800
uh runes here
um
level up first no i don't 2 800 is not
enough for a level up
wait there was two i've only remembered
one
mommy you picky skull boys and i got
them
[\h__\h]
i sake
remembered one of them
oh man
my heart
very donkey donkey
go there i see you
on every an arrow would be nice man
all right come here fight me
okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay i mean i know this part
so i know it's coming so for now we're
fine i don't know about later though
isn't this annoying dungeon
oh i didn't think i was the only one who
thought this was the annoying dungeon
this is where the fire starts so
i'm
pretty worried and and also we get an
enemy attacking us here too i remember
that and that's where it ends that's
where i'm like out of
like come at me come at me oh there you
are ah that's where you came from come
here
come down here
calm down
i got the first hit
okay
well
is this dungeon
long
no i finally know where that one came
from
i can shoot the fire thing to stop it oh
no it's not okay
but wait um the thing is it's a one-hit
kill
i don't
i don't think i had did i have
i have one can i use it do i have arrows
i don't have arrows do i [\h__\h] i don't
have a rose
ah
i don't have arrows
a shield
i do
oh i can try to craft again
um can i hit him with the bone darts too
ah i can't craft arrows yet
all production projectors okay cool
[Music]
15.
okay what exactly am i aiming for the
middle where the fire comes out
i forgot how to use them
uh
[\h__\h] i don't know how to use them
i don't want to waste them
it's too far
but i can't i can't i can't like uh
part targeted
and does the fire have to be gone for me
to do that
damn it i can't
[Music]
i do have arrows
i have bolts
and great arrows which don't work with
the bow that i have
okay we're just gonna run
oh
[Music]
i want to give myself some time
i'm so
so stupid i'm so stupid i'm so stupid
yeah i was trying to run but i i pushed
it like so that it makes me roll why is
it on the same button what the hell
oh [\h__\h] go back
is there is that one of those [\h__\h] up
here again
probably
okay
surprise attack don't go
no surprise attack really you're sure
about that
i saw that coming
they get me every time
[Music]
wait if my body is there i can i can it
will be spawned up at the top right
i hate them
i hate them i hate them so much
ignore
[Music]
can i just run through
i wonder
yeah
now they're all just gonna come here
[\h__\h] i shouldn't do that
[Music]
goodbye two thousand or three thousand
runes
it was a bad idea
i wanted to run for but then the other
one would start to and i would probably
i would probably i thought
i would die but then i died anyway
[Music]
that's okay yeah it's only three giant
guys no problem thank you for saying
that it's true
it's true it's just a couple
couple big boys to kill
no problem okay i'm gonna kill you
before
wait is this where i died
up there
did i like
kind of circle it
[Music]
grave violet
i'm i'm trying to use my shield
sometimes but i think like um
yeah i use it in between hits and he
doesn't have enough time to my character
doesn't have enough time to put up the
shield
so slow
like i'm pushing l1 a lot but you guys
just
don't
don't see it
hi
[Music]
yeah yup
calm down
and why do you get the first hit now
no i'm holding in two
anyway
anyway anyway
go go go go go go go go go
okay
back to where we left off
mm-hmm
not this time
so how are you gonna get back up huh how
tell me how
wait a second can i
am i safe right now
cause i feel like the sound was uh weird
oh is that just a game
i don't know
take the flowers great oh what does it
do
i hope that [\h__\h] goblin gremlim is
gonna
come back at me
and and uh repay me take revenge for
what i just did
oh
oh oh oh oh oh
okay
wondering oh wait is that the end of it
what
wandering noble ashes is that a salmon
is that a summon
i look like a salmon thingy
that's the end of the dungeon
i thought that would be a bus
at the end just loot oh okay okay okay
where did i not go
ah there's still that door right can i
uh was it here
wait how do i get to the door is it down
below
am i supposed to jump here
boss is for the door oh can i go for
that one now
if i
[Music]
was this
where is that buddy now where is that
where is he where is he where is he
ah
you
were doing camouflage thinking i
wouldn't see you no no no okay i pull
the lever
it opens the door ah
all right
and does the bus come out or do i have
to go in
i have to go in
where did you come from i was here
before you weren't there i know wait i
guess you're the one that fell down and
the one up there was uh still there from
like before huh
okay when you'll think you're safe but
you're not
is the door gonna stay open when i die
huh
wrong way
i just noticed
that's it
hello
scared
thank you
it
left all right
and i should get back and go my get my
flasks because at least here it's pretty
close no
wait no what
would it wait
or wrong huh i thought
i thought this was where the door was
worth so confused
what ah this is where the door was okay
okay now now i am able to orientate to
myself again
but i'm going this way anyway because
because i want to get my flasks
oh but then the enemies will respawn
never mind don't mind never mind never
mind
ah
although
only the ones i only meet the ones that
are there right at the door
i won't face them anyway right yeah okay
okay
yeah actually yeah there are no enemies
there
okay
door is still open
i'm going in guys i'm going in
but i need to
turn on the lantern again oh i see the
i see the
hmm
what
you see it
all right let's see how kiwa will do
this
[Music]
am i time ready for this
yes i am
what the [\h__\h] is that
what is that is it a cat
what the [\h__\h] are you
good that i have my fire thingy
what a funny looking enemy
oh but so easy holy [\h__\h]
oh
[Music]
i thought it would be stronger it looked
funny though
and what the [\h__\h] is that
so sorry ashes okay but what the hell is
that man
disgusting
oh well
we did the cave that i never wanted to
go back into
successfully
yes kind of grim you're saying this is
kinda grim this is more than just kinda
grim it's very very very very [\h__\h]
grim
anyway we did it hallelujah
that was four four caves five caves
four five
i think that was five caves that i did
oh
they're um shorter than i thought they
would be i thought they would be like i
don't know diablo two dungeons length
capes length um
um all right which i guess they're also
not that long but still eh i want to
look at the new summons uh how do i
place them in the pouch again here
um
ah
let's say
what's what's memory of grace again
who's that again
oh why would i do that why is that even
there
no
wait one second let me kill him fight
dragon
it
do you think i have a chance
it's useless okay okay okay
um
so let's say we replace that oopsie [\h__\h]
we replaced that with but how do i do it
again remove
uh switch
uh
you got it to half dragon is easy
okay we can try we can try
what am i doing
here we got uh two new ones
someone's five wandering noble spirits
someone's noble social spirit which one
is better are they even useful at all
this one is really cheap
so i guess you could summon it more than
once because it's so cheap both useless
both pretty mad uh vote for junk oh okay
no no
no uh
okay then i guess we don't even need to
put them in there
maybe we'll look at it once but
yeah
okay
then in that case i
will
go
to
dragon
again
wait where am i
where did it go this is where the dragon
was no no wait it was here
wrong place
somewhere here
uh
yes oh no oh
oh
we're going up
level up
uh i don't have enough to level up
don't have enough
you sure
okay
let's see how far we can get i will have
to focus though
what do you think is better wolves or
jelly because jelly dies fast
wolf's probably gonna die fast too but
at least there's free targets and
they're going to run around and
jelly wolves
will also die pretty fast too
hot
jelly better more health okay
okay
what is that
try again
we're fighting the dragon
once again
equivalent
oh my battery level is low
[Music]
how much longer does it work if it says
battery level is low
[Music]
oh you're burning all that beautiful
grass and my jellyfish
oh god oh you're using a lot of fire
stuff
[Music]
okay
again he's like spamming it is it
because i'm too far away
okay okay oh he's cleaning the area so
it's easier to fight
oh again again
stop it what the [\h__\h]
no more fire
oh god oh god
okay
okay okay so far so good we did some
damage
i was too slow
ah [\h__\h]
okay okay
[Music]
oh nice nice it's like a shield for
me dangerous things game i wanted to hit
his head
but
um difficult difficult target
okay bye bye bye bye bye bye
for him this is probably just a little
game
just playing around a little bit
wow okay first hit
go for it go for it go for it
has anyone ever tried uh slaying a
dragon without the horse
just on foot
i feel like that would be funny
definitely somewhere someone did it
before
no i wasn't fine
oh i wasn't even asking if if whole life
members tried doing it is that is it
easier it's easier with the horse no is
it
i'm pretty sure it should be easier with
the hoist
no i understand was pretty amazing man
with this game
dragon burnt ruins uh yup that's exactly
what it
is i'm coming for you
[Music]
you thought i was leaving huh
i'm not done
i'm not done with you
yeah i already used a lot of flasks
my first run was pretty damn good man
more fire more fire
more fire
[Music]
we're so far away from where we started
this battle
let me get closer to you oh
[Music]
okay don't be scared just go for it yeah
oh guys i knew it i knew it
no more flasks i don't think i can do it
i don't think i can do it
oh
oh i knew i knew i knew you were gonna
do that
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
she's
[Music]
did he just reset
did he just
don't tell me
he didn't
he reset his location i guess we can't
lead him too far
astray gonna die anyway though
i don't have enough health
damage
hp
[Music]
yay how do you dodge that when you're on
a horse jump
maybe i can do it
[Music]
okay bye-bye see you later alligator
you can't turn his neck that far he's
not an owl
oh wait maybe
maybe we
can do it
run run run run
run faster
try me
i did it right what's up
what
i did hit him
hey yo
hey yo i'm so sorry dragon queen
i'm so sorry and yo but you were too
crazy someone's gonna take down your
dragons otherwise you're gonna take down
the world i'm sorry dragon lady i'm
sorry
oh yeah
nice job we didn't have flasks for a
long time at the end but
yeah it still worked out because i
believed
i believed i can kill i believe that i
can kill the dragon
that's all you gotta do
yeah
level up hell yeah
six thousand nine hundred
we're gonna go
to the island because now i have a
dragon light um
apparently i can learn
some
power now some new power
first of all we level up we do
[Music]
let's get to 20 here
and then we're gonna do strength and
decks soon
ah no no no no oh [\h__\h] i cancelled it
i'm stupid
wait how hot
okay
need faith
oh for the dragon skill
how much
faith do we need
i can't get it now but
um
soon
13 14 20 13 okay okay i'll work on that
i'll work on that
but is it even worth it because i'm not
really i guess i'm not um
building like a magic type of character
it's kind of i mean i wouldn't mind
doing that but i feel like we're focused
on
sword fighting or base fighting at the
moment not mace
star
uh thingy yeah
i can do a mix hybrid
does that work well
but i can still get the skill now right
or do i also need it just to buy it or
whatever is happening there
crafting or whatever
wait that's just
just now i realize this is the shape of
a dragon
and this is the head i didn't i thought
i didn't know what it was i thought it
was like
oh no
i didn't see it until now
i can't buy it okay
works well
oh
wait
can i buy it dragonfire dragon claw
dragon mall
channel's dragon to bite foes before
caster
uh these ones need this ones need uh 24
and 16. this one's 1713. uh-huh
this one is the cheapest one in terms of
attributes
spew flame breath let's do it
it's vine owned my own
i have dragon skill now but i am lacking
the power to use it oh hello jellyfish
friend
hello
you
[Music]
cute pretty
you're cute
cute floaty
i'll kill more dragons later really i
thought it was so special like
damn a dragon enemy
felt like something really really
special
mm-hmm
there are a few more they are special
okay
let me tell you a bit more about my trip
before we continue okay
a bit more
a little little break a little story
time break
it
up
where where did i stop so we ate nico oh
and then we ate on the next day we ate
soba
mm-hmm
uh all right oh yeah after that uh we
walked around in dusseldorf in that that
street that has most of the japanese
stores
and most of the japanese restaurants
it's like mostly on one street that's
actually uh
like leading or
going away directly from the
main train station in dusseldorf
it's called imam strasse yeah yeah
so after eating the soba um we went into
some shops because there are like some
japanese supermarkets as well not asian
but specifically japanese supermarkets
um it went in a few of those and looked
what they had uh we bought ramune i uh i
like ramone i showed rmt what ramune is
she liked it
she liked it yeah yeah
um
we had fun opening it up
i thought it would be a nice idea to
show her that one there because that one
has a fun way of opening the bottle
where you gotta push
with all your power all you might you're
gonna push down like a little little
glass bowl
through the top of the bottle so that
you can drink
who is auntie she used to be my roommate
i used to live with her that's rmt
roommate
um it's not that hard to push it i
always feel like it's pretty difficult
pretty
pretty tough uh
yeah there's a glass orb inside yeah
yeah yeah
um oh yeah her room made much density
much dance
and
yeah and then uh we went into some shops
and then yeah we just went for a lot of
shops drinking ramen oh no wait that's
not it that's not all that's not all of
it oh yeah yeah yeah
you know what i did then i showed her
um the location of where dokomi happens
every year it has like this huge huge
huge crazy huge big park
and
it's called north park and park of the
north
and it's it's like right next to the
venue where dokomi always happens and
usually every year
when dokomi happens people are not only
inside the venues but they're also like
at the huge park next to it and it's not
just a normal park it's crazy it has
like a japanese garden in it and it has
like big big fountains and all that it
has like a little tiny baby lake not
really a lake um
but yeah it's a really cool cool chill
area with beautiful photo spots
yeah
that's that's where the party happens
people like to chill there at the park
so
uh i i showed her the place and
and it's it was um so empty which was
really nice it was a nice park walk walk
for the park with rmt
um and i told her oh this is where me
and my friends like to hang out during
the convention we used to chill here we
would put a blanket here and and oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah we would walk around and
every five steps there would be someone
we know and then they would be like
hello and we'll be like oh wow and then
we will continue walking after a little
chit chat and then after five meters the
next person comes across us so we never
get to the point where we actually want
to go or at least it takes us a long
long long time
we were we were also bird watching there
were some interesting
yeah there were some birds bathing in
some water geese yeah there were some
cool geese oh yeah right there was a
canadian geese we looked it up
me and our team were using a google
photo lens to uh figure out what animals
and what flowers we were seeing and uh
google was really useful
canadian games and they were pretty i
was looking at them bathing it was so
cute they were like bathing their little
heads in the water and then their little
butts
um
i loved watching at them okay then
connecting this can be annoying
oh wait i feel like i heard about that
before was it canadian geese that were
the the annoying ones
eh
they were totally chill
there
i might show you a photo or a video
later on not today but like on twitter
or something
i was really fascinated they were so
cute
so i showed her around and we walked
through the park we saw some baby baby
bunnies hopping around in uh like in the
distance
yeah when there's not a million of
people there because they're going to
document and the park is really empty
and then there's like bunnies hopping
around and geese
bathing in the water and so on it's
pretty chill and and relaxing
and some things were already some
flowers and some trees and so on we're
already um
uh
what's the word they were already
[Music]
uh
that's the word i forgot blooming yes
blooming
but uh it was still a little bit too
early but i saw that uh the photo that i
uploaded uh with the
the ume the ume tree i think it's
plum
not plum
but something similar to a sakura cherry
blossom tree it it blooms earlier than
the
um
cherry blossom trees and a lot of people
mistake them for
uh sakura trees cherry blossom trees
when they see them because they do look
similar but they're i guess in general
you could say
that the plum trees are
have way
wider
wider whiter
uh
blossoms flowers
than the sakura trees do the sakura
trees are a bit more pinkish although
there i saw some pretty
white ones before too but generally if
you see a white
uh
blossoming tree
that look like sakura it's probably if
it's only one and it's like blooming
pretty early then it's probably a plum
tree
i i mistook them for cherry blossom a
lot myself
[Music]
we took some nice photos of what we saw
and then later on later on in the
evening time it was finally time for my
beloved helicopter although we're
actually on after um after after our
walk in the park um it was getting
pretty cold and the sun went down and um
i called an uber to pick us up but he
was taking so much time
um and and i was like trying to you know
shake the coldness out of my body so
i turned on
gas gaskets
while looking at my uber app hoping for
him to come faster
yeah that was funny we were listening to
gas gas gas
and i was dancing actually and then some
people some randos walked by me but i
just continued to dance and rmt was
chuckling and giggling at me
just dancing to gas gas gas while people
were looking at me
i was vibing hell yeah
i'm gonna step on the gas exactly
that's the spirit
yeah power move yeah
yeah and then after we listen to that i
i um
i showed rmt a german rap song from many
years ago
that you guys don't know either unless
you're german maybe
and unless you're a boomer
it's a really cringe rap song that i
remember
when we were in school like we made fun
of that song it was really ridiculous
um
it goes like
this
only
[Music]
uh it's really bad
who knows that oh god oh you know it
probably yeah yeah yeah
she didn't know it she didn't know the
song
so i showed her the cringe music video
the lyrics are so bad i should i should
show you guys a link but you guys are
not gonna understand how funny it is if
you don't know german
tekken
english
copy link address there you go
it has a lot of views because it kind of
turned into a meet me so i don't know
did they do
did they make it so ridiculous on
purpose or were they doing it seriously
i think
i think they were serious about the song
but it was it just turned into a
complete meme song
yeah unfortunately you probably won't
really understand why it's so funny
early youtube they were serious yeah
yeah
we were just always making fun of it
when when i was in school
240p quality let's go if this is a
german meme you're welcome i tell you
guys a german meme i don't know many of
your american memes and so on but here
is a german meme for you
uh 11 million views
yeah it's [\h__\h] ridiculous
[Laughter]
you guys need to look up the lyrics
maybe there's a translation somewhere
henna
yeah i guess it's like kind of like how
you know
i i like the song friday but
kind of like that but even worse much
much much worse than friday
cause like i feel like for rebecca with
friday she was a child and so on like
but these are grown ass man
these are grown ass man singing the most
ridiculous
cringe lyrics
in such a serious manner
with the cringiest video ever but i feel
like because this is so old and
really
um
boomerang youtube times
[Music]
a video like that like they really
thought they were cool when they were
doing that
um
just having the
having the power
the chance to do a video like that in
the first place
makes you think you're you can do
anything it's all looking cool on the
screen
yeah yeah i i don't i don't support
though
[\h__\h] that also she she makes really
great songs nowadays i think i listened
to one of her newest songs um a while
ago
uh it was really good
it was really good
hmm
the only youtube voice special yes
she still makes music she does i liked
her one of her recent songs i don't know
what it was called again uh
what is it called again
no sure why wait i think it was saturday
which is funny because you know it's
kind of like an answer to friday i guess
i think it was that one
or i'm not sure
[Music]
no maybe not i'm not sure which one i
listen to don't take uh what i just said
uh
i can't recognize those thumbnails at
all
anyway
anyway if you're interested you should
check it check out her songs
so then finally we got into the uber
uber driver was a weird guy again
again a talkative guy but as in like
i i got into the uber and i told him uh
that we're kind of about to be late
not really asking for him to uh go
faster faster but
i just kind of wanted to hint at it so
that maybe if he knew a shortcut or so
he could maybe take a shortcut i don't
know you know i just wanted to hint at
it that we're like getting a tiny little
bit
late to our reservation
and then he was like
he was like
he said that he's never gonna go faster
ever again when an uber uh
guest
asks him to because once he did that he
drove people to their flight and
so that they wouldn't miss it he he was
like speeding and then he got taken uh
his his his uh license was taken away
from him because he was caught they got
on their flight but he was caught which
okay i understand you sh if you if this
is your job then you know
and you do it so many times a day
no no need for you know
speeding
and
breaking limits and [\h__\h]
but he kept on talking about yeah i'm
never gonna no no i'm not gonna
if someone asks me for that blah blah
blah you girls are fine but but no no no
this happens and i'm never going to lose
my [\h__\h] license ever again he was so
like i don't know
cynical it almost felt like cynical
yeah i opened the wound definitely i
poured some salt into that i opened the
door that i didn't want to open
uh it was kind of annoying yeah it
struck a nerve just by saying that we're
a little bit late
[Music]
that was annoying but eventually we
wrapped at the restaurant and and i
ordered
because it was on the menu oh
i ordered basically a dessert for
my drink
um
cream made on soda
which is made on soda with vanilla ice
cream inside of it you kind of like let
it melt in there and mix and it
basically
becomes kind of like milk shaky
mmm
but i was like
the vanilla ice cream was so good that i
couldn't hold myself back and i ate like
half of it before letting it melt in the
soda
yeah and then
and then
i saw
and then my beloved
my beloved
tongue
[Music]
i want to eat it again
it was so good and rmt really enjoyed it
too
juicy thick meat
with that yummy tonkatsu sauce
um i always order hirakatsu if it's
available
definitely always prefer it because
hirakata is like more fillet-ish
while
the the basic tonkatsu
has more like pieces of fat in it and i
don't like that
[Music]
i was eating so fast
uh and enjoying still enjoying every
single bite
i was in heaven i want to go back
but
guys
one sad thing that i was really really
sad about
i don't know if you guys remember me
mentioning this before
but this restaurant used to have
something on their dessert menu
that i ate before a couple years ago
when i went to dokomi
honey toast
honey
toast and you might be thinking what is
that
let me show you
i was looking forward to eating that
again
it is basically
um
a big chunk of toast
let me show you uh let me show you an
image
[Music]
it's a big chunk of
toast that is not cut uh
i like this one
i'm gonna show you this one
damn it why is everything saving as a
dot web page
not as images
jpegs
i need a [\h__\h] jpeg what the hell
okay how about this one
oh man what the hell
look what's happening
all right this this way it should work
i hate that yeah me too
oh where is it what
i just put it in here it's not here
no it saved his web page again
ah
it's okay rad you guys know what it
looks like right if you google honey
toast or honey toast japan then you will
see what it is
so they had that on the menu
but they took it off they took it off
like a while ago apparently i asked like
do you not serve honey toast anymore and
they were like if like the the girl that
i talked to she didn't even know like
they had honey toes so it must have been
taken off of the menu a while ago
you know i knew that it would be so
tough to eat because both the tonkatsu
and the honey toast would be so filling
that um
i i don't know how we would have eaten
all of that but i would have only
ordered one honey toast for us to share
and just somehow
somehow
filled my belly with it but they didn't
have it anymore they didn't have any
desserts at all anymore and to be honest
that's normal for tonkatsu place
normally a tonkatsu restaurant doesn't
have desserts to begin with the fact
that they had honey toast there was just
i guess a funny gimmick for them uh
as a restaurant outside of japan to
serve to serve any dessert at all
but they took out all of the desserts
make one at home that's what i was
thinking like i'm really craving honey
toast and now i'm thinking maybe i
should make it at home
i wonder if i can it's basically a big
chunk of bread
with i guess honey and
ice cream and fruit and
yeah
whipped cream
but oh it can't be that easy there is a
reason why why it's so yummy
um
[Music]
that's the entire loaf
i'll i'll try to
i'm sure there's like youtube videos
that explain how to make it i'll try to
look them up
and
japanese style milk bread or make it
maybe i'll buy a bread machine just for
that
i have to add the secret ingredient love
i have a lot of love for honey toast mmm
i wanted i wanted my rmt to eat it too
first and foremost i wanted to eat the
honey toast ah
sad
that was disappointing
but
it led to
a different
exciting
uh
happening
so we ate our tonkatsu and we were
pretty full but
uh
we were like we gotta eat a dessert
anyway now that i'm so disappointed
about them not having honey toast
anymore i want a different dessert so i
looked up um
where we could get a dessert close by
maybe something jab vernees related um
because we're here to eat japanese food
that was still open after we're done
eating and
i found something interesting that i
didn't
know they had in dusseldorf
so it's actually it was quite lucky
[Music]
there was a place there that had taiyaki
and it smelled so good there was quite
some waiting time because they were
pretty popular
um
but it smells oh it smelled through the
whole street man and it was so good and
there were different choices there were
like all kinds there were there was the
classic one with the red bean inside
there were matcha ones there were
nutella ones there were uh oreo ones i
think i got um my favorite vanilla
custard and oreo
to two different ones and uh rmt got
vanilla custard because i recommended it
and nutella so we brought it to the
hotel but we got that and we got them uh
to take away and quickly ubered to our
hotel and then we um made ourselves cozy
in the hotel watching some
late evening tv shows and eating the
taiyaki
and oh my god it was actually so good so
yeah it made up for the lack of honey
toast
so kawarini
it was great it was so yummy they were
still warm when we arrived to the hotel
still warm and fluffy have you guys ever
eaten tayaki
the name comes from thai the fish and
yaki is grilling and and they come in
these these shapes not because they
taste like fish just because they're
called taiyaki i actually don't know the
original reason where it came from but
never
i remember when i when i lived in japan
um
at some point i lived somewhere where
there was always like a little taiyaki
um
food truck outside a supermarket close
to me and i would always on my way home
i would go by the taiyaki place and i
would order one or two taiyaki's to take
home with me yeah so i have good
memories of taiyaki i love taiyaki hmm
it's yummy it's like a kind of like a
waffle and inside it's filled with uh
some kind of cream depending on what you
choose
[Music]
um yummy it was good made me happy
we were still craving taiyaki on the
following day we were walking through
dusseldorf to the main train station to
catch our train and for some reason over
the course of like
one kilometers even though we were like
very very very very very very far away
from the taiyaki place
we felt like we were smelling the
taiyaki even though it was impossible we
were probably just smelling some kind of
crepe or waffle place or something
but we were thinking we were smelling
the taiyaki and really craving it even
on the following day
yeah it was that good it was that good
so i if if i if i go to um drisseldorf
or dokomi again i want more taiyaki from
the taiyaki place
yeah if you go to dusseldorf you should
try them those are really yummy
they have other stuff too
there in that little cafe place
oh but yeah
yeah you see they they like make them in
this little
machine
and and they can make so many at once
and on the right side you see like the
the things that they cut off
of the taiyaki
the remains of their bodies
[Music]
i was so happy because everything i ate
there
really tasted the way it should taste in
japan
the remains yes
i was i was like
thinking yo you could give me those
remains i think i would like to snack on
those these those are basically just
waffles hmm
i wouldn't mind taking those remains
home
which kind
yeah
i would pay a little bit for those
waffle chunks
okay
okay now
uh
story time over
more on this later but i don't even feel
like playing anymore
i didn't play so long today but i i feel
accomplished and i don't want to play
more hmm i'm lazy
uh
is there any
any other small thing that we could do
we did i did kill the dragon i did
unbelievable huh
first try
oh yeah my controller my controller has
low battery oh well i have the cable
right next to me um
i should have connected it while i was
talking
also
uh
we should play a bit more i guess
[Music]
oh no control is running out oh no oh
how unfortunate
you could probably there were some
people telling me about the about the
uh
about the tree
because we didn't actually go there
maybe i should should i go there
[Music]
it
yeah we did a lot of little caves so i
think in theory it's fine
i saw that the other girls also mostly
did like ellen ring for three hours like
inna gouda ammo and
like free approximately three hour
streams
i probably don't have to feel too bad
about
uh
what show
doing shorter streams but you know when
i think of eldering i feel like uh it's
something that could be played for hours
and hours and hours
but i'm feeling lazy today
i guess it's all it's good to enjoy it
in small bites
small pieces but we're gonna go up here
and see what there is to see what is
that
[Music]
they don't have much hp don't worry
don't
worry in the train
oh there's more
ow wait i want to try something
well
yeah i wanted to try this i didn't hate
them at all
[\h__\h] the poison
i hate your weapons they're so big they
hit fox man [\h__\h] you
[Music]
[\h__\h] yeah
[\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you maybe i should just
get off my horse
oh what was that oh cause i killed the
group oh nice i got my flask back
i'm oh want to get off my horse
oh
is that the tree bus
no no the statue of marika
is ready
oh
need to heal though
okay
i can
which friend do we call
it looks like he's gonna turn around
and uh
immediately kill me
gently okay
i'm scared i'm scared
i'm scared
oh
miner l3 miner okay
we can deal with a miner l3 oh [\h__\h]
oh
holy moly
keep your distance kiwawa
don't hurt my jellyfish
ow oh they're not
nice weapon you got there man
whoa what's that whoa
oh holy [\h__\h]
not a hotel when his magic starts run
you kind of said that a little bit too
late
you said that too late
oh what's that over there is that just a
friend or he looks pretty big
is he big he looks big it's not that big
let me kill him before we start the
battle
i want my
exp by the way
i'm not planning on
just leaving them there
okay
still think you're gonna rock this bus
easily really
we will see
let me think
all right
go
already starting off bad
oh
my head
you killed my horse
damn
ow
okay horse dead now for real
[Music]
using mount is harder really
easy on foot really
okay
okay are you sure
you know who you're talking to
the one who cannot dodge
but okay
i will try can i sneak up on him
where's my body
oh
should be uh
i cannot sneak up where's my body
where's my body
i can't see my body
[Laughter]
where am i where the [\h__\h] am i where's
my body in
it
what are you called
here
you [\h__\h]
no what a [\h__\h] ridiculous run
i can't find it
[Applause]
i was looking at the conference it's
confusing
i hate it
[\h__\h] you
okay
what i hate you
i hate you
i know i don't know why i keep on
jumping today it's as if it used to be
um x um dodging
it feels like it used to be x
sometimes it works though
i see the body
ow
ah
i was better on my horse
i want to roll into him
ow i want to roll into him again
it doesn't work
okay okay okay
uh
[Laughter]
okay we we dodged the magic once uh
let's see where we go from here
it reminds me a little bit of margaret's
mortgage my judgement
he's in the face too now huh
oh [\h__\h] oh
why why why why why why
oh
if i wouldn't have rolled into that i
didn't see it coming
then i would still be alive now
it's okay
i need to go on an idol meeting but i
will kill him before that
uh body
uh
[Music]
hard to see now
ah i think i see it okay
oh [\h__\h] i forgot
oh
i thought he only did that a little bit
later okay
oh going well going well
nice ah
why you keep on missing
wow keep on missing
i saw that coming reacted a little bit
too late
ow
you bunked so hard
dangerous
did i get my body yeah okay
okay
jellies jelly goodbye rfp
oh i found him
so cocky so cocky i thought i thought
i'm
thought oh i wanted to get him to bleed
and i thought i had more hp that was
dangerous
not now
not now ah oh [\h__\h] yo give me time to
recover man give me [\h__\h] time to
recover ah i'm not again
just getting one hit
[Music]
it didn't give me time to recover man
every time i was ready to attack he
attacked me
wait did i get did my dead body take the
exp though
[Music]
what
yeah i did get the exp
the po
what i need to watch the
vod it's like a uh like uh on the
finishing line it must have happened
like literally what
the poison got him the moment he hit me
or what
it
that's funny i thought i had to do it
again
[Music]
nice during my death animation oh that
still counts uh-huh
that's funny when i hear a sparkle
i think yeah
the soyun
plot armor
that was very lucky of me
where is that oh
beetle um
you just reload flasks don't you
i don't really need that i literally
just died
oh
easy
[Music]
okay so we did that noise
another enemy has been failed
i hear singing
what
who is singing
is the game audio desync it shouldn't be
no
does it feel very decent
funk
who is what the [\h__\h] is singing
who is singing
sounds good okay
[Music]
who's singing
no i think it comes from down there
why
do i need to kill them
what it's so weird
it's poison dangerous oh it's a siren ah
harpies
oh
come down
wait i don't know i don't know the lore
about sirens anymore they sing and they
get you to
get lost at sea or something like that
what was it about sirens again
yeah they drown you oh
sounds fascinating
why is it uh burning here
oh because of the butterflies
i need to do a level up
i know like me what
no
how can you compare those two
oh yeah it would be cool to see a siren
reach a widow
oh wouldn't it be cool to name like um
to have a
b singer
be
like a siren character
that sounds interesting it would match
it would like kind of make sense i think
damn it i'm not playing soccer okay
v-sinker
because in syncs
she would sync her fans
and another one
yeah
how do you low hit
how do you low hit it
damn i guess you can roll over it okay
okay
yeah they need to implement low hits i
would appreciate that
let me go level up
cause i suppose we're kind of done here
let me kill this guy and then we're
gonna leave
to kill or to be killed that is the
question to kill
yeah yeah
you can see here all right going to
somewhere
[Music]
over the rainbow
i can't click buttons because
i don't know where they are located
sorry
all right level up another one let's do
one decks
i don't care about faith and arcane
right now
we good we're we're all in no hurry to
get that
to be able to use that dragon skill
whatever it's okay
um
oh wait maybe i can use
some more of my
golden
yeah
oops i should have used all of them
weapon upgrade ah i can try
wait didn't did they need runes for that
i feel good were runes necessary
yeah okay then i should not use all of
them uh um
then uh
let's go
to the table of lost grace
we have some smithing stones
don't be so scared
there's nothing to be scared of
maybe i'm more on edge because i um kind
of need to go to an adult meeting here
you are
yes yes
uh strength and armament
oh we can strengthen the shield because
we ah we did it once oh
won't you still plus three okay
smoothing stone yes do it okay is that
all i was able to do
oh what does that need for that
six oh four oh
[Music]
all right
all right and that's okay is that all i
was able to do
oh
nice effect back already no matter
what's this again
ashes
ashwin what's this again
ah
oh i can do that anywhere though
at the graces
okay i think i'm good
[Music]
not worth leveling shields what
not even the turtle shield
not you oh no not this woman
eh okay i'll remember that for next time
it gives more stability no most people
say it's not worth it i'll i'll trust
you on that one
it reduces how much stamina they use to
block
i mean that sounds good but
apparently still not worth it
only a real a chats of shields
oh
can i level up no almost
almost i want to get that last level up
uh
do i not have any big
runes
um
rune ruin fragment not ruin fragment
doesn't look like it
another giant
i don't know what else could we kill
i would try
this guy but i i don't believe in us
winning what do you think
i mean we've already felt so many great
other enemies
wouldn't he be a piece of cake and we
can even summon someone
let's try
do it okay
attacking
[Applause]
give me a break
[Music]
oh
oh my god bye bye jelly she she's strong
pushing lipstick with the money wasn't
[\h__\h] lipstick
what
nah not me
not me no no it couldn't be me it
couldn't be me
okay
try number
two
[Music]
[\h__\h]
what
how do i keep on doing that because
probably i'm i'm like
um
uh
like i'm just i'm not trying to push it
but i'm i'm going so far to the side of
the joystick that it takes it as a
as me pushing it in
yeah you know what i mean you know what
i mean ow
ow
[\h__\h] get out of here
[Music]
what if i do it on foot
am i at a disadvantage if i do it on
foot
i'm sure good players can do it well
maybe i can
[Music]
too early too early
aah
me
who's up for some
phoenix sashimi huh
add some soy sauce it might help or some
gravy to be honest replace that soy
sauce with some good old gravy
i don't give up
can i surprise him too
no not anymore
again
and when the jellyfish is still there
it's kind of tough to reach him ow for
[\h__\h] sake i hate you
hey
i got some good hits there though
oh too early drank too early could have
survived another hit probably
okay he seems to be a little bit at a
disadvantage right now
ow
you just stomp on me
i'm not into that
you're not my mommy
not saying that i want my mommy to stomp
on me but people say step on me mommy
and i don't i don't see you like that
blah blah blah try playing with other
controllers
what do you mean but i am running out of
um batteries and when i
attach it like now the cable is kind of
short
and i have to hold my controller to the
side let's see how it goes
all right we'll start on the horse and
then we'll switch
to
uh foot fight
[Music]
okay
i guess this is uh it for a horse battle
oh
[Music]
okay okay i'll go go go go
[\h__\h]
how did it hurt
oh i didn't see him coming i wasn't sure
what movie was doing man
oh interesting shield move
oh
i'm out of flash ah
it's not happening it's not happening
it's not happening
oh
okay at least i died close to the church
yeah
the shield bash is yeah oh hello kelly
what does kelly say that shield is yucky
yeah what the [\h__\h]
dodgy's on oh thank you
[Laughter]
man isn't that a pretty ah i guess it's
still
still a decent time over there
good evening m'lady um
i know it's optional it's a lot of the
things are optional in this game this is
not about it being optional
this is about getting exp
we start again
uh
wait no no no no no no no a little
mistake
go
let's start strong
yeah
i've got kelly's mental support now
i'm invincible
why are you both here
are you laying
in voice chat together
preparing for a collab oh wait what's
happening no it's not uno uno was last
night what's happening
what are you two doing here
sit i need to show them my cool side
i've been i've been pretty um
good today this is
me at my worst
[Music]
this is me and my worst okay don't don't
think that i'm really this bad i got
better okay
this dude is hard to figure out though
i want to stay on my horse for as long
as possible
[Music]
i think the horse took all of that
damage that's nice
very kind
ah
even one hit is a good start
oh he's really bullying my jelly
it's a rodeo baby
who falls off their horse first it's
probably gonna be me can we can we uh
keep kicking off his horse i wonder
it seems like if you do it if you fight
him the right way then you can do it
um
retreat
he's starting the shield bashes again
no
no i reject that i reject your offer
again
i think we're doing it this time i'm
getting i'm starting to get dizzy though
whoa
run run
these rocks are [\h__\h] annoying
yeah
okay we're doing this on the horse for
real now he's not
able to
get me off of it
what a loser
when i lose that
he still has five flasks yo what
yeah did he just bleed the [\h__\h]
we cast dumpling what a weak [\h__\h]
gyoza you are
how did i do that i didn't even hit them
so quickly so often
at once
i'm not there that's a tree
do i look like a tree to you
oh yeah baby
my heart just went really dunky donkey
man
i feel it thank you now thank you chad
oh i feel my doggie ducky i feel my
heartbeat oh
oh doki doki doki doki doki doki
damn all on the horse damn
damn yeah we found so many enemies today
dragons
uh trees
uh
big giants
i doubt it i'm sorry i kneel
you better
neil before me k of people
kneel before me
i'm in the bus rest yeah boss and k
fresh today
the tree sentinel mm-hmm
the wolf man oh yeah and the cat the cat
lady the cat's statue enemy
that was a weird one
i knew oh thank you thank you thank you
very much
uh did i actually just tried to kill him
to get some more exp now we have uh 7319
okay chicken i respect this are you guys
respecting me because i did it on the
horse and only used one flask yeah no
that was pretty amazing
[Laughter]
i was really controlled like i was being
careful oh but still aggressive
and did a good job at not getting hit
took me 40 tries wow
nice
all right success
game of moment
it was just probably the thought inside
of me of not wanting to look um weak and
embarrass myself in front of gouda and
kelly
strength
yeah baby
all right
i just wanted to experiment
okay
now
we will move to my office and read some
super chats and maybe i'll finish
telling my story or i'll keep some more
for tomorrow i'm not sure yeah but we
will have a tiny break to go to an idle
meeting
okay so if you wait then you will see
more of me in a little bit uh if you
leave then i wish you a good night
um
hey okay so i'll see you in
a few minutes two minutes three minutes
okay in my office you know where it is
okay of people you've been there many
times
i need to sneeze
[Music]
uh
should i realize i have an updated
version of this background already
um
[Music]
okay
ah
can i close the game it it's fine right
wait let's try to close it properly how
is it
uh
system
there quit game yes okay
yeah
uh eden added something from afla
uh the chicken in the back will be
replaced it's like a collaboration
background
let me switch it up let me change it
there it is empty
you didn't see that
don't look at it oh
wait wait
cute
oh cute
yo frodo's cherry blossom petals through
him yeah oh that's speed man that's kind
of dangerous
that's kind of dangerous the speediness
of that uh elevator thingy
it's a bit too fast
for say a safe work environment
uh
can you slow that down chimkin i'm
scared of your safety
and where it comes down is fun but the
way it goes back up
he's so cute though cute animation
and
dangerous on which floor are we i think
we're pretty up high so
he doesn't even have proper like secure
securing uh belts or something does he
no no belts at all he's just sitting
there on that piece of metal
if there's a little bit of a wind whoo
then he's gonna fall off be careful
it's too fast no gas gas gas stop
listening to gas gas gas while you're
throwing pedals
you can just fly if he falls
i'm not sure if he knows that
he's a chicken after all they don't
quite realize that they can fly
i mean they could probably he could
probably like float to the ground right
like rather than flying
he could probably um
slow
make his fall slower by flapping his
wings a little bit
yeah glide
like in what game was it
what game was it
like in minecraft but that's not what i
meant
that's not what i meant what game am i
thinking of
and zelda right yeah i'm thinking of
zelda
i think i think i'm thinking of zelda
and by the way if you're if you if you
are after all of these album ring
streams today from whole life are still
craving eldon ring
yeah ina has a elden ring stream
afterwards uh in like i think two hours
or three hours
thanks for the stream today i have to go
now thank you for watching
never enough elden ring oh i really like
that game don't you
yeah ina has been playing a lot a lot of
small sessions
it was awesome of you to do three hour
streams oh well i'm probably gonna play
again
today was fun
today doing all these small little
missions
was fun
but i guess the next mission would be
going for the castle i suppose
um
i wouldn't mind playing again oh yeah
today's sunday we didn't have a schedule
for this week but i'm gonna make a
schedule after the stream and upload it
okay because we're going back to
normal pretty much
yeah sorry for the wait uh i i basically
did it because i didn't want people to
know when i'm leaving and when i'm
coming back
um
for safety reasons oh
yes
water
um
oh wait
[Music]
it's crony's birthday um
tomorrow uh for some countries it's
already today
i was gonna
make her a video though because i
um want uh i won't be awake
all of the girls recently are doing
these birthday streams while i'm
sleeping i'm sorry that i can't be there
alive
but it seems like my videos have been
received pretty well
but uh i think i'm gonna make this video
or or maybe not
i'm not sure like i've been trying to
not always do the same thing i'm tr i've
been trying to mix it up you know
sometimes i sing
sometimes so i do you know for example i
did uh i did the shark thing
um
uh
oh yeah for kelly uh i did a drawing
at a before
no that was not even a birthday that was
just i don't know why i did that
uh
but i also did the song for kelly
i drew for ina
mm-hmm
uh
what did i know for amen
yeah i gave her flowers that's right and
i called in because that stream i was
able to call in
yeah flower is for um
[Music]
yeah i don't know what to do for cronia
i can't think of anything new
um i'm out of ideas do you guys have an
idea anything that i can do maybe in the
shape of a video
please
something in korean and
[Music]
maybe not
um
but
a poem
it's kind of like a song just not being
sung huh
at least then that way you don't have to
adjust it to a melody
want to come over and see my cat oh here
they are
record a dance with the 3d model
oh that's actually something new
original
a dance for a birthday dance
a birthday dance
i have to set up my whole [\h__\h] now and
have to ask uh for help to record it
because i don't even know how i would
record it i don't even know like amma
always invites me to go to the worlds
that we're uh streaming in i don't even
think i can enter them myself i wouldn't
know how to
i'll keep it in mind
even if we don't use this idea this time
maybe for another time
stand-up comedy act i'm not much of a
comedian i'm more of a philosophical
phoenix
fluster her somehow oh that's easy
that's that's not really a challenge
that's
every word i say flusters her so
um
why are you exiting me you know about
hazak philosophical phoenix i guess you
also know about comedienne
[Laughter]
but don't see
[Music]
i don't know what to do i want to do
something special for everybody but
i ran out of ideas
like what's it what i can do in
this form if this were real life i would
like to give her um a physical
um
a physical uh present
just kidding
[Music]
i love that duallipo song
kiana wrapped
can i write myself in ribbons can i um
you just gave me an idea she just gave
me an idea
you just gave me a good idea
i think i'll work on that after the
stream i think what i'm doing is you
know how i do my am zoo videos i'm gonna
draw
like a basically naked body uh for
myself to put on top of my head
wrapped in ribbons
and layer it on top of myself
i'm the present [\h__\h] i spoiled it well
only you guys know crony doesn't know
cronie there's no genius idea thank you
[Music]
hey
unwrap me please i oh no i'll be i'll be
like
cronie i was um i was wrapping a present
for you and accidentally tangled myself
up in in the wrapping
uh
a ribbon uh
could you help me get out of this
otherwise i can't finish wrapping your
breath
you're welcome to use that pickup line
yourself guys i think that's 10 out of
10 smoothness
never heard that one before
oh man
all right
music
music music music
not for writing a song just for now um
unravel me
i'm trying to unravel me alexa
play unravel
all right um did i just hear meow
[Music]
what are you not hearing it turn off
your headphones or your speakers
[Music]
pow
bow
uh
[Music]
every day is wonderful when i love you
you make the world brighter than it
always used to be come on and take me to
a fancy rendezvous dance like no one is
watching just you and me sparkles in the
air
it is love
[Music]
i'll never fix that part
every day is wonderful when i'm with you
you make the world brighter it always
used to be come on and take me to a
fancy roundabout there's like no one is
watching this view of me sparkles
[Music]
for the people who don't know this is um
a song that we created
while reading super chat so
because the audio stalk is awesome
[Music]
during a minute
every day is wonderful when i'm with you
you make the world brighter than it
always used to be come on and take me to
a fancy rendezvous dance like no one is
watching you steal me sparkles in the
air
it is
love we share love
right
[Music]
ah the ending is always so scuffed
don't mind the scuffed ending man
yeah
anyway i'll try to play that in the
background without constantly vibing to
it and read the super chats that i need
to read which i think are the dance uh
collab super chats and a few ones from
today
i suppose
oh yeah the chicken in the background is
kind of supporting me
by throwing those petals to make this
whole background even better than it
already is
[Music]
yeah
oh and the cupcake video oh yeah yeah
yeah did you like it i came up with the
idea last time it was more mostly cupsy
uh
um
figuring out what the video should be
like like the the whole script
uh but this time i i came up with a lot
of ideas and i was like [\h__\h] this idea
is too long this idea is too long
um because it had to be a short video
and then i came up with another idea and
i i
quickly
wrote the script because we had to work
fast and then i quickly recorded it and
then i was like cubsy you're just cool
you're just cool do what you do
[Music]
was it funny
yeah you like my punchline of uh
me
um
being the hero but um she literally
choked on
no wait i'm explaining it wrong the
punchline is
that
[Music]
it's shocking that what she spit out was
alive
yeah
[Music]
my stand power
i mean ow
you mean
[Music]
i don't know if that's now uh uh uh
lore but uh
is that a jojo jojo thing
i am once again confused
oh ah i didn't threaten you with a gun
no
now that was your imagination
[Music]
no
no no
no not you seeing things
silly chickens it's just your
it's just your imagination
isn't it
[Music]
clap clap clap
anyway let me read super chats
starting from the dance collab which was
a lot of fun we're gonna do it again
soon
uh
i think
uh also very exhausting and i'm so sorry
about the glitching it was funny too
that a lot of funny gifs i was laughing
my butt off man
looking at the gifts and the screenshots
so funny
i don't know
i will fix my dragging problem
um
i i have an idea what it could be and
uh i think i think probably you know
okay
call me stupid or whatever
but i thought
that you know those base stations
kind of
sense where i am and kind of see-through
furniture maybe not for walls but
through
some furniture should be fine i thought
i found it i thought it kind of like
scans it you know and you know
um
there wasn't that much in the way but
[Music]
yeah i guess yeah my feet um i think if
i if i would have placed the base
station at the exact opposite location
looking at itself
uh at each other
then
probably nothing would have been in the
way but the way they are now
uh yeah there's probably something there
your headset has to see the stations
i think my headset was always visible
but my feet track your trackers maybe
sometimes not
i shouldn't have said it now you're like
you guys surely have a lot of stupid
moments as well
[Music]
and i thought it was something that kind
of like you know scans it like you know
like um i don't know
like a laser thingy
and maybe it sees where where the heat
of my body is i don't know something
like that or because i mean my body
would sense where the trackers are i
don't know
[Music]
i don't know man
but um
because of that i will be uh
um
changing my layout asap my layout of my
whole room like i want to move the
furniture around and i'm getting
some help to do that in time
yes yes
i think i can
move the furniture around so that i have
more space for vr
[Music]
how's the prep
prep going well i mean i have to
choreography already since
[Music]
like many many many many months ago
because i commissioned it way ahead of
time
uh choreographies for my songs
so
yeah
i actually already kind of
had like the basics of the choreo down
since a long time ago
i was just waiting for time to show it
um but yeah recently i've been
practicing
uh some more to like get it back into my
memory and and and perfection
uh the moves
[Music]
yeah
but
stamina definitely lagging but
um
i have like uh
i feel like
it's a bit different when i
when i
dance versus
when i sing versus when i talk
like let's say
i do one song and
um
i feel like i when i sing i have a
better control over it than when i talk
like over breathing because
um
i think it's because when you learn a
song or when you record a song and so on
you
figure out where to breathe
so your breathing is really controlled
you there's like certain
spots in between lines where you have to
breathe
and there's others where you can't you
don't have the time to prove so it's
like
really like already decided when you're
going to breathe
and i feel like when i when i dance and
sing at the same time my
breathing control
at least for the length of a song
is pretty decent and then once the song
is over
i'm like falling apart like
[Music]
and also i mean for example with we are
i have a different um vr set than ama
has
um
i don't know i asked her if hers also is
that heavy and uncomfortable
she says not so much but mine is pretty
heavy and uncomfortable and like dancing
uh energetically
in vr
is just you guys gotta give me a break
it's really [\h__\h] exhausting i mean
you've seen us do vr chat collabs where
we don't dance and sing where we just do
normal things and it's still very
exhausting makes you sweat so much and
blah
[Music]
it is it is pretty exhausting and then
adding dancing and singing or talking to
that dancing and talking at the same
time and talking in a in a clear
um
loud way
it was it was a bit exhausting i ow i
actually
i had um quite the
sore muscles throughout my
germany vacation because of this dance
collab
my body was really in pain the following
days
i feel like with with vr my body is like
even more tense because of the [\h__\h]
equipment that is attached to my body
it like tenses up you know what i mean
[Music]
um
develop muscles oh yeah i mean i
probably did
but i was
very much in pain and sitting in pain in
the airplane is not so nice
[Music]
well anyway i can't honestly i really
can't say much because i don't want to
spoil you guys but yes i've been
practicing
and i'm looking forward to it
a lot a lot a lot a lot
i hope um i can impress
some people maybe
a lot of non-kfp fans as well i hope i
can
um
leave an impression on them
[Music]
i want them to remember me remember me
oh yeah i saw the
new idol outfits for
the
um
fifth gen
yeah i mean it's not a surprise
we all know how those idle outfits look
like but they look cute in them i like
um how shishido botan because her image
color is kind of gray so the the color
the um individual color in her dress was
also gray it looks pretty cool
um
but
with managing
i am like got it
[Music]
ever since the santa outfit and now the
idol outfit
are her boobs like legit getting bigger
or has her 3d model
always been like this
[Music]
like
they are um
huge
was it always that thing it just it
doesn't look that big on on like 2d when
she's 2d
so when i see her in 3d i'm like
i i didn't realize you were
a big oppai
person
[Music]
um
it was um i was like i had to look at it
several times like i was like
turn to the side please
i need to check okay am i saying this
correctly like oh my god
[Laughter]
am i am i seeing what i think i'm seeing
these are huge
i kept on looking and looking and
looking
to make sure
i'm not imagining it
[Music]
yeah from all angles
bye
ah
yeah
anyways
we're in super chats okay
i will tell you more about my trip um
tomorrow i suppose um i should keep some
chit chat for that
[Music]
and can i snack a bit on potato chips
[Applause]
i'm a bit hungry
i'm also kind of um
my throat is super dry
what's happening tomorrow uh i'm
thinking of doing justice up but i'm not
sure yet i haven't looked at my schedule
that much yet
[Music]
i mean
weekend will be busy there won't be any
normal streams on the weekend obviously
so i need to play some games during the
weekdays
[Music]
yummy well whole tony happened oh
um probably not next week no i did ask
sweater sound five
you gotta give it some time
[Music]
i'm trying
i don't know
[Music]
i said i was gonna read super checks now
i'm just eating um
potato chips
[Music]
i'm eating the ones that are like
um
ah wavy wavy
[Music]
yummy
no more elden ring for today yeah we did
a lot today
actually salty i always just get salty
um chips i know that's boring
um
but i really just like classic salty
ones
guys
[Music]
what's not broken exactly
what was that again
ah one time when i was on a flight um
[Music]
i'm not sure where to
where i went
but there was this one flight that had
like some special brand uk popcorn
and those were
like the best popcorn i've ever eaten in
my whole life
and i tried to get those popcorn um
at home somehow by ordering online but
they didn't have that flavor that they
um served in the in the airplane
so it was like
like a legendary popcorn to me that i
was never able to meet meet again really
rare legendary popcorn
it's been so long now
i don't even know what they were called
but i would recognize them if i saw the
packaging
[Music]
it is it was a brand from the uk i'm
pretty sure
a couple years ago
i think i think in this case it was
caramel or like some kind of sweet
popcorn but
they have other ones as well
[Music]
kettle corn no
butter kissed
[Music]
no
that doesn't look like it that does not
look like it although they look yummy
the packaging i can't describe it
it's so long ago but i think it had it
had a nice graphic design
proper corn wait a second proper corn
that sounds familiar
yes
that was it and i think
ah i'm not sure yeah sweet and salty i
ate the sweet and salty proper corn i
really like that one
that's why i said something sweet it
wasn't caramel it was just something
sweet
where am i where are my uh uk fans can
you guys send me like one
whole suitcase of sweet and salty proper
corn please
[Music]
another quest
but the last time i checked for that one
many years ago maybe we have it on
amazon now proper
peppercorn
it is there
but i don't know if they can
ship it to austria
[Music]
it might just be germany
um
[Music]
what
why is it so expensive
ah 12 times 30 grams
[Music]
still sounds expensive 30 gram how much
is this
this one is
this one
where is it 150
wait 12 times 30
for 30 euro that's like 30 bucks that's
like really expensive
i think oh well it's important food what
do i expect maybe there's a shop here
that has imported like a like a real
life shop that sells it
um
for a decent price
oh well
it's okay there were there were
sometimes after eating after i once ate
that on the airplane
that i really really really really
[Music]
really craved it so much
and i was thinking about it for months
but that's years ago and i'm over it
kind of
because i forgot what it tasted like
if i tried again i would probably miss
it again you know what it might be time
yeah
yes might be time for another food trip
i'm just gonna take an empty suitcase
fly to uh london
get me that proper coin fill up my
suitcase and fly back
a different kind of food trip wait
that's probably gonna be more expensive
than ordering it on amazon
if i ever have a
different reason to go to london or or
the uk again then we can do that but
doing it just for the popcorn is
probably not worth it
[Music]
custom will have some questions
um
[Music]
they shouldn't be the one asking
questions i'll be the one asking
questions
i'll just answer every question with a
follow-up question
they're gonna be like why
why do you have so many potato chips
with yours with your with your suitcase
and i'll be like
why do you not have these potato chips
with you why do we not have them in
austria
and that'll be like it doesn't matter
this is not what this is about why do
you have so many potato chips with you
are you trying to sell them or something
and i'll be like
why do you want some
[Laughter]
[Music]
just answer everything with a question
don't give them answers
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] i used the voice changer on the
wrong person
[Music]
you can bring them over you mean for
dokomi
you you said if i do a fan meeting and
at the document who says that i'll be a
document what the hell
but i wouldn't mind
if i ever appear at a convention again
if you would bring me um
bags of
proper corn
[Laughter]
however
dad i would probably also have to send
for the mail although it would already
be in europe
and then
probably
let's just say what's happening in
europe
well anyway
[Music]
don't know i can't talk i have food in
my mouth oh no
yeah
food donations are kind of um
conventions where i am in in person are
like kind of the only the only
opportunity the only way
where i can get physical presents from
you guys
but food is still kind of a no-go
[Music]
so
yeah i guess it ain't happening
[Music]
i can't stop eating potato chips rmc
where are you
[Music]
remember that one time when i was eating
potato chips and i was still living with
rnt and i was crying about i need to
stop eating and then she came in and she
took away my potato chips and she gave
me your veggies
[Music]
um
you guys do
the same thing that i do when like you
have a bag of potato chips
there's big ones and small ones inside
i like to take like a couple of the
small ones
i prefer eating a lot of small ones at
the same time and crunching into them
then the big one i don't know for some
reason it tastes better to me
having a lot of small ones
[Music]
no am i weird yep same here yeah
oh there are some people who do that
[Music]
and look for the small ones in the bag
yeah
yeah they they feel like kind of juicier
when i like like stack up a bunch of
small ones
[Music]
someone stop me
why did i
if i ever asked you guys again if i can
eat potato chips say no because it
doesn't stop it won't have an end to it
don't make me open the potato chips back
it's the end of all of us
[Music]
last one
one more
one more stack
[Music]
um
oh
[Music]
huh
now
[Music]
potato chips
go away
[Music]
my lips are already like
feeling
tingly and burning
from the salt
it's a good time to stop
[Music]
no i have not read a single super chat
yet that is true
[Music]
what i mean i said super chat said chit
chat didn't i
[Music]
super chit chat is what this is
my lips are burning
um
i think they were kind of open
[Music]
okay
kiana not only it's my birthday coming
up on wednesday oh no
i missed it but i also just finally
became a member for full year and
[\h__\h] this is my thank you for being a
wonderful source of happiness for the
past year your fun streams great phantom
direction and cuteness are what pulls me
to watch you each time kfc is one of the
best communities i've been a part of
thanks to you i'm excited to see what
you have stored for us in the future
[Music]
oh you pre-wrote the message on monday
but it was already wednesday oh
happy the little birthday moon dog
love you
[Music]
happy birthday day to you
happy birthday to you you
yes you
could be no one else cause you're
wonderful and i
wish you all
the best for now and the future and the
past
not that i
can change anything but you could ask a
man happy birthday happy birthday to you
happy birthday happy birthday to you
happy birthday and thank you for
supporting me
congratulations on becoming a bucket
and getting older
yay
[Music]
thank you for your support and your love
thank you so much i hope you had a
lovely birthday
um
hope you celebrated yourself
on an eventful day we had an eventful
stream hey
great combination
thank you for everything
james lockbug thank you for the pinky
super excited for this and it's extra
dimension squared and multiplied by an
extra guest back of the envelope that's
like ten thousand times the normal
cuteness levels of a stream what what
are you doing like math in my super chat
huh huh
sounds like math to me
yeah
uh guna being a guest was really last
minute
um but i think she made a great addition
to the team and i updated the thumbnail
i don't know if you guys saw it but i
updated the thumbnail and now she's
there
now she's not a secret anymore
hope you enjoyed it thank you
there was a good reason for it to be
excited for because it was a great
stream
[Music]
i don't know if i can
make the next one
still so funny i feel like i might end
up being very serious especially if my
tracking gets fixed maybe i should keep
my tracking [\h__\h] up
[Music]
otherwise i might be too serious about
teaching
i i would get too too into it too
focused on it
[Music]
i mean that was my original um
at least for teaching the choreography
my original
goal was to be pretty serious about it
but my body fell and broke apart so many
times i couldn't stop laughing
it was so ridiculous at some point man
i tried my best to teach the girls but
uh i think good i picked it up decently
no hate but i mean i'm it took some time
but i think she just doesn't have that
much
experience with learning a choreo and
it's really not that easy
so it's really normal i said it to her
too during the stream but it's really
normal to not be able to remember a
choreo that quickly i told her
learning a choreo of that complexity in
two hours
is
[Music]
as an amateur really unrealistic
i'm gonna say it herself that she kind
of uh pre-practiced a little bit
[Music]
but yeah i i don't i'm not giving up on
ame
she's got some natural groove you know
she's got the groove
she got the funk
[Music]
i think if if she had more time
um
then yeah she would totally nail it but
yeah that was just a big lack of time
i remember my first um
tries to learn choreographies many many
years ago it took me a long time and
even then when i
the thing is with like learning a
choreography you also yourself you don't
realize uh when you're doing things
wrong
and you think you're absolutely copying
what the reference is doing but
you're actually not
it takes you some experience to really
notice all details and be able to
control your body the same way that the
reference is doing
yeah you need a full visual of your body
that's a good point
i remember i thought i had a
choreography down but now looking
back at how
thinking back and how i did it i really
didn't and i looked so ridiculous
so many things that i would have done
better um but that really just comes
with the experience
[Music]
um gotta keep on trying and improving
yeah
yes yes yes
i can luckily say that at least learning
choreographies and dancing is one of the
few things that
um
i i used to be very good at i can still
do it it's like um
[Music]
my body may be a bit more stiff than it
used to be but besides that
i still i still think i got it
[Music]
yeah need a bit more
stamina
i always say stamina just because i play
so many games man
even in german even in german i say that
it's more of a gaming term than it is a
real life term isn't it
[Music]
don't remind me of the chips rail i
already forgot about them now i want
more
austella yeah and now
endurance
it works better in english than it does
in german i still use it in german
though
okay
because you can you can put your stats
on stamina in a lot of games
stamina builds not not really
recommendable though it's not that good
in games usually
[Music]
if you practice more than you'll build
up more stamina and need it for your 3d
concert soon i hope oh
i don't know man i i'm not sure like how
how soon
we will be able to do like a proper 3d
after the a proper pretty debut
after the concert
um so it's hard for me to plan out
things right now
[Music]
yeah
i don't know like the time what the
timeline is gonna be and uh
when things are gonna be possible to do
[Music]
i want to
do 3d too of course but i also i don't
really want to use
my
3d model
like too much before even doing a proper
free dw you know what i mean i don't
want to mess up the order and i don't
want to take up a take away
the specialness of the 3dw
so i'm
currently wrecking my brain
um about these things also the song that
i'm currently working on i told you guys
originally i kind of wanted to make a 3d
music video out of it
but then i was like other clothes don't
fit though but now that i think about it
maybe it could work with certain filters
and all that to make it fit to the song
um
but
but then
like i i i
i was tending more towards doing a
fruity music video after all but then i
was thinking like ah but that was it
once again it will kind of like
take away
the specialness about the fruity debut
if we're ever doing that and i don't
know when that will be happening so
[Music]
yeah i don't know what to do man
um
[Music]
i was always always always dreaming of
like a cool 3d debut
um ever since i joined
whole life because i always looked at
everyone else's
amazing 3d debuts and it's just kind of
something that i was looking forward to
so much and had so many ideas and
visions for
but it's been so much time now and and
now
because of the concert coming first you
know obviously it's not ideal for us
either
we wanted to do a 3d debut before that
too it's not ideal for us
but we we didn't want to you know
obviously
say
no like
not being in the concert wasn't really
an option either
yeah cause like turning that down when
when is the next big concert gonna be
one day one year later
i don't wanna wait that long i wanna be
part of it so
um
yeah it's
it's a lot of
difficulty
in
the situation now
it's like a preview i i i
would say so too
so just the concert before the 40w i
think is totally fine but more than that
i don't know if i really want to like
spoil so much then like
doing a fruity debut won't be won't be
special anymore
but anyway
that's something for me to
ponder and think endlessly about
um the paywall most painful thing well
there will be screenshots because
screenshots are allowed
screenshots are loud um
yeah
i'm sorry if you can't watch it because
of money issues that is sad
but at least you'll have screenshots
and
and and and it's better that way anyway
because because it should be special the
3dw should be special
it should be a special reveal just look
forward to that i will do my best
to push it so that it happens asap
i'm pushing don't
don't worry about it believe me i'm
pushing for it
pushing pushing pushing don't complain
to me about it being paywalled or you
know the order of things don't complain
to me about this is how things are
i know some people maybe aren't happy
with it but not that i can do anything
about it and as i said would it be
better for us to not be at the concert
no
so let's be positive positive thinking i
told you guys the other day there's
so many things that people get upset
over and and get mad over but if you
think about it think look take a step
back look at it from a different
perspective
is it worth getting mad over
no
i can't do anything about it either yo
i can't do anything about it
and yeah let's just be more positive
what the
hell no no reason to get so upset over
it
consider like why things are the way
they are and if it's really something
to get so upset over
[Music]
take a step back
think chicken think
but thank you guys for being supportive
and so understanding
thank you
before i start eating potato chips again
let's read some super chats
indeed
satisfied
miss miss duncan
even if it's not full for you i've been
looking forward to seeing your dance
moves for a long time
oh yeah you know i was really glad that
the low poly models that we were using
they showed body movements pretty well
pretty well so i was quite happy about
that i was thinking about doing like
solo dancing streams as well
where i
um pre-pre-record
uh
the audio of me singing the songs
so it's like a kind of okay and dancing
but i don't want to do it at the same
time because uh kind of scuffed audio
and so on i feel like it would be
scuffed so i want to pre-record the
audio i still do it like one take or so
no no mixing or whatever it will still
be like natural kind of
and then dance the choreography so i
would only choose songs that have like a
choreography um
so like vocaloid songs and idol songs
and so on
and then i can dance along yeah yeah
yeah
you like the idea
[Music]
no in vr i'm not gonna do both at the
same time it's it's [\h__\h] difficult
also for technical reasons
not only for
body physical reasons but also for
technical reasons it's difficult to just
sit like the both of them live at the
same time in vr
we tried it before
it didn't work that well
track your head without the vr headset
what do you mean
ah
no
i didn't i did buy a new microphone
though it should arrive uh
in the next couple days a new microphone
that's like separate that i can attach
to my
vr which i think is ridiculous just the
thought that i have to do that to begin
with because the vive
pro or whatever i have is is really
expensive one of the most expensive vr
headsets we are set
uh in the market
why is the microphone so shitty
why
why do i have to buy my own microphone
to attach to it
when the when the valve for example has
a perfectly fine microphone
[Music]
ain't no the [\h__\h] no like
that's not an excuse it being old it's
not even that old and good microphones
have been around for years many many
many years
hmm
the valve was around at the same time
when life was around but still valve has
a better microphone so
it's not it's not an excuse excuse at
all
anyway
a roll coco as far as i know wouldn't
even work with vr because they use
different trackers
you have to
like like i don't know program it in a
way that it would like
see the rokiko as a tracker but it
wouldn't
wouldn't automatically work but but but
i want it anyway
for
non-vr reasons
anyway i was saying yeah yeah um great
though i have a model like that now i
mean it's very close to
uh the reveal of our 3d models
so who knows if we're using them that
much anymore afterwards but to be honest
i think they're charming they're pretty
cute so i i can see us using them even
after that especially because i said i
don't want to use the 3d models
uh until we get a proper 3d debut anyway
so
i see more times of us using those
i think they're good in between
of you know when we use wealthy we want
to be derpy and all that uh
but if we want to be derpy but still
have visible body movements that's a
good time to use the low poly movement
low poly models you know what i mean
know
[Music]
you guys are so smart you always know
what i mean
[Music]
thank you for the support very generous
of you thank you i appreciate it
candy stamps duncan cruz duncan the
gaming crew duncan trevor g duncan daisy
donkey shoe and super
thank you for the red super chat
red heart no orange heart is that an
orange or red one with a yellow heart
yes i'm a torii
i'm a tony cute
the
there was a a lot of good amatoni
moments and some good uh
ami same tony moments and some good ami
sami moments and some
good
summer toni moments
a lot of good moments a lot of titty
i think everybody's heart was healed in
that stream
no supposed to be
hot
kp is the only password chain with its
own dance school
i would now say that that is true but
there's so many things in the world in
in the world that you wouldn't think
they exist so maybe it already does
exist i don't know
honestly
it could be anything could be
[Music]
um
but yeah
dance school sponsored by kfp
[Music]
looking pretty cool i think we look
pretty cool
it's only us
of course it's only us yeah because we
got the moves
we got the rat dance moves chicken
chicken dance
[Music]
book book
we might be lacking some other things
but we have those dance moves
[Music]
thank you for the pinky i'm compelled to
super chat by the power of egg
the egg was so cute wasn't it
i like that eggbot egg body
egg
looked like humpty dumpty didn't it
um
[Music]
egg
i kind of spoiled my my you know i said
i wanna once i'm pretty i wanna
hatch an egg
kind of got ahead of myself
having an egg in vr chat with me
[Music]
i had to sit on it i couldn't hold back
yeah
but it was comfortable
and when i sat down it just kind of
crawled under my legs and was there
i had school on it if i wouldn't have
hatched it it would have been an egg
until the very end so
i just did what i had to do i am a hero
just like that
yeah
it won't be my last time
hopefully
some guy danke said
[Music]
i've seen a lot of
great british pound super chats my
british friends sent me some popcorn
kyombres thank you soon hollow knight
duncan flack armor duncan phase in
motion duncan brock six thousand duncan
oh
i gotta read that part
parley or party thank you soon our
roland duncan vegan anime dance
[Music]
dan question
darwin thank you for the pinky
i'm so i'm sorry attention but i think
egg is my new or she yes
[Music]
you're kidding me right
my
coconut broccoli
[Music]
yeah i wanted to wash it thank you
that's how it's supposed to be
can't believe it's that easy for you
guys to leave me for a [\h__\h] egg
ah
how how is that
round shape of an egg
more appealing to you than this sexy
body of a phoenix waifu huh i don't get
you guys sometimes
[Music]
365 dc video challenge duncan soon crown
tech thank you for the pinky
was waiting for this collab so i could
super amatory but i guess this super is
for egg too comments on one million
dreaming tutorial thank you
finally seeing these models worked so
well for both of you thanks to everyone
who worked for this thank you yes big
ups to everyone who worked on the models
and the background and everything
yeah
everything turned out lovely i was
really really happy
it turned out to be one of my uh
best streams on my channel i would say
even even though this got like oh even
even with knowledge stuff that means a
lot
so thank you for watching krantek
there will be more dancing in the future
so i hope to see you there thank you for
the support
axel duncan pride
oh thank you for the pinky
as a big fan of you and all of my having
my models used in an mv and in the vi
collab has made me so happy oh
this stream is so much fun thank you
again for the opportunity konmucho amore
oh mia more miami ccc
thank you free too
or preacher originally made
models just for fun i think
it wasn't originally the models that she
made
for uh us were nothing commissioned
um
but
you know one cannot leave something like
that out there
without it being used
yo
that would be such a waste richo is here
hello
something like that needs to be used and
shown to a bigger
our audience a bigger amount of people
so that more people can appreciate it
yeah
thank you for letting me use the models
and and and and for working so hard also
to get them available to us uh even in
last minute situations
i hope i can use the sparks version two
at some point maybe for that solo
dancing stream that i wanna do
for the solo one i wanna wear my sparks
outfit yeah
it looks so cool
[Music]
that's the closest you will get to
having sparks my sparks outfit in 3d
or yeah or in 2d or in any in any shape
on my body
that is the closest you will get
[Music]
docker attack thank you for the red
super chat this was great we're all
getting hyped for have fun for the
concert great work to all who helped you
set this up the strict idol step dance
teacher
the dedicated and motivated students and
the crystal exactly delinquents truly
sparked joy
glory to hollow ian thank you
yeah
it's a good way to hype up leading to
the concert as well even though it was
originally just supposed to be you know
like an amitoni song cover celebration
thing
but i guess now it's also a way to
um hype up
the concert that's happening
in the coming weekend
indeed indeed
thank you for watching and thank you for
the generous support duck attack
it's so soon yeah
yummy
[Music]
two amazing women an amazing song to
celebrate an exhausting dance routine
and the legendary third or so
third or so birth of gargura
oh yeah because she did come out of an
egg before didn't see
who knew her egg form could have enough
gravity to get
properly pulled to yank chiata around
stage thanks for the amazing song stream
and whatever comes next thank you too
thank you very much yeah it was very
funny to see how my body was heated from
one side to another
in the middle of dancing
[Music]
oh it's a shark egg i mean it doesn't
look much like an egg
just a uterus i guess
it looks like a uterus
the shooting says
[Music]
i love that so much
oh
[Music]
power
one of those petals are not petals but
there are potato chips out there
they look like potato chips
[Music]
yes throw potato chips into my mouth yes
yes
i love this music thank you come kamsa
nida
it's very joyful
i want to join
[Music]
so thank you tyson did i give you a kiss
yeah here it is
easter clown dancing dog joseph duncan
thank you for the pinky
such an amazing stream thank you for
sharing your dancing passion teachout
chi-cho
your son's a great instructor and thanks
for all that help this set this up
excited for fest let's go
yes so exciting i'm excited too
i am looking forward to it and you
should too it will be a very special day
or very special two days
thank you for your support thank you
joseph
alfredo guild augustine for the empire
danica
alexander pizarro thank you for the
pinky hold on let's go my friend
alejandro you panky and i are here to
cheer you up thank you for supporting us
thank you thank you
hope you and your friend had fun
watching our stream
um
maybe one or two laughs hopefully
thank you mega
our comedians are slowly turning into
idols sniffles is beautiful oh thank you
for the pinky
we were never comedians which is funny
okay
we're not we're not comedians
yeah oh no where's my hands going okay
my hand i can't i can't control my hands
what's happening
um
[Music]
you guys saying no motivates me to eat
more
i'm a rebel you can't stop me i'm not
part of your sister
i'm going to take that potato chip and
i'm going to throw it in my mouth
forward in my mouth
[Music]
it's vegetables after all men
just a bit salt one thinking unhealthy
[Music]
don't worry i'll fit into my clothes
my blood test
oh yeah i'm having a blood test soon
again
[Music]
i
apologize for this snack break i'm back
on track
and court midnight thank you seafoam boy
oh dangerous i actually had no idea guna
was gonna be involved but i had a hunch
that's why i decided to create this
extra stage as a bonus on my own i
really like it i like the the colors and
the lighting in it oh what the [\h__\h]
some weird window just opened up
[Music]
i like the neon lights like it's not
really neon but the the white the white
light
it's so soft and and uh
it works really well it feels like like
the amateur version was like light on
and then the other version was kind of
like lights off but neon lights only
turned on
made it look very special
very moody i liked it
thank you for making that we can use it
for the next dance collab as well
that's what you were going for
it worked really well um
yeah it looks so smooth
so comfortable
yeah
i wanna wanna film a synthwave
dance video in there
[Music]
everything looks great it did thank you
so much for your work
i will use it again we'll get some use
out of it definitely
[Music]
dankeshen this was such an amazingly fun
stream great job everyone look forward
looking forward to more dancing streams
ah
don't worry about it i'm working on it
thank you
[Music]
dana retweeted your video from today
what
what video
what video did i upload
i don't remember uploading a video
[Music]
the stream you mean
probably because we were just literally
talking until uh 10 minutes before the
stream
um
sweet of her
name
[Music]
while we were talking
uh
i don't know if i can say that i'm not
sure how much she shares
i'll not say it i'll not say it
[Music]
but i'm excited about
our vacation
[Music]
kind of wishing now that i booked it um
for an earlier date because oh
i'm so excited for our hotel room and
and and for the beach for the ocean
[Music]
it's going to be fun it's it's so
expensive though
yo
i tried i tried paying with my card
first and it didn't go through i think
because it was so expensive
we chose quite the nice um
[Music]
place to stay at
and yes it will be like probably like
six days or five days
and
yeah i ended up paying it with um
a different payment method because my
card
apparently has
a too low limit
[Laughter]
i don't have a credit card though it's a
debit card
time for me to get a credit card yep you
yield
but there's excited like for this one
for this one i really
i really think it's worth it because i i
want um this will be my
[Music]
my
how to say like i'm going on trips every
once in a while but this one will be the
vacation of the year for me where i
treat myself to something that i've
always dreamed about
you guys know where we're going right i
said it before right
[Music]
i started before i think
yes you know maldives yeah yeah yeah
yeah so my dream my dream um is not
specifically the maldives but the
moldovs has a lot of those hotels um
apartments houses thingies that are on
top of the water and that's that's
that's that's
what i'm dreaming about they're a bit
expensive but but but fun fun but
it's worth it it's gonna be so relaxing
sipping that coconut juice on top of the
passion even though i don't like coconut
but it just looks cool
a common running destination yeah the
bungalows yeah yeah yeah yeah
there was the rows and the rows and rows
of bungalows above the shallow water the
shallow bright
water
[Music]
tomorrow
i'm guessing that other places not only
mulders have that too i'm pretty sure
but like maldives is like when i think
of those um houses i think of maldives
so yeah
we're going there
[Music]
um
i thought it was valley
i want to go to bali too one day
a lot of places where i want to go
um
i hope we can do some exciting um
uh activities too but i talked about
that uh just last week i think
i wanna go to scuba diving and maybe
ride on one of those boats in one device
i don't know i wanna do a lot of things
and just chill i also just wanna chill i
wanna i wanna
um
i to sit in in like a blow blow up uh
thingy and just
float in the water ah and get a sunburn
hell yeah
[Music]
yeah you have your scoopers here well
you need a scuba certificate no way
of course i don't have that
will you share a bed
yes
there the room that
no we're taking as a double bed
uh
but i think it's pretty wide
[Music]
i think they don't even like have twin
beds options at uh
at these places because like
[Music]
yeah
usually couples are going there
it's usually a couple's destination so
[Music]
it's okay though i mean i've i've slept
in a double bed with my friends before
with
my bff and my an rmt
i mean i prefer a separated bed tube
because i i'm i move around before i
fall asleep a lot because my body is
like in a lot of pain
and i have to adjust my body like
constantly until i fall asleep so and i
feel like i'm embarrassed about it so i
prefer to be in my own bed
but yeah
no i'm not a sleep kicker no no once i
sleep i'm
i'm i think pretty
calm
but until i fall asleep
yeah hopefully she won't uh
be bothered by it
[Music]
plenty of massages yeah i gotta book
some massages too
oh where was i
anonymous two four seven and thank you
for the reservation damn twerk seriously
the amazing show tonight loved every
second of it keep working on this it's
pure gold thank you i'm so happy with it
it was such a success
and people enjoyed it so much thank you
very very much
i will make more
and hopefully maybe for making more of
these dancing streams i can build some
stamina too
thank you for watching
i'm glad you liked
angel thank you for the red super chat
can this please become a regular thing i
totally start dancing if i have a weekly
lesson with such cute as heck girl
sleeping oh thank you
i don't think i want to make it into a
weekly thing because because then it's
just not special anymore
no not weekly
um
but still still considering um
doing another one of these
in this week but i still need to talk
with ame about it because we both have
some
have some
worries about doing it um this week
we're very busy with uh
and and practicing
um
but in theory uh preacher is already
working on getting everything ready
um
but yeah
both me and i may have some some worries
about doing it before the concert um
now that's also a reason why i actually
can't quite make the schedule just yet
um
maybe
[Music]
huh
maybe maybe i'll put vr dance stream on
the schedule
and if we turn
if it turns out
that
we're generally too busy
then i'll just do it solo
and the other girls
can do their stuff
[Music]
hmm
cause i'm fine i know i know my
i know my what i need to know for my
performance i'm pretty much done
so i'll put it on the schedule because i
just want to bring out the schedule
after the stream
but i'm not sure if it will be with the
girls or me alone
[Music]
we um see
um but but even if it won't happen with
all of us during this week then we're
still gonna do it very soon after
was kind of
very
spontaneous so
you should clarify so no one
misunderstands what do you mean where
you mean on twitter or what
[Music]
clarify what
it's it's on purpose not very
supposed to to be not very clear
because i don't know yet if it's gonna
be with five or was just me in that case
if i put it already on the schedule
that's that's the
that's the reason why i'm not being
clear
[Music]
yeah i need to chit chat with ahmed
after the stream
after the stream i'll chit chat with
ahmed
we are requesting my question my
question well
yeah but then it's almost the same as
just saying we are downstream
um
anyway
[Music]
i'll think about it leave it to me leave
it to me
and thank you anyway angel
look forward to more
thank you
thank you for supporting me so
generously
[Music]
hey liar danke shin
i'm no duncan
fried squirrel thank you for the red
super chat
great work potential showing your sensei
idol side i can imagine you with a big
rulers making the other girls till they
get the dance moves right and they get
no breaks
can't wait to watch your performance
with proper tracking and hula vest it's
gonna be amazing
well the thing is if they don't get a
break then i also don't get a break
and mommy needs a little bit of a break
in between nowadays yeah mommy phoenix
saying i'm not the youngest one anymore
um but
um
when i was thinking of the dance um
school i was thinking a little bit of
you know being a bit more strict like my
dance teacher used to be so i tried to
bring in some strictness you know they
also need to respect the phoenix respect
the teacher
[Music]
there's some discipline
an important thing for an idol is
discipline
[Music]
discipline and you're not gonna
pick that up on the street or whatever
in the supermarket or whatever they're
not selling that
peter learn discipline from your teacher
you were not strict at all i tried being
strict for a little bit but then i felt
bad about it
maybe i'll be more strict next time i
don't know
the thing is that if i if i act strict
like a boot camp person then people are
going to be like
you are kiana is so mean what a [\h__\h] so
[Music]
very annoying
you gotta be nice
[Music]
even if it's just joking
i can't i can't joke around like that
anyway
just just a little bit just a little bit
of strictness i will try to sprinkle
into my dance lessons
no thank you wait where was i oh yeah
can't wait to watch your performance
with proper tracking and holofest is
going to be amazing yes obviously it
won't be a vr chat so
so please look forward to it fred's crew
i i'm i'm guessing you have your ticket
ready
i'll see you
i'll see you on stage then
take some take some eye drops before um
watching
so that you don't have to blink
and not miss even the tiniest
millisecond
sasha booty yeah boy
spawn finally worked for me oh nice what
what was the problem
[Music]
no blinking
no blinking for my performance you can
blink for uh the rest of the concert
as you need to but not for my
performance okay no blinking
piano
i know
april helm thank you for the pinky thank
you for hosting this amazing stream
kiara you're welcome i would like to
host it again soon so your yoroshiku
we always welcome in the dance school at
kfp
carpe up sodom thank you for the rest of
the chat this whole stream is certainly
a 2022 moment thank you canada ahmed
khuda and the whole team of all involved
i am glad if it will be remembered like
that thank you very much car props to
them
very generous support
don quixote
thank you for investing in the dance
school um thank you for paying the dance
school fees of my students
er flat armor dankesh and brendan
dankeshen random collusion thank you for
the rest of the chat beautiful thank you
you too you too
[Music]
thank you very much have another call
thank you also for a ransomware chat
this one's great canada you look so good
out there i knew you were an idol but
seeing it is something else i hope
you're working on your stamina or we
might need to have another debut stream
thank you thank you thank you
yeah um i think one when one um good
thing about that model is that my poster
is not as shitty as with the wealthy
model i always have a hunchback with the
wealthy model i don't know why
but with this one it works fine so
now you can finally see
my body
posture and all that a bit more proper
and no i don't stand like a [\h__\h]
witch from the forest
with a five meter long nose no
i'm a proper idol okay
i mean the wealthy models are freaking
cute
and i wouldn't mind using them again but
but the little pony models have um
they're good good things about them
they're good points
[Music]
you were so cute when you had your hands
behind your back
when they go crazy just by putting your
hands behind your back not even trying
to properly pose oh this resting pose is
already cute as [\h__\h]
welcome you are now being charmed by
takanashi kiara
you are now
part of kfb forever you are in love with
kiwawa and that's okay because how could
you not be
i have you wrapped around my finger hmm
[Music]
[Laughter]
cute
you guys are cute
you guys are cute siren no i'm not a
siren
my name is takana
not a siren
no no no no
um everything's cold i think i forgot to
give you a kiss
[Music]
for the
it was so great oh thank you i'm glad
you liked it that much
[Music]
it was a good stream after that i was
quite um excited for the following hours
so
yeah
i was like on a high
on a high after the stream
[Music]
you guys
apparently felt similar
thank you
[Music]
red thank you and jim tracy duncan for
the pinky that was a legendary stream
thank you for such a fun time you were a
great teacher and it was so cool to see
amarillo learn the choreo and improve
plus good i was so fun you guys all rule
and i can't wait to cheer for you all at
holofest thank you
thank you thank you thank you yeah i
hope next time we
can improve the sinking thing as well i
don't know uh how but amish surely has
something cooked up
to improve it even further
and i'll do my best being a teacher
again soon
thank you jim tracy
shadow pencil down because she's looking
for the job done question for the pinky
your dance is so legit it's no wonder
you got two students instantly thank you
your dance school is going to be so
successful you won't need the kfp
restaurant branch anymore so you can
start freeing all the chimpkins in kfp
already
what do you mean freeing you guys are
here voluntarily yeah you came here and
signed the contract voluntarily and no
need to free anyone
no no
[Music]
but i'm glad you guys um
like to dance because to be honest i
said it uh
on the stream but that choreography was
mostly
uh just memorized by watching the dance
over the course of like
many many years
[Music]
i just hammered it into my brain
a few hours before the stream
so i can properly teach it and not just
rely on
my memory
[Music]
yeah there's just some dances then i
don't even have to try to learn like how
the yukai
or the
uh
partially the lucky star opening dance
[Music]
yeah stuff like that it's just
ah
just by watching the video so many times
um
out of touch tuesday
what
what does that mean my dining dining
please so cute man lucky stars so
nostalgic
ah
love lucky star i saw some cute fan art
of it today
[Music]
foreign
the one that i like more though is
[Music]
every time i see a copy pan i have to
think of lucky star
it's so cute
[Music]
yeah
the coffee fun song is so cute
[Music]
should be arrested for being so cute
i want to change the music
[Music]
i want to do that i just don't have the
instrumentals for it
uh shadow pencil thank you looking for
the top oh wait i already read that
um i'm done with these thank you guys
for watching that and supporting me on
it thank you
and
the kiana to the rescue video
has some super chats i don't have the
thumbnail downloaded so bear with me
doc joseph for the pinky happy friday
thank you in advance for rescuing us
boss oh
sure
i mean that was a customer that i
rescued but
i would do the same for you of course of
course
if you're choking on something i will
i'll catch you from behind and then
try to get it out of here
jake it's monkey donkey they call it a
hero hug
no i just i actually just came up with
it they don't call it a hero hug but
they should call it a hero hug
and captain jerk pants duncan crispy
duncan brandon
typhon
foreign
yeah thank you guys for supporting the
that little little small video
hope you um liked it i am sorry uh that
that was the only thing that i provided
this time during my trip
not even the zoo video but i was kind of
not feeling recording one before i had
to go and
didn't have a way to preparing anything
else
next time i go on a break i'll prepare
some more again
[Music]
thank you guys
and i'm gonna read the super chats from
today from the lost um
elden ring
free chat
okay
and then we're done
[Music]
foreign
apparently sparks has reached 3.5
million views thank you
thank you guys for um
liking sparks so much it's actually um
been pretty pretty
pretty helpful
um for future productions
if you know what i mean
thank you
for making that possible
[Music]
thank you
it has some
problems as well in the beginning uh for
release time and so on but it's been
doing well
thank you everybody
here
[Music]
um
turned off glad to have you back but
i missed you but i was glad to see
another cup z video it was funny and
makes me look forward to eventually
seeing you and the rest of the girls in
hologram oh
i love ever being
i don't know about any plans but
yeah maybe we can do something like that
one day with our proper models once we
have them available
[Music]
would be nice indeed
i don't know i don't know
i don't know what's being planned
hmm
[Music]
good eye is already in holodown
it's funny but i can't even seriously
laugh about it but it's funny i'll give
you that it's funny i mean it's not
really funny
it's not really funny but it's
kind of
funny
yeah that's your joke hey
the kia tea or joke must be pretty high
up there right that's a high tier right
right
and who is tia
that was a high tier joke because you
only get that if you um
know german
[Music]
and the germans will laugh about it
because it's an exclusive joke for them
and delphi's they'll they will feel
special about it
you're laughing aren't you
the game recruit duncan
[Music]
savage thank you for the rainbow savage
i thought you were leaving me
there's something i've been feeling
lately i was having fun walking around
kfb and civilization but without you
something is missing
right
because you're my only aussie always
love you kiara pinky that only chicken
can see i saw what
what do you mean i saw it too
not only chicken chickens and phoenix
a little pepper
rainbow could keep super chat value
kiana above moment
[Music]
savage what does that mean you're not
leaving me after all you're gonna be
here
um often
yeah cause you miss me too much
understandable
very understandable
i could have told you that
i told you not to leave me so stay
i want you to stay
[Music]
don't go
thank you though for the beautiful
rainbow
hope you're doing well
thank you for saying hello and
supporting me
dog joseph thank you for the pinky
attention you're back i mean uh we're
good
you can totally enjoy your trips without
worrying about us but thank you for the
tweet updates in the video oh
like i said i feel a little bit bad
about not tweeting much and not doing
many videos thingies i actually had a
lot of time and was on my phone a lot
but i just didn't know what to say to
you guys
especially because i couldn't quite
spoil what i was doing
um
yeah
well thank you for waiting for me and
thank you for letting me do something
stupid like a food trip just because i
can't control my urge to eat food food
is yummy
i could have
never mind don't say that
[Music]
stay away from the phone well i didn't
really stay away from the phone much but
more than usual maybe more than more
than in my everyday life life maybe
a little bit maybe
and also i i made myself
look pretty for once again
did my makeup and [\h__\h] and and stabbed
my my hair i mean i woke up like this of
course but
um i would look even more amazing if i
tried
and i did that while i was in dusseldorf
so
you gotta give yours as a girl you gotta
give yourself
um if if you like
if you especially with the sea thing and
you stay home a lot i feel like a lot of
us
we just were like
well or at least i was like this i don't
know about you guys but i was a lot like
why why why would i do my makeup if i
don't go outside and even when i go
outside just going for groceries and
even then it's not worth it so [\h__\h] it
i used to
here's the thing
are you still doing did i ever say this
before i used to do my makeup like every
day
in order to go to school or to work
even even for junior high school
every day i did my makeup nowadays girls
are like more fancy looking um so
nowadays it's maybe more normal but back
in the day
no one did their makeup but i kind of
like i feel like um
i i i felt very ugly and and
i always did my makeup
and it was like a routine it was normal
i mean i wish i didn't have to do it
because it would save me a lot of time
and a lot of makeup
but like even even just for going to the
supermarket i would feel like i can't
really go
unless i have makeup on
or meeting up with friends even with
close friends
i didn't want to do it unless i had
makeup on
and then i felt really insecure about
having people who know me with makeup
see me without like at sleepovers for
example
made me feel really really insecure
had a lot of
issues with
how i look like and
yeah
but
thanks to this new job where i can just
stay at home and thanks to the sea thing
where i can just wear a mask
things kind of have changed i give less
[\h__\h] now and also me getting older i
guess i give less [\h__\h]
i
yeah when i go to the supermarket i
don't
bother
making myself look pretty anymore and
meeting friends as well
if it's a close friend then i don't
really care anymore either
it's it's a good thing but also i feel
like i
i need this sometimes i need to take
some
take a day and some time to do my makeup
and look pretty in order to feel pretty
again
and
you know just give myself a day of being
pretty
i need that sometimes especially
um when it's been that long
of me doing my makeup
because i'm always looking like a
[\h__\h] hobo
um yeah so maybe maybe some girls can
or even boys
or anyone maybe someone can relate to
that yes yeah yeah that's self-care
that's what i meant to say kind of it's
kind of
self-care
especially if you have like um a problem
with the way you look like or i guess it
doesn't even have to be makeup maybe
just you know putting even if you're
like if you don't use makeup maybe it
can be compared with just styling your
hair
or going to the going to the hair salon
or just putting on some nice clothes a
suit or something i don't know
feeling a bit better about yourself
looking into the mirror
and to be honest to be honest i felt i
felt pretty cute
i felt pretty cute uh when was it the
day before yesterday
um
when i did my makeup
but i noticed as well that uh i don't
have the routine anymore so
it's still kind of like it works
automatically but sometimes i forget
some steps
because it's just been that long and i
forget like doing my eyebrows or
something
sorry this is girly talk
really girly talk
[Music]
thank you for sharing thank you for
listening
thank you
makeup is pretty expensive
at least the decent one
so if you do your makeup every day
it also kind of piles up
but i have not been doing my makeup and
it's also better for my skin
i suppose so that's good
[Music]
i'm getting tired let's finish the super
jets
i i don't know what happened man i mean
of course according to my
monthly
streaming times i don't stream like much
less than i used to
in general
but still i feel like
i feel like i used to stream longer
hours like a year ago
and i feel like i kind of just uh
kind of i kind of
can't handle such long hours anymore as
i used to one year ago i feel like in
this one year i aged like 50 years
yeah i used to stay maybe a little bit
longer but in general i'm still
streaming usually if i don't take days
off and still still streaming the
longest out of whole lab english
but still it's less than before and i
feel like i aged like a million years
man
i can't i can't keep up with these
younglings anymore oh boy
yeah i saw they they streamed every day
and [\h__\h] respect for that and i still
streamed more than her even though i
took way more days off
which
um
is
weird why do i stream so long
i was wondering about that too
but i think bales um
in order to be able to stream every day
might have scheduled
a lot of shorter ones
in order to
do it
physically and mentally but she's
amazing holy [\h__\h] bae
i respect her work ethic and
and how hard she works uh in order to
you know put out some projects and [\h__\h]
she works hard and and i think she's
great
yeah there were some short streams in
between yeah yeah
yeah we're playing jrpgs and stuff like
that they're just really long so it ends
up being
uh i end up being the one with the
longest hours
[Music]
me feeling that much older after a year
makes me really respect the japanese
girls
holy [\h__\h] they like they keep up their
pace and they keep up their streaming
lengths and all that
uh as far as i can see at least for all
most of them
and they don't they don't seem to like
be losing energy or anything
holy [\h__\h] like
that's japanese work ethic for you again
how
[Music]
i'm too spoiled
me growing up in europe i might just be
too spoiled
[Music]
m
[Laughter]
japanese people man no no this is this
discipline though i gotta tell you when
the discipline that i have
now
i learned
living in and working in japan
my discipline is not something that i
learned by
living in austria
i picked that up
by living in japan
working with japanese people
and being taught
by japanese teachers
even for it was even if it was only
let's not count the third year because i
already had my discipline there let's
count the first two years
that's where i built my discipline and i
i'm proud of it and i like it that's a
good thing to pick up yeah yeah
um
what was i supposed to say where was i
going with this i forgot i lost my
i lost my friend
um oh yeah i think i was trying to say
that
yeah japan to me equals discipline
it's crazy
but it's like so normal it's not like
they don't even see it as discipline
probably it's just normal acting like a
normal human being
yeah the fine line yeah gotta be careful
there
foreign
[Music]
yeah
i agree with the overworking thing
that's that's one thing i i really
appreciate in my country that like
overworking is like
when in my old job when i even
overworked like 30 minutes
on the next day i would leave 30 minutes
early or
come 30 minutes later
and
and yeah that's like nothing
and and i would i would barely pile up
uh
uh over working hours
barely
and when when there is a little bit
piled up by the end of the week then
they're always like oh you gotta you
gotta get rid of those next week okay
my my old job was really nice
about that i mean i i suppose there's
still like other places
where you're not 100 that lucky and and
maybe it's a bit more difficult to get
rid of your extra hours but generally
generally
generally europe or austria
is pretty pretty kind
about that
[Music]
pretty gentle and sweet
and that's why i'm so [\h__\h] spoiled
about overworking i have discipline but
when it comes to overworking
no
i'm not staying longer
unless unless like at least not in a
normal job if it's something like whole
life
it's something i'm really passionate
about
then okay what a normal [\h__\h] jump
no
no a normal job that i don't care much
about no i'm not staying longer no
no
unless unless you give me back my hours
on the next day
[Music]
but that's also because i worked at
places where i can afford um
being like that because they
encourage me being like that
because they did not have a lack of
people mostly lack of uh
workers they did not have a lack of
workers most of the time so yeah
i should watch how much time is spending
yeah sure but
for something like whole life i
i don't mind if i need to work more than
eight hours a day
because
it's fun and it's worth it i see
i see a res
what's the word
result oh okay that's what i was trying
to say i wasn't sure if it was the same
word because we have a similar word in
german sometimes brain goes blue
questionable question mark
results of your labor yes and value in
doing so yes
i need to read super chats
mary pippen song
[Music]
thank you
thank you i think it interfered a lot
but at least it was so funny
pepsi dance and pets
[Music]
um
taxi thank you for the rent of a chat
wow i think it's even a double a double
red super chat
you're going crazy there thank you tai
chi what's up what's up did you miss me
is that why you're spoiling me today
thank you thank you very much
trevor g thank you for the pinky out low
attention
outlook
[Music]
really trevor really
well that's weak
weak
should be kiki why do you need to
try to create something new when there's
already kikitiki
[Laughter]
and welcome back okay that works that
one i like kfb just isn't the same
without you seriously they changed the
menu while you were gone what
what i didn't approve anything like that
for some reason they thought the vegan
chicken was tofu like this past year
and a half you haven't been selling
vegan raised chickens
[Music]
anywho i'd like to place my order today
one phoenix egg burger was the elden
bling onion rings and a dozen buttery
dodge rolls
and the vacation tangent t to drink
please and thank you
speaking of tea
on on the day where we left dusseldorf
uh in order to waste time until
our train was about to leave because we
had a lot of time
and
i needed to leave the hotel
we went to one
um cafe
that had
great coffee for arm tissue she said
that was a great coffee they had really
really good
um
uh reviews on google
and i
i had a tea
and it doesn't only look nice
it tasted so good
the the the waiter he didn't only just
pour
hot water over a tea bag no
i saw him preparing it
with like so much grace
and
elegance
passion and professionalism
that cup is not broken that's where the
water is supposed to flow out
it was like a tea ceremony but for like
not green tea
it was divine and exquisite yeah my
tomato
uh
fruit tea
it's also it's at other
if you if you're wondering and you want
to go to the places where i went to
next time you visited
this one was at a cafe located in a
hotel
uh on that street the famous street in
manchester and it's called fia
and the number four in german
they have amazing coffee if you're
looking for great coffee or also amazing
tea
and
one thing that i thought was
fascinating is i went to an idol meeting
while uh i was having a tea
i mean i left the tea on the table but i
went to an idol meeting
and
sasuka
japan street
that hotel
had public
i mean i don't know why i saw that
because i went to an island meeting i
don't know why i saw a toilet of course
but it had a public
japanese toilet
and when i say japanese toilet i mean
those magical toilets would go like
they open when you enter
and then you can wash your butt which i
don't like doing because i don't go to
the toilet anymore i went i go to idle
meetings but yeah
i've never saw that before outside of
japan
[Music]
it was
amazing
i felt like fascinated seeing that
outside of japan
yeah i mean i've seen even more advanced
ones in japan but that one still was an
automatic one and that was fascinating
um
it was a weird cafe weird hotel
because they also had like
in in the lobby
you know how there's like seats in the
lobby right
you know in any hotel lobby but like
some of the seats
where
only some of them selected ones
wear
like
hair salon seats
with a big mirror in front of it which
makes me think that they would um if you
need a hair appointment they would call
someone to go there for you and just cut
your hair right there in the hotel
and and dye it or whatever
yeah it was a very interesting hotel
with japanese
toilets
amazing [\h__\h] coffee and tea
they were also selling uh japanese uh
cup noodles at the reception and they
have hair salon seats
in the lobby what a weird hotel
hmm
weird hotel but yeah i don't know what
the rooms look like but it's probably in
the hotel because it's right at the
japan street
[Music]
it left a big impression on me
and the cafe design was also really cool
like though
you don't see it on this picture it
doesn't look so impressive but it was
very comfy had like big plants and
comfy
huge comfy levers so fast we were like
oh we were melting in those levers so
far it's not because it was hot but
because we're like
about to fall asleep because they were
so comfy
what's the name of the hotel
uh
i don't remember
but if you but it's the cafe is sofia
number four in german and it's located
in
the hotel
kind of belongs to it
and it's in the imma
say
no it's not hotel nicole
i almost wanted to go to hotel nico for
karaoke because supposedly they have
karaoke japanese style karaoke in the
hotel but it's kind of expensive
and um
yeah
and and rnt said like she doesn't like
karaoke so i would be the only one
singing
i can recommend it
actually on my own list too oh
we just went there because uh rmt said
she really needs coffee or she's gonna
die
so i looked up a coffee place and that
one had really good reviews so we went
there because it was also really close
by
[Music]
atta
okay going back to the super chats we're
almost done i think
[Music]
all right skye thank you for the pinky
welcome to quick kiana miss you so much
kind of surprised to play elden ring
again so soon but i trust you will be
doing great viva la kiwawa i don't
understand why you guys are so surprised
last one was last week
um
you guys thought i would
not play it
so soon why
why
[Music]
i said i wasn't sure if i would play it
oh
[Music]
i don't know today was i think
i mean last time
might have been a bit exhausting for me
i guess that didn't sound so eager huh
but i didn't say i wouldn't play it at
all anymore
today was more
enjoyable because there were not so many
deaths
yeah that was good that was good
yeah i think i was just tired after that
long elden ring stream last
time after
killing those bosses
i was probably just tired a little bit
um
cocoon thank you for the pinky i
didn't miss you at all the only reason i
was standing in the rain in front of the
kfp building day and night was because i
was enjoying my freedom
what freedom that's right i was enjoying
the absence of tyrann show i'm not in
love or anything tyranitar
kakun
i am
the kindest
most gentle
most merciful potential
in the whole wide world
are you sure
you want to call me
tyron joe or do you admit that you made
a mistake
hmm
[Music]
i'm waiting
no you are a tyrant all right i'm taking
away
your power
you're going to the usual room
sorry about yeah
no no
no
no it's not no just um it's just
me giving you the freedom that you want
yeah seems like you don't want to work
at kfp well you won't be able to
for
two
[Music]
i'm weeks now
i'm not proving any points except my own
points
okay
[Music]
i wouldn't do you that favor of proving
your point you gotta improve your point
yourself
get out of here
no
i'm a team thank you why why don't
people
why do people perceive me like that i'm
not a tyrant i'm always so kind to you
guys what the [\h__\h]
don't i give you enough love
[Music]
huh
what about those people that say kiwawa
loves her community so much
[Music]
what about unions what do you mean what
about unions aren't we a union
isn't our
relationship a union to you
[Music]
aren't we united
by love
no need for any other union
because we are a union
is what i thought
maybe i was wrong
maybe
[Music]
i don't have any sap being jammed is all
i have to represent my feelings but it's
not quite fitting either
[Music]
you disappoint me
my calling me tyrant
when all i give to you is love
[Music]
what else can i give
and all my dedication
[Applause]
what else can i do
[Music]
i love you so much
and you seem to hate me
[Music]
after poisoning me like romeo
and yet i am not your juliet because you
won't let me be your doing yet
[Music]
m
spanking on thank you for the rest of
the chat
aha she hasn't turned them off yet whoa
ready for another fun cuddly and
non-violent er stream with no jumpscares
well i mean
you know i know you joked about it but
mostly that is pretty accurate
there weren't
only a few jumpscares not not that bad
either
it was actually fun and not so much
failure eva so
would watch this play again what
is this just the game to y'all
[Applause]
[Music]
why you always playing why you always
playing
stop playing around with me
[Music]
yummy
when i when i was younger that reminds
me when i was younger i
i used to i had a lot of had a lot of
different phases where you'd like to use
different emojis and different ways of
laughing but there was a time where i
would type
muahaha m u a
h a h a h a aj muahaha what a [\h__\h]
cringy way of laughing on the internet
but i thought that was so funny while
typing
xd
[Laughter]
[Music]
sometimes i would switch it out and
write
m-w-a-h-a-h-a
[\h__\h] cringe man
so cringe
[Music]
oh god there's so much xd in the chat i
feel like i'm in the wrong
wrong um
time
dimensions
did we travel back 10 years
i feel like we traveled back 10 to 15
years approximately a decade more glumps
oh [\h__\h]
get out of here
get your glumps out of here we don't do
this at kfp
no you disgusting
not even i used the word glump
[Music]
nothing wrong with xd it's still used
yeah by bales the only one in the whole
wide world who still uses xt just
kidding
[\h__\h] roasted
oh man
[Music]
i feel personally attacked
i am not sorry
you people need to be exposed
you people need to be exposed and go
back 10 years
and leave your xds there and then come
back here
you forgot to leave something in the
past you're not supposed to take it with
you into the future
i'm so sorry it's okay do what you want
i mean it feels weird for me to see
people using xd nowadays but if you want
to use it sure do it
[Music]
and the game mccree
and ultra
noob
no need to feel bad about this red super
chat
no need to apologize thank you thank you
for the support
my aunt
austin mate aussie or say mate i still
hear that you get uh to go to bed yet
ultra noob are you sleeping
you're probably sleeping now aren't you
so yeah so yeah
so yes we are crikey dreaming of crikey
dreams
oh yeah
australian friends be sleeping let's
wish our australian friend
sweet sweet dreams
we'll be joining you in the dream world
soon
it says okay but this is just divine
exquisite hi kiana i hope you have some
good fights today it's monday 1am here
but i just wanted to ask where is kotori
these days
what do you mean where is kotori these
days
shows up every once in a while on top of
my head is also in the back in the logo
and in the back as a plushie and in the
front as a mug what else do you want
ultra new base awake
why are you not sleeping
young man
why are you not sleeping i said young
man
it is not good for your health i said
young man i guess you love me too much
okay please continue
that and
wow
[Music]
it gets you addicted you can't stop
watching
you just always
[Music]
i'm almost done reading super chats but
i can't stop ten
ah thank you ultra noob
you will be able to sleep soon
hallelujah
man these people in those time zones
they always must be thinking
must you always drag it out so much
please just stop please mamma mia my
sleep schedule is so [\h__\h] because of
you i don't have a life anymore because
of you
because of you i can't sleep at night
anymore
because of you i always watch streams
and don't go outside
because of you my friends have left me
my mom also gave up on me i don't have
anyone anymore
because of you
kfp is all i got
[Music]
[Laughter]
hey the same thing
counts for me yo i forgot the word the
same thing
for me
it's not only you guys it's me too
man it's not nothing sad about it we
have each other
we have a gender
relatable
and thank you ultra new noob this is
your good night case
spanking time
and that's it we're done
one for once i don't have to refresh
because we ended the super chats before
the stream
[Music]
yeah i will
hopefully get a schedule out soon
and
i will see you tomorrow for a stream
probably yakuza or if not tomorrow then
we'll do yakuza on tuesday no no
probably on monday
or
yeah monday probably in one day
um
yes
and thank you for watching thank you
welcoming me back i still have a little
bit of uh
some
some tangents from my trip that i will
tell you tomorrow if you're curious est
changes to ebt by the way what
thank you i will be careful i'll
probably [\h__\h] it up anyway somehow
i'll do my best
back-to-back long streams well
i need to make up for the time where i
was gone um
[Music]
and but only only
america
i think it's not time in europe yet is
it
i looked it up a while ago and it looked
like it was still
still
uh
[Music]
sometime until we get to summer time
yeah remind me when it changes here too
please if i forget i will need your help
okay
and in germany
auf wiedersehen
mmm
[Music]
i will
cry
some tears
please
[Music]
my
you