foreign
[Music]
hello everybody
wake up wake up ladies it's time for
Pico Park
[Music]
s
there can only be one yeah
hello everybody we're here with pico
Park and uh maybe we should do audio
tech really quick just in case we'll go
down the line uh
[Music]
okay come on
no no
did you have a breaking yes hello
[Music]
hello all the butter
okay yummy
oh I'm so jelly
[Music]
okay Audi I'm here and I'm I'm square
that didn't rhyme the whole life Ian's
rapper everyone nice to see you
um
thank you for coming to the yeah we're
gonna play Pico Park it's been a long
time coming but here we are hello Ivana
I'm green I was the well maybe not
everyone had to fight over colors but as
the only green Ian I have it pretty easy
oh I am Green With Envy
[Laughter]
oh
you got the joke did you get the Joker
nice job girls
and she doesn't get the other balloon
it is gray on this I was lied too I was
promised another blue shade
[Music]
this game is like Pika you guys know
what Pika is
no no
I'm happy
that makes you want to eat non-food
items like rocks
[Music]
oh Pico
[Laughter]
[Music]
that's fine just don't worry about it
we're here to play a puzzle game who's
next on the sound check oh uh
it's purple rice
um
um I played too much Splatoon last night
but I'm here
that's right let's go yes
okay
Oh Me Oh
um
hello it's Oro crony from Halloween
English Council and I'm blue I'm a DW
die
nothing wrong with being green
I would die yeah
I'm currently being terrorized by my cat
uh
nice to see you all I'm happy to
participate
in Pickle Park
[Music]
okay I think everybody's good chat right
sounds good
let's do some puzzling yeah let's go
all right I'm gonna start it
where's little girl
No No Escape there is no door what is
this this is not allowed I guess this is
the first level one one
okay we're gonna work together
[Music]
and push forward push forward everything
somebody
become steps
[Music]
I thought it would be good screaming
content um
wait wait this is all that stuff
yeah
position is
head yeah that's good all right you're
gonna die okay
we'll leave girl okay somehow
you're adult movies
[Music]
this is easy
I think we need all of us
goodbye
no you don't get to go back
you have to pay for that all right
already left no wait no no wait really
was this the Hunger Games
what if we all try
hmm
what happens with the last one nothing
okay I'm gonna do retry okay
okay all right now let's not have any
Traders here okay all right
together
High School Musical movie
[Laughter]
all right ladies one at a time ow
no fussing
please use my body as a staircase
I will step on everyone
[Music]
okay nobody take the key nobody take the
key
we have to take the yeah
everybody's stand on the platform and
wait until it gets to the top before
getting off wait I'm stuck
we have to wait until all of us are at
the top all of us have to be on the
platform
you can't get up without you guys here
with us wait till it gets as high as
possible okay okay
wait this place
[Music]
[Laughter]
wait how do you go in
[Applause]
I'm already at the end of my room
[Laughter]
level two
two how many levels are there three
Infinity
oh wow that's comforting oh three people
pushing you need three feet goes over
here okay I'll be a part of it
wait oh never mind there's not enough of
us come on I'm gonna need to make a
staircase I think oh I didn't climb up I
can't get up there we go wait
I think the bottom one needs to like fan
out
yeah so okay so let somebody all right
kind of spread out a little bit Yeah
like make a stairs and then we'll all
close in yeah yeah okay
oh
is it all right
where's first and then we all close in
on it yeah
a single row no reason to be there
we look like tiny skulls and I can't
unsee it now apparently we can just push
it
we're lying all right okay all right
closing in closing in just at the bottom
wow who's not pushing I pushed
okay who's this
oh no we're gonna squish cute no no no
no no no push
[Music]
oh God I'm stuck
can we push back can you jump from the
bottom people do not go through the door
yeah we can't probably push back why do
we need to put what happened
[Music]
for some reason I have it okay there we
go
all right sick Kelly be carrying I miss
this purple right yes I see you and
Callie for stands for Kerry
trying to help
um
yeah
all right so like for example Amelia
nice and I guess yeah we're good from
just here nice yeah we're gonna have to
help out babe
all right so one of these can stand on a
button for us however the rest of us
need to get on a butt get on a button
nice and that will be freeze
is there a reason Bae always getting the
key is because she has it in her outfit
oh yeah
she'd be dangling that key
Lord of the Rings yeah
hold attracted the shiny objects yeah a
kleptomaniac
all right six what
oh no
maybe one on top
all right guys
all right now let's go let's go
and now everyone wins up there
jump jump
okay
[Laughter]
guys
we just need like five people
who's that I think the bay is on the
edge
[Applause]
[Music]
okay okay
all right Hop On Hop On Hop on
okay we gotta wait oh okay
we're jumping
all right two at a time two at a time
right now partner
partner up no one gets left behind
is it three huh
mystery oh well that is unfortunate two
people come down
before no
no what now what now you're gonna keep
jumping absolutely balance it by a joke
why is Kelly so so wise no don't don't
set high hopes for me
[Music]
laughs
yeah oh no pushing guys
no it's because I'm the only one awake
right now
it's easy
[Music]
go together
oh no everybody grab the colored Donuts
everything is wrong I'm connected to
crony giant
umbilical cord
we're connected by a red string of fake
[Music]
so for example
uh first Watson
[Music]
on top of Watson's head okay next time
on top of crony's head
I'm just making a bridge again
wait mine's all twisted
okay oh
[\h__\h] supposed to be okay just Watson
first thing crony
then gura I don't know because mine gets
all uh no you're fine you're fine it's
just uh you just yeah around your neck a
little bit it's fine
yeah next up is Kiara
climb the steps next up Iris
[Music]
like it's too high
can you jump to the other side I wonder
oh yeah we gotta get closer to you sorry
yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
like when someone's like falling down
the mountain and someone holds their
hand like I Won't Let Go
[Music]
oh
okay
we have to send more down there all
right who's more towards the back
am I connected today all right let me go
ahead and get down there Laura has to go
yeah
I'm stuck
order
[Laughter]
dangle
okay
all right next up
all right then let's go ahead and try
and get up
yeah nice okay
my work my neck is gonna break
maybe fine boys
[Music]
good
[Applause]
absolutely powerless all right
yeah
okay okay
I want to end it but it won't let me
wait I can oh uh I think it's better
just for us to die it'll start at the
beginning yeah
Push Me Down
I need your strength everyone to commit
Sudoku
h
[Music]
I feel the gravity
[Applause]
Okay Okay Okay
jump up
I can't I'm trying to hold it back
up and then yeah
go ahead and jump up here okay
we're gonna come up here
and then oh yeah okay okay jump on
Kiara's head and then Kiara will go
nice
oh well should I just stay here
[Music]
[Laughter]
um just kidding not perfect
okay guys this will work nice
it's polar yeah dangling here
is that the key never throw it away
[Music]
[Applause]
that was hard oh we all figured it out
together
next up level this is just the start
ladies
it's gonna bring the string back isn't
it
[Music]
that's amazing
come back up at all okay yeah
good idea all right she's in front
everybody
[Music]
ready to run
oh yeah is everyone gonna run early the
person on the bottom person on the
bottom
fun is good there yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
nice amazing
everybody's brains are waking up right
so fast in the morning with no energy no
breakfast I didn't think there was going
to be a key over there yeah but it went
out well well I love coffee oh my God
okay that's the little three people
maximum three people
okay
we need to swing
[Music]
yeah we have to jump
okay pull back pull back okay make a
stack maybe Cody if you stand on my head
and get it on crony's head
is the ceiling gonna let this oh maybe
not okay
maybe just that should be fine yeah give
her a push yeah it didn't work yeah
maybe
I think you have to jump as I walk off
yeah okay okay all right
let's not let the Rope get too tight on
them guys okay
yeah you have to be pretty close behind
her because you're gonna limit her all
right here we go ready one two three
oh I got it
yeah well we're getting the hang of it
yeah
we'll bring them back to safety all
right get on my head again okay okay
three two one jump that's right
[Music]
oh gosh okay I better to fall down maybe
yeah
yeah this isn't gonna work
okay
whoever's at the end now I think Bay's
at the end of bait
Ed
okay okay here we go all right this
works again
look at that
I need your sweater
all right now remember those of us left
over we got to be ready all right yeah
okay on three yeah one two three
[Music]
just let us die I think when I when I
when I say three you guys have to also
run the opposite direction the people
who are not jumping okay okay okay
all right I'm in the way I can't
all right recony on three
one two three
okay
um
[Music]
for us that's very impressive looking at
our history stairway up and then we can
pull whoever's last up here so maybe um
okay we'll just pull you guys up
nice
[Music]
nice let's go
very good
[Music]
stream of Fate which is like and
relationships are complicated
you sure are all tangly now this is
probably secretly evil so let's okay yes
it is oh yeah it is I guess we'll do the
same thing we did before but I wonder
where the key will be yeah
maybe in instead of just doing one
um someone's down the other ear yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah like that oh
[Music]
yeah oh can you come over here the pink
calendar oh go I get you
eh
there we go
yeah there we go
nice nice
formation all right ready ladies
wait should I just stay on top like this
maybe no I think there might be an
obstacle like last time so we should
probably keep it a v-shape or a candle
yeah okay ready here we go ready
[Music]
oh
you got a key nice
[Music]
go next Galaxy brain
we're super smart
go together
thank God they need to be connected to
you guys with the leash anymore I don't
know how to go back
okay
yeah that's like a cuter version of
human caterpillar what
[Laughter]
[Music]
all right we may need to separate eight
seven
[Music]
warm up
top come over here and all the work is
uh
yeah
with the left side the right side
[Music]
okay okay now we do right side
there's still more there's still two
more over here step on me step on me
oh are you kidding me
[Music]
all right the timing was a little better
this time around yeah yeah
okay everybody left wait wait
got the cards two step one oh it is more
okay
team up with me fauna
okay okay nice okay nice somebody stand
here to get ready to grab the key okay
okay
I'm a stepping stone step on me step on
me go go go go go go go go go go go go
go go go
all right get on my head Watson you're
someone step on me
let's go we got time we got the time are
you kidding me why did you give me this
is
Pizza
[Music]
that was so close maybe everybody should
like Whoever has this should be a key
person
get on my head
oh okay
no I keep getting knocked off
okay and we we get out of the way we get
out of the way I think next time
we need to stack oh what around instead
of jumping to get the yeah it's a good
idea okay
maybe we should all be like a cop except
for the key person yeah okay make a
three everybody except for Bae go up top
one more please one more please
[Music]
I'll get the ones down here
it's a bit laggy sorry okay oh
there's one that bothers me someone get
on me
okay okay okay
[Music]
I think the key keeps getting
transferred to a different player yeah
we all like stay on the top floor or
something so that it doesn't get
transferred
okay we'll figure it out
that's cool triple stack jump on me jump
on me one more one everybody get on top
except for baby is our key person [\h__\h]
all right all right okay maybe we stand
over here on the other side okay yeah
where's the key go go go go
go go
it transfers when you walk past one
player essentially
so everyone needs to get away like
actively away from the person in the
middle who uses the key
all right so
and then we can go you can do it
why not
okay come on maybe everybody else stand
by the door
or something okay
maybe we're all supposed to be at the
point
let's go
come on
[Applause]
no clutch
very nicely absolutely nice job
we have three more times
oh
now what okay
who's jumping
to the right
oh okay okay
gotcha okay
Google
okay let's go to your right side Ronnie
can grab the key
[Music]
yeah this is no problem
boy
first day of here
nice
[Music]
just like before except
I'll drop down okay oh okay we can do
that later that's fine because I don't
think about it
okay all right everybody
back on top of each other Maybe
you want to jump on my head
okay
go go go go go
not nice
yeah
yeah just a little surprising
wait how many stages are there
oh Jesus
oh this one's a free-for-all huh no
cooperation required just oh no wait the
top ones you have to oh you do have to
snap yourself
that's me that's me
we need three there we go we got it two
one three got it okay
[Music]
let's try to get the the top ones first
one okay oh whoopsies okay oops okay I
got a snack over here I'm good as hell
what if you jump and then I jump oh here
I made the stairs I made the stairs
let's go nice
okay where's that key gonna turn up
so close all right I'm gonna take the
Lone Wolf root and get this who's there
someone's gotta grab those too
coordinated
all right okay all right
come on
[Music]
damn it
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
all right last one yeah
[Music]
this way we need lots of we need one
more people
okay okay Chronicle only one person
needs to be on the bottom I think okay
yes
we need two up there too okay
push push push
[Music]
[Applause]
wait did the did the top one need two or
just yeah
zero right on the top yes like the top
one is zero and then the one after
okay we got two here so yeah
oh
[Music]
nice maybe not the key person go first
what okay I'll go first
one by one ladies
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh I can go back out
oh we can bye oh hello
how did that happen is it because the
first row needs to I see no I just need
to go past first
um okay
[Music]
okay all right now wait somebody at the
bottom somebody in the bottom can you
talk too I don't know we need two on
each okay there we go okay okay
nice wait so let me get out first before
we push yeah yeah yeah yeah okay and
then okay top rock okay now you guys can
get up yay okay
nice all right nice
okay
with 10 seconds left amazing very nice
very nice
yeah there's only three like worlds left
that I don't know yeah because uh
[Music]
okay I think it's random what are we
doing with this
oh
okay
[Music]
we have chronix yeah you guys have to
get underneath
please be our umbrellas
you can stand under my unborn umbrella
okay
but
should we go higher yes wait yeah I
think so I think it needs to be four
people per Tower which is how math works
yeah
Kelly be at the front in case this is
the laser in front of us I don't think
it really matters at this point
on Kelly's head a little bit Two Towers
okay okay okay all right and then I'll
say somebody stand on base head so we'll
have two separate Towers okay there we
go okay this works it's probably fine oh
at least there's no time in here I just
realized oh yeah is it fun I don't know
wait it doesn't matter we can just have
oh
sorry
[Music]
just like that yeah
somebody transfer somebody transfer over
yeah yeah I'll move over okay all right
Cali get up here
[Music]
awesome okay nice nice okay straighten
out straighten up straighten up okay
let's go
[Music]
okay oh beautiful beautiful okay
[Applause]
[Music]
easy clap gaming we're gaming now
a couple of Gamers
such a cute game
Crayolas
all right
okay okay okay okay
[Music]
nice
every time when we start I think so
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
10 gallon hats oh a cowboy hat go ahead
oh yeah look at the little hole
oh
okay
[Music]
I think we should get two lines one on
top and one on bottom okay
[Music]
so we're ready to drive
I don't have a license okay okay okay
okay
I thought I'd give you enough clearance
[Laughter]
oh good okay two lies nice nice nice
nice nice nice
okay push push
nice get the cake
almost we almost got it
oh lordy
the world is a cruel sad place
[Laughter]
I'm just not gonna do anything I'm gonna
be in the back of the line oh yeah
you're fine
just don't worry about it
too far ahead painless
[Music]
thank you
it's okay
[Music]
okay
that seems strange but okay again what
happened I think maybe she hit the floor
literally no one knows I think she hit
the floor
ah and then we get real close right
around okay
I'm going so far ahead because then you
don't know where it is
like in this in the second opening we we
all have to push yeah
yeah it changes every time oh it doesn't
yeah so far
I go grab the key okay
somebody who's like towards the back
probably has to get it because if you're
in front and it's moving forward yeah
true that's hard like there's not enough
time okay bass key
you get to keep it I'll get the key
oh
and there goes okay sorry
I just gotta know
I like how we sound more dead
yeah I came into this full of energy
[Laughter]
[Music]
but someone took Blue from you no I'm
just tabbed out completely oh in another
window oh she's not focused in the game
I'm not focusing people Park oh no
y'all know this game is like Geometry
Dash that's what it is it's that level
of Geometry Dash
[Music]
you know okay
okay
there was someone on top of me sorry
maybe let's just make a straight line a
straight line okay that's what I'm
saying all right myth on top Council on
bottom
what about
helping bottom
laughs
[Laughter]
and it's on bottom Council to just make
you happy all right okay Council
no council got offended so now they have
to be on yeah we weren't offended
[Music]
nobody else worry about it I didn't say
anything
foreign
we got a little bit further every like
one like one centimeter further than
before true Eva made cookies wait yeah
they look really good they look so good
I saw pictures what do you mean Amish
cookies looked great too sorry
taste good
did they taste good yeah they're sugar
cookies so they're pretty uh oh sorry
it's holiday cookies you can get in the
store they like their Halloween cookies
yeah yeah I tried to make them like that
yeah
food Pillsbury yeah the shape ones yeah
those are good I don't think they're as
good but they're still pretty tasty
couldn't move
[Music]
no running in the holes
we'll make it we'll make it we're
getting further each time
yeah Mom someone pushed me
that person
I'm not moving we go fire ladies
I was going on a streak for never having
Hits From The Bottom
everyone has single files yeah
it's only fair yeah it's like operator
I don't know Mikey
it's close holy [\h__\h]
don't worry about the keyboard okay
go down
[Music]
[Applause]
first try yeah
[Music]
close your eyes
[Laughter]
this is pain
oh we're supposed to go wait what oh
Alaska oh we have to wait until it goes
down to one or three
whoa okay okay all right everybody just
chill wait what okay we tried to hit it
as close to zero as well okay yeah
wait but our timer ran out
yeah don't let it run out okay okay
oh yeah okay yeah okay I see you two one
why
we're really close though we'll get
another try It's gotta be under one
second I messed it up oh okay I messed
it up
we have to reset ah okay okay sorry oops
I stepped on it by accident oh if we
okay oh together we have to be under
yeah yeah yeah
between four okay
[Music]
sorry
[Laughter]
like we already messed it up
okay just stay in the next to the button
just let it run out let it run down
okay why are we pressing at a meeting
wow you guys look in your own tower look
at your own timer
make sure it's under four foreign
[Music]
wait I thought everyone was supposed to
be under four no no no no total has to
be underfloor
yeah the closest to zero okay that seems
too easy yeah I'm sorry I messed it up
though
okay I get it yeah Mommy were you trying
to have your personal record or
something is that why yeah no I got too
close oh sorry
I was like let me enter a misery fast
[Music]
um
don't mess it up wait oh my gosh okay
you're pretty close I need to get under
a second yeah
if everyone gets on their second should
be okay
[Music]
100 half a second oh we have to get
under half a second oh okay okay
[Music]
it's amazing
under under half a [\h__\h] second that
was a little too early sorry
[Music]
I stepped on it by accident I did too
it's okay
it's hard not to step on it yeah but you
want to get close you know okay here we
go
okay oh
okay someone was greedy a little too
greedy for there we go
[Music]
figured it out another half a second
under half a second
damn it oh sorry
I don't think we'll ever get this is
yeah
not with that attitude we were really
close yeah
[Music]
oh
my God
I already gave up mentally on us
we got we've gotten really far in this
game yeah yeah is this considered far I
think we might be able to do it today
oh we have to be small
well
you're real tiny
all right let everybody go first since
I'm
big yeah so cute so cute cute
welcome to my world involving probably
out together we gotta get on people's
heads some people
oh the smaller we are the more ones
oh wait can you can you jump so that I
can like since you're taller
oh
three of us carrying a big
a big Cali okay
wait thank you you need someone else
oh gosh
they're like fleas
[Laughter]
a little tasty fruit please oh wait
isn't there a Japanese yeah yeah
oh the Japanese what isn't there a
Japanese folk tale about this about this
lady with a hammer and like oh she like
me
[Music]
okay
stand on my head feel it we have this
one
um
should I no okay
there we go there we go
[Music]
everyone yeah everyone's stand up and
then they can grow I think should I
should I stay big yeah no we all got to
be uh we need one big person I think
it's good just to be on crony's head
because we all need to like stand on
everybody
everybody's got to be small yeah but
let's all be small first
excuse me okay all right now it's not a
shrink
um yeah
a little bit at least
no normal size is good okay now
everybody stack up everyone can get on
Cali yeah yeah yeah I wonder if you
don't press the button I don't think
that's tall enough okay there we go yeah
she'll get bigger once we're on her head
yeah true true yeah
[Music]
small yeah true
I'm sorry not everybody's tired yeah we
need something
[Music]
huh do a good jump nice
job
[Music]
nice nice
Stairway to Heaven okay I can't get up
oh it's fine
oops
all right let's reorganize the stairs
yeah it doesn't matter the orientation
small enough it looks kind of big
[Music]
oh my goodness
oh yeah I think it's too big
really
okay insane like everybody else how
insulting
not now I started on that
okay
oh okay I'm on top of you
come on up crony we get to YouTube I
don't know if Korean can get up uh no
girl get out of the way for a second
wow
[Music]
[Applause]
no I want to be big forever
this is good whatever
[Music]
yeah
we sound so tired all of a sudden
we're close to beating it though we only
have two more words oh really
what does it mean by offline only oh
[Music]
out of the way out of the way no make me
you guys are too happy
oh crony push that one down there on top
of the other
on the other side yeah okay yeah
maybe
I swear to God
okay that works I think you need to push
it a little further
a little bit like push it in or in yeah
yeah yeah
nice job
and then father gets on top over there
I'm sorry
[Music]
oh
can you please
[Laughter]
okay okay
my head is a jumping pad all right hold
on
okay
here we go
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
all right babe we'll help you get up
come on Kiara if you want to jump on my
head uh give baby please trying to be
the stair okay go go yeah all right we
need people up here to help them
jump get on my head
true
stop okay that should be good maybe
I'm sorry yeah
nice nice
yeah good job nice okay
[Music]
do I need to go first
we need it
I don't know if we need it one of the
blocks just need to be a staircase put
it on because it's not staircase
is that possible because Iris can push
her block and make it like more even so
that we can adjust the stairs
to the other side Maybe idea should I
just Sudoku
let's have gouda jump over to the side
and then she just pushes the very bottom
one a little bit yeah that's a good idea
make a stare
let's make a stare okay I mean even from
here I think we could do it if we move
the the gray one a little bit more to
the right then she can pass through
but then how did the people on the other
side get up when the staircase is
flipped
we have to we have to make a staircase
[Music]
all right
okay looks good
nice nice
I'm here to get my orange black
staircase shape staircase shape I need
to get my purple actually matter if it's
staircase shape as long as any person as
long as everyone's on the left side yeah
nobody go on the other side okay okay
wait wait wait let's go down a big one
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait
come on either side of your block and
fix it I tried and it pushed it forward
oh that should
be I think you should feel fine even if
it's not a stick or will it I think it
needs to well because they're smaller
anyways So eventually at the end if
everyone's on the left side is that
gonna land on it
I think it's good I Drop It Like It's
Hot Okay
Legendary and I think everyone needs to
come to the top for now yeah yeah yeah
okay
Kira
okay wait okay
you know we gotta get funny I'm gonna
get Subway give me a second we didn't
need that oh my God yourself
love yourself crony thank you all right
um
what the [\h__\h] okay
well let's see ready for me to drop it
like a side
anyone else needed to get over there no
right I want to hear you're eating a
sandwich of Subway that I hear I hear
Subway paper it'll fall on the other
side
I was gonna jump
[Music]
what happened I was I was gonna jump why
didn't you
all right no worries
[Music]
we have the hardest job in the entire
world
uh Reese's Puffs
a Subway
what's up boy you want a uh
out of your mouth
thank you
God we're losing it now we're losing it
what's I think crony meatball marinara
again how many days old
[Laughter]
can you like not finished the sandwich
in one day or something I ordered two
foot long oh
that's just order another one stop
judging me I've already just in case
okay that's fine come back
we gotta make a staircase yeah
all right good good
next next we need there needs to be more
people up there to make stairs
okay I made it whoa just from Emma's
head big jump you can try to get up
there guys
okay yeah yeah
okay okay nobody move oh sorry sorry
hold on
okay
nice shuttle Bay maybe yeah okay
all right okay we won't ask questions
all right line it up
looking good
concentrate oh maybe okay
um
[Laughter]
we're getting to the other wall so push
come on first I got it all right don't
push it yeah don't push it all the way
right oh God yeah
just be careful when you get to your
block that you don't push it over but it
might be better all the way just in case
[Music]
or so funny you want to go next
oh Ami and I are at the safest so we can
probably go at the end
[Music]
no it's fine it's fine there was a lot
of space okay
scared
[\h__\h] I'm scared off mine yeah it's okay
I think you can push my ears a little
it's fine yeah yeah yours is pretty safe
[Music]
nice nice we did it
yay
all the way to the right side anyway
because they're all a different width
yeah I think maybe we could have it
maybe it's a typical
levels
moving your screen's moving oh God oh my
God okay okay wait no jumping just wait
till the end okay
okay
are you still eating your sandwich
cronies
[Music]
[Laughter]
while we're trying to win this why are
you eating
fine I guess I'll never again
if we stack and go with bees I know
right oh yeah
[Laughter]
all right stack on the first two people
that get on the elevator yeah
stack on us
don't die right every man for himself
here imagine dying yeah
okay
stand up going into your color
um
[Laughter]
I can't get up
I can't push anymore okay there we go
there we go there we go okay okay wow
wow wow we're making it go go go go go
go go go go go go go go go go away
[Laughter]
it's just
no blame appropriately please
I blame everyone including myself all
right A lot of people guys
it's okay I'll just let it end I figured
believing
leaving all right hop on us meet and Bae
no one else I think the problem is
though you'll need to jump to get out
when the platform Falls and you won't be
able to jump if people are on your head
so everybody gotta get a quick up get up
quicker too late too late
when we stacked on two people's head
yeah to jump off is the only thing the
people you guys have to remember to jump
off okay okay
I just don't have any comment anymore
just laugh oh just wait till you get to
the top
okay
Autumn can just walk yeah exactly
what it's because the bottom two can
just walk off exactly it's okay it's too
far though you won't be able to walk
here we go
fun nice
I was just looking at it I think it is
probably the same thing happened we were
just looking at the people on the
elevator still
laughs
all right go go go go go go go go
you guys are being selfish
this run wasn't gonna be the one anyway
it wasn't the one it didn't felt it
didn't feel right didn't feel right yeah
if we just stack like stairs against the
wall okay
I go
nice okay
huh you go away
you guys just gotta wait you're gonna
hold your horses someone used to play
more Super Mario for practice I was
gonna jump in midair but didn't let me
double jump
everybody go
down
Mario
it's not how this game works not every
game has this game
oh you can apply it totally
all right go
okay that works all right okay one at a
time don't forget to jump into the
screen
don't forget to jump
ing at the bottom okay
at the top careful we don't really have
to be alive yeah it's just me at the
bottom it's actually it's actually
better but you probably shouldn't be one
yeah
don't touch it anymore okay okay let's
go
[Music]
nice
hi hi
okay yeah
[Applause]
well done everyone
oh thank God elevator
not this
ah at least so strange not me yeah
not a scrolly sorry
[Music]
oh my God
I didn't realize I was going to be
listening to some ASMR mukbangs
I go beautiful
okay there we go nice all right why are
you eating
foreign
how dare I try to live
how dare you
that's how far it goes yeah yeah just
wait till what
nobody has problems if we go as high as
possible there we go okay okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you
can we get much higher yes we can
actually we can get a little higher
that's why you got it
I said get some jokes now incredible
nice job Kiara hell yeah yeah I'm
rocking GT I'm about to finish it in a
few streams oh nice cool look at him
hell yeah I have a question
excuse me jump off
thank you
look at the door yet though can I ask
you a question why the [\h__\h] why the [\h__\h]
did you fall Bae first when I was ready
to go to the door but you fell off thank
you
take the key
because
okay now you can come back now come back
just don't die okay okay
we just wait until it goes all the way
up high as it can in which case you're
stopping it crony so maybe move on
well
we're Flats remember
okay okay okay okay
all right that's it she was stopping I
think that really is the highest we can
go yeah I'm three
no
okay okay
[Music]
oh no yeah
wait will that make some low-key stairs
yeah smart now what now we all jumped
that was a good idea though
gives us at least a little bit of a
leeway I guess right no I think it gives
us less of one because then
I don't know let's see I'm still clearly
ready or so clearly so if we make a
Stairway that goes over the ledge then
those people can be the first to walk
off as quick as possible yeah but then
it's so fast that the people behind
don't get time
they would have been able to get off
how to get out again
[Music]
make a Stairway that arches
one more can be on top of me
I think no okay I mean it was possible
[Music]
you're trying to make as much of a
Stairway as possible before it rises all
the way to the top like Dura and Iris if
you very quickly
[Music]
at the end
do I go to the top first so gura Kiara
fauna Iris walk off as quick as you can
ready
[Laughter]
[Applause]
it was good there's the execution was
not very good how is it
break it again
[Music]
no I think I think it's nice
[Applause]
[Music]
all right last one all right last one
please don't say that don't push
all right well do not push the button
is
[Laughter]
an obstacle I know we all want to push
the button when we see a language so
make sure what it would do right right
now
we know it ends the game so oh don't
push none either I think that one ends
the game as well
too early
stop eating
here
this is a rapper easy Mission
what if careful watch what if
make a big old stair over it and jump
you guys can jump on my head
you're smart
I'm so sorry
[Music]
I'm sorry I'm sorry I really didn't mean
to blow up at you like that we're
snapping snapping on stream
this game I'm sorry I didn't want to
yell at you Amelia
[Music]
it's all right we'll just snap and then
we'll have a big group hug afterwards
I'm gonna watch this game okay
I want to slap someone right now
pushed each other and just be real nice
hold in here don't slap anymore me
the peer pressure of being yelled at Lee
you don't want to be the one to end the
game
no we're fine we're good I want to slap
that sandwich out of your hands
not the sandwich
[Music]
way out of this
not the subway
okay I'm holding froggy down okay for
security reasons just walk on it no no
no
no jump now
I'm good you can do it no don't do it
yet okay
all right one at a time one at a time
Kiara
um
[Laughter]
this is the worst level in the game
this one we thought it couldn't get any
worse how bad could it be
[Music]
okay
I have a really hot pink man on my side
your server
that's back up at the end yep move up a
little hey we gotta move
all right we're good we're good
all right I'm gonna jump over this
little button okay we got it this
is
push it it says don't push in big
capital letters
okay and what do you normally do with
buttons you push them oh this one says
don't push fauna
presence if not to be pushed all right
I'll take the fall one more time one at
a time
but push your buttons
here someone else come on okay nice
okay okay
now we're gonna need to make a Stairway
Stairway to Heaven
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay you gotta come closer guys you can
come closer okay
there's someone crying
I'm
sorry no I didn't mean I'm sorry I'm
sorry
[Music]
all right
we're doing a good job
guys
yeah
stop talking badly about meatball
marinara
I'm scared how dare you not during Pico
Park crony not during people Park it's a
pretty on the Belt
okay
whoa what wait what
I was so shocked what I jumped how does
that happen
I'm the king is ping
sometimes it really is just pink it's
because this game is a bad game
there's nothing fun about it
let's hide together with leashes
oh yeah not kayoshi I was spicy
sounds like a Pokemon
it means good friend
um
oh I was waiting for fauna okay
all because of that meatball fudge and
marinara
hey guys leave plenty of space for the
other person to land
okay ah you know it's okay it happens to
the best of us
I've lost my sanity oh see see this
thing it blocks the way
yeah you have to do it by the head you
can still oh yeah okay they're doing
great
even if you get stuck on the head you
can still jump it's like really good
okay let's see who pushes the button
anxiety
[Music]
thank you
just don't push the button
all right Iris I'll go okay
all right here we go
oh okay
foreign
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
it oh man hey welcome back bad ping
hurt oh yeah
we can do this yeah yeah now I feel like
we're getting kind of talks
don't hate the player hate the game okay
I mean you can kind of hate the play for
a bit it's fun no well that's a really
toxic mindset let's see you screw up huh
yeah yeah I'm watching yeah okay
[Applause]
[Laughter]
which is funny because this was supposed
to be the last level why can't we finish
this because we just want to be together
longer yeah
[Music]
what if we all Stacks we don't have to
worry about pressing it we all do stairs
and then the last person has to worry
about yeah you can jump really well over
things
somebody stand right on the edge on like
on the ledge wait babe okay that works
Let's help help them get up
screw your buttons game
I think whoever like if you're already
passed that you could probably just go
because
okay
all right who else needs help getting up
Superior okay wait like Connie's back on
on Cali
hey I haven't screwed up in a long time
now long time
all right
I get some room
[Music]
what I don't I don't know if we should
go that high
yeah
Iris just drop down just drop down Okay
Okay
[Laughter]
jump on Kiara's head okay okay girl jump
on jump on iris's head wow okay okay
okay
wait wait stay there stay there okay
somebody else jump uh This Way yep okay
a jump on Kiara's head Bay oh two people
for each stock yeah yeah okay okay
okay okay nice uh maybe I should go over
there too okay okay I think we can reach
the key probably
I think if they jump she can reach the
key all right hold on yeah I probably
could but okay just in case I really
want that responsibility not really no
okay I'm scared all right we'll start
new stairs jump on base head coach
listen listen to your Senpai
all right well that was a really good
idea though that was a really good run
yeah
we just have to we just have to
replicate it
okay somebody just stay in front of the
button Cali yep
okay all right guys
let's take a deep breath take a deep
breath okay let's find ourselves go
ahead and get them jump on Kelly's head
and jump over her jump over
yep okay you're good you're good
don't let it get to your head
yep all right I'm on the way
[Music]
all right
hold on Tony wait
I know just giving space
okay
all right you can go
Iris you want to go
[Music]
this game breaks you down jump on your
head scared me for a second
all right all right fauna do you want to
go first or do you want to jump on my
head or okay
new stack
all right hold on just wait all right
Cara jump on my head was more scary I
mean
maybe we just need to make the stack
taller so that there's no there's no
yeah
[Music]
sorry that was just so scary
all right uh you guys can jump on my
head
all right
I hear cracking noises I wonder what it
is
just the Subway sandwich I haven't
touched my sandwich in like 15 minutes
you have like a you have more than just
the meatball marinara yeah like I said I
ordered two foot long Subs I thought he
ordered two of Meatballs
okay it's about variety my friend all
right
oh yeah this one or you guys can jump on
my head
Okay jump over okay okay it's fine just
stack this up you're going
keep going babe
[Laughter]
yeah it seems okay it works
now with that breathiness this is like
almost more toxic than Monopoly all
right babe you can jump over it all
right uh Kiara you want to get on my
head and jump over oops I didn't mean to
jump over yet or actually maybe you
should get them Watsons
okay
okay all right we'll make a tall stack
so make it make a tall stack make make a
style yeah I don't wanna I Wanna Be last
all right okay Iris
okay okay be careful okay do I just stay
here and don't don't jump yeah yeah
don't do it okay uh bait can you jump on
iris's head just be careful
okay
okay all right corny jump at Bay's head
maybe you should move a bit faster okay
there yeah yeah okay all right keep the
Stag okay and then uh fauna do you want
to jump on on top of bay or do you want
to oh never mind
here okay okay here we go nice nice job
here all right
somebody should not yet not yet wait
Iris move a little bit Iris moves yeah
then this way or this way
could safely just walk off without
worries of touching the button okay nice
okay okay
okay
all right pressure up with me
or put more pressure that is scary wait
stay there stay there just stay there
okay for now we'll figure out a way uh
uh okay whoever screws this up is gonna
be hated
[Laughter]
um
like that
and then get on the snack the stack all
right I'll give you two days
I'll happily eat it if it's yours okay
Cali come up here and grab the key get
on our stack yeah I'll give you a five
day old one
okay
jump down okay okay babe go on Cali's
head yep okay okay
all right we're making a new stack okay
I'm gonna you have to jump over at some
point
you can wait until until I okay
[Music]
then
okay come over yep
okay it's so close guys we can do it uh
Cara move a little closer
[Music]
thank you okay okay so yep wait there
okay just wait there good I haven't died
yet okay okay
um
[Laughter]
uh how about this how about we do this
wait wait fauna can you drop down on the
other side of Iris
because I trust you to jump more okay
Iris get up on his head
okay okay
let's jump on the next deck
okay okay okay you can go oh you just go
yeah yeah just get out of here
whatever happens okay
thank you jump on you first and then
climb up to Bay yeah yeah
you can jump over
Kiara wait there don't I don't like this
okay
okay now fauna can you jump over next to
Kiara you could do it okay Kiara get up
on his head we move closer to the
pressure yeah crony you can jump takes
her very high okay
oh where'd you move okay okay
trying to get over here
Cody just jumped yet okay now he's right
here Kiara jump jump on base head
that's good
it's gonna rip out
real quick stop here don't do anything
okay I'm gonna move back a little bit
yeah
back yeah yes she can catch you you
can't okay
you catch me all right so just go Full
Speed Ahead towards me and don't forget
to jump
please slide just in case
you can jump on my head
I'm good I'm comfortable here
okay yep okay now I'm gonna go and then
you guys need to go okay wait go to can
you put me a little closer thank you
okay now gonna go first
okay let's go yeah yeah you want to jump
on Cali's head yeah
there's no pressure there's no pressure
no pressure at all no pressure
Mommy
did we make it do we have time to try
again
[Music]
we could try one more okay someone left
oh my God so many people left
and not answered
[Music]
uninstalled I'm gonna uninstall this
game as soon as we're done babies let's
go let's jump space bar I think I think
some people might be checked out forever
I lost my appetite I love playing this
game
[Music]
we're missing a little
not being her position because once you
[\h__\h] up at the end then everybody hates
you forever
[Music]
that's okay
I'm getting messed up for existing it's
fine
I will put fauna higher
at a certain time
so we might have to do it without her
oh yeah yeah
[Music]
that's a sad way to end it
is a snack oh no okay it's okay
[Music]
it's just a game oh I can't die if I
leave no no it should be enough
[Music]
thank you
damn
no just so chat no she didn't leave
because she messed up she's just uh you
know sometimes sometimes we have
appointments or we have meetings or
schedule stuff we need to do so yeah
yeah that's why yeah
it was just weird timing yeah
let's go stay there well the screen
never says offline yeah I think if maybe
if I try to retry maybe she won't be
there okay maybe maybe yeah yeah okay
there we go okay we don't look quite as
cool without green we don't look like a
rainbow we're not really balanced yeah
Irish
no risk yep jump over I didn't like four
minutes until we win I don't know about
that you know honestly I feel like peace
the more people mess up Yeah the more
you don't blame yourself anymore yeah
the less the less spot like the less
spots you know I'm so confident I don't
mind going last next next time we go
through the buttons
yes just really let it oh
I did jump
yeah sure you did I didn't believe it
wait wait wait
let me stand close okay you guys can
jump on my head now
laughs
[Music]
yes yes
[Laughter]
we all played games are more
difficulties
what do you mean
see see all right let's do this
okay who's not confident uh whoever is
gonna drop first here is gonna stay at
this button for a little bit so maybe
Kelly okay never mind
Callie just stay until the end all right
Kara jump on iris's head I am very
confident okay
scared about being scared oh boy oh
lordies
[Music]
stay there
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah nice
all right
um you want to go
wait not yet
um yeah jump on Kelly's head yep
okay all right there we go okay go to
the next one
[Music]
all right jump on the other side wait
stay there actually we need to get the
key all right
um Kiara you're gonna have to jump
okay
you can do it you can do it should I go
closer like this
all right get closer
uh okay I thought Kiara could get it if
you jump but sure I think yeah yeah it's
fun oh my being pro look at that okay
yeah look at that smooth moves all right
jump on my head players over
[Music]
sorry I should have caught you okay uh
Cali you want to jump actually Iris wait
wait wait because I think Iris gonna
need help getting over a movie okay oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
this is the worst game I ever played
he's not saying much because I've played
a lot of games still but oh man oh my
God
[Music]
all right here we go again
round two round three yeah
breaking right now
all right thanks
all right let's drop yep all right you
want to go to the next one forever okay
Iris oh okay sorry to go to the next one
yep okay carnego onto Kiara's head yep
do it I'm here
all right uh running on to iris's head
all right stay there purple
all right guys here
I can I haven't died yet okay
uh I think you might be able to get the
key yeah careful okay I'm good don't
worry all right
uh Cal do you want to jump maybe on base
head if you can make it can we die
I won't die what do you mean if I die
just die yeah because of the Ping all
right come on over jump on the other
side all right wait there
all right um we gotta get Kiara and Bay
over so yep just stay just worried start
glitching for a second I thought I'm
really worried about it okay Bae go up
the top look at you
come here all right jump down into my
arms yeah we are next
good huh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah come
on Kelly's head yeah yeah okay I'm
really good all right go to amekiara
come to me into my arms everybody
okay
um wait
I guess crony either way Irish you're
confident right you can jump over after
I'm worried about Iris yeah whatever
happens just remember I love you guys
all right get over it get over on
Kelly's head that is so not convenient
you can go over
all right uh bay bay next
my my new song says love hey it's all
the same if you know
okay just
scream all right Iris okay or actually
do you want to clear give her clearance
maybe or something yeah I kind of want
to clearance all right let me get out
let me get out of here
[Laughter]
thank you
[Music]
that's what we're gonna be doing
turning into one yeah maybe in a few
weeks I'll uh I'll see you maybe if you
guys want to do something again
always yeah
[Music]
well besides that I'll see uh some of
you tomorrow at Amor Goose
Club
pretty early too for some of you guys
yeah but it will be worth it and yeah I
can't wait I think it will be fun we can
show you guys the Cosmic Cube the whole
life Cosmic Cube thank you everybody's
been waiting
yeah if we unlock them in time yeah we
unlocked one hairstyle okay that's good
oh
yeah
I love everyone here and everyone
[Music]
yeah
I might have screamed at people but that
that don't mean nothing it's okay
[Music]
so uh I realize that I've been turning
off was this automatic gain control this
time so do you mind if I scream and see
if it like adjusts the screaming for
sure you bet okay
ah
is it still loud oh my God I think it'd
be like the entire time but
um I mean it sounded like a like a roar
it's funny
I like sounded like a horror movie a
primal scream oh so it doesn't get
adjusted that sucks okay yeah I'm sorry
about that chronister it's still
beautiful though thank you you're
welcome
I didn't mean it when I said Subway is
Made Me Love Subway no Subway
um but you know what crony is allowed to
like whatever she likes yeah I'll treat
you too a Subway no I would no you will
not do that we will not be eating Subway
when I come over sorry could
it's uh what excuse me did I hear you
correctly and I hear you ask what's
wrong with Subway
the bread is actually officially not
bread did you guys know that what
oh yeah
the ingredients uh make it so that
officially it cannot be considered bread
so crony you might want to reconsider
your life choices
so many other good sandwich shops out
there though
is it cake
oh yes I need to go make some soup to
give myself I'm gonna go watch horror
movies with my college friends
um they didn't they haven't seen the
Mist before and I want them
yeah I made them watch that then we're
playing a tabletop so that's gonna be
fun
[Music]
yeah this is really fun though thank you
guys for joining
me that was super fun yeah we can do it
again sometime soon in the next few
weeks if you guys are down who knows
maybe some people music again I feel
like it makes our bombs stronger no yeah
have another six
thank you for watching
[Applause]
[Music]
everybody
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign