[Music]
do
so
[Music]
wow
good morning afternoon evening
hello
hi
guess what today is
can you guess
yeah yeah
yes it's international
taco day i've named it that now
ah
thank you everyone for your birthday
wishes thank you thank you thank you
oh my goodness i've
i've been overwhelmed since like well
yeah well into
you know
yesterday
just oh just over overwhelming amount of
happy birthdays i've been getting and
all your support
i have to i have to be careful i have to
be
i have to make sure i don't let my my
ceiling came in today um
because it's a very important thing for
everyone
because
it's not only my birthday but it's also
also a day i want to be most thankful to
you guys as well for for supporting me
all this time
thank you thank you thank you how's your
day how's your day been everyone
been good
being well
still alive
barely alive
excited i'm excited too i mean
so many people worked
with a lot a lot
i can't even talk properly
so so so many people worked so hard to
make today happen including you guys
um so
i'm really really really
happy to be able to share some
some fun things with you guys
yeah
ah so after a little bit it's hot it's
gonna go
um we're gonna do our first set of uh
collins in a few minutes and then we're
gonna take a little break in the middle
to do some announcements
then we're gonna have more collins
yes yes there's lots and lots of coins
and then at the very end of the stream i
will be
revealing
something else announcement number two
yeah and uh
make sure if you guys haven't checked it
out have you guys seen all the all the
happy birthday artworks and gifts i've
been getting on twitter
oh man actually before i went to sleep i
saw that my art tag was trending i was
like
and i spent a lot of time looking at it
i forgot to uh hit like on a lot of them
while i was looking at it first time so
i'm going back seeing all the all the
messages
yeah
it's just the thought of imagining
small tacos taking out their pencils
their
tablets their pen paints
finger paint
and just drawing something for me it
really warms my heart
it really does so thank you so much
everyone and those of you who didn't you
know just just came here to hang out you
know for the celebration thank you thank
you thank you
you too can be the sneak up
i don't know where my thought process
was going but it made more sense in my
head
oh man i can tell i'm kind of nervous
i don't get nervous that often but right
now i'm just
keeping it together i'm okay i'm okay
i'll be fine i'll be fine
ah
i'm nervous because
especially since since we're collins too
um i feel like i haven't had the chance
to talk to
everyone one-on-one
it's often lately
i've been busy everyone's been busy so
i hope i hope i hope i can i can i can
put on my
improve my communication brain today i
haven't forgotten how to communicate
i can do it oh man i prepared balloons
for the garden and everything i hope i
hope i hope yeah i hope that you like it
oh
[Music]
ah okay
where's the cake um it's still in the
oven you know a lot of things in my life
still need a little bit more time in the
oven including including my own cake
i actually
um i've been so
out of
touch with how time was going i wanted
to order cake for myself but i realized
i realized i didn't order it actually i
had it in the cart but i forgot to check
it out so i need to order myself okay
i'll probably get it tomorrow the day
after tomorrow and
yeah
[Laughter]
i'll be fine i'll be fine
what kind of cake is i want to get a
strawberry
strawberry i like strawberry cake
no
i've been so out of it but um i think
we're gonna i'm gonna start going in and
waiting for for friends to join me oh
okay
i'll be fine i'll be fine everything
will be fun everything will be tied up
everything will be tied up
okay i have everything ready i have
everything
okay
i'm so nervous
i'm more nervous than house for for
for the interview for whole life you
know oh
happy birthday
[Music]
thank you
i'm so nervous
it's okay it'll go by fast it'll go by
fast we'll make it go by fast okay
thanks sir thanks for thanks for thanks
for calling oh my i can't even speak
of course on international taco day um
as is tradition you know you must uh
first greet the priestess and then pay
your respects to the taco duchies
would you like to do a short
introduction of yourself oh sure
hello everybody amelia watson hello i'm
number one detective here to wish my
favorite you know happy birthday
thank you
yeah
i actually um i made i made you
something well it's not something that i
can give to you in person right now but
um here here's the
oh wait wait this is the wrong way this
is the wrong one
oh my god
oh there it is here it is
oh
yeah that one's you're safe to show that
on the stream if you wanted to oh can i
yeah
ah
hold on hold on i need to open up uh
this is so cute
oh my goodness yeah
uh
for chad i can't see uh i made i made a
a taco duchy terrarium you guys are uh
very comfortable now inside of a small
tank these guys are so comfy
i wonder [\h__\h] ah it's big
sorry
it's okay look at this
oh you know i actually love terrarium
except like everything i've
tried like
making or i'm bad at taking care of
plants and they all die and
every time i see pictures of yours i'm
just like oh my god this is so good
sometimes the plants do die but you just
need the right lighting i think and then
yeah and just observe them and sometimes
they die and i'll replace them with like
better plants that suit the conditions
but yeah yeah it's not terrarium ah
thank you oh my goodness oh i'm like
grinning from ear to ear right now
did you like
make the stone like how did yeah
it's it's a piece of concrete that i
carved by hand so i like uh oh wow
yeah i mean it only took like an hour
but
even though
it's it's sitting in my terraria right
right now but one day i'd like to
actually give it to you if you want it
it's just a little stone
because i'll be i'll be getting myself
an office sometimes you know i wanna
decorate it i'll take good care of it
thank you so much
welcome it was really fun to
make oh
okay i do i have to make sure
oh no emotion
but it's so cute
i actually i should have thought about
more more topics to talk about but have
you been
i'm pretty good oh why don't we do it we
could do one of those uh
i guess the impression thank you so yeah
even though we've done this so many
times oh yes what was your first
impression of nina my inaudible
ah
well i remember being really nervous
obviously to debut with you and
everybody else but i always thought you
were so nice and and sweet and and i
remember it was like right before debut
and i was like you know i need a drawing
because i was going to use it in my
video but then i ran out of time to make
the video and then i i felt really bad
because i never used the drawings oh no
no no
it's kind of like uh it's kind of like a
a treat for chat they know it exists
yeah they're hard drives
yeah they're just waiting one day one
day
it's a secret
oh
but yeah um i could say the same thing
to you honestly my like
like
like like you on stream when people
think you're like you know the gamer
gremlin and stuff but like the army i
know is like the most
helpful sweetest person i've like
one of the best like friends i've ever
met and oh yeah
says you ina yeah
but yeah and i'm also i'm so happy that
i actually got to meet you in person me
too
oh man i hope we can do more fun things
in the future yes we will 100
lots of fun all right
it's my time bye ina happy birthday i
hope you
can go so i'm excited for the
announcements thank you
thank you bye
ah that was on me
put an icon right here
oh this is so cute i actually wanna i
actually love visuals where it's like
um
but there's a lot of like plants and
flowers in here in your office and house
what
could it be
[Music]
a little nervous and probably gonna be
leaking ceiling from
fields soon but
these are very emotional yeah it's like
it's your it's your special day so all
the it's like everything
uh all the pressure building on from
everything and then it's all about you
and then it's like wow and then yeah
there's a baby
like a truck feels like you're just like
okay i'm gonna be fine i'm gonna be fine
and then like it hits you and you're
just like oh man
the voice to your falls
oh yeah
oh the plug is gone now
it's gone forever the flood is coming
all right yeah
i'm holding on so far though so
oh so boy so far so good
how are you
i'm good i'm okay i'm very tired i slept
so much i slept like i think it was
thirteen fourteen fifteen hours yeah
i think it's a mood like sometimes you
don't get enough sleep when you're tired
but sometimes you get too much sleep and
you're tired and just like
yeah just never handing it
yeah
well i'm trying to hold off until i get
the caffeine headache but i haven't
gotten the caffeine headache yet so
maybe it's good to you know like detox
from caffeine sometimes i do have to do
that on purpose because i drink so much
delicious it's so yummy
that's priceless
sometimes you gotta trick yourself into
thinking it's like caffeinated by
drinking decaf
i know
should not
exist said it
caffeinated coffee
oh
oh it's like the place
you know with coffee sometimes
no
it doesn't taste as good
i know but you gotta trick yourself for
your heart that's beating so fast from
all the coffee
think of your arteries think of my heart
my arteries my health yeah
hmm do you have a ques can you ask me
one of those questions on your eyes
what was your first impression of enoch
my very first impression of
my nemo um
oh you reminded me of like the really
quiet smart kid in school the one that
has a lot in the corner
yes it does
she have asked
raised glasses with the shine
exactly
and then your art skills were freaking
crazy
like that one kid in school that was
always drawing
something
always
that was mean
yeah
i was always jealous of those kids
because they were just so it's so
effortless but it's not effortless
because you know drawing takes a lot of
time and effort so it's really i don't
know it's really i look up to you a lot
ina oh i look up to you a lot too girl
like you know
you know like when when people first see
you
like
they think you're like the what's
ultimate
kind of aura
but like but like you're
not like the softest like
sweetest person i know i say the stomach
too but like
like everyone and myth too especially
since we've been i guess almost together
for
two years now like
man i would have not been
able to stay staying without you guys
yeah
oh
talk to you later
[Music]
okay that was that was close i almost
i almost yeah
it's okay it's holding on my tear doctor
holding on so far but man ame gura
everyone everyone really really
is one of the reasons i can continue to
try try so hard you know
deep breath deep breath
okay
so
ha
next
guest is actually actually sent in a
video
yeah one of my dear dear senpai's
i want to share with you guys i haven't
watched it yet
watching it for the first time
it's everyone's favorite
what time is empire
okay let's see let's see let me let me
get rid of the
background music for a bit okay three
two one
[Music]
she's so cute
um
[Music]
has a beautiful voice i love all her
songs
[Music]
i can't say the same thing
[Applause]
or my hair
[Music]
is
so
i would love to
ah she's so cute i'm sorry i'm standing
[Music]
yes together together together
together
we will sing an original song okay
[Music]
hi
[Applause]
hey
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah
what tommy 75 so
cute
oh and she drew me in four minutes i
should show you what i do
what time
it was with my mouse okay
i drew her drawing me
uh
yeah she also put her her icon in
wait
yeah it's so cute
ah
oh i'm so happy actually i do have
another video
um
message
put you put this on top of chat
message this time from
staff son
aka our favorite
ichan
also i think a chan aitan um will be in
the hospital for a bit um so everyone
please go wish her well let's see let's
see what she has to say don happy
birthday innocent
yay
[Music]
maybe it's difficult to guess your age
because you're a taco
ah please
wait
i actually saw your stream that you
mentioned why you know hololiver first
and i'm glad to know you get us through
my twitter or something
all right yes
i like your intellectual humor and your
oh my god
voice i love the atmosphere that only
you can have
of course i respect you of of course i
respect of your talent for drawing
drawing
of course i respect your talent for
drawing and i want to say thank you for
drawing me also people
i'm looking forward to seeing your
various activities in hololens
i'm happy if i can be support to you
thank you so much bye bye
[Music]
it's actually so bad at english like
like sometimes you can tell when people
use like translators and stuff but ah
really tries hard to communicate like
you know normally in english and it's
it's amazing
and yeah even even when she's staff
she's so kind to all the talents and
works really hard behind the scenes so
oh thank you so much ichan
yeah
she is really good at english and she
says very kind and i hope i hope for a
swift recovery and uh yeah thank you
thank you so much for taking time to
send me a message even when you were we
were super super busy thank you thank
you thank you
yeah
ah
okay oh my goodness
ah my heart is like it feels fuzzy
my heart feels so fuzzy
huh
[Music]
my heart is
all over the place but i'm doing well
how about you it's kind of
nerve-wracking isn't it doing it it's
talking to so many people yeah it's like
it's different because like the first
one i was like you know yeah
just have just have uh my gemini's
calling but this time i'm just like
more than more than more than like
people i've interacted for the last like
couple of months all talking to me
we all want to wish you a happy
birthday thank you
i did i see you you have just done a
little ms paint drawing and i think
that's a wonderful coincidence because
i also made you an ms paint right
[Music]
i love your drawings oh my god oh thank
you
i don't know why i did that but i'll
crop this okay
it's okay look takodachi's
it's okay they can have it for a bit
so generous of you sharing on your
birthday
they'll give it back right
certainly they'll give it back
they won't have a choice surely they'll
give it back
oh
how have you been
i'm good
can i can i also answer the question oh
yes the first impression
yeah well i feel like it's
a little different
since i got to watch your streams before
meeting yeah but
i did think um before
you all debuted and i saw
saw your pictures for the first time
i
i think you might be the biggest
surprise
i think i was expecting some kind of
evil
kusogaki
we got the sweetest and softest and most
talented priestess of all oh thank you i
mean i could i could be you know a
spoiled brat kind of person
well
today is your chance right on your
birthday you're allowed to be spoiled
brat right
that's true but i feel like i feel like
i probably apologize like straight after
i think you would
you don't have it in you but but that's
okay because we love you just how you
are oh thank you you're even better
yeah
i should say like
like i think like my expect like not
expectations but like my impression of
you like when i saw
you for the first time like
your avatar and yourself you just like
you just like radiate
comfy
thank you and i was like i am healed
oh but it's the same for you you guys
comfy comfy queen comfy cocoa
extraordinaire oh comfy sunlight
sunshine nature
fauna
i will shine my nature beam onto you
yeah oh man
oh i i miss you guys i hope we can we
can hang out sometime again
[Music]
i still i still remember you just owning
the games at the work oh no why is that
what everyone remembers
it's like you like people would expect
you to be kind of like you know laid
back oh i don't know how to game so like
when it comes down then you just like
you're like pro gaming
on my secret
actually that's another good question um
my impression of you
at the off collab
was that you had the most senpai energy
i've ever seen
maybe it's because you were parading
around your kohai but
it was like you were opening all the
doors you were checking on everyone
making sure everyone was okay
you were
you were so
so such a senpai
thank you
oh very well taken care of by emails
i'm glad you felt that
i'm sorry it's just walking behind
everyone and like just keeping the door
open for like my family and stuff
so it kind of charged right over i guess
yeah
we were well taken care of oh i'm glad
and glad
well happy birthday ina happy birthday
you deserve all of the best birthday
wishes i hope i can eat something yummy
thank you i'll go i'll go get cake after
yeah yes get get the cake
okay thank you love you thanks for
joining
bye bye bye
thank you
that was far now everyone
oh i forgot to add eight town
oh
i feel so warm and fluffy inside right
now
oh boy
wait
okay
could it be
it could be
it is hello
hi
happy birthday
thank you
oh
you're sort of you look so beautiful oh
everything looks beautiful oh my
goodness
including this uh icon looks very
beautiful
[Laughter]
no
i i have a gift for you ah
i have two versions oh
i lost some of my heart
i have this one but i forgot something
very important oh and i didn't realize i
forgot until i saw watani senpai draw it
in her doodle
uh i forgot your beauty mark oh it's
okay it's okay one of the blushes can be
good oh i need to crop this too oh my
goodness
oh [\h__\h]
look at me
i have my
now i can draw like one two three
four five more times
same time
you have like are you you're
right-handed right yeah are they all
right right hands you have four right
hands oh my goodness what a deal
oh he's so cute
i actually really love watching your
like drawing hello ma'am streams cause
it's it's like so
unexpected something i could never do
i love it
if you if you close your eyes
close your eyes and imagine the worst
things possible i bet you you could
oh that's so weird it's so weird to hear
because for so long i've watched you
draw and watch your drawing streams
it's like probably my most watched
hololive content oh my name
is oh my gosh so it's really weird to
hear you say you've watched me draw oh
gosh my abomination
it's like the side of creative drawing
that i can't really
do myself like i just i just don't know
how and you just do it flawlessly and
hiding like high level i'm just like
mummy's a genius
i don't know i just look at i can i look
at curse things and remember them and
put it together that's that's a talent i
should say that that's a real talent
[Music]
thank you
you're welcome i hope you have a good
birthday and have a lot of cake i will i
will and don't be too nervous i'm
nervous right now too but don't be too
nervous everybody loves you and i'm so
happy to talk to you thank you
i love
[Music]
thank you
thank you thank you
oh and i want to say i love your new
cover i have it on loop thank you okay
bye
[Music]
precious precious moment
so adorable
all my friends are so adorable i don't
know where to place every everyone's
gifts i'll put it on top of my my tea
set
oh
by the end of the stream you'll only see
my eyes that'll be fine right
i think that'll be fine
i love all my friends so so very much
[Music]
no it's international attacker day
why stop at
international
wow
are you gonna dominate the world
yes why are you stopping at nations
why is why are you settling for less
oh i don't settle for less i just try to
smile
you know one step at a time they say
one arm one leg at a time well one
tentacle at a time you know
no
a picture that we made you
those middle legs are oh making me feel
weird
like don't you just i just kind of want
to
be in the middle
i mean
would you like a child
for a low price of 3.99
3.99 that's like a steal what a bargain
oh you forgot a few digits at the bar i
just say 3.99
okay
anything anything for you on your
birthday
oh thank you you said you don't get you
said you don't get nervous often
when you
i'm like oh here we go again if
everybody's every single
every single stream where we have to
spoil spoil you you just
i'm just like praying no comprehend
please explain
yeah
you don't give yourself enough credit
for all you do and all you accomplish
right
especially yes why stop why stop at why
stop at the why stop at nations you
should just like take over the world
already i mean if you know what if you
know a couple of planets you know your
space after all if you know any any old
planets for
for uh take over talk over you know yeah
i'm sure
yeah i'm glad that
yeah honestly okay seriously you don't
you don't give yourself enough
credit for
all you do
and i'm just glad that at least today
there's all these people and oh that's
how you thought she used to spoil you
spoil you and remind you that
you know you're just loved and you
deserve it all and i hope that we can
give a little bit of your joy
back to you
ah
there it is the flood
wow i just wanted to really for the
floods
[Music]
do you know like of course you know do
you know i give really good cuddles
i do and i just want to hold you close
and pat your head and
tell you that you've done so well
and
you're just going to keep doing well i
just know it
i
like crying too
i'm just so proud of you
thank
[Laughter]
here i'm happy to
uh i wanted to cuddle you and hold your
clothes but i'll probably cry over you
now
what day what's good
but yeah thank you so much sarah
uh okay and yeah
good luck with the rest of the call-ins
you can do it thank you thank you yeah
receive all the love
i love you santa thank you so much
[Music]
all right
that was probably uh
it was probably more emotional than i
thought it was gonna be but
it seems we have come to time for our
first
uh announcement that was probably
not a good time for the flood to come in
because i need to do announcements
where's my
well i know why i i let the the
flood come in i turn up the pgm
anyways
it is time
it is time for announcement number one
[Music]
and what better announcement than the
goods
birthday exclusive goods
of nino mai inanisa's birthday of 2022
time has finally come
to announce our next step in world
domination
[Music]
birthday celebration
on sale may 21st yesterday it's still
the 20th year
[Music]
i shall go over all the items that will
be on sale to fund our world domination
number one
is
a magic clear file the art is by
purusala atsushi-san
they're i think they're most well known
for
their uh pokemon card illustrations most
recently but i've been i've actually
been a fan of their work for many years
and um
yeah i really wanted to you know
get this chance to to work with them
um this is the special clear file in
that if you
but normally it will look like the image
on the left but if you put in the paper
like white piece of paper it'll change
into the image on the right so you'll
see the line art
wow
i love clear files
every time i go travel all my documents
and stuff is all in a clear file and use
a different one every time i travel
and i love clear files i think this is a
very very cool
cool clear file look at that beautiful
art sunflowers i love sunflowers one of
my favorite favorite flowers
it's so graceful beautiful beautiful art
thank you so much
for the beautiful artwork and in order
to also celebrate
how cute this artwork is
we oh there's a japanese version could
you fire this
there's also
a big button badge with the display
stand
it's around it's around what like uh
it's pretty big
it's pretty big but you can use this as
a decoration on your desk uh
on your office in your office uh in your
kitchen
in the bathroom i don't know
anywhere you want it to be
it's beautiful you can you can see ina
in in the flower fields every day
and uh
next one
drumroll please
oh wait that's japanese version
[Music]
they said i could become anything taco
fish laundry pouch
have you guys
do you guys know of mesh laundry pouches
they're pretty useful when you have like
fragile piece of clothing
or or plushies like the top ratchet
plushie
you can put it inside these mesh bags
and put them in the laundry like in the
washer and it'll protect it from all the
you know rolling around and stuff but it
is made out of mesh material so you will
be able to get stuff washed inside and
it won't be as as mad it's very useful
for cleaning
uh
um
the clothes you wear underneath you know
or
or very fragile uh graphic
t-shirts with like uh prints on them
just like you know that
the taco taco decks sweater or hoodie
or the takorachi
this is the item that mamanis wanted
like five of
cause we use these quite often and um
as you can see
the zipper
is on the head so you open up the tacos
taco's uh hand brain to see an empty
empty space where you can put
uh your laundry or items in it before
wash also you don't even have to use it
for the laundry you can just use it to
store stuff
it's very useful
blend into your everyday life first we
took over the world with our plushies
next we're gonna take over everyone's
laundry
and
if there is
laundry you need
somewhere to put the laundry in right
what is the japanese version
[Music]
and what better
place to store your dirty laundry
than a laundry in a bag
wow
these are pretty big laundry baskets
it's made out of cloth you can wash it
as well
so you can put all your laundry in it
and then when you sort out the laundry
you can put the fragile stuff in the
taco taco pouch
but as you can see i drew the art for it
um it's the takora cheese on a laundry
day outside hanging up a cute laundry if
you can see close up
you can see some familiar tacos in there
that we have met throughout the year
can you guys can you guys find them all
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah that is the
big laundry bag where you can put all
your laundry in it i was very serious
when coming up with the goods this year
because i really wanted
um
i really wanted to
for it to have a little bit of a theme
and i really wanted something useful
that everyone can use
and you know everyone does laundry or
they need
something somewhere to store their
laundry i was like this is a brilliant
idea
so
yeah those are the
four items
in the
uh
in the package
and
to say
if you buy everything in the package
you will also get
a bonus postcard
with a special message on it
and my autograph
it's gonna be a foil stamped autograph
so you can also put this in a
in a you know i don't know some
somewhere special
[Music]
and uh
yeah
isn't my autograph pretty cool
[Music]
i can't buy autograph
but yeah those are the full items
for this time around
this is the merch set list
you can buy the whole bundle or you can
buy each of the items separately
that's right
what a deal
[Music]
and
the
uh
that's it the page will go live
in around
six minutes
on the hour the page
will go live to buy the goods
links will be in the stream description
and as a pin to comment
so please
look forward to it i hope you guys like
it
what do you guys think do you think do
you think you're using the laundry
tell me honestly would you use it in the
laundry which sacrifice your fellow
takarachi who have volunteered to become
[Music]
the mesh laundry patch
to
to promote a cleaner
clothing
world
[Music]
yes 10 out of 10 yes no no
security
security department
we have we have code code 7.
[Music]
you have a cool 7 dirty laundry taco in
the chat
[Music]
ah but yeah those are the ghosts this
time thank you so much again
um
everyone for
your support
and i i think i stared at the main
artwork for for quite a while
um
it's so it's so beautiful and look look
it's so cute
ah but yes
that is how things will go
yeah
i know we brainstormed like maybe coming
up with like an umbrella and stuff
before but um when i saw
when i saw the uh
when i saw the mesh bag and the laundry
bag combo i was like oh
that'd be so useful because right now my
laundry i'll be honest with you it's
just sitting in a pile
in the corner of my bathroom i have to
admit it needs a little bit of
organization and you guys know very well
how much i
try to make goods that i use in my daily
life
so yes that would be uh a good way to
you know cute
uh very cutely organizing my life
but yeah daily daily life of inna now
laundry time will
be fun with takarachis
[Music]
but you know the basket and stuff
doesn't always have to be used for
laundry i feel like anything that you
can store stuff in like the mesh bag in
the laundry bag you can probably use it
to store just about anything
yeah it'll be useful
brilliant
[Music]
okay
oh
man
i
announced it announced out the
announcement
[Music]
in a few minutes the links will go live
to buy
the words thank you very much all
takodachi for coming to the info session
of the new birthday
goods uh
oh man
i'm always so so so nervous
[Music]
okay
but don't worry about the takodachis
that were uh that volunteered to become
mesh bags i'm sure they will also find
comfort in
being
placed in a loving environment
in your homes
in your dorms
[Music]
yes
oh boy
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you
i kind of think maybe it would have been
fun if like the eyes of taco were like
like in those spirals like
they're in there in the uh in the
washing machine but you know i think i
feel like i feel like the takodachi
would enjoy
enjoy
the trip in the washing machine with a
smile you know they're strong strong and
independent tacos
ah
okay
i think
we will
resume what call-ins after
the goods
go live in a little bit maybe i should
have it on loop automatic
[Music]
okay
i'll put this on top of
you're being covered up chat
[Music]
okay
ah it seems like
the links are live
whoa
so please check it out if you guys are
interested even if you're not it's okay
thanks for joining me today
on a special special birthday party
stream
[Music]
okay
i think i think we can resume
resume
do we crash the site all according to
plan
oh according to plan
[Music]
now i'll rearrange
these numbers
[Music]
oh
it might say sold up but it's because
it's like uh what's it like a
pre-pre-order kind of item
oh yes
hopefully
people can access it
soon p.m
[Music]
i think i think it's live now you can
you can see
the items
[Music]
i believe the official shop ships to
more countries now so
it's good thumbs up
it's just pre-order yes
[Music]
oh if this is sold out you just need to
refresh the page
thanks
[Music]
oh my goodness
yes
[Music]
thank you thank you
now we're waiting for our next friend to
join us
boom
[Music]
oh
i'm starting to be relaxed a little more
i think
[Music]
happy
thanks for calling in so early oh my
goodness
[Music]
and charcoal
i just had a look at your uh merch
before the site crashed she's so cute
thanks bear with
[Music]
it's going
amazing thanks for joining
of course
i was gonna draw something
but then i looked at um
i
i may have forgotten everything from
drawing 101
oh is it time for drawing me drawing 102
i think sorry
[Music]
it's all right it's all right
i always forget to i'll be honest
[Music]
but it
was what happened
did you get any
amazing i just had a dream about you
actually you did
yeah
i think
do you ever like i don't know whether
it's because like my self-conscious like
i sent an alarm
um for the core and then i had a dream i
was doing
your makeup for your birthday
and that was monkey
oh
look look how cute i look right now it's
because of the uv
oh look at my name
guys credit me i want to see my name in
the credits oh
[Laughter]
thank you i know you must be really busy
too but i'm happy i'm happy i got to
talk to you again i feel like it's been
a while
i know right now
i'm going to do drawing 102. oh let's do
it
[Music]
okay
thanks for joining thank you thank you
[Music]
oh she's adorable in the morning
okay so the next
[Music]
next
friend um actually sent in
an audio
audio happy birthday because she was
very she's a very very very very busy
busy friend especially recently too
she's very hard working really hard to
prepare
um none other than our glad mori
yay
she sent me a little little recording i
haven't heard it yet but i hope that uh
oh she's saying okay i hope she's not
overworking herself again
okay here you go
[Music]
hello
hi there ina it's mori sorry for uh not
being able to make it in real time to
wish you a happy birthday but i just
wanted to say that i am so proud of you
in everything that you've accomplished
in the past two years
and um every single year
i come to admire you more and more for
your amazing talent and your kindness
and uh you're just wonderful and um i
hope that we get to play some more games
together more guilty gear etc hopefully
eldon ring on pc someday um but yeah
anyway
i hope you have a wonderful birthday and
again i'm sorry i couldn't be here in
real time but um i love you lots and um
i miss hanging out so i hope we get a
chance to hang soon again and um your
new cover was amazing and so beautiful
and i've listened to it 50 times already
and the art that you did for it is
fantastic and uh yeah i just wanted you
to know that so um anyway
happy birthday
you know
this is this is mori signing out bye-bye
peace
oh cali
oh callie
okay
no more flood
cali
is i honestly don't know how she manages
to be so
high output and so strong and
oh
she's she's amazing and
i'm i'm so happy she took her time to
send her message when she was so busy
[Music]
yeah oh yeah bgm before i start
flooding again okay there you go
yeah i i honestly i respect cali so so
much for just
how dedicated she is to everything she
does and i i got a lot to learn from her
i see that
oh
boy
yeah i just hope that she can get some
good rest you know she also has her
her live coming up oh i'm so excited i'm
so so excited
so so so excited
um
so yeah
oh man
my heart
[Music]
yeah and i've talked to i've talked to
cali
off stream couple times to just
asking her for advice and stuff and
she's always there for everyone when
when we need her and she's
it's amazing
she really is
yeah both of you need rest i think
callie needs it more than i do feeling
being honest
but she really loves what she does too
and i love what i do and i think both of
us also agree that we do stuff
for you guys because we just really love
doing it
[Music]
lovely day lovely lovely day
um need a little bit of time to digest
this fields
it's a lovely day oh what a day what a
lovely day
[Music]
i'm like
like every day
i just think about how i'm surrounded by
such talented talented people
so kind and so dedicated to what they do
ah
i'm blessed
i'm i'm one of the luckiest
luckiest person in the world
[Music]
witnessed
oh man
all right i also need to order goods
for my buddies
oh boy
before before
before i forget about it
[Music]
you know every time every time she sees
you you and how
how i'm just not gonna
ever give her you in the end
she always asks me to
buy extras of stuff now
[Music]
ah
yes
[Music]
oh i guess i guess we're kind of ahead
of okay i can't order my stuff
okay um
laundry bag
[Music]
he said i could become an eating taco
wait
[Music]
brilliant
i can't believe
i'm holding ordering this ceremonies
annie's apparently wanted to wish me
happy birthday too
at midnight but i fell asleep before
that
[Music]
how could you
i know
[Music]
it's rough
wait i forgot my password
what's my password
could it be
i'm not a robot
[Music]
am i a robot
i got it right one shot let's go
[Music]
oh
express checked out
[Music]
i feel like i haven't ordered online in
so long i forget all my
[Music]
credentials do you guys always have your
credit card number memorized
[Music]
because i think i do
it's a bad habit
no
yes no
that's probably why
you know in the uh what's the big
oh
huh
[Music]
credit card number and the three numbers
in the back your social social
number
wow you're revealing such special
information for your birthday
yes of course of course
such fan service very big respect
and uh i just looked at your birthday
version it's
oh thank you
we need we need twin till inna
i want 20
too
uh
yes twin tails ponytail
the different kinds of hair iris
[Music]
iris salon
stream
your hairstyles yeah
is it kind of like what you what eofy
does like where should you make
something yeah
for the salon
oh yeah
[Music]
uh like it just reminded me oh yeah
i need to read chap read the more recent
chapters
i know you and i have like pretty pretty
similar tastes when it comes to
manga and anime so i was like
i'm glad you read shadowhouse too it's
great yeah so shadowhouse is great yeah
it's very unique
i love the whole concept and the mystery
history
and how they like come back to like
stuff in the beginning and like pick up
like on the foreshadowing stuff they're
like
that's what that was
yeah oh my god speaking of like
um
like out of it like this season what are
you watching you know oh this season i
mean spy family for sure
yeah
i've been craving
watching um
uh
like manga it's like small short stories
it is yeah i think it's definitely
something you could probably binge later
on
my current recommendation right now is
summertime render oh yeah
so good yeah
is and oh my god like i i know the first
episode was like it was didn't really um
hook me too much but and the second
episode really hooked me up so
yeah i remember reading the manga a
while back ah yeah yeah like i picked up
i picked up the manga after watching the
second episode and basically read the
rest of it so i'm just like yeah the
manga
finished i think so if everyone has time
they can just
breathe basically just binge it yeah
it's great
as your merch you know the what you call
it you know the the laundry bag oh yeah
the taco duchy laundry um that's like
the
the laundry um zipper bag where you put
like
your you put like lace stuff yeah yeah
like the more fragile stuff you don't
want to get mixed up
that's why the taco taco's face is so
happy because you know
oh it gets to collect me it pounds yeah
it makes sense
[Laughter]
this is so cute i need my i need myself
a taco duchy laundry bag i'm gonna get
one oh thank you
you mad
like
it just reminds me how i have to do my
laundry i try to
i try to pile my laundry as much as i
can i'm such a procrastinator how many
times do you do your laundry
ah
i just do it when there's like a certain
pile
[Laughter]
machine yeah
and i don't i always like forget to
separate like the whites with like the
colors the number of times i ruined my
like white t-shirts
i know
i'm just like oh yeah i wasn't supposed
to mix this so yeah i don't really buy
white t-shirts anymore
[Music]
oh my god
oh i'm going out over time okay okay
it's okay we have some we have some
buffer time too so
oh great great stuff oh my god yeah
wonderful version of your cover ah
oh can i ask yes you know um
the back chorus like after like the
second chorus like there was like oh
like oh that's awesome the singer yeah
the love for singer is that youtube
that's made us
oh my god the low notes are just like oh
you sound like a totally different
person
i had my doubts oh my god
[Music]
yeah oh my god that sounds like a pain
to record
like i did my best to reach the note but
i was like
who did the mixing i was like
that happens with me all the time
the low register if it if you don't hit
it you just don't hit it you know yeah
you know you just gotta be confident so
they have something to work with
yeah yeah just as long as you have
something to worry about
magic but oh my god it was amazing so
yeah
and the art too it's like so much shadow
house reference oh yeah i had a lot of
fun working on it but you know iris you
know the the the song i asked you but i
feel like if you're free sometime i
would like to you know start
oh yeah
many times
[Music]
it was amazing song suggestion i'm just
like oh yes
that is perfect
but i also want to say you know iris
please take care of yourself too i know
you are feeling too well not too long
ago so
yeah
thank you i will
ah and yeah of course you know don't
push yourself i know you work so hard
and i don't know how you juggle
everything you're one of those people
i'm just like how does she do it so if
you have make sure you take care of
yourself too
thank you
now happy birthday thank
you bye bye
ah that was iris everyone
oh
the most talented talented singers i
know
oh
you know i replied to iris yesterday
about how she said she was looping
nine nine but i was like not as many
much time as i looped diorama
that's like that's like my favorite song
from iris
it's like her voice and like
the uh
the song itself is just amazing song
love it
[Music]
um
yeah
oh boy
so we have a little bit of a little bit
of break
short break until we have our next set
of guests
oh man
i am honestly
overwhelmed with love
oh boy
[Music]
so so good yeah
i wish i i not not wish i i hope to
practice enough
singing down the line to be able to sing
as well as iris one day
she has such a wonderful clear voice you
know
[Music]
and i asked her
i asked her a while ago uh if she wanted
to sing this u.s song with me she was
like yes so
ah we wanna we wanna work on it as soon
as we can i guess
[Music]
and uh
again thank you everyone for your
birthday wishes thank you thank you
thank you
very very very happy
um i also saw some like the special
gifts that you guys prepared for me one
of them being
a vr chat world
with uh some fan artworks and 3d models
and stuff that's displayed in the world
it's a very beautiful world to
take a small peek at it
before the stream but um
you guys can also go hang out there too
to meet other takadachi's
yeah
[Music]
one of the reasons i really like vr chat
i experienced it like firsthand after
doing the vr collabs with uh
myth and console for several times
because like even when we're not
physically there beside each other
you kind of
start to
feel like they're really there beside
you you know like
i was giving i was get for example i was
giving kiara like virtual virtual vr
hugs but it really felt like she was
there and
you know we haven't not everyone has met
each other yet but um
but vr i feel like you kind of
demolished the physical laws between
people
to some extent and that's pretty
exciting
[Music]
yeah vr is amazing for that and uh
ah
i need to call i need to calm my heart
down before
we were the next uh
next
relay of guests because
oh
with the en en
girls it's mostly like
i
[Music]
i talk to them a lot you know
and they're like they're like
great great great friends but
some of the whole members i haven't
talked to that much yet so i'm i'm a
little nervous but
i'm gonna be i'm gonna be you know who
knows how to communicate today um
[Music]
yeah
i think i think i think
like collins are one of the ways to be
able to interact with them a lot better
so
[Music]
and i also also know it's like a really
early early early time for jp too so
i was very worried that's why i try to
delay the stream from the normal normal
starting hour
as much as possible
[Music]
thank you thank you everyone
oh you guys are all so lovely lovely
people
[Music]
ina ina can communicate
i can communicate it won't be like
what what's what's uh
[Music]
it's like
it's the face that she makes
[Music]
okay
inaudible
[Music]
yeah
this is pretty
fun oh maybe i should drop myself a hat
i don't have a i don't have a
no birthday hat
oh no
[Music]
i will
require help from the takodachi
[Music]
okay
doesn't this music remind you of uh
like in the visual novel you're like
standing in the lobby
[Music]
and then you see like a whole bunch of
dialogue
[Music]
wait this isn't gonna work
she's a dialogue
[Music]
we should make a visual novel someday
actually one of my plan was to make uh
make an rpg with the rpg maker right
we can make it kind of like a visual
novel
a visual novel our peach
should we add fights to it
what do we even fight
[Music]
yeah i also wanted to try more like
pixel art stuff too
i've i've done pixel art before but it's
been it's been years since i last did it
i think that'll be like a really fun
long-term project too mm-hmm
[Music]
ah
don't overwork yourself yeah well i
won't oh yeah i did mention in previous
streams before but i will probably be
taking
um
a bit of a break
after
after today's stream
i i wanted to hold on until until maybe
next week or so but i feel like
i feel like with the stuff that's been
planned for later in
the year
it's probably better to start early
it's probably better to start early and
come back earlier
and um
then delay and mess up with some of the
uh
some of the scheduling i do have a
collab
one collab plan and one
um sponsored stream plan that i can't
change the dates to that i really wanna
i really wanna do so i'll probably be
back for those but most of the times i
will probably be in the back and i wanna
take the time to
one take care of myself to plan out some
new things long term short term
and kind of get myself back on track
i'm like a very derailed train right now
i need to roll roll back onto the tracks
so i can
steer myself in the right direction
[Music]
so like the stuff that i wanted to do
stuff like the rpg making or like
more cooking streams and stuff
i got planned for
a plan for finding a proper office
with the kitchen
and whatnot
and i think i can probably do that all
while i'm on break
[Music]
oh thank you thank you
you deserve all the best from this world
you guys too i know you guys are all
wishing me happy birthday but please
don't forget to
congratulate yourself too
because
my achievement or not mine alone it's
it's everyone's everyone who supported
me you guys
allow me to try new things without
worrying you know whether it's gonna
fail or not because
i have confidence
from you guys
[Music]
yeah pat yourself on the head
love you guys too
thank you thank you
[Music]
oh yeah
hello
thank you so much for joining this oh oh
my goodness
[Music]
that's
oh i know it's really early i'm sorry
you're excited
oh how are you senpai
oh fine i'll watch you
oh my god i'm sorry i'm like
okie dokie
oh oh now that i see we look kind of
alike here senpai with the purple and
the orange
or yellow shorts
my mind is more like yellow
oranges and
and yeah our color team is like the same
and also you know did you know that i
actually put
this all right and one of my elvin it
was gonna be high tight ah really
[Music]
yeah
you should watch i did there i was like
a little little of tentacles for me oh
my god i never know
because i i um with my recent cover i
contacted ramsay's song because i really
love their work with your with your um
movie and oh my goodness i didn't
realize
everyone go watch it again
[Laughter]
oh i guess i was just just stunned by
your your beautiful vocals and visuals
that i just
i just didn't realize
oh
but oh man i know we haven't talked much
before but i gotta say i i really really
respect you senpai and your
powerful vocals like
in in the in the fest when i saw your
performance i was just like
my heart just skipped a few bits
beats and i was like oh my goodness
she's a diva
thank you
i really i really like your music it's
it's so calming like
and also
and also actually sometime a couple of
times i just like using your stream as
my video as the call me
when i play games thank you
i also have a lot to learn from you in
terms of like minecraft too because i
saw i saw some of the stuff you've built
especially your house too it's so
aesthetically pleasing and like
so well made and
high-tech
[Laughter]
thank you oh yeah and then i know that
we might be planning to make that portal
to id server i hope i can i can also go
visit what you you built so far in the
server as well
looking for my channels
yes
i can wait to show everyone
to be server you know
like it's been it's been like a couple
of
i think once that's
playing on the id server
i usually usually play on the jp server
a bit and then
all of the members go grinding a lot and
building a lot
so yeah which is another way to show
everyone a while ago i'm looking forward
to it also i'll also become your
your student in in terms of
thank you so much for joining today i
know it must be really early and i know
like everyone in whole life has very
weird sleeping schedules so
waking up early is really difficult
i i put my alarm for this and i just
like oh my god it's over this hour and
it's like
that's that's god i'm not i'm not late
thank you thank you
oh i'm so happy to finally talk to you
like one-on-one
oh
let's talk more
[Music]
she's like she's definitely like a diva
in my eyes
the senpai aura is great
ah thank you nice hand fly yeah i got a
lot to learn from her you know
from the powerful singing to
minecraft building and
so much to learn so much to learn
and we're both purple there's actually
quite a few like
purple themed
all over me
come on
[Music]
happy birthday
[Laughter]
a present is it you
it's kind of me oh
oh my goodness okay hold on hold on this
is really impressive oh my goodness i
need to actually save this so i can use
it as transparent ah
it's so cool oh my god
hey i'll put it
i put it on my flaps
wait oh no not your brushes flaps
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
i definitely wasn't laughing on me on
your birthday no no of course not of
course not you wouldn't do that
dude yeah no i'm a i'm a good guy
but not your precious flaps oh
i'm
sorry it's like my shoulder pad
oh my shoulder
nice pillow
beautiful
comfy
beautiful it's multi-functional
oh it's so great thank you i actually
really love your buns
so
really fun to draw
i'm glad it is by the way
congratulations on your new cover thank
you
[Music]
it was scary that i kept on listening to
it i have no idea what song it was but
the first part where you go to tutu i
was like
wait what
i always love your singing oh
i love yours too actually i was so
amazed by your like holo song mentally
like i was like oh yeah it's good about
the end right and then like
it goes on i'm just like oh there's more
and i was like yeah there's more and
there's more i was like how did she like
manage to sing all these songs in like a
flawless like fluid melon like
wow
let's not talk about that it's it's your
birthday but uh anyways i am also quite
curious what do you think about the the
violet part i loved it
yeah i got it i was like i was like
when i started watching and i was like
okay i was watching the premiere i was
like okay it's gonna be next it's gonna
be next it's gonna be next
and when i got it i was like
ascending
i love it it's so fun to sing but also
it gives me the feels oh yeah i'm glad
you like it and oh
all your
energy is just so
so
what should i say
[Music]
addictive
in a way like
when when i feel a little down i can
just i know i can just tune into your
stream and just be like back on my feet
you know energetic and you're so such a
hard-working kohai and
so so lovely
wait who's having the birthday right now
why why are you
not turning it around
no
just so you know i get inspired from
your singing from your drawings you're
always very chill sometimes i stay up
just to watch your streams you better
remember that because you're my favorite
taco
thank you
you're my favorite zombie even if
there's a zombie apocalypse and i gotta
get rid of all the zombies in the world
i'll spare you for sure
and your family
and friends
i don't know if that's a compliment but
[Music]
thank you
yeah
oh she's so sweet look at how cute she
is
you know how i always said like if i had
a little sister i just imagine her to be
like you
really yeah
oh
i think will you be my only son
yeah sure
like
then i i'm more of a oh yeah oh yeah
kind of person but i mean for you
i'll take it
i am
yet
descended
don't worry she'll she'll be back she'll
be back she's a zombie she'll be fine
[Laughter]
anyways happy birthday i'm wishing you
all the best thank you ollie
[Music]
she would definitely be the kind of
little sister i would spoil if i had a
little sister
like fun to tease but also would like to
spoil
oh boy
ah you guys like the the hair that ollie
gave me look at this
oh boy
hello
[Music]
yay
how are you
uh i'm good it's
it's 6 a.m oh my goodness i'm so sorry
it's okay now i made you a little
something it may not be special but
anything special for from you
everything is special uh
let me
hope you like it
i love it
i love you
it's so cute
nice add to my collection
so cute thank you
oh no
no worries
oh
i i listened to your cover ah
thank you i love it i love it thank you
have you watched
really well i really need to check out
shadow's house
it's really good i've heard stuffs about
it but i don't really watch enemies
these days unfortunately so i haven't
checked it out yeah
yeah i love that
yeah thank you i'm glad you like it
yeah the art do the illustration
everything oh so good thank you
[Music]
i just want to hit pad you
yeah
i mean we
we have the uh
[Music]
it's going to be next week
maybe next week
maybe next week probably maybe probably
maybe perhaps possibly probably perhaps
possibly most likely yeah something
something will be happening next week
so
yeah happy to be able to talk to you
before then too because i don't think
i've talked to you
since like
last quarter
yeah it seems like less collapse yeah
time's on and it has been a while and
stuff really hard to
catch everyone
wait no no we didn't talk we didn't talk
after the collab and i think it was on
my birthday totsumachi
right
oh my god i i have no sense of time
right now no no no no it's okay because
the collab was like um two days before
my birthday or something that's true i
don't i don't exactly remember but yeah
yeah
oh my goodness i've had
i'm gonna be looping your cover like um
50 more times
[Music]
i really like your phony cover too
oh my god
you know what we should definitely sing
together someday yeah
if you have
that let's do it
let's do it let's do it let's do it
someday
thank you so much for having me today
thanks so much for joining us
love you too happy birthday thank you
oh anya
adorable also i should probably take off
my hat
wait
that fits perfectly
yeah oh
my cool highs are so cute like
like how fauna said i radiate senpai
energy like how could i not when my
kohais are so adorable you know
i love them so much i love everyone so
much
it's great
[Music]
you just yeah perfect look it's like it
just feels meant for my head
flawless but man
everyone who's called in so far i know
it's like the usual time that i stream
people
um
usually don't stream around this time
other hall of life members
so
i was always like
worried
i have to wake them up so early in the
morning but
thank you thank you everyone for your
happy birthday wishes i'm so happy
i'm so happy it's like
it's like i feel as if i'm floating in
in in warm clouds i don't know if that
makes sense warm clouds probably doesn't
make sense but you know like fluffy
it's like when you have a bath and then
you have a lot of bubbles around you and
you're so comfortable and so
so happy that's what i feel like right
now
mm-hmm
ah
everyone is so solo
oh my goodness
happy birthday thank you and also happy
birthday to other people who have
birthdays today too you know you guys
also deserve happy birthdays
and the ones who have tomorrow the day
after tomorrow
and any other day in the
in the year
i know there's actually a lot of
birthdays this week in holland i have
like we had sora senpai we had chloe i
know
uptown also has
birthday and nova goes in by two right
there's a lot a lot of celebrations
tomorrow
yeah
and
i don't know if i've said it before too
but like i
i don't celebrate
birthday is big
but
um
ever since you know twinning hollow
birthdays has been
such a big celebration
um i'm glad that
i'm able to celebrate with so many so
many of you guys and so many of my
friends all men everyone
[Music]
it doesn't feel real
honestly
and i hope that you know after the break
i can also start working on some things
that we can celebrate together down the
line as well
i think that's very very exciting
oh i am such a blessed taco
i mean human
such a blessed human woman
oh
a slipper what do you mean
for daddy
bean beans
[Music]
foreign
wow
oh man i'm kind of getting hungry
i should have ordered that cake maybe i
can order cheesecake
cheesecake is a good alternative to
strawberry cake right right
[Music]
i'm sure i'm sure i'm sure i will be
forgiven for ordering cheesecake
i can treat myself today
cheesecake mmm delicious
no
i can't order cheesecake
[Music]
or cheesecake
no cheesecake i need
i need
i need sugar in my system
i'm running out of candy actually i have
a
i have a case with a whole bunch of
candy but i've been going through so
many of them this week
takes a lot of brain age you know
wait they have salad too not salad
like actual food
oh my goodness
cheesecake by the slice oh yes
[Music]
oh no i'm getting hungry
okay okay
everything looks so great
how many sizes should i order three four
for my whole family so probably four
two for me one for mama knees
one for puppy
[Music]
all of them 25 i can't eat 25
at least two one million
i feel like the order is gonna come next
year if i order a million cheesecakes
[Music]
maybe four think four is a good number
green tea
[Music]
oh
lemon
lemon cheesecake
i think that's good enough
dog biscuits
they sell dog biscuits
huh
[Music]
oh i think i understand why chiara just
adores you
[Music]
thank you good morning oh my goodness
thanks for thanks for joining the call
and uh
i this is my first
so
ah
i don't know what to say
[Music]
it's okay i'll take care of it
yeah i just wake up
no no no i'm sorry for calling you so
early
no it's okay i'm happy i'm happy
thank you thank you for inviting me
[Music]
oh you're so cute
how are you
go ahead
i i have a
present for you but a present
where did i need to send it
uh
you can probably tear it to me
um
yeah yeah it's yeah
it's so cute oh my goodness
wait i think i need to save it as
png first
so
yeah
better
hmm
what are you doing at kobo how are you
enjoying your time the whole life so far
it's very great
it's very
fun
mm-hmm though i just collapsed with
uh
two senpai's outside whole life id
but i'll try my best to socialize more
and
[Music]
what kind of activity
that will be good for collapsing
don't think of something if not we can
also meet up in minecraft when we
connect the servers too
yeah
show me around
now i can show you around because i'm
i'm
really really a newbie
it's okay it's okay i think even when i
was pretty new i was i was trying my
best to learn minecraft but you'll get
used to it very soon i'm sure
okay
thank you for the thank you for the
umbrella it's so cute
yeah uh i know
i
[Music]
i just wake up and i haven't
prepared my speech
and
but i wish you have a
good day today a very
spectacular birthday and
i
wish you all the best
i wish you have a good health wish you
have
uh
wish i wish your dream come true
thank you
[Music]
keep walking keep
keep walking forward
to the light and keep
keep keeping
i don't know what to say
but i wish you all the best yeah just
yes
thank you so much
you're so adorable
my cheeks hurt from smiling so much
okay i'll go to sleep again
for helping me thank you
[Music]
oh i think that was my first time
actually like talking talking to kobo
she is so
adorable
oh
i am healed
my cheeks actually hurt from smiling so
much
oh and look at this umbrella look
this is the umbrella we could have
gotten as good maybe next time even has
a tentacle handle
perfect
i don't know where to put it properly
though also my stomach growl really
loudly
oh
we have our next next next friend
hello
oh yeah i think i think you're cutting
out a little bit hello
[Music]
hello hello everybody hello
hello helena senpai happy birthday
thank you happy birthday happy birthday
yeah
yeah i'm sorry the first one is actually
my little sis
she always wanted to get into everything
that i can do yeah so yeah i'm sorry oh
so cute
yeah
how are you
i'm doing fine how about innocent pie
i'm doing good too i know we haven't
like
talked in voice before
yeah yeah yeah yeah but
this is really first time talking right
yeah
i know we chatted before briefly but
got to finally talk to you
yeah yeah yeah um
yeah but um
i wish i can
give you something but i'm sorry i oh no
no no no
here is enough like i could not ask for
anything more
ah
yeah
maybe something we can please read it i
don't know
yeah let's collab sometime too
i know i know you've been really
enjoying playing a
a certain game called uh raft
[Laughter]
i haven't tried it out myself too but i
really enjoy watching you play it
oh really yeah yeah you should try that
you should try that or maybe if we can
play rough together someday
almost all the cohorts maybe
how are you enjoying your time
at home
you are like
[Music]
yeah it's been really nice actually for
these uh two months and
yeah
and
i don't know because i
play
games
almost all of my time so
i think it's really nice to have some
i mean
not some i mean a lot of people uh
supporting
us
streaming especially for a very long
time it's really sweet and nice
it feels surreal sometimes
yeah
i think even even when it's almost been
two years for me still feels surreal
every time yeah
and
yeah everyone's there to watch
well yeah thanks so much for coming too
thank you so much for inviting me
yes yes
thank you
sweet sweet koh hai's
i don't know if i'm putting them on the
spot by asking how they're doing so far
but i'm curious too you know as a senpai
like if there's there's anything you
know
it can help to
make their stay much comfortable too you
know
hello
our next friend
wow
i'm
sorry screwed up too no it's okay i i
honestly feel so bad making everyone
wake up so early ah
no it's okay it's totally worth it
i slept
i thinking i'm gonna talk to enos by
tomorrow ah i was so happy
i'm so happy to finally talk to you too
because cause like with kyla too we've
only chatted a little bit like briefly
but we haven't like talked talked before
yeah that's so true we haven't this is
our first time talking in vcc
oh
happy birthday nice and fun thank you
thanks for joining me today i made it
much more special with you here
oh
wait
i actually made him
i actually drew something for you it did
it's not it's not
oh
i'm sorry i couldn't do much but
love you
[Music]
thank you
i just want to say that when you debuted
and you put out your cover song too and
you did the art for it i was like man
she's such a talented cool hi
oh no no
oh it's because i'm also a big fan of
emmy as well so i was like
wow that was amazing oh
boy thank you i've also listened to your
um
in my night cover i'm so good thank you
oh you're so sweet
now you're asleep
your heart is amazing i hold on here
i hope we can draw together so yeah
definitely
definitely let me know when i'll be
there
[Laughter]
thank you
happy
birthday
i hope you can achieve whatever you want
to
achieve one of them came true because
you're in the tatsumatsu right now
oh yeah
oh yeah oh yeah
but um i also asked it to kobo color too
how are you enjoying your time and whole
life right now
how's it going so far any difficulties
anything that can help any difficulty
no no
i just had so much fun all the senpais
are so kind
and
i've just been enjoying my time just
vibing
[Laughter]
that's good
[Music]
yeah having fun is good having fun is
good
[Music]
thank you
so cute you can put it right here
i feel like the the screen is getting
very crowded but i'll find a way to
display everything
thank you so much um i hope we get the
belly collab sometimes we can draw
together
yeah
it's gonna be so much fun yeah yeah yeah
of course of course we can collab every
day
let's do it
why not
maybe
tomorrow tomorrow
all right
happy birthday
thank you have a good rest too
me too
bye bye
thank
[Music]
you so sweet
tomorrow
oh no now everyone knows that my voice
crack
[Music]
everyone knows of my voice crack i guess
that's fine
right
goodness
lovely lovely
kawaiis
oh
oh i'm speechless honestly
everyone
i don't know there hasn't been a day
where i didn't doubt myself where i was
like
do i
it's hard not to doubt yourself when
you're
surrounded by such talented people such
dedicated people you know
it's like
yeah
am i doing enough am i do i deserve to
be here and
it's hard to not think that sometimes
but
i think
definitely
feel it
recently that i
oh please stop it stop growling not now
i'm talking about serious stuff
oh no i hope you didn't hear that
quick i need to i need to eat something
maybe a candy will do
but yeah you know
sometimes
when i'm at my lowest
i don't
feel like i'm doing enough and stuff but
when i when i look back at chat
you guys and
other members and talk to them they made
me
think that you know i am
trying
oh my goodness i should have i should
have brought snack
i'm telling you every time i stream i
eat right before
i still get super super hungry
midstream because my
my metabolism just kicks in somehow
that's ridiculous
[Music]
i am hungry i'm always hungry
i think it does use up a lot of calories
a lot of brain sugar
on this stream
[Music]
yeah you know
salsa goes out to all the other
tacotachis out there who dot themselves
and then i'm also one of you you know
i doubt myself too but know that
you might seem like it might seem like
you're not doing that much but
you are
you're doing what you can just keep bad
never give up
yeah
so we have a little bit of time
a couple more minutes
until our next guest i gotta i gotta i
gotta work on my nihongos
i gotta turn on my japanese speaking
brain
[Music]
uh
uh how do i even turn on a different
language brain it's hard
have you guys watched gabriel dropout
that's where it's from that quote
and memorized the intonation of it
so i could use it sometimes
[Music]
wow
foreign
[Music]
thank you
um
[Music]
m
oh it is a
robbery in the
soothing
i like your illustrations
it is my dream to how to how
[Music]
here
you
[Music]
thank you
not
[Music]
i haven't talked to
yeah
the horrocks
one to one as much before
i am doing my best
yeah it's
has my japanese gotten better over the
year i'm not sure i still talk to myself
a lot in japanese trying to
converse with myself
[Music]
thank you
yeah they
[Music]
i think my
number one problem is not knowing too
many
vocabulary so maybe i should work on
that first
[Music]
foreign
um released with only the japanese
version before but so i was like oh
maybe i should try
try uh playing it two in japanese to
practice but they released the english
patch not too long ago
[Music]
duolingo actually there was a
there was um
[Music]
a special mood in duolingo that wasn't
there before it was like a
kind of like a situation comprehension
kind of thing so i think maybe maybe i
can
i can do that again
[Music]
m
maybe it's maybe it'll be a better
practice
because you have to read it fast right
i'm actually not that great at reading
fast
hiragana so
i still gotta work on
[Music]
is
i found the i found like one of those
was pre-made packets before
and and the mart i was going to
it was like
ah that's it
there was a pre-made package for otezki
that was great
is it called autistic am i mistaking i'm
pretty sure
yeah
it's like where you have rice and you
pour there's like a little bit of
toppings and you pour
pour like tea in it kind of tea stock
tea
[Music]
yeah it's kind of like porridge in the
way
kind of
but if you're if you're being very
simple about it you can just sprinkle
some furikake on it
and then just pour some
some some tea
or
or like
a stock i guess depending
it's it's a quick meal you can have
[Music]
good
thank you so much for coming in i know
it's very early
thank you
uh
i
i i sorry prison
happy birthday uh uh i try send you
message okay yes
happy birthday
i love your voice because
your voice is so lovely and so amazing
keep up the good work please and
i
would love to get to know you better
so
i have a question yes question
what anime do you recommend me
recommend
the command
is there
what is your favorite anime
recently i
love
yeah i i saw
gremlin yesterday
oh
you
[Music]
which character do you write
with god
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
we must
talk deeply
about
this
this program yes yes definitely
yeah but today happy birthday
my recommendation recommendation
um
if you want something
calming
very funny
um
[Music]
towels
yes
okay uh
i try
i try what okay okay
tell me tell me how it is
okay okay okay okay
that
[Music]
[Laughter]
i'm glad to
talk about talk to you about granados
thank you thank you thank you for coming
senpai
thank you
happy birthday
bye
oh slightly same fight
come on
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's okay it's so very cute
thank you happy birthday
[Music]
how are you
i'm good
so sleepy but
would you like to sleep on my lap
leave
your lap on my lap
it's very squishy
[Laughter]
but today uh it's your happy birthday
it's your birthday so you can sleep my
lap ah i get hot my slap all to myself
oh yes please
ah
how have you been hachama
how have you been
halloween
[Music]
so
foreign
[Laughter]
me
[Music]
um
maybe
i have gotten the one summer title
it's okay any time for you chloe
senpai
thank you
joined me um
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes
no lying
you
you have you have
many many
like
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
yes
foreign
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
my
oh
um
[Music]
i'm slowly getting buried and gifts i am
i am i am happy
yeah have you guys also heard chloe's
new cover she posted not too long ago
wasn't it so adorable
well it wasn't it wasn't adorable
adorable but like but like at the end
when it when when she goes like
i took off i was like
she has such a just a wide range
of voices
it's like it's like when i imagine chloe
an unusual
usual cute chloe in the like there's
like the gap moy i'm just like oh she's
adorable
oh yeah
hello
happy birthday to you
thank you
nice to meet you
i'm happy to finally talk to you
yeah me too
thank you
[Music]
yes yes
uh send your message so
this code please wait okay
so you are
photographed your bracelet oh my god so
the fire is so big
it's okay
it's so big
oh my god
the picture
so big so big really
oh my gosh
it's cold
okay present so see your twitter
[Music]
but i'm not good at
writing a picture
it's okay
i'm really really really happy
i can talk to you
that is my cousin
it's a present for you
hi
present
hi very very kawaii
ready so i'm very happy
[Music]
bye
thank you
[Music]
ah
um what do you like the kind of game
oh
what kind of dude i like all kinds of
games
all kinds of games
[Music]
so
[Laughter]
no problem okay
have a nice day
[Music]
thank you bye bye
bye bye thank you
[Music]
ah
everyone
is so cute so nice
running out of space
oh i am so blessed to be here honestly
let me let me try to just rearrange so
there's there's more room okay i can
just cover up
oh i can probably send this to
atame senpai later
oh okay
more space now
ah
yeah i'm glad that i can talk to some
some some of the other members that i
have not a chance to talk to yet
it's amazing
[Music]
ah
umbrella
oh it's so cute i feel like if i ever do
[Music]
collabs with uh some of the members i'll
use the gifts that they gave me
oh it's so sweet
too right maybe we can talk about that a
little
[Music]
uh although it's been it's been a while
since i've played seriously so
[Music]
ah
oh boy
love you thank you
thank you thank you thank you
ah
i feel like i shouldn't drink so much
because still have some
more guests to come visit
thank you everyone
i feel like
i know i said this last year too last
year's
birthday stream was a lot shorter but
this year
you know i feel
so so
so loved
[Music]
happy birthday
okay okay
[Music]
um
yes
[Music]
um
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
mom
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
bye
summer
ymd
[Music]
it's so fun talking to everyone
oh
[Music]
thank you
um
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
um
[Music]
so
um
okay
okay okay okay
[Laughter]
live
foreign
[Music]
thank um
bye bye
ah poor guy
so so cute
so lively
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
is
foreign
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
the
it
[Music]
you
[Laughter]
three works
foreign
[Music]
she is one of the
one of my senpai said i look up to the
most because
she really really works hard on
everything she thought she always gives
a hundred and ten percent
it's something i wanna
work hard to do it too you know
um i feel like we're gonna be running
out of space here we need
we need to uh
we need to reorganize the screen a
little bit
oh
man didn't realize i was gonna need
so many
so much space
i am i am blessed
[Music]
okay now we have a little more space
ah
i feel like i can probably just like
cover my face but
and
i
i'm so happy i got to talk to some of
them that i want to talk to for a long
time
i feel very full i feel like i'm going
to sleep well tonight
gonna sleep very well tonight
and cover you guys up
i mean i could do that i could do that
okay
oh boy
[Music]
i am at peace
discover chat
but i also want you guys to be part of
the party
maybe i can make you guys a little
smaller too
you have more space
yeah where's all the images
do this
yeah it's great now i have more more
breathing room
my breathing room easily
how are you guys hanging in
still alive
[Music]
ah
good water
alive
yeah
oh my goodness
oh
oh wait i gotta keep ordering my
cheesecake maybe it'll arrive by the
time we're finished
ah
okay i'll leave some for you guys too
make sure you check your fridges
maybe you'll find the crumb in there
i gotta split it between a lot of you
okay
[Music]
let's go
oh
okay
am i happy happy
human
taco human
i feel like i feel like i'm getting a
little better at talking to talking to
people you know
maybe
oh no all the images are not
not lined up
i tried i really did
uh
i feel like
i still feel like it's like kind of a
dream right now just like i'm still
dreaming and then i'll have to wake up
and actually do the birthday stream
maybe maybe that'll be
that'll be it i'll just wake up and this
has just been one wild stream
who knows
oh
and i have to do this all over again but
then i guess i will have i would have
had practice so it would have been okay
right
[Music]
wake up
oh wow
[Music]
don't you guys sometimes have those like
really realistic dreams
um
[Music]
good morning
good morning samurai morning
samurai morning
[Laughter]
okay you said
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Applause]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
me
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
thank you happy birthday
goodbye
[Music]
mmm
ah
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
right
[Music]
uh
oh
[Music]
so
[Laughter]
is
yes
[Music]
hey
foreign
[Music]
ah
it's been a while since i talked and i'm
really happy
[Music]
could it be
thank you for joining
well good morning good morning do you
guys sleep well
uh
yeah we're gonna sleep more after lunch
yeah it is pretty early there too so
thank you so much for joining even when
you guys are on vacation i'm so happy
i couldn't miss it for the world oh i
love you
how's it going pretty good pretty good
oh
are you guys cuddled together right now
nice nice balls you got there
[Laughter]
cheeky volleyball i also have a lot of
a lot of drinks i got coupons it's great
it's great
happy birthday
[Music]
thank
and what you should do
oh i think i sing happy birthday in
german
and anything is in indonesia at the same
time let's go chaos
sorry we're also kind of tired it's okay
it's okay i'm just happy you guys called
them oh no
okay okay let's see same time yeah we'll
be scuffed we'll be good happy birthday
[Music]
[Applause]
oh definitely you know i installed uh
google translate into my brain not too
long ago
[Laughter]
[Music]
what did you wish for for your birthday
i wish that one day we can all hang out
together
and enjoy
i don't know like having a nice meal and
relaxing time together
[Music]
relaxing time and hang out you can come
to the maldives right now
we got space
you're gonna be fast
i'll try but i don't think i can swim
fast enough
okay okay okay
what are you what are you on let me see
you for if you can't swim fast
[Music]
maybe i should i should somehow
make a propeller out of my tentacles or
something it's difficult
apology
oh my god
oh yes
i hate like your baby is on like the
second day or so
oh what
delicious inna thank you
oh no has anyone seen gym
wait what why why does everybody name
the people they're looking for a gym i
called my chicken jim too
remember there was there was jim from
accounting too you know
they were they were
uh multiple jobs you know there's
multiple identities multiple
chiefs i thought jim was a chicken what
the hell
oh man i've been
bamboozled you know but we're one the
same you know it's it's
it branches off the same company in the
end so
you know there might be some overlaps
yeah oh okay
yeah anyways thank you so much for
calling in from so far away and while
you're relaxing
enjoy enjoy the rest of your your time
thank you
[Music]
ah
well i'm really happy they called in
when they're on their vacation
i can just imagine them cuddling and
calling on the same phone huh
[Music]
um
you are right on time
yes
i am right on time happy birthday eenay
it's an
inextraordinary
birthday isn't it
indeed indeed it is
[Laughter]
how are you
oh i'm i'm doing great especially since
it's your
birthday
you know you you flew by so fast that um
i thought it was still 2021 but behold
it's my birthday 2022.
i know lo and behold it is
time
i really like your merch your laundry
oh thank you thank you yeah it makes so
friends to be very useful to everyone
hopefully
oh it will
i want to get them
ah nice nice i hope i can just send
everyone
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
are you liking your birthday so far
though oh it's great i feel like
i feel like i've talked to
more people than i did for like the
entire year so far
but it's it's all been so nice like
there were some i wanted to talk to but
didn't really get a chance to and
there's
some i didn't get talked to for a while
no
now you are here too so i'm happy
everyone's here to celebrate your
special day because
we
like you believe it or not believe it
that devil
believe it
oh and
yeah i'm i'm i i'm
i'm speechless with all the all the love
i've gotten today i definitely will be
uh
fixing my broken ceiling leaking
afterwards
for you really
i've been holding it in pretty well i
think so far
but yeah um
yeah oh
uh
i i think i asked this before but after
i move um
you wanna
show me come over
yeah
i will definitely i will definitely um
yeah and you get to see time might ah
i can't wait
yeah
timeline do you like big dogs
i like all dogs and cats all animals i
don't know if they like me but i like
it's like it's like more like ignorance
you know like they don't acknowledge
that exists a lot of the times
oh
it's like i'm kind of thin air to some
animals but maybe it's just the cats
maybe dogs will like me a little better
i don't know
that happened to me too just like
like a few days ago it was pretty crazy
yeah like i was asking them to come over
they just looked at me
and just
went to the other person it was amazing
it was an amazing experience well it
kind of it kind of hurts differently
from when like people ignore you it's
just like
oh yeah
it's just like what did i do
what did i not do
because they're such innocent creatures
exactly
maybe they just they just know
something's up i don't know
maybe there's a side to me that i don't
know who knows wait
they they think we're bad
maybe maybe we just don't smell like
good food
we just don't smell friendly i don't
know
next time
you're like maybe we should go to like
kbbq or something beforehand
and the dogs will love us right
please
please please
but yeah
thanks for calling in um
i know we talked like not too long ago
but still like it's good to talk to you
more often yeah
yeah me too yeah let's let's hang out
yeah hang out sometime soon
sometime yeah
okay good luck
thank you you rest a bit too you sound
very very sleepy no no
like you you've been preparing a lot for
this birthday
you're probably gonna be tired after
enjoying today's birthday so
yeah thank
probably pass out after i eat my cake
yeah
yeah thank you so much
yeah no thank you
thank you bye bye
bye
well
that was a long
long
long list of course
well we made it
i'm really really happy um
to be part of all alive to have met such
wonderful friends
um along the way
um
yeah i'm just just really thankful i
could be here and i hope to continue to
work hard
um
yeah
i'm really really happy to be here
[Music]
ah thank you thank you so much
oh
okay i think
that should be it for collins yes okay
you guys waited a long time good job
okay
so
oh yeah while we were talking also torah
senpai also sent me a happy birthday
message thank you to our senpai
i hope to talk to her someday
um
yeah and as i said before
there is
uh one more thing i want to show you
guys before
before we end the stream today
okay
let me just uh
turn on the music for it
do you hear it
oh it's a serene
serene place i wonder what it could be
okay
are you guys ready for my present
to you guys
for being such wonderful wonderful
takarazis for
the year
um a lot of the things
ceiling stay
okay a lot of things that i achieved
last
year or so
i probably would have not been able to
do it without you guys so i
um wanted to create something where you
guys can also
uh you know meet other takora teas have
fun
um
and such
and i was surprised because it seems
like the uh
santa tacotachis also had the same idea
as i did
this is my gift to you guys okay hold on
let me show you
oh
what is this oh
i didn't want to show everything yet
so as you can see from maybe
maybe uh the ui it is a
vr chat world
i got specially made
for you guys to hang out in oh you see
my logo look how pretty it is and look
are we
are we under water or
marbling floors
that
so um i gathered
my favorite artworks that i've done over
my time here at hall live
i got a small gallery area
made for everyone to you know check out
everything i've drawn or you know meet
other taco that she's in and such look
look how beautiful it is you guys can
get a small peek at all the artworks out
here
but uh before i show you guys everything
i do wanna
take a moment to show you guys
a
uh
the wonderful people who made this
happen
uh
[Music]
look sassan the vr chat team and hilma
who made this entire project possible
uh thank you very very much for making
this happen um
it's absolutely amazing
like i i want everyone to be able to you
know visit the map in vr chat because
you don't need vr headsets in order to
you know check out
um
check out the gallery you can play on
desktop like i am right now it's very
calm for a place where people can hang
out and look at my art close up there
are some things i didn't show
some things i did show
um and oh
what is this
an audio guide
for
commentary very short commentary on
some of the things i thought about while
drawing a group of pieces you know you
can walk close up to it look at me oh
wow
i know the top ones it's kind of hard to
see but you can maybe adjust your height
um
yeah these are the pieces i do for tabi
nato too and i don't i don't think i
showed
all of this before you can walk close so
you can even see the pixels
yeah
and uh what their latest released cover
of nine-nine this is why i didn't show
you guys the full art
in yesterday's stream because i want you
guys to see it up close
in the vr gallery
and see the
art i know you might have to adjust your
height i'm i'm small enough right now so
i can't really jump that high but
you can see
all this and some
never before seen concept art of the
outfit
and you know the familiar backgrounds
that i drew for the street the studio i
actually have like a winter version and
like a nighttime rainy version of it i
didn't include it here because i want to
keep the format the same there's all
there's the garden we were just at
beautiful garden
and
beyond the void
maybe a scene from a dream
and oh yes this is one of my favorites
to see like up close it's just the scale
of it makes it really cool violet
and there's the uh
celebration picture i drew for two
million plays
and these are some of the gifts i gifted
to other members and members yeah
iris ame
vera
[Music]
and this is collection of ina
this is the new year's wallpaper did
it's the valentine's drawing
this is a pretty recent one uh having a
tattoo the spring ones
and this is still one of my favorites
but it was the first artwork i chew of
myself
can't believe it's almost been like two
years since i drew this one hmm good
memories right
and these are some of the other members
i've drawn i was so hard picking out
picking out some of them
yeah
of course curl need to
and i gotta say this is the highlight of
the gallery i'm looking down because it
has a very special effect
it's a image that everyone is familiar
with because it's been my
ending screen for the longest time
but if you look closely
it has a special effect on it
a parallax effect
you can see
the different layers of the image kind
of move i think it's more more
more visible if you see it in person i
don't know if it's uh more visible
on the screen right now but i really
wish you guys can check out this uh this
piece because when i first saw the
ability to add like parallax images like
this is the first image i thought of
so
that's great
yeah
it's different when you walk up close
look far
yeah
that's the gallery
um and there's one more surprise
well actually i want to show you guys
the view from above
um this is actually based on an existing
world that was made by israel and lok
sachsang but we uh we remodeled it so it
would fit every artwork
i wanted to showcase perfectly
exactly
it's very nice
and there's one one last
um
place i want to show you guys before i
end the stream
but um i gotta say the name of this
gallery area is a trip down taco
lane i think
and uh
i really wanted to be a place where you
know you can check out what i've drawn
but also you know maybe if it's a public
world you can meet other taco dachis and
make new friends a place to hang out for
everyone i want to make a place where
um
you can you can make new memories
together
hopefully down the line maybe i can add
more artworks to the top or something
but
um
last but not least the highlight the
very big highlight of the gallery
is this
teleport
use
of the monolith
[Music]
where does this take me
are you guys ready
to venture
into
beyond the void
okay
three two one
wow
isn't it so beautiful
it's a
something you see in the
middle of your dreams
yeah
and uh this world will be
a gift from me to you guys to hang out
check out the artwork make new friends
etc
um
and it will be available for everyone to
access publicly
soon after the stream i believe
we have we have a team on standby to
make it public
so
yeah
uh you guys can all go check it out
and have a lot of fun exploring
i believe i'll also tweet it out and
stuff um
it's called
a trip down
taco lane i think
i think
yeah chip down taco lane
i wonder if i can just copy paste
but i'll post the details on my twitter
too
afterwards
um i hope you guys like it
uh thank you so much
for
um
supporting me all this time
i really appreciate
all your support and making everything
happen it's it's really a dream come
true
and uh yeah let's have more fun i want
to do more projects bigger projects down
the line as well
but yeah um thank you
uh
for
everything i'll continue to do my best
let's all do our best okay
thank you so so so so much
everyone
and
i hope that uh oh yeah it's also in the
description of this of this stream too i
think
if you want to go visit right away yeah
but thank you so much i hope you guys
um have a wonderful wonderful
rest of the morning afternoon evening
i'll see you guys
as soon as possible okay take care
love you all
see you next time
bye bye
thank you
[Music]
love you akota cheese
you