[Music]
thank you
laughs
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
wait
kariki
[Music]
oh
um yeah I have a mono Monaco Monaco
Monaco
which one is it number one Monaco or
number two Monaco
Monaco a monocle not one some most
people say one well did I say Monaco
Monaco
monoko
when you don't hear the audio
ah that's not the
ah
[Music]
how to
you know what I'm just gonna throw it
into and draw the ass but it might hurt
your ears
I'm gonna put something into obsc maybe
you hear it right away and really loud
okay
three two one
oh
wait wait
[Laughter]
there you go okay okay you did it you
have endured it congratulations
[Music]
did it hurt
when you fell from the sky
oh
you lived I lived
nice congratulations thank you very much
oh let me have somebody jam up that
one's fine it's all volume okay
um foreign
[Music]
uh we are going to look at some more
what muted what's this add some more
Polo bags today
[Music]
hello bags what
it's back the best the best program I
have ever thought of possibly one of the
best ones but not the best I was irony
it's bad oh wait I need to look the
music
okay
yeah uh uh will there be repeats I don't
know we'll see maybe
um but uh my goal is well my goal was to
have uh if possible only new members but
last time we already did uh quite a few
or like almost all of the union members
so
so this time I I asked kindly to get
some more Banks from uh ID and Japan as
well if possible
oh 26 months of membership thank you oh
and I just got a last minute submission
yay thank you
a super secret
[Music]
uh super secret
um submitters
well I cannot do two things at the same
time no no I uh yeah
um yeah goes back clearly
kind of asking Yago
um
at some point we will have a
yeah go submission let me put this last
minute submission into my um Photoshop
so that I can show this off to you guys
too
right now you're just seeing a gray
screen but in a moment we'll be looking
at some beautiful Hollow backs foreign
[Music]
flip 90 degrees there we go no that was
the wrong 90 degrees
do you also never know which
in which uh Direction you should flip it
and you always you always somehow choose
the wrong one now I got it now I got it
yeah
but if you would think about it for a
moment maybe you wouldn't have so many
mistakes oh well
[Music]
okay so
um we might have like
maybe two two less submissions or so
than last time but I think it's fine we
should have plenty to talk about plenty
to look at plenty to inspect just
imagine this is a security check at the
airport
hmm
please please remove all the liquids in
your bag also do you have any any liquid
uh no not liquid any
lithium lithium batteries by the way
guys what's that about by the way like
don't they like at the
back check and add the back check in
both for a hand luggage and for the
check-in I always ask like about the
batteries but like
and I always say no but I'm never really
sure because like in my laptop I don't
know what kind of batteries then
probably there might be a lithium
battery in there but if you say yes
do they just want to know that you have
it or are you then forced to remove it
laptop batteries are safe really
because yeah laptops and phones I heard
they have lithium right so
within League limits oh okay okay okay
[Music]
because I've been always saying no and
every time I say no to that I always
wonder like am I risking something like
being arrested or so
that's is that travel size okay okay I
wonder what would not be considered
travel signs anymore
hmm
you can only carry it on hand carry I've
had I've I've put my laptop into the
um old or the laptop laptop I can't
speak anymore into my big luggage before
um just because it's so heavy and I I
just didn't feel like putting it in my
hand luggage and carrying it around the
whole time and I know a lot of people
always like well you crazy just because
uh you would be worried that it breaks
or gets stolen or you lose the whole
luggage and all that I was never really
worried about that but
I just want to know to be prepared for
an explosion
[Music]
power
bank should be on hand carrying
interesting
to know they exist and kind of achieve
it if it ignites in the cargo
compartment they cannot handle them
people eat Luggage in the airport yeah I
know I know I know um
they don't treat them very nicely but so
far I've put like many
fragile things into my big luggage
before and they never broke until now
and I've never also never been uh like
robbed out of my suitcase before but
yeah generally you should definitely
shouldn't rely on it
definitely not let's rely on it but
recently I've been carrying my my
um smaller suitcase around a lot when
traveling so for my hand luggage so I
have been putting my laptop in that one
instead so no worries hmm foreign
puppets also which are very fragile they
also survived in my big suitcase and
nobody stole them people should have
really stolen those suck puppets have
because they could have been worth
millions
up on eBay
[Music]
oh my yeah museum piece
PC yeah
they are like so valuable
let's all exaggerate why
hmm fools yes fools it's Modern Art
exactly I would cry if the puppets by
the way no I would cry too because I
spent many hours while I had the sea
thing
making those puppets
those were my only friends at the time
just kidding
I love the whole theory that uh
[Music]
I made those puppets out of
um not being very mentally stable at the
time and missing my friends because
everybody was gone all all the hollow
members were somewhere
and I was going crazy
I love that theory so even though it
wasn't like that I don't mind going with
that so
anyway I was a little bit a little bit
of a tangent in the get-go from the
get-go uh all right
[Music]
who will be
revealed and exposed in today's episode
of
we want
I need a logo for hollow packs but I
don't know how much more often I can do
this show
um because there's a limit of you know
people with bags so
yeah it might maybe not need a logo so
let's enjoy this episode
while thinking it might be the last one
it's bagging time
yeah that's infinite number yeah episode
two just time we're holding them oh I
guess so
I guess that's exactly why yeah for the
purpose of hollow bags episode 3 we will
all now start auditions for yeah that's
why today uh was there
uh and there was um and yeah let's get
an announcement exactly because I am
running out of bags
no
um
hi so let's go look at the first one
tell me we're just gonna do it like last
time I'm gonna like blur it
uh
this
[Music]
um even though I blurred it some things
are pretty visible
[Music]
um don't don't mind that where should we
start like it's pretty clear this this
is like pretty simple
but whoo could this be from let's start
but uh oopsie uh revealing
the most obvious things here oh
cute and yeah
some Anya merch that's that looks like a
coin purse maybe
um
but I wonder if that's their only person
or maybe they don't even put coins in
there it could be something else
foreign
[Music]
before
I think there are many fans of Anya
aren't we all fans of Anya you can't
though for sure
[Music]
maybe the bag maybe the Bamboozle here
is that this bag
the bag ingredients are
sent to me by a non-hole life member AKA
maybe the voice actress of Anya Forger
[Music]
what would you say if that was true
wouldn't you be like holy oh my God
will ever
[Music]
oh my God
Nani
[Music]
well no that is indeed this time not the
case now what is this
it kind of looks like a DS but no I
guess it's a power bank now that I see
um the buttons up the button the dots up
there
that looks like a power bank huh it's a
cute one with a with a little face on it
yeah
yeah now we already have two pink
objects pretty pink but you know little
girls girls like pink stuff or even if
you if they don't like pink stuff then
girly things are often just Pink by
default
foreign
[Music]
so this
seems to be
uh uh a toothbrush set that this person
seems to carry around in their bag at
all times so someone who cherishes their
hygiene
a lot
which is probably not an info that you
normally get out of streams
from the members so maybe not very
helpful
oh but yeah we see Japanese writing here
so possibly a Japanese member or any end
member living in Japan or an En member
who just is currently visiting Japan and
bought a set
now you cannot know there is or there
have been recently and there still are
yeah members
you know visiting and who knows
maybe someone
Among Us
we can't know for sure
[Music]
well I got one my submission
whoa cycle
[Music]
nice nice mess I got another one let me
let me let me let me save that real
quick
[Music]
it's okay
so now I think we're pretty much on par
with last time y'all go came through
thank you Yago
all right okay so this by the way
this I I found really interesting
because I've never seen this before
it says
which means like uh let's get rid of
those stains
oh I need those I didn't know this
exists like uh
to go
like stain remover
oh I guess yeah it's like a wet tissue
but
there's even two different types because
this one says it removes a soy sauce
coffee and stuff and this one says it
removes Curry on the right side ah you
see my muscle okay this is the right one
says Curry ketchup dressing
Etc why is it okay
um
a mess either no no I wouldn't say
necessarily just I mean you know there's
a there's a toothbrush and then this
like they're just generally just trying
to stay
oh wait
maybe there's a mess either I don't know
but in any way it seems Seems like
someone yeah uh clean and neat yeah
[Music]
a neat and meticulous person meticulous
I'm not sure anymore what that means
something like neat right
oh
[Music]
I have to answer something from from for
genma really fast
ah
[Music]
okay
hey
yes no no it's that Jen was back
although I did say to her today maybe
maybe eventually I need your bag oh
[Music]
foreign
has carried these around how do you even
know even that
participated last time and she did not
have these in there
not enough Spider-Man
exactly yeah not enough Marvel and so on
I mean that's I'm not saying Spiderman
is Marvel but I just mean in general she
likes that kind of stuff right
um but it's Spider-Man Marvel laughs
this is
okay thank God okay because I know if I
would have said it wrong then some
people would have uh canceled me so
let's be careful
nice safe all right this to me looks
like a proper
um pouch for money so maybe this is like
more for
um
you know paper money and this is for
coins so this is really just for really
something different hmm
we might never know the insides of the
bag that was inside the bag we need
another Hollow bag review of the bags of
the bags the the smaller bags that are
inside the bags we need to review those
too I need to inspect those
yeah
what's inside anyway it's a it's a cute
cute pouch with like a purse with uh
with bunnies on it but I don't recognize
the I don't recognize the brand but what
I think you might recognize already even
though it's blurred is this one up here
foreign
[Music]
very popular with the girls you know
I've I've seen a couple of
Hollow girls who have like Vivian vests
with stuff but there seems to be a
little hand towel yeah and she's um
carrying around
so we have uncovered everything
and now what do you think guys I've I
I've seen already some but we have
[Music]
does look like a Holier is that what you
what um you guys called Vivian Westwood
[Music]
oh okay Iris
sticking with coyote
well
you all right to stick with coyote
Sapphire because this one was coyote
Sapphire
no way it's clearly how did you know
how did you know
why are you saying no way it's coyote
why are you so sure oh did I say Senpai
okay
ah she might be watching this uh I told
her that we're streaming it today
foreign
[Music]
that's why you all are wrong wrong wrong
no from your point of view she couldn't
be a senpai from my point of view
possibly but no actually not I'm the
same guy so
oh God damn it
um
when will I learn
when will I learn hmm
foreign
[Music]
by Senpai a lot like putting Senpai at
the end of their name but you don't do
that with kohai which is maybe one of
the reasons why I keep on going back to
Senpai because you know
foreign
[Music]
I like
um
really
what is it about coyotis
that makes us want to call her Senpai
what
I'm definitely not the only one
Senpai aura yeah no she's just so I
don't know
well okay
next Hollow bag
nice okay let's go for
um this one
[Music]
thank you
next one is this one which is so
colorless
so dark
it's two photos by the way we're gonna
clear it up
in a moment it's a drug bust is
you guys look at this for one moment and
just because it's still dark and gray
you think it's um
foreign
[Music]
let's take a look all right all right so
first the picture is um here I'll I'll
unleash the whole thing
okay it's just like a rough look inside
I guess
uh so we see a relatively small bag
[Music]
um
not girly at all I see one like badge
inside one pin and a wallet that's the
word I was looking for wallet
and uh oh phone
and some like ticket or something up
there I can't really read it
very functional yeah I'm a part two it's
it kind of looks like it would be like a
photo from Ahmed because that's kind of
how she took her photo yeah and her
stuff was also not that girly
um
this is definitely a one out of ten and
the girls suck me right here
yeah I I was thinking I need to have a
conversation with this person
um but you know to each turn around
okay so let's take a closer look
although it's really only free things
that
um this person is letting us look closer
at even though I see there's more things
in there
how dare you hide these things from us
okay let's go first for the wallet
the wallet
I
I will 100 understand
if you guys will not be able to guess
who this is from
because for me as well I was like
shocked I'm like this doesn't match my
my image
of this person
image
yeah but it seems to be a brand I see
Chanel logo on the
on the golden silver whatever thing
there to close the
wallet so
okay it's simple
but it's a it's a brand
that's Brandon it will look very closely
we see Chanel right there
it's you
uh audit why is it so it's such a weird
position foreign
okay
next
gonna unveil the phone
which none of this is really helpful
um but the phone is a bit broken on the
side
and what is this is this an iPhone
or a smartphone I think it's an iPhone
is that Android
[Music]
so Android person
yeah but
I wouldn't say that the shattering and
the screen tells us much
also it's only a small shattering on the
edges
so even the reflection that I see very
clearly doesn't help me because I don't
know what that is reflecting maybe a
beehive so maybe it's on me again
because she's a bee
[Music]
hmm I see your behavior so now you see
the style of the bag it's
it's uh I guess you could wear it as a
shoulder bag or around the hip which you
know what I feel about those if you
watched the last
the last Hollow bags episode
I hate
at least on
yeah I don't know no I hate the funny
facts on everybody
fanny packs I like
I don't even get me started because then
the fanny pack people will cancel me but
I think there there are
no don't say okay well don't say it
don't say it don't say it it's too harsh
it's too harsh people who cannot handle
your opinions you know
[Music]
um
so I had to sneeze
um but it says Adventure awaits and
somehow I think
I think this at least gives off Vibes
it's not a Japanese member doesn't it
doesn't it
I don't know I mean
just because of this English
written on there hmm
but yeah I mean this really
this gives us no clues in my opinion
foreign
now could I see all right guys I have in
the chat not seen a single correct
answer and I've been looking for a while
until now it is incredible
[Music]
it's Kobo
yeah
I am as confused as you guys are
[Music]
um what yeah there's no blow at 809 it I
mean there didn't need to be blue but I
thought she would have some cute things
in there who knows what that badge is
though Mary that badge is something
super cute but that doesn't make up for
all the lack of cuteness but okay I mean
as we said to each their own but it's
like so confused
that's not even waterproof hmm maybe the
fanny pack is but I want to
know Kobo
if you ever see this are you watching
are you wearing this over your shoulder
or over your hips
or over something else
I need to know to judge you more
that would have guessed it yeah me
neither if I didn't already know I would
have not guessed this I think
yeah
a couple of Android makes no sense to me
I don't think that really tells us much
but oh my my throat is kind of rough
today again sorry guys
[Music]
okay
needs iPad why why she weren't like VR
headsets Maybe
hmm
Rose Canada I got some well I'm okay and
the stream won't be long
[Music]
wake up Apple Apple stuff is expensive
yo Andrew's kind of makes
[Music]
have you heard to find out indeed indeed
yeah
I will I will have to talk with her also
she needs to show me the rest of the
items in there there's some link papers
and I need to see them
all right thank you Kobo for
participating
next bag
let's go next to Next Door
I
we continue with the pattern of
basically having nothing in their bag if
that is true I cannot say
uh I am doubting it but this is this is
what we get to see okay so let's let's
accept it
is
that a candy well what else would it be
it doesn't need a candy in Japanese
so
evil Japanese member or a minimalistic
en member that is currently residing in
Japan
a mini flashlight
[Music]
do you know girls
lipstick or something like that okay
a mini flashlight maybe for an energy
but of course that size and that shape
would be
chapstick but a lipstick or so but I
like your I uh if that was a joke I like
it very much
I also bought the flashlight
who cares
ome
at all times and out of three the very
few free things that they would show
you know the one thing they would have
is a flashlight huh do you really
believe that the one thing they would
have is a flashlight
[Music]
no I don't I don't believe it
I have a pen light I have a pen and a
flashlight oh well there's a couple
people have like a pen combined with a
flashlight that's cool that's smart
because having a pen in your back makes
a lot of sense I would say
[Music]
okay okay next next we have
a wallet which doesn't have many okay I
also don't know how you guys would guess
this one
but go ahead
throw it at me I will be
um very surprised give me your reasoning
too give me your reasoning why do you
think it is the person that you're
telling me this say say the name and
then give me a reason
what makes you think
polka said before that she carries candy
Louie because very business-like uh-huh
then because it looks cute enough Iris
because of candy and pink wallet Iris
because she doesn't go outside
could be anyone because no details yeah
true
based on
[Music]
based on low effort must be an end
excuse me
so it seems mature
baby because she's traveling
for stingrays
okay never mind I do need a fruit candy
in one second maybe I can take the one
on the screen no that might not even be
a fruit candy
let me
take my own fruit candy yeah
[Music]
if it is in the end that roast would
have been amazing hey no it is a
Japanese member I'll give you that
Japanese
falling live Japan member Deva armas
member
[Music]
well I see no correct answers so
let me help you it's someone who is in
a hollow cure
I think yeah I think I think I played
her in Hulu queue before
foreign
[Music]
answers
it's matsuni senpai
which I mean the insides of the bag
don't really seem unlike Matsuri it's
just surprising because it wasn't much
information to go by
oh god oh oh God
that's that's a a way of saying oh God
with a context that you know I've never
thought you know I would say it like
that before
not like oh god what the it's more
like oh God ah oh you were talking about
God oh God
Goto
[Music]
I can't believe it well you must believe
it it is true I wouldn't lie to you
about God about Godly things
just these cute lips apparently yeah I
guess so
I met her before and I mean I didn't
look inside her bag
but I think she was very well she was
carrying a a decent sized bag
than to think that there would only be
three things inside there I I don't
believe it but you know I told everybody
they don't have to show everything you
know they they can just show what they
feel comfortable with showing them maybe
that was the only thing you know
so that's okay are you doubting God
not this God
okay next door next Bang
[Music]
which one should I go for hmm
oh let's go let's go this one
[Music]
now we have some more stuff okay
finally more stuff to look at
it
yeah we have lots lots of things to look
at where do I even start now
well you guys are already already
guessing what is up
Wallet not wallet at first red mullet
again so starting from the wallet I like
the pattern it's nice
yeah it's cute
a cute wallet relatively cute but not
like like super super girly cute right
it's just a a nice a nice cute
hmm
yeah this one's labeled Danke Schoen
because uh I might have not known that
this is a wallet otherwise yeah
foreign
um then
we have some cards but I guess we can
say it's not a Japanese member because
uh the labeling is in English
um
some cards are these like I think I've
seen them before like some collectible
cards
ah it's a
is that yeah
not only that but this person carries I
own the scarf to carries the uh a whole
life merchandise scarf around
um which is a little bit concerning
[Music]
I would like to tell this person to not
wear the scarf
too much outside maybe
and then we have
a hairbrush
yeah okay okay I'm important to keep
that hair untangled at all times
especially because I feel like when you
wear a scarf it makes for me at least
makes my hair tangle like crazy
[Music]
and then you know a hair clip
exactly how did you see it someone with
hair
with someone with hair was there someone
with hair in Holland
a lot hey
also not fun
oh come on poor father
[Music]
I mean Effie
makes a lot of people bald at some point
[Music]
there may be more bald members than you
know about
[Music]
yeah streaming since 7 20 p.m sorry my
laptop is at that setting for LPS I
think it's better that way anyway
yeah okay let's go up here
I see some notes with a pen
yeah
but those nose it's not whole life I
don't know what that is have you guys
seen it before
is that something
that I should know
can I zoom in
thank you
hmm
[Music]
Bubba
ah
ah is that YouTubers so is that like
Indie YouTubers because they have names
[Music]
does no one know in Indies
okay okay okay okay
and then we have a phone
and
ah a playlist
pen lights
a power bank
I never bring power Banks and I always
regret it some scrunchies
a very hair focused person because we
have a brush and two hair accessories in
here wow
Kristen likes to do stuff with their
hair a book what book is this
[Music]
what
Shaheen miral and What's the title of
the book confront Your Shadow heal
yourself transform the world
[Music]
what is this book
so Tyler what's this book about
eyeshadow let me look at the eyeshadow
as a girl I have to judge this oh
foreign
thingy brush on top of it but I think it
says the body shop
The Body Shop has makeup
realize
[Music]
uh a Rubik's Cube which I feel like is
just a flex on us
I ain't really caring a room is killed
around really really and it's solved too
foreign
[Music]
this actually looks like a pretty heavy
bag at this point
and then let's look at the back it's a
red shiny
pink rucksack
[Music]
comfortable to wear comfortable to carry
many things around that you may need in
one day and well I mean
oh YouTube is uh lagging a little bit
[Music]
are we are we okay you guys seeing me
YouTube okay here okay okay
well well well
let me make my chair higher
which is hello
well yeah I don't think it's worth
hiding it for much longer because it
seems very obvious actually sit still I
showed you the wallet I already saw
correct answers which maybe just came
from the fact that it's written in
English and then I don't know I don't
know why but it's Ollie a second time
she did a second submission
foreign
she submitted before last time and she
named this one all these bigger bag
because I guess in the previous one she
had a few less things in a smaller bag
yeah
[Music]
I think a lot of things gave her away
like the cards the merchandise the
Rubik's Cube the light stick and the
other things maybe if you know her very
well then they would also all give away
something
but I know is is this a different phone
case and a different power bank than
last time if it's the same phone case
then that's a huge giveaway hmm
but yeah the merchandise and all that oh
my God it's so obvious
[Music]
ly
um
she's ready for concert yeah
yeah
games
games where the games you mean the
Rubik's Cube
only only I feel like I wanted to ask
you something I have what's that book
about somebody in the chat by the way
when I showed the book was saying Ollie
is the only one who reads
which
is kind of sad for everyone except only
but only tell me tell me
tell me about this book what's that
about I want to know I'm curious what
kind of stuff you're reading
[Music]
the title is
yeah I think I'mma reads too
that's all right really really
does she read more than just comments
where's the rest of her
only
did you did you write it already and I
missed it
tarot for travel times confront your
timer for travel times didn't want to
show the title at first because I didn't
want people to think I'm true
oh but it's about Tyrone 10 roads cards
[Music]
that's interesting
so it's like a set aha I didn't want
people to think and travel
[Music]
um
foreign
yeah well a very interesting bag thank
you ollie I don't know if you've been
watching for a while but
um there was some very empty bags so far
so thank you for giving us a big
interesting bag yeah thank you very cute
it shows your personality thank you for
participating a second time already
thank you soon
[Music]
this one
now this one also has a lot of items
should I start let's start here
we have Japanese
Band-Aids
okay
either this person gets hurt a lot or
this person just likes to be prepared
but maybe this is the remaining things
in her bag that we're missing because
her yeah this was just free things
no but you know I mean it could also
just be okay so others get hurt who
knows
and we have
[Music]
um
oh we have some bobby pins and uh a hair
tie
[Music]
okay okay
oh let's welcome here
this
is cute
I mean look at you
it's like a little keychain plushie that
uh looks like a bird but also like uh
what do you call them Matryoshka
inspired bird plushie maybe I don't know
[Music]
cute
yes okay okay it reminded me of several
things so oh
interesting interesting
it's cute I guess I guess it's not a
bird somehow it looks like a bird to me
because I guess those green thing is
they look like P foul feathers to me
okay
why do you think this is I have already
gotten the information what it is
from the person
is
a spinning top
stress thing
earbuds
stress toy fidget toy
it is I mean you could probably use it
as a fidget spinner or something like
that
but it is indeed a massage a little
massage toy uh a thing
that you like you know you hold in your
hand and then you like rub it over your
shoulder or something I guess
um yeah so yeah moving on uh uh yeah uh
um for your teeth what do you call those
strings
tube strings or yeah
looks painful to me oh would you decide
how much pressure you want to apply so
it doesn't have to be painful that's a
plus
it should just be two strings okay
hmm
AKA two strings
let's make it simple just make it
[Music]
soon okay so and in addition to that
another person who carries around
toothbrush set
yeah oh
um besties with coil living coloring
possible
they could be brushing each other's
teeth
when they're together who knows like one
brushes the others Chiefs
in the bathroom huh man I don't know I'm
just making suggestions like you know
it's kind of Tainted kind of fitting
[Music]
thank you
and then we have a little box which is
probably
a glasses case but it looks very
rectangular for that I don't know I
guess it is a glasses case
oh
they're very versatile yeah
jeans yeah Jin's glasses
do they exist um overseas
now
[Music]
um
it says sniff upside down
oh what is this
[Music]
foreign
take a bath
like in random places
Chloe's out hey
[Music]
first you roast Ian
and then the oh man
you guys are so me
[Music]
okay next thing
although I'm still wondering about the
bath salts what is this
is that like tiny stickers of dogs
[Music]
I think I have some info on um
the items
sent to me let me see if that's if
that's like explained
[Music]
no
oh this one this one is not
[Music]
long
that's probably stickers it's already
pretty soon
here it doesn't help much I would say
I guess that's like tiny stickers dog
stickers
maybe he has a gift or
I don't know to put on notes or so
oh okay next
[Music]
uh
fish
mince right probably
[Music]
it's probably breakfast right
but there's like isn't that card still
in the box isn't that cards no
it looks like cards inside
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
playing cards yeah I don't know
we'll have to inquire again because I
thought I had enough explanations but
turns out I don't here's a wallet which
is not very girly
it's just a pretty normal looking
Brown then we have some pants
some more writing stuff
uh Japanese signature stamp
yeah because they don't normally they
don't sign with their hand they sign
with stamps hmm
uh something to know the time
AKA o'clock
wrist wrist uh
uh what do you call a clock on your hand
a watch
oh man and then we have some more life
cards which you probably already kind of
like
noticed
um because they're kind of obvious
uh which are like collectible cards um
so what do you think
[Music]
who does this belong to that in order
we see someone who cares about their
hygiene someone who seems pretty serious
about you know work
and but still supports whole life
and has some cute
[Music]
um
with some interesting items there
well well well
it was it
s understand
okay hey hey
yes
I think it's very obvious a lot of you
guys have been saying hey John for a
while now yeah yeah
um
gave me some explanations
it just said the thing about the massage
ball what that is uh
she told me also
that's the Dharma on the top right the
little plushie is a souvenir that she
bought with as soon as I buy it when
they went on a trip recently sweet isn't
it
and uh
uh-huh she says that she doesn't have I
mean she does have a wallet but um most
of the time she doesn't carry a wallet
with her
because she mostly pays for everything
with her um like card on the phone like
a digital card basically
um
and also that she carries the toothbrush
set with her because at all times
because
[Music]
before she meets
a member or before she streams
when she streams you know in the studio
or so
she will always brush her teeth right
before I guess you know because she does
a lot of program programs official
programs where
um she talks to members next to her and
she wants
she wants yeah Pleasant to be around
with it
yeah very professional yeah
I still don't know about the stickers
and about but maybe the the bathtub
could be a souvenir as well that she
just forgot in her bag
[Music]
s
good
is it everybody
or is it just some people
[Music]
we're back okay YouTube please don't
bully me like this
please
we're fine okay hello yeah so I wonder
if this uh the bath salts are just uh
also a souvenir that you forgot to put
out of her bag
take out of her bag maybe possibly
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
okay next one next
if you guys are ready
this one's aichan
okay next up a very
beautifully properly aligned one as you
can see
foreign
[Music]
it's like Tetris
okay let's take a look it oops it
it looks kinda
ladylike elegant hmm
just buy this blurred image
here we go
eyeshadow seems like I have to bring
this person to Girls Talk eventually
our Channel
lip tint I know this brand even it's a
good It's a grand
[Music]
son
you guys learned about Lipton recently
and girls talk didn't you do you guys
remember
it's not just liquid uh lipstick no
it's even more liquid than liquid
lipstick
because liquid lipstick is very gooey
but lip tint is like like really just
like water liquidy
it's like tint
when you put it when you wrap it on your
on your lips
are lip balm you don't get
free watch the girl suck
I told you what it is it's applied like
a spray no it's not
ah
and a lip balm
probably to put underneath the lip tint
some cute hair pins
currently oh some pretty perfume
[Music]
a wallet and this one I find interesting
because
it's Nightmare Before Christmas uh
character
right
I mean maybe that character is like
Standalone not only that member for
Christmas but uh yeah hi Dad dick
Wellington
um so someone who's a fan of Jack
perhaps
[Music]
I know they have like a wallet maybe
they
got it in in Disney
maybe or so hand sanitizer
because I think it's Disney isn't it I
feel like I saw
[Music]
that
in Disney before
Maybe I'm Wrong
hand sanitizer yeah
it is right okay
airpods
and we start again I'm surprised this is
the first time I'm seeing airpods this
time last time there were like in almost
every bag almost everyone hadn't had
airpods or an off-brand or like not
off-brand but like Samsung or something
like that um
surprised it took this long way right
right oh oh fancy stuff here well indeed
so far pretty fancy a cushion which I
think it's like not a cushion in a
conventional sense it's a cushion for
makeup like cheeks and foreign powder
cushion mm-hmm
not a cushion to sit on that would be
too small
[Music]
here's the phone a green case but I like
the screen
but that's kind of surprising
because so far
it's been like pink purple
that kind of stuff
rose gold
hmm
actually gray I think
could be I guess looks very like
greenish tomato
look I do like it
classy sophisticated oh
that
is either a covet nose swab test
kit
or uh a clear gloss or no hahaha
sorry got a bit confused there for a
moment
um
sunscreen
huh what's that language
[Music]
so what's that language
that's French or something like that
right
hope
interesting a charger
iPhone charger
hair clip oh cute cute
solid proof
do you really carry two perfumes of you
one solid and a like liquid one
yeah
and I yeah there must be some confused
people about solid I guess you just like
rub it like a lip balm around your neck
probably or behind your ears or so I
assume I never use solid perfume before
but probably no no foreign
[Music]
no I don't think it's deodorant because
then she would probably ride deodorant I
would think
there are solid uh perfumes yeah
I have some makeup
a hair stick
Point hair stick
foreign
interesting I know
about like hair sticks that like can
cover like bald spots or so
or like gray hair
what
EU charger
[Music]
is it my bag
a nice observation though
it does seem like an EU charger
[Music]
oh
what little baby was in the last uh bag
review wasn't she pretty sure I had her
in the last bit bad review
[Music]
in which places do you use EU blocks do
you use them in Indonesia
then I don't need any um converters if I
go to Indonesia is that what you're
saying that's actually amazing let's go
and then a Kate Spade bag which is
um
I think girls who choose Kate Spade as
they're back they have a good fashion
sense generally but a kind of like a
chill but still elegant and pretty and
sometimes a little bit girly but
generally they're just like they have a
good fashion sense and they're
they're just
cool girls in my opinion
so this Kate's paid bag tells me a lot
about them yeah I like them yeah
is it your Factor
that is
Muna final answer
[Music]
tell some crony Believers interesting
like froni you see a European charger
[Music]
European charger I guess we could say
this is someone from Indonesia
hmm okay it's Muna but I want to when I
saw this picture I was I wanted to tell
Luna why did you make the make the
purple you are like influencing
everybody's consciousness
uh to make them think immediately it's
you
also that even the carpet is kind of
purple and a lot of the items are kind
of purple looking everything the whole
picture has a purple tint Mona
everything's purple it's like
brainwashing and it's too easy when
everybody was it was spamming from the
beginning
[Music]
one comment one comment already uh
before I when I first showed the picture
when it was still blurred before I
uncovered anything somebody already said
Luna
how
it's hot
ah you made it too easy apparently
[Music]
yeah and because it's very organized
and and purple you're not saying this
because you weren't you were
subconsciously influenced that's why
you're not saying it you say it's
because it's organized but I don't think
that's the only thing it's organized and
it's purple
yeah let's be real
the hair stick is not for calling but
it's like a hairspray but using the same
brush like mascara it's for your bangs
oh yeah I think I've seen that before
[Music]
so
um
it's like more like instant not not so
much like Hairspray but more like hair
wax
for like smaller parts of your hair like
I think I've seen like Kpop idols
use it before hmm
yeah
you have to let me try that someday I
want to test it out is it good is it
good
yeah no of course it's not always uh
obvious by the color also no no
no no
um thank you yeah oh Muna why do you
need two perfumes while you're here
explain please why do you have a solid
perfume and the normal perfume why are
you just flexing your perfumes just
trying to improve your image
I bought it in Japan if you're in Japan
you can find it easily oh I guess okay
yeah they probably have that kind of
stuff yeah
did you also buy your wallet in Disney
when you went to Disneyland
didn't you didn't you go to Disneyland
when you weren't
you is this Bots there or
[Music]
20 questions
ah
whoa
you could also use that one on your skin
though couldn't you
she's been maxing
oh
interview stream yeah tell me more tell
me more where did you buy the wallet
tell me more tell me more why do you
have two perfumes
liquid not lasting as long as someone ah
if you spread on the body not a hotel
thank you very much Mrs hoshinova for
your submission
beautiful really like oh compare this
to this
[Laughter]
[Music]
no shade but
10 out of 10 bag and 10 of the 10
presentation I love you know uh how it's
like so cleanly
put side by side and then the picture is
like from a perfect bird's eye point of
view
it's so good to look at
it thank you thank you okay next time
next is this one
whoa it's so bright
that's your child so what that's exactly
why I have to be strict
now that's also a lot of stuff a lot of
big items everything looks so big to me
here
foreign
let's start here
um I think the image has been brightened
up by a lot but that looks like hand
cream
[Music]
vanilla scent
hand cream and this does not give away
yet if it's Japanese or so because uh
it's uh French but you guys are still
saying Japanese do you remember
[Music]
Canada
okay okay okay
uh oh God are those airpods
no maybe not airpods but they could be
like Samsung whatever
but I don't know why I hate them but I
have a fight to pick with them yeah
they're catching up with me guys I
cannot escape from them
my pods and convenient no they're not
because you lose them
it's not
all
here
perfect this is exactly the size of my
what this is so this is so satisfying
the brushes if I knew how big this would
be
that count baking
perfect match
it's a pressed powder so some makeup
powder with a sun protection Factor oh
and here we have some bigs which is not
only
this is an over over over International
uh brand but I don't see it much in
Japan actually but they're good
okay not Japan here you go now I have
Bamboozled too now you're confused but
here it's written in Japanese
actually they're in Japanese
so I cleared that one up immediately
got him
[Music]
okay next we have
um
as a brush for the powder in a plastic
cover okay okay and uh this looks like
um blush this is a brush and this is a
blush and this is a powder
this is a skin color powder and this is
a blush pink color
[Music]
oh Iris was eating a Vicks earlier
next we have
[Music]
not spice Japanese spices I guess this
person when they go out to eat
[Music]
probably doesn't get enough spiciness
it adds her own spice to foof
[Music]
um
it could be jenma
could be definitely a member who likes
spicy food and we have a a hand towel as
uh well as someone else who's also
carrying a hand towel around
interesting you know I understand
carrying around the hand towel in
Japanese summer because it's so humid
that I also tend to carry a hand towel
around when possible to wipe my sweat
because it's insane actually
absolutely insane Japan is the only
country where I do that
um but in Winter interesting in Winter I
don't
see why I would need one
but
I guess I guess could be useful
[Music]
public tones without hand trying I don't
really think that exists in Japan I've
never seen one
they all have like even like disposable
little tissues or air drying
or so
um
ah
[Music]
um
some Japanese broke wrote that her
carrying around a towel
at all times even in Winter must mean
that this person was raised well and now
that you say it interesting I I think I
understand the like reasoning or the
sentiment I think I I think I get it
maybe that's true
then this wallet I like the design
I like the I think that's supposed to be
blue like a
um
[Music]
marine blue and red I love that I love
it
um I like the design fancy
it's pretty thick too yeah it's so thick
it needs to be closed with a really
strong lock
okay
yo I'm done we have some more makeup oh
nice
and
oh I guess it's a bag for the makeup
and some lip cream and
maybe what's that there's another cream
the top one but I don't know for what
so
your turn guys
go ahead
how does all that fit in the small bag
no not that I don't think that's
supposed to be in there that's just a
bag for the things that are on top of it
I'm pretty sure
[Music]
sorry my chair is squeaky Iris Iris or
Subaru
[Music]
Iris I RIS
we already had it
you know
we already have Ina too
well interesting so
apparently you have been misled
it's not Iris
apparently it could have been judging by
the vix
does Iris like spicy food
well it's not Iris
[Music]
it is
this one is by Louie
oh
I think I only saw like one person
saying rui
so yeah that's quite a surprise for many
it seems
makes sense now you think so
I don't really think that anything here
specifically speaks for Louis
specifically like in my mind like this
could be many girls there's not
something that's like super personal
it's like makeup although I mean the
spice is interesting the spice is very
interesting yeah
that just tells you this person likes
spicy food very much so much that they
cannot live without it
[Music]
the other thing I think about it
um me and Louis ate curry together and I
got the
um spice level zero and I think she did
get like maybe not 10 but a very spicy
level yeah she does like spicy food
that's
skin foreign
[Music]
next one
we have this one okay let's go to
oh we had this one let's go to this one
how many more bags um free including
this one I think should be free
[Music]
yeah
oh cute already isn't it and you see the
Louis Vuitton
oh
I like
um some Louis Vuittons I like the
pattern from Louis Vuitton I just like
the pattern you know
and this one in particular the color
combinations I do like this one ah good
taste
good taste
now
nice wallet so that one out of the way
is that what brand that is yes Louis
Vuitton hmm
yeah the LV
and we have oh okay there's many
expensive things here
um what's this one called again
um
uh
Saint Laurent or so was that that
um
what do you call that one again
yeah I've I've seen
Lawrence
which I think is like this one's
probably like a lipstick or so
and a pen okay oh no wait maybe it's a
hanko no cases
[Music]
lips
lipstick or something like that
umbrella
is this some merch is this umbrella Corp
from um
is it really like some specific
merchandiser
is that Resident Evil
that's Resident Evil much
foreign
[Music]
now this I don't know what that is so
please help me guys do you know what
that is it doesn't quite look like an
airpods case but because what's that
pointy thing up there
[Music]
inhaler our bank phone bank mini power
bank
[Music]
is that so
Curry
a very modern Ocarina
hold on what charger so thank you
I never seen one before in that shape
huh okay then we have eye drops I think
yeah those are eye drops
they're good Japanese eye drops are
really good
I've used them before they're really
good but I don't think it's just
Japanese items but the ones I found
there I can't find those in Austria like
that type of eye drops
this is a power bank how did you how did
Google tell you that
is Google a person that's sitting next
to you
how do they know
damn yeah
Japanese item indeed
and this
is a mirror I think but I don't know if
this is some kind of merchandise or if
it's just a really cute fancy makeup
brand
well hard container from some
um
[Music]
yeah I don't know it looks a little bit
like like a sailor moon to me or I don't
know
looks like Zelda
you know if they sell that then I want
that too
if that's a Zelda heart container
um compact mirror or so then holy
thank you for creating cute girls merch
thank you soon
I want that too
but I doubt that that's Zelda related
but it would be actually yeah I don't
want it I want it
next we have a wallet from Samantha
which is um a cute bag brand in Japan
um
some candies and yeah I'm I'm trying to
stay away from this but now I have
nothing left but to uncover this
[Music]
I'm not sure if
um my manager this time I let my manager
contact
UM the people and ask them if they want
to participate I'm not sure if my
manager clearly communicated that
um they're not supposed to make it
obvious
[Music]
uh then it's supposed to be kind of like
a guessing game at least for a little
while
I feel I feel that was left out
[Music]
it's bad girl
yes oh Batman yes yes
[Music]
but I don't think I even think without
this
I mean this is so obvious but without
this I still think it would have been
pretty
um pretty obvious I think it's very
characteristic of her especially after
meeting her
she has like quite a few brand things
and the style you know bright colored
girly stuff this is just up her alley
but yeah the pen now that you guys tell
me that that's from like Resident Evil
biohazard is very interesting to me did
she play that on stream
[Music]
ing
Resident Evil
even if she played recently would you
get a pen of that so quickly after
hmm maybe she got it like as a present
or so who knows but uh
oh oh it's just called biohazard and
that's a Japanese style I thought it was
two different games
that are somewhat connected with one
another uh-huh
she wakes from
[Music]
you know the thing is you guys were like
when you were guys and when you guys
were spamming umbrella Corp in the chat
you know what I was thinking of
I thought you guys were saying that this
was
Umbrella Academy merchandise
I know I'm so unbased I know
[Laughter]
[Music]
ah I'm sorry for disappointing you
that's what I thought it was first yay
high five
not only me
um
[Music]
bye
they have an umbrella Corp and biohazard
interesting
I'll look into it
okay okay okay
let's look at we have two more bags
let's look at the next one thank you
Mega standby for your cute submission
also Imagine Empire
[Music]
your next stop
I'm not gonna rinse super trucks today
by the way guys I think first of all I
have to try to sleep early and second of
all fruit
um but let's let's
[Music]
um oh it looks like it's not uh with a
bag just the inside of the bag
uh it looks drawn because it is drawn so
let's take a look
uh I think Ina also Drew her back before
a while ago let's take a look all right
[Music]
oh my God
she wrote what it is because otherwise I
wouldn't know what this is
a crayon yeah
[Music]
a very big cigarette
the other thing
it's a ChapStick okay I saw that as an
option
[Music]
that's funny
oh my God okay
next is
[Music]
okay that could be a lighter for them
no I think that's a lip gloss or so yeah
yeah
let's go
[Music]
with the rocket
okay what is this ah
what's this is that your pet huh
hey hey
[Music]
you
are making it
a bit easy to guess this one
[Music]
all right all right but this is this is
cute yeah I will I will need to inspect
further if this thing is alive or not
[Music]
[Laughter]
do you guys
Maybe This Time It's the flashlight for
real no a headphone jack
that's a huge handful jacket for this
one
screwdriver
for real what is this
is
everyone
um yeah probably for the phone because
nowadays they all have like USBC
no actually no this looks more like for
um
like bigger
microphone thingies
[Music]
um
but I've seen something like this before
pretty big though I didn't remember it
to be this big
yeah 3.5 to something like that yeah
yeah yeah yeah one of those
oh I guess it just happened to be in her
bag no no which which one one second let
me let me check something real quick
yeah okay
so here we have
[Music]
uh a little pouch for
something maybe money maybe uh
this uh ChapStick and the lip color
no probably that probably belongs
together and this is cinnamon
[Music]
yeah Japanese cute character and
matching to that is a cinnamon roll
card carrier
yeah um
you guys are
[Music]
this is this is Gouda
the lizard typo
you did this on purpose
[Music]
the freaking comic sense
I told her if you want to write like
what it is then maybe don't do it in
like blue and she was like oh yeah right
that's right good idea because I guess
she was planning to do it in blue and it
gives it away but then you know she kept
the the comic sense which is also very
good I like
but cute stuff interesting thank you
good uh for for taking part in it and I
do love cinnamon roll and this is really
cute
I'm guessing that she probably bought
these things during her stay here I
would assume but maybe not but maybe she
did because I feel like merchandise like
card carriers
are
way more common here in Japan than
outside of Japan or like yeah
she just talked about cinnamon roll in
the Stream
the giveaway oh yeah what's the lizard
oh I I must ask
[Music]
might be watching this what's the lizard
is that lizard alive
yeah what is that is it like a little
keychain or something you got from a
gotcha like a little figurine or so hmm
hmm But yeah I wanted to say that the
card carry is you know for for uh public
transportation cards they're very common
merchandise thingy in Japan
very useful well I have a feeling like
she must have gotten it here
she keeps live lasers in her purse for
snacking later definitely
but yeah a cute very cute
[Music]
I'll ask her later okay
I'll inspect thank you Google
I met her today too I mean how can I not
meet her
we're meeting every day
yeah
I I
walked um I walked back to our place
with Cuba and when we arrived at our
doors
I I've been starting this thing we did
it a couple times now but I've been
starting to do this thing like we were
we would like open the doors at the same
time with our keys and then
I would like to start doing a race with
her
but without even announcing that it's a
Race So it's not really fair so I I race
to open my door and
get inside and then right before I close
the door I look over to her to her who's
still like scrambling with the door and
say loser and then she's like ah damn it
and then I close the door and just
disappear
worked yesterday worked today
okay let's see how many more times I
will win the door opening race
I'm always the first
[Music]
all right we have one more
back let me just
um
prepare it by throwing it and into
Photoshop and then blurring it because I
just got it
oh
interesting
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
but I asked some more people today
during the day if they wanna do a last
minute submission
and this is what I got from it yay did
Kiana show her back I showed my bag last
time and I mean the insides didn't
really change uh so you know if you're
curious you can watch the VOD from the
last back reveal there were a lot of
other bags there too so yeah
[Music]
oh wait I did it wrong once one second I
didn't separate the layers
let me redo that
[Music]
let me throw a Second Blur on there all
right here we go yes we did it simple
it's not too many things
um let's start here
with a hand cream
it's like a oh like a flowery scent
peony
gardenia wow and again so French oh but
I know this brand I like I like this one
there's some things from that one
um long long time ago
they have like all kinds of like bath
stuff bath salts
and creams and bodies soaps and all that
you guys you guys have been memeing
around for a while in my chat
making very wrong guesses
and next we have a cute again flowery
brush a cold cold actually a comb I
never use Combs I hate Combs I always
use brushes and because comes with my
hair they just don't work there's just
there's just no synchronization
um
it just doesn't work I it just gets
stuck all the time even if it's not that
Tangled but I can't untangle my hair
with a comb
foreign
[Music]
then what does go through your hair
anyway next we have
[Music]
uh
oh what's working on there I can't read
that but it's a little
handkerchief a little hand towel
uh no I can't read that but it's again
flowery
so far every
Earth
but it's like it's not like the the
super like Hawaii in your face cuteness
it's more like um
subtle
and calm
sweet sweetness
yeah all right I like it
then we have a Kate paint
wallet and I already told you what I
think about girls who have Kate Spade
stuff
[Music]
top-notch lady that we have right here a
top-notch lady this must be
yeah yeah
yes yes yes yes yes which makes me think
why don't I have
anything from Kate Spade just in order
maybe if I would get something from Kate
Spade I could get closer to the kind of
woman I want to be or the one that I
Aspire huh I should I should get
something from Kate Spade how much how
much are Kate's paint wallets huh
not as much as Louis Vuitton I would
assume right maybe I'm wrong
um
[Music]
isn't even that expensive really hmm
interesting
[Music]
300 500 range oh that's fine that's
totally fun
foreign
[Music]
Kate Spade New York
Kate Spade's kind of doxing herself
I have to censored in New York oh my God
please guys I don't want to be in charge
of the doctor I I didn't I didn't dogs
can't Spade okay just for the record
okay she docks herself on here whoever
wrote her location on the purse wait
this means that this person
stole the wallet from Kate Spade in New
York
how dare you we have to bring it back to
Kate
it's Kate Spade is she a beatable
maybe they're friends this this Holo
member and this
Kate Spade maybe they're friends
anyway anyway
can we unblue the bottle yeah
I'm doing it all right oh
oh
perfume
and this might be the only thing that
really
um seems to be a Japanese thing because
it says Shiro
freesia missed is that for clothes
because I don't Mist isn't for the body
white it's more like for Fabrics maybe
no actually no I guess not
the people are
anything for rooms but also for you
about is it for your body
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
you think she would buy it because it's
in her name
is that your reasoning
well well
uh that's all the items we have here but
they're really sweet and the girl a
little girl yeah
a regular perfume oh okay
[Music]
I know
Trump
last bag belongs to
the one and only
please hold your horses because for some
reason their reactions to her are always
like huge
[Music]
Empire
you did not see that one coming I do
think this one's also like you know
nothing too personal here so could be
could be many people
you lost me
Angel bag yeah
[Music]
I do think
this looks like you know the things of a
beautiful gorgeous
woman so it makes sense don't you think
don't you think
that beautiful beautiful
I think it suits it matches it fits
perfectly
but like what did she do to Kate Spain
oh yes you must have done it together
with who is the other Kate Spade owner
Muna
I think Muna right
foreign
[Music]
oh team purple
girls love Kate Spade hey but orange
girl also loves Kate Spade
me too
me too it's not not just because they're
purple orange also like orange
ah
oh sure all right so that was actually
plenty of bags we have done enough for
two hours yeah
thank you everybody for submitting this
time you know
[Music]
thank you also the verbs on my head
thank you for inspecting together with
me for helping me out you know
looking through everything closely so
that we don't miss any details it's very
important yeah yeah yeah yeah there were
some liquids in the bags I unfortunately
have to confiscate all of them and throw
them away
no just kidding done just kidding it's
okay
the other day at the airport I was
actually allowed to keep my full bottle
of water
I don't know if it's because I asked
nicely but they they um and because I
was the first one
uh in like their day shift because it
was like 4
00 am or so and there was no one else
there it was I was the first one want to
walk up to them
it was after like my my first flight I
was like switching yeah and I was like
can I keep those bottles because it's so
full and they're like yeah I'll just put
it separately in a different tray and
there you go sometimes you just have to
ask even though all the signs leading up
to the check
um said remove your liquids
but the bad the the the the the the
bottle was also closed like it was never
opened before it was really fresh yeah
but sometimes sometimes you get a pass
yeah
um no they seemed really fine with it
they didn't even think about it but
maybe it's partially because there was
like no one else there like in terms of
like Travelers you know I was not so
busy yet so they don't
care so much or hmm
it was nice
water
[Music]
the one and only gorgeous Flawless
beautiful
goddess angel
guy she washed up
[Music]
yeah so I will
um go do like a quick dance practice now
before I go to sleep in my room because
I have a long day tomorrow
um
and then I will go to sleep maybe one
more quick snack because I bought some
snacks from the convenience store
beforehand thinking that I would
probably get hungry
um
thank you thank you thank you too so I
think tomorrow I don't have a stream
planned right I was so smart because I
knew I would be
busy the whole day and I shouldn't plan
anything in the evenings I think it's
kind of like my day off in terms of
streaming but not at all in terms of
working because much much work to do
tomorrow
[Music]
thank you for the stream thank you for
coming I'm glad I could do this because
actually I had a lot of bags uh lined up
already for a while now for weeks and uh
yeah now they're finally exposed
you're welcome I'll probably maybe one
more episode at some point there's still
a couple members but you know I don't
want to force anyone and and I
understand like some members maybe don't
want to participate at all which is okay
too but um maybe I can squeeze out just
or for one more stream Maybe
um
I'll see what I can do yeah
um time to get the Yago back
yes I get really desperate but I feel
like the Yahoo bag would be so obvious
in an instant it's just too easy
but who know I mean I mean looking at
kobo's back today
never mind and actually actually you
guys might even consider it could be
someone else but yeah go yeah
janma is also open to
um showing me her bag apparently for
next time maybe we'll see we'll see
[Music]
maybe I should just like when jungle
takes the picture I'll tell him to just
like
Mia put some kind of girly looking items
in there to throw us off the scent so
now we don't know immediately
so the snare yeah
[Music]
of random lipstick yeah
yeah
[Music]
or like a perfume a nice perfume
okay so thank you guys for watching and
in Germany Michelle videos and I am
gonna go now another long day over uh my
eyes keep on like opening and closing
separately to say
weird
thank you for watching what's up what's
up I'm gonna rest my throat now because
it's why must be the air it
didn't talk that much today
foreign
I don't know if you hear that but I
sound like this
[Music]
foreign