[Music]
e
n
[Music]
h k k
my game capture card is not
[Music]
working
why why you're not working come on maybe
now maybe now
oh what does that light
mean
[Music]
kitty Hello mhi mhi G capture Cart
please give me a sign
give me a sign of
Life why is it not
working Elgato
[Music]
hd60 white light blinking if elato blah
blah blah blah blah blah when live
com live commentary starts six white
lights will briefly flash three times it
did just do that and then it goes to
doing nothing n oh
wait come on come
on
no it worked two days
ago it just worked two days ago I
already like disconnected and
reconnected the capture
card
igh OBS property no no no it's not just
OBS where it doesn't show up so so the
the I mean normally I think normally the
hd60 I think it normally has a light on
when it's working and now it doesn't but
when I reconnect the white cable it
flashes
white couple
times uh
wait no it that's HDMI
[Music]
out I mean the switch is
working it's not a switch problem
[Music]
came here to distract me didn't you
H
El oh that's too
funny um those y see oh god I've had
this capture call for a long time and it
works
but sometimes I guess it has problems of
stability do you hear uh chunky wonky
purring ah just listen to the
purs slight slight purse of
Elgato not
hd60 yeah yeah ah don't I've tried
everything that I normally do I feel
like maybe if I restart my PC it might
work you want to although why would that
work you know like like Lo logically
thinking why would that
work all right I'll try I think I've
done this before and the stream was fine
before when I did that
H oh my neck hurts oh god
um uh no stting all righty all righty p
oh am I back do you guys see
me okay okay we're back nice good job on
holding up stream and
chat let's let's try capture car oh I
have a bad feeling just being a [\h__\h]
today how about now let's
go it's
working okay now you have to move from
my chair
chunkers this is my chair I have to
stream now I I'm should I sit on you I
will attempt to sit on
you oh oh you don't mind okay now she
goes ah stupid
elado let us get comfortable controller
here
[Music]
and how's my how's my hair looking today
I got it on today let's see how long
until it snatches off because I have to
switch app again or
so
oh looks good toothpaste hair shut
[Music]
up we do it like this and then I guess
I'm ready hi guys Kitty
branded conditioner oh I use
um I don't know
if what's it called again I don't know
if people have it in like outside of
Europe
uh what's it called
again ah guhl is what I use I think it's
a good good
brand G u h l for shampoo and um
conditioner but doesn't really matter
like I use I always change it yeah g h
l i always change it
but it's one of right now I'm using the
one Tim
[Music]
Tim what I liked in Japan but also kind
of disliked I the same time is that
shampoo and conditioner normally they
sell it only in like really big
containers while here in Austria they
only sell them in really small
containers and you use them up really
fast now and then in Japan you buy the
big container once and then you buy the
refill um and they're all fancy and then
the designs are good and all that I like
it so on long term it's good but if you
need shampoo and you're only go there
for a while for a short time
then yeah it's hard to find the the the
small ones it's only only big
ones but it can also be very useful you
know refill yeah
yeah see good at some places really oh
they must be
international well fancy
[Music]
there a refill yeah do you guys not do
that the thing with the refill see we
don't do that either but that's that's
one thing I find is smart cuz then you
know the the main container it has like
a fancy cool container but then the
refill is just a plastic um bag
basically
so you get the refill cheaper and if you
don't care about the container I guess
you could just buy the plastic bag from
the
[Laughter]
getco smart and environmentally
friendly guess that that might be so
yeah more than other things where
they're not so environmentally friendly
like wrapping every piece of candy
inside of a plastic candy bag in a
another candy bag and um you know stuff
like
that when you got to win some you got to
lose
some I suppose oh [\h__\h] I forgot like a
proper um glass VV chato
I need to drink more water I think
recently I've been slacking on drinking
water I was gone for 2 seconds you're
like
Po guess you're not as bad as the
teammates
yet I'm I'mma goes away for one
second it's like an apocalypse
[Music]
okay let's do this l r press a when
oh we're still in the same place same
time dog is dying on the
floor they like object
permanence oh
[Laughter]
um
so we have a choice today
oopsie cuz last time do you hear the
audio guys don't follow me
stalker um last time I said next time we
do Tiki just because everybody told me
do ti do ti do TI
and I was told today on
Twitter that maybe I shouldn't do Tiki
today
because of reasons spoiler
reasons and then so we basically I can
either I I I collected opinions what I
can do is
either collect Tiki which will take 3
hours minimum so apparently it's very
difficult to get Ticky or long
long uh and then have an easier time
later
on or do not get
Ticky uh do more story progress
today have maybe more struggles later on
but at the same time
story-wise it will make more
sense
apparently um because Tiki comes from
the
DLC and and I mean I can't
imagine why it would make sense or why
it wouldn't make
sense move ahead we about take you later
well the thing is also though that
people have been telling me the later I
get Ticky the more it's difficult even
though at the same time people tell me
it's
scaling so it shouldn't be more
difficult but maybe it's not scaling
properly not as properly as it
should it's my choice well the problem
is I'm very
indecisive you have way better skills
later for
Tiki to to beat her you mean beat her
up oh
well I feel like I know what you're
going to say
[Music]
if my whole party is promoted that be
fine okay well see then again there's
people who say Tiki has more value the
early I get
her it seems if it's better off to sa
for for short F stream all for now
n you start getting that win earlier
ah will she still be of help to me if I
get her later on I I do want to get some
of that pay to win
experience cuz I'm suffering I'm
suffering yeah okay
M
okay I'll do her afterwards then then
we'll normally progress in the story
today which I generally I like that idea
anyway cuz if she really takes us three
hours then she'll take like half of the
stream
stream okay
[Music]
okay H how are we looking on the side of
like bonds and [\h__\h] now hold the warm up
time thanks for your opinions guys oops
want to eat chocolate good
morning morning s training hard again I
see though normally I don't find you
using a shovel that's a deep hole you've
dug too won't this be hazardous for the
others oh sine this isn't training and
if anything I need to dig
deeper the bottom of the iceberg what in
the world is the purpose of this I
overheard the kitchen staff this morning
complaining that there wasn't enough
water so I'm digging a well for them par
uh Alfred if the water supply is low
there's a river nearby we can fetch more
from what possessed you to decide that
the solution to the problem was to dig a
well hey you're right that's using your
Noggin I better find a jug and like it
to the river thanks for the tips
sine you haven't changed one bit it
seems better that you should dress in
pelts and Furs to warn people of your
barbaric mindset
okay I need to warm up to
this RPG
conversations okay besides that we're
done can I go straight to story yes I
can yes I
can weapon upgrades I just want to go
straight to story
snow
[Music]
mountains upgrading weapons what do you
mean there's no upgrading you mean
buying new
[Music]
weapons as far as I know there's no
upgrading
weapons see what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
I did oh I did I did do that
before it's in the
thumbnail how do I get to the
[Laughter]
thumbnail okay
now it's chapter
10 speeding
[Music]
through I wonder how far we get
today people told me to do chicky after
chapter
11 so maybe we we will get to her
today
[Music]
maybe upgrade to
cool was it you
sir no probably not why
you well hey
there oh immediately after it's also bad
take
[Laughter]
care not
hold um yeah smoothie smoothie woke me
up today at 7:30 that little [\h__\h] and
then I was like sasani no no no no then
it took me a while to fall asleep again
cuz she was like meow meow meow meow
meow but eventually she finally shut up
um and then at something like 8:30 she
woke me up again like meow and then I
get up and I'm like [\h__\h] sake to give
her the food but turns out uh I had no
more wet food so I'm like I'm sorry I'm
sorry Smoothie Please do not assassinate
me in my sleep I I you have to
wait so I go back to sleep um but I have
to wake up somewhat early a little bit
later anyway because I was going to take
her to the vet again H not her chunkers
but you know still have to get up so I
was going to I was going to buy the wet
food
[Music]
then which one should I upgrade guys
maybe oh iron great l or killer l or
Rider's
Bane yeah and then she let me sleep
thankfully after a while I did get some
more sleep after that and then I woke up
and I took chalkers oh one of those
maybe I took chalkers and she was so
good today but Liberation again iron
dagger yeah we use the iron dagger a lot
where's the iron dagger where it go
she's so good today she did not meow a
single time not in the transport not at
the vet she was such a good baby today
where's the iron
dagger ah I think I saw
it but okay it's already plus two
oh I still upgraded again what about the
others that I'm not upgraded
yeah this time I Uber there from the
beginning cuz I thought I didn't have
much
time all engraving on the iron dagger
for un what's holy
engraving what's
that do
you oh oh what's this
stuff what does it do 100 bone fragment
oh that's that's not
expensive and it it
proves
uh WT goes down what's
that a void goes up by 20
though pretty
good wait aha it's good that it goes
down okay
[Music]
M any other
recommendations um on you build it
reduces your speed when you use
Liberation plus
five I can't do that I'm
lacking uh what are those things again I
can do plus three for
[Music]
now what was that silver o need more
silver killow for crit all hopefully it
doesn't need
silver wa I don't have a
killable I don't have a
killable
[Music]
n Maybe iron great
Axe use all the engraves for
[Music]
now I'll do the killer
L plus
one I'll do you know what I'll do
whatever I'll do whatever I'll do the
iron CR and EXP
one and I'll regret all of this later on
maybe anything that sounds
cool
oh finding dagg is extremely worth it
Hammers and pole
axes
okay although I don't use this is on bu
right now right I don't use him at the
moment
H
Thunder why Thunder not
fire tell me that I'll do fire
too give it to Jade
yeah th has more
oh does it now have even bigger
range already had big range
beforehand what about oopsy oh we should
[Music]
exchange uh I could exchange some iron
for silver but damn the exchange
rate let's say thank you
what that's it feels expensive just get
dogs oh do they get the
silver iron is probably more valuable
this early uh-huh uh-huh
uhhuh okay well I'm going to put some
more dogs in the farm then okay okay
that's um something I appreciate the
information
when did I put
an holy engraving on The Liberation I
don't even remember
that maybe we can put one
[Music]
on
on the
book Hill
L
okay which one
that's not true
evanel focus on crit okay crit goes up
to 40
here and also 240 on this one so Mar or
our
wifeu yeah I appreciate cor too that's
that's true cor sampai
s
oh weight goes up with that one and then
here H avoid there's more avoid here but
more Dodge
here this hard more right yep
more specific
life uh
um can I only have
uh each engravement for one weapon or do
they lend their services to
everybody also I feel like wasn't it
less expensive a moment
ago oh one to one oh
okay not
all
well oh that's a
Liberation okay then it will be this one
[Music]
uh should I does she use her iron l a
lot should we improve her iron
L we use her a
lot iron dagger to steal
dagger what iron dagger to steal
dagger how do I do
that you mean this
one gets weaker
though you mean buy
steal yeah the question mark one that
makes it
steal and good for that's okay that's
what I
thought I want to waste so much
time I'm just going to upgrade
everything
I don't know what's good to
[Music]
upgrade see now you say waste of
ore I don't know no okay uh no yeah you
you too you too Lou I use Lou to
[Music]
all the
javelins all the
javelins okay now I'll stop I'll stop
now stop now I put more doggos in
the
uh
Garden hello
K all right um
stall uh
stable stable and
stable oh I don't
have enough dogs huh what ises this Mar
do they like uninhabited area such as C
that doesn't tell me anything it doesn't
tell me what you do what does a Marmet
bring
me one kfp for
lore oh yeah let's bring in the chicken
oh my God so many
dogs and our beloved beautiful chicken
hello shouldn't be kison chicken it
should should be K kiaan chicken you're
my
chicken my chicken my chicken call Janai
you're my
chicken did you see Callie
oh h M did you see Calli is doing her
new outfit uh
reveal on Monday I
think yeah the reason why I just went oh
is because that kind of leads me to
[Music]
something
ah well so we're not doing like uh
everyone together is in the same time
frame um outfit reveal this time because
you know they're all getting done at
very different times Callis was the
first to be
ready
and well uh
kiaha kiaha might be a last one this
time
and I have I haven't even
seen
uh a sketch or
anything
um
um um but
um um one
thing no uh yes but no um remember a
while ago when I
said I think in I said in Spring
you guys will find out something that
makes me sad or
so remember you guys were always
wondering oh what could it be what could
it
be uh yeah so um the sad news is um my
outfit is not being done by by hooka
Papa okay maybe some people don't give a
[\h__\h] about that but for me it was
uh uh not good news that's for
sure
uh and oh oh also remember uh I
announced like
a I think I announced an anniversary
hairstyle on my
anniversary that one also not being made
by hook Papa but that one will come
sooner than
later but also not very soon I mean
considering how long it took um um so
that's just you
know many things that are not you know
are just being made by other people and
I mean I mean I mean uh for the for the
outfit uh I did get to like
choose who will make it but and that's
great the person I chose I think we can
make something cool together
but
still it's it's just weird to it feels
weird to me
to
um have someone else do it you
know I was I was very frustrated by that
for a while um and kind of
disappointment by the
development it's not like hukap Papa
want do uh an outfit for me anymore at
all I hope that the next one
afterwards hook Papa can be in charge
again um but the upcoming one will be
someone else and because of all that
like back and forth like you know a lot
of time was being taken up and that's
why mine
is really slowly going forward oh
so that's my that's supposed to be my
2022 uh new outfit remember cuz we
didn't get a new one except for the dle
which was different cuz the the 1
million subscribers
outfit
[Music]
um H I don't think we'll like
necessarily imitate hookah's art style
but uh well the face stays the same and
then the the hair and so on will be
obviously redrawn because new hairy Etc
but the thing is I think like even with
hook Papa he drew my hair for example in
different like shading Styles and so
before um so I don't think it will look
too weird I think I don't think it will
look too weird um I think it will blend
in it will blend in I'm sure of
it yeah what well so that's that that's
uh
something in the end I don't really
think it affects you guys it only really
affects
me and then well
2022 uh out with reveal starts of CI I
don't know who's next I don't know when
they're revealing the others but mine
will be late late late late
late but I did ask to sort everything
out with hookup
for the next one as early as
possible so that we don't have
to ask someone else again ideally I mean
I I I also do kind of like the idea of
like going with different artists so
that they um so that I can have
different experiences different
varieties and like
outfits in theory that's cool and that's
the the bright side that I'm seeing of
it that um I get a chance at Yeah a
different vibe that wouldn't be possible
for hook
[Music]
Papa what was I going to
say I forgot what I was going to say I
guess that's just that's that that's
cool but on the other side you know and
I feel like you know I was born by hooka
Papa and normally and whole alive your
own artist continues to do your
art normally so just feels weird
but okay yeah yeah yeah shut up I'm
going to play the game
now KF for kfp that was an important
notice okay so don't
complain don't forget to give ALR a long
bow do we do I have one in my
inventory look he he looks so sad
because he doesn't have a longbow it's
like when is this [\h__\h] going to give me
a long
bow
uh
[Music]
when ah you can have
hers take
this yeah
[Music]
Jade doesn't have a ring cuz she's new
M wait did I have to go no don't have to
go to the thumnail a ring for
Jade what's a good ring for
you definitely so one was this death
death and
luck death and luck
stop a ring on the fer yeah before
someone else does
it sigard is okay I'm not going to give
a
sigard
what you mean one of his
like these ones or his actual ring
J would make her real fast well but it
belongs to
Alfred thank you Lena R thank you SEL
crew thank
you um I you know I I I can't say
anything about it now who knows maybe I
will like it so much that it won't be a
sad thing but I I just in in theory I
think the whole fact that this is
happening to me is kind of sad but uh
disappointing but but it could turn out
to be a really cool
outfit I'll just give her whatever luck
magic no that's that's not
[Music]
happening wait that's
Ticky I just realized that's Ticky
[Music]
not ah I'll I'll give you I'll give you
what this strength and
[Music]
HP yeah I gave them a lot of input like
I want this and this and this and that
and this and
[Music]
that I trust that your eye for artist
will make this better than you
think thank you I think uh I think I did
ask like a lot
of I did ask for like I I did give a lot
of different
um ideas on who desia cathedal is our
enemy's home base I suggest we stock up
on supplies I just
did eh there's a series of battles
before you can
n what's the thing I can only do
insomnia take Ms with my so
hard two chapters in succession
eh healing items I can buy those things
in the marketplace Norm
too inherit skills is something I can
only do there should I should I do
[Music]
that second CH
short okay let's do some skill
inheriting and then we'll go go go go go
did you eat for stles no I didn't I
guess I
didn't okay forgot about the
eating it's important to eat I just had
my second burrito before the
stream L now you're
here um all right new one in town Jade
and citen how about you guys and we'll
eat
caramel nutcake is good or again the
crap
pizza oh this one could work
[Music]
too
oh no no I ate one last night and then I
ate one for lunch today cuz I made two
it was enough for two oh you know what
I'll go with for this one it doesn't
matter doesn't matter extra ingredients
here take this take this and this and
this okay was no it was
like so nervous
Torito I didn't waste a single scrap of
food on this one it looks good well
loose a sigh of
satisfaction oh my I would employ this
Chef for a
lifetime yeah it's like a sausage M wow
wow wow if
female they gain
more resistance
okay I made you a too meal hope you like
it thank
you yay leftovers oh wait I still have
leftovers from like previously don't
I that's a good meal though
[Music]
y if I may we must put a halt to the F
dragon's vile ritual and make ready DES
in the cathedral white
tunnel and
then uh ring Jem well do I inherit
skills in the ring
chamber they dispose of it when I eat
again
[Music]
ma thanks for the membership
R do you eat those
lunches uh on the
battlefields or where can you eat
them uh inherit
skills how's this work
again oh oh you guys told me to save up
for those yeah again but
[Music]
likeing item not
a okay let's say yaka for example oh she
can't afford [\h__\h] how is that
possible oh you can with
Mikaya cuz she had Mikaya most of the
time but now she has Leaf I guess
had the bond to right now okay she'll
have to wait then Chloe and Mar they
should have something else should I just
get them all you guys said before to
save up I can only get one though maybe
avoid plus
[Music]
10 I can join it with the emblem true
sounds good okay inheriting
but for example if I um with uh yaka get
one of these do they even still apply
when she's not using
MAA h no this effect will not stack if
equi was Sy no okay
don't she still gets them
okay but they I don't know she's not
using a staff now
maybe resistance would be the only one
that
[Music]
will can equip two
skills who whoa whoa whoa how do I equip
them have two slots to apply them with
two so after this you need to equip
okay
okay just save SP for caner what's
[Music]
caner I don't
understand you don't have a good
relationship yet you also
don't Alfred must have good relationship
there we
go what's headl long Rush immunity to
freeze oh ooh maybe now in the winter
area that will be a
thing it's an attack uh-huh oh I can get
cancer unit can move two spaces after
acting
oh all
right inherited that's all our money
gone
Seline the most expensive one is Magic
plus two stands if a corrupted attacks
unit deals 10% of damage taken back to a
fo
10% grants hit avoid plus s using a
tomb should I get to pression
free most of those aren't good PR pris
is good okay I'm going to get this this
good one
oh that means I inherit the other ones
too anyone
else may want to play the feas
games I don't
know I don't
know so you guys told me I have to do I
have to like put them in the slots or so
afterwards how how how how
H
inventory why is that in the inventory
it's a
skill
F
uh menus are so confusing I mean that
that just makes no sense
[Music]
so which one we gave Alfred something
manage skills there we go
inherited can only do two at a
time uhuh and then we gave Seline
[Music]
something and that's I think it let me
check did we ever in equip her oh we
never gave her one
what
uh I don't think I bought anything else
can
I chlo oh we have chlo
avoid
okay so we ate we did the
skills think we're ready to
rumble give cigarette to Lou of can in
here that you can give secet to someone
else but but what if I want to use his
special
attack you just want everyone else to to
learn caner
they become
[Music]
faster canther is the greatest skill in
all the
land Diamond Dam Diamond that do you you
you Diamond but he's bonding with Roy
right now he's kind of busy right now
okay I'll
give uh yours to m
someone said
Louie Lou or
Jade you know what I'll give it to
Jade
oops for now and
then sirard we go together and then
afterwards Lou can have it too you know
we share I don't have an unlimited
amount
of rings I have to have to
save and be be mindful and and think
about who gets what we have to share
okay sharing is caring you just get this
one
now mhm it's like you know like kids in
in kindergarten I don't have endless
amounts of toys we have to share you
know this same toy I don't have five
copies of the same
toy here's there's some uh golden
conversations over there is that the
bonding
stuff hi oh welcome thank you thank you
for allowing me to set foot in such a
sacred place I'll try to be on my best
behavior
support Jade are you okay oh Divine one
I heard you were attacked by Bandit I
rushed here to check on you thank you
but I'm fine I drove them all away why
did they attack you like that I've run
into that group before I used to be the
guard for the mine near my hometown I
stopped them from looting it once they
must have tracked me down for
Revenge now after all this time I was
pretty Infamous among the bandits in our
area they used to call the IR wall looks
like I'm the target of a few deep long
she's doing an idle performance it's
fine I can handle anything they throw at
me they're not much of a threat I know
you're strong Jade but I'm still
worried if you ever need backup you can
always count on me you must imagine she
has like 30
40 kilogram of armor on her thank you I
don't find that arm movement
realistic don't think she would choose
to do
that armor is not heavy oh oh [\h__\h] yes
it's
heavy oh it was very much
heavy wait where was a reference makes
no
sense oh that's it oh no that's not
it doesn't have little arms like me
excuse me Divine one I wanted to thank
you for aiding me in battle the other
day you're welcome in appropriate I
would like to find a gift for you to
fully express my gratitude
gift that isn't necessary citrine I only
did what anyone would it is
necessary Divine one you're too modest
give me your gratitude a gift idea has
just come to me an acquaintance of the
Broan royal family is looking to sell
their private island at Cost what would
you say to your own private Island
Getaway my treat of course an entire
Island WA that sounds amazing actually
really not not enough I agree shall I
add some of my antique jewelry
it's just a few Generations old sure CIT
I don't need expensive gifts really then
we already have the thil GI would you be
more ined there's so many people here by
now if I can't talk you out of it to be
honest I would prefer the kind of gift
that money can't buy something say that
canot buy no private islands no jewelry
I value gifts that aren't defined by how
much they
cost person receive as if you don't want
a Tesla I see let me just think on this
for a while in a yacht farewell for now
Divine One and the Gucci
belt I don't buy
it yeah clearly she doesn't own an
F okay let's go
before I
die well
map so I know but in between I can't go
to the thumnail but in between can I go
shopping I think I have enough in vulner
and all that
though wa let's go I'm scared
new iron
set new iron
set i
r i of
what said I'm not worried okay
good luck on this one yeah thank
you I don't need luck I have you guys by
my
[Laughter]
side the first difficulty spikes no no
no there were difficulty spikes
before iron armor sucks you can't iron
iron armor a the snow's really coming
down out there yeah the cathedral always
gets hit harder than anywhere else huh
and Ivy's late
we've been waiting here for ages what if
she never comes maybe things went bad at
brodia Castle and she didn't survive I
come here as a messenger iy can handle
herself thanks Rosado you're
sweet why is this happening anyway ever
since Lord Som Bron was released
father's been acting weird he used to be
so kind to me but since they came into
the picture it's like I hardly exist you
mean the ones who showed up up at alusia
Castle with Lord soman yeah that kid
with the hood and the four weirdos who
follow her around father probably only
likes them because they brought him so
many
rings I thought if I could get him some
he might praise me like he used to a
look how that turned out I'm sorry
ortensia it's not your fault what
happened at the Grand Crossing that was
all me I just I don't have any clue what
father's up to I don't know why he wants
the Rings or what this ritual is about
I'm totally in the
dark
Hortensia pardon me for interrupting hey
gold Mar King hin has asked you to join
him at the
altar and he wants you to have this
that's a cool ring an emblem
ring whoa the king gave you another one
huh he said you should wear it and
prepare yourself for
battle that must mean the Divine Dragon
com has calm whispery voice like I'll
get some answers about what happened at
Mommy hairsty let's go you
two
now we've arrived theia Cathedral
directions really did
help let's head inside
quickly hold on a moment what is it
Marth I sense the Fel dragon's presence
he's waiting for us inside emblem
anymore you can't tell me what to do we
not ready to fight him if the ritual has
been completed we should Retreat and
even if it hasn't I think we had best
escape at the first sign of danger I
don't think we will leave King Moran
behind I'm worried about all this we
shouldn't stay any longer than we have
to whatever we do we must avoid a direct
encounter with the Fel Dragon it'll be
all right Princess Ivy said that Som
Bron can hardly move remember plus we
have half of the emblem Rings even if
they had the rest we'd be evenly matched
it is true that with the Allies we've
gained we are formidable but I urge you
as our leader do not fall prey to
overconfidence perhaps I am being too
bold is that what's going to happen
still despite everything we're facing
I'm
calm I think it's because you're here
Mark with you and the other emblem
supporting us we're all feeling more
courageous I hope you'll always stay
with us we are not going anywhere we
will remain by your side until the end
of this journey thank you are
you now is everyone ready it's time to
put a stop to this ritual and bring King
Moran home
okay I'm
[Music]
scared
oh ride into the
Trap PO is it I B you welcome toia
Cathedral we're so happy to greet you
loathsome Divine Dragon spare us your
lies alas your presence indicates that
Ivy lost her
battle a predictable outcome of course
wow okay a shame you don't appear to
have taken her captive thank you I assum
her body has been left for the
birds you mean my sister is dead no not
dead I'm sorry you hidden King
Moran all will be known in due time tell
us now look over there there's someone
beside the altar can it be tant's father
he's alive
you good don't worry father we're here
to save he's not even looking at us what
oh no they turned him evil something's
wrong what the light is off oh the
lights not
off father he's
been it appears you were a few moments
no we have to fight it
as you can see the ritual has been
carried out
hent you
bastard we have to leave at once call a
retreat without delay we can't King
Moran is beyond our Aid what do you mean
you would have us leave our own father
behind I cannot I will not abandon him
here the only option is to fight hent I
won't flee after after what he has done
de oh
Chris foolish but I'm not a bit
surprised oh we're
stuck the doors yes we're trapped
within this Grand Cathedral will serve
as your grave thanks to your
impetuousness you brought the Rings unto
my very hand I since you stupid ass
you're a monster that's our father
you're going to pay for this here and
now so be it
Hy now we
[Music]
fight here we go first of all let me
see oh Treasure Chest oh right here oh
there's someone on like a bombing
machine oh damn
e that's so mean
no
what then we have Rosado right over here
U no one special
here gold Mar
here potencia and question question mark
question mark oh her
emblem red Roy or marf or whatever what
red Mar is what what
and
then corrupted ah Daddy
on and the other
Daddy okay but first there's like a door
here to get
through a first we eliminate the
children and then we eliminate all the
daddies I see I see I
seei there's some fly a lot of flying
mobs um
there but here not
[Music]
anymore well so what we'll do is we'll
bring our Archer on the left
side
[Music]
and you over
there and you there but besides that I
don't know about my
[Laughter]
lineup what do you think should I bring
someone else
[Music]
what if you user initiates combat
attacks twice is that what you wanted me
to see if there stairs in your map there
probably be
reinforcements
Oh Oh you mean like those kind of stairs
ah yeah that looks like they'll run out
of
there eventually
's a pillar to
survive o
yeah s this SN s this n you will need
healers in these
Maps
Okay
[Music]
I don't
know we have who's our healer right now
again Anna right Anna's no she's a mage
healer so her and then maybe a proper
healer
instead of maybe
lapis we bring for but I feel like
she'll die so
soon Chloe can heal
too yeah cuz she has the the
men you think that's enough Seline can
heal Seline can heal to yeah maybe maybe
we'll bring all three of them
then I I think that's a a
safe relatively
safe way to go then because they're all
three all three of them are strong
attackers
[Music]
too yeah okay uh wait where did she go
right behind kiaha Okay Who Um I want to
ask flying units are like like Chloe who
what is she strong against because I
know that archers are strong against
flying units but what what's what's a
flying unit strong
against Mages oh
Nar
okay
[Music]
fight wait a
second from all the units that we're
taking with us
now um are there are there any no okay
all the special rings are this um are
shared in my selected units
Okay Jade no why oh Jade got no
[Music]
items yeah that's
uh good to notice
now let's optimize her equipment okay
yeah now she got it
all diamond are we bringing Diamond
think we are maybe give him some stuff
too oh no that's all he gets he gets
lapis's meal
aw maybe he would appreciate a
vulner there we
go I give chlo a the killer
L
Chloe Chloe kill who has the kill alred
no yeah why
not uh L
search does she do
magic doesn't right
okay okay it's time we're 1 hour in and
now we're finally
starting eh why are we not lapis is
still with the great ax
what I'm not even bringing lapis I
think
so yeah okay
I'll get to your senses but I think
he'll die huh father it's me it's your
son too far the doors are closed he
doesn't hear you is there some way we
can change him
back there's nothing we can do the king
you knew is gone oh man
no we have to end
this what are you saying
brother you think father would want to
live like this as this Abomination
fighting for hin we have to let him die
as the proud noble man he was as the
king of brodia I don't know if I can do
this having to kill your own father we
will free King Moran's
soul and take down
hin should we let someone else do it or
do let we do we do
do we let them do the deed for the sake
of lore but I think it will hurt less if
we let someone else do
it uh Magic artillery you can use magic
artillery by placing a unit of Crypt
phome on it and selecting Fire magic
artillery is powerful and has a long
range and is ideal for attacking at a
distance like a Ballista uh Magic
artillery has a limited number of uses
plan
carefully the Bros the sons
you guys are
mean
understood I think Jade
can
um take whatever is coming at her
[Music]
there whatever you need I'll put her
here I could already go with chlo right
over there since they're going to attack
me anyway but ah then everyone else
wants to attack me too so I'll stay
here you got it Anna you go to this
side all right and you guys so we have
AR but how far I'll protect
you he could attack
already ah but only only the one uh down
there I didn't even see that dude are
there there's not one on the other side
right
yeah ooh
okay I can't even stand
there
Lance Axe and once
again now I have one person with an axe
but the person with the axe is on the
wrong side damn it I bait for for for
now well I ba Rosado for now
Rosado B him yeah
it I
guess what's our
[Music]
move yeah I'll do the first hit with
diamond
100% 15 Dam 15 damage
back that hurts
though he can solo left
side engaging so early I didn't even see
uh charging I no they're over there
three of
them it's not many
but this engage attack doesn't get
countered or
right but it does I think less damage
though
okay I will
win see there's already people saying
no oh and the fire oh you know what I
don't like that
anyways here we go already using
a reverse I don't like that
because I want to use make use of the
fire
elsewhere very
well
[Music]
magic all the heavy
armor
and we have a mage already there we
could send a second Mage here too but um
heavy armor
normal normal and normal M might as well
send my second major over there
too and then kiaha over
here and
then yeah oh so close to finishing him
off I maybe I can finish him with my
Archer though oh yeah yeah that's that's
going to work that's going to
work or or should I hit with archer
first
alist oh H the steel bow does some
damage ooh Archer first and then um
maybe I don't I can kill him without
getting damage back we'll see that was
my fault
I know didn't do the math but maybe oops
see no he has 8 HP and I do
six unless I crit with my 9% crit
[Music]
chance
or you have a traveling don't you
one it only does one then i' be left
with one God
damn HP on
him why are you guys so
sucky that's not even worth it but okay
here Javelin
hit one damage you want
at least he can move afterwards into
that pillar and
[Music]
then of course he doesn't but it we took
him down with the power of everyone we
involved everyone what great
teamwork okay they go
for Jade
and can't touch
things can't touch
[Music]
Jade okay you can touch her a little bit
it
seems no that's not fair
[Music]
yeah oh 51 hit chance they didn't have a
chance at
all to begin with oh oh oh here comes
Rosia
sad she's making herself sad by being on
the wrong side
Man O oof oof oof oof oof damage damage
damage
okay H I want
start on this side
so first of
all first of all
UD I will definitely heal Alfred for
sure how much do the stuff
here uh
uh I wonder maybe maybe I heal at the
end I don't know I'll I'll figure it
out now I could kill that
one with one hit or I can do teamwork on
Rosado probably more
important try attack
oh oh he's got a killer
axe steel bow steel bow
95%
okay I'm
here oh that was
chain shocking ooh HP X speed
death yeah yeah I'm focusing on Rosado
don't worry don't worry
I
guess if we want to do as little hits as
possible then I got to finish him off
with the
magic
[Music]
Thunder yeah that's
86% or I move her over here and I go for
fire that's
100%
yeah my turn chy te help yeah sorry
R sorry for roasting Your Dragon you
took me out just like Princess Ivy
huh no
no just just go away just fly to the
hospital whatever get
treated and then you can come back you
can fly up to insomnia and you can be
part of the team I welcome you with open
arms ooh one hit really oh because axe
and breaking him
in easy peasy lemon
[Music]
squeezy
it's
fight oh speaking of doctor so I have to
bring chers to the vet one more time vet
gave me uh some more
antibiotics
um but
then o I don't want to stay in the
pillar but maybe he
goes can she can't heal him if he stands
here if I want to put her in the pillar
[Music]
right oh she's okay she's doing really
well she's doing fine sine can
kill but sing can also heal
risky risky I guess okay I'll give I'll
give him a a vulnerary
[Music]
then yeah chers is being a good
kitty oh and yesterday
yesterday we uh built some more stuff
for the kid C and they were very happy
about it very
excited
so I think my cats are in cat
heaven now we are dealing with this
illusion Soldier so want to take
illusion Soldier down first M can we do
that yes not engage
fire happy kittness happy K that's
exactly how it works and also happy kfp
is also happy kiaha I'm pretty tough you
know one
shotting always feels great now the rest
H what's the best
way of doing all this oh I can onot this
dude for real but then everybody's got
their eyes on me maybe I can kill the
other one first and then stand in his
place and then maybe not be
targeted let's
see that that's that's a decent amount
of
[Music]
damage I guess with a javelin I can
break this dude too with
Chloe from
here then the question is what good can
yak do she can I mean I just wonder if
we can take out all of them in a smart
way how much damage do you do um maybe
Jade in combination you you do like half
the
damage in combination with
kisada well we might have to engage at
least one
[Music]
person cuz this one's the only one that
doesn't die easily
right so okay here here's my here's my
idea Javelin on
you oh I keep calling
her I I'm getting used to it it's coming
naturally now she replied to me by the
way on Twitter she said thank you
[Music]
now we put you
here I can definitely kill all of them
that's for sure let's say uh let's say
you take down this small
boy remember you're not is UN
true God damn
[Music]
it all right I'll engage though
because I can engage someone lend me
your
strength and then I guess H we're doing
a houses unit that ends up with
one no want about normal attack
leaving them with
10 HP but also getting a lot of damage
back maybe not worth
it what yeah let's H with Jade
[Music]
first steel
ax also getting a lot of damage and 59%
s that's really
low
[Music]
ah better go with a weak attack that has
higher chances like
84 84 is the the highest the compact Axe
can I not throw that what if I throw the
compact axe wasn't that the one you can
throw
uh I don't I don't want to stand here
cuz then I'm just asking for them to
hurt
me oh that's the hand
[Music]
X whatever
I must insist now please die oh she's so
polite again I'll strike you
[Music]
down she has The High Ground is that a
thing standing on
stairs gives her The High Ground what
what what what what
64 84 ah don't miss don't
miss e okay for God oh it's just a
meme I mustn't add to anything thing I
think standing on the stairs should be a
debuff because it's difficult to balance
and there's not much space to move
around should be a
debuff energy drop what's that again ah
ah expense to Grand strength plus two we
haven't used our previous energy
drops
okay
um I'll go
here is anyone in the range of the bomb
no and they're even leaving oh okay okay
okay
ha okay next step is going up here
that's pretty far for them but the
enemies on this side are
closer
okay can already reach the
thief at least with one of
them but when I reach a fa everyone else
will reach me
too better to bait them
first and I didn't even use
it good for me I'm fine with that
what happened to D is that another
meme that must be another
[Music]
meme once I go
there I mean
free
free of them targeting Me Maybe maybe
kind of worth it because if I manage to
oh yeah I can get a Kill from I can I
can kill the
thief
probably yeah
can uh I would also love to attack the
Mage but then I have the axe guy on me
too all right all right we'll do it
we'll do it it it will cancel each other
out it will balance each other
One hand washes the other uh
oopsy uh what are we using a
javelin okay okay okay okay okay
okay yeah the
Archer ooh ooh right there's an Archer
over there that's dangerous for ch
wait which Archer are you talking about
never mind there's no Archer ah that
one ah that one's still far away no
worries uh okay then I
will do some of my
[Music]
magic wait
what okay okay okay okay no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no huh
[Music]
H I changed my
mind Thunder can keep me out of Counter
range
F
true that's enough but
[Music]
78% and that doesn't
disappoint okay
and I'm a fallen star cuz we
already I mean might as well use it cuz
we already used up the other
thing Master tactician well if you guys
ever you know plan on doing something
like this feel free to call
me and I can be your War Tac tactician
strategist I'm on your side
kfp I'm on your
[Laughter]
side yeah who knows who
knows anything could
[Music]
happen might want
to
protect
already uh
already baiting them anyway might as
well go that as far as we can um
now okay horsey flying horsey boy will
be the only
one greeting us there but he we can go
so far
[Music]
wow oh one step back on this side a [\h__\h]
I should use the [\h__\h] vulnerary okay
never mind I'll heal you
might as well get the EXP right he's the
only one that's really wounded on that
side
[Music]
anyway henia has freezed ah I knew
somewhere
somehow we're going to get
Frozen in
this uh area in this
continent oh was that
what did she just
do she kind of cursed me or
something
nice what was that J can't move well
it's okay they're coming to her for how
long one turn two
turns that's the first that we just
talked about
everyone's literally coming at her and
she's being the wall oh reinforcement on
one
side I did not see that one
coming I should have seen that one
coming um
Archer
guess easy
peasy yeah B for close
oh no
[Music]
worries he arrived and then did
nothing oh this one's also
simple seven
[Music]
damage that's all
right 60 CR oh w w w w w
w that's the good thing when you're so
small you're so
Dynamic Advantage uhuh oh
profession going to do some
magic
[Music]
100% fire kills incredible
absolutely
incredible all in a day's
work I should
know I know or do I know do I know
oh wait on the left side I didn't even
see they were they didn't
show that that Archer came from their
left side
right oh no problem no problem no
problem Oh I can go just far
enough to take down the
[Music]
horsey space
nice he did oh I have no choice but to
win I'm looking so much at chat I didn't
seei I can take down this
Archer might might want to take down the
left the right
Archer so
I'll either go in there or o so many
possibilities I think Diamond would need
less protection so I'm not going to put
him in the
pillar he can also K so far I'm not
struggling at all with this when am I
going to start to struggle
guys that's what I'm saying they're like
butter why am I so
strong next chapter okay
the good thing is he can't attack back
the The Archers so if I attack him with
diamond cuz I'm right in front of him
right so better to do it this way all
right here we
[Music]
go are you watching
father crit remember this
didn't even need the
crit okay and then I think I'll put her
there and she can oh no never mind I
need I need Seline on this
side can she doesn't she have a
sword oopsie she does and that one kills
[Music]
too ah magic she wouldn't even get hit
back by the mag if she uses her magic e
cuz she's right in front of him doesn't
matter doesn't
matter what's that one damage I would be
taking from him he doesn't like it it's
not on a arrow that goes to the left
side how's that
work Sil like a
skill takes one damage when you use
magic to do more damage all flowers
eventually will okay well as long as
it's just one HP it's not so bad steady
oh yeah I can move him over here too I
didn't even use him
yet I might use this
vulnerary
no
um hard behind there we
go oh wait there's still some stuff here
to do ah okay she can't
move oh wait I thought I already killed
everyone here
my problem
is I can't take him down with these two
can
I would override override the debuff I
wonder yeah I will not that's
okay Lo star R yeah let's see how much
that
does oh
oops and get
emem
engage wait that
works that works that works that works
forgive
[Music]
me that freaking works I took down
everyone after all hi thanks for the
[Music]
membership I won't forget
this oh you know what would be a cool
asset just U like a straight normal oh
hi Hortensia you took my sister from me
I'll never forgive you sorry I can be
your new sister are we not going to tell
her that the sister is alive oh
[\h__\h] please don't attack again oh oh
no I
could
defend I have to withdraw so I can no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no can I undo this
[Music]
somehow no no no no I don't think I can
do anything about it because she she has
the reach
and I can't move
her I can't protect her maybe she had
full HP I wonder
if okay I I'll try without and there's
not that I say there's not that much
left but they're still getting
reinforcements probably
[Music]
oh
luo I
can rewind I still have to enough
charges
but don't
know how
to fix that
oh
[Music]
cigarette it's casual yeah yeah yeah
yeah but what if I need her up there I
need my
units okay okay let's move on then like
suppose uh what was I saying before this
I saying
[Music]
something ah an yeah yeah so a straight
hand just like um like when you do rock
paper scissors paper just normal hand
open hand uh
facing uh the Palm facing my face
um but then with one of the engage rings
on my finger so I can just have the hand
just po poking up from the bottom of the
screen that would be a Cool Fire Emblem
engage
acid which ring H the the
um my uh free houses
ring or all of them both hands 10
Rings or or with every Fire Emblem
episode one more ring start with one
ring next episode Another ring and so on
eventually I will have them
all I think that um makes
sense that gives me like lore and and
story it's a story line character
development I'll be the lord of rings
I'll be the lordess of
rings blue says
okay what simple
enough second HP bar here we go all
right m
oops
see could to poison Gambit then the
damage I do to her afterwards will be
more
perhaps with
Liberation I don't know if that's a
stupid idea or Dragon yes you're the one
who kill my sister aren't you can we
tell her that would go then where is she
if she's alive prove it I don't know
where she is see I knew it you're lying
it would have been weird if we would
have for what you did continued to not
tell her even though she just confronted
us about
directly sasuka kiaha okay okay
poison aqu
chill
chill okay so
now o I might not be able to kill her no
we have to what's our move can't get far
enough maybe with engage
let's see quadruple headit yeah okay
that
[Music]
kills okay is that worth
it and know yaka didn't look like
it Yona has extra crit on
terrain it's a boss definitely wor it
hell yeah hell
yeah all right I'm going to do it o are
we seing this one for the first time on
her on unic I think
so
oh
sick why do I always lose well I won't
let you kill
me
ah she so cute I like the stars in her
hair so much
Mar I like yaka o magic up for Yuna wait
Yuna you don't use magic anymore do you
I'm so confused freeze I got a freee
stick it's a popsicle
basically now I can heal
someone I will
mend
K that helps
don't forget the loot oh the chest I
forgot about them thanks for telling me
I really just forget about them
W ooh ooh that's a really good one she
got magic
tool and
resistance
nice okay going for the
loot a
do I have to destroy the
door I do have to but should I open it
already if I open it do I come through
the door
[Music]
already I don't think
so not
yet take your time okay
[Music]
okay enemy face what will they do send
more reinforcements no thank God okay
that would have been a [\h__\h] Boozled cuz I
was ready to leave is it Go time it's go
time
chest or can we get someone else to open
it
[Music]
though wa kiaha was Kiwa was charging on
her own pretty well two is that doesn't
mean like in two rounds you can use her
engagement
again
no yeah okay well then I think um that's
enough time she doesn't need the
charging thingy they charge by fighting
oh it doesn't chargeing this on oh oh oh
oh a
oh uh how far can you go ah you can go
there and alha can go to the other one
okay number one Al
fire ooh
Nar that's a better fire
[Music]
right I guess
I I could start doing something
damage and she does not need
[Music]
charging who needs charging or Kaa needs
charging
[Music]
uh
and and
the others are still in their engagement
phase Chloe and un
yeah Draco Shield H what's
that okay then we'll have to
wait can I do anything useful I could I
could heal
thank you plus two death St item like
something for
K do you have to have it in your
inventory to take up a whole
slot
door you can just open the door cuz
she's a thief is that what it
is say the word
oh it's consumable
okay next
face okay she's charged uh you need to
charge you are going to charge
eventually o you come back up and we're
almost ready to go
[Music]
almost s s how do you like stop
everything again there end
[Music]
turn okay what she's charging
now and Anna also
needs I have to press wait oh okay
[Music]
you're not need the charge ah I got the
wrong
one well that's not worth a uh a
rewind
[Music]
um I'll
just it will just mean we'll have more
turns
[Music]
okay switch do a switch a rule and
maybe we can work on destroying that
door what you
think it's only five five HP left after
that and one more hit
Liber
us there we go beautiful oh with that
emblem at his side King hin will be able
to fire arrows from a great distance
proceed with
caution what does great distance
mean all right I already already move on
a little
bit ooh
is that the fire bro oh my God it is AST
[Music]
storm really [\h__\h] far it just feels
like
um let's it in English again I'm scared
of moving
forward shade could tag them
unfortunately no more
Jade bait them closer to you 40 damage
on Chloe oh hell
no oh my
God wait who out of my remaining units
could take it somewhat reasonably well
so we can walk up there and then walk
back
[Music]
Diamond gl's dead no she's not in
range she's not in range what are you
talking about she's not in
range is she in range
[Music]
how much damage on him
15 all right if it already reaches
here
then I could already go here and then
that dude we can bait him
[Music]
put can next to him for minus three
damage they Rush
anyway
oh that will work I think it will work
yeah can always heal him if it
hurts where is
kiaha ah Ki already
acted K already did something
damage
[Music]
25 this is so
mean so mean
40 how can I ever like go over there
everyone will
die
heal all right here they
go that's why I really need all those
healers huh
he can't do it every turn oh okay he can
only use it
once one once
right oh there he is
Daddy Daddy Daddy
do why must we do all this pain to
you he didn't use it yet
though man why not
what that actually pisses me
off God damn it should we move back
should we fall back
[Music]
be
aggressive move back of your
name all right I'll use a vulnerary
here ah
he's still in range for the arrow but at
least it wouldn't do that much damage to
him and then this this this is my
choice I
think I'm not
retreating not completely just moving a
few steps back it's a it's a
tactic
oh you chose the wrong
target what do we have
here you put up a good
fight mhm mhm oh [\h__\h]
ooh oh never mind not so bad
but thanks for the
membership ooh here come some extra
targets all right all right all right we
have gotten them pretty close
uh let's
heal should I he
now I [\h__\h] sh first first
[Music]
um what is
this for you
anything
ooh it she won't be in range here right
so she can throw an iron dagger at this
one
I'm
here another kill for me she
is
well oh no she's
not no no no no
no I mean in range of this fire
arrow now let's take care of this King
but but
uh you guys say attack him with the Suns
which pains me so much to
do um but they can't even take him down
together in one go so they will need
some
[Music]
support
kiaha kiaha can you help oh she only
takes 10 damage from the astr storm
got to hit the monk
first kiaha can reach the Monk and can
one hit him all right leave it to her
leave it to
her yes yeah
kiaha is resisting to the other evil
Daddy it's like she was born for this
she was made for
this okay now now now we have so any
choices still what to do about you
Mister um I'll I'll start with uh
alfri you know I would love to throw the
javelin from a distance but it's kind of
like everyone's squeezing in
here what if I bring you
here doesn't change like oh but he has a
throwing axe huh does he have a throwing
axe he he's got a Tomah Hawk but
61% oh if I break in first that would be
smart
but oh wait no no no no no no no no no
no no let me look
again that's okay I don't take
damage this is our last sparring match
isn't it
father when I was a boy you taught me
the meaning of strength you made sad you
were preparing me for when I'd have to
fight my own battles that day has come
and you prepared me well your life was
devoted to protecting bro's honor now I
take on that mantle oh
no was I a good
son I should have asked you that sooner
you instilled in me pride and
strength but most
importantly you gave me your love I
should have told you what that
meant but from what I can
tell they've they've had a good
relationship and
they oh no feel like
they wouldn't have too many
regrets except for his dad regretting
that he went
there thank
you now let our travel go
to level
up mhm mhm
[Music]
he's already broken right once I break
him for the whole
turn he won't be able to fight back
[Music]
yeah K has a unique dialogue
too n well he has a another HP bar right
so for one attack
well it seem it seems fine though he's
not attacking
back okay steel ball here we go
father if you have to die Let It Be by
my hand this would be an unbearable
burden for
Di so
I I
must thanks for the
input I must do this father if some part
of you is still in there
just thank you for everything I love
you I always
will My
Turn ouch I'll apologize later and
there's no later
alist there's no
later this is his grave do you know not
understand he doesn't understand he
doesn't get
[Music]
it
do don't want to put everyone in such
danger maybe I'll leave them on the back
for now
alista
cool I don't think that would like reach
anywhere from here in the
back okay okay okay
peel
peel well that's
interesting uh I don't think I can what
oh wait I can break him again wait maybe
I can take him down in this
turn there's a chance
with the wind it would kill him anyway
but
wait we can't risk that no no no it's
too much damage that would we would be
taking I I'll break
him I'll
help we might not get the unique
dialogue of Ki I'm
sorry it's
probably not a big deal come on
M I don't want to get that close with
the Mage to be honest but well oops
see okay yeah Ki barely knew him what
what important thing could she
[Music]
say it's all
right here we are
one more boss to
go strong of heart strong of body strong
of
heart I will carry those words with me
for the future thank you thank you thank
you okay go
next is he going to
shoot no no no
he
is feel about the new brodan king no
that's going to hurt is that going to
hurt is that going to hurt we had no
need of him but we corrupted him for you
am I not generous you can show your
gratitude by dying
20 for Lord
s% she's going to survive she's going to
survive oh that's a
cool skill attack
yes she
survived okay okay he heals it up so he
can't use it next turn so it's time to
rush can he use it in the turn after
though like how much time does it need
to charge for
him can't use it again only once oh
okay I have no chice okay
[Music]
okay
easy so far though generally I
really it doesn't even feel like I'm
playing hard casual but easy
casual easy Club
[Music]
you later thanks guys I'm overleveled no
how would I even be
overleveled
n how far do we want to
advance I want to I don't want to get
them all over here oopsy let's go uh not
hold
[Music]
see okay now it seems like I'm going to
bait them all anyways I think I'm okay
with
[Music]
this I could I could throw Javelin from
here but then I'm also baiting the
boss so early and he would be in
range when I'm not ready
[Music]
do you hate Alfred no I really
don't okay let let's let's take it step
by step all right the Mage over
there is it safe to put Seline here I
wonder
uh oh oh Anna forgot about you hurry
hurry Diamond needs a little break right
now his father just died let's give him
a moment of
Peace
ouch that's also ouch for
you okay goes for
Seline and not Seline diamond
oh okay fine too oh there he goes what
what is that how is this possible doing
like some kind of Naruto thing used the
emblem to create bubles
careful wait what is is if I kill the
middle one are the other one's going to
disappear or how's this
work is he trying to confuse me
at the moment I know which one's the
real one the game is also telling me so
it's not that
confusing what they have one HP oh my
God what a
waste now they're all here now I have to
deal with them
[Music]
the fire
aooe uh who had that again was
it no no no no got
it diamond
ah ah
do I use it here or one step back no
I'll use it
here it's the engage right mhm blazing
lion
[Music]
engage okay so I'll do it
here and then it hits them
all there's my opening
is he going to summon them again
hopefully not cuz that would be annoying
[Music]
attack better not
miss my
turn okay here we go I'll apologize
later okay
then we can take care of this one too I
just
wonder who does the most damage to the
to our friend over there he's he's an
Archer Archer Archer Archer
Archer I can't reach with Ki in that
case let me bring kiaha over here so she
can get closer
kiaha oh oh no no no what what
what what why brn who has that right
[Music]
now who has that ring right
now Seline
okay I had to stop you level
[Music]
Apple well that's a good level up to
anything looks like a good level up to
me as long as there's like more than
three
okay I want to
try
please okay I'll do
it oh but then she's in the fire oh but
the Fire doesn't do that much damage
[Music]
Dage that doesn't do that much
damage was
here
10 see I fire is nice and all
but oh the Mage is still there I didn't
see it
there fire is nice but but but
it kind of hinders me
too I'll help want turn and only one
turn and the copies will be gone and
then I can go full
[Music]
end she can at least stand on top of
these chairs
ooh can she fly over the fire or does
she get damage
to oh maybe don't get too
close she gets damage to no damage fers
ignore that
[Music]
I'll
wait maybe I should have
healed I cannot accept this I claim this
Victory she gets the XP from that right
oh that's
she no h
not worth my
time okay my last vulner on
Alfred
okay they will attack
me no cuz they die first oh
Yahoo very good very
good very good oh wait fire can't kill
why the heck did we do the
fire huh what's our
move
what survive yes
why did we do that
[Music]
then ah
ah ah so many
options well okay I will jabing the [\h__\h]
out of you this is what I train you out
of the
way move away make some space for
others oh yeah you can get a
hit you did because fire is cool all
right all right you follow a phoenix
after all I understand that
sentiment sense oh why the [\h__\h] do I
have seven
[Music]
manions no
n
n oh
hold no it's not direct mentions I'm not
that
popular can you heal from here no I want
to heal the other
[Music]
one okay now
I
heat I'm going to
doeg this anyway right are there going
to be more
did you see koba's tweet what did she
tweet don't hold this against me can go
all
out mhm
this item is not for
sale great
sacrifice I have no choice
how's tweeted that CI was cheating on
me
uhhuh I guess it has something to do
with that um Host Club
stream that's what it called turn on
investment
yeah okay who can do the kill Diamond
might let Diamond do
it what diamond is level
17 s 17 what 11 12 uh three but uh
[Music]
citen Citron can't
kill a Roy gives him five levels oh
[Music]
okay okay I just going to make it a
smooth
end the Lance rer
cannot accept this it's over you
bastard you have done too much evil no
more no
more cry like a baby I want you the I
want you the I want you to cry for me W
five now what we got the master
seal stage clear 14 turns but only
because I waited in so many turns
and someone said the next one is
difficult but someone also said the next
one is uh
[Music]
shorter
got we've won hin it's over get away is
that a flower do not come near
me what are you going to and now Mor I
avenge my
father stand back he's going to Mo
[Music]
that
spell it's you the one who killed my
mother W chrum girl oh thank you thank
you I thought I was finished there I'm
not being merciful merely pragmatic the
ritual was a success the fell Dragon
will be here in a moment it does sound
like could be means the sacrifice
worked here he
comes
don't you going do that's
me ooh oh I've seen this dude in the
Lord somon
trailer it seems my Powers have returned
because of you spooky eyes it was an
honor my Lord and and yet I still Hunger
for
More please my Lord devour these
fools alas I have a different meal in
mind n are you going to eat him and then
turn into him only Sovereign blood will
quell my Hunger oh okay you
understand yes I do I want your
blood I take it four
[Music]
blood wait was I
right this is the past
right so he turned into him
father was that now oh I thought I was
looking at the past cuz no one else was
around I thought he and the fell Dragon
were on the same
side now that was
entertaining
what did you see his face the sh they
were the only ones
there stop laughing what's wrong with
you po D you already Rec for me hurting
her is that fail you irritating
girl we going to fight him you had to go
and ruin my fun cute this is why I
detest
humans no it can't be but that's the
bandage I used to dress her
wound why can't it be of course it can
be introduce myself
I am Som Bron's
daughter princess wow only Veil pleased
to make your
acquaintance what do you mean the foul
princess How Could You deceive us like
this deceive you we've never even spoken
before what say that Shad fail take the
Rings don't say
that as you wish father
well well well if it isn't the Divine
dragon in their merry band this looks
like a vtuber generation it's you again
I know you you're the wret who storm
Fier
Castle wretch not much of a greeting
that but I guess the fault is mine for
not properly introducing myself
you have my apologies for my man's
actions in fear and a I take
responsibility for what he's done take
comfort in the fact I killed him myself
what as for who I am my name is zephia
zephia I am a mage Dragon of great power
and Lord Som Bron's humble servant in
all
things as for my companions here they
are like family to me he looks noral the
four hounds
tell yourself that she's a dragon and
the rest of us are humans family she
calls us the name's Gris and I'm not the
prisoner taking TI Why ni Marney I heard
we'd be meeting some royalty today but
you look like a bunch of losers to me I
am Maier the pressure is all oh my
father was his eyebrows
going that's a different type of mono
brow yourselves you're in our way stand
side come on we can fight our they not
of nowhere there's so much space here
Eng with
[Music]
emblems the
Rings something the
matter the draconic time Crystal of
course you had it with you all along I
know you're down there sorry but I just
had to take it back again no I grabbed
it during your little chat with zephia
amazing you didn't notice you must not
be very bright hold on you little [\h__\h]
yes now all your rings are here right
where they
belong give give them back of course
she's not going give them back I have to
admit I'm impressed six Fire Emblem
Rings
Rings six emblem
Rings well done now the Rings are in my
possession good now now to purge them of
any trace of divine Dragon power what do
you mean to begin the Ring of the hero K
what do you mean what are you want to do
Mar no no no emblem of
beginning
hey
hey Mar red mark for real
mar mar speak to me
please it's no use my father's spell
power is now coursing through the emblem
ring uh-oh he's no longer the sweet
little Mar you
knew please provide for us emblem of the
holy
war
no card card care for us emblem of EO
noal fools no you look hot in red though
all of
you stop it just stop fre us emblem of
genealogy rise emblem of
binding how he must announce everything
hey Roy I can't do this without
you say goodbye to your beloved emblems
now they belong to
us oh how I wanted these two
and S why after killing Lum why I was
forced to leave them back there with you
do you have any idea how irritating that
was for me sorry fail we must Retreat to
find
one oh so now you want to turn tail and
run we have all your rings and you have
nothing abandon hope you will all die
yay give them back give them back to me
are we going to fight the emblems the
evil emblems or her or or all of
them no
n we got friendship not anymore they
don't hate me
now do we have Jade back now by the
[Music]
way excuse me I mean
kada yeah we we probably have my um uh
free houses ring right
and that's why you guys said don't get
the other one because this Mak sense now
then you would have two rings at Le I
have one
ring you have nowhere to
run and no rings to protect you at last
okay I can unleash the full force of my
hatred I like when she's evil all your
allies will be killed by your beloved
friends the emblems
oh no they're here for real no those are
just normal
enemies oh they're part of they're
teaming up with
them no Divine one veale has the time
Crystal and the Rings we're not going to
win this one I don't have to tell you
how powerful the emblems are she's
immune we can at least survive this
thing uh uhhuh
if we make it over there we might be
able to shake off
Bale do we just
run where are we we're here and we're
and there Veil is here okay so it makes
no sense to go up there and fight them
unless we want all the
XP but basically if we walk down here
they're going want to attack us anyway
so we just go step by step attack step
by step attack step by step attack and
so
on until I reach this place and they're
also going to follow me I suppose these
ones up here or do they stay
there are they going to
stay if I take too long I'm going to get
overwhelmed they will follow me
oh man they don't chase at first
[Music]
okay thanks thanks for the sneeze
chat and now what do I do about my team
is Jade
back a she's back hi
good that you have
revived she's slow though
uh doesn't matter we all have to like
move as a group
anyway Dragon oh I should give them the
bone rings at least sword is
n all right which one do you
[Music]
want this magic one sounds good for
Chloe
oh ooh I have a DEX speed rest one want
that one I can
have you
not oh I keep on thinking of her as the
magic un
now um
what
else ah see now now I wish I had more
silver and golden
ones you can have the luck one I don't
know doesn't matter least better than
nothing uh what's this or
HP oh this one's lock
too get this
one m
uh you can have the magic one right you
were Mage as far as I
remember
uh
Diamond speed
luck speed
strength no I will not une equip the
free house this one no I'll keep that
one I lost access to any Engravings I
didn't use
forever
U boots are you for real are you
speaking the truth of me
[Music]
boots yeah I paid for that one yeah
engraved weapons are still engraved okay
uhhuh
uhuh uh I'm asking for spoilers well
that's kind of like a given that we'll
get them back eventually
so oh what's this one speed
unlock whatever take
this
Anna
uh something with magic would be
good
luck here Magic
and
Seline doesn't necessarily have to be
magic but I'll give you this one too and
then you can have
[Music]
um strength
okay did I forget
someone no oh actually I mean Lou has a
golden one for example could give that
to someone or bring Lou cuz we didn't
bring Lou last time how about we oh I
can't oh it's a serious ah I can't
switch
now okay at least then I don't have to
wreck my brain about
it
Lou you have a strength death HP one all
right let me give that one to
Diamond at
least thank you just borrowing it thank
[Music]
you can't rewind
time I can't rewind time in this one
[Music]
a oh this is hell when you're playing
classic this is what where it gets
hell
no okay let's go oh wait maybe swap
spaces the ones who can go
far can be in the
back okay
okay Victory K escapes defeat K is
defeated here we
go uh did I save in
between did they make me save I'll save
now oh I think I did
okay in maddening Classic this chapter
is a
nightmare ah
what is this puddle does I do avoid
minus 30 oh
okay okay I'll start by breaking this
bastard don't you dare stand in my way
don't you
dare sleep now it's a rainy
day it's a sad day for raining isn't it
oh one HP left wait did we crit because
I didn't see that one coming damn good
job here I
go yes I did
nice a kill for our good boy Al
Cris with the long
bow hey level up
mhh there's a ring now's our chance oh
we got the ring can we put it on I think
not I guess it's probably like not still
corrupted or so there you
[\h__\h] I so enjoy your
flailing I do too maybe I should um Can
can she be my protagonist I want to be
on her side I like Veil I wouldn't mind
coming to the dark side for
[Music]
her
okay I'm
ready go ahead everyone move
oh fers on the side
[Music]
and last but not least Alfred okay what
happens
next that's all you
got
weak what just happened she was going to
like talk to me but I didn't click
anything I did not click anything
what was
that okay
okay oh she just said D do do wow so
many
words no no she going to St behind
no go my corrupted soldiers kill their
every last Shred
oh oh [\h__\h] I don't want to leave her
behind I'm going to leave her at least
with like one
person God damn it the least thing we
could do is kill that bastard
here can I fix that somehow can I undo
that that too
much a warp stuff I don't think I have
it equipped on anyone
[\h__\h] that would have been great
huh oh well
okay
um let's
see kill the
Archer I'll do
[Music]
that oh
o no he does some decent damage to me
though maybe not let me think about B it
one more
[Music]
time W look at my HP what the [\h__\h] I
need to be healed I think that's what
we'll do
with the whole Seline and silica thing
confuses me so much I don't know
what's her name
anymore
okay he
[Music]
he's
mocktail it has Red Bull and orange
juice and kiwi and or
yummy what do you mean botan's mocktail
though like did she make it in stream
recently or what's
that same here also confusing huh not
just me
then I see has the emblem strength deck
res okay class skill
ignes
rip
what does he hit back if I do that
oh I get the plus
one oh I could also do steel axe 52
ooh ooh ooh wait
67% is kind of low and I can't
[Music]
rewind how about long bow you can't
attack backr no he has Thunder but
71% 20 +
1 I'm going to risk it total 71 is
really low I'm going to risk it I'm
going to risk it feeling lucky we'll see
c yeah I apologize
later it's my lucky
day hell
yeah
um
[Music]
magic I think together with the magic we
can take care of him does he have a
javelin I
wonder there's a master
Lance no wait wait Magic
first wait can he hit me too with
that one step
back one step
back okay yeah that looks good 100% hit
rate
Thunder the Mage what Mage what
Mage did I overlook another enemy magic
plus one let's
go enemies
enemies I don't see
[Music]
anymore okay and
then o I would take six damage first but
that's not too bad unless let me
see no
okay and then now I'll do it with the
[Music]
javelin part of the whole life X red Tok
your Tel Club remember oh well I mean
that doesn't mean that she can actually
do the thing herself
right H but I'm definitely planning on
doing though is that um ooh is that
collabo uh the potato chips one and as
you may have seen I'm bringing my sock
puppets over or like I'm sending them
before hand that's my plan maybe I guess
I'll bring a
webcam and then we can perhaps if
someone's up for it the sock pupp stream
with someone I have many choic
H I've got uh so many but um I'm not
only bringing them for that
purpose I think I'm allowed to say this
right because they already said there's
going to be like an
art uh thingy at the forfest
right some people some members are doing
stuff for that on
stream yeah I was thinking bringing the
sock puppets
for
display yeah I think it will be
interesting cuz I'm expecting probably
most things might be like like art
pieces uh like drawn something drawn not
everything though I saw like some
Japanese members
made uh like a Yago
head oh [\h__\h] I left her behind after
all oh on please survive ah 42% all
right all right all right we're good
we're good we're good yeah bye did you
see that Yago head that they
made I wonder um did they use that uh
what's it called as a child I used to
make things with something called
papm foror what it's called
[Music]
those were I memb who did oh paper mch
oh it's so close is that what they used
I wonder CU seeing that they made that
hat I was thinking of paper machine I
was thinking ooh maybe paper making
something out of paper mch would be an
idea for a
stream I'm so glad I got super Expo
tickets now yeah hey hey no concert
tickets but I think there will be things
to see any anyway plenty
plenty kfp Cafe too right but they
didn't call it kfp which um oh no they
in the end they called it whole life
fried Cafe which would be hfc if they
wanted to call it kfb I'm guessing they
didn't do that because it's already so
obviously
like feed after
me and that's already like plenty of
references to me I
assume so maybe that's
why they didn't want to pay me
franchising fees I should s
them
bootle yeah yeah yeah if they called
[Music]
it no why would they call it KFC that
makes no sense if anything it would have
been kfp but now it's hfc
but speed after me so that's sweet sweet
sweet
sweet ah not that much damage taken but
I I'll give you a little heal why
not a pick me up I'm so happy that
they're doing that you know
every like ID and we and some other like
themed
Japanese
uh booths are being made
so I'm quite happy about
that that kfp was being chosen I think I
did like um submit like an
idea like when we were asked oh what you
guys want to do I probably put in like
hey make use of your one and only food
themed
YouTuber last year last last year at the
Expo the Ian food was cookies
right just some cookies right I was like
guys you should have made use of
kfp I can cater to you guys
he's coming after her again that piece
of [\h__\h] and he misses again she's like
no no no
[Music]
no yeah yeah I do think that fried
chicken or chicken nuggets or so all of
that like generally fast food whatever
we sell at kfp fries too all of it would
be great food for an expo like finger
food mini burgers also could
work oh there's so many
choices I love I love that kind of
food at a convention I would totally get
myself some chicken nugget and french
fries with Mayon
May how far can you
go you can't reach see I'm trying to
catch up with her and it's working quite
well she can walk while also taking down
some enemies that is
ideal can't really reach the left side I
guess I'll have them come to
me I don't want to move my butt over
there
[Applause]
girl no well I mean that
hfc thing as I said before there's not
like actual food there that's like a
themed
Cafe um but who knows who knows
maybe there will be more fun
things uh wait maybe I should have was I
in range to attack that dude with Seline
now it's too late anyway I can't I can't
go back and Di
anyway no I wasn't okay good that's
that's probably why I didn't
attack it feels like I'm trying
to like avoid these people but not
really trying to avoid them I just ended
up being on the right side of the
[Music]
map run Everybody Run
Run Master
kiaha uh
oops oh she can even be on the mountain
all right looking to be really EAS just
breing for I really am uhoh ax is coming
ya he broke me I'm
bastard he won't live for
long okay more units coming for the from
the back but we don't care about those
they're never going to reach me the
corrupted alone Aren't Enough oh she
sending the dragons
now take care of these pests not dragons
huh
oh she's sting
down I understand what must be done
should I try to fight them for exp or
should I just run which of those morons
is going to be my first
victim orders are orders I just hope the
other side gets probably too strong H
big no no no you won't let them Escape
lady Bale you have my
word and okay
enemies are coming we cannot allow them
to slow us
down they're cutting us off how can we
endure
this become as Dragon oh the Divine
dragon's forces good I was afraid we
wouldn't catch them in time catch it
does not look so good to me you're
joining us right now right right and
they have no emblems we had best get
them these rings
I am back Princess
Ivy zov how did you fair I was unable to
recover the stolen rings from the dragon
girl but I did get
this oh pretty Crystal perhaps these
gifts will be enough to get them out of
this bind shut up let's hope so why are
you speaking like this hello Divine One
hi Princess Ivy why are you here I
wanted to try one last time to change my
father's mind I was too late but I did
retrieve these rings from destinia
Cathedral Rings yes here they are the
Ring of the lady of the Plains and the
Ring of the princess Exel are you sure
about this tur against your own country
spe impediment now turning against UIA
is the only way to save it for my
kingdom L Luc father
this is the only course of action I know
this isn't enough to atone for all I've
done but will you let me join yourself
here we go
course thank you theing of the lady of
the Plains belongs with you since it was
entrusted to UIA sweep across emblem of
Blazing wait wait wait
wait now I have free emblem rings I
that's the green haired the chick that I
know
I thought that was Tiki judging by that
art they look similar don't
they Lynn I know her I've seen her
around I'm lindus just call me Lynn
ready to turn this battle around hell
yeah they're both green huh and and
don't they both have
[Music]
ponytails a childhood wifeu
understandable y new cute Wu emem Linux
excels at fighting without giving her
opponents a chance to counter M the stin
SK alacrity
alacrity enables a unit much faster than
a foe to follow up before the fo's
Counterattack
uh I can't and that I don't know the
engage weapon killable lands Critical
Hits frequently m H that giv call
doubles creates illusionary decoys of
the user that can participate in chain
attacks oh there it is there it
is the engage attack Astro storm un just
five b attacks on the F for really I can
use
that reite us em I thought they were
going to Nerf
it if given to
me wait that's another wle that I know
[Music]
those two are really famous huh I know
them I've seen them so
much Mar no did she just
call it is I Lucina others look way more
like Mar and she did not call them Mar I
cannot replace him but I can Aid you I
strive to be a light in the dark a light
for all Fallen to despair for now we may
only Escape but as long as we survive
hope will abide now engage with me
engage no no I don't need your
engagement I already have free houses
engagement Emblem lucina's Power is
collaborative she fries on fighting near
her allies the S skill dual strike
empowers the user to take part in chain
attacks regardless of unit
type oh
okay the engage weapon Noble Rapier
deals Bon damage to calorie and armored
fors
oh M the engage skill bonded Shield
creates a high chance of nullifying
attacks against adjacent
allies oh the engage attack all for one
inspires all allies within two spaces to
take part in a chain attack regardless
of un okay okay okay okay a lot of
teamwork I have one more gift yeah what
does this
do the draconic time Crystal
how did you get it I borrowed it while
it is not one of the stolen rings
perhaps it will help what is
it and they joined my group now I have
to make even more people
escape don't you dare hold me back all
right this dude
asterisk uh it's a broken mechanic
really
you mean lucina's thingy
this oh
really she disguises herself as morph
got Miss a lot of the story
hi welcome
welcome we killed two fathers
so I am feeling very evil so evil that I
want to
join her side
right smells good over there smells like
evil all right what do we
[Music]
do oh wait there's some peeps over here
too ah do do
arch your boy kind of Fall
[Music]
Away we got this K yeah we'll be fine
just trying to minmax the situation
God damn it I'm thinking so
[Music]
much okay let's go with
you
first you don't have a vulnerary anymore
huh I think uh I
can
follow with
our
[Music]
healer but it's so dangerous
there H oh well I'll be
fine yeah okay if I get her on the green
spot but there's some standing on there
so I'll have
to
come hey thanks have to remove them
first forcefully at least one of them
right so link kills the heavy armor I
know but she has to heal
[Music]
you
oh so close and yet so far oh wait can
yay she got the Thunder she can do that
and they can't attack back so that's
[Music]
something and she's got the emblem ring
on her
now did they did they take away my DLC
ring and just just switch it out to
Lucina we could have given the Lucina
ring to someone else and I could have
kept the Fire Emblem freeh house ring
what the [\h__\h] they should have asked me
they did not consider not very
considerate cookie yummy
dick
bambooz okay
oh maybe I should have used that engage
protection thingy already now oh wait
what am I doing what am I doing H focus
focus focus focus I wanted to move her
away so I can attack with him
[Music]
maybe
or oops did I
press ooh
all right that looks
good set
[Music]
R it doesn't go
away is that the is that the arm I'm
pressing that now it goes away okay and
a kill for Anna someone said
m one HP
left hold up okay how
about oh [\h__\h] that's a lot of damage too
I just want to move her so that Anna can
stand
[Music]
there give me strong foes
why does it not can he not break
him why
not why not they s the ah the
armor ah should I pressed a by
accident all right thanks for taking the
thinking away from me and he misses St I
didn't even see that only had 35% chance
of hitting all right all right sometimes
when you can't make up your mind
your fingers do the the the work for
you
okay quickly
[Music]
now no I don't have the time Crystal
back yet right can't rewind you you're
pretty tough you know
[Music]
okay will finish
you this is almost as satisfying as
ironing my
clothes but way I think someone stole
my um
drill yesterday we were looking for it
like
everywhere I looked in every space a
million times the last time we used it
was to fix my my dining
table so that's my sister was there
right
oh my brother and so when I asked them
if they know where it is but of course I
don't how can it disappear how can my
drill disappear I can't I just couldn't
find
it no I looked in the in my closet where
normally I would store it a million
times I
swear a million times
stiletto checked the Frieza no but I
also looked in a lot of
other I was hoping for that I didn't
think it would happen I looked in a lot
of locations even where it wouldn't
where it shouldn't be where it wouldn't
make sense but no I couldn't find it
what the [\h__\h]
man just couldn't find it now I'm
wondering should I buy a new one but
when I buy a new one of course that's
one is going to show up
[Music]
right also uh you know those like water
scales is that what you call them in
English too I just directly translated
it from German
but I used to have one now I can't find
it
again
and but I
improvised I improvised and I was like
what how about we use this and guess
guess what I offered
to use
[Music]
instead yeah the the how to
know what's oh maybe I should have
engaged now it's already the end of the
map no not a l bottle that would I think
that would be hard to read Because I no
so big
well actually here we go uh a long time
ago I got like some uh perfume
Samplers from Louis
vuon they're really tiny like really
tiny balls they're smaller than my pinky
can you imagine and they're SE-R and I
thought they would be perfect so we used
them as a like a level scale thingy
instead big
[Music]
brain isn't that so big brain please
praise my brain capabilities I think
they're
insane
uh that one can go really fast I feel
like he'll follow me and kill me I might
I might stay in the back with two and
kill this one
smart move right thank you thank you oh
thank you
guys thanks for
[Music]
PR it isn't that so
girly using a
perfume when trying to do some
construction it's a
scale it's a level thingy what are you
calling that reminds me of um there's an
episode in gim girls where oh [\h__\h] where
Rory um I think it was Rory yeah she
goes to some construction side for um
helping uh to build uh a building
voluntarily don't spoil us for that he
may have been pass up I don't not sure I
had no choice but to win and what she
brings you know everybody has to bring a
hammer and she brings the cutest little
pink cute ass tiny
hammer and everyone makes fun of her for
it but it's like so typical cuz she got
it from her mom laurelai Gilmore and
that's so typical of
laurelai what's
our sizewise I have a similar hammer do
you guys remember
I'll take the
damage I think I showed that hammer
before my hammer my one and only Hammer
it's so small we used it again this time
this is what I bonking the wall Bonk
Bonk
Bonk it's it's a cute Hammer
okay we're so close Ki just has to step
there and then we're done zo ooh
[Music]
I know she's in the way now but at least
no one else like an enemy can step on
that space
then I'll do some damage
here engage oh I keep on forgetting now
because I'm like oh I can't engage
anyway
[Music]
is that worth it that that might not be
worth it cuz they'll kill me next round
I'll stay in the back with
her who's left oh he's so he's so dark
like this is the whole time he looks
like I already did his
turn to me
he's like the same blue gray shade shade
as everyone
else
[Music]
right who cares if he dies after this
it's just
casual he's got an iron great L
damn but that's a lot of damage but he's
only got 10% chance of
oh no way he's going to be able to hit
me
back I can
rewind wait that that that thing was for
rewinding that thing that wasn't the
ring wait that was that's what that
was oh well
Foria oh nice what we attacked
[Music]
[Laughter]
first yeah I know I remember we picked
that up in the beginning of the
game but never like in my
mind clearly understood that that's what
that was
for excuse me
I thought that was just the power that
was given to me by birth because I'm the
Divine Dragon I mean what else can I do
if I can't even you
know
uh if I can't even turn into a dragon as
as a Divine Dragon then you
know I'm going to get this kill before I
go I'm pretty tough you
know once I step on the green thing it's
over right so I can I can play around a
little bit here
right
okay all
[Music]
righty I'll apologize later
okie
dokie besides that they're all not
really in range the
enemies except for this
one who wants the
EXP maybe
KAG I'll give it to you
engage with kiaha oh oh you want to see
that what why why why
why oh I could do some damage with her
bow okay we can do
that but she also needs to step on the
green plate though yeah and then then I
I left my unit is here in the back that
they're going to die if I do
that yeah
nope all
right make
[Music]
space that was two backto back fights
and we successfully Escape come on
everyone let's get out of here I I Ivy
has it so
well I'm so
confused but he we did well I think no
one died in this one and in the previous
one only one person
died so we good we're
[Music]
good we can travel to S through this
Forest I hate to abandon Hortensia but
staying in the kingdom is not an option
there's too much for leaving
behind father it's pain
but we can't turn back we lose
everything I will lead the
way I failed you
Martha I failed you
all are we having a protagonist
depression Arc now iy was scheming
against
us she
mad she stole two emblems from right
under my nose she's so mad how
irksome regardless
the advantage is mine I have all of the
Rings they gathered you shall all be
destroyed I will cut your allies burn
down your countries yes and crush your
spirits oh yes do it crush
me destroy
me we should be safe now Vale is Som
Bran's daughter and now she has our
emblem rings
I'm sorry
everyone I should never have brought us
to the cathedral it's not your fault
Divine one I should apologize I asked
you to let me
fight I was so angry about what they'
done what about me I'm the one who
wanted to return father to brodia that
was illogical excuse me if you hadn't
gotten in the way calm down everyone
we're on the same side no we're not if
not for her we might have made it in
time we might have saved him Al chist
Princess Ivy told us about the ritual in
the first place without our help father
would still be one of those creatures
diamont she helped kill our father why
are you making excuses for her princess
Ivy's not to blame her father was and
the fell Dragon murdered him there
wasn't even a body left behind
behind arguing won't get us anywhere
apologies Divine
One Princess Ivy I hope you'll forgive
my brother he spoke out of turn no it's
all
right I am sorry that I couldn't stop
the ritual I
just I can't bear the thought that I'll
never see him again and the ring he
spent his whole life
protecting G we'll get it back we have
suffered loss after loss but the emblems
Aren't
Dead we can still get them back and we
will I know we will to find
one you still have emblems on your
side that's right don't forget about us
pretty nice ones too Lucina all is far
from Lost we can offer our unique
strengths as emblems you can still
challenge your fate you don't lose by
retreating I wish it didn't come to this
my mother told me that a Divine Dragon
should never run away we're not running
away as Lucina said we're retreating
there's a
difference time and again you've shown
true bravery even in the face of
daunting odds but refusing to move on
that's not bravery it's Folly there's
courage and there's stubbornness Luma
would have Tau you the difference
unfortunately in your short time
together she didn't have the chance
perhaps that's why Mar said what he did
outside the cathedral probably so now at
least I
understand we're not running
away we're stepping
back Gathering our strength for the next
battle I'll become a better
fighter a better leader I'll make sure
no one not one more person loses their
life under my command and I'll bring
back our friends the
emblems what do you say
everyone are you with me you know you
let's turn the tables on them I won't
rest until we reclaim what we've lost
even now you have
hope I will stand with
you will if you'll have
me thank you everyone
now to the kdom of
s stay with me is that the the desert
area new area here we go after this cold
ass winter I'm so ready for it a dry
SAA yeah if V tells me she wants me I'm
immediately going to
[Laughter]
jump I wouldn't say she sounds like 40
nah we're in what chapter 12
now did we finish chapter 11 just now
I'm so
confused back the
snal Y
yeah we're in chapter 12 now all
[Music]
righty so let's see what the doggos got
me this
time so in God that's how I like it eggs
good job KF
be appreciate your effort iron
steal a little bit of
everything good
do scary ghost horse is there again oh
there's two now they're multiplying
it's time to do the chores again
oh
N I forgot one oh I'm now able to play
wife right wow this once that
scene me just staring at Vander staring
at the sky made me able to play
Wern ride uh-huh
yes whatever that is oh Princess
Ivy my favorite
unit that's a tough
[Music]
question m
I can't
decide I
[Music]
like
can't and why mind you fly for a course
while shooting floating
targets
uh try to hit the special targets and
aim for a high score more courses will
luck as you progress in the story oh
dear oh look at her she looks
like H like a traveling Merchant wife no
a traveling tarot card reader traveling
witch ride
Cy okay have a nice flight oh yeah
she'll help me let's do it how do you do
this they didn't explain the controls
how do I
shoot oh my God it's it's Zelda Zelda uh
which one was it
oh
oh aim aim aim Aim so aim
the controls are all but
mooo 2,900 this mini game is so
[Music]
stressful it is are we done or is there
more oh there's
more oh yeah
baby oh
6, 6 second this is so difficult oh
man it it feels so
stiff who that was
easy oh it's also an auto shooting
huh who who who who who who whoo whoo
well now we're talking
cool almost had
it no motion controls oh I wonder is
there I didn't
try I guess
not as the doct does the other sitting
here there are motion controls I need to
try this was fun though it was kind of
difficult
[Music]
B I want a or is it also
s until next this might be easier with
motion controls can I only do this once
no yes one my wait what did I get Bond
how many did I get would you
like how many I
get up to
SSS shiny smiley
story 50 oh that's
60 I'm guessing I get more if I do
better
maybe items with a good score okay there
is no motion control you lied to me at
least not with the controller I have
right
now o oh not bad
[Music]
W okay that's already more than I had
before I
think need to need to smash buttons and
hope it hits press
plus switch to motion controls o I hope
that wouldn't like mess up my aim speed
[Music]
I hope that doesn't mess up my
run set aim tilt aim
control
okay no wait what why is my default why
am I looking up by
default no let's go
back what the [\h__\h] where am I that's the
[\h__\h] I I demand a a
r oh oh now we oh oh it's working
perfectly
now
okay some scuff
[Music]
there have to like reset camera to the
middle I was sabotaged I totally
was oh look at that ay maybe I should
shoot the snail
hey baby look at that okay with that oh
could
get could possibly get SSS at some
point fun was there more I think that's
it
right 32
[Music]
woo I get just what i' expect from the
Divine
one oh I skipped A and S guys w w w now
I'm hooked until next time I'm
hooked wait did I not get bone fragments
just now is it just once per day I guess
otherwise you could like spam
it even then I want to go again have a
nice
flight wait
s+ are we motion controls by by default
now
hopefully other
difficulty okay motion controls
if you can't do this platoon would be a
re really I'm using T
[Music]
controls
hey so far not a single
[Laughter]
Miss bring it on baby this one I don't
think it f I don't I don't think I can
do a
full full
one did I just do
that I did
I
did what a
gamer
[Music]
37,000 I could have even done that
without qy to be honest cuz I don't
think Q helped that just what I'd expect
from the Divine
s++ hey're about Q would have done would
that have been s Plus+
plus damn
[Music]
bam until next
time okay that was fun fun exercise
D like I'm playing Star Fox
Adventures H where is this one that I
missed I it am I blind I saw it on the
map ah There It
Is iron
[Music]
okay so okay after this going to do the
bonds on the
[Music]
conversations uh cook some food look at
the
Rings
uh so there's not always many things to
do in the SU Neil time to join the Apex
event no no no I'm not joining
that not my
thing
100 do you want to be pet as well here
pet pet
pet you take now you need the ring it
will take 3 hours though but I guess if
we do taking out then I'm telling you
that will be the last thing we're doing
today if that takes 3
hours we
done but people said it will be too
difficult for me now are you sure
guys takey worth it completely
busted the Skirmish Skirmish takes so
long i' rather do Tiki all right we'll
do Tiki we can manage somehow right
right right is it realistic the SC with
my Hero level will always be difficult
[Music]
TI it's her bee
song
MH I wish there was like some kind of
Auto
collect next we go ring
chamber TIY will help my girlriend
it's easy if you wall off the
reinforcements
oh I can wall them
[Music]
off let's polish them
first
um who will I want to give Lynn to
because I'm going to give kiaha back the
free houses
[Music]
an
Archer okay we can give it to
alchrist then I will let him polish her
now
Sparkle that looks good thanks that was
F huh finish already that spot needs
attention I admire your
work t l better on you kn
[Music]
yeah I do like the idea of giving it to
someone who doesn't have a bow so that
they can use a bow when I need
[Music]
one maybe I should not give it to
alist
Lucina
currently uh Ivy has Lucina or wait no I
I have Lucina currently I don't know but
who am I going to give her
to give it to someone slow who doesn't
use
bows I to Chloe Ivy ivy has Lyn
currently like ivy on
Chloe you're a little bit confused
sir he's a good boy look L Louie maybe
we can give Lucina to Louie they start
with the same kind of
letters Lou where are you I don't see
you here there you
are let's clean this up what do you
think about this idea guys what what do
you think about this match
up he deserves his wife
now how does it look oh it's all shiny
now we ship it are we shipping it okay
you guys belong together
now speaking of
marriage when am I going to be able to
marry someone
huh
[Music]
guard in the game I mean I can count on
you that's not helping much that's not
helping much of course it is helping
look at the bar
up near the
end thank you for taking care of
it after the a rank
okay didn't get anyone to support me I I
will get there should we inherit the
skill we probably can't right now
maybe create some Bond
Rings oh I do want to create at least
one set of bond Rings or is that a
waste just just one
set one
set I want to do
[Music]
some well that was pretty
bronze oh BRS
so Matthew
be go go go go
go silver Jafar
be go go go go go go
gold Hector
SE please
Sil
jaar last chance
baby no one
more and another bronze oh n she's cute
who is
she n weren't that lucky this
time okay wait what's this about engage
weapons oopsy what can we do
there you can use certain materials to
augment your engage weapons crystals
increase stats while Banes add
Effectiveness against unit types ooh you
can earn the materials to augment engage
weapons in Tempest trials or relay
trials each engage weapon has an
augmentation capacity you cannot augment
a weapon pass it capacity you can strip
away augmentations to try out new
effects or increase and engage weapons
capacity by raising the emblem's bond
level is this for multiplayer end game
ahuh MH now yeah I didn't do any of
those battles
yet I another
[Music]
time why did I leave like this where are
we going next we have we have to have
some
[Music]
food I have Bond conversations let's do
those OK with
Ard I'm having a hard time deciding
which weapon truly suits me how did you
choose well the hero's Relic passed down
in my family was a lance I suppose it
was decided for me
uhhuh again we talked to Dimitri we get
eligard on the screen and here it says
Demitri
again
[Music]
okay so where are you from oh look at
you shooting off questions like Barbed
arrows out of camouflage sit an ambush
like that and you're liable to
drive see I'm glad you're here D
somewhere in uh frodia oh I see Thanks
for opening up listen could I ask you to
keep a lid and like eight padlocks on
this particular jar things could get
unpleasant for me if this gets out and
folks start connecting dots gotcha my
lips are sealed thanks Alfred look I
down like that all the time you quite
that simple I could get really both of
us if you ask me the wrong kinds of
questions oh uh I've got a lot to hide
oh yes yes yes as you were just hiding
it now please continue hiding that
position absolutely will because it's
far preferable to the trouble that could
find you if you learned too much about
me I'm sorry that's how it has to be but
no no I get it I won't push you I'm not
out to make you uncomfortable
I appreciate that Alfred truly but I
said last time I wanted to talk more
with you and that's what I'm going to do
it doesn't have to be personal stuff we
can talk about anything like our
favorite flowers yes love it henceforth
your brain's going to be stuffed with
obscure weapon
factoids thought was about
flowers
n now we have a Selen and Alfred
conversation
do you know what you are Alfred a
barbarian in Princess clothing huh what
a nice thing to say thanks s how did
that strike you as a
compliment you meant that I've got
muscles all over like a barbarian right
that's really even if you're just saying
it cuz I'm your brother that is not at
all how I meant it hey hey it's okay
sine if that wasn't the idea then what
did you mean by it your first impulse on
hearing we were low on water was to dig
a well oh right some mixup huh boy was
my face red would that it were the only
example what about the time you heard
some soldiers wishing they could cleanse
themselves you immediately left to dig
them a
hotring oh that sounds nice hot
springs that isn't my point why is your
first instinct always to go digging it's
good
training save your breath it's instincts
like that that Mark you as barbaric
which would be fine for most men but you
are a maybe best weapon would be a
shovel not a lens all right S I get your
point from now on I'm going to train
even hard should be an official weap
days pretty soon I'll be so beefy that
everyone can tell right off what a
barbarian I am no more
confusion one once again you have
completely missed the point shovel night
conf well kind of
cute
conversation all right
um let's have some food come on
in dispos of ly meal again oh no I'm
going to do
Ivy and how about zeluff I
guess o baked potato
yum I should probably cook today too cuz
like I got like
two um
meat dishes to cook from hellofresh the
one non meat one already cooked on
Tuesday I don't know why I did it in
this order but actually you know the
recipes they say um cook this on day
three cook this on day five and so on
and for some reason even though it makes
no sense this time the meat dishes they
wrote cook on Dish five h on day five uh
on the one that has no meat therefore
could hold longer in the fridge was on
dayree makes no sense I thought
they like decide which day depending on
which ingredient s go bad the
fastest maybe it was a mistake oh cuz I
looked on the dates of the meat
expiration dates and they're pretty soon
I think one is probably tomorrow and one
might be
today so kind of have to cook
something today after the stream unless
unless unless I don't mind cooking the
expired meat tomorrow or putting in it
in the fridge
or in the freezer I wonder if that still
works if you freeze it on the day of the
expiration is that still
acceptable yeah okay don't freeze the
expiration these expensive ingredients
I didn't waste a single scrap of food on
this one pushing the edge oh seems like
this one did not
fail quite a pleasant flavor I would
like to ask the chef to teach me the
recipe you will never know you must
subscribe to
hello here see I made you a
to see but uh lots of stats up so we
good thank you
how about some
chitchat oh wait gift after support I
want to give her a
gift I forgot to gift people gifts
recently iy did you need something from
me no Divine one must I require
something to remain near
you no it's not that I see then please
feel free to ignore me I would but it's
difficult to ignore the anger on your
face oh diamond is always bad at cooking
ofia worships the F Dragon that's the
cas I can certainly see why you would
feel uncomfortable around me you can't
imagine how I feel well if you can
explain it I'd love to understand you
wouldn't get it she says it might reduce
this distance between us true but we
should get used to each other first
we'll talk when we're more comfortable
for now I will leave you be and worship
from afar
worship LEL
[Music]
see thank you you're welcome here's your
little gift a welcome gift o Spirit CH
do you think she might like it favored
by all it says take that thank
you you're
welcome no not Heman is it is she
actually the one who likes
said I don't trust you oh my God Anna is
so tiny right now
what was she always this
tiny damn here's
a there's a pebble
thanks she's like 10 she's 11 she's
12 no I've heard she's is very young in
this game and in other gam she's not
that
young I really like Santa Claus today
just because you know recently it was
Christmas after
all there's some gifts for you and for
you and for you and for
you who's down here oh
you I prefer to give stuff to girls
hi
[Music]
youa cute look at her chilling in a
swimsuit by the fountain she's like Ki
can you take a Instagram picture for me
please
thanks she has the perfect perfect pose
and background right now that would look
so good on the
photo in she
how do you talk to someone who's in the
pool by the way do I just wait until
he's on the other
side no I can't talk to him not that I
would want to we
good okay um do we need to stock up on
something especially if we o are we
really
[Music]
going it's 8:00 p.m. though
but I don't have to get up early
tomorrow just need to cook later and
case I can make a pizza too oh yeah
Arena
[Music]
MH oh yeah I have a super chat back luck
too that's right not too much though
right but yeah I'll read them
today but not now not not so early yeah
who needs
this this gives them normal XP
right should we give it to Anna
again Anna go go
Anna become strong call me lady I will
let her do it I am a
royal want to not not to buy
anything how are you feeling are you up
for a long fight I guess oh she might
win this
one
wow to win next time have I got just the
thing for you I'm
impressed oh yeah I got Master Seals
too I should use those
I'll do Seline too cuz why not shall we
have a cup of tea
afterward I am zov retainer to princess
iy this really feels like I'm playing
Tekken speaking of that game is been a
battlef wait what was take which game
was that which recently had a new
release
a street fighter that was
it should I play Street
Fighter should I should I should
I yeah is it let this chance go to waste
Clan 33rd Steward of the Divine dragon
oh that one's an easy win or is it oh
maybe not maybe not to Easy Go Go
Lis one more hit can we take it no we
couldn't it's not out
yet I feel like I saw someone play it
what was that saw someone in Ian not in
Ian in maybe that was
a
demo like I saw yeah cor on it cor on it
didn't you play it oh that was an early
version I saw cor play it she was
playing C of
Five Oh I thought I was
six I thought it was already out
[Laughter]
[Music]
then
okay don't oh I guess okay we do
Ticky now I wonder oh we might have new
clothes
right
oh oh they're just the same clothes oh
this one's kind of
new green so
green oh
H
oh so similar this looks something like
what the nerys would
wear
agree come to Brazil come to Brazil come
to Brazil M doesn't make it more likely
if you say it
more can I help you let's see can you
help
me how about we improve this weapon
seems special to
me
[Music]
and killer
axe what are you trying to
do maybe a steel
bagger yeah steel
bagger should I sell the extra
ones sure I can do
[Music]
that so we got another Mage now huh with
Ivy she's a mage from what I can tell
even more choices I feel like we have
plenty
Mages I don't know what to do I'll be
here hey what's up for all the Bots why
are they here what happened what do you
want I got nothing to give to you
I
know how do I sell from the Convoy oh
okay
oh
so this is everything that's that
nobody's using
right it's less I thought don't need
this steel dagger probably don't need
this out
we should use those energy drops
[Music]
though do come
again let me see what you got though cuz
maybe you have an
interesting
[Music]
stick what's physic is that a stronger
healing oh no it's ah healing at a
distance oh
oh and they got a reward I might you get
that cuz we haven't gotten one
before prevents folks from using Toms or
staves not hold oh they got wait they
got monster
steals I thank you two of them I thank
you and second steals I thank
you I thank you I thank you I bought
them all do come again oh yeah who do we
want to use those on and how does it
work again uh
inventory and then change class
right who who can for uh someone like
Anna she would need to be level 10
right to
upgrade and can Seline not upgrade
either but
she's what Jade
[Music]
could D's already Pro then what level
does she have to be to be promoted
again Jade can promote okay
coolo 10 again
okay um a
General she can become a
general do we make her a general that
sounds so cool but the other
ones Mar probably makes sense to not put
her on the
horse General
Jade is she going to wear even more
armor oh wait she looks even more like
kisana
it's not like more armor but it has a
has a different shape those FES the
Knight started her new attire and um do
you really think this is a good fit hell
yeah she's so
protected nothing will get through to
her heart except my love
hopefully okay congratulations
[Music]
m h can
she be
Advanced she's level
[Music]
17 she can become a lindworm what magic
using VI Rider who destroys enemies from
above can use powerful magic and
staves what
unique
class I didn't even get used to this
outfit what's she going to look like now
oh wait her outfit looks kind of the
same huh did she
change if this is what you wish for me
then I will embrace it without
hesitation everything except luck
increased she has a flower in her Grill
now
she looks the same to
me the Roses on her head ah yeah that's
what you mean with Grill I thought you
meant with Grill her
boops but that's look
[Music]
slang can
Diamond I mean now I don't have a master
seal anymore right or do I successor I
do still have two Master Seals I can
make him a a
successor which makes so much sense
L let's
[Music]
go glow up
incoming oh yeah oh yeah that's what I'm
talking
about I feel powerful and it feels good
time to bring honor to my kingdom for
brodia let's go bro he can use axe
now give him a Toma hook uh uhuhuh n we
have one more Master
steal we can I think we can do
alist and citrine I think
too maybe let's do
alist wor it to what's that toite that's
French isn't it an Asha gifted with
Incredible aim each shot can eliminate a
full he's protecting broo while he's
gone he can do it from a distance don't
worry Kings sometimes leave their ooh
leave their countries for war that's
normal you you used a valuable item like
that on the waste like me I'm I'm sorry
I'll repay your
death I'm sure you will prove yourself
worthy okay what about the silver ones I
bought they're just if I want to change
like someone who's on B right now to a
different B like reclassing
someone not a hold do we have an ex
Tomahawk I'm guessing
not no okay so he's got two slots we can
give him but he's still mainly a sword
user right we can give him
Tomahawk
and Tomahawk is the throwing one right
do we want to give him a normal one too
oh we have a killer axe just give the
killer
axe uh
feel like he's going to be really strong
they don't sell a
tomahawk maybe in the
future andex will do for
now here you go more
and
then let's steal killer axe from who has
it right
now ah well you definitely don't need
it
nice also iron great Axe lapis has an
iron great ax that she can't use right m
but handex is worth it for now I would
say
okay cuz then we can attack from a
distance
oh give lire to a mage oh yeah lire oops
I'll give it to
citrin maybe or
Ivy Damn wait now we have so many majes
that I want to use can I reclass one of
to something
else Anna is there citrin and Ivy I like
all three of
them oh the change can maybe does
citrine work is something else
too I is a better version of
citrin that's so sad I really like her
has some good
supports Seline can go physical Seline
oh you're right I mean but Seline is
like kind of
both so I
[Music]
guess two Mages and Seline having those
around I don't know but she's also heal
she's she can she's an all arounder to
me Seline is such an all arounder she
heals for me she does magic she does
iron
sword
sometimes
yeah oh man what a conundrum I will
give see I'll give
the lire to oh I already have an lire
well then I'll give it to Seline
[Music]
yeah cuz it's more likely that that I
will have her in my team all the
time I feel so
bad what about that L
surge ivy can also heal
well she has a physic and the Rew warp
in her
inventory
so that's
fine
M okay what else should we
[Music]
do no don't take that away don't what
what did we just take away from
there a staff right a sta no wa
what oh was a free step okay
Steve and I I'm going to give
[Music]
her oh we're actually like kind of
like out of vulner almost
oh wait you can't use that
anyway that's healing safe if I ever
need one remind me that I have one on
her now what about
those how do I use those those usable
items who do I give them to what did I
have why don't why can't I just like
open up an inventory in general why do I
always have to go through a character
it's so confusing
give them to your favorites okay so for
example the energy
drop guess we can give one to
kiaha
[Music]
um would give it all to the MC see maybe
all but one how about
that I what's what wait what's that HP +
5 oh what Spirit does magic plus two
oh
okay who's magic you're magic but I
probably won't use you much anymore well
I'm so sad
[Music]
use and on Ivy to
use secret book decks
M who needs who needs decks dexterity
was what
again oh
oh you know what Diamond can have it
too um ax guys or high crit units
accuracy and crit diamond and
alist okay
[Music]
okay did
that go to the dude who was carrying it
just
now I think it
did speed plus
two speed what does speed
do now I'm good
okay um
[Music]
we're hting
twice
[Music]
oh so I could give that to anyone really
right Dodge and double attacks
[Music]
anyone you get this
one you also get this one when in doubt
give to protagonist
resistance
boots movement plus one here take
that luck
I give that to unaka because I love
unaka okay I'll leave some for another
time cuz we got to go we got to go can I
go to TI now you think I'm good to
[Music]
go t shield on a mage
yeah long battle ahead that's what I'm
saying is it just one three hour
[Music]
battle
uh say it first
okay
ah okay
hours that's how much I've played it for
wo wo wo wo W
whoo man I'm going to put so many hours
into this
game what what am I guessing 60
70 if it was 60 then that would mean I
would be already like halfway through I
doubt that that doesn't feel like I'm
halfway through oh maybe I'm going to
the last continent now I have 73 hours
and I haven't beat the game 96 hours
classic 60 sounds right really I guess
I70 oh wow okay okay okay oh Beach
Paradise K my sh
roast candy
time I forgot
to no
so I automatically went there thany
don't
worry I'm coming to get you right now
I have one way to do it rewind
rewind
rewind yeah safe before that of course I
did you guys not watching the screen
what are you doing on the side
huh what are you doing that's like
keeping you from watching the stream
actively
huh also playing the game
working
emblem I wouldn't do such a thing if I
didn't
save there we
go
okay I want to do the divine paralog
please playing a rise
oh that's a good game to play
okay the part two Divine
[Music]
paralog free for it in the morning well
thank you for watching
[Music]
still Dragon
Temple I am
scared I hope it's not going to be too
tough
oh yeah but there we're starting a
dialogue that's why I wanted to here we
are the island South of f ended I
definitely feel the presence of an
emblem that looks like an altar over
there with a bracelet resting on top of
it inside I'm
sensing yes I feel it now what is it
Divine
one I think an invocation just came to
me I'll I'll try summoning the emblem
now
oh Dream well emblem of
dragons
Tiki a
[Music]
cute I thought you were a dragon she
dragon
she's
cute
marar no excuse me who are you I'm the
Divine Dragon we came here because I
sense your Australian Divine Dragon well
that's what I am too my name is emblem
Tiki why
she me I feel as sleep for a very long
time I can relate to that Tiki do you
happen to remember anything from before
your sleep H I know my bracelet friends
and I were all somewhere very far away
we fought in so many battles I cannot
recall how they ended I do remember
someone very gentle helping me to sleep
I wonder who it was someone
gentle I was kept asleep in my former
world too it was me but I was still
quite frightened but then Mama made it
that I didn't need to S
anymore the time of the
heroing emblem Mar has beenos for a long
time if you'd be willing to join him in
fighting to save this world is there
Japanese voice like I would love to join
your special too I wonder traving with
so many new friends no I'm just
wondering but if I'm to join you i' like
to see what
drives will you show me your essence of
course in Japanese she's just super
polite apparently you can battle against
me then I'll know your true name no and
you don't need to hold back no special I
am really quite
[Music]
strong no she she's childish in Japanese
but no nothing like
[Music]
Australian so she grew up in England or
something so she had the
accent you mean the voice actress grew
up in England not Lynn what Lynn Ticky I
[Laughter]
mean it's interesting she's the only one
who speaks like that okay so who do we
give all these rings to here with Lucina
right now we have got to change that I
want you to have ad count on
me you got that one and then
M I was going to
give Lynn and Lucina
Luc
yeah hell yeah okay so the team that
we're going to
use what are we dealing with holy [\h__\h]
this map is huge where are we
going what the [\h__\h] is
that that TIY in there is that where I
going to go TIY what why is she there we
just saw
her
uh going to be a long battle yeah this
looks long sparkly item near the lake
lake oh
where the [\h__\h] do I go
first okay well there's there's so much
to see here so I need a balanced team
right oh God where do I go after
reaching this point I should probably
just go up right is it worth it going to
this side ah he has an
item if I really want that item I
guess up and then
left here
maybe oh cuz there's treasure chest okay
basically you want to go
everywhere oh but to the lake I have to
walk around or can I send a flyer just
all the way over these
walls walls seem too high for a flyer to
pass through I can warp at the end ah I
can we already do have a warp
stfe hold on hold on hold
[Music]
okay
okay so we'll do that
eventually unit
selection it
eight are we being joined later by some
because eight is really not much
what the
[\h__\h] I thought we were good 10
no all right um Ivy I
[Music]
guess one
Archer oh
God okay probably not two
Lancers then I'll
keep
clly
[Music]
perhaps and then
take Jade or
[Music]
Seline could also consider
taking m
[Music]
need a Healer but also want some
tanks those
you oh wait I don't need Trin that's for
sure okay so how about
this I think this is pretty
balanced trade diamond for
ketu no no I'm not yet
like m I haven't had much experience
with kitu I guess so that's why I'm not
quite like
convinced but the crits
huh bring arches more than one I can
only bring eight units you say bring
this and this and this and this how am I
going to bring all these
units he's really good at being
good bring Anna she can handle
it if I could I would bring
everyone yeah I just promoted Diamond I
just did
that
fight
fight now then show me your oh sorry
okay
mm these doors are protected by a
powerful force
why I got three rings and I have them
all are the only way to me do your best
to reach
me perhaps it would be wise to head for
that sigil first okay thank you for the
hint mhm defeat emblem
TI you don't join me b terly
huh how do you get up
here is there like a door you walk
through
here wall
impassible how do I reaches do just by
flying I'm
listening only a
flyer ah fun
music flyers or you do n okay let's
begin I
I hear
you this will be such a pain in the ass
here
goes I got to play it smart guys I have
to okay we're going
to take care of this axe dude and if
we're lucky we get a crit
come
on you did not get a
crit it's always the one HP yeah kind of
lame I will do what I
[Music]
must what you
got
mhm
ooh music is super interesting
it's not like a remix of her old theme
or so is it tell me where something like
that
understood she can't go very far oh but
wait we have an IR handex on her we
smart smart people oh it is a
remix oh that's a nice reference and she
missed oh wait
4% I guess it was worth a try I didn't
see
that
uh uhuh uhuh I'll protect
you uh how do we do this
[Music]
don't like
this okay okay okay
okay all right we we'll start with a
thunder then we can bow and then we can
Lance my that was awesome
I want to redo this map
already
huh
[Music]
no 34 what but they're all [\h__\h] they're
all [\h__\h] 44% that's so [\h__\h] and he's got
100%
he's on the protection tile that little
piece of
[\h__\h] this so
[Music]
mean his kind of like forcing me to
engage but now it's kind of too late
because I moved all my freaking engage
units who would
help
already I mean what can I do besides
hoping it
hits oh my
God oh my God
42 it's all at
[Music]
42% what the
[\h__\h] what the the
[\h__\h] why not rewind because we're just
started anyway I'm not going to waste a
rewind on
that so this is still like the same
units that I chose
right should I change
it do something here
Seline mhm
mhm okay and then maybe engage with
someone
[Music]
you're going to be such a pain in the
ass you better be worth
[Music]
it out fire 90% 90% okay okay okay well
now we're talking
[Music]
or long bow no it's
okay I will not
miss can always rely on
[Music]
Seline I've got
this I want her to take care of the axe
guy though is there any other person who
can help me out with
this I will I I we should be able to
help here we go but her her funer was
also [\h__\h]
though
22% about alire
[Laughter]
27 should I
engage yeah iy doesn't count as a Mystic
unit
but isn't her um engage thingy the super
far shot I feel like it's kind of a
waste to use
[Music]
that as storm
but what can I
do oh look at her in green F it's the
same hair color as fauna it is a waste
watch
this it would be a waste it is a
waste but I can't think of a better
solution cses upon our enemy I'll
recharge it where are the recharging
tiles here's one here's
one okay who can reach
that ah but first I go there with
kiaa and break him
Liberation do we have something to talk
about during these long long long Ticky
hours there
something oh the flyer doesn't benefit
from the ti well funny simple
enough all the Japan Japan Tes done I
think
so at least the ones I can think of
maybe at some point randomly something
will come to mind I need cat information
kiaha cat information
well I would have told you I took Kato
to the doctor the only thing me I can
tell you that I didn't
tell I told you the food
[Music]
story I told you I've been cutting
cutting hair from
chunkers there was a crazy cat on the at
the
vet who who was like meowing so much in
pain cuz she was right before uh
surgery but choners would not get
influenced by that she was so so sweet
today and the other cat was
[Music]
like you know a cat only does this kind
of meow when she's in big big
pain only cat own owners know this stuff
yeah sounds too
familiar poor K cat y I felt so bad cat
should never be in pain cats should be
immune to
pain it's not
fair let me see
[Music]
8600 I hope that cat got some good help
I think
so right after I left the vet started
some surgery on the
cat this ice is rather slippery we could
use it to hasten our step so long as we
are
careful so we can go faster
but what if we're not careful
[Music]
74 89 89 should be
good they give plus two movement
increase
range I have poison
damage oh no I I don't think I have an
anti toxin with me
does it not like go
away St a
normal I can use a
convoy is that's
so someone drops it oh okay I think I
have one in the
Convoy uh can they take it out
themselves and then use it right away or
or does someone have to like how does
this work again trade
maybe no how do they use the Convoy
probably
fine if they're next to the main
character yes ah that next to the main
character that's how it
worked uh-huh uh-huh
uh-huh
M damn she's carrying so much [\h__\h] with
her we'll have to swap it
[Music]
though guess I'll swap it with a
vulnerary thanks girl so nice of
you I'll do this one for now
[Music]
shiny question mark question mark
question mark top of the
map what you mean the one at the lake
yeah I already saw that one that's what
you
mean I should
work I'll help
the Indonesian learning stre with Raina
oh yeah we haven't talked about that in
a while I've been talking with Raina
about other things but I feel like we
both forgot about
that H I wonder if she has something
scheduled for Sunday cuz that could be
something to do on
Sunday she probably has a schedule out
right remember that cuz that's something
she did on would do on Sunday anyway
right I repli to me m remember that ID
classroom we wanted to
do why not do it on Sunday or are you
already
[Music]
busy tap tap tap tap no Fatal Frame I
don't remember what that
is uh
uh waking
go I want my emblem Wings
back I can call
dou she's
aable let's
go but Sunday was one day a I kept
open because I didn't know what to do
this
week
perfect we can do kimono
collab okay all right we got a date for
[Music]
Sunday still not sleep yeah wa not
sleeping
attack should I be worried about sending
Ivy all the way over here
alone n wait how much was the percentage
I didn't look 100% thank
God yeah what the [\h__\h] what what what
what what what did I do
what
[Music]
okay don't fear for me
actually wait she could also take it out
of the Convoy right now I mean why
[Music]
not wait all three of them went to the
other
chick I thought I only took
one but it was three of the same item
right so I can trade
Chloe oh
[Music]
he 67% wasn't even that
low oh oh oh here we go
again this time he hits me ah but then
he misses ah he only hits with the train
attack y
baby anyway thanks for bringing up the
ID class cuz I really still had no idea
but that reminds me of another thing did
fauna put up a schedule this week by the
way just just wondering asking for a
friend
[Music]
okay just uh doing things now that I
just remembered to
do yes um
[Music]
ah
don't think I'll go for the land
sky is is calling doubles worth it
am minus well wait does that count as an
attack can I not attack
then not for now good for baiting
enemies uhuh can I control them if
they're not dead
yet no okay h
ooh lire
Kos wait how much has the
percentage now I'm so nervous the whole
time about it calling D is really op is
upon our enemy they block all ways to
attack you I see unless it's someone who
can attack with
um
with uh you know you know you know what
I'm trying to
say yeah another
Alp all the mjes getting all the kills
look at them
go you so what have you guys been doing
today besides watching me tell
me oh 1 3 4
five
hey work work work eating dying and work
work work work work ah you guys are like
trying to sing a Rihanna song huh KF be
at work work work work work work all
they do is work work work work work work
they love to work work work work work
work all they do is work work work work
work work quack quack
[Music]
quack so this turn is mostly moving
donating blood oh
got to pay bills that's true small trip
to next town over recovering from
helping my friend yesterday with his
Fallen
fence
not nice of you to help your
[Music]
friend if a friend asks you guys to help
you with moving are you happy to do it
or are you kind of like feeling
obligated to do it
[Music]
cuz I feel like most friends probably
just feel like they're obligated to do
it happy
really
really wait she got the
antitoxin uh who's I giving it to
ah take
this nice
and that can heal her
too
yeah efficient what a I have a truck and
light to flex it oh I wish I had a
friend who has a truck would have made
my moves over the years
easier
man you ignore the message and
prot oh yeah that oh no almost I almost
almost dead oh my good oh my good please
nobody attack her again she could die
[Music]
now I'm nervous oh okay we good that
scared
me I'm getting
hungry oh that's scary
great help help because I like packing
other people's things and seeing what
kinds of stuff they
own yeah
packing packing seems a bit more fun
than
unpacking I think so
too and yeah you can see what they own
lots of conversation starters
huh out what's this what's this this is
that and this is that yeah yeah yeah
yeah
oh
wow I enjoy unpacking but I hate
packing easier to help friends glad when
they aren't great for rude about
it I guess you guys don't expect
anything in exchange either except me
for
pizza oh you guys are so nice
but you know yesterday you know RBF was
helping me um put some stuff up and this
time I I rep with homecooked food
by cuz I had some food left over you
know the food I the the the noodles that
I posted on
Twitter that was threee servings one for
me for dinner and and then
yesterday one for like really early
dinner and uh actually it was more like
lunch cuz I cooked again after that in
the a couple hours later yeah and had
still one left over so rvf got to what
you said what do you mean poor RBF he
said it was good it was
yummy don't you
dare sh it was really good
[Music]
I was happy some like finally I could
share my cooking with someone most of
the time I always just um eat it all by
myself all by
myself I want to be all by
myself a [\h__\h] no wait we
[Music]
good is his girlfriend good to cooking
according to him yes she
is very much good at
cooking I've had her cooking before
too look like a dragon out of
Yu-Gi-Oh are you better well the thing
is I was just um being held
back I was my my skills are being held
back by
the recipe from Hello
[Music]
beep by
potential
no although I must say those noodles
that I cook that's that probably will go
into the folder of my favorite hello
recipes are we going that way should I
go that way just to charge cuz there's
nothing else there
why are there these tiles when there's
nothing
there
why oh he's got an
item
me all right I guess I'll go over to
that
side we're going to spend hours on this
anyway
[Music]
the other side also have an
item does he I don't I don't think so I
checked actually I checked in the
[Music]
beginning he
doesn't
uh killer axe
he we got a crit we break anyway so it
doesn't
matter
break oh no mercy you put up a good
fight cool cool cool
cool yeah my best friends boyf Ando oh
there we go here's an
antitoxin I to Convoy though
[Music]
I'm getting wisely me me
wise I was already wise to begin
with don't you know the wisdom that has
been shared by the
Phoenix for centuries for now only sent
the flyer
uh okay I'll send uh Kiwa to charge
[Music]
though and her
too here she can charge
there and kisana goes here
okay yeah only one enemy but I thought
maybe I don't know I guess only the fly
can even reach it
oh wait she doesn't need I didn't use
her what was I
thinking I thought I used her thing up
oh what am I doing confused brain what
the vism of the Phoenix
today start your day with your favorite
breakfast and your worries will go
away I've been eating the same bread
breakfast every single day in
Austria recently the strawberries have
gotten fresher again in the supermarket
I
feel oh
wait could have used the antitoxin
oopsie next turn next turn is another a
[Music]
turn just going to cast magic through
there that's just mean
mve plus
two if I just walk straight for the
middle I don't have to deal with these
suckers could kill them here though
what's up there more Mages shesh there's
so many Mages y
I could
shoot the one at one at the
topage you put strawberries and cereal
um I think that's a good idea but no I
don't really do that but um I I buy the
like uh ready to go pancakes at the
supermarket o I can't kill them for
real
weak could use it on one of those though
if I wanted
[Music]
to should
I um oh yeah so pancakes and a Nutella
but like a um more a healthier version
of
Nutella and SP feris and starting the
day with that breakfast makes me so
happy every day I me my breakfast I sit
down on my beautiful now fixed working
dining table by the way RBF was
impressed he was like how did you do
that oh wait so confused
uh and and watch on my iPad some
YouTube
[Music]
yeah makes me so happy oh my God can you
stop can you not
[Music]
oh did he just what silence me can I not
move or is that just not
attacking that little
[\h__\h] oh
God you little [\h__\h] I swear to
God oh I can attack just
uh no magic no ST now a hold all
[Music]
wait the only thing he can do from a
distance
is
uh use a stupid stfe
right actually attack for Jaelin from a
distance
[Music]
pretty good pretty good she's going to
lag behind
though I had a poptart or two this
morning watch some vid
listen poptarts is that the breakfast
that makes you happy wouldn't you be
happier with a more
nutritional healthy breakfast
h I think you would
you
[Music]
should if I use Shield gamut I can't
attack
right there's nothing helping but
pancakes and but there's strawberries
and there's helping them Pop-Tarts
probably and tased them
Pop-Tarts po can be warmed up yeah my
more pancakes too I always warm them up
I'm going the pop
spons corn flakes with milks I with milk
I I like that too um but when I eat that
I like to put in some sliced fresh
bananas I think that kind of improves
it it's I said it's a healthier version
of Nutella it's not real
Nutella it's plenty prenty good me and
and Hey My My dinners and so on are
usually
healthy mhm I mean maybe sometimes a
little bit less healthy
but yeah hazelnut spread
basically uh
[Music]
you eat hot dogs for
breakfast
what Dream
well wait one second
guys something great is
happening we're spontaneously changing
the pro the the the the the plant M
[Music]
collab where it wasn't decided what
we're going to do
anyway
[Music]
to Girls
Talk Girls Talk Girls Talk girls talk
[Music]
finally
yeah I was going to get um a background
done for girl talk but I don't think
that will happen now uh we'll just use a
normal background for now but girl let's
go all right weekend is looking fun now
two collabs one with Rea and one with
the girls
[Music]
no I never said M and funa were part of
it I said the M collab will be replaced
by a ghost talk cab
now y it might cry don't cry problem
don't
cry it'll be
fine but yeah happy development y time
is still the same I feel refreshed 3 P.M
EST you ditch M well who who are the
girls of the girl
talk we might might never
know no you will
know don't understood oh you can kill
that one
amazing s is best 87 97 doesn't kill
87 yo if that misses and I'm a little
bit
[\h__\h] should be
fine nothing of
Victory
hey
laughable at least give us a hint
well okay it's m and
FAA it's m and FAA I will endure
oh it was crit noise a [\h__\h] she can't
move
huh walking to fer you're just in
range but I'm scared should I heal
myself instead do I even
have I do have the vulnerary
M we've never guessed
Dragon will kill
her hey how
far Well it can't attacked me from there
that's for sure
[Music]
right but if I put him in front will it
maybe wait I can go that
far leave all your worries behind kfp
might not even heal but attack with her
first
[Music]
tippity tappity
okay is ger collab with you Alex sand do
you like write all of this down or
what how do
you how do you remember all this huh huh
huh you have everything written down
don't
you you're still on top of everything
okay so I can't cannot kill
immediately but hey maybe the kill ax
will crit there's a high chance of
little crit and then maybe we will get
him for one one
hit come on CR come on come on come on
come on come on come on come on come on
come on come on I didn't oh
maybe okay are you watching killer AE so
far A little bit disappointed there
comes the crit I would have liked that
one
[Music]
first we're like dwarves everything is
going on a
list oh my God leave us alone
stop what's he doing now ah he misses
with the silence this time
good
morning good
morning funny funny one aren't you
wait all right taking you
down town
and they lived happily ever after who
who lived his his parents whose son you
have just taken you think they will live
happily ever
after how much does physic heal probably
he's a little bit less than men right in
exchange
for recovering at a distance
[Music]
an
illusion well but still she also says
that to Alive people I guess lesson
[Music]
Me Maybe instead of
a I'll send it to the comboy now maybe
we can pick it up later if we want to I
guess somebody already has that one
anyway I think
iy uh
no those two Mages
man
I have a problem
[Music]
here I'm going to keep on bullying me
but I can walk pretty far trying to like
get away from
them could attempt to kill at least one
of them but I'll need like two
hits all
it oh wait the Archer can take one down
completely but Kara can't do [\h__\h] so
she'll go as far as she can and
hopefully she has
ay yes
oh my God I'm going to run out of vulner
y fly the dragons of
arrows
yeah oh this one works too this one
works
too warp with the use one now ah warping
over ow ow ow hey
warping over my flying wife over there
you mean fail
it D has one to
[Music]
R I got a
w i Flinch creating my FL flont line
front line here
when I just noticed the
pillars didn't notice them before blind
CH
ah okay he doesn't no he has a l I use
by
accident is he going to
die please please don't die
what x means I
I he dies there okay iuse the Ste Ste B
steal bow steel
bow I'm still
alive hey die when they are
killed he was also surprised that he was
still alive you just like me for real
for
real using the antitoxin
now
and she only has the physic
I owe you
one this is the hardest parallel yeah
I've heard it's a struggle
ybyby it's okay I haven't used my rewind
a single time yet and damn that hit
hard okay okay okay now angry with 31%
he really hit me but this is what he
gets
[Music]
back Jade is the wall she literally
is so girl we're going to make our way
back now
H she can't can she not get over the big
walls for
real then I guess I'm going to use the
warpy one
[Music]
I want to hide please don't attack
me re
warp
H wait I thought I could warp her over
to
me a that would be too easy ah
we don't have that
huh godam
it okay then I have to
fly sorry guys tell me again I can't go
over this big wall
right have to go all the way
around damn it all right at Le this part
she'll be able to walk faster
[Music]
tell me
where all right
mhm tough choices
everywhere I wish I could shoot down the
Dr
[Music]
but I can shoot down
this
fabrication engage your MC you could
fill it up again okay I might do that
cuz yeah I fill up for kills
right engage
more although sound like I'm kind of
struggling in this situation right now
I'm
not stressed out or
anything right now I mean I got so many
units here and there's only one enemy
left I'll maybe
engage next turn or so depending on what
direction we go this way or that way
then I might need it but right now I
think I know need that would be like
Overkill let's see how much damage
damage do you do back that's a lot of
damage how do you break this kind of
enemy or is he unbreakable like kimy
Schmid Archer my Archer can't reach the
only one who can't
reach what about dragon versus dragon is
there some resistency no
can't break them wind book
wind what doesn't she carry a wind book
[Music]
no of course
not oh
wait I knew someone could kill him one
hit ah
but it's okay I can heal right after
I can heal right after I can heal right
after I keep on telling myself I can
heal right after it's okay it's okay
it's
okay I'm so sorry
v a battle fit for
brodia got magic plus one
okay
H oh that's a weak
[Music]
heal is her
stronger they're about the same
H okay then I'll use normal
heal and
then maybe another time more
heal Selena is the one who has win I
knew someone had it
oh
okay they said first go here right
okay straight ahead to the Archer
boy oh
oh I can just walk straight up to
perfect range and he can't find back oh
I feel like
um I'm doing like war crimes here exed
by the
emance but from my per
perspective I'm the good
one I'm not the evil one so please
forgive me for my
sins I has no vulnerary I has
VY I thought I gave it
away if not evil why hot are you so
sweet little heel
won't
hurt okay here we
go we are making progress we're in the
middle of this system right now if we
wanted to we could go straight up here
no I guess we
can't but are there like more than one
seals yeah
two maximum two
one third of the way
y need two seals
okay what do we when do we have there a
mage uh not a mage a fist fighter
monk if I go
there they going to come at me but I
think K can take it she's going to be
fine I believe
her abilities oops
I'm in a well we here
yeah Marshall
walk Shield gavet that's what I should
have
done I have not used a single one should
I use it
now I feel like I feel like I I can I
can use one
charge
yeah and in dead I will not get any
damage
[Music]
y I always wanted to use this one and it
comes in the right
moment at the right time at the right
place heck yeah this is the perfect time
to use
it do I really need to have everyone
enter this place though could send some
people to the left side
right no or
not just kind to
like gather everyone in the middle now
cuz I also got to wait for Chloe
[Music]
anyway
okay and then next turn I'll send some
to the left already and then kiaha and K
will just lag behind a little bit for a
[Music]
while
okay let range oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
ow I thought I was safe there uh now the
other one was kind of baited too I won't
falter
W that 15%
crit wa all the people from the right
side are coming after me I should kill
them
first I'm going to help out after all no
that doesn't
help m
M might be time to engage
now let me
see yes yeah I think I'll engage
now what do you think for axe oh oh let
me see how much damage it
does
nothing nothing
he is chain
guarded
oh but does a house just
unite yeah it breaks it right it doesn't
work
then I'll strike you
down I don't play by you rules your
defeat was inevitable
you can call me a cheater or what you
whatever you want
but I'll play this game my
way unfortunately I don't get a kill out
of
[Music]
this okay
yeah all right let's take care of
these ones but uh where are you Chloe
come on we're waiting for you don't let
us do all the
[Music]
work there's a dragon
there
perfect let just move over
here o
o can't do
that no no it wasn't one hit
[Music]
this fight does drag on a
bit oh yeah it
does so
funny now wondering yeah this is what I
was hoping for that if I kill that mob
that's standing there first then I can
stand there and use my Longbow and then
the dragon can't fight back
oh I was thinking connecting the dots
and thinking in layers my brain bra is
working in
[Music]
layers it's like my brain is made up of
an
onion now this sword dude
um oopsy
it will most likely need at least two
people oh yeah this
works going to be baiting the Mage you
kidding
me so but oh right I can combine this I
can stand here and then we're good
[Music]
MH
mhm there we
go it's almost like someone else is
playing this game because kiaba can't
possibly be this smart can
she nothing short of
Victory who has the controller in her
hands is it really k
M no you're the gamer of Ian except she
can
Jers
n
uh should I use the
physic all
right I thought I was done
for so dramatic you're far from being
done for
move you all along o five stats
up okay enemy phase oh yeah I forgot
about this part
[Music]
here can't touch
kiaha all righty o we got a reor m that
helps us walk
back um
[Music]
wait doio should I get rid of some oh
she can't use it anyway
oh
true damn
it damn it
[Music]
okay let's open the
chest what's inside 2,000
gold I deserve more for all this
effort Al I'm getting real hungry oh my
God uh what am I doing
uh what I'm I thought I have to do
something here on the seil do I just
stand there
wait
okay the door's open we should use the
other sigil as well oh more of the floor
is turned to ice tread carefully Divine
One hi
hi oh
[Music]
now now we can move over here let's go
wait the
ice are flying doesn't isn't affected by
it anyway
yeah I don't know how I'm going to get
that shiny thing out
there someone who has the wary thing
when they are around that area close by
right then they could warp out and could
warp back
[Music]
in yeah I know Ivy has
it maybe after this turn
[Music]
okay no no
my always don't they always pick on the
ones who can't fight
[Laughter]
back this was a fair
fight be nice to have m
k for great sacrifice or
what oh they're all coming for me
now Look Who's Talking hey came for
me I gave them a choice move out of the
way
or die
what staffs does she have okay
[Music]
okay wait she's poisoned again wasn't
she poisoned before
already can't be bothered with it oh we
can break
[Music]
him she's been poisoned for a while at
least it's not a do damage oh that would
get me in
trouble so many
units that I
can kill all right I'll take this one
down 6 76 81 96 steel sword
s you put up a good fight do I need to
charge uh
well ain't nobody got time for that let
me see how far we get with this Rew
warp oh all right she's out of here or
should I wait until
they let me see let me see if they need
her for one more
[Music]
round ooh ooh I see the same pattern
again for the
dragon okay okay okay okay I'll
fire
yeah then now I put my Archer
there it's so smooth everything's so
smooth it's just another day at work
one more nice shot I can't believe I did
that believe in yourself have
confidence I'm good level
up Longbow is so op thanks for telling
me to get that
one okay attack co wait
uh wasn't sure I didn't look closely is
that
okay it does look like a compound B
papaya hi
papaya okay I think she can
go she's going to be AFK for a moment
BRB
[Music]
sorry I have barely any tangents today I
used them all
up but as you know I'll go back to Japan
soon so I'll be making more tangents
every day there will be a
tangent cuz I I'll be the camera with go
and Ena and maybe others
[Music]
collecting more Japan webs oh I already
have so many I don't want to be
[Laughter]
[Music]
greedy yeah I've been doing many long
streams that's that's what I was fearing
that's what I why I wanted to keep the
tangent to myself for a while cuz I knew
I would need them eventually oh look at
all those dragons
coming I can take one down from
here
I these dragons be dying like
FES want a b about how energy drink
affected you I saw someone made a clip I
liked it on Twitter it was really
good about
[Music]
yeah maybe I should drink energy drinks
more often If Only They were not that
unhealthy
[Music]
man I would take them more
often why do the helpful things always
got to be unhealthy huh
this a girl eating the T every morning
excuse me you can grant me something at
least the Nutella pancakes won't really
give me a heart attack or I don't know
whatever the energy drinks is destroying
but did she just create that girl thank
you sheez
she took all the work away from
me I guess I have to wait for this one
too silver cart what's that
n select an item to buy 30% off going
tojoy 30% discount at the Army and item
shop what like
forever or just one
time oh
for the rest of the game damn holy [\h__\h]
please ALR he would have died now if the
other one wouldn't have missed wait
there's there's reinforcements
coming I'll be greeted by them if when I
walk back from
here then I'll be greeted by them huh
all right no problem no problem a thank
you
Pandora
nand nand
y thank
[Music]
you I can wipe her to the button or and
just walk back with the rest cuz she can
open up
the chest too I guess I mean it will
take her some turns though
[Music]
M loving this game so far yeah me too me
too I'm getting really hungry
though
I wait why can I not
ah they stabed
[Music]
him now it's kind of hard for
me
oof whatever you
ask you are making me very
angry little
[\h__\h] have I eaten since my breakfast
yeah I right before the stream I had a
almost a full
burrito I made a such a big burrito how
do you need a burrito we been falling
apart I even put like a toothpick on it
and then eventually it just
[Music]
rips that
hurts I think I'll take this
one H 52% he might miss actually never
[Music]
mind now we finish him
off
beautiful are you
watching whoa you doesn't have to go
that far
right in a pan on the edge to seal it
shut you mean when it's already
rolled I feel like I also put way too
many ingredients into the burrito though
it's so
big the thing can barely
close I by the way that was a hello beep
recipe but I upgraded the
recipe smart W oh I should go down
actually oh I could go while I'm waiting
[Music]
here I upgraded the recipe cuz
originally it said um like something
like burrito bowl cuz it was
actually uh without the what do you call
it a to
Tortilla
the pancake thingy the wrap
and and I also added
corn yeah it's a naked burrito and I I
was like yo this kind of
looks it's lacking something so let me
go and buy some
toas and that was
genius like it improves the the dish by
like a million times
[Music]
no no how about
no let me just do this
first chest
open
oh
oh well now I don't really need
that now I is the who's far
away
[Music]
huh can I use it on myself
too it would have been good before when
I needed Chloe to come
back no okay well then come boy
[Music]
okay let's go back to the
middle shielding and on the
pillar so I think we're good cuz the the
dragon is always r attack right probably
going to attack me if a ranged one
so quick regrouping yeah yeah yeah now I
don't need
it okay
kisawa wait if I just stay there he
could still Target
me or would he go for kiaha If I Stay
Away actually let me just go up here
Lu W will be
fine
okay Kwa
[Music]
Kiwa good
girl oh Dragon also went into the
but hold another mess and there's even
more
coming I'm going to not wait for those
though I'm just going to go to the right
side are you going to keep on coming
endlessly or
what
look now the problem
is I might miss no wait it's
100% oh because the flying unit it
doesn't matter
I
guess the pillar doesn't affect the fly
unit I had no choice 10
waves man okay today's
MVPs
are uh
alchrist
mostly yeah I I I'll give the MVP to
alris that's for sure
there's so many
dragons but yeah one Archer was
definitely enough
actually is Dad dying motivated
him it's a pretty
farh but so far I think I got used to
the heart um
difficulty because
I don't know look how smooth
everything's going even here I mean this
is just a really really long map but
it's not like really
difficult do you have the no you
[Music]
don't and just really
good
thanks okay front line and then here
another
one what's
next a
warp wait reor at
warp a staff with space Waring Jason
Ally
ah this one for this one it has to be
ajacent and the other one that we just
had uh a moment ago it doesn't have to
be adjacent
teleport
someone there's so many
okay the other one was like teleport
someone far away to
me
mm but that it has to be to me
right a jent to me I guess
uh that's the way uhhuh uhuh I like it
uhhuh uhhuh that's the way uhuh uhhuh I
like it uhhuh
[Laughter]
uhhuh they they might actually catch up
pretty quickly those guys down there
H but 10 waves I don't want to stay
behind for them
anyway not that I
[Music]
care isn't crony playing fire blin this
week too I think I saw it on her
schedule did she start yet or is she
like starting when is she
starting he was gone but got the
oh no I want to know I want to watch her
a little bit I wonder what Moi is going
to
[Music]
choose for she delayed it for power
what that's not even a legit
reason I thought it might be a reason of
like no perms but I mean we got perms
but what crony we need to talk I thought
you were fire blem fan why are they
laying in for power was simulator
what what what's up with that I have a I
have a cre I have a I have a cream why
in Japanese uh the word for complaint is
Kuru in like Katakana which means it's
like a borrowed word it's not even a
Japanese word why is
it
cream I have a cream
maybe it doesn't come from English maybe
it comes from French or something a
claim a
CL
claim okay it's not quite
complaint using it for claim is actually
yeah more
accurate I never realized I just you
know I just accepted it as a Japanese
word kind
of kind of like that
claim oh my
God some things are just like I don't
know how to explain the other
door you are incredible hi to give this
my
all honestly TIY you making me run
through this whole map so far really
makes a lot of sense cuz you're
Australian and if I wanted to reach you
in AUST Australia it would take me about
this much time to reach you cuz you're
on the other side of the world upside
[Music]
down
yeah realistic it's just
realistic and I don't want to play Power
simulator no lame lame lame lame lame
lame lame lame
lame lame lame lame lame lame lame lame
lame
lame I see like the some charm in it but
lame perms
lost ah don't
die no I have to redo the whole thing
cuz I moved her first is
this
soori here goes our second oh God damn
it I a second uh
rewind that funny
well well that makes everything a bit
more difficult doesn't
it maybe instead
then
stay I don't understand this like from
where is he going to
attack can he walk past his uh Ally here
can you just walk past him and come over
here I thought the map was a
cute can
well one of them I can take as long as
the dragon doesn't come over
right open the
door oh I could probably just lay
opening door yeah but then I'm wasting
another turn for her and I want her to
come back as soon as possible you are
in take his range
I don't
know it just doesn't really help
me don't
understand but I guess it's pretty
far there's like a lot of red
[Music]
a is way better than ZL what the [\h__\h] ZL
doesn't help me at
all okay
uh I'll try to not go too far
then how far can I go
[Music]
uh have to wait anyway I mean not really
I don't really I don't really have to
wait you think he's going to die it'll
be fine
[Music]
that's it already Okay okay here he goes
he goes for a diamond and he misses wow
he had 80% chance of
hitting oh oh okay okay okay we baited
them very good very good very
good now what do we do about you
re warp over here she's like
jumping between all these walls at least
it gives her
[Music]
exp should I CU they're going to catch
up with me anyway next
turn can I do it from here at
least cuz then the axe guys will come
for me
[Music]
man even if you stopped and took a nap
for f years he would still be
you a little shook there
what what does that tell
us are they heavy armor oh they are
wait a second this is it ends here
so I don't have to send all of them
through if there's going to be
continuous backups and I could just
leave one team
behind would leave one Mage here
and
then she always forgets the
story oh someone slept didn't
they the main
character oh just he wait B and Ali are
both slept for thousand
years does every fire BL MC sleep for
Thousand Years or is it just those
two
oh no no I didn't why are they so tired
[Music]
my my brain is starting to stop
working it's been 6 hours but I think
this works my turn I'm starting to uh be
slow in
thinking I am
the was five
oh I I to sleep for a thousand years oh
I would love to sleep for a thousand
years but when I wake up the world will
probably be
dead and so would I then
apocalypse memory le brain
sping you know I was okay with that
little exp uh h be being taken from me
I'm okay I want to give yaka some kills
you know she hasn't really so um how
dangerous is this situation like who
what does she
do also she turned into a dragon
again did it
again we have to get close to her
eventually she's not going to move this
sh is this like magic like a magic uh
skill she comes to me got three life
bars she comes to me but only if I like
walk all the way over here
right who's that Arrow
from oh the first dragon
[Music]
how far do I have to go to bait
her I'm losing my
patience regardless if I bait her okay
well then I'll be
chilling Kur
[Music]
she'll be fine right she'll be
fine ow
[Music]
they don't go for my Archer
interestingly
enough do they know that he's standing
in an avoid tile but wait there's more
wait TI it and come
chy thank you map
Leaf well we'll talk about that another
time
why is she not come huh why did she not
come over
here we CH
there wait who's the one ah you're the
one who has L I was just going to be
like I'm just going to shoot her from a
distance
wait which one going from here from
here if I go here that would be
good or actually why not go
here oh yeah I visited the moon before
[Music]
she came as soon as the door open so I
just hold up by the second
[Music]
button why did she not go after me yet
after the reinforcement stu oh did you
already kill everyone at that point all
the reinforcements
no
problem I need a bit more power over
here but she can't do
[\h__\h] okay okay okay okay okay okay
yeah I might end up baiting with Lynn if
she's not coming out by
[Music]
then it doesn't look like a kill though
I'll
help even with everyone's Powers
combined
ah my
turn to bait the ice
dragon we'll look after this turn now
I'm dealing with
this mess
here so
close cool look at
that one [\h__\h] HP you must be kidding
me wait how much crit
46% but if I don't
[Music]
kill
then
ah
46 just need one more damage one single
damage I've had my eye on
you she did it simple enough girl
girl you had it in you after
all I don't know what to do I don't know
what to do I'll I'll wait one more
turn can't stop winning
[Music]
so what do we do what do we do what do I
do grant me
strength shoot
is it still the same team no this time
it's two Mages and one
Dragon [\h__\h] off
[Applause]
already now I'm going this way now
ah
should there you go there you
go
thanks let's end
this let's end this
already yeah was going to do want free
six woo just going to do the the arrow
BL next turn cuz can't
now okay
oh emblem
do I go for the front one or the back
one I can't kill
[Music]
either said fa it really looks like her
okay watch
this shooting star
Dage was from standing execute
well I don't recall that at
all I could ra
[Music]
Dragon
but yeah that was a bad level up but
that feels like my first really bad
level up
Killa no I'm just going to I guess wait
here
now I
[Music]
guess the reinforcements are annoying
what does his engagement do
again going to wait
understood Ally
boosting okay
maybe I use it next
turn oh
everyone
FY she heals her bunny
[Music]
ow and another round of reinforcements
are you [\h__\h] kidding
[Music]
me it added an extra HP
bar oh my
God how many times don't you do
[Music]
that now they are cornering me from both
sides got to push towards
T TR I to completely ignore the back
door or try
to do something here it's not like
everyone can just walk through here
anyway m
well I think I'm going to start by
[Music]
healing thank
you if I go all the way to the corner
then maybe I'm not in
range I'm going
to uh I'm going to try
to take down the dragon in one
go by
first getting rid of the first stage
people uh 23 to
me that's rough that's really rough
who's the other one with a healing
thingy where's Ivy by the
way a that's Ivy don't
recer Maybe
ah I can't
move oh let me use the lire
then that much
damage who who else
has healing do you have the healing
stuff yeah so like could great deal of
an LSP I could heal
afterwards heal and then the second HP
bar with the bow Is My
Idea dou
[Music]
decoys
doubles but then I can't do my magic
attack that was blocking more than the
enemy I can't
move I'm just going to do what I think
I'm going to be doing Let's see we can
still return
rewind my turn if we don't like the
outcome m m I know I know I know it
hurts I
know a thousand curses upon our
enemy and then one full HP bar all right
no
problem just watch and learn kfp
these are kiaba
tactics what was I going to do
next I
Archer he can he can safely one
shot
oh wait one step
back yeah
yeah that's what I wanted to do I can't
believe I did that
mm and now the path is
free I'm scared
though think I'll save my
engage with one
HP or do I wait again but she's just
going to use another HP bar thingy on
one of them isn't
she and maybe not the MC good
idea should I do the engage
now Jade can Frontline it you sure
there's no space right
[Music]
now she only had one
oh
okay ooh I could kill the first one even
without
[Music]
engaging kind of want to see that
possibility can't even fight back
[Music]
I'm going to do it no time to
waste I have some things to do
afterwards to cook
food oh yeah remember stream tomorrow by
the way I didn't decide what to do
though what are we going to do it's
going to be uh I think a late M stream
what time did I say I would do it
that what you
say more
ironing mean I do have more things to
iron and
Fe 800
p.m. shy level
up for my MC that makes me mad for the
other characters I don't care that much
you for
[Music]
real you
doing a little to the left part two
[Music]
no maybe I'll decide after waking up but
I mean if you guys are up for watch
along I wouldn't
mind but other than
that I we can also do some kind of hand
cam stream but I don't really have
talking topics right now and for hand
cam streams I need talking
topics so does it make sense to engage
now stand down or
perish I don't understand this may prent
first attacks on adjacent
allies when right now he only has
two and I don't think they're going to
be
attacked
right it's like a chain
[Music]
guard just use
it I can only is it want
still yeah okay why I Out Of
Reach
say watch along we have so many choices
for watch along there's so many things I
said I was going to watch I was
wondering do you enjoy being a Divine
dragoni finally I didn't always but now
yes I think I do it taught me what I'm
truly cap why is she a dragon I see I'm
very curious to learn all about you will
you tell me more about yourself do all
emblems have a dragon form I will tell
you all that I
can
goodbye
scared
ouch oh she's she was born
once oh [\h__\h]
nice out Chris he was just in the
perfect position for
that we are in a difficult position now
guys God this could
[Music]
go God Dam it
why why did I do this to
[Music]
myself the only helpful thing here might
be
[Music]
um I might do this and then I move um
alchrist over there then he can take a
shot too and then iron dagger and then
kiaha with engagement and so on that way
even if we're on line we can do some
damage you're not sure why I did this I
was quite expecting to get stuck
here oh he can't move right
now okay but we have um Thunder I think
for
example let me just let me just test
some stuff or or I bring kiaha back
yeah she doesn't die but the thing is
the reinforce reinforcements are
hold ready here
and deal with them
[Music]
too we're probably going to have some
people die
though so Ki moves
back K almost back
which is a vulner to I don't know how
much I can
heal who has a big
heal ah I could heal her from here
[Music]
even yeah yeah I have to kill the main
boss if I just focus on that
[Music]
just a scratch I'm
so unsure he needs healing too he can
heal himself
[Music]
okay heal with chlo and use El axe
uh
Chloe what does she
have but Chloe would have to be right
behind her to do
that I did grab the silver card yet
[Music]
yeah I can move yonaka back but she
would have have been able to do some
damage so that's kind of
[Music]
sad and maybe maybe you can oh no she
can't reach
[Music]
I guess we're doing it this
way that
helps why are we doing it like
[Music]
this not hold maybe do that
after engage attack first and then try
to throw in some Thunder even though
it's just a tiny bit I'll do my best
[Music]
maybe after
that I don't
know don't hold this against me she has
free live
bars that's the golden deer for you okay
okay okay
okay ah
H
uh should I call the
doubles I can't move them though they
might be in the
way does she know what do I know I don't
know if I know
[Music]
yeah it's two
packed this is so [\h__\h] so
[\h__\h] so [\h__\h]
what do you mean b do you mean his bow
he can't
[Music]
move I don't know what to do y bot maybe
have to
rewind no more a that's the golden deer
for
you what what why did she get us into
attack first anyway TI was attacking
us what that's the golden there for you
H she just got right off that one HP bar
as if it was nothing
T I was wondering yeah that's the only
real explanation that she used a smash
weapon and that's why I got
first oh can't believe it I thought we
would like have so many problems right
now but look
[Music]
oh my God wait 67% is kind of low okay
if it fails I
[Laughter]
rewind but wait before I do
that I'll protect you
um let me get some
exp ah
uh go here
[Music]
I'm here greedy greeny no oh okay that's
fine wait that's not fine die all right
I'll finish him off with someone else
yeah comat art
still that's it I can do that
[Music]
too oh that might not be so good if she
misses she be fine there you go a twist
ending
what's with all these shitty level UPS
now
huh uh any
other no okay the rest is not really in
reach so I'm going to do it now it's
time
[Music]
unless just going to do this too
we got to e spe for for every for every
attack after
all want to make the most out of
it
byebye raging Storm atrocity Fallen star
what's our
choice 67 wait these are also
[Music]
this one's
82% this one's more certain okay
okay welcome to the T
TIY this [\h__\h] really took me 3 hours or
what how long did it take
me when did I start this what what
what's with these level UPS what the f
[\h__\h] well imagine if we didn't have the
DLC we wouldn't get these levels ups at
all so I guess we'll just see it as an
extra 25 turns 2 hours 45
[Laughter]
minutes I better have been worth it wow
that was incredible I tried my very best
but you still won bloody helmet you
showed me your true Essence as well even
in
you were warm and kind I would be glad
to help you I quite look forward to
working together thank you Tiki it's
very reassuring to have you on our side
does she like turn into a dragon when I
use hered to hear you say so oh and it's
not just me my bracelet friends are here
as well I'm sure they would be happy to
help bracelet friends are even more
bracelet emblems here in Elios yes we
just arrived recently what I'll tell you
where they
so she turns into a dragon I do believe
they are all sleeping she turns me into
Dragon they having good dreams I used to
have terrible nightmares about turning
into a beast and hurting people oh
that's exactly what's going to happen
been awful I'm so sorry we going to hurt
bad people though together but it's
better now I don't have those scary
dreams anymore don't worry now that time
with you I think my dreams will only be
happy ones that's why I'm so grateful
not to be alone I want to become friends
with all your friends she reminds me so
much of to get along well with
everyone I cannot wait to meet them it's
not only the Australian accent but that
probably is not
helping I mean it is
helping and the whole like happy
cheerful attitude and I don't know the
things she says man mm Tiki has powerful
draconic attacks and can grant Divine
protection to her allies the engageed
weapon breath deals damage to a f in an
area that and changes based on on the
unit typ this is an AOE finally
AOE the engaged skill draconic form
turns the unit into a dragon greatly
raising stats wow the engage attack
divine blessing grants an ally and the
Revival
Stone which they consumed to
recover oh
am
Dragon it's incredible on Jade should I
give it to Jade cuz I don't mind like
giving this to someone else not
kiaha everybody needs a an emblem ring
it say it's more of a British accent are
you sure I are you sure are you sure
it's incredible for everyone
[Music]
y you were a pain in the ass Ticky wow
you're Al so strong that was impressive
I'm excited with friends K I guess me
too let's
see I got all the items on the map too I
got all the I got the card
Beres cat oh my God it's a Siamese
cat Okay adopted it's not
fair it's not
[Music]
fair yeah 30% on everything forever
is that's quite
something it's definitely worth
it hi what are you guys doing here I
didn't bring you along
[Music]
so uh I guess after this I'll quickly
try to read some super
chats and
then I will uh cook
something tomorrow Members Only
oh this one I can
[Music]
adop okay I got it
all you came too late welcome to the
stream yeah I'm done it took ages you
came very late because uh it's been 6
and a half hours
but
no I have five dogs now
y to
theil you should rest
more thank
you thank you so considerate
[Music]
okay I will leave all the like extra
stuff for next
time I'm going to save now
30 hours
becomes oh 30
hours and do off stream that's right
maybe I will and next fire BL stream
sometime next
week this week I am
done G
[Music]
long game is
long
okay
[Music]
office
okay where am
I you may ask
yourself I also ask
myself there I am
thanks for watching for so many hours
guys Fire Emblem is fun it's been
getting much smoother I think last time
I made more mistakes for some reason but
yeah the looks of it I have an
interesting V to catch up to well I mean
I didn't have many tangents today but I
think I did a good job fighting today
you have been doing very well in the
games thank you compared to First stream
thank
you tal Kima action I know what that's a
reference to thanks to
P hyp for girl
Yay good that FAA didn't already like
set everything in stone for her week and
like busy or so no it works out yeah
yeah y yay you guys hear the fire BL be
gim seeing your playr helps me plan mine
[Music]
really like this so free hous is
more it's hard to say cuz free houses is
so long ago and then everything was
still so new to me the whole genre and
so I think I was struggling more in free
houses
but I can't say I liked it less because
of
[Music]
that that's difficult question you know
was what else was long ago christas that
was just like 5 days ago what are you
talking
about you have no grasp of
reality yeah it's too soon to answer
have you side the game of M oh you
missed that M collab stream was
replaced it is now still a m collab
stream but also a funa collab stream cuz
we're doing girls talk because these are
the members I chose for girls
CL at the same time though and still my
[Music]
channel okay so I read until the point
of the end of the unarchived Cal stream
right
[Music]
okay so next is this
one by the way um I want to do girl talk
like more than once but
um I might like have different members
here and there I'm not saying that these
are like set and
stone maybe I'll switch it around every
now and then
[Music]
yes perfect girls podcast girls
talk yeah good I could be on it to yeah
I think
she's she has some girliness about her
and actually you know when you first
think of cie you maybe don't think of
girliness but I think we all know she
has girl girly things about her she's
very girly about her hair and her
nails she's um she very cute in terms of
other things
too maybe her fashion isn't girly but uh
I feel like on the outside she's not uh
oh I mean except you know you know hair
and nails so
but her Fashion Is Everything But girly
although she can be girly she I saw her
wearing um more of a like a girly dress
before
yeah I need to like look into her closet
someday and see like how many like you
know cool rapper clothes she has
versus cute
dresses how many
M boyish
[Music]
clothes white pants or
whatever but even her like her her like
for example her 3D like rapper
outfit I wouldn't say that's girly but
that's like cool
edgy it's very Charming too I want to
see myself and cloes like that too
wardrobe
review holoc clauset sequel to Hol
yeah you know that comes with some
problems I don't feel I don't think many
people many members would want to
participate in
that the insides of a bag are still
acceptable
but the insides of a
closet h of fridge is better yeah
maybe you're going to be shocked though
but actually think Hol of fridge might
be really funny cuz we can like
see which girls cook and which don't
probably a lot of them are not
cooking a lot of them I I saw into I
looked into the fridge uh for example
Mar
Senpai Mar senpai's fridge was like 50%
water
[Music]
bottles
and
H I forgot what the other stuff was but
it was nothing really edible
[Music]
maybe just yeah it was mostly air but
from if if 100% is whatever is inside
then 50% was water bottles a lot of
water got to stay hydrated yeah but like
there was nothing edible in there part
of OBC after all that's not an argument
now I asked her if she had some tea and
I thought you know everybody would have
tea at home especially in a tea loving
country like Japan but she was like tea
and she was looking around rumaging
around apparently she really doesn't
have much tea but the one tea that she
found was the I maybe said this before
but was the one that she got from uh F
Senai I think other members probably
have lots of tea
around but M Zea had like no tea the
only one that she had was the one that
she got from someone else as a
gift whatever floats her boat yeah she
doesn't drink uh tea herself she's not a
tea kind of
person okay let's read Super Chat cuz
like oh my God Tiki took me so long man
Che Monkey D iie clipping d
thank you for the
[Music]
red thank you you know what ta you
should send a red and a blue one so that
you can send uh an Al alar super
chat cosplaying through super
chats kak
unknown D for the
pinky colate Super Chat yeah I really
wish I could stay up and watch this but
I'm feeling sick right now so I don't
think I can but I hope you have fun T
I'll definitely catch up with the vaud
when I wake up oh no I know what's going
on recently like the ones who always
catch my streams
24/7 are having issues catching my
streams not feeling while or being busy
with work or I'm fine now that's good
I'm happy
thankfully it was nothing serious
huh oh my God thank you thank you thank
you for being here again make sure to
stay healthy eat your vitamins and drink
water and sleep lot okay unknown I know
I'm ra uh robbing you from sleeping by
streaming so much at your
nighttime I hope I'm not the reason
you're feeling sick or we feeling sick
Garden par D
soon come on Garden par that's a waste
of a
nomination I picked you as the best FPS
streamer after seeing the clip of your
death Loop
[Music]
game
and
and what a waste put my nomination
somewhere else Mo dun smle stream dance
dun thank you oh glad you like my for
blood cover sir 956
danak Mr kasic Dan Mr kasic again dun
the social artist face with pinky I
start laughing when I hear marf talk
because I'm a I'm playing a game about a
certain wall crawler where I listening
to the
stream uhuh marf and PP share the same
voice actress actor w
crawler also did I miss why you switch
to the English Pas yeah it's because I
know that a lot of my viewers watch me
or listen to me rather than watch to me
ah Spider-Man oh they have the same VA
what that's
funny I switched because so that more
people could enjoy it without having to
look at the
screen
basically and I mean I got used to the
voices by now so it's Nots so bad and
then the one that I didn't like so much
I'm not using anyway
H yeah I think all the others are using
Japanese dub
right don't know what cron is going to
use though boohoo 723 Dan dog Street
Dan would you pat a cat every day for
1,000 bucks a day you mean I have to pay
but the cat will run away
someday but who's receiving the money
well would you two ice cubes every 3
hours every day for th000 bucks a day
but you have infinite ice
cubes who's receiving the money am I
paying them or am I
receiving I can't solve this riddle dog
Street
sorry
Peter
CH
artistar
orar orar Max thank you velv
Nim Riley do charm thank you for the
pinky hi Fire Emblem has been one of my
favorite series since the parf of
Radiance recently I haven't found time
to enjoy jrpgs but I have also been
playing engaged while you stream it oh
thanks for helping me enjoy fire BL
you're welcome we're playing together
just imagine me sitting to next to
you yeah always uh try your best to stay
a little bit ahead of me maybe or or
right where I am so that you don't have
to miss my streams because of sport
alert
okay hope you can stay up to date with
me thank you for the support D oh wait
that wasn't a pinky didn't I say thank
you for the pinky it was an orange one I
think it confused me because then the
profile picture is
pink well you got your um your Super
Chat read properly
anyway I did
huh Le pet d so yours is not leave
righton Dragon Days thanks for the big
red Super Chat hey boss I got a raise at
work and just wanted to share some with
you I already saw that thank
you yeah working hard pays off everybody
take take Dragon days as an
example going to work hard going to work
hard good job
respect thank you for the big big big
support D I hope you're enjoying my
streams hope you're having a lovely time
here thank sh for being part of
kfp thank
sh yeah work is hopefully treating you
well I wish you the best Nathan cotton
thanks for the pinky glad I could make
it for anyone of another fire BL stream
D awesome what should I eat for dinner m
burger burger yes Burger cuz I want
Burger now I wish I could eat it so that
I can feel like I ate
it instead of me Nathan are you here now
Nathan or order
burger order
burger I just finished some burger
burger
yum I don't see Nathan
here
Thom
Le than thank you I'm excited to hear
about the album plans your music and
performances are my favorite cont in h
life it's been a long time coming and I
can't wait to hear what you come I can't
wait to hear what you come up with f
thank you
oh yeah yeah I think all the kfps will
love it what comes out of it that's for
sure Chris m a d for the pinky good
progress today Teno if you want more F
there's always a gba GBA games that are
on the Wii U shop closing soon get what
you can I feel like people have been
told telling me for a year now that the
Wii U shop is closing
soon but please make sure to tell me
like maybe in the free day countdown
that would be helpful I think then I can
really think about whether or not I want
something or
not March 27 okay that's so plenty of
time tell me three days before and then
two days before and then one day before
D take
47 oh wait that's a different stream y
I'll do the hand cam ones then
too yay best stream ever
thumbnail kind of lame though I mean the
font I don't know man what I'm doing
there I was so tired when I made this
thumbnail just want to get it behind
me uh panopticon says K does course ches
truly the idle content we've been
waiting for thank you based fire BB
sorry I can't make it but enjoy use
aluminum foil to get better press ah I
think I've heard about that before but I
think I'm like too
too traumatized for aluminum
foil I never saw someone using aluminum
foil though for
ironing interesting I ran out of
aluminum foil though maybe another
time take Monkey
[Music]
D invad happy belated birthday it's my
birthday so I thought why not share the
joy a bit around thanks for were two
years of great content boss and
hopefully to many more a you're welcome
you're welcome thanks for supporting me
happy belated birthday not that belated
AC was just yesterday
[Music]
congratulations I hope your birthday was
good I wish you much health and
happiness iron Ma and M when I'm in
Japan soon again might be tough again
for EU viewers but uh you'll get through
it might have to be B gang for a while
hope you forgive me Moonlight Dark Spar
Moonlight Dark Spar
P
dereo guy a Christian wee V
fashion Ro thanks for the pinky
K let's
say that ba offers to make it so that
smoothie and chers will live longer the
catch is that from now on whenever you
kiss them GAA or Ena will also feel a
sensation of being kissed will they
understand if you accept face
off I think Ena will be fine with
it I think GAA would
also eventually like I mean understand
if she if I tell her what it's for it's
for a greater
CA but I think Ena would be less
bothered by it than
gura
dark Niki K shees
the winter Moon
D
[Music]
Tre I agree tree bobber for the sake of
streaming content clippable content I
should have
burned at least one piece of clothing
shouldn't
I
ssrb py thanks for the red super chat
than
oh oh it's my birthday in 5 days it's
such a sad
reality
no wait there something Korean there
too oh wait it's not
[Music]
Korean I understand I I am a phoenix but
I I can relate you know I I get
you but I don't know how old you are but
oh hi
what are you
[Music]
doing
yeah with getting older some things
maybe you know more depressing but other
things are still opening up to you or
you know new adventures
[Music]
await so make the most out of it make
the most out of every year let's try to
enjoy life
okay m is making herself comfortable on
my iron clothes that I put on the bean
bag so she's like why is there no space
for me now what's going on cuz the iron
is also on the bean bag okay I should
probably put that away
later anyway youbody I will not say
happy birthday yet because it's too
early
okay I will I will say happy
bir uh-huh you get the rest of it later
I'm holding the rest of it uh hostage
Happy
Bird Happy
Bird
girl Garden Park thank you UF mod
Nicholas
Jag a
that's
[Music]
sweet I hope your friend can feel happy
again and move on and and maybe get a
new cat
eventually the gamer crate
D andert dun elite elite Blaze
danan that's someone that used to fold
Pick Pack work apparel this triggers me
thank you tel you're welcome
[Music]
Leo Phoenix than for the
pinky wake up and watch kiaha she's
screaming as her units get taken out in
fire blim night time now it's a hand cam
stream am is opening Animal Crossing
amiibo cards oh is that what she was
doing what a member stream or what time
for sleep but first more kilala she's
screaming like aelia from
[Music]
bloodborne what
she did in her phone call
stream I'm missing so much of am these
days cuz I'm like sleeping early I
guess when did she do a phone call
stream is that
unarchived n
[Music]
YouTube YouTube where the [\h__\h] do I see
oh
God where's
my YouTube so confusing I go on the main
page and I can't find where I see the my
subscribe uh
channels overie
[Music]
There It Is Ring Ring pick up the
phone did I change something
again I mean you know the channels are
on the left side but it's
like not not what I'm looking
for oh
well um well Leo Phoenix you seem like
you are subscribed to just the right
people I'm in
kiaha good taste
thanks for supporting
[Music]
USAC
as thank
you I've always been Ving but I'm able
to watch you today just want to say I
missed you so much although I've not
been abiding to Hash woke hash what have
you been doing you'll always be my
oi oh thank you what have you been doing
where are you H you didn't even have to
tell me that but you did so honest man
too honest for your own
good thank you do for saying
hi thanks for watching the
V jeffar thanks for the pinky got my
ticket for for Fest oh yeah that that
one got me hyped at first and then I
realized you meant just the streaming
ticket but that's cool too thank
you need you guys to watch the stream
too especially if you can't come to the
venue please
putting in a lot of work this
time thank you excited to see tenu on
stage again let's
go I'm excited too we should do uh uh uh
uh memb only rewatch
again after the
thing I think we did that last year
let's do it
again so k
[Music]
and that's
it okay all that left is the ones from
today it
seems but I'm going to go
now h
[Music]
and reservation for tomorrow going up
tomorrow
and go get that Ki cooking yeah I can't
promise I'm going to look at the
expiration dates and going to make
excuses for myself but probably at least
one I need to cook today probably
so
[Music]
L I don't know what we're watching yet I
might do a community post when I wake up
in
case I don't know what to
choose yeah be a watch long
tomorrow it might be yeah it might be
hope it's
okay all right
I'm going to go now thank you guys so
much I have fun today even though you
know no tangents but game was a lot of
fun today h going
smoothly halfway through the game maybe
roughly we did Ticky so that's some
extra work
there you make recommendations yeah but
I already have so many recommendations
that I have to go
through you didn't really want today
thank
you thanks stream no thank you had a
great time watching thank you thanks for
thank you thanks for nice stream thank
you enjoy CH but not everything needs to
be time thank
you I said you did good thank
you just have gotten great at the
game the other gamers are finally
acknowledging me as one of their own and
are adding me to their pack oh my
God thank you
m i was a true gamer today thank you I
know enjoy your food thank you I hope
the food will enjoy me
[Music]
too so I'll be the alpha gamer
yeah you seriously did well in the game
no
stop more more no just
kidding what
your family had group that World of
Warcraft sessions you're more than a
certified
gamer I wish you could see my eyebrows
now you can see them a little
bit so
covered yeah H still
[Music]
here I can't say Hood's name normally
now it's just
[Music]
toally
okay byee
[Music]