foreign
hiya Darlings this is hello love English
advents devilish Diva the one and only
narissa Raven craft
hello hello
how are we doing
uh how we doing everybody
you're doing well having a good time
chilling
not chilling let me turn up the game
volume it looks a little quiet uh let me
just bump it up by like 10.
this is that hopefully better
hi yeah Darlings how are we doing it's a
little early in the morning for me
a lot of early in the morning for me
but that's okay
um that's that's quite all right
um
how are we there there they no one's
abandoning me
um well anyways the point is we want to
go through uh the character
customization so we've all already done
it
but I'm just gonna show you my choices
and talk about them
so uh you can see this is what we look
like for this run uh I don't know
anything I've never played a previous
Boulder gate game I've not played this
one before so this is my first time
as you can see uh she's very cute I
really like how she came out uh I picked
this sub race uh I don't know
I don't know what any of this means
so please don't ask me
um yeah she she looks just like me just
like me for real for real
um we picked Bard class now I actually
was kind of conflicted I I actually
really wanted to go cleric
um because I'll be honest I have a thing
for being able to heal people it's just
like it's my thing you know
um but I I can't uh I well it's not that
I can't uh we I picked it when uh Kyoto
Senpai wanted to go clear it but I think
she changed she changed her she changed
her class so I'm gonna be a Bard because
I got too attached to my liar which is
the instrument I'm going with but
um
can can trips
a can trip I picked uh a vicious mockery
and true strike and I'll figure out how
to use them
later
I picked charm person because I like to
think I'm quite charming and capable of
a Charming you guys sometimes
uh
and then healing healing word a true
true strike is bad okay well then you
guys are gonna have to help me pick
something else
okay what's actually good then
because uh sometimes you guys have a
tendency to you know troll a little I
had friends originally
but I they fixed true strike yeah I I
heard it's it's good
it's good
minor you guys
um
[Music]
true strike is useful I I think I'm
gonna stick I think I'm gonna stick with
what I what I have I'm sorry
oh it's it's too late to change it now
um spells I have fairy fire Tasha's
hideous laughter healing word and charm
person
um I'm starting with a liar
because I like the sound of it I think I
still need to up the game volume it
still looks really quiet for some reason
let me just up it a little bit more
for you guys
hopefully that's better it's probably
still a bit quiet but I like this song
it's good
why is it so quiet no matter how much I
turn it up
okay 50 50.
surely
flying was good before well is this
volume good too
is this is this volume all so good
okay
um well see a lot of people the thing is
we're trying to be a bit balanced
everyone can already talk to animals
anyway I gotta move on we gotta unmute
soon I went ahead and picked charlatan
uh it was either that or urchin and I
didn't like the idea of being an urchin
that I don't know why that just kind of
made me feel uh not so good and these
are my ability stats
um
we're just being we're keeping it simple
she's narissa
so
um
finally found your horn no
there's no option to have a cracked horn
in game
and then we have the guardian character
so I tried to kind of make like a
I just I made a male version but then I
wanted the color scheme to be a bit
different so I changed it I changed it
up
um I can't change his outfit so I'm
gonna go ahead
and unmute so that when everyone else
starts pouring in
they do too and you can hear everyone
50 volume and
yeah blue is he single I think so I
don't know he's my guardian
oh man it's baller's time this is the
gang
the store let's go oh I gotta turn you
down Cali keep talking we waited we did
a big old Mario
yeah hello how are you okay
I have to ask you things Yes actually
this is good maybe you know because when
we were creating characters yesterday
people said it might be good you know to
like balance out everything so that we
are have ever like you know uh recover
everything you know what I mean yeah
yeah and then they told me people they
told me uh just now that I shouldn't go
with Mage breaker because true strike
sucks well they said they kept saying
that to me too but then other people
said that true strike is fixed now and
then they fixed it so I fixed it
yeah
what was wrong about true strike uh I
don't know I don't know too much about
it I think it's hard too because it's
just like everyone always has their own
play style and things that they like and
dislike
um
uh I don't know is it is it possible
true strike sucks
[Laughter]
let me just ask you people one thing
yeah did we say somebody is gonna have
investigation as their thing or uh let's
see if you guys look at your abilities
and look at your proficiencies what do
you have because we should cover our
bases okay yes
let's do that all right uh I'll go first
I'll go first okay so I'm playing a
barbarian
um as like my class I'm a huge huge half
orc
um Outlander and my abilities I have
really high strengths 17 strengths uh
dexterity is pretty good 13.
Constitution is 14. uh stamina and
physical endurance of course because I'm
big and girthy uh intelligence nine
because I'm just not very smart uh
wisdom wisdom is pretty good smile to me
than me too
I mean you're not that stupid it
wouldn't let me put it into other things
so this is how it has to be Charisma is
uh is 10
um like it's it's like how is
Shrek smarter than my house
don't call her that her name is not true
okay get it straight first of all
um but yeah I guess I can kind of tank
because I have high Constitution as well
um and then I have plus two bonus to
strength one plus one bonus to
Constitution uh my skills in particular
I've got plus five to Athletics which is
really good
um you know most oh that's good I have a
negative one on Athletics Good Luck
running away
um and then animal handling plus three
oh what's three
um and then Insight plus one medicine
plus one perception plus with survival
plus three good Survivor I'm pretty
intimidating so I've got plus two there
um yeah that's what I'm good at where do
you have all these weird stats I'm so
confused um if you go to abilities and
skill proficiencies and you can hit
change and you can see what you have oh
okay yeah
it's okay I can handle a lot of weapons
so Cali what's your strongest points
then in ability in skills skills uh
let's see so the highest my highest role
is Athletics
um
well I don't know my Athletics is plus
five
um okay let's see and then survival plus
three animal handling plus three
okay I'm strong
um
what was that
but
alrighty what's
up
uh 12. okay well you can't beat me in
strength so an arm wrestling match
you're gonna suffer anyway continue
onward your turn your turn
well I don't really know if I should
change any of this um you don't have to
so just read it off okay we're right now
um
uh stealth is plus five
[Music]
oh that's good yeah
um another strong one is animal handling
inside both a plus four perceptionist
plus four survival is plus four
um I don't know what do you want to know
people should I tell you my weak points
too then we can cover those or so
yeah sure
um
and weak in history
and religion oh yeah we wanted someone
to cover religion and history huh oh I
have plus one in history I have negative
one oh no I have negative one in history
I have plus one in religion okay
okay well we don't have to cover
everything I guess but
um okay and then yeah basically my
question was if it's if it makes sense
to go in uh you know bounty hunter that
gains me Proficiency in investigation do
we have anybody else who has Proficiency
in the investigation because of yes then
I won't do it I have a negative one in
investigation Okay negative one an
investigation oh okay so go ahead go for
it go okay it will only bring me to plus
one but okay
then then I'll just say with what I have
now uh yeah I think it will be fine what
does narista focus on uh well I'll read
my downsides first with all the other
skills I don't have so my Athletics is
minus one aerobatics plus two sleight of
hand plus four stealth plus two Arcana
plus one history plus one investigation
plus one nature and religion plus one
animal handling zero inside zero
medicine zero perception survival zero
deception plus five and then
invitation and performance and
persuasion all plus five but then
strength is eight the dexterity is plus
15. Constitution is plus 13.
intelligence is plus 12 so I'm smarter
than all of you wisdom
[Laughter]
wait does does anybody have deception on
a decent amount because me and there is
around zero
um
[Music]
I feel like maybe well maybe you could
instead choose to rule persuasion or
intimidation instead of deception yeah
can we choose that zero it depends it'll
give you multiple it'll give you
multiple like dialogue choices and you
can choose what you want to roll on yeah
I'll press five in my deception too oh
so oh you're the charismatic one yeah
wait you have plus five interception
well then there was something else that
I heard was Zero yeah okay okay cool oh
cool do we have persuade persuasion
covered by someone yes I have plus five
persuasive okay good good good me and
Bieber will do the persuading yeah we'll
do the talking I think both of us uh
scale on Charisma so we will be the
razors you guys am I the talking we do
the killing yes yeah the only stealthy
one well I'll kill two but yeah yeah
it's good to do both oh yeah you're also
healer right Bijou
I am swapping to sorcerer I'm only going
to cleric for about two levels and then
I'm swapping to Source where uh for
extreme magical violence
um I do have heels and Marissa should
have heels as well as Bard so we should
be okay just have some potions with you
well then I really didn't need to be a
Healer okay good good
yeah uh did everybody show everything
off on stream then yes wow and they're
Guardians oh wait I forgot to tell the
mine
the what my my thing right yeah you
haven't introduced your character yet
yeah
Google yeah okay hi
they forgot about me it's okay
[Music]
yeah I'm
not cleric
um strength is nine backstroke uh Dex is
13 Constitution 13 intelligence eight
I'm not very smart or strong but I have
Charisma and that's all that matters
um and also wisdom is 15. here's my 17
and then my proficiency
uh I got persuasion plus five
performance plus three intimidation I'm
very intimidating plus three deception
plus three survival plus two perception
plus two minus and plus four inside plus
four and we're handling plus two
religion plus one and then nature
investigation history Arcana all
negative one but I got still flight of
hand alphabetics and uh yeah what's my
chance yeah there you go
I can't
uh
oh they're telling me to add one
Constitution but I can't
don't do it yeah you have to take away
from something else
but the plus is grayed out even when I
have one ability Point extra I do I wait
like this okay
wait what but it still has no no where
was that where did uh
[Music]
now I don't know where my bonuses were
fine it's okay if you take a picture and
put it in the group chat last night wait
I did have a video go check real quick
it's okay thank you for the reminder
it's okay no need to panic we have each
other yeah no worries we got your back
for good but they really want me to have
more Constitution
I've got the constitution for the group
oh wait now the picture I think was of
something else
[Music]
now I don't know what to do okay hold on
well I think we just have the
recommended because we didn't really set
them right
hmm
so you can probably agree oh it was okay
okay okay you keep recommended yeah
okay okay we can start then maybe cool
all right
so we're gonna like RP as our as our
characters
but yeah I think we're all just us
except for you yeah oh yeah
wait was it a lot easier how's
everyone's Guardian
oh yeah we make a sexy a sexy love
interest or I already showed it off but
mine is my mom yeah mine is just me
grown up
not just a random a random that I made
yeah mine is literally just the older
version hello bearded lady
hello bearded lady let's go all right
are we ready to get started yeah I guess
yeah Adventure four Adventure fourth
all right here we go
what's gonna happen look oh
I don't like that guys
you cracking oh uh David Jones yeah yeah
yeah yeah baby John yeah
wow he's got alien feet
Taco it's Taco Time
that's a single escalator in the game
ask what's happening
[Music]
over the world
we're on a big ship yeah it's so cool
yes I think I missed the first one let's
see yeah we are on that ship
we don't like it there though we were
there against our will okay because that
looks very evil that yeah
yeah we did not choose this life
the rendering is great on that that man
no right really high quality Graphics
particle
grip strength man
ah
I don't know where the world's all over
again oh they're getting captured I
thought they were getting disintegrated
hello
let's go
well technically they're not dying
they're getting teleported
the goal the calvary is here I want to
ride a dragon like that same what the
[Laughter]
scream
ing why do they do they have dragons
they're the targaryens obviously oh my
God they're not blonde though it's fine
let's go I guess oh the other the other
ones weren't blonde right yeah yeah
[Music]
all right well cable management
let's blow this Popsicle stand boy
chat is the audio and the visual is fine
is it lagging or anything
it's pretty loud yeah I had to turn it
down it was so crazy so loud oh good
nice I think you'll turn down when we
exit the cutscene
um
are the dragon people here to save us
specifically or to save all everybody
no that's not my character okay
she's always angry all the time yeah
she's kind of cool though kind of based
your character still seem much more
stance outfit than that one even with
Kelly oh yeah when I checked and she's a
star moriope is a star she knows it
wow
[Music]
wow Safe People Dragon people hate
tentacle people oh we're waking up
good morning it was slimy
we will not be joining forces I'm sorry
you're going straight to the camp but it
was nice to see you anyway
beautiful rendered and also whoa excuse
me
I like that
you're like what nothing that was not
enough but
it's the number three yeah like Baldur's
Gate
immediately
yeah we got wormed yeah you got worms in
your head
private dialogue off
leave it oh don't don't check it don't
check private dialogue all right it's
off okay keep it oh there I go pretty
[Music]
yeah I look great
I look awesome looking real good here
let me oh we're all together
so let's freaking go okay
[Music]
playing with like a much like not wider
screen
if you guys don't mind I'm very going
I'm going to very quickly turn my
settings to best or extremely good
instead of ultra just a moment please
yeah you want to see Cali face
let's take a look at Cal you can still
mix oops let me really quickly change
the video to not be ultra how how do we
do that
Could you um if you go to settings you
got to press the start button
for me and then go to settings okay
wow well we have a lot of hair
who
mean Cali
nice sisters yeah it's a workout because
you'll eat me later
or the genitals you'll eat me later no
none of the yeah I get to throw you
later on why aren't the genitals why the
genitals what do you mean the genitals
because them off from the beginning of
the game but apparently it's not really
turned off so I need to turn them off
we're at Agenda oh go to settings it's
probably instead and said careful
okay okay uh maybe I checked it instead
of unchecking it yeah we're all scared
what about cinematic genitals
probably turn that off too
yeah okay is it an accessibility
yeah in gameplay and then scroll down a
little bit actually you shouldn't even
see it
nudity off share private moments off
yeah none of you guys are getting my
private moments
none of mine are checked so I think
we're good you're going for the demon
lady I wanted to go for the demon lady
too bad she's so cool
we can fight for her you can have the
best the bear I thought you wanted the
bear wait you were you were so excited
you were so excited about the bear what
are you talking about okay look the bear
is cool all right don't get me wrong but
look should we turn off karmic dice
avoids failure streaks while keeping the
results mostly random no that feels like
a good thing to have on
right Dynamic crowds
say it again
uh I would just have it off turn it off
they say off yeah off off off okay
wow are we ready wait wait sorry I'm
just trying to turn down some things no
problem I'm turning everything down to
like medium and low or medium yeah
you know what medium is good
medium's good actually
it's better than whatever I was playing
on the other computer I don't know how
to do anything by the way well but
nerissa oh same I don't know what the
hell's what's going on okay Bieber and
Cali you will have to like uh tell us
everything sorry yeah
I know a little bit that's about it I
know a little bit too
just a little mm-hmm
okay wow it's so pretty though the game
is pretty yeah yeah it's very very
detailed oh we're moving I love how you
move like you do in League of Legends I
thought that it was gonna be like I
could play with the controller oh yes
you're the league player where's the
karmic dice by the way uh I don't know
hey Chad where's karmic dice
I hear it also on the first one gameplay
so we're turning it off right yeah they
say turn it off okay
I should look for that and then wait
size is a league player yeah I like
League are you ever gonna play those
kind of games on stream uh it's kind of
hard because they're more fun if you
have more people to play with but some
people just don't like want to try it at
all which is understandable but I feel
like you would be filling a niche
because no other Ian I think is playing
those that genre on stream I'm not good
though they make it bigger
I might try it I want to do DOTA two two
because I haven't but I I'm more
familiar with League than I am DOTA it's
been a really long time wide look at uh
whoa It's shaking why is it so wide
why whoa whoa whoa whoa I think I need
to change
the solution to not be white and then we
can start and we can start aspect ratio
gotta change the aspect ratio
this is called sphincter I don't like
that
I don't know why not well I mean we're
in a thing we're we're in it's the wrong
way
you hurt me look you can hear you can
heal there's a healing right here
all right
she wants to kill us off
huh
avoid failure oh okay anyway back to the
game
[Music]
you just go through it or do we have to
like yeah go through this thing yeah go
through this
what I know it's gross what you have too
oh
okay come up here come up here
well I need to get used to those
controls okay get another platform oh
yeah you got it okay
okay is that you someone go talk to that
person right now
we'll drop
Charisma people hey get it done and then
I'll loot them afterwards who is he
oh no he looks dead listen no he's still
alive barely
right now yes
yum yum
ew
freeze
yeah
[Music]
those are the yummies
turn the music up uh
is it important what I say
whatever you want what would your
character say yeah
um
yeah maybe that's so high-res
the high-res brain
I like your face
you look so you look so like disgusted
[Music]
no don't destroy the brain it's good
it's good let's ask more
any memories
okay
oh okay I see you guys I'll fix it in a
moment
let's
Rock them no before we destroy it we
have to you know cover all our what's
the plan
yeah what if it comes out and hurts you
oh yes free free the brain it sounds
pretty nice it sounds it sounds nice it
does sound very nice
it's nice to us it's a nice little brain
well my strongest one would be the
dexterity one yeah I say I say go for
the next question
and we prized the brain from the soul
brother
I will I will do that let's take a look
good skill checks some dialogue options
require skill check a dice roll at most
meet or exceed a target number your
character skills add a bonuses right
okay okay
good luck
yeah is that good hold on you guys
yeah nice nice nice oh it has to be
minimum 10 right
yep then we grabbed it or if it matches
it it's fine
[Music]
all the strange creature
to prove a threat
what am I looking at
uh yeah let's mutilate the brain yeah
[Music]
what happens if I fail
something bad uh oh no do I does the
brain take over me oh you just wow you
just stuck your thumbs up
sorry it was so wobbly
don't we have a pet now that's cute
it ran away oh it's running away
[Music]
destroyed
I don't I don't destroy today I I knew
we should have killed that thing
yeah
I'm sorry no it's okay it will follow
and haunt us forever
I'll be back oh we left we left
where is hero
okay I'm here wait um do you have
do you have it do you have improvised
melee weapon use it on me
on you improvised yeah do you realized
melee weapon yeah
I don't even know how to use a weapon
yeah I do I do I do improvised melee
whip I found it okay there's too heavy
to pick up
me yet yes I can't hold on a second
improvised melee weapon
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh oh wow
[Music]
yeah it sucks well anyway you'll get in
Rage thrill later and that's the big eat
oh we're gonna use that
okay
yeah okay that's pretty sick I thought
I'd provide some some background
Ambiance for you guys this fight
wow thank you I like your playing tiny
horned winged one uh tiny horn hey guys
yeah okay okay I changed my whole uh
layout in OBS I'm ready now okay oh
[Music]
oh man it's gonna be a long journey
let's go okay let's go
forward
Bonk them in the head with my the hammer
oh oh
my gosh
yeah beautiful right orange I like it oh
no oh no
no you cannot join our party
is she your sister
excuse me I am much more beautiful wow
she's so insulting yeah what a rude
Abomination doesn't sound too wrong
oh we share a brain we share a brain
cell
s
you cannot join my party
sorry
they all want to join us
yeah
we're just we're just that cool they
want to join the squad party's full yeah
squad's full sorry
about that
she knows you okay well you got to go to
the camp
um
are you making these decisions now who
are you what do you suggest who are you
who are you who is you
uh
what made you think I was a thrall
parasites
unless we are
basically if we let the thing stay in
our head we turn into one of those
tentacle people oh
yeah
yeah sure
okay Escape
oh the yum yum
getting the the snacks the munchies
Perfection once we
okay okay bye
[Music]
delicious go to the camp and wait
ress combat
yeah
oh so Angie
oh look at that Bloody smile wait I
don't know tutorial I kind of get it
um all right guys
around you during combat so you have
time to come eh
uh wait there's an order
yes
but I can jump as you
all right well anyway you're never a
dull moment cam
okay we're pretty strong right off the
bat dude I can't move here you big piece
of dirt
nice yeah yummy
and ax I don't need that I could sell it
though collect everything sell for Big
Money
Take It
we have to wait for
does everyone have to end their
individual turn yeah oh yeah ah okay
Luke Goblin engage
okay our attack shall be in front of us
I guess I'm also playing as wow
wow why would they do that to you
for giving you this responsibility I got
gold yeah
[Music]
they're leaving all these nice food
around here we've left it for you
because we know you you would want it oh
I'm going ahead so I can get all the
little first he's got so much good stuff
hey
Google
[Music]
restoration
what's this I want to go up there we go
let's climb up this now climb the thing
yeah
people took all the loot I did gotta be
faster than that but you'd rather share
the money from it the revenue yeah
because we split the prop put the profit
no
climb oops
oh there's a girl in here oh
yeah they do not react okay this isn't
dead
uh oh what did I I pushed the button
oh what happened what happened we're
killing a guy
I guess I guess
it'll take us some getting used to team
but that's okay
um I have to end my turn so nice hit
Bijou
it was still alive here oh you okay
not enough movement yes I'll just move
forward I don't think I have any range
range attacks all right
unless I could throw
do something to me wow nice Miss idiot
here we go no I want to do something oh
[Music]
I'm Barbarian
oh oh
[Music]
no I will not help
it does okay I'm having a brain the
brain you told us not to kill
let's get him let's go okay hello now
there's two of us die
okay all right cool I mean that works
yeah
oh wow wow I'm so powerful
you're pretty strong
already
is there any loot left
let's see what's over here how about you
what are you holding why do you guys not
want to see this
oh thank you
I saw I snatched that before my eyes
what's this do
I'm gonna go free Shadow heart I'm gonna
push this button
places
oh
all right I'm gonna free what what's
happening you
everybody needs a ranged weapons
inserted
freedom I am late
[Music]
did you get her out okay well free here
I'm freeing her now
place your hand on the console just let
her out let her free
you took my key why didn't you take my
key I could see that knocking everything
else you lose Goblin I was gonna share
yeah sure
well this is dark mine guided what are
we doing
um
[Music]
rejected me
no it's over does he die
yeah I know she's super dead
tear it open I'm not giving up this is
all my fault
what are these ass rolls
oh what the who the are you
kidding me I'll create you a shadow
heart I'll free you hey no I want a free
Shadow heart I wanna free I won The Rock
can't use a reaction shock
already Limited
already in use
hurry up Freer
you gotta free your nurse
can I do it critical failure I haven't
even had a critical failure in my game
that I'm playing right now
okay so I need to
I can't free you
I'm still trying to open her thing
yeah it won't work
only one at a time yeah only only one at
a time
do you need the key
[Music]
I guess rip Shadow heart it was nice
while it lasted
wow
oh poor oh what's happening to her oh
why do we want this anyway
super dead oh well a place oh this is so
dead
I mean he's still alive you can use that
key that you got to oh you already
emptied it you know how to play this
game I guess we should just move along
ladies no I don't know
he's a romance option well it's not like
we'll never see her again if we don't
free her okay you got this you got this
you got it do you have people are saying
it's almost like karmatic dice are off
okay
[Music]
I only needed a two and I got 19. yeah
we both got one amazing well how did you
only get once
[Laughter]
there's four of us am I right ladies uh
critical success
iconic Duo
here
looking I'm so glad I could free you wow
thank goodness I freed you wow wow good
thing I freed you myself
all by myself
I know it's fine you
feel that just now dangerous companies
what you need in a fight looks like this
let me come with you this is very pretty
thank you
got a heart beautiful no way you're on
your own if you're if you're waving if
you're waving compliment already uh we'd
make three double lady I want I want a
shadow heart okay you can have Shadow
Hearts okay I'm taking Shadow heart yeah
she is good yeah
why
[Music]
why not you can't tell me what to do
sometimes yucky
too
all of your dreams
come back this way yeah we came that way
let's go to the right
so we have a big party now yucky vampire
out of our camp
y oh but he's yucky
[Music]
that fiend
okay
okay you got it then we step on the fire
in the butthole
time I don't want to
I'm ready
yeah yeah we're ready oh you know it the
soul squad's here
the whole Squad
oh
okay you guys are without us oh no
I mean yes wait
get in here get in here
out
we must escape
now
do it we must escape
uh we got it we're on the tentacle dude
side for now
but that's awesome
no who am I right now um Lily killed
everything that we see yeah
and probably do some other stuff oh yeah
I forgot to rage
[Music]
oh my God
so angry
okay
who's alive here
I mean okay we're pretty strong Jesus
yeah we're strong you can try and shoot
let's go oh
good luck dumb that was so dumb I mean
it hit
oh
okay so yeah you must take the
transponder I'm gonna new new
um
over the transponder
it's on the other side
got a dash
was that oh there's more there's more
bad guys here I can't get there can I
Dash
I'm still damning my Dash attack was
resistant and they took half damage
what if I want to fight the devil
is level eight it has a hundred HP okay
never mind all right never mind
[Music]
for you
wait we have 14 turns remaining by the
way we're on a time zone
that's how the rage works so I should
probably use it up beforehand what I'm
about to hit I'm about to strike my rage
ended
flute
oh oh I can move now okay
foreign
okay
yeah let me let the tentacle monster men
fight we gotta get those guys but I'm
just very slow I need some assistance
I'm trying no way
okay we hope why do I feel like I'll do
this myself
I'm just very slow
I didn't need your help I can't reach
everyone's dead now
everyone's dead
who's Dash do I have Dash yeah you do
have Dash It's on your it's on your
other side how did I miss it okay people
you were too strong
well no one was helping me so I was like
fine I'll do it myself
oh
they're still fighting yeah I just
killed everyone here it was all me oh
he's dead
oh I'm gonna go for the thing I'm going
for the thing go go for the thing
oh
yes already I don't have a tattoo
in fact I'm playing on normal mode
however I have not really played much of
the Barbarian last year whoa I'm really
good at Magic but I'm not playing Magic
this time
um can you guys see the cutscene yeah
okay good
yeah big old dragon
it's painful
wow
people be careful
[Music]
sounds about right
get ready this is the rest of the
campaign
it's okay I know how to dash now
I I don't know how to do anything I wish
I had a con I would say controller
worked because this is so confusing that
like I have to use my mouse to move and
then to turn the screen stuff I have to
or Like to Move It I have to use the
thing but then yeah that's rough it's
like yes to rot I'm like what
you can use
middle Mouse button to rotate yeah what
do you mean middle Mouse button
click the scroll button click it yeah
like click it I'll try it
I mean I prefer a controller personally
oh the Goblins I know those guys you do
I know them now are you are they your
friends no no they're not
definitely not
um
goblins are never good guys in any
medium
can I say the thing
for it
people how could you
I saw it in chat before you even said it
[Music]
Darkness will fade away
oh
okay
who's safe a big UPS
who did save us I don't know
oh Magic that was plush
then you are so beautiful
thanks I know
feel gorgeous Bell of the ball
oh what's up sis
feeling good what what me
[Music]
check for injuries am I okay
yeah Uncle given everything you've been
through but it'll all be for nothing if
you don't find help soon we helped being
through the death sentence and the clock
is I love the narrator's voice yeah it's
very soothing very ASMR
what'd it do Beagle
okay
please teach me where the dash is
um it's on the left side of your bar
it's like a foot with wings
dummy
I just don't think I have eyeballs all
right
I'll flip with wings is very important
and jump is also very important you will
need to jump so yeah definitely nowhere
to jump buttons all right leave it to me
your way give me one you guys keep
moving I just gotta take a sip of water
real quick hey
oh what's that
it's the it's the cube from that one can
I link it that one scary franchise
tight tight and take this take a ticket
Hellraiser tesseract
give me some and Pinhead
oh dang it I think that one's every
morning guys like I don't know the name
of it oh people what were you doing
oh uh checking to see if you're okay of
course she's in love right away
I saved you obviously
uh
we made it it doesn't matter it seems
like we're the lucky ones judging by all
the corpses strain about
I remember the ship
I remember falling
than nothing
damn ah I love the deadbeat inside jokes
where where are we
I don't recognize this place
but anything's an improvement dang
Sheila good
things first I'm gonna steal her clothes
no I'm gonna steal her clothes
band
no man
oh no stealing clothes let's go together
no it's fine you can steal their clothes
as long as you don't steal their
underwear
oh
yeah overburdened with Hangers On
already oh excuse me kill at the camp
that's all you're good for just stay at
the camp there you go bye yes
all right ladies let's let's bust a move
all right yeah
oh we leveled oh I'll click on your
character portrait to level
up
level up what now
this is alive
it increases a lot I'll spell something
yeah
danger sense nice and I'm getting
tankier
oh I have to choose the Spells now
I'm gonna have to read these to give me
a moment I got destructive wrath okay
I'm good
while they're busy leveling up
[Music]
I think everything everything
is good
oh yeah you're a barbarian you just hit
level up and you're good yeah
can't focus you guys have to tell me the
tent
are you a man do you have a man voice I
do but I'm a lady who's you sorry
excuse you sister
you're so cute and small yeah I'm
perfectly eatable yeah oh we'll be doing
lots of throwing yes then he throws away
at us both
Waypoint discovered let's go
uh
oh money
I
I felt just that's cool
what did you just find oh this is a warp
point you can
yeah so you can fast travel here
I think this is our first one though so
we can't go anywhere
where's everybody
um
[Music]
no you never split the party
doesn't seem like we know uh I'm
exploring so
I found some little brain guys did you
guys take all your fish too
are you okay um
you're gonna need help here okay just
please I'm a small I'm just gonna turn
this around just insult them install
please okay they're so close to me I
guess it's not worth checking anything
could be
me
oh okay help me help me I can't
there's nothing I can do whoa whoa nice
oh that was good
are you okay yeah I'm good okay thank
you she's fine she's fine she's fine
she's okay vicious mockery
okay we just kind of we just gotta kill
this guy I don't have that though uh
they said bibu apparently you hit me you
you yeah you were in the way
so there is a friendly a fire yes there
is correct
oh
[Music]
I mean
I got you I know
you can run so quick why all right I got
you I'm gonna throw you a poster I can
be used to heal here I'll heal you yeah
I hear the lyrics how do you have so
many attacks
I got help
we're fine we're fine
someone smacked this thing right in
front of us
excuse me did you miss oh no you didn't
okay good what's going on
okay yeah I didn't hear a smack or
anything it's weird
oh god oh
there's no idea what's going on I want
to go up here
I Will Follow You Marissa yeah
wait Marissa come here don't you want to
meet a nice elf man I do I do want to
meet a nice Elfman come over here and he
join my team and help me yeah do a lot
of things if you want him to that sounds
more than one okay if you really want
him to
okay walk walk up the hill narissa look
up the hill here yeah go go meet him
go just go talk to him I don't see
anyone
just keep walking yeah keep going how
big will it be oh I see a man yeah
he's got a brain thing cornered
you girls are so fast you can't
um
what are we doing right now
oh you're listening okay well that was
so based of Marissa right there he wants
to kill me yeah
let's see this part oh good luck
am I gonna die no you got you
baby
much money
he's playing hard to get Marissa he's
playing hard to get well bounce whilst I
was trapped in that pot oh off man
tell them how it is
um this is chaotic I like it though why
don't you think we belong to them
we're obviously good people
we share a brain cell
AR
why is he trying to kill me I don't
understand
he likes you yeah no what's going on
that's why that's how he shows affection
the Mind flares were me connected us
that sounds uh
identical monsters whatever they did
whatever they put in us now he's
annoying
connections
let's go
whatever just happened the typical DND
slash world of Darkness vampires
is he even a vampire yeah he's a vampire
look at those teeth
um just gotta gotta learn I'm out of
wine with flowers that looks very much
like one also it reminds me of Victor
Vic Victor Good Old Vic yeah but a
little bit less obnoxious still yeah
true
um
[Music]
in various ways are we yeah I think we
are all of us yeah I think we we all got
we all got like joints from from the
city I think okay is that so
um wow
ladies
he's like Bernie
TV
can I kick him out I don't want to talk
to him anymore why did you guys make me
do this
no I don't like men I like evil
men not men
ah what's the difference the big
difference big difference
kick him out
no thanks
it won't let me think do what you want
I'm leaving don't
hilarious is it gonna make you send him
to the camp I don't know I don't want to
say based for trying
it won't let me pick any of them
uh
pick one you can't click one no it makes
the sound but nothing is happening
huh
click and double
look at triple oh thank you so much
alone I'm clicking so much guys help I'm
stuck maybe
we're both
what if we stop listening yeah guys get
me out of here
how do we stop listening
it's on the top right
X on the top oh
my cute friend
oh did you find this Kiara I I summoned
it I have I can summon like five six
different animals I just realized that
it was six numbers don't work numbers
aren't working you guys can we can we
knock her out of combat yeah can you
like kill me I got you yeah I'm sorry
guys you destroying me
[Laughter]
oh my God
this is so dangerous they're staying
safe that I even save and reload is that
even possible
wait wait wait okay
I got a different I got a different
option I got different options
oh okay
wait no no I'm stuck again kill me
oh back down put it back down we want
her to survive no kill me
I don't wanna well that's Kiara
wait I'm sorry I didn't mean to okay
okay did you get it did you get an
option now no
I'm staying in safe distance
[Laughter]
I don't know what data it's gonna show
hang on let me yeah I got it I got your
back let me save the game really quick
please
help oh can I help you
third game
[Music]
going back
did you did you get into a loading
stream or screen yeah yes okay
a bit late to save
knife safe after every workout
sure it'll be fine we're new at this
okay
I'm dead because you killed me
you'll be fine we can
we can save you oh you're back down okay
I'll let me help you up okay yeah I'm
good thank God for talking to this
freaking guy yeah someone else talked to
him I don't know hello
I
can move my screen but I can't I can't
move
oh God they're broken
The Matrix oh do you have an earlier
save do you have I look safe I think
maybe go back to that earlier save
before we met this freaking guy yeah for
everything
let me see auto save all right um
there's us on the beach okay we probably
will lose some loot but that's okay we
can get it again better than better than
whatever's going on right now yeah
whatever whatever this is thank goodness
for autosave it's like pasta
oh yeah save save Lots because you know
something like this might happen
good that we encountered it early now
that we're cautious yeah
back here oh I think we have to level
again too yeah yeah okay oh no I'm good
I don't need to um
I can't level
oh oh Shadow heart hi oh we talked to
her again hold on let me watch y'all
handle that and go faster you do your
thing boo okay uh
go into the camp
I don't have the leveling thing guys
yeah I don't either neither do I I think
I already love it's already after we
leveled it yeah I'm not sure because
mine's only at 13 and I thought I was at
like 20 something
oh there we go there we go we got it
just popped just popped
okay
get those levels
[Music]
okay let's do that again
yeah let's save if we decide to talk to
that guy again beforehand uh since he
broke the game
yeah oh yeah oh you know there are
always other greener pastures like uh
maybe Houston you know I bet you like
houses next time who
house and is a great kind soul I think
you'll really like that character
[Music]
yeah no why wouldn't you trust me I mean
I feel like he's just a very Charming
character that you'd like that's all
that there is
no tricks no trickery no just give me
different clothes
[Music]
okay
uh can I walk around this
I'm probably gonna have to move around
it
okay how do I need to equip something
long range pretty sure I have a short
bow your frog is so cute
can I eat
why does it hurt me still
it's pretty easy you stepped in like the
little corner of it
ashes in action
hey can I not how do I can I not attack
when I dashed no no you can't yeah you
use
I can at least leave a Hunter's Mark
nice it'll do more damage if you if you
shoot him just throw axes oh I can throw
axes oh you're so right Chad I didn't
know that because I don't play my very
oh boy
you're good you're good on the way can I
control the Frog
you should be able to yeah if not the
Frog's turn yet
oh okay
oh yeah
Froggy's friend
broke his friends wow loot
give me brain frog only one HP
oh there's another one up there
Maury smash
my turn
I love the frogs portraits ah okay wait
now it's frog okay now it's froggy time
yeah
[Music]
some things can froggy attack no not
enough movement okay froggy just follow
oh cute he can be butter you know cannon
fodder or bait
oh yeah I guess so I guess I can't do
anything special ah wait wait A Touch of
creature can I do this no not enough
movement I guess if I would have dashed
but it's okay
you're good oh you need help okay your
HP is only half
ah am I gonna be okay yummy okay it's
not bad yeah it's fine it's a frog good
shoot the other one girls he has a
hunter's Hunter's Mark on the Hunter's
Mark nice yeah
oh
what the concentration broken uh
what is that
you had to concentrate to keep the
Hunter's Mark active
you're good you're good good luck it's
only for me
[Music]
and rage nah there's no reason to end my
rage yeah keep raging keep raging I
think it's over though after this
[Music]
a bunker there yeah this one
I need healing
um do you have some uh oh there we go
potion maybe oh that was on that was on
the wrong side
thank you a little bit oh hello okay
oh thanks
oh
it's more open no smash
and only smash all right time for you to
go kill that guy we can also apparently
just invite him to the party steal his
clothes and then kick him out we want to
steal his clothes but we need to save
right before we talk to him then yeah
I'm not talking to him again this is up
to someone else I don't want to deal
with that
you were so cool when you like when you
like got him to the ground and like like
beat him up
okay
make sure you say if man is my worst
nightmare yeah my name don't worry okay
oh yucky oh yucky
help
ing you guys he's useless
man
well don't worry
you want a Tango dang pretty boy he got
you on the ground good luck
put yourself to yourself at the same
time Arctic inspiration
is that okay
I want to be cool
wow yeah success
apparently he's good at getting locks
yeah he's a stealthy one
um
Arian fans and shambles sorry
I haven't done anything to you yet he's
kind of a jerk you know yeah
no ribs no ribs but it
fadesh the lights
thank you
the knife away and I'll tell you any
everything I'm not an idiot
it has to be if I do this game chat it's
something they did
they took you too
I saw it during
just happened everybody tons of things I
was ready to decorate the ground I would
like to after this cutscene rest for a
moment you bet I can heal my HP apology
accepted oh yeah oh you can press short
rest yeah I just need apparently
everybody too
I can't rest alone
Dash through this guy's dialogue yeah we
just need we don't care as close yeah
go to the camp dummy all right we can
rest we can do a short rest we don't
need to do it there you go
oh much better yeah I feel rested let's
go ahead and do a save here
oh yeah good
call yeah
it's popping off in here hello
and it's hurt I'll kill it
yeah kill it
beat him up
you guys talk to him you little
it's you James
I don't know
you're right you're right you're right
for that
that was kind of Awesome
all right I think we need to go this way
just suddenly die
oh Goblin scimitar
Cindy
oh that Bijou kill it during the
cutscene
yeah I bonked him right in the head that
seems too good for it
punch the sigil on the stone what is
that magic glitch glitter that looks uh
crazy Marissa do you really want to
stand so close to it
yeah slightly dangerous yeah
Marissa was stuck because of a party
boat I don't know what that means though
oh I don't know because every other time
when people were voting it didn't get
stuck like that if people didn't vote so
um
I think I think the Voting is just like
a suggestion isn't it yeah exactly I
don't think it was a party boat a hand
give me my hand there is um
on Christmas
let's go
wow
I'm just too good meanwhile critical
pale hairs on this whatever
I don't have any I don't have any
strength so
my weak little bird arm strings
it doesn't really look like they're
pulling that hard wait who is he oh oh
this is what you like I don't know I
want to know who he is though
oh
[Music]
he's Mr Magic Man yeah
a bit shocked I'll be nice to him he
doesn't seem like a mean guy
I like his fluffy hair in a manner of
speech
the wizard of water d
yeah
[Music]
I ship it
the result
what's a wizard
I just think how soon is really cool
unfortunately we have no clerics with us
now
soon to be something else
I have one
we're most certainly going to need a
Healer I'm a really dumb cleric though I
don't think you would trust me to like
get worms out of your head I trust you
oh
okay
see you're traveling with plenty of
company already
if you play solo are all these dudes
like joining you yeah if you play solo
they they join up and then you can like
hang out with them and do their like
story quests but we have our own we have
our own Squad we have our own party
which is so much better I wonder how we
get their approval though if they're
never on our team like out in the field
with us oh this way
you got to get their approval if you
want to raise them up but if they're
always in the camp you can't get their
approval no reason why are you walking
like that I don't know I don't know what
I did what are you doing
she's like normal no and now that's back
to normal okay
[Music]
hello
there's so much to look at
oh there's people here hello
should we kill them
yeah it sounds fun I just saved the game
uh tamman and wouldn't uh gimbal gimbal
gimbal box
oh you're real nice too oh my God hey
what's up it looks like one of my old
cats
I am not impressed looks like a raccoon
I summoned over the raccoon
but it's probably a cat
attack
oh it's fluffy oh I love it I have a
meow action and what else
just meowing attract the attention of
nearby creatures to draw them closer to
you don't knockers
[Music]
on cat cannot move too much WoW
the distraction no one will hurt this
cat
I heard the cat I will destroy them
destroy them
whoa
well it did attract attention so
understandable
hi kidding me
bye
was that info
all right hold on I got you
loud put your nostrils
what's with your nostrils you infect my
eyes and nostrils wait why didn't you
rhyme
I was trying to throw a potion at you
oh she did
yeah I killed two people though I killed
two people it was worth it I'm in danger
too never says in danger too we only
have Cali at full HP
what's happening right now
um someone's turn oh oh
okay what's wrong with that person
[Music]
let me oh okay all right let me hold on
a sec
thank you you're welcome now let me see
if I can
anything else I might go to sleep
how dare you do that to narissa
so rude can I use a Potion No I mean at
least if I'm knocked out I heal right if
they make me sleep that's how it works
in games
[Music]
I'm gonna try to wake you up okay
next time I kill him
I'm not the team baggage
am I doing this right to chat
um can I help you wake up
die
how much 80 I'm dying still
don't range yeah that's not what I
wanted to do yay oh you guys
nice damage something
I am holding a ranged weapon now
uh oh wait this wizard is still alive
okay okay
[Music]
it doesn't matter it doesn't matter oh
wow
thank you
[Laughter]
my eyes hey
what's up
Point Blank oh where's your shot oh oh
are you okay you wanna ground
oh
[Music]
this is like a dungeon oh Jesus okay um
oh that is a lot of people okay that's a
lot of dudes yeah that's more than one
okay we got this who are they
stinky
oh
it's fine tomb Raiders okay I'm gonna
try to blast all of them here we go now
blast them okay anyway I start blasting
how many can I get oh okay
Yates look at this
I got
I blew up there I got I got nobody you
did good
I tried my best I did not have good
rolls so it matters
push this person
yeah
okay I'm out of here somebody set the
oil on fire do it oh it's a fireball
you can shoot it
out
I don't have fire but there's oil on the
floor now I don't know if this really
works I also do not have I don't I don't
have
fired
[Laughter]
How's It Go five five you're fine oh
brighter higher as you desire
chasing all that we aspires
take the chest and with my lighter
oh
that's your age too all right we're
screws
[Music]
tank
of course they just point blank ignore
the tank
[Music]
wow
um I don't know what that means but I
think you call him stinky uh he is
stinky
he's smelly dude
what are we doing wait what's that uh oh
they added more people endorsements
hold on a sec if I go here and then
I do this get him
oh let me get off this oil
just in case oh yeah maybe it would have
been mine
dang it took Columbus wait don't leave
me in here
[Applause]
fight them on your own you go okay
I'm still in Rachel I'll apply haunt
this Mark on him I'm going to perish
I'll fight him next turn
laughs
hopefully their weekend
just let me take the damage
[Music]
what do we have our tank for don't
attack the the weak ones
it's not the glass cannons
help
oh
y'all oh dear good luck
no spells
oh
it's like they know I'm about to die
wait let me use this on him can I not
he dashed oh it's gonna be fun looting
this place afterward if we live oh there
we go we definitely will
oh
yeah what
hmm no damage
we had a few damage
so well don't worry Bijou we'll take him
down
I bonked him on the head and he took
zero damage
yeah we all keep missing
seven damage on your Mama what's that
mean
um well you're choosing how to react uh
you can react yeah you can react
sometimes you can get back with a
counter spell go go
die
yeah oh wow wow oh I didn't know do that
okay
I wanted to throw a hand ax
okay well that's one person
oh
wow
what's the flounder isn't that a fish
it's a fish
it was your father a fish wow goodbye
it's up to you guys
no no no we'll revive you somehow I'd
love to revive you but I do need to do
something no no no you do something I
I'm on my way don't I have a Revival
thingy oh yeah pretty yucky attack right
there
um
uh I'm gonna try to revive her then
if I can only things to remember is when
she comes back it'll be at one HP yeah
it's fine it's fine no win uh now I
can't can I take half as interrupted oh
I'm in the way
okay let's go around me I'm so small
though shouldn't you be able to aim over
her head
come on now why is it only 42 of me
being able to throw it properly because
because throwing is difficult yeah
drunk's hard okay oh wait is there
anything else I can do like they say
just touch her yeah just touch it there
you go okay don't give her one HP though
so you gotta heal pretty quick after
that or someone will just knock her out
real fast all right
oh oh retreat
oh you little
again
here's what he's doing he's using real
straps wow I mean smart man I should
play like that
why have any um
no oh I'm on the right side of your body
there you go nice okay if you throw the
potion right at her it would hurt her
because it's an attack roll so you have
to throw it right to the ground next to
her is that what happened to Cali before
yeah I think yeah oh because like the
Polish is made of glass so you're
throwing a glass bottle yeah so that's
probably on the ground when we want to
do that thanks for the help chat
so I can't do anything
um
except uh perform a ditty okay yeah
[Music]
I can shut this guy's head off okay
we're gonna do one of the all-time
battles let's go
[Music]
do you know Ragnar the red no uh Ragnar
the red you gotta learn Ragnar the red
I just know the power this is this is
all this is this is what you get in does
that even does it do anything oh oh good
okay
oh okay it's fine
um
I'll help I'm helping
me
nice nice nice
thank you
I want to change back to my other weapon
was a team if
okay
oh there's still one person yeah hello
sneak attack
ow yeah
I think that didn't do that much damage
yeah I don't know how I feel if someone
called me that uh
free period
owie
okay
okay let me add him yeah get him yeah
this one yeah
thank you okay
okay you gotta go when you kill the guy
in there
let's see yeah
let's go
[Music]
[Laughter]
um I suggest we all take a long rest yes
how do I do that who's over there the
race that come come on okay I'm coming
with you guys
long rest wow I sit like such a lady
at the end of the day no no I don't I
just wanted to sit down
oh but I want to sit we're doing long
rest right hey what were you able to say
art
Shadow heart
Gail has something close
oh my closing adventurers yeah
good wow
everyone's everyone's backside is
finally crafted in this game even ours
yeah
I want to close
why do you want to take off our clothes
so badly
no I don't I want to wear her clothes
because they're nice what does she kind
of wear then huh
I doubt that they will fit her
uh just FYI says somebody in chat I
don't know if it's a one guy situation
you can't steal their clothes before
dang it interesting
oh
briefly I don't need a stereon right uh
I guess we could just murder it how do I
take his clothes
by killing him was there anything what's
your damn mouth
the game
[Laughter]
I slap his cheeks around a little bit
roll initiative
literally
crimes certain actions are frowned upon
by others like I give a let's go
yeah I killed him oh my God
what are they doing
wait that sucks but he wasn't wearing
the right outfit yeah
take his underwear
oh yeah
you guys are crazy
conversation with him yeah it was sick
why
I want his clothes
now I got like fancy clothes I'm pretty
sure we can just undress them I don't
think we have to kill them
no we gotta kill him you want their
clothes
sadly with four with four player
okay well
I'm happy
okay put them on
I did
well
would you like to go to bed you sure
yeah yeah let's let's sleep you can you
can resurrect them back apparently yeah
canceled what what
me not me
what is this oh yeah
somebody canceled again why not your boy
another players it's currently choosing
camp supplies for long rest yeah yeah
okay so someone oh wait I think I think
Cali has to choose the town surprise
choose it okay okay no more players
denied the requests
go to bed yes okay yes
okay we'll rest
I'm sorry
[Laughter]
hey noodles who is trolling
behind them oh yeah we can always
rosarize the series I don't think we'll
need him but this is where are you party
affordable whatever
skull
plus I don't think anyone's interested
Force the tab pull out of your mind I'm
not very intelligent so I'll use wisdom
I'm smarter than all of you
all right well I'll use wisdom I'm Wiser
than you guys
okay I'll try it too
angry I succeed
you know it's our first meal in the game
Big
successful Journey
drift shot oh it's a brick but why is
this a mountain exactly I mean it's in
character right
then character
isn't too much
food Memorial
I can't wake up because you guys are in
a cutscene
when I get to sleep if I failed this
what what would have done what what did
that even do the fact that I succeeded
hmm
what would it have done if I failed no
idea
um
somebody says you you said you wanted to
multi-class yes apparently we can't on
this difficulty what yeah it's disabled
on the difficulty because it's fairly
Advanced oh my God huh you're clear we
do
um it's okay I'll just when when can we
change when the re-roll happens I can
re-roll
changing difficulty and menu option I
can change it oh yeah change it to
normal yeah change normal we'll be fine
well yeah we'll live we will live yeah I
don't know about that you guys
no no no no we've already been a bridge
of dying a lot of times
well we'll be fine it's okay
we're only on the brink of dying because
we don't have Stella yet exactly okay
turn it back easy
it's too difficult yeah but then the
multi-class things
change multi-class then go back
so
really
um
hi
[Music]
come on
no you're the only one that's kind to me
Liara
okay I Love Leona oh yeah no you maybe
you need you take like two spaces I do
I'm pretty
okay there we go oh look at us nice but
there's always going to be one girl
excluded yeah one's our our poster so
all right
why don't we sit like that how do I
steal people's clothes without killing
them
something yeah
are we gonna go back to the fight yeah
we should I'm already here
how did you go absolutely stuff yeah hey
click on the bed click on the bed roll
the the bed roll the bed the bed thing
uh leave Camp okay
uh
are you trying to end the day no I would
explain about it again
the ladle wait no I don't need this
stuff open this
oh
[Music]
and I already took all the treasures I
took it took it for me
[Music]
I'm stuck
where are you stuck oh okay I'm good now
is there nothing left in here did we
already kill everybody
there's a there's a thing over this way
[Music]
why would I need the cutting board
I think you guys are still inside yeah
yeah
I'm on the other side stealing all the
money from here
[Music]
it's weird why does the books have HP
can I jump oh
what's this sturdiness
is there ever something yes I did
something
did something happen
you do not recognize the language on the
plaque oh oh
it's all loaded sometimes girls have
magic oh there's a there's a door I
opened over here
I'm on the way
um
which door
this way this one yeah this one
where is oh no we saw yeah why are you
giggling
why are you giggling hey
[Laughter]
so I'm just exploring some more
she's losing let's go
okay
there's like nothing of value in there
did you already steal everything in here
Bieber no
oh oh where are you going
oh
[Music]
oh oh
what's gonna happen
fine what's happening
we're fine
what what's happening for you girls when
I ended my turn uh I think yeah I think
you have to end your turn
oh but there's a button apparently
what button
go back to entrance okay I'm gonna run I
can't go so far
oh
okay that's about what I thought
[Music]
yeah at least it wasn't hit this time
no maybe now it's it's not as dangerous
anymore because it's shot once you think
it's gonna shoot again
maybe it'll be fine no it's not safe
it's not over okay okay uh let's leave
yeah yeah what if there's treasure
yeah oh oh okay
stand in there with your hands and your
hips just fired consumes you
we
now not until you turn out of the
turn-based mode okay
whoa whoa okay
oh
they're like
are you guys fighting something
oh oh we're fine no it's fine it's fine
it's fine it's fine oh uh people does it
ever stop it you're dying I'm dying yeah
and you're almost dead now over there
okay where's Marissa I'm I'm not nearby
oh
never gonna be at all
I I earned it I earned it I went and
grabbed it and survived I earned this
sure I turned it off
okay we'll go find them
oh oh is it good now
yeah I turned it off in here oh
I found something with 71 health
he's dead though
but his tentacles are still kind of
moving oh no
that's locked
oh
you know
you're finding I want to see what you
is this better than what I have oreobe
only find dirt
this
we're too dumb to understand what's on
the plaque yeah not very smart
equip the shield
are you guys still down in that uh Place
yeah we didn't finish exploring Lauren
okay still exploring the Crypt I think
yeah no now it seems finished
yeah it looks like we'd be all done well
there's something over here
there's dead people with loot oh cool I
love that
my aesthetic
oh religion failed oops that's quite
right
oh they have so much money
I pressed a secret button oh
nice mine mine Memorial past things
maybe it's a trap again
[Music]
very happy to see their Mori oh hello
where is it oh okay
um there's a person next to me oh yeah
one right next to me too
nowhere
oh
somebody oh
get him deadbeats whose side are you on
boy
all right
oh he almost died I wonder how tanky
these guys are I need to see their
health nice shot
oh we can take him that big yeah that
attacking Bijou now
they're surrounding me
it looks so strong though sheesh I have
the same thing all right fine I'll go
help my friends but
um
[Music]
[Applause]
I was having a good time
on a little solo Journey yeah I was a
looting looting things on the beach the
beach side wow
rattle them boys oh he's dead oh
another one
oh wow it's been frosted hi
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah if you can pay
yeah bye
bye I love that smell
[Music]
um
okay
okay this is what yes okay one HP left
hmm
use the other one
oh
back off that beat you don't want this
you don't want any
I'm too lucky
they never hit they always miss
oh angry
let it all out it's good to let it out
uh
let the aggressions out
and beat back off
deadbeats have a bad aim yeah
out of things do I already use my bonus
action I'll live through this shortly oh
yeah yeah I should be fine
oh I forgot about him
he has a different Target
no it's okay now six
[Music]
how many enemies are left
only three
oh they're all pretty good
yeah we got this
boom
oh he died he did die hey
[Music]
yay
nice
oh what you're gonna do when we said
yeah
is there there's one left gun
there's no one dude yeah on the right
behind people who kind of yeah behind me
I see him I see him okay
I'm here for Batman
let's go
oh money
they have money
[Music]
all right
what's in there what's inside big
treasure beyond my wildest imagination
oh
huh
oh this doesn't this scares me I know
this guy
do you oh you're talking oh he's got
pretty eyelashes oh my God
if we found your Romance
[Laughter]
right
right you know that nose what a curious
way
it's got a little beaten up mhm now
now question for the what is the worth
of a single moment it was a test from
sensei okay um
let me see the multiple choice questions
for the crawling out of a tomb peaceful
and dead interesting why aren't you
attacking me attack what's the reason
for your question
no attack
a question
yeah
again
why do you like that hold on this is
this is on the quiz I'm trying to
remember the real answer this ogre is
having a harsh time answering the
question it matters is mine it's not
Immortal oh my God
I am sure the believersed was I right
Sensei there are different ways I can
phrase it
I am satisfied
[Laughter]
we used to see each other again no join
our team time and place oh he will he
will
see each other
[Music]
missiles
oh actually
Allie do you want this Amulet of lost
voices it lets you speak with the dead
oh yes you can speak with your homies
okay here I'll give it
oh you hold on what is this Soul point
the coins can power infernal engines
um do you want magic Missile
I'm not gonna use it oh sure I can hold
on to it no wait I don't want it just
stop I don't want to use it
I'm still the controls they still Escape
me okay sorry I remember how to do this
hi Lisa
does this do a new phone
there's a ring on my finger
why are you holding a Stairway what did
you just do
ladder way out
the same other one
underwear
[Music]
yeah is wearing it
yeah what
no yes you are what do you mean I'm
wearing it
we're wearing it I checked your
inventory
what
what I didn't
consciously equip anyone's underwear oh
you're wearing it
there's a ladder
oh no shallow
I find you guys don't worry
oh we left there's some stairs all
because of all half elf underwear is the
same okay
is he a hotel
[Music]
I didn't know that that's a lot less fun
no vampires
so yeah I mean you can you keep going
your link is underwear I believe but I
don't know if anybody did that
all right I'm out I'm on the way
where shall we go next team
the question can you short rest we're
here before yeah
oh so I gotta I gotta do the short rest
huh
as the hose
don't worry okay
okay
I'm here now
where are we going I don't know you guys
need the way okay I'm going this way
I'll follow people add them together
strong how about the other strong oh you
know you never split the part
where are we going
um actually no not this way not this way
we've been this way we didn't go up this
way yet um
left or right
well this way
wait actually actually wait hold on
there's someone over here
anyone can short rest but it's good to
talk about it gotcha
oh there's a b oh it's the it's the girl
it's not it's
[Music]
no way no no that's not no it's a
different situation uh
oh
oh no she's like a prisoner
garlic
and if it escapes
oh hi
hi
what are we doing Liara
it's up to you that's what you think is
right good luck
get rid of them well
um
[Music]
shoot the Trap down oh
but am I saying this to her yeah I think
you're saying it to to the the two
fillings yeah
uh
but I don't really have much persuasion
yeah also maybe but I could I could try
to talk to them because I have both of
those
I'll
I guess do your best do your best
over ten come on yeah
[Music]
hmm get out of here tieflings
check out that
block tea flings tea
German by the way for for deeplings oh
really yeah that cool they just make it
sound fancy
um
good so we came for a look
I'm in dire need of healing I don't know
not really but we'll find out we need
help to get to get the the things I ever
had hmm oh okay
[Music]
totally doable
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
worms out
look for Nettie
say whatever really Goblin traps even
the warms oh cool they're pretty nice I
killed these dudes no wow
me down
say please yeah
hi well then you're gonna stay up there
too bad
get me down we could just kill her
they even shoot it questionable internet
what if we accidentally surprising
um
throw something at it what does that
mean what a panda is
atrocities We are Becoming hold on
bro
there's nothing for us it's dead I know
oh
release me and she will share it okay
bro go
now share
you're free
maybe next time talk to her
I did skipping
oh hi
I must find a crash
we'll go our separate ways uh thank you
what's that uh what is the correct it
sounds like a French
grounds it does
we must report to Augustine for
purification
[Music]
all right we'll journey together
dismiss your weakest Warrior all right
who's the weaker wow
wait at the case you're the weakest
Warriors
get out of here
go back to the camp you you're the
weakest go okay we're all very strong
ladies yeah
also her armor looks like plastic so
yeah it does yeah yeah it does simply
made
okay should we invest okay investigate
the thing
the thing oh yeah yeah the thing they
just told us about before they left
oh God the area the campsites they came
from we're like you're shouting up ahead
yeah we'll get we will get there for
sure I think
oh something's happening quickly save
hold on
quick little saves oh oh yeah okay this
is I think this is the right direction
foreign
[Music]
Portland yeah
a lot of facts let's go well maybe if
you open the gate sooner yeah right
that's a that's a life they lost for no
reason
can we help him
yeah we can let's do it
let's go well I love will oh
oh
yeah Mr Hero man let's go I love that oh
man oh I'm so funny it literally one
right in front of me okay great or bad I
can't I can't do anything
we are pretty far back I I might need
some help
well you should have waited for us
[Music]
am I dashing I want to dash yeah we are
pretty far away Dash might be in order
why does it even start when we're so far
away should I get on the hill
I I either use it go on the hill I
didn't know
oh wait no no oh that's I thought that
was one of us
okay uh
before I get there
well good luck babe good luck goblins
these guys look like they can handle
themselves yeah
you never split a party yeah this would
be the reason
oh ow
aha
[Music]
oh we're doing a little dance
oh I get better accuracy the further I'm
away with bows oh
interesting
yeah I thought I thought that was number
one of us that's why I got so close okay
um
oh
you can jump with yourself it's true
it's a dude horn from back in the day
the old days
wow
wow Miss twice
push this person all help 40 I will I
will risk it please do it
dang
too bad double your movement speed
should I use that night
attack good good I'm not gonna use it
for this battle whoa
I'm sorry
okay cool cool
nice I don't know how I did that but
[Laughter]
so you can push and then also attack
still I guess I'll try the same thing
Chad if he's like down here and I'm up
there
can I shoot him because like
realistically I don't think I could
no you have the high The High Ground is
an advantage you have The High Ground I
mean like down yeah oh right there yeah
because he wouldn't be what do you mean
do you see what I'm pointing at
because you want to follow you yeah he
is kind of hit so like you know what I'm
pointing at I mean right below like
right it doesn't matter
it says it says that like it doesn't say
you're past obstructed and it just gives
a regular like percentage should be okay
oh got him nice oh nice well then
[Music]
um
and now we shoot yes
oh nice we get them
[Music]
enter
nice oh you can paint hold out and right
click please almost in the pad I'm
almost there
the dash was helpful
good to know
you girls know how to Ping because now I
found out
uh I think yeah like that
this is what I meant here oh I see I can
see it is it right click or left like
right click and I click okay oh okay
yes yes
okay can I go help them
I'm good luck go help go help
they're really far away
yeah I think you can scale down the
mountain
where the hell that we're on
there there she is see there I am yeah
okay has arrived
um
uh let's see
piercing shot
let's go
oh good crit oh oh he's mad at me
it works are scary yeah I know I can
throw the knives but why do I know works
from
oh you hated that he's mad
[Music]
uh
pretty strong because throwing would be
nice what was that
foreign
[Music]
good luck why go down yep because
they're so far away
I did not see that
yeah
thought so
they're they're front lining I'm in the
back
yeah
are you feeling it oh that person's dead
yes
[Music]
he'll be revived surely
okay I'm gonna go establishing oh I
can't do this more accuracy
[Music]
um
okay oh wait I you stabbed him okay I'll
stab this one then oh yeah yeah one
damage
let's go awesome let's go not a staff
that was a poke
um
[Music]
okay oh oh that's AOE damage Ross yeah
it would appears whoa thank God it's
okay
you did damage oh good well now I know
that I have AOE damage on that one
you guys left I think they're pretty
much outnumbered I think we'll
definitely win
yeah
we need to fight more things so we can
level one more time
I want more stuff yeah we're weak oh oh
that guy's dead too
oh oh oh
[Music]
no
okay all I can do is stab so I'm just
gonna keep stabbing
something
guys
[Music]
that was one time use yes
maybe maybe we can have a rule whoever
killed got the last hit get started
what is this fight what is more angry
yeah
I didn't do anything to him uh I didn't
I didn't either oh wait the battle isn't
oh what what happened that was but it is
a goblin the bad guy I think you may
have accidentally looted one of the dead
people do we okay can we run away
is he temporarily hostile or Perma
hostile maybe
oh he's in his temporary sorry
no I think I think we both did it Bijou
I'm not sure
oh I don't know I just thought the
goblin wasn't bad
you guys can travel non-lethal attacks
and we need to fight him I think oh how
do you turn that off
yeah there's like a switch so like you
know where you have all your spells and
stuff like go to the first wheel and
it's like at the top wait not available
can we just can we just disengage
I'm not sure
goodbye
sorry will sorry
one person toggles it for the entire
world
[Music]
I might resent you but they won't be
actually hostile I'm in capacity
okay good okay come on be nice pretty
let's go nice one
can we just okay Enter
I'm leaving no more entering
don't hurt me you hit him he'll never be
your friend we just gotta run from him
yeah don't enter they say one person
says don't enter
charm just means he won't attack you you
gotta run away and then flee to Camp
uh-huh oh okay I'm running away if you
enter okay people might try to find out
oh so you have to run away and get far
enough so it disengages through combat
but we love will I want him on our team
he's so yeah it was great oh
[Music]
I wouldn't even lose it wasn't even me
he's not up for reasoning
okay just just right oh
I remember I remember that yeah I should
have remembered that was gonna happen
it won't work on him he can't be an
enemy please
this goes poorly no no no no no we'll
just have to run away for it far far
enough
okay green people
erisa it looks like a heart I like it I
know run away
can I disengage now
can I can I please leave from combat
am I far enough
how do you how you tell if you're far
enough I don't think there is a far
enough
get out of the battle
I'm trying
okay
yeah
27 meters isn't so much okay well I'm
far enough now okay you're gonna chase
me oh wow leave me alone
I I spam the red button the red button
didn't work
see
right
I should be okay flea combat yes
Wii combat flea combat we're almost not
working right
is it working for you yeah I flee I fled
to Camp how come how come
it's not for me I'm like are you not far
enough I got pretty far away I'm using
oh you're using dashed yeah I'm like
super far I also have flat into combat
yeah oh his eyes are open just keep keep
running keep running
you can play from combat and go to Camp
if you are far enough from your enemies
and it's it it says it's fine enough
they're closed
how many camps are there
this one's pretty
can I buy arrows here
yeah it won't it won't let me press the
button okay well I'll keep running I
guess
maybe again
please I mean
ice arrows oh
it's okay I'm still in combat too so
oh he's coming after you
people are you pressing the disengage
thing yeah I'm pressing I'm the bottom
white red one I'm pressing the bottom
white red one but it I think it's bugged
because it doesn't say how many meters
you're away from him because for me it
says I need 27 meters
I was out of his range because it didn't
say the 27 meters anymore but now he got
closer so I don't know
but he's chasing me
well they say that he likes you when he
chases you yeah
anymore because I'm far enough but it
won't let me disengage still I
disappointed I am going to perish go on
without me remember me good luck I got
something to say nerissa what got
something to say about this what I'm
doing over here no I'm just uh concerned
um my ring how do I volunteer without
killing him is that even I think he's
gonna kill me
I can hide okay
you can reload if you want that battle
was easy so yeah we can just do it again
you want to reload it must be unarmed or
using oh I can maybe I can Bonk him I
failed yeah hold on I'll try to oh okay
I'll try to Bonk him hold on one second
yeah as long as the damages
always though
yeah
[Music]
knock someone unconscious okay I need to
be unarmed so I need to take off
weapons okay come here I'm gonna Bonk
you
I messed up
Marissa I'm chilling
you you look so beautiful they're
basking in the sunlight but also
partially being covered by the beautiful
leaves above you thank you I'm just the
sunlight just does work Wonders on you
you guys Romancing each other
you guys having fun I'm sure glad you
guys are having fun
well well well you should look like
oh oh this is your trip if you ever
being a dirty Luke Goblin oh another
chance
why
why did nobody nobody carry away the
dead body of a Starion
there it's hilarious
to another camp
look at this look at his underwear what
the heck
okay well
[Music]
I'm going to die I don't think we can
help you oh no okay well I am actually
deceased roller revive a fight to bring
them back to life well maybe my skeleton
friend can help for a prize
um yeah
hey buddy can you help me bring my
friend back to life
by cross attacks no isn't Callie a gift
Yankee
yeah
can you tell me the class uh resurrect
someone yeah resurrect me please
resurrect bagel oh look I died in a
teapot as well where's the gold
oh
okay I'm gonna bring you back oh thank
you
so I will
surely he'll forgive you yeah we killed
I'm a new person yeah
me really thanks for
annoying and if your upturned fat snout
is any better
[Music]
hello there you are are you back buddy
at the battlefield or where are you
girls now I'm in I'm in Camp now okay
okay I'm talking to the lady I want to
rest I have one HP yeah yeah
what should we do we have one short rest
left but maybe we should just sleep we
should just do a long rest probably
we'll just do a long one oh that
whoa
uh
um oh oh this oh he's still here
yeah huh
we just we just keep bringing his dead
body with us to camp
I guess so that we can one day bury him
which is very respectful exactly that's
what it's all about the respect are we
ending the day
yeah yeah because um okay okay
I'm sleepy burning someone in Camp still
wishes to speak to you go to bed anyway
huh uh if you want to speak to me just
speak to me
I mean I don't know who would want to
talk to me
why can't we
[Music]
now if you're too sad you can DM me you
know oh
every day I spend in your DMs
all right good morning everybody good
morning good morning dead person good
morning you guys ready to go back into
the fridge
yeah let's go
Hopi is it still mad at me well we'll
find out won't we
fingers crossed where do we enter The
Grove
there's a lot of blood around here nice
yeah that's that's where I died
that's my blood
this bagel's Blood right there for
whatever reason is he done being angry
now yeah is he is he done
is it safe now
hopefully
oh yeah
[Music]
level
who do I get to choose a subclass now I
wonder
I think subclass additional rage charge
nice
okay I get to choose a subclass gonna go
Brazilian okay okay we'll need to take a
moment maybe look at the Spells oh yeah
everybody okay no more cleric I'm done
being a Claire yeah I think the one I
wanted to do was a college of lore oh
should I go for this one now that's a
good one
guys wanted me to take this one
[Music]
yes okay
so is it even with animal enemies like
the work just now that I could speak
or just like random toggles and so on
yes also with the works oh okay I'm
gonna hit the shop really quick don't
mind me I can now speak with animals
let's go
should be helpful I take Shield or magic
missiles magic Missile useful I gave you
a one magic Missile scroll so you could
test it out well not now obviously oh or
I'm taking orb nevermind I'm getting an
orb or pretty good yeah
Thunder damage lightning damage okay
ignore okay
do not the subquest was already the one
I wanted to be I think
[Music]
that was what I already chose
I think beforehand yeah I remember that
um
[Music]
Cass speak of animals
friends are strong
okay until long rest
so until we rest I can speak with any
animal are there any animals here I
haven't seen anything
are you animal
and I can use Chad I can use frenzy
without using rage first correct
Pals hmm
do it
oh wait why do I have to press this
again
and can I speak with my own animals
frenzy replaces rage
I see
for better rage okay
oh my God
[Music]
I'm taking this
why is it following your calories that's
my best friend
sorry guys I walked into something
else oh
what let me listen wait what happened I
don't know
oh I see you're in the hollow I was
gonna talk
a bear oh cute
cute yes oh did you just walk into the
crab
yes can I talk to that bear now can I
talk to your crab
I'm not wait you also have speak with
animals yeah I'm a I'm a gnome so no
one's can speak with animals
a little bit then I shouldn't have taken
because
you step back
[Music]
I'm talking with a cow
I have enough salmon
no um
[Music]
I am going to bring in our song
oh some new good armors whoa that's sick
I stole your Raven
head you're Raven's mine how could you
be Savage your Raven likes me uh I can't
help it uh you know I I understand it
because I like you too
it is what it is
[Music]
pretty good
oh I see your bird cute you can talk to
these uh you can talk to these cows I'm
doing it right now
be gone I'm hungry eat my eat my Raven
oh
yeah you're right I don't need armor
cause I'm a barbarian I Gotta Get Naked
bye
oh okay I forgot uh Callie can you do me
a favor what's up uh when you have time
can you save and reload the game I'm
stuck in combat music probably because
of the whale thing oh
you got it hugs let's go bugs the moment
success no prob actually what's wrong
with this
[Music]
oh
what I just rolled a success
um
speak right
[Music]
oh all right
through the carved door is the cow being
mean to you oh oh sorry you had to quick
load the game it's okay
I should have said something I am very
sorry I should have said I'm quick
loading the game
pardon me
pardon dude I'm sewing gross like the
power I have I don't know what's
happening
there are people like praying and they
were really mean they did not want to
let me in but then oh are you fighting
them no no one's fighting me I'm just
talking to people ah
all good the music's back thank you see
no problem deeper in the Grove ah wait
this one's good
come on give me a good roll they're
gonna eat you Kyle you better tell me
yay
Battlefield blood not resist death but
embrace it
Ah that's my job oh hello it's a pig
hello
oh
we're waiting
to confident oxide
apparently animals in this game are
jerks
I believe it
this this
um this pig wants a mate
yes the refugees
oh my god oh it's a bird it's Marissa
hello who's gonna say looks like shadow
yeah that's the one I summoned I can
summon two apparently
familiar and another one
anything
[Music]
fine I won't kick the bird are we down
in the Grove
I love these random animals following us
treasure hunting
you guys get down in there I just walked
in they were like cool
team never returned
right
must have done something right
okay
oh
I held to the birds
don't don't hurt the bird
heart fancy myself I think that the
Druids won't like that yeah but it has a
shiny key though I'm gonna yoink this
key from the bird
you pickpocket bikini look at the bird
no I'm just borrowing stuff thanks bird
oh
my God what happened what happened
what's happening
[Laughter]
I didn't mean realize that I thought I
would talk to it but I took it
they don't seem to have noticed no they
they did I'm in a cutscene right now
they didn't notice it was you the thing
y'all just lost
oh gosh
you have started a conflict
yeah oops
an actual
or why are they all running well okay it
does seem that they are cool
let's reload I'm so sorry I will not
take the idol again
this is wait hold on there's a little a
slight spoiler though which is why I'm
confused in the campaign there's a child
that steals it oh huh yeah well today it
was me
huh
we would have taken them it was supposed
to happen I mean I think it'll happen
regardless maybe maybe not it's just the
difference of who does it I think the
child tried to steal it and she failed
apparently it just tried okay we're back
to here um
[Music]
are you trying to deceive the cow now if
he failed before I before I did yeah
watch me face my dice roll this time
well I already saw the oh yeah
follow cougar every day I feel like I'm
stuck in a Time Loop man this is the
first time I'm talking to this cow
so what are we actually
um doing in here
looking for someone looking for the
looking for the Healer we're looking for
Nettie
this lady because of this she said she
told me where she is if you talk to
episis over here she tells you where
where she is
foreign
by the pig
I use few words
oh no
YOLO
bolo
hmm
they go this way
can I have your key
little bit of leg
you like
oh
first edition
Volo we believe in you
Square
oh I found I found another bard
nice
[Music]
I'm talking to his Queen wolves
what do you think
oh no
[Laughter]
it must take the thing I am strong
enough
did you stole from the bird
well if we didn't reload
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
squirrel because I had critical success
chaotic
wait
oh my God
I only we only have to kill these two
people
you guys know you guys are fighting
five above me
I'm in my battle
uh you can't steal things wait where are
they you can't steal I lost the roll
okay roll away this one I won I won the
[Music]
you gotta tell me hey Maury I'm about to
do a really risky action save the game
so show
maybe you're proud of your critical
squirrel
maybe you can do it in the next life one
more quick load okay
[Music]
then we lose the bear because we just
gotta play foreign
why did humans get mad at me for
stealing the birds key I don't
understand nature they love nature
they're Druids so yeah don't steal
anything don't steal
you want to be friends with these guys
you can steal from the Goblins okay well
no it seems like it seems like they're
being kind of corrupted they're being
kind of like racist to the tieflings and
stuff you know like they're they're yeah
like they're bad yeah so I think I mean
uh it's it's hard you actually need to
Bonk on the head yeah they need a bonk
on the head but we need to find them
with our so not with our ass here I can
tell you where Nettie is listen to me
she's in a room through the carved door
deeper in the Grove
so that's what she says
and I'm not touching the bird because
I'm scared okay I'm gonna talk to the
bird yeah again oh my God I lost this
one saved the game oh thank God no it's
okay I won't I won't eat it if I fail
every day
I'll I'll be good
and for the sake of plot I'll be good
yeah and we will be safe I know how you
really want to play it it's fine
uh
I'm gonna add guidance
I'm gonna go find that Bard lady again
she was cute
so I'm kind of curious I wonder if she
can join our team
okay save it so I don't have to kill
this bird yes okay
we're good now and
yeah I'm chilling by the stone door
what's going on here where we can find
the Healer and there's so much lag here
wow hello there buddy oh stone door yep
right over here
once we go inside the healers inside
I was having trouble okay
[Music]
it's ready to enter
sorry save the game I saved the game yes
all right into the stone door
mm-hmm
shall we follow yeah sure that'd be cool
there's a small child here no
they haven't played at all oh
wait it's like a dragon snake
oh dude
uh what is the girl's actual crime
put one of your guards outside said you
wanted to see me here I am
no care about this
want to smash
all right well that's a little messed up
I do have a moral compass it's not cool
[Music]
let's go Mario pay mad all right I got
these added so let's go please work
let's go let's go
my son yeah
[Music]
I want to see her roll I can't see her
roll
I got 20. it worked okay
Let Her Go nice persuasion
my Grace has its limits oh thank you
that was really cool Mario
yeah the house is great I think you guys
will really like Allison
um
so cool chest here I'm not gonna open it
of course because that would be thievery
[Music]
come on
Silva
what a pretty dog
well it says nice goodies in here that I
will not be taking because we're friends
[Music]
guys we lost I lost it I went to Romeo
Valley well what's up nerissa where are
you guys
we went into the where you said Nettie
wise yeah
I don't I don't know where that was
either okay I'll leave and then you can
see where my icon is yeah yeah yeah yeah
well let me know here I come okay let's
uh all right I'm outside okay follow
where my icon is okay okay wait yeah I
see it okay I can get there you can go
back in thank you all right you're
welcome I saved games
I save game every two seconds yeah
because I accidentally steal the idol
again
oh did you find the Healer yes nice oh
I'll start a conversation she's healing
a barb
good woman
oh
[Music]
um
excuse me and more important than some
bird now whoa who rude anything I can do
to help
why the feathers like so weirdly what a
weird bird
I'm looking for nothing need help now
don't need help now
do you know anything about mind players
much grace I've got plenty of them
I wish it was a frog tadpole
I'll be kind of gross too though oh yeah
what other kinds are there it's not like
a frog hopped into my arms
help me
but there's four of us can you help all
of us please
let's go she stole the ice
oh all of this stuff that she has I
can't pick up sad I don't know she'll
get mad at me
hahaha
you should you should have expected to
be a thief
I really should huh
you've showed great metal at the gate oh
the metal unskilled sword for higher
I won't just provide your services
find whatever bro he runs to and report
back to me remember you are only a scout
do not engage not kill anyone simply
observe and return I shall decide what
we do next M if they are not but who are
you talking to I was reading a letter on
this person's body ah
so you killed him and laid him on the
table is everyone being captured by
myself
this tail ends but one way
with the Outlander rot cleansed
and because you're not answering me
forever shrouded knowing you're given
the other cold shoulder eh
he's gonna stick it's pointy
eh
oh she does have a stick so what are you
gonna do with that
hit me with a pointy end
you can use the amulet to speak with him
oh nice idea maybe I'll do that after
this oh the bird does look like shadow
right
oh God Jesus what are the cats doing
what keep going do they knock down I
don't want to be so rude yeah
I'll take anything no tell me what time
oh baby any symptoms
oh I have a bug
you see that right
um I wonder if what I click is actually
though not what it seems to be and
I'll just checks okay okay
not that the others know they're victims
of course how'd you pick up the parasite
halson was desperate to find where all
this was happening
okay
um
help us
should I go for the first one I think
that yeah I'd go for the first one no
okay they're okay they're safe
with me so I'll be straight with you
thank you I'll watch you put the stick
away
oh cool okay
I'm sorry can you say that word again
how did she pronounce it was it wyvern
or wyvern
I would say why foreign
all right let's go
I swear to me you'll swallow it if you
feel any symptoms
I thought you could kill me what about
that branch of yours
quoted in a fatal toxin oh
bunny she said I was gonna kill you
she's very honest though saying that I
think she likes us at least she's nice
versus like the mean lady oh yeah
definitely yeah
yes
um uh I swear I hope it doesn't come to
that but I mean we can use it on people
yeah yeah
we'll be useful later I never once saw a
mind flare infection then suddenly
there's dozens of you guys maybe more
Master Halston and I were tracking pick
up a hint whoa what is uh what the hell
I like it apparently we can kill kaga
yeah cause you should all be changed and
I think we should
[Music]
I think we could I think we should kill
her
I mean I agree that she's well
identified but thank you
what do you mean should be changing
[Music]
first
I yeah maybe maybe we get we get house
okay yeah we can we can murder her yeah
I mean I I love violence yes I agree
with you seven gruesome days later we
only have seven days oh the thing we
need to stop sleeping it's different
it's already been like two days right
because I know right
it doesn't seem like we're turning into
my players is like the is the thing um I
see we're special so maybe it might be
more than seven days
um
hard to say maybe we're special
infectious of course we are have been
converging on an old Temple of saloon we
have plot armor we're the main
characters
we're heading that way he saw a chance
to get him oh okay let's go find him
okay he didn't make it back
mmm
go and get him
don't get him to find him but the place
is rotten with goblins it's okay we can
kill the Goblins yeah
technically speaking I mean they're
gonna kill someone carrying their
parasite oh you can
you get him out one of us one of us we
can discover what he learned
and perhaps he can save your life okay
how's that sound
hi
okay no they'll find him let's get him
it would mean everything to the groom to
me
you know what happened out there
oh and I can say for sure
is the all went to the old Temple of
saloon Master halson didn't make it back
sounds like there's a lot of treasure
to Temple temples of Fortress remember
your oath hi
hi
let's go let's go
oh yeah save save the game well for I
accidentally steal something
hold on I'm sorry guys just a moment my
cats are batting something around out
there no I don't want them to be batting
around I think they might try to swallow
so just people
oh
and is this so should I uh you keep this
because it's single use yeah to get you
a new outfit yeah help me seems like I
could use a keep it
drink it
I can code a weapon with it yeah the
syrian's armor too oh oh yeah
apparently there's a secret room if we
check behind a book case
real fun I took it I took it away from
them we're good on how they found a
little thing to play with a new toy
let's get out of here
wait wait wait apparently there's a
secret thing behind one of the bookcases
but all the bookcases are red meaning
yeah meaning if we touch them we'll uh
die we'll get to come back save the game
oh wait I got perception what was the
perception for
open locks
read Stone tablet
[Music]
yeah there's there's apparently a chest
so it'll lead us to her room and there's
this yeah oh
all right maybe my sneak
oh apparently this this door can open
but it's red
oh does it say locked or is it just yeah
it's locked and it's also red ah
yeah maybe maybe we go save we can lose
the stuff
not this room
we do
negative five bagel
what are they doing what are you doing I
didn't even do anything that time yeah
I'm sure it just randomly
I just readily making people angry
that's a big woof
[Music]
I want to talk to the rats
rats yeah the rats surely have a lot to
stay
can I kick this one too did you find it
I found the servants quarters what about
you oh
boring
I want to kill the rats okay kill the
rat though I can't I can't they won't
let me do anything it's a little cool
[Music]
I mean I think you probably can you
probably could kill the rat if you I
don't know
come here come here come here The Druids
alike okay I found it where are you oh
you found it but I don't know how to get
into it it's locked
I heard a click probably need a key
maybe you could pickpocket the key oh
wait how did you guys
walk around okay you go from up here
you're nice I thought I picked up a
thief kit
I mean if no one's here to see us please
um
anyone else not sleight of hand same my
sleight of hand uh only got six even oh
I can roll yeah yeah I'll try it try it
give it a shot
nice
oh you succeeded
all right Luke Goblin it's up to you
I just want to see what's in it I just
want to say what's in it
we're not we're not okay no one saw me
so yeah yeah and they can't just sense
that it's on you right so yeah what did
you get okay let's let's go let's go
what did you take what was inside uh
let's see there was a ruby there was a
is there a Nook someone said yeah okay
I'll read it okay um read
the Mars crisscrossing the page don't
look scribe so much a slash uh kaga
swamp docs tree meet me alone allodon
okay I don't know where the swamp is oh
no Don wasn't that one other rats oh oh
we got a quest though we got a quest for
it we do Journal updates
well done all of that is one of the rats
okay
Brad talk to me
rat Whisperer
do we follow all of that I don't know I
only heard the last word all of them
that's all I registered in my brain
[Music]
doesn't say anything
Madonna's not actually a rat maybe we
can make him say something
cool
um
I'm beginning to feel like
hold on
let me talk to you again
now speak to the rat
no okay it really doesn't want to talk
okay I guess we gotta go with a swamp or
something
yeah well let's go
okay they want me to talk to the tafling
leader and they she's like get them out
uh yeah that's right get him out so we
could just like escort the tifflings out
of here read the book I have to read the
book you heard what happened to the
squirrel understandable
balance is a myth where any clowns trust
nature struggles he already is a fiction
man of mere flesh seek only to tame
beast and raise Flora we are the Thunder
and we are the rain we shatter Mankind
and grow new life in its place okay it's
amazing
I'm looking at your outfit before I just
realized can you give me your cleric
outfit
oh can you wear heavy armor I don't know
I don't think you or can you wear medium
armor I just I just want I just want to
change out of what I'm wearing now
here I'll give you oh
I'll give you
a series okay
we don't know where they'd go in my
items perhaps yeah just checking your
bag
um
I thought I did did I need to pick them
up I don't have it
wait who did I give it to
I I gave it to you right yeah you have
it a padded armor okay yeah I was in the
wrong I was in the wrong
um uh can I uh live for uh two minutes
or one minute
go for it we can eat some chips too
Cali yeah you're in um underwear yeah uh
so the reason for that is because um as
like a bird as a barbarian yeah it's
better that you don't have uh armor oh
okay are you sure about that
is that an actual thing
I may have been LED astray here
um they're basically they don't count as
armor okay
your normal clothes don't count as arm
okay well I mean okay this is bad I mean
okay I'm not bad
well you have you have like a six pack
yeah you know she she works out yeah
it's almost an eight pack you know we'll
get it there though
is that does that look better are you
happy and new clothes Marissa they look
good on you yeah yeah I feel much more
comfortable not in the ugly default
clothes
I could I could play a little ditty
mmm they're not what I meant to do
yeah that Tyrone it's not it's just the
equipment armor you don't need gotcha
it can work with that hey nice tune
thank you I'm sick I like it
well what the
what the did you what was that what
was there
I didn't do anything
there was nothing in the pot
you could throw the pot
well
oh my God
[Applause]
oh my God look at that
mine are way more decent than yours okay
now this is the top isn't the top so
cute like it is but put some pants on
please
these panties are the ones that that guy
was wearing yeah I mean yeah maybe maybe
not the yeah
is
how do I take my clothes off
okay you look like you're about to go to
Coachella
[Laughter]
I mean the hair the Buns the colorful
buns and those clothes you look like
you're ready to go
really likes Coachella
oh that's actually kind of cute yeah oh
wow oh at her you will look Bijou but
not at me
good thing I can't I'm gonna quit my my
uh instrument because half covers wait
wait wow let's keep it on keep it on
your character
together oh my God at least give me a
jump scare warning
look at those ladies yeah oh my God
what is the stream turning it's just a
it's just a strawberry
um Banner please
okay thank you and Cali too in those
okay okay I don't think they're
unfashionable yeah the cheeks are
protected yeah your cheeks are very
detected they're very strong I need
another vase to throw at you guys
okay how do we make progress where are
we going oh yeah yeah we got distracted
no not at all very very distracted no no
no no no that's okay
um now here's what we can do
yeah let's go yes
I really want to steal the idol again
you know I don't know you should do that
it's just it's I don't even stolen
though it's still there don't do it I
want to fight something okay wait let's
save let's save let's save and test our
power level
what's going on here all right okay
everyone get close bye get get close so
we can all be kind of together
okay wait okay are you tell us when
you're done
okay
I I won't grab it I won't grab it until
you guys say you're ready
but I just want to see if we can take
take the idol you know
on Friday wait can you hide I'm trying I
don't think there's a lot of people
around I think that yeah the sight of
them is listening to widespread
oh
yeah see that in history let's go oh
nice unbelievable
yeah no they they're they're questioning
they're like why are you sneaking around
they're watching
this is a legend
he's a legend
oh
yeah oh I have an idea okay
are we ready to do this
okay hold on we need to wait for kiwama
to be ready
uh
he's a lore important NPC legendary
figure in DND
[Music]
okay uh there was no drunk all right how
do I play my songs for some reason I
only have the option to do bartic
inspiration and I don't want that I want
to do my actual song playing is there no
like regular I I think I broke it
something performance because I don't
remember how to get to my regular
performance
I mean it's like at the bottom okay yes
I found it I found it you were so smart
thank you
you passed a performance check playing
as a barred the NPCs will come watch you
play your instrument and then biboo can
pickpocket them from behind me oh yeah
yeah
just for the future oh someone's here
maybe don't pickpocket him maybe maybe
[Music]
everyone can see
okay here let me see if we can distract
these people
maybe probably not but
we'll just see I'll Stand between these
ones
okay I think they're busy I think so too
but just yeah just forget they're doing
like their blessing you know
yeah but I'm a Barbie
they're ignoring you
know
don't ignore me
oh the boy likes it oh yeah
[Music]
that's so adorable look at him look at
him dancing shaking his little butt it's
so cute
that is so adorable I'm done okay save
and let's oh we actually tried this okay
why not
okay okay come here and I'm gonna do
something okay okay what are you gonna
do
oh hey
yes
okay go get it there's a fog Cloud go
get it
huh
nice okay wait what oh no they noticed
right away
I mean they were blessing it like two
seconds
welp I'm
there it is oh you gotta watch this guy
get beat up again yeah yeah watch his
skull get bashed in it was free pretty
sick
you know that heard him
oh yeah that's gotta be painful
how
well like oh he's feeling it wasn't it
was his fault no ow they're just blaming
the tieflings for a lot of things
apparently I don't understand
[Music]
it's not very nice so okay
are we battling or are we running
battling of course we wanted to fight
something you're gonna shoot the bear
the Corvette yeah tough it
he's gonna try to kill us
[Laughter]
we're in a fight guys so many people
yeah I don't know man I I don't think
there's a way to win yeah
well we can always just reload again too
if you guys really don't want it's true
I guess yeah since our since our plan to
steal the idol didn't work with the with
the smoke cloud
what was that yeah I don't think you can
steal the Idol without getting everybody
upset sadly
oh attack our creatures eyes and blinded
oh
you can see yeah
we can't kill the Bear right
what's happening good job shadow oh oh
your weapons
he's still naked
and webbed you alrighty let me trust my
because I grow
they're like
photos
nice
I fly somewhere safer
probably not
dang
oh that's cool I'll throw them
apparently they kill all the tieflings
when you do this so even if you beat it
all the people yeah it's a little messed
up oh that's silence
don't get a good idea if if you guys
want to kill a bunch of stuff we can go
to the goblin temp okay
wasting our time
I was trying to win a battle we are
going to lose against the Bears if I
drop my ax
no somebody heated your metal and melted
yours
um Cali a voice of reasons
I I remember where the goblin Camp is by
the way
make our way over there yeah yeah I
remember nice I follow I have only ever
gotten as far as the goblin cam how's
that I do not know what happened okay
so let's we gotta exit the town first
I'm following you
yeah just follow follow Mario Pez lead
that's all let's look at Cali's butt
while she's walking up the stairs
let's go let's go oh yeah there's a
shopkeeper by the way if you guys want
to buy items like healing potions Etc
wait which one which one
uh up here uh past these cows there's uh
a merchant does he have ice arrows
selling stuff here
maybe I think I saw ice arrows really
cool I'm pretty sure that I saw some in
the inventory but you might want to yeah
grab grab some stuff really quick
just some bits and Bobs I no longer need
oh he has armor oh
he does have ice Arrows by the way yeah
as well
can I sell all these weapons uh guys I'm
sorry yeah what I'm stuck oh wait no I
got out I gotta it's fine it's fine oh
uh one at a time yum one at a time
that's too realistic I know it'll even
go this way I'm just gonna open up this
part of my map oh I can actually we can
fast travel there and go oh yeah let me
know when you guys are done shopping
okay I'm just selling stuff okay
oh money
how do I get him to give me money oh
give me money
give me all your money
come
on you can do that
we should be getting drunk at least
no fun waiting for that so well he's
right
okay
definitely has a frost Arrow
can I okay it's a good idea
make use of your services please yes
okay only one person
doesn't will normally appear around here
you guys
uh doesn't he like show up and he's like
hey and he's like teaching the
yeah is he gone he's not here
he's gone
uh he's not very bad
surely we'll run into him again we
didn't kill him
we don't have will can we not find
wait I don't know who that is but I'm
down to find whoever oh no no no you
don't need vote for Carla
I don't think
man who's parlax
the hot demon yeah
um
oh um do I need any of this I wonder if
he's worse I wonder if he's where like
he killed me
um
[Music]
should we go look
I'm gonna go check I'll go with you
around where I died
I really hope he doesn't aggro me if
he's there though
we just need to have a chat with him
yeah
oh if you go to Carlock first he will
find you apparently oh okay so we could
we could go find her yeah what's
bartering
where she is and stuff we need to look
up first oh he is there oh I'm scared
I'm scared
maybe just go talk again maybe yeah see
the game save the game first
hello hello
are you okay
hold on I wait I have no money oh I
can't even click on him yeah I can't
interact either how do I have no single
money
how is that possible we're broke any
gold I got gold but didn't I did I I
feel like I picked up money before
you remember opening like a chest and
having yeah several I mean I thought it
was cold
oh well I'll sell things
gotta loot more
yeah
I dug that up that was my treasure thank
you I'm never helping you again
yeah I'll give you I'll give you some of
the loot you wanna I wanted the girls
across the party
yeah
how much more was it money is shared in
the party it is it yeah then I guess we
don't know it goes on zero okay did
people use up all the group's money oh I
didn't I didn't buy anything weird
well it was definitely on zero and now I
I made some money but
someone said to try attacking him but we
don't want him to aggro is shared
apparently so
we can but we don't have she has to send
it to you
is party gold is 329. aha
nice so I guess technically we can use
each other's money yeah I mean if you
guys need some gold I'll give you some
gold
okay territory right now I could just
take y'all's stuff I'm gonna do that I
won't but I could is the thing
um
[Music]
oil I know you can't make it go boom
yes I can I will I will punt you so far
over the mountain if you steal something
else
it doesn't do anything huh
okay
um
and anything else that's worth buying
here
would be common drops luckily really
okay
okay yeah I have the amulet I can't talk
to that
yeah you gotta talk to the Dead Guy
it's cool I'll talk to him later when I
quit this please I want to look and see
if I can buy anything
ah uh yes uh green green bow green bow
sorry I'm blind uh uh
there's green green I'm blind I'm so
blind
um
[Laughter]
this Wing okay okay that's that's okay
cool insufficient gold uh oh that's
expensive I'm never reaching that money
um
yeah
um yeah maybe another time Sylvanas oh
calm down
your attitude better well met is there
anything you need I wonder if she'll
know it just some bits maybe another
time what did you do
what are you doing here
I did something good go check
yeah what'd you do so look in your
inventory
and I don't know what's different
look at Cali's inventory I see gold
I don't know how to even look at other
people's inventory do I put this press
tab I love this it's just mine okay
Andrew do you not do you not see my
message
is there a message
oh it's not reflected oh man man too bad
I spelled something for you in your
inventory but I guess it doesn't uh
oh yeah yeah it says
why are you fighting I'm gonna take your
word for it
saw it
that's the idea yeah that's very strange
I mean
she just placed the items in an order
that makes it look like a letter I see
it on Console no I'm using a controller
oh it's different with a controller I'm
ready let's go okay let's go to the
goblin hands
we got some goblins to kill
let's gobble those goblins up gobble
gobble
saved a turkey in person
[Music]
why not they're huge they're
terrifying that thing called body you
boo
I'm sure all of you have seen the turkey
for Thanksgiving I mean like a live
turkey eggs they make me feel so
powerful when I eat one you know I have
some big ones that used to live near the
old my old place
[Music]
I remember seeing some cross the road
once and I was like holy
oh my God
before we go to the goblin place I want
to
make a little detour I remembered
something okay all right there's it's
combat though okay we're ready to fight
we gotta go ah already saved let's go we
gotta go this way oh we gotta see the
dog too hold on yeah the dog the dog's
over here
mama
[Music]
right
oh God and when animal mouths move right
yeah
[Music]
I'm not an enemy she would just you just
hear the sound
so one candy
oh I can make it I can make it yeah I
believe
I believe in people power
is death in your scent yeah
you should go
a friend I think your friend is
dead
[Music]
he's with his God now I'm sorry not over
yet
and then we have a Revival scroll
Revival fly I have a skeleton here here
come with us come with us
I won't leave him oh he's
his court his name is scratch he's so
cute
um here
follow my sentence
I may atiku never leaves the side office
okay now now he may show up okay
okay another detour we are going over
here there's combat it's the combat
detour all right let's do it
I'm ready to fight
always ready to fight
me too me too I want more fights I've
spent too much time in that City yeah
yeah yeah
it's okay we got a Goblin suit and then
we got this
okay take all those goblins
I need you to kill the mom and not kill
the child okay remember this yeah yeah
yeah yeah kill them
not not the kid okay hella cash okay
yeah I don't want to kill a mother
well she wants to eat us oh okay yeah
that's that's okay
she's really mean
hey maybe you guys should wait for me
Mia Wawa oh yeah yeah yeah
I know it does not end through without
y'all yeah so we're not like spread out
super far
I loved a little bit
yeah okay let's go
oh
okay well you can talk to her actually
because you can talk to animals okay
I have a little cat how do I talk about
uh oh no just walk up to her okay okay
oh it's never though oh oh and the race
is already talking I didn't mean to
oh
do you have animal handling no
well time to get eaten
we were planning on that no please no oh
lunch time yum yum yum yum yum yum yummy
so pretty
[Music]
well
we have to kill it I know
oh nice striking while the iron is hot I
guess
up in the air like you look at her go
kind of Awesome
[Laughter]
oh
um
can't go so far so go as far as you can
oh fly to Target's position
[Music]
um
the baby
hold on
hold on don't worry
um
the baby is coming to defend his mommy
um this is a bonus hour and then I can
also do a rage attack
ah
I feel like you're scarier with
underwear on intimidating
she's cute
oh
let them bleed
oh oh
my God oh God it's really angry
oh her voice came out of it
who killed the baby uh did someone
why are you freaking out I don't know
but the baby's still okay okay good a
crap crap
you can grab something
crab crab no crab attack crab cannot
attack
maiming pinch I'm like one step too far
away
uh
I believe well
crap Maybe
maybe act as a fate
damn it that would have been so epic if
the crab would have gotten the kill
[Music]
and now I now listen to the baby yeah
yeah someone who can talk to animals
preferably
don't kill the baby where is it it's
over yeah let's save let's save real
quick before one of us accidentally
kills it
okay I'll talk to babble yes don't you
guys get the egg yeah
don't um don't ask
supplies by the way okay hungry
don't do it
whoa
wait why do we why do we have to leave
him here uh we will we will find
him again later he'll come back to kill
us because we killed his mom no no we we
we'll take him as a pet yeah so there's
a shrine back here yeah look we can't do
anything with it because it's sealed by
Magic uh I want to go look
I remember correctly because I see it I
see a chest
yeah it's sealed by Magic so if you try
and open it
oh
don't touch the chest I think me and uh
oh yeah now also people we might wanna
you know heal
ing
I broke my legs oh my god
um do it do a short rest yes please oh
yeah sure no problem
so it when you try to open the chest is
that when you got damaged yeah
does that happen to everybody who
touches their chest oh yeah I think so
even I want to touch it I know
they're dedicated to Saloon imploring
all to accept the moon maiden's blessing
and share in her Bounty I like her
no religion failed
oh wait I think I have religion there's
a prayer behind the statue
how do you jump again
in front of the chest it's one of the
actions on the
who has good religion I have plus one I
think
it works
eh did you get stuff
oh
what
necklace Bloodstone Idol
pendant
oh nice okay now we can go kill some
goblins okay go pretty works all right
goblins goblin killing times
suck yeah
you don't have to pass the check if you
just know what to do yeah wow
pretty nice it's true
just an old prayer
[Music]
seems simple yeah well I mean I'm not
smart I'd be dumb no I'm not stupid it's
okay
do we have who's the smartest one in the
in the party again me in terms of uh
game stats
I see
oh I see
okay
I think up there is Goblin yep up here
yeah we got across oh wait yeah that's
right across the bridge and then we go
that way yeah I will wait
yeah I'm trying to catch up
um any charismatic people want to lead
the way oh oh yeah charismatic we're
both we're both charismatic
yeah you guys can you know take the
charge
wait there's no one here
huh good luck what why did they get mad
I don't know
they didn't even give you a chance to
yeah no one
oh they're up there they're on top of it
yeah
ow
I am here now this is I did not have to
fight this so I'm not sure how this will
work we'll figure it out get it here and
help us Goblin yeah Goblin goblins okay
well we wanna Goblin let's go let's go
oh not where are the memories they're
they're on the roof yeah huh or the
house right next to us yum what what
um
Alex really don't see them okay you see
where I am they're a little hard to go
to the left
and in the middle of that roof and then
there's also one at the end if you go
down just downward
with an arrow
okay well we want to combat here we are
I guess
oh well okay
yes I can't do anything
let's go bird let's go
through the front door how does the
flying work
can I not
what what does that mean not enough
resources
oh it means you are used in action or
something yeah movement
Etc
oh there's another guy
oh
can I get some from oh can I get them 65
percent
hello
[Music]
these other ones
yeah that's a little
not so digable
oh I missed that would have been so
awesome
um yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
I'll be fine I know what to do with them
there's one on the other side
um and then there's one inside the house
oh that was good
you really couldn't take me talking to
him like that he said yeah I love your
insult insult me please I could never
you're
perfectly Point discovered
[Music]
don't die
I'm on fire
we can get them well let me get a bit
closer
look at that
oh nice nice
[Music]
take him down
go burp go
no why not rip go here
oh
broke getting closer
archers okay
if this this person has a ball right so
that means they won't attack me if I
move behind them right
probably yeah okay it's fine okay
the building below
here we go don't miss
[Applause]
[Music]
him so good and I feel myself
a couple left I think two goblins left
but now that we got the Waypoint we can
return to Camp as well if you guys yeah
okay
he's cool oh your words are very strong
my words are hurtful
it's my job
demon Awards not soup or song
oh never say if you go too far into the
village you'll aggro more people oh okay
I'll stop moving in I thought I needed
to get by the Waypoint to unlock it
yes
nice okay there's one in the house and
then one by Marissa this one by me
yeah there's one right in front of you
oh I mean
oh yeah inside the home
almost forgot about that
I'll fight him first
that's all right I can survive this you
got it
oh
are you okay okay I have one HP yeah I
like how do I get this person
can I like shoot it from the
oh I wish you guys he only had free HP
that's why I didn't do it I'll do it on
the next Target
Cali only one HP what the Yeah that's
okay I'm good don't worry about it it's
not okay I'm good
you're bleeding you get in there you can
damage I guess it's the address
oh
I don't know where the other oh there's
one in there
take the killing shot on Cali what
excuse me so you can get a keeper
healing potion when we're literally
about to go rest at the camp
so I'll just chill here
you guys might need the help though I'm
not close enough I'm sorry
maybe I will pop the ocean
take the shot get him
oh
[Music]
nice
and I wanted to check out these bodies
oh fire everyone here
that fire arrow
okay
oh
my God
okay
I have endless response isn't this nice
okay we're done should we go to the camp
Camp yeah all right we've got this uh
already all right so let's let's go back
to I'll take us back to the camp yes
uh and leaving us a ride
oh I think you guys gotta return on your
own oh
so it's in the scroll wheel same one
where you like go to your inventory and
stuff okay
icon click that
dlss
I'm Gonna Save really quick
victory
it's chilling with one HP at the camp
all good I'm just hanging
let's all take a little nap
what a bed
come on the camp wishes to speak to you
oh you want to speak to us they always
keep wanting to talk to us why are there
too well
what why is he why is there two of them
[Laughter]
what is going on
[Music]
what let him cook I don't know what's
going on but I'm into it he says
what's he gonna do with himself
make an army out of himself right
all right oh Shadow heart wants to talk
to me really
oh no we gotta talk to Shadow heart
are you hurt him I'll protect you always
Shadow heart
oh Gail what are you doing here this has
nothing to do with you brother
let him live
oh please I failed oh yeah he's like
right behind you wait what you made her
mad how deep is this inventory you can
talk to her separately can't you
know
did I aggro her forever no she's she's
fine we should get to know each other a
little more
yeah
I think her like you
us
[Music]
huh somebody said don't don't put the
silver and open oh I think I'm raising
her up yeah let's go maybe I'd like to
get to know you better what if I do
come on I don't want to watch this
yeah do we have what happened to go on
what happened to a Starion wait oh wow
whatever she's wearing is very sexy
okay
for now I'll leave her beef and I won't
press how do I oh see don't even work
she approved of me okay oh nice you're
getting it I'm I'm doing it I'm doing it
um I'm sure we'll get along perfectly
well she likes what is the other half
okay
okay there's no story
entitled okay anyway I'll I'll talk to
her again later when when we have more
time I don't think she wants to talk to
me she doesn't want to be interrogated
right now
gotta give her her space you know yeah
gotta give her space
all right ready for sleepy mine
yes
[Music]
sleep sleep
Supply pack we're gonna need to steal
more of these from the goblin yeah
saving her ribs for the real prize you
caught me
ah so we got the dog
where where dogs
oh
no
who is a good dog
[Music]
that's so sadly scratch
all right oh he can talk to me
um sorry about what happened to your
master
friend
oh
monster
stayed with him until then until I knew
he was gone
the pets pets you can pet the dog 10 out
of 10 games you can pet the dog
I mean you're small enough you could use
yeah the dog is a seed
a dog
everyone approves when you pet dog pet
him again
does he ever like say stop that I wonder
maybe not you know can I keep petting
him
oh thank you that's nice oh I can only
leave now
um
well he liked it yeah
okay shall we save now that we're all
full health
yeah a good idea good game
um
goblins
all right
another another crab
[Music]
how about this
whoa
that's so cool that's a big one I didn't
expect it to be so big I did I wasn't
expecting a spider
look they look so similar
same amount of of legs and hands yep
[Music]
you've got a good point
um an armored spider aren't shrimps the
Cockroaches of the sea or is that crabs
big crab
perhaps are cute they couldn't be
cockroaches of the sea just like you
you're cute too
[Music]
[Applause]
everybody
likes me
[Music]
amazing
wow
ah the gold why
I thought Advent was like really
friendly with each other
it's always going on
oh there's a lot of blood test I guess
we gotta sleep one more time because
y'all are injured no we can just load
the savings we can just we can just
short rest
oh wow
time to load the save
it too
I have nothing to say
try me again
don't let me shoot you with my lightning
Dylan
you you hit me first I just it was a
lifetime it literally did one damage
after we just healed mm-hmm
down down down down by the river
[Laughter]
[Music]
all right what do we want to do you guys
okay
fight fight but like actual enemies wait
did we end the date we did okay yeah
yeah how do we leave the camp
um so I'll leave well you go first uh
it's the scroll wheel where I don't know
how it is for PC um
click the bonfire again
ah okay
um all right we're in the blighted
village which okay this is close to
where we're supposed to go you may
follow me and well I know where the camp
is from here oh wait uh
I pressed the uh the the bed right no no
no no no
fire so go to the scroll wheel
um where like you have like level up
inventory Etc click the bonfire again
wait I can't click anything no it's
waiting for another player yeah
something's wrong cancel can somebody
cancel this oh you just have to wait
till the timer runs out yeah oh okay
yeah
ah that bonfire okay different bonfire
yeah yeah
the one on your home three two one the
only one of the scroll wheel I'm using a
controller sorry
leave Camp okay gosh I'm so hungry
okay mess with these guys I recommend
not really messing with the blighted
village right now
you gotta cross this bridge over here
might be locked across this bridge I
believe
okay well let's cross it okay Crossing
is there a reason you're letting me go
first
waiting for Wawa Chihuahua there's a
there's a there's like ogres in in here
yeah yeah
I don't think we can take them yeah
maybe yeah they're really strong and
there's three of them but don't worry
they haven't noticed me okay yeah maybe
you just yeah let's just keep going keep
going what's with the leg
are you sure we can't kill them
yes oh let's look let's keep going for
now maybe later okay come back later
yeah when we're really strong we can
beat them up behind
behind me
hi honey
no if you have high enough frizz you can
persuade them that you're cool okay okay
I have rays
oh good you saved it okay hello
hi
it's just boxing casually people go
alone first
can you convince them ew there's like
poop on the ground yeah unless you've
got another reason to be here what did
you just call me
yeah we don't need to hire those big
ogres yeah
bonds
I feel like that was a mistake do I have
perception oh I have deception okay let
me add guidance we'll give it a go
like yeah
oh I made it I made it nice
yeah yeah nice nice okay
yeah well
huh
stays down hey what's that supposed to
mean okay that's kind of rude
oh nice yeah
[Music]
how did we get here
absolutely not do it do it do it you
follow them now
you follow him dead
the sake of the team
the one you have to do um
um let me see is there anyone close by
I'll just Dash into battle
mm-hmm
oh mandalag
Bieber let me do everything next time
what so you were gonna put poop on you
yes
then why would you need to when you
could just kill oh bee boo
we need to make good relations so we
don't have to fight so much
why not it's fun yeah
yeah
oh oh
[Music]
go go Bird go fly as far as you can
and speed dance
you can speed up a dash okay
there is a large dark monster up here
that is very frightening
yeah I'm nervous
dark monster
what's that icon for it I don't know
what it is it's like a pitch black
spooky thing it took some damage already
behind us
[Music]
oh
oh there is one monster behind us you're
spooking me different one
oh my God okay wow sharp-eyed snerd what
a name
probably spider
um
the icon didn't load at all no it's
definitely there I see it it's very dark
um
pitch black portraits
hello goodbye
goodbye
classic
come over here
nice one spider good even though I love
that daggers
thank you for taking that damage for us
yes
wow why you so mad that's a good thing
sand damage good good good
oh
that really sucks
no no we're not we are not thriving
a better accuracy
oh can I talk to the work
even in the middle of a battle eh
oh oh no
oh yeah he's going for the alarm
[Music]
somebody
knock them dead
what's the matter
so the one that is behind us
oh bird is gone too oh
Shadow is dead there is a no bird for
you anymore
not my boys
what would you like to have next
you I can bring you almost any animal
food not kitty cat because I just don't
want to see how that ends ever again
anything else I feel you
that's right
oh
are you gonna kill him yeah okay please
I was about to say Jesus
get him
get him I'll get him
that's my girl
nice
I can't reach it it's my Loop okay
there's still one over there okay
probably should have walked I had to
walk around
wow
oh be careful be careful of the daggers
it's fine I'll just die in the water uh
the water is electrocuted
huh
my dad uses non-lethal I don't know it's
not why is it not toggled leave it why
is it say non-lethal damage I don't
understand this
okay I can't take it off
I have that too
I think no I guess if it's grayed out I
don't have it on or you can change it is
it grayed out for you oh
that's my own fault it's fine we go just
eventually
[Music]
yeah yeah yay and then I think I can
actually I can bring you back
knives well because I got an extra turn
I'll try and be like kind of bait I
guess this guy hopefully targets me
instead of you
got anything nice on you no
and taking a shot
okay we just got that one left
yeah
always going
oh I got you okay you try to run don't
let him leave
or
in holding back this whole time I can't
yeah electrocuted
nice go team
we're doing it is that it I think that's
it
[Music]
yeah we need need a short rest I'm
worried about narissa maybe the short
rest will be good yeah look at that
short rest real quick and I'll save the
game ah
yes right
[Music]
here bring my babies back I've never I
didn't go up there what do these guys do
what's happening
I don't know the goblin the temple is
over there
is over there but then there's these
guys what are they
miraculous
they're probably gonna want to fight
yeah so maybe maybe we'll just go to the
temple
sample time
I'll quickly change some graphic
settings oh what happened sorry whoa uh
brain worms Oh no
control yourself
Saloon
the Temple of the The Loon
whatever it is it's irresistible
[Music]
and the infinitely stronger I thought
I'm so beautiful
can she speak up I can barely hear her
louder
oh
that's an easy smile
why can't we see them young woman
oh yeah
[Music]
the weapons
oh
sick
elsewhere
whoa what is happening
the presents oh it's the tesseract
eh let's go take me to the underworld
like needles in my face let's go
[Laughter]
yeah wow
I raised volume I know so I didn't die
voice those visions
uh put the artifact away
yeah put it away
put it in the old pocket okay uh this is
another situation where I really think
you guys should go let me go behind in
case it turns into a battle and I need
the tank but I think in terms of
Charisma wait wait it's The is it is
what
oh he's performing for them
well even more lags I want to challenge
him to a rap battle
I reverted back
chicken chasing
let's go let's let's go guys
outshine that big silly
see they all came over when it was me
crank a brand new move he's so cute
backup dancer thank you
okay shall we move on
yeah yes I mean you've really captivated
them I don't know man I know I'm
distracting them wait I found
oh yeah
wait I want I want the owl bear
s
roasted dwarf flag
good evening what did I miss
anyways we're just in the camp we're
just chilling play the game
before we go into the temple
wait can you can you talk to the people
about the owl bear
give them a chat the game okay
they're only talking about Volo to me
oh it's so cute
oh chicken chasing sounds fun Count Me
In wow
are they gonna burn him is this like a
steak
oh I hope not
uh we gotta get rid of Volo first oh I
found a waypoint
all right I want to talk to the owl bear
okay we gotta get rid of Volo then okay
do you mean kill
no
uh I think
hold on dialogue is moving pretty quick
let's go
yeah very cool Volo tell it how it is
wow okay can you leave now
damn those rhymes
amazing
[Music]
oh come on I'm just telling you how it
is
you like you Lloyd oh man you failed the
deception check she's so British
yeah he's a shitty Barn
why is he here
I don't know
[Music]
I don't think he's doing very good
he makes up words like I do
Mari all right
sorry guys I tapped out it's crazy
okay
nice chicken chasing time
[Music]
you have tomatoes in the chat for Volo
no distraction time
well chat I don't know if it's normal
but it's taking up 38 49 of my CPU and
7500 of my Ram I don't know if that's
normal
oh that's a bit better now I guess okay
I'll place a bet
that's fine
I just saw that too it wasn't always
this bad but now it's fine wait
he's running oh
what's he doing I don't know wait how
did that Albert Cub even come here
was it already here before
in there
oh I can't use both okay I'll use
guidance okay oh
yeah
the Goblins get them
[Music]
small oh man he's very angry uh-oh hey
we're not involved in that battle Yeah
I think I think there's a straight arrow
that hits you might want to get out of
the way
oh baby
baby
[Music]
can we reload I don't I mean I can't
have it it was I don't think everything
here you you know we boo
but there's gonna be a better way to
help
[Music]
you can later apparently but yeah then
we have to bring him back to life
this little guy
and I don't know how long ago we we had
to save yeah I don't either
weren't we supposed to get something
super cool for leaving the mom alive
we're leaving the baby alive I mean you
take it yeah that's what I mean hell of
money I guess right
um
well shall we go thank guilt yeah are
you sure are you sure we're in Savory
silly
hold on a second I'll give it I'll check
it I'll check it out
alrighty let's see uh
last save the load game
um
have to do the Volo thing again but
that's fine
space bars
save scum I mean yeah
yeah
some people are saying you could group
them with a performance and then use all
the AOE attacks on them
oh nice that's you yeah that's a good
idea that's actually really awesome
so should we should we kill a ton of
goblins fur or yeah because they're not
fighting us I really don't want them to
fight us yeah I don't you really don't
need to I don't think we should enter
the temple yeah okay
I'm sure he'll find a way where is there
Albert is worth keeping around chat says
by the way
um I guess we can kind of skip this part
because we've already seen it
all right cool nice
let's Jump Right In out there I'm gonna
Boo this guy off the stage okay if you
can stealth it you can slip poison into
their boost tub
oh we got a voice do we have we do we
have the wyvern poison remember
where is their beer tops I'm down to try
uh but we should save before we do that
we should we should be getting rid of
this guy first sounds good get off the
stage
where is there okay I found it I found
it it's right here okay I just need the
poison because I don't have it
um I think uh game save
okay see I'm right here
um
crab looks so cute so what do you do
uh just poison you gotta put put it in
the Boost tub how do you put it in I am
not sure but there's a ton of goblins
around so
um maybe what if you did a performance
over oh yeah do a performance do a
performance let me let me gather them up
so they don't look at you
[Music]
hey wait another one's coming over so
oh
[Music]
okay wait there's a guy right behind you
guys yeah staring one is watching you
directly oh but his head he likes I
didn't do okay I didn't do anything I
got a sharp eye
yeah it's a good thing
oh yeah yeah it's a good thing
yeah it's an extra delicious it makes it
makes it tastier and she's talking to
him
yeah yeah yeah yeah
he's happy with it now
okay are you distracting people I'm
trying but they're not they're not
paying attention
let me let me try a different song
it'll give it
a kid why is he watching you like that
I mean I just would too to be honest
maybe maybe you guys why don't you walk
away from it for a minute and see if
they don't maybe you know walk away and
then you can try yeah nice idea
still watching me
yeah isn't you he's like the potion guy
looking at it it's like Fire Emblem
oh you ran up
nice
[Music]
hard to be The Bard
yeah yeah yeah people walk all the way
over here sneak sneak don't even sneak
come over here
foreign
they're taking some booze
they keep seeing me yeah there is
there's a guy the guy he's over there
yeah oh now he's gone oh my God made it
up but not the wolf okay what if I oh
wait this guy's leaving this guy's
leaving this guy's ah
okay did you get it
no there's too many people you're really
thirsty
whoa
oh I think you can
does this mean that they're not saying
anything that's in here because
okay it's poison it's poisonous okay
okay oh even in the red huh
huh what's happening let's all drink
boys we're gonna all die
ah no thanks thanks
what's happening fine because we toast
too
hmm
oh are you guys seeing what happens how
come I didn't get a cutscene
[Music]
um
okay well may I bet each and every one
of you before the sunset that's crazy
tell me what happened okay
I'm like uh
do the bartending drink
oh cool I've literally stopped let's see
how this goes oh why do I have two can
you enter the cut scene yeah it's okay
we're gonna make them drink it I trust
you yeah
surely it was a success yeah no it was
drink drink oh do your trick
I want to see it too but it's a banger
oh
[Music]
drink it up something's happening
oh yeah yeah
yeah oh
I didn't do it not me so what are you
talking about I literally just like
danced I did a jerky dance over there I
did the stinky leg that's literally all
I did I should have your arms ripped off
please please work because I need to
roll a 20. good luck
let's
[Music]
find I'll take a critical success
my freaking thought
Memorial hey
he knows nothing about nothing yeah
nothing yeah no I still think we should
kill him yeah so many of them are still
alive
yeah oh wait is bear okay now there's
only there's no
I should save the game yeah same
I'm saying
that was gangster
bear okay save him
he runs away
only time will tell if you yeah
[Music]
okay now yeah now we saved okay now see
yeah save the game okay
yeah we'll see what awaits this in here
yum real quick oh my God okay get out of
this leggy area
it's a lot smoother inside the temple
okay
oh yeah
get away we're doing the absolute one
it's a big idea yeah what's wrong with
your business oh what's our business
guys
a strange thing a great question
figure out a story
straight hmm
um
I've got an audience with the one in
charge
you have good deception I think yeah
to be a bit more specific though mate
absolute's got a few favorites oh dear
oh
boss rexley
or the drown oh we're here to see oh
definitely yeah
but she knows her business
she's Intel in the war Chiefs what's oh
next ride is gonna be a bigger oh yeah
restart the game
oh you know actually I was thinking
maybe we maybe we'll stop it here for
today yeah okay yeah okay we've been
going tomorrow
I've been streaming for five and a half
but yeah so the Journey Begins yeah yeah
the journey began and it's only going to
get crazier yeah
next time
yeah attempt yeah at least once a week
like to beat the camp that we really
want to yeah
yes yeah
more bowler skates
yes yeah no problem it'll be fun yes
um I'm hyped to see where our journey
takes us from here on Earth
yeah that was fun um I'm also kind of
playing on my own as well at the same
time with a different character so so
maybe next time you'll see some improved
gameplay
yeah thanks
turn into the Barbarian ways
Masterpiece of a character
he's after my own heart you never put
those clothes back on no way confident
lady you know it there's Shredder stuff
um so yeah everybody take care hope you
guys have a lovely day wherever you are
please hope you guys
you guys are uh doing well and have a
lovely day yeah yeah are you all ending
the stream uh I'm gonna talk for just a
little bit and then end so yeah I'm
gonna I'm Gonna Leave the call here
[Music]
all right
thanks for tuning in yeah
there's the cuties
guys that was so much fun sorry sorry
for being quiet I'm uh obviously just
learning and I've never played a game
like this really before and so I'm very
engrossed
if you couldn't tell if you couldn't
tell
um I was very into what was happening
there
um
that was really a load of fun
so I hope you guys thought so too I'm
looking forward to the next time we can
play
yeah no thank you guys for the poisoning
that that made that really freaking fun
[Laughter]
that was that was a fun thing to kind of
like end off the game on I think
hopefully you guys think so too
uh yeah that was that was interesting
I've always wanted to do like a DND
campaign type thing but I've never I've
never gotten to because uh it's not that
well you know I was also trapped in jail
forever but like
you know it's kind of hard sometimes
because like uh you don't really you
don't really have like for me at least I
I'm a very visual person so like I need
the visual aspect I I need the set I
need the nice characters I need it to be
immersive if I'm gonna do something like
that
um so this this is like as close as I'll
probably get to a DND campaign
kind of I know it's not exactly but you
know it's like game d d so I'm really
excited
I'm excited I'm really enjoying it but
um it looks like no one is live right
now for us to uh stream into but I do
want to let you guys know before I go
that I will be streaming again today I
know crazy since we already did
um just did a stream but uh we are going
to
yeah we're going to be we're going to be
playing Terraria tonight at 7 pm CT uh
six uh 5 p.m PST I believe and I'm
looking forward I'm looking forward to
it we're gonna be playing with fuel Moko
for sure and I believe actually all of
advent is going to join and then uh
hopefully some Senpai will pop in too
but in the meantime I'm gonna head out
so I can relax for a bit and eat some
food before I see you guys again tonight
so for those of you who join thank you
so much and for those of you whom I'll
see uh later I will look forward to it
so have a good day I'll see you guys
again soon
foreign
[Music]