[Music]
thank you
la la
laughs
[Music]
foreign
la la
[Music]
la
la la
[Music]
laughs
foreign
[Music]
oh
I got a key
and
[Music]
um
sounds so lame what no it's not bad
there's a reason I went for kikiriki and
not cock-a-doodle-doo yes the German
version it it's kind of yeah I'm
spelling it a little bit differently but
it's definitely how we would say it in
German
[Music]
tilt their heads to block their ears to
stop them from going Deaf from
themselves because it was so loud yeah
oh did you know KFC did you know that
thanks for the lore that's kind of crazy
it's really crazy actually
oh well we're back we're back we're
Baldur's back baby
[Music]
chat is the sound okay maybe the other
chats can answer it too
why
oh really uh maybe it's because I'm like
constantly lining up
wait let me try that lower my or my
wrapper hat
I'm lining up for you
I mean you're permanently lit up
actually yeah oh yeah you're permanently
oh that's weird
[Music]
there we go
according to uh Discord my buzzing is
like so loud I'm so sorry if it bothers
anyone it's not that bad if the music's
also in the background
from the background yeah okay good I
agree I feel like well you choose
lower I don't have to light up people
probably recognize my voice at this
point
I can't maybe I can get your PNG or
something what my opinion Jay now you
have it so that it doesn't it doesn't go
dark it just completely is not there
no it's there but it just it's just
permanently dark oh okay I'll give you a
bright PNG yeah give me a bright PNG
yeah there you go let's see how about
how about these it's from my thumbnail
today
oh yeah
I want this okay context I got a super
chat a while ago that was like probably
just a parody but they called me a
yellow ostrich streamer tanaki shakarya
and it just cracks me up all the time
yeah
honestly I thought that was hilarious
right it was great
don't worry about it
quit worrying about it I I finally
understand Cali thanks to me using Carla
in my private playthrough that you your
thing your class or whatever is like
stronger when you naked
yeah that's right well see here's the
thing is that like this I mean clothing
I could at least put on clothing that
isn't armor and that would be fine but I
just thought it's easier to cut to the
Chase and just be naked
assert your dominance yep
[Music]
changed my mind we're breaking up
oh nothing big or terrible just a small
little detail about me
likes you wow
the nipples
mind flayers death he's so naked hey
dude he is naked so naked naked little
guy but we just had this conversation
you just confessed to me he's a vampire
and I'm very confused I thought we
already went through that and then he
will leave
no you can't banish him all right
well man
can we permanently remove them from the
party no just kidding I'm joking why why
do you hate us I just pretend he loves
you
I'm a magistrate back in the city it's a
world
he's a magistrate oh my God what's
waiting for us I don't know
neither do I actually that sounds like
adult speak yeah right big words that
adults use
all right cool I get it moonrise Towers
uh well I don't need you in my party oh
game quiet okay
I'll cry to you guys uh small anyway
so today's uh leader we have decided
generally will be people but maybe if we
go to the tea house then the leader
there will be Kelly because she's the
only one who hasn't really seen the tea
house yet and it would be nice to have
some innocent mind going through it I'm
far behind
mm-hmm
oh that's okay oh we need to get the
lady that's the first thing we should do
yeah
yeah yes let's go I don't want to do
that let's leave we're missing
best your best wife Carla
can I meet you guys at blighted Village
play The Village yes oh yeah I'm I'm so
sorry that was not silly of me
aren't you the head of all of us Marissa
uh yeah but still I I can't go to this
area anymore so ah I see oh you can no
return
you can't go back here and after act
three you can't go back anywhere except
for the new areas
so wait there's something I want to get
from the blighted village while we're
here oh okay yeah you know how to get it
um I I think
so
people your footsteps are whoa okay
they were they were very very bloody oh
yeah I stepped in a puddle
come on a minute
the blind the village is so much more
than you think it is so good
um
oh Authority
um fisticuffs
thank you
I'm not seeing that what's going on
like something's happening
yeah I also don't see the role for
whatever reason
yeah
but mind your manners of course we will
worry about it no reason signs inspired
it was I don't it's in one of the houses
right yeah yeah I think I remembered the
Alchemist building yes
yes I think
you need it though if we need it you
want it I I want it so bad okay
shot do you remember what I found that I
wanted narissa to get with myself stream
do you like the universe no it was
something I told you that we need to get
this house it's the other house it's the
one it's this house sorry
ah yeah
the the it's it's in the the bottom the
bottom uh it's in the underdark yeah
sword I know yeah I know where it is
yeah yeah okay okay maybe we can get
that too why is there so many things for
you and nothing for me I found it I
found it yay alcohol
give me all the booze oh all right where
did they go down there oh okay okay I
don't know where it is down here I just
know it's here okay go explore
okay be careful no potion of sleep yum
yum
[Music]
I totally didn't know that there was a
lever there I didn't know that at all
did you guys go into a different room
oh yes I had
it's okay is that not where it is
it's fine did you see the patch now I
just I don't have it no
I mean it Blends in really nicely so
cute where's everybody
I I get you cool
suspicious poison that sounds fun
it does
Alchemy
is this past the perception check yeah
do you think it's in this room because
there's other rooms the one that I just
opened the the door to oh probably
the problem the more interesting stuff
is like probably never in yeah
yeah sounds accurate
feel free to open all the caskets good
there's nothing in there I need my book
oh wait are you looking for the
wow surprise indeed are you looking for
the next yeah oh okay all right I missed
it in my run so I need it please
and fully now you are surprised
character again
[Applause]
I just marked first
I think this is how I play it and then
what do I do
it's been so long it's just a
Refreshments
just a little refresher course
can we welcome to the battle oh I'm
ready to all right got it all taken care
of I guess
the book she should talk to them which
is a thing over there never so you
already know it right I don't I missed
this in my run through I didn't even
come here oh you didn't get the book
okay we need no the book and the book
key so the book key is also somewhere
yeah
right yeah I know where both are
[Music]
what are these answers
oh
good luck
what wow has Disney tried to sue
what oh my God this looks literally like
Snow White
yeah like one to one I don't think they
invented that
yeah I know but that won't stop them let
me in
about this
um
I wonder what that is oh my God what's
that looks like a trap do you need me to
disarm it did not get sued I think your
book's in there oh wow okay wait let me
see if I can uh I found a bunch of
Scrolls may I take them
yes yeah
take everything that looks interesting I
have no thieves tools so I can't lock
pick this
attack the door
oh I can lock quick this yay
oh we're in this room now
are we where are we I want to take us I
failed I'm here
[Music]
I have a weapon can I just
no thank you can you Cali
you knocked down
uh attacked Jesus you big daddy I've got
gloves for you oh really good gloves
thanks let's go in my inventory if you
find the blue gloves the bracers of the
fence those are for you oh thank you let
me equip them really quick yes
Mario
you girls are so weak
I'm ready
I gotta let Cali do this I can't uh I
can't take them from you actually here I
think you got to give them to me what
yeah okay stuff is blacked out for me is
stealing illegal now wait it also has
resistance now put it in your inventory
thank you
oh it's working oh never mind
it's the only thing I can do
it's an important thing we need that
skip a big tank big tanky Brute
that's your book
bro
oh
this is why I love playing with
controller I can just spin in circles
I love this book oh
oh you dropped your book
like you drop it no it I didn't have an
option
it's dusty
what oh did you do may have activated
he's got a little fire breath in my
inventory okay be careful let's just
walk out of there just walk just walk
out yeah
gargoyle dude
doesn't need to be in turn-based
oh yeah well good thing we got out of it
yeah
what the
okay
is the gem down here to unlock it too no
I will show you I know where it is oh
okay
okay it goes pretty deep we have to go
pretty deep for them yeah if you want to
like be fast and we could get out out of
here first and yeah then we have to jump
into the into the whole of the other
building I think oh we can go through
the well the well isn't that bad oh yeah
there's several places to get everything
down there it's all connected was that
the key to the
It's gotta be a like a stone round Stone
I picked up a key I think that was the
key to the cell that well it's okay we
have Molly we don't need it yeah yeah I
can break any okay
smash everything
oh yeah oh you're back still down there
oh
where's the egg oh there we go right
here and let's go through the well the
well is fun okay
yeah I will even break the the lock on
balder's gate
the Baldur's Gate Mori opens what does
the gate go into
what's a gate guarding yeah
who founded Baldur's Gate you know oh
yeah I guess that's true
really quick
Callie being a little bit aggressive
over there
Kelly followers you got it just just
definitely grabbing some things wait
I'll find them sorry
you're in the well gotcha Kelly
I have no eyeballs
[Music]
I trust you baby
oh there's a spider web that's not
creepy or anything
don't get caught ladies
oh that's the same fail can I rescue
oh me looks like yeah something didn't
like that
oh no
ah let's party let's rattle them wait oh
you guys already started oh
up there where is the battle going on
because oh behind us
okay
well now I know where we are okay oh
they're behind I see
are those little alligator dudes no
they're spiders
too far away
they they do you're so right oh they're
kind of
cute girls
hi
all right um I don't think I have any
ranged attacks
oh I'm just oh music's changed ah
I'm just gonna get this
this one
good luck
nice one
oh there's another one far away that's
coming up oh blue one oh they're coming
oh
my God yeah
no lupus not the Wolfie am I stuck I'm
stuck you are
in the web still
yeah can I hit him from over here too
far yum Chomp jump try jumping or
something no I'm stuck
after this one
oh well good luck
wait I'm still stuck in the web you guys
need to get me out
another one skill issue yeah sorry
nerissa that's pretty rough
is helping
okay well
I guess I'll just keep let's go play
music yeah
I'm sorry I killed your enemy no it's
cool I'll get the spider hold on yes
we'll chill yeah we'll just chill back
here two damage please jump down well
I'll try to I'll I'll come over here
I'll come to you but I have I don't have
no more action left I have to okay you
can wear them this way I have range if
you want I don't know do I not have I
bet I don't have any arrows oh it hurts
all right let me throw something
they'll teleport probably next turn
again
to the face there she is
okay can I have my friend here
oh I'm not lived anymore good yeah well
okay get out of here
go kill that spider biboo
Eric Gonzalez I like the idea steals
lunch money
yeah
let's go I want to fly out of the web
too
my voice is so husky because it's really
early in the morning drink some tea with
honey oh you got out of there yourself
what did I come here for
if it makes you feel any better I just
woke up too
where's the other spot where's the other
yeah oh it's up there I mean I guess
guess we can just range attack it I
suppose
or he could just come down here I mean
that's what I was not being a baby
little baby yeah
oh I'm an idiot
that's our Ranger I guess okay
something's possible we're not supposed
to cross that bee boo is that correct
yeah that is correct that is not the
correct way you told me I knew that the
poison tunnel was the way it's good to
explore you know yes yes you're right
you're right oh you're going that way
I
think you're naturally progressing
correctly oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
don't do anything
like this
nice
it's prone baby that's kind of awesome
this is good it did Big damage
of course the babies
oh
she coming
I want she coming
it's kind of awesome that was one third
of the health let's get it yeah we could
continue that whenever she's on the web
if anybody has something with fire just
shoot the web with the fire
[Music]
okay
she's currently is she considered I
don't think she's on the web right now
huh no she's on the she's on it's
offline yeah
oh okay
okay I killed most of the babies nice
nice you feel very strong
30 that's nothing
I gotta rely on the
wow
wow what's what's going on today we're
on easy mode
yeah
okay our real opponent
hey come back you okay as we should be
honestly
oh
come here
go up to this little spider
um
[Music]
kill the spider okay I'll try if it lets
me not enough movement all right I guess
oh you guys are blocked oh that's why
incredible
are we blocking your paths
yeah I can't see past nourishes She's
Too Tall I'm too short
yeah Point Blank all right never said
duck
fan yeah
whoa
gotta get rid of the smaller ones too
that is true
yeah
yeah I'll throw something you know what
to do
I threw it wrong Maybe
should have gone on the web more than on
the spider Maybe
okay
it's okay
we got it
I hope this one attacks me oh you
inspired did you inspire me there I saw
I got some bartic roll here
because you inspire me every day so
I ah
does it go away
and use it or am I using it
oh now I'm using it
it hit
Mutual inspiration not the discharge oh
it's running and it flew away
baby
dude
what a freak it's okay I can take a
little bit of pain a little bit
very much
oh it's so big
so Bieber can we still multi-class Yes
you well you have to turn it back to
normal I think
but if we turn it to easy does that undo
the multi-class thing
no because I still have my cleric stuff
double Miss okay maybe next time we're
at Camp it doesn't have to be right away
it doesn't matter but um I might want to
stop now I can move away
I want to be strong nice cloud of
daggers
just making making me excited to play on
my own at some point I just got it on
PS5 baby
um
could somebody
I agree there's robe
it's a different game is this rope that
the spider dropped good oh you are we
not done yet no no no yeah
that might be good for people oh
maybe maybe
okay
Kelly is stronger without armor no
hmm
oh wait oh it just doesn't like wear
clothes just like me for real for real
oh hello
it never ends
kill one spider find five more
World business armor okay okay
this is some alone in the time with the
Vampire oh shut up
Cali looks so much better without
clothes though
um sorry I mean like well your character
because I gave that same rope to Carla
and she just doesn't look good in it
I get it yeah
oh I killed that one
yeah
I believe in you guys
time to throw
yeah eat yeah yeah I'm not interrupted
what are you talking about
um it's not that bad
can you jump sometimes it gets a little
frustrating
here we go
yeah
all right rope for somebody in the big
spider
are you okay oh
oh
you fell quite far okay okay I've only
got eight health left dude that's a far
fall oh at least you got the thing right
I'm about to I'm trying to pick it up
but it's it's tiny there we go dark
amethyst acquired
for now okay how do I get back to you
guys
over here where I am there's a little
climbing thing
yeah we should probably short rest
okay
better than nothing
oh no I'm not basking in in the the
weird God's love anymore oh wow what a
shame I know I mean I still have it I
thought so whenever I'm blessing no it
is but uh it's you you have to meet
certain standards to reach it you know
what I mean I see so it's a it's La Via
Tara's love pain is the path to Clarity
when you have 30 hit points or less you
gain a two percent bonus two attack
rolls and wisdom saving throws for three
turns it's pretty cool that's a buff
that's pretty cool have you not been
engaging in the sadism enough these days
it seems not
so do we wanna like explore this place
even more or do we want to move on to
the Tea House
okay
all right yeah yeah okay we're gonna
just teleport to blighted
um
uh yeah I know how to teleport I got it
waypoints
hello
[Applause]
I'm ready let's go yes yes
we gotta meet the hot lady a hot lady
literally and figuratively yeah
she sets my soul on fire
mine too man
he's great
well I have a story in this round so you
can have it you have a Syrian though
I will steal him again
all right good luck I mean you can have
him but
I just don't think he's feeling it
I think someone else
I think that's right over here if we
jump
yeah this was a bit of a hard one I
remember a bridge
that you had to jump
I walked over a piece of a tree a long
tree log yeah
I think we can just oh we can go on the
other side there's there's a side over
here down here what's the Ping again
Google
it's up by the Risen Road
um oh yeah it's up over here
yeah and then we go up I believe
we'll find it eventually
you okay we gotta get our car
loading off my weights to you girls
because I'm my inventory was excuse me I
found people it doesn't feel happy
because he Boo has a conversation to do
I have a conversation all right I'm on
the way
get into
oh this one oh I guess we go down here
and then I don't know how you guys
climbed all the way over there but we'll
find it find the way jump
maybe I can jump we could find a vendor
at some point that would be cool
big jumpies look at this guy balding oh
my gosh
I'm watching you she looks a little bit
like Nami from live action yeah a little
bit oh my god
oh yeah is it good I've heard you guys
it's so good it's good okay
it even made me like one piece who had
nothing to do with one piece until now
why can't I jump please just let me jump
game
I'm begging you
I don't know how you guys got over there
dang it went down over by the the cave
for the owl Bear yeah so I'm in front of
the cave down down by the river and then
we just walked over we didn't have to
jump
you can walk over the water oh I guess
you can just walk through the freaking
Ninja
just not the brightest
that's all right okay let's go
it might be useful
Psy
yeah
I'm a true soul
you are oh my God oh my gosh I'm special
well
um
the last one I think I consumed so
and Theresa got one so Kelly and Bieber
should get one I want to eat a worm yeah
she's going to rip down the old world
order they don't know we killed all the
Goblins oh yeah oops uh
wow so I can make them do whatever I
want
um
You Will Rule it flashes back to bibos
like half this person's side
that's comedic
a crude summer you have more to learn
about faith novice I'm sorry true soul I
only repeat it learn more than you it
seems the absolute still has a great
deal to teach me
um good job guys lighting her yeah just
just time to leave just tell him to
leave
oh yeah I did
guide your hand madam as for us we won't
take any more of your time May the
absolute guide us okay bye
the body
you can have it
oh
where'd you put that robe I wanted to
see it oh the Rope it's uh it's in my
first row oh
I think I swear by weight transport it
to me I will take the weight off your
shoulders I have work if you want it
sure okay I gave it to you thank you
oh
very cute little robe
talking to you
can I wear this
yes it reminds me of your RPG outfit
yeah
what which one are the one I'm wearing
now true yeah oh it's me it's you oh
yeah
wow nice
okay oh okay go next
oh okay let's go this way
the way
wait
I need to go this whole one let me think
um I don't think we've been to the Risen
road yet
but the reason I remember being able to
get to Carlock from here
um
but I think it's up I'm pretty sure it's
up yeah it's up more we need to go north
we're going south
I don't remember anymore this place is
too large
oh it was I think it was the other way
from Playa Villa to the other side oh
yeah I remember jumping over this uh
wait not this bridge there was jumping
over a bridge
okay I guess I'm doing this
I didn't really care but apparently I'm
talking to dead board but not really I'm
just examining it I'm back at the
blighted Village I've walked back over
in a few hours I presume we go north
from there yeah we go out the other side
and then go north next
a vampire
has been eating it
has been completely yes
it's over this side I think okay
is that you it not anymore oh is it that
way
I follow I follow Marissa
it could be wrong
saving
oh oh quick save oh no oh no that's
probably what happened
where am I that it's quick saving
in trouble
I come help to smell please
[Music]
smash yeah
big fist
and Meaty thigh
fish I like that fist meet the eye
oh yeah you don't I can barely jump over
this actually eat me eat me I would like
to be eating I got you hold on a sec
I'll see where is my I need to watch
this improvised melee you know I might
not make the jump you know so just in
case okay let me use my mouse
let me just use my mouse bagel
no do not pickpocket baby
bro
here go on
yeah oh wow that was pretty good
come back got that really okay
not bagel
thank you
jump
getting thrown by Kelly's son
your back is broken down hello
oh what happened to the doggle
oh what happened we're fighting we
smashed them
it's not my turn
hyena
how do you say it in English
definitely kill them very quickly I got
a lot of strawberry jam
at the hunter I am
nice
some very fruity Jam
s yeah that's a lot it's a lot of fruit
chunks in there yeah I guess they like
it chunky yeah and there we go
oh Lord
I'm sorry I have to make you wet hyena
I thought Inna was in the chat
because hyena
you made me scroll up in the chat guys
where is she
inaudible
Cali punch him smash him kick him he did
again I can't yeah
damn it oh okay oh boy
you see the glitch yeah he was going a
little mix
really all right here we go
nice
I'm just gonna electrocute us like that
I killed them
this will not be the first time I
electrocute you don't worry I'm sure
I'll look forward to the next time
oh
that Caravan agent okay
oh wait come on kids wait let's take
this food because
um we need camp supplies oh okay yes we
do desperately we need to loot Goblin
all this stuff okay I'm trying to loot
some food too here and there oh yeah
nice idea grab all that all those
goodies
more you'll be fun red apple
oh milk
I like I like your um
well I like you
got food
did you find her yeah she's down here I
haven't interacted I'm waiting for you
guys oh down down
by the weather is she down by the river
I'm gonna talk to carlak okay see the
one who who wrote the lyrics to that
song no that's easy
I love her
too she's on fire just like me yeah
Sparks like the flame
yay she's starting a fire every day
oh the leg oh yeah oh her Flames
always make my OBS lag so much is yours
lagging two girls yeah mine is a little
bit yeah
she's so yummy
met some of the alturians who got
trapped in the Hills though
she's so cool so weird
I love when she lights up yeah I love
her too it's you from the nautiloid
please tell me I found you before those
so-called paladins of tear did does she
not remember me only the restaurant
good
great
glad I don't have to kill you don't hurt
me carlak oh please hurt me Carla great
fiery as the hells then your last
envisions of demonic armies she's so
beautiful
Jesus
this woman
line
ready
I relate to her on another level
um
my my Burning Angel
s
all right I love her I love her swearing
more please all three of us wear quite a
big except for beers
it's okay I like her swearing though
and you are I'm your girlfriend now hey
you already have vegetarian don't you
yeah no I'm joking I'm not gonna take it
she's all yours Kiana I know you love
Carla background okay all right I see
how it is everybody's turned their back
on me just because the Starion decided
that he wanted a little poke even though
it's not like it's not my fault no no no
no
everybody deserves some love made me her
personal assistant
but now I'm free
but believe me when I tell you I'm not
going the latest yappy little dog she
sicked on me you're nearby
posing as paladins of tear yes
we're gonna kill him for you carlak
um
[Music]
yes beef yes
he's great
um
we're cutting this parasite and take
faerun by the short
sound good
um my favorite companion I think oh oh I
would like you if it wouldn't Scorch
your skin off
we already have a Berserker Barbarian
yeah don't rule for the party for you oh
no sorry when it's time to count sorry
this one at the camp Queen fun stuff
without me got it
wait never mind I can't do it why can't
I use myself
yeah let's go beat up the dudes yeah
those guys suck Marissa needs healing at
some point yeah
no I've got potions um I I was trying to
use my spell but I found one of the
things I had applied wouldn't let me do
my healing word so
I have okay can I do one more short rest
before this fight mm-hmm
okay
thank you
hi tires that's a dude's head cool
look it up can't wait to throw it at
someone you
I'll let you mojimoshi
I want to go up here before we start the
fight oh sure okay I'm gonna loot it oh
I just want to kill him yeah yeah we're
going to Hannibal for sure I mean wait
wait yeah Kiara you want you want to
talk to someone who will sell you things
yeah yeah pass this door there's a
person you can buy and sell things from
we'll have to kill them in the fight to
come but if you want to quick sell off
some stuff you could before the fight
starts okay for you that's that's
awesome wait we're selling
eh
there oh maybe out out here out here
well good maybe I thought I thought they
were inside but maybe not Cyro Amy
try try talking outside
oh yeah she sells stuff here you can go
first here okay here
oh
she's going
to her sales table or what
you could say oh well you guys are doing
that I need to how do I turn off nudity
again I turned it back on for myself
well as you turn it on there is
something
[Music]
for my private personal run I think I
turned it all off because private
moments has nothing to do with I am yeah
private moments is like blocking the
scene for so no one else cool how do I
uh
quick way of doing this again
is there a quick way to sell stuff I'll
just double click okay
double check and make sure nudity off
[Music]
yeah I don't want I don't want little
leaf covering my my nip nops I know what
they look like already you know
I get you no yeah yeah you understand
yeah all right whatever you say
need any supplies almost done be cool
take your time
yeah
next one okay okay
wait two seconds
okay
we just wait for Cali I'm I'm ready I'm
just getting ready so can you will get
away from him so I don't make you wet
sure I'm gonna go on this side oh yeah
you gotta plan don't you yeah I do have
a plan freaking go I can throw the
goblin Scimitar or something okay Nick
thanks let's do this poison resistant I
could use that all right um you know I
guess that's probably probably about it
I don't remember I thought I remember
her talking about them and I was like oh
I've never used this once no yes you
need them for her I think you can you
can slot it in her body and it makes her
stronger like a slime machine yeah we
also need to save the infernal irons so
if you see that don't sell it okay okay
let me see let me just grab a dagger
really quick
so I can throw it and then yeah oh yeah
good idea
I hate having to do math
um right hold on
they should they should really make this
a little easier to figure out but that's
okay
I'm almost done guys sorry my eight plus
two is eight eight plus six is 14.
all right I got it let's do it all right
kill him okay hold on I'm gonna enter
turn base
and then I'll kill her
yeah
okay
don't make noise so wet
oh I didn't make him wet oh yeah he's
white noise okay
now go ahead everyone end their turn
please yeah oh
turn ended
rattle them
environmental turn
environment okay oh okay there we go
die
oh I missed it's
just kill him
there we go all right now we now we go
we ball oh what the
Ellie
owie party time just murder exactly as
planned
I can't see
okay
I don't want to go down
I'm blocking it you can't oh wait no oh
yeah he can't climb up the stairs
then take these
guys
crazy we still have some more right yeah
they wanted to fight Mario game
I can't blame them really yeah who
wouldn't want to fight Mario fish a
pleasure
I need this book for my collection yeah
it's interesting I guess I should go
down though because they're all like
yeah out of my view
theme
okay let you down
[Music]
oh we're gonna kill the poor oh she's
invisible
poor lady
oh did she turn invisible yeah
but she's still there you could like if
you have some AOE or something like
something like cloud of daggers you
could place it there and hope that it
hits her let's try it I'll randomly
shoot
no
foreign
[Music]
that sounds kind of neat would that be
good for me
that might be I gave it to you thank you
loot load of content I found a fan
fiction a fan fiction
a pleasurable deal this is an excerpt
from the play a pleasurable deal of band
in no fewer than four cities for its
lewd
contentless nature led to a number of
widely distributed and illicit printings
should I read it to you yeah give us a
dramatic yeah I'll read it okay
narrator come here fearful good tail now
lost to time in grief this man will sunk
to death's Sublime a gift he saw to win
his lady's heart our Campion smiled for
now the game did start enter Robert male
thiefly crying Carlisle stage right
flash of smoke
weep not young man dough free your wife
has fled and comfort found in comrades
arms and bed she licks her lips and
cries his name oh my and now seek you to
be the apple of her eye quite yes Robert
how does a stranger no such things I ask
I watch you from the shadows and I see
your shame and grief for Nature's Melody
you seek to win your lady and her bed to
have your name upon her lips instead
Robert you know my curse my pain my
grief my woe Carlisle of you I know you
seek a larger hoe to plow a Fair Maid
and sell sower seed to grow but lag do
ya Mighty Hornet mask with which to
guide a maids to be bad and fast
that's the only spicy book I found in
this game
no I respect it
um I'm downstairs
cool I love it
what
I got a severified I was thinking of
putting it in someone's inventory as a
surprise
now what did you do cucumber
cucumber
I can't wait
I put an armor on you
more you'll pay I need you downstairs
yeah sure what's up
please come downstairs and help me knock
down a door well with your power if you
tell me where downstairs is I'll
definitely go there
in the house a hatch
um
yeah I can't I can't yell I can't yell
things at the door to make it break um
I can't burn a wooden door okay we've
got Goliath moriope
show it to the door oh yeah there's a
trap there's a trap there's a trap
okay
okay someone come sit on the other chair
on the other side disarmed
okay yeah you're gonna go loot in that
room all right I'll tell you what I find
I guess but
you're really going there be careful
it's dark
oh there's a marble plate maybe I can
get around it
jump jump all right
just a moment oh yeah
um
let's go let's try and be wary
there's 203 gold which I'll take and
there's a split and then loot everything
all right hold on there's a great act
and if I do great sword Give Me
Everything
and sell all these
no
I failed
one this arm pleasurable deal hey they
really like this book here and I got
another one another copy that is what it
is
another one
okay the other pleasurable deal is there
supposed is there a voice is there a
part two
which one was it Cali let's see this
one's just hold on oh oh this is kind of
good stuff yeah no there's really good
stuff in this room make sure you take
all of it don't miss anything okay is
that is that the same a pleasurable deal
it's that book right there
it's just a regular puzzle
the book it seems just wanted the sequel
really
cold
did it say it was illegal because it's
too lewd
yeah it's been enforces
behind where you just came from
on the weapons in the middle the Quarter
Staff looking great
okay get out of there before I lock you
in run
this great ax is so nice what did you
just say Cali great ax
no no before that
you say Cut and Run Cut and Run
what does that mean it means get the it
means get the out of there
retrieve thank you
I wonder Sword of Justice or great acts
that's really nice but I think I'll go
Sword of Justice
book
um
I have to give it to a Syrian
I'm way too to do it
the book oh
you say anything about it can you summon
any small animal
oh maybe
I can summon the perfect thing a rat
[Music]
okay
and then and then interact with this
whole
uh oh I don't see the whole uh
[Music]
oh I haven't perceived it I think
do I need to perceive it I think so
I'm way too big
also I can't walk around there oh here
let me get out of your way
it says can't get there no I'm not
perceiving it ah wait the borough hole
yeah turn it okay okay
I could fit
[Music]
I'm not sure if the rat can go there
I can't I can't fit no one can
I can click on it with the mouse with
the rat
you would need you might need to Wild
shape or Mist form
yeah
or can you like enjoy your familiar
but uh
um is there something we can can we
remove something
no it doesn't it doesn't
I don't think it wants to go there
that's weird it just says can't get here
oh you need to be a druid oh
nice rat
you can shape-shift into like a tinier
Mouse
oh it's just another entrance to the
locker room oh Okay click and dragged oh
what
what what
did you figure you can click and drag to
move boxes look yeah yeah
oh my God
I got it I just keep rolling above 20s
because I have some things I'm just
reading the book
which book add a Necronomicon
oh I need to put the stone in yeah
you look very concerned
see it
he won't let me in it's closed are you
guys seeing it seen too much you've seen
too much I I'm seeing noises cutscene
yeah
I've seen it before knowledge I've got
to the port a bit in knowledge now
I don't know what that does to me but I
have to know right now yeah
yes
yeah cool
well I don't know it's just as long as
you're smart it's good oh I'm not smart
yum
I only have Charisma you're smart just
uh I am I'm really smart yeah
without you
I was waiting for you
hi hi hello and a cute new little rat
friend
with two HP had a dead sitting
around
oh have uh any of you gone to the gith
Yankee uh crash no
crash did they crash what correct
it's holy quresh in case you didn't know
[Music]
what is going on
I don't know
I don't want a hyena here
yeah I don't want those either
just leave it stinky I wonder if we keep
walking down the Risen Road what we'll
find
oh wait there's a there's a teleporter
here
nice Discovery Bijou welcome to the
Discovery Channel the accident
what the hell is this yeah I've never
been up here before so I don't know what
this is
spooky
well there's some pretty good stuff we
can get if we
move on a bit from
here okay
I don't know where it is though
just exploring exploring this whole area
there's so much fun stuff you know
something is over there
you and me
sorry people you leave oh I'm being a
little nasty yeah be bullied everybody
okay calm your calm your feetsies
we follow people more European like
simple commands
what's up here
don't worry I'll be understand
I understand follow
there's more death thing yeah there's
lots of dead things everywhere I don't
like that ew they're facing
can we kill them oh wait wait I don't
have spells by the way for this that's
all right
um okay how hard could they be yeah it's
fine
easy let's go
yeah the feast is over the feast is over
come inside us you fools
oh bad could it be
[Music]
yeah
what are these things anyway
so numbed what's that mean
couldn't tell you
[Music]
how scary
do you think these guys can speak
English no like understand
oh yeah you're gonna insult them
yeah I'm a boss never loved them
wow okay my first Miss of the day
they're like hyena people oh yeah
Arenas who learned to walk on two feet
okay and they look like hyenas it's
pretty cool please Mario face smashed oh
my God
is here to do
bonus action
this
off strike
yeah how do you like that nice
no
goodbye to the rad I was sure he's gonna
last longer than all of us
mm-hmm
rat gone
yeah oh yeah
rip Bales
wow got him nice one
getting out of here
good luck okay I can tank it stay
okay
come on
nice shot
nice shooting ticks
what
oh thank you you're welcome I had a
bonus action
I probably should have given it to
narissa because
it's okay because they went for me
okay I've gotta I've got a thing so
yeah rattle them
nice yeah
what's going on
I don't know what's happening actually a
murder is what's happening I'm getting
clawed
die
why
let's go
chance
oh that's rough
70 minutes zero oh boy
I don't know what three Frank does yeah
should we do a long rest or uh yeah yeah
long rest
yeah
an open letter a letter to peacocks on a
press cleaner is Elena being oppressed
we gotta go Savor any kind
oh there is a thing shall we rest before
we go in there though oh absolutely
okay absolutely going to camp
okay okay
who's Giselle
relax here yeah Kyla
oh Carla I took care of those paladins
for you
but a fugitive okay girls we want to
have uh conversations together right not
two separate ones yeah let's talk to
Carla everybody together
I always take care of my people Carlock
oh she likes me I love car lots
but I'm just happy they're off my tail
can
boys
Inferno
you want my coins
maybe girls
anytime soon so I'll just make the most
of the extra heat
just don't get too close until I found a
way to calm it down
we can't give her a hug yet
certainly can't do other things too
that's a dynamic tune back off shitty
what other things it's a bit early in
the game to begin don't worry about it
[Laughter]
for tragedy meanwhile I'll need to find
someone who can tune up my engine sooner
rather than later oh you mean
hand-holding yeah
I'm so vulgaria
he might be able to stabilize things if
I can find him
um
there's some tea things in our okay we
will look there sounds like they're not
there anymore
we saved them and they left a Boulders
game remember it's good oh but yeah they
did leave but she needs a tiefling help
uh yeah but he's on the way to Baldur's
Gate oh oh sorry Carlock I guess oops
oops
man
well Yum Yum Yum you want to sleep oh
she's trying she's trying to raise up a
Syrian again oh she's trying
I'm trying so hard assuming we don't
turn into mind players of course
on things
even though he loves Mario Fame he does
spikes made me who I am
edgy oh wow
you think that's a threat
let me give you the book why I can't I I
can't how do I give him the does he have
to he I bet I can't I bet he has to
really party no it's too late you
already read the book uh what wait if I
read the book it can't be used again so
you can't read the book no I can't read
the book I don't think anymore it's like
a one time take it from my inventory
okay oh my God
oh my god did you learn a spell from the
book no I didn't get anything I don't
know what it was supposed to do oh I
passed all the checks so apparently I
got the knowledge
you keep the book until later
I don't need it on me wait I'm gonna
read the book
see it doesn't open for anyone except
for the person who read it oh so it's
stuck to you now well
my book
look at carlak dancing I love when she
drops
she drops it
oh cool yeah yeah hold on Bust A Move do
some head spins yeah some head spinnies
oh
that's right I remember if you okay
can you for good after the Mind flare
ship we just can't get it crazy can you
Carlock
Advocates diaboli just think of averness
chill
why am I making the choices
I am oh I mean I know okay it's a
suggestion sorry just a suggestions
oh it's me okay good and you've got
hello
is he is he back here to kill me yeah
will he join us
isn't he still mad at me no he's
probably forgiving the waste of a
furnace
just ahead a diabolical figure red skin
single curled horn blazes with flame
bloodied great ax held high he chases
the fiend ignite you know Will's pretty
good she is an infernal yeah I really
like will he died
I don't really have him in my party a
soldier in the arch devil zombies
and I didn't even have him on my team
barely and I was like what do you think
I am how can you struggle with making
these NPCs like you like I feel like
everybody's lusting
yeah
eyes Dart around
relax desperation
yes he's a victim
's helmet
no he gets it now you're not being
tricked
I may be an effective Soldier but I
never wanted to serve zariel legged it
away from her the first chance I got and
yet you served
ah
Stand Down
you're sorry stop it Devils cannot be
trusted oh come on will
um
stop being so stubborn will would you
listen to sense
this doesn't have to end badly
for either of us we could be friends no
monsters right yes
you're not what you think
my mans were you not paying attention
he just doesn't want to believe it come
on man
that's okay well
we forgive you even though you didn't
forgive Bijou for looting your dead
friends but okay we forgive you the
difference maybe he'll join us after
this thankfully maybe off threats today
truce
I'll do you one better he missed a
little baby begging face
parasites for good stab him right
through the chest stays more JK
you're proud Adventure I've not grown
any tentacles yet thankfuldrin but luck
won't be on our side forever
yes you have my blade Your Leader
willing of course
okay
um the more of the merrier as they say
no dies kidding
he killed me before and my ass my life
to protecting
and my bow tonight
I was the rampaging
paging I see the good in you Carla I
promise not to lose sight of it even
when the hell is burn hottest
wow
friendship where you come from
are you seeing Shadow heart because I'm
seeing nothing I'm saying nothing
well
oh
he has a little I want to talk about her
head
listen blood will Source sense even more
glad he decided to stick around it takes
a pretty slicky movement to track down
yeah he came out of nowhere yeah I'm
just glad he's not mad at me anymore
right now if he turns on you again he's
dead yeah you've got a little butt chin
Kiara someone wrong but do I look at
your character your character has a
button
I respect someone who can admit when
they're wrong
bet there's a good story there
you'll see next time oh that didn't see
next time maybe yeah you'll see though
you have a butt chin oh I think will
wants to talk yeah Will wants to talk to
his conversation
been witness to a pantomime I'm sorry to
say
and I've played my part all too poorly
poor guy
sheesh I can say I believe this
will be lifted everybody looks real good
thanks I know maybe the most good
looking is me yeah and you'll have them
possibly I can't promise you'll like
them
well tell us about yourself
you want to talk more of him or sleep or
house and what's going on Allison you
haven't really been oh how else
interacted with it
have a little conversation with him oh
father's blessings to you yes you have
anything he wants to say oh God there's
literally so much well that's a lot of
things
what is this
Shadow curse foreign
those who remain
ing beautiful Memorial your face is so
beautiful it's hard for me to look at it
for anyone to resist
ant
hideous but fascinating like nothing
else in nature I'm glad to say yes
hideous but fascinating like me like
I've chosen a successor
I'll take it the highest complimentation
we talked about
Africa though and neither do any of the
others The Grove needs to move
quantity an outsider who can enforce the
Oak Farms in ladies this is why you
choose Francesca do you guys want to
know a fun fact I learned about houses
he's one of the only companions that you
can date one person also date house and
at the same time and he likes it yeah
yeah
I believe it
what about the secret passage in the
underdark tell us how to go there
because we definitely need to go there
there's stuff he went there one of his
cohorts where did I go there I think I
went there
like it's not for the content
that's what it's for guys right it's the
content
obviously those illicit creatures
threaten the natural order it's my duty
to do what I can do we've got to
entertain the shadow curse it's an
affront and must be cleansed under
Darkness I feel like that's just the
better way to go years ago but I failed
to prevent him from unleashing Darkness
across the region
if I can join you and get close to
moonrise perhaps I can lift this curse
just as you find a cure for your
infection okay house and I'm kind of
done talking to you because you just
really talk a lot more
Molly smash Molly no talk
another player is choosing camp supplies
leave it to you
I made dinner
hope it tastes good I made tonkatsu last
night
yeah by myself wow was it good it was
supposed to be a Austrian schnitzel but
I realized I can just make it into
tonkatsu because it's like pretty
similar nice I love making tonkatsu with
curry too oh yeah yeah
our bodies
before we go we have to open the door
oh and the game was dying I guess I'll
check on him crazy guy
I'll do it
it's like okay steal the poor dog's
balls
[Music]
good about himself maybe yeah
or he'll bite your hand off we should be
sick where's the ball he's like oh
that's not something you see every day
oh that doesn't seem right
I'll try again really quick come on this
time it works there we go nice
the ball from his chin
and it must hurt
why are you stealing the ball from him
he's just a little guy you okay there
boy he needs attention
and then we can leave oh will and the
car like a proof
[Music]
yeah you'll have the ball in your
inventory if you show it somewhere he'll
bring it back try it
let's see you can pet the dog why are
there two Gales I don't know I think
he's glitched so the way closer to him
oh no he goes crazy look
look at it he's coming friend
dancing
okay Gail Gail needs a probably a magic
item oh somebody talked to him already
yeah I gave him a magic item oh that's
so cute
I know I gave him what I was wearing so
now I need to find a different one but I
you know in this camp for whatever
reason I can never find the Traveler's
chest
I feel crazy oh it's over here oh yeah
okay it's just my shadow heart he's not
glitch to talk to him oh so he just has
another dude version of him yeah don't
question it it's normal
no it belongs to only one of them
belongs to you there's four there's more
there's four yeah there's four there's
one for each yeah we don't share no we
don't share they're pretty
how do I know which one's mine
what everyone lets you open it I guess
driveway's chest traveler's chest I mean
I think you can open it in the blue
see like there's a bunch I'm blue oh
this is mine it must be mine because
it's got a separate head
nice someone else's chest now
good luck
I don't think you can yeah why is not
the orange one so I'll put it in your
inventory then
or I'll just sell that
supposed to store my gold
[Music]
what's next
or let's just keep it wearing up north
because there's stuff happening up North
and then the tea house is down way way
yeah I'm interested up north because I
haven't been there before okay yeah okay
have I been there
I'm just dumping have you been to the
crash the crush I don't think so
then you haven't been up north
okay are you still in the camp
I am I'm coming out right now though
pink chest
did everyone leave hello
yeah I just love I mean yes should we
just stop stop running
feed you wait it just happened to me for
some reason really far away from
everyone
oh yeah I'm just waiting by narissa all
right thank you please hold my hand I
was alone I was so scared what was that
why that's right
lead the way
this is a burning Village
oh why is everything on fire yes I don't
know I wonder what could be up here to
cause everything to be on fire like hey
what's happening is it like a raid maybe
the village is being raided maybe Oh by
Goblin oh wow I did not see this yet
okay I'm in a conversation okay oh oh
grant me the mic to carry this burden
grant me the faith to Facebook what
is this
that's no good
oh all right oh okay all right I guess
we just guess what once we're doing what
they want us to do
okay might as well loot
time to lose don't get mad I think if
it's wouldn't it be red then
it's fine somebody's house to find it
for goblins it's probably fine but what
are they doing you guys need to open
them what I'm sorry I'm in a
conversation
uh strength push I don't ask questions I
push
a little bonus yeah
okay
good enough big muscle
um
[Music]
well that one my work year is done
oh everything is
everything that's pretty wild
nice bathtub
this place it feels wrong what can we do
I mean they're not using it anymore it's
on fire might as well get it before
the potato porridge
to find
well we could also go in where I opened
up the door if you guys want yeah I
think yeah up here is a dead end it must
be a reason why you opened the door yeah
we gotta go in
wow
um oh I'm burning
comfortable
yeah I mean it is a burning building
I must save the ham I'm Gonna Save the
food let's do it get the food
oh yeah save the kitchen stuff
I saved the sausage one thing that I
wish you could do in this game is Cook
Ed yeah like I know you technically are
when you're camping but like it's not
the same it's not the same this is a
recipe you know
mm-hmm
Apple
I
have a pineapple we need to cook
did you girls go to second floor
I'm loading all this food so that way we
have food for our camp it seems like
there might be somebody behind the store
oh boy
oh
yeah I'm gonna I'm in the scene
yeah I mean I just opened a door and it
exploded so oh
right
I don't think so
I can exit that yeah okay okay who are
you talking to the reason oh it is
no
but I'm saving a guy
oh
I'm trapped
I've just run out of the building
um there's like a person underneath
I'm gonna oh she just kind of wrote oh
right oh I'll try to keep up hug
does he follow you now oh he has one HP
uh oh
I'm like not in the same area as this
guy well yeah why did he die
um loot him and get out of there I mean
completed the quest in a different kind
of way uh okay we completed the password
it was there a quest that we could have
gotten with that guy yeah well
wait wait for me I'm getting I'm loading
all the food in here
sounds good that's pretty rough buddy I
gotta save the food yeah that is super
rough actually
that didn't go once blend
maybe not that's okay a lot of burning
things in here
yeah
okay I saved the food I'm coming okay
so is he dead
yo what the are you doing out there
eh is that will who's that guy yeah he
looks like will right yeah what's he
doing office recruit Pavel
table
no that's not will just look like
the council Floric needs help too how do
I get there
oh there's like so many people up there
well go help you know what I realized is
that I bet I could have saved that dude
if we had did you use the waters
[Applause]
yeah that's all right you got your
priorities yeah sorry I didn't I didn't
even mean to talk to that guy
okay
I see a bunch of people here
they need help do you need help stop
wasting oh people hi hi maybe spread
some water wherever necessary I gotta
open the door maybe there are still
people to help
oh wait hold on maybe I can
yeah
oh what is going on
okay proper thanks must wait she says oh
let's go let's go run
run
is that water okay oh there's water
barrels all over the place yeah notice
yeah maybe
oh Callie what's damn hit you hard huh
counselor yeah a little bit are you all
right
it takes more than that fire to break me
Eva
Beauty calls drow have taken Grand Duke
older Raven guard Western man with
my eyes and ears can be believed
we weren't
and you I must ask again for your Aid
please rescue ravengard from his drow
captors
Council will reward you for your effort
more your opinion
uh why and trust this to me who is the
Duke Raven guard
um
I'll I'll travel West and rescue Duke
ravengard thank you easy
yeah the land itself has been swallowed
in Shadow
reinforcements and join you when I can
who are you left
all right yeah
rewind
reward rescue the Duke we learned that
the Grand Duke was captured by drone
taken Westward
can only choose one bro
whatever it's the same thing
um let me see
there's like a tried I don't really know
what would be good is there is there a
bow there's a bow
I heard there's a bow yes yeah well I
guess we can do that
I accepted it
can I have both I don't know do we need
I see it the Joel shooter
did they just give that to us already
even though we haven't completed the
quest
it should be an inventory yes it is not
I took it already Okay I think I think
this is the one yeah the jolt shooter
what does it do electric blood when the
wielder deals damage using this weapon
they gain two lightning charges
oil
thank you
no more Goblin bones yeah
yeah short rest now now shall we
immediately uh look West
I guess so we can say that yeah keep
going west for now I'm already members
in a conversation no they are not
short dress guys I'm trying to share it
says a party member is in a conversation
and cannot rest right now oh weird
so odd
please let us rest
oh yeah it says it for me too wait can
everyone try the short rest oh oh
maybe now
um well
there's a person over here so maybe if
we talk to them it'll get us out of our
predicament oh yeah
you see that shadow in the background
yeah Shadow yeah it's a looks like a
dragon
above apart from the trunk her hair is
popping off
killed her yes swarming all over the
bridge
I don't know what they want but it can't
be good oh wow
another way around you ought to do the
same
would go your way we could just fight
them why because this is a different
group just another harassing fool trying
to stay alive
there's plenty of us around
she's cute
you want to join me instead
just follow you around yeah yeah Go My
Own Way
have a nice day that's it did it reset
where should we go try to get down there
and yeah see what those guys want oh
there we go ah hey
error of Darkness it looks like there's
a path down here yeah
minutes to the ants before I do that
well they all kind of look similar
no look up that was your last chance is
stick now burn uh oh oh
it's dark in time
I think you should run okay never mind
um wow
what the hell is going on
there's a dragon Daenerys Targaryen
please calm down
Yankee
of course we merely sought to no excuses
question kill then move on find the
weapon the weapons
suicide
oh my God
uh we should save before we talk to them
by the way I say whenever we see them
again
they're around here somewhere if we keep
moving
just don't remember don't worry I have
rizz
yes
I think I'm experiencing a problem oh oh
wait
okay
do your besties
these creatures are so simple
you knew too much about your task
forgiveness Kid Rock
and as for you
tell me the dragon's kind of big I run
you
yeah a little
tell them people I should
really I apologize at all no
I'm gonna add science
I add friends oh wait so I add guidance
to friends it's two dice better
I don't know
oh two dice is nice
I love just looking at Mario pay's ABS
right it's okay I get it I get it
thank God
because I want to see the see the dice
roll of course you are not a threat you
are nothing until I wow really all right
can we kill them to keep sucking air it
is necessary for you to tell me
something of worth a vessel fell from
the sky we seek a precious weapon that
was taken from it a precious weapon only
feel a strange anxiety take hold not
your own but that of the artifacts
Shadow heart space possibly
the artifact does not want depart from
you it does not want to fall into the
Geth Raiders hands help us find it
tomorrow leave your blood beneath your
skin unspilled don't let him know we
have a biboo
um
hmm
it'll cost sure I'll help if I can't
should I say that yeah like I'll help if
I can obedience is your only hope now
stand still oh he's gonna Frisk you he
begins
me
wait wait wait
um
steal my mind
give me guidance
please yeah it's mine
my mind is sealed you cannot get past my
mind
SU uh
I wasn't even approaching a useful
thought in that skull
oh
my head empty my head empties you know
what saved the day there you go uh can I
detect his thoughts Ryan
oh I have minus one intelligence oops
maybe not oh good luck well ah
no thoughts
can I roll again yeah sure go ahead I'll
try one more time
I prefer we not die
let's go a worthless no sport if this
one was even slightly useful I might
spare oh
um
first one why not no it makes you Hasty
I I just read your mind unlikely
but it costs me
I mean very well is stick
from the ship that crashed on this
wretched World definitely not us
giving me the weapon not to succeed the
reward will be great now go
here we go I'm good at original people I
just gotta be stupid
and they will hurt me yeah I wanted to
fight a dragon time oh you didn't it has
so much health
oh really
like over here okay there's a path this
way oh be aware that inspiration caps at
four so we have four again might as well
use it if you fail things okay I don't
know I was going up there oh I just
follow you guys
follow
eh
oh here kitty cat yeah she thinks I'm
done streaming because I haven't been
talking yeah that's her signal
I'm still streaming this movie well this
movie people looking oh we're here
there's a gate there's a gate is it
Baldur's Gate I must be
it's the first gate we've seen oh my God
oh no this is for the act two no make
sure you type anything
but we can come here later
so but this I wanted us to get the quest
so we can come back here
there's a good weapon in there we we
less less we lose it okay okay
interesting
well where to next oh ladies we might as
well go south oh Tea House the house
okay we're going there's the underdark
thing right yeah yeah there's a really
good weapon staff for me there I heard
so yeah
I want to keep a lookout for it okay we
gotta keep a lookout that should be easy
all right
well
Which Way Tea House
flight a village everyone teleport again
okay okay
I'm fast quick
um okay and then we go this way
I love River
I'm so
encumbered oh we're starting too much
again
if you right click on things you can
move it to Camp yeah send to camp and
it'll be in your storage box thing yeah
I'm gonna take these clothes off
no more naked
I'm not in cucumbered anymore
thank you okay
um
so tea house is down here Molly you take
the lead over here okay once we get it
yeah
over there but I did reveal how many
thirsty strange people are in my chat
what's going on
talk to them hello
I've never clapped eyes on your poor
sister clapped dropped
it was elasticity
go be nice to The Hags they're ages
please I don't know
it looks like she needs help no this
isn't she nice ask again yeah she seems
nice how about you all just calm down
this has nothing to do with me goodbye
lower your weapons she's just an old
woman
she's with the hug don't bloody stand
there gaping get off seems like we're
going on that same outcome
I mean I've seen this somewhere before
we have to protect her
and destroy
you want to go proof that natural
understanding that she's a nice lady
that's all that she is
I didn't mean for this she's got like
blood all over her granny gown what
happened it sounded like a heated
argument the best thanks are paid in
Gold I like that option oh yeah it's not
lethal boys you forgot about it again
who's
with me
my staying with her but I made a promise
May Rita begged me not to breathe the
word if they came looking for her and my
word is my bomb wow she seems like
she's evil isn't she
can't let her know
why would she be even look at her she
stole that little girl and the dudes
were going to go protect the kids like
thank you
I'm only leaving this note so you don't
panic and do something stupid I'm going
to the hag
come on man so rude I owe it to Conor to
make things right you know he'd do the
same for me I'll be back soon so not a
word to ma'am all right she has enough
on her plate
mm-hmm and then yeah
a nurse is looking at something I didn't
mean to
I don't think I can roll a 20.
you rolled a 20. I have a bite to eat oh
whoa what the whoa what's going on
is this like some hand sign oh
changes
swamp stinking and Insidious assaults
your senses
no it looks so pretty I don't want to
walk around here anymore
the reality of this place poisoned
apples give me
okay yucky putrid bog we're in the Bog
bog Beach what's going on
poisoned apples
who is that who's this little dude
I'm not sure but I don't want to know
Burlington the piece of gold hi
minions have creatures
what's going on
for
supposed to scare me buddy boy
pretending to be a sheep
take a deep breath and say bye
see if you're having a conversation
there wow yeah that that was a
conversation
seems like there's so much to look
around here
yeah it's pretty big area
[Music]
what are these stairs up here oh yeah oh
stairs are you going the right way Cali
you have Natural Instincts oh
they have game instincts that's a frog
hold on let's go down here
wait I'm talking to I'm talking to a
frog I think the frog doesn't really
matter until later no
what's wrong with the Frog I don't know
oh yeah
I wonder what are you croaking on about
you he's thinking you catch a waft of
something found
um
he hasn't taken a shower
there's something wrong with the Frog
most monsters will think twice before
making a meal of me oh that all sounds
bad ask your scent
spoil it
follow Cali Girls Sally look at that
behind me
oh okay bye frog okay I'm coming okay
all right
okay
oh who's this
don't
know whatever you're hunting your stench
alone we'll kill it a quick Witch is
rare indeed it was actually pretty slow
it took me about a minute to answer all
beings can spot whatever you say suggest
you find yours before dealing with the
lady of this house what's wrong with
this why you came to her there I take it
to bargain it's a bargain Lady of the
house
a more innocent name than some I could
call it we're here for tea what it is
what she is they don't want to concern
you uh wait what did I miss since the
first Darkness
and their knowledge is matched by their
spite it's just stinky
if you're full enough to pay their price
I look so at home here this just looks
like where I belong you know I'm Blended
yeah it really does it's your swamp yeah
uh what price is that whatever's easiest
to lose and the hardest to do without
quit speaking in your riddles bro it's
gone to crowd
she can tell me how to draw him out draw
who else I guess that she's a witch who
is it you're hunting truth is like a
blade my friend
we can arm ourselves with it okay
pressed against our throat
I would not put you in danger
oh good yeah that's not what this is
about is it
Barbarian I like danger the truth no yes
gonna try I believe in Mario babe come
on and well 20.
is what I excel at I'm made to
intimidate
[Music]
words
yeah yeah a little bit loser
dummy tell me what's going on
don't help him
alive absolutely not brother don't help
him we shared a special moment together
you see we have never met anyone named a
Starion ever he's no vampire we've met
you can give up your hunts of starion's
under my protection
attacked in the night our camp set upon
by a band of vampire spawn
okay the chaos of battle one of them
stole away with our children
oh
what children we believe this Astorian
knows exactly what happened that night
and where to find our little ones
people will make him talk
so I ask again
is he known to you downtown he's never
met a stereo we've never met there is no
we've never met it's I'm protecting him
or I know him
just leave just leave just leave
just leave no no no
oh I'm kind of curious don't leave
actually
give a pipe to come quickly you do know
him quietly never I'd never tell you yes
don't help him
I guess some people are saying they
killed him in pretty good loot
apparently I hope you find him diluted
him can we kill him
yeah he's easy easy you'll never heard a
Starion I mean not that I like him or
anything you know we did share him
oh yeah sure
so what happens with my Lightning Charge
plus one attackers until additionally
I consumed next time you deal damage
oh
what you gonna do what are you gonna do
it for him yeah
you got nothing on me okay now you do
never mind
what if you go up to him in hysterions
in your party
I did that um and I was like I literally
was like hey he's right here and as
Darren was like what the and then
we had a fight and I was like sorry it
was a dark histarian sorry about that
but it was funny it was very funny
pretty good
ganderl's aspiration there's a brand new
bow for you if you want here I'll pick
up this stuff you can take it out oh I
think that one wasn't was that one good
for me you didn't kill him you just
knocked out how do we kill him yeah well
good we can leave him here like that I
mean if you keep hitting him he'll die
eventually but you want the bow
do I wanna I mean you already have a
pretty nice one right
but if you want another I'll take the
bow if yeah take it take it hold on what
is I'll give it to you give give to
narissa that's a crossbow yeah I think
the crossbow
there we go I love a crossbow
um what a thing okay okay
um
yeah yeah beat his ass
you dead now he always did
sorry
let's go a nice trap this arm kits
that's exactly what we need well let's
see
um now that we got that guy maybe I'll
go to the house
yeah we'll do a little Explorer it's
showtime
okay I don't think we should jump in
right now yeah I think we should be
going to the house first maybe we should
just go through the front door drink
from the well what the no
stinky water I guess we could just go in
the front
Spider Sense
I don't know why you would have a bad
feeling it looks like Fiona
not the
um
[Music]
so get to it oh she's pregnant
come in come in you look really dirty
like the best yourself
a Cuppa
found me patience eat up Marina
I won't say it again this is messed up
poor girl I have some bad news for her I
killed your friend
no your guests so poorly I have some bad
news for her under your nose shut or
things will get messy
probably can lie
nothing I mistook you for someone else
Ethel killed your brothers
pretty insane but yeah she did it she
did that Rose sick crazy
not very convincing and I uh can I try
one more time
before
go for it
you've got me up man uh probably
gonna have a big fight now
however if we don't get it this time
it's not meant to be then it's a
critical failure
critical I mean I suppose that's what we
deserve Arena my darling it's not true
no
this scoundrel gotcha bro damn they got
us
a girl isn't really worth it anyway
[Music]
oh
no
anyway last sometime in the cage should
do her good you're not mad about it
my business oh it's just a jerk
it's yours oh
Sailor Moon transformation just magical
girlies
oh good wow she's a magical girl just
like us you're cute
all right I don't want to fight her what
I mean why not she should be easy she's
a chump yeah no the good thing is she
gets invisible
I think it's better if we don't manage
to kill her right away anyway
okay I don't even see her anymore so I
don't know where to shoot
[Music]
I I was here to hear a solo run right I
killed her here and it broke the entire
Quest so that's what I'm saying oh
really yeah what should we do
I want to kill the red caps that are
that are attacking us
yeah
and then we follow Where She Went
basically well she's still here just
invisible no yeah for now she's she's
running away though
oh okay
where are the red caps wow you killed
him
uh so far bring him in what if we all
just came inside and closed the door do
you think they can open the doors
um possibly I think they can maybe
they're too stupid to open doors
[Music]
Epic
yummy yummy yummy yummy yummy
[Music]
if it sounds like they're saying how'd
you get their yum yum whose hand is this
Now where's his hands kind of close to
my butt
right where it should be
[Music]
yeah yeah
I don't know why I went the other way
maybe I can maybe I can distract oh ah
there she goes okay she went for the
the fireplace run away
[Music]
she's gone now let's focus on the red
caps okay
welcome back
Sacramento
you guys ain't
grumble
yeah
you stood there like a statue
oh
yeah
and I get up again
I'm gonna break me down nice
you got it
get up Wawa get up come on
that was a sick burn
yeah for real
wow Theresa couldn't you have used that
magic hand to give me a hand
a too true Did you
back up again mommy mommy
[Music]
mommy mommy
oh what was that it was me being giving
you safety
whoa that's so safe
yeah
oh there's two
yeah too late there was more
yeah I think they're on their way oh
they're yeah they're about to enter
they're about to acquaint themselves
slowly but surely
oh yeah dude
you're a little little music to jam to
you know jig oh I can't
why can't I
hmm oh
why can't I hmm
what are you trying to do
oh nice nice okay one left I'm Gonna
Save my weapons
so I'm just gonna use this for now you
guys always like Pro daggers on spares I
think
if you have some
well
or Bagel nice try for a bagel
when in doubt
get him get him bow and arrow I need to
get my bow and arrow back damn
um
I think I can throw some I can't throw
anything but why I think I need to be
enraged
um
bro yeah I can't match
I probably could have been a bit further
away nice
you got one Health left yeah just
whatever
cool
wow
I'm not doing so well no
I love that
oh they're Scrolls
where's my knife yes
oh well
so they're done for and she ran away
that little castle
okay we follow all this stuff I guess
yeah yeah
I found a chest I'm gonna open it open
of Greater healing I steal because I
don't give up I don't give a yeah
yeah steel oh I got a key yeah steal
everything yeah she sucks there's also
so much bread
yeah take the bread yeah and we can have
dinner once
yeah
we do like buttered buns and this helps
yeah I had a I had a bunch of bread
today I love buttered bread right about
now with cucumbers and uh what do you
call the Schnitzel
isn't that the best thing I love China
so simple right never understood putting
butter on bread I think it's weird what
you're weird
maybe I'm weird but it like butter on
pancakes too is so weird to me yeah that
I wouldn't do either
there you are
because butter is like a salty thing I
associate like bread with like jam and
stuff so oh but you can still work with
the butter and there's unsalted butter I
do like garlic bread though oh yes
okay
oh thanks
I look like I could be related to you
actually
you're prettier oh thanks tell me where
the girl is or what do we can stay a
while no I don't think we care about the
girl married already
leave
oh you'll end up in tonight's stew she's
gonna eat us or I'll make you try it
already marinated
we'd like to see you try marinating
Marina we're gonna go in and do it oh
there's a lot of funky things here oh
it's pretty wacky wait what did I
perceive I perceived something I'm gonna
talk to this guy over here
family portrait used oh it's for some
reason it made me talk to the tree so
I'm in a cutscene I'm sorry yeah yeah
okay hold on watery eye can I leave this
poor dear wish
yeah everybody's suffering yeah
bad she's got quite a few prisoners
okay I'm gonna leave so Cali can do this
but I want to talk to Lauren
oh
this guy gnarly yeah
what's wrong with him what's his problem
magic spell
did
shining it does look like Legolas
he's a Legolas gone Golem
um
no can't stop can't and don't stop don't
stop just go your own way oh please
please
poor guy give him a hug
[Laughter]
the Mind dripping
and we said such a Sages
be nice to him realize there's magic oh
my eyes are so wide and kind
Ness whatever you're seeing it isn't
real
nice
no lies
I don't know why are you talking like
this
he's cursed like the others this is
nonsense
but it's true oh I mean his stuff
together always say and it's not
separated
everyone looks like you do elf it's
shocking I know
[Laughter]
he's beautiful
and this guy must have been inspired by
God Slayer
no
I'm not a mine get away you're so mean
is there anything you're ugly not be a
piece of uh later but we have to
continue uh so why don't you look at
this door Mario babe all right gnarled
door
presence within the door recoils
not again a nice ass
this is pretty good we could just stay
here and look at this for a while but
let me see yeah
I'm here to kill that nice muscles you
have like good leg muscles
very nice
shrouded in the glow of the
of this they charge
yes
let them in
for each you're mine for 30 more years
don't petal
s
nice leg this tag will be the least your
problems if you don't open up twitches
Barbarian into the Roar
do it you do it yeah
oh ogre Roar
um
the door shut don't imagine it's wooden
frame cracking
I wish that other guy would shut up I'm
trying to listen
she walks through the door heads form
shimmering with a jack you're pulled
from the vision
you feel the presence within shrink
replied wow until the door open
oh
Tim open the door
cool
should be easy to find her from here
right
can you get in Kiara
yeah
why not
why can't you go through you you don't
you just just walk through you don't
need to you don't need to talk to it
that's what I thought okay now now I can
now again
let's run it please
let's battle some randos yeah yeah
non-lethal attacks why would I do that
random people fight they have to die
yeah
who can I read
it and I really gotta go anyway
oh I can read incredible I thought there
was something in the way
it's going up I want to go apparently I
don't know if this is true but they are
saying pickpocket the masks and save
them
yeah I picked up some masks
no pickpocket the masks like take the
masks from them via pocketing
[Music]
yeah I think I don't know oh
it sounds not possible we can turn on
non-lethal
it's it's an insta kill when you steal
the mask but we want to kill them anyway
no never mind then yeah let's kill him
oh okay fair and square
sounds good to me
ah I feel kind of bad murdering all
these people yeah the same
kind of complicated to not kill them
we'll go ahead and kill them
yeah
yeah no one will know it's all happening
down here in the cave no one will know
yeah
that one needs to know Harley's secret
our little murder Secret
murder Secret
ly
oh wait you're not wearing any boots
yeah yeah Reckless attack
the ndu
and then
another frenzied stripes on you
nice that was pretty nice
ah there we go whoops nice they're
knocked out I should just kill him
or just take the masks uh you know oh
give it a go yeah good idea
one more left behind yeah yeah
everybody's in such good shape in this
game
yeah
I love it
everyone's feet now it's going down so
annoying
From Below he's not very smart is he
yeah oh yeah
oh what are we doing yeah that killed
them oh nice swag I'm not sure I think
you can wear them masks don't don't
seems not great
I mean weren't they being controlled
yeah you've got a good point
maybe for Cosmetics
yeah maybe I mean
laughs
do they carry anything besides the masks
I take slime bomb
let's see there must be another there's
like a ladder okay over here
oh oh
um
it's a waterfall we can jump through oh
yeah I thought that we could not go
through there yeah
oh my gosh I did not disconnect
yeah
um I would not short rest until we get
all the way down to say
we joining uh yeah hold on my game is
glitched
um oh no are you okay
joining failed cannot join the party
it's really weird
no it's just every time I say accept it
like glitches out
yeah let's restart my game
oh good thing I just saved yeah yeah
yeah gotta restart the game
no problem
thanks for me goodbye babu's gate bye
bye bye that was super weird
very super weird
oh
some glitches here and there we can take
it I mean for the most part it's really
not that bad but occasionally you still
run into them as you do with anything
play game
[Music]
all right I'm pulling it back up and
then I'll invite you guys okay
[Music]
okay
please sing it for me Kelly
oh Down Down By The River Why do I still
have a morning
voicemail are you hydrating properly are
you drinking yeah did you drink anything
yet today no yeah valid it's crazy
does it hurt when you talk
it doesn't hurt but it does feel like a
bit of a struggle to speak sometimes
I need it well while we're doing this
I'm gonna quick run and take an idol
meeting so I'll be right back please
grab your snacks
movie and then I'll invite the ladies
hmm
mommy is not done streaming
cute
[Music]
invites a game
I invited everyone play a game thank you
yes
I love this movie back in the game
yeah
working now
where are we okay here
foreign
HP
oh that's not great maybe a short rest
wait no anyway don't don't short rest
until we get down there okay yeah
but I can throw them maybe she can drink
a potion of healing
oh we have no short rest left
oh we don't yeah oh
maybe big rest
we might want a big rest before we do
this
[Music]
I'm fine with that
let me see
actually
I've returned welcome back
thank you
we have to leave the tea house though
because it's not safe here yeah yeah oh
yeah cause the map is red yeah okay
we can always come back though right
yeah
I'm here nothing bad will happen surely
motion of animal speaking
yay I wish I was real
I know right
right
mm-hmm trembles at the thought
we can see through your fancy Magic
lady
shut it please
please oh he's still talking I mean yeah
he just goes on he just goes and goes
Legends say he is still talking to this
day
oh we can rest up here yeah
alrighty ladies to the camp we go
[Music]
yay
oh well
someone want to talk to him
I'll I'll talk okay
see look you have a budget
I need some Bulldogs Charming
older Raven guards been taken who's sold
the forever I don't know
oh that's the guy who the who were
supposed to rescue who the father yeah
from the fire rebuilding yeah oh okay
the one that died
no no they they said he was kidnapped
and that we needed to get him back
remember him okay and then he got the
bow
if Floric says he lives then he lives
and we need to free him from his captors
you see oh Grand Duke Raven guard is my
father oh no I haven't said
our relation is no matter of pride not
least for him oh
[Music]
what do we say
and the choice is clear we should rescue
Duke Raven guard that means a lot but
what about ravencraft
no this is no drow plot these absolute
Nutters these true songs are behind us
absence
if they were to infect him he could lead
Baldur's Gate to ruin
all the more reason to find him
he got him us
but the future of the sword well it's
kind of cute
yeah
um
you should keep secrets like this for me
will hmm all right yeah when I look into
it yeah
right some expressions are really Sims
like
the coast
foreign a
man who belongs to the Past
I wanted you to hear the blade not the
shadow he left behind
deep okay we'll do it for you we'll
see you guys
okay what else nobody else wants to talk
I think are you okay
yeah yeah he's asking he's asking I told
him someone was looking for him
uh
but yeah why because casual sent him why
else tell me about this hunting he
always sounds so offended whenever he
talks about anything I know something
ferocious surely
Camp
um
a girl what are those vagabonds why
would they I suppose I shouldn't be
surprised what do you know about the
children
yeah but you know about the kids man but
why send anyone after me
um
maybe he wants to make an example of me
to show what happens to runaways well
maybe he thinks death is too good for me
I mean true
we just have to be vigilant keep our
wits about us
and kill any Monster Hunters on site
you had to
oh I'm not good at it please call me
beautiful
oh
I'm gonna kill you you're my enemy
friend zoned
more Story Time more more
oh I
remember this part yeah same oh
whoa hot if even why hot well
you've been naughty and you know what
happens when you're naughty God's damn
it anyone but her
oh
uh aren't you a luscious thing
get out of my camera
but I'm just getting comfy
I'm Will's Patron the fount of his power
will has a patreon I guess he's a worse
warlocks have like Patriots I think
oh
whoa she's in control
but carlock's still breathing I've taken
more pleasant shits than you mizora
buried
girl lady
by the way Carlock zariel sends her
regards
shut up mizora don't even mention zarya
Devils only
she's a tiefling not a monster oh
precious that vocal delivery is really
good but his face does not match
Target shall be limited to The Infernal
the Demonic the heartless and the
soulless
karlak meets the criteria by virtue of
having no heart will
[Music]
last
last at all
you better not lay your damn finger on
Carla don't you worry that oh they
all approved
stick nice that's a defined pup must
still pay his price
to wit no
no no
well
strike his flesh
so not well
gaining their essence
[Music]
I mean is there any way to attack her in
the camp
no
oh he just got horns
[Music]
he got horny bonked yeah
that's better I think
I think he'll like that what the hell
have you done suits him yeah good the
price paid
you know the terms get used to the new
form Pat
There's No Going Back
some magic even I can't undo then why
would you do it
tears Fair without their pressure
I have a swimsuit with a cut like her
dress oh yeah
yeah
I worry it's okay for me good pick I
think I know which one you're talking
about
oh
now a Starion wants oh oh so many people
want to talk I've ever listen to First
no
yes
[Applause]
hey
I mean don't do it some things we just
got to do about the content
[Music]
and now my game's going
there is this is
joining fails cannot join the party is
full no companions
trying to protect my viewers
I'm gonna commit to puku continue
all right well hold on a second uh we
might need to
the screen
oh no am I gonna get jump scared with
something lewd
this glitch is really bad
foreign
yeah yeah this is really annoying
what's your screen look like
it's uh it's kind of oh my God uh
it says it just
it's like how do I describe can't join
party full or something um
no problems again
confused all right well now we wait to
be invited again yeah
we shall safe more often now if this
happens again yeah yeah well we I mean
look all we did was reload go to Camp do
that scene and then you know so we we
really haven't lost that much
progressively yeah I can switch to mouse
and keyboard that's fine but I'm gonna
have to relearn the game
oh is it because of the the controller I
mean that's what people are saying but I
don't know
[Music]
no companions can be dismissed
your mouth
hmm oh very odd well maybe if I stop
using a controller it'll work all right
let me get you guys back in the game
shall we okay
we'll redo the will scene well we'll
have to retalk will first and then we'll
have to do that again cool let Maury
talk more you talk to hysteria and
Marissa no I refuse
there is a you horny
horny girls
for the content here it's for the
comments yeah
are you talking about it's for the
content
you're just so crazy I didn't expect
that from you Marissa you're the one
that had nudity turned off on the game
whereas I kept it on let's not go there
let's not go there
there's one leader of the horny Patrol
here and let me tell you it's not me
bless you thank you
all right no I just printed off let's
see how do I go how do we go to the camp
oh we gotta get out of here yeah
okay well let me switch back over to
Games Shall we push back again
bless you thank you
all right
go away yeah we're going okay chill dude
all right let's see
okay
hey you guys talked will I'm just gonna
tell Starion again about the guy same
text Skip through
okay I'll talk well
are you guys at the camp
wait wait wait for me to the camp
I have no clue where
please hold on camera
oh this is so weird to control
how do I Zoom around do I how do you Pan
the oh there we go you can rotate it
like that
maybe was it back up here
I'm coming to pick you up
you don't have to it's it's okay oh
there it is got it there's the door
little trembles yeah
no one left behind me
I'm Sorry by the river all right
hey thanks hey hey hey
let's go
controlling the camera will be a little
it'll be a learning process but we'll
figure it out
called me Stinky oh that's not nice
no I I took a shower today
thank you now which which key do we
press to go to the camp
press the campfire icon and then hit go
with your mouse oh yeah long rest just
everything clickety-clack
and I think Kiara already talked to will
yeah indeed so yeah after she's done
talking to Carlock we can just go sleep
redo that cutscene
take a shower I just want a bond with
Carla a little bit
oh
I wanna give her a hug did you give her
a hug oh you look so sad I wanna wait
what does that remind me of there we go
okay ready for sleep anytime yeah ready
for sleep ready end the day
remind me of
um
yeah surprise yeah thank you we talked
about this before
hey oh is it me again okay
um
uh get out of my camp
I'm trying to say the same things again
yeah yeah
don't touch Carla well
yeah
I'm wild he's getting crazy
oh that's it yay and then
together
I can't I can't stand you wow I mean
questions
by virtue of being you know
I understand I get it I can't believe
him he wants to put his hands on the
muscles part Wants What It Wants You
know very dangerous
I mean I guess I'll come find you after
everyone is asleep
I guess
kind of stuff
she's happy
we're all uh doing our best here that's
all right don't think that what narissa
was trying to do was very homey like
Anyway this whole time she's trying to
steal your man like what the hell
I'm getting Shadow heart plot something
hurts
oh no uh she's she's a drama queen don't
don't listen no
she's always hurting
I'm gonna go Snoop on you guys this
conversation joyous little Affliction
that visits me with screaming Agony on
occasion you mean
is that supposed to be Shadow heart
that's me from time to time yeah you're
really concerned about it she's she's
just nothing to do
in case your imagination is in danger of
getting away from you
it's just something I have to live with
are you okay
quite a lot if I'm being honest
but it always passes quickly so I can
manage
meow big baby oh that's the kitty cat
yeah I
I watched Garfield today how was it nice
it was cute I know
fluffy I don't understand how exactly
but I felt it go to you
it's important we're gonna get another
Memorial Day scene
I don't know if I want that to be honest
I mean you don't have to watch are they
still making out
but the artifact yeah no I'm I'm going
I'm listening I'm snooping on something
it likely won't
the best thing is to stay close
by real Snoopy eventually I'll need to
she complained about Garfield not
showing his balls
[Laughter]
[Music]
when they do like uh drawings of cats
and they include the little cat butt and
the little cat you know yeah yeah the
balls it's kind of cute they're so round
and plump you know they're cute yeah
Garfield didn't have that and there was
so many shots of his like back where you
could only see his his big chunky
stomach and not not the balls though it
was like something's missing man
maybe why can't we go to sleep
I'm not casting I'm like oh
that joke bro goodness gracious
all right well hey
this is a great time to go ahead and let
you guys know that time to look at a
cutscene oh no oh what's this
um should I get big for this maybe I
have a big announcement you guys
so great news everybody
oh it's over oh swear I mean cool anyway
I mean oh well yeah yeah go ahead yeah
it's the vine whoa
whoa I know I know let's go
um yeah I asked I asked ahead of time
the ladies said that I could oh yeah it
is showing her
whoopsies
um it was it was secretly secretly shown
there just kidding huh it's not a secret
because you guys definitely saw it right
oh God the PGM is so loud sorry
um
I asked I asked the others permission to
be allowed to show because I I have to
because in about in about seven minutes
my my brand new EP jigo six the EP is
being released in a big old record what
uh look at this it's vinyl
mingle vinyl record this is the shell
hours by the way everybody's gonna show
some stuff hopefully everybody so yeah
check it out you guys in about seven
minutes correct so be sure that you
check the link there's gonna be a big
old big old Link in the description
check okay make sure that you click you
grab it before it's gone because I don't
know if we'll restock this bad boy so
you wanna you wanna get it quick you
guys you'll want to get it quick
congratulations on the vinyl
thank you you guys thank you yes the
Mori store thank you thank you thank you
David thank you thank you
guys Maurice store has really fast
shipping by the way
um the more restore you have a more
store yes a universal Universal made it
uh it's a Mori store that it ships very
fast
ship to Europe
I'm not sure I I think it does
it ship to Europe because I know I have
EU beats I don't know I don't know if it
ships fast but to Europe but I think oh
it's a U.S because I think it depends on
the country but yeah it does ship to
Europe but um it's it probably won't be
fast
[Music]
made a mistake but anyway you guys can
get it I have a couple more images to
show sorry for people that aren't on my
stream that can't see big Starry yeah
there are two records go to Cali's oh
it's Cali if you want to see pictures
yeah you want to click the link in the
description it'll take you to where it's
going to be sold
um but yeah it kind of looks like this
and then uh there's some of Uranus art
that's also going to be included it says
sample on it because no no thieves No
Stealing about that no stealing yeah no
beavering no thievery um but yeah unless
you're playing Baldur's Gate yeah then
you can be a thief
that's totally cool that's way totally
cool no problem
um let me get the link I don't know if
if the if they're gonna paste the link
in there hold on a second I'm gonna put
the link in the description myself
because I am my own master
um
I can do my own multi-test yeah I sure
can so yeah that was what I wanted to
um promote for today day and
the description is now updated so grab
your coffee board the Maury train
ing just kidding but it is really cool
it makes a nice decoration piece you can
frame it you can play it on your
phonograph
Etc so please check it out
um who's next on the the show the show
board yeah
game afterwards
chilling hours yeah very specific timing
no skip ad yeah I'm very sorry could not
change it but yeah Kiara's next
yeah I recently
released an album it's still open for
pre-order uh link is also in the
description if you want to get a
physical version and oh surprise
actually today I released the Korean
version of do you it was so good yeah
because it was actually one year
anniversary of Julio so I thought let's
make a Korean version because it already
sounds like K-pop let's go yeah the
album and uh Korean version of do you
and pineapple MB is still out there to
be streamed yoroshiku please please take
a look at it and yeah keep on streaming
the album so because it's my first one
so I hope it can do well
everybody go listen thank you there's
something for everybody on it yeah it's
my first my first ever physical like
music thing because all my singles
before were like online only digital
only and this one you can actually get
as a physical thing yeah so very special
yeah
that's a stream point of view point of
view point of view
anything else oh
um let's see oh uh this Friday or
Saturday depending on what time zone
you're in uh but Saturday for uh c
um I'm going to be appearing at Thai
comic oh yeah uh yeah it'll be my first
panel ever so I'm kind of really nervous
for it but um I'm calling my mom so she
can you know coach me and teach speaking
Thai better so I can I can talk to
everyone I'm really nervous that I'm
excited uh lots of views
[Music]
thank you
that's it for me cool
that's so cool that you so quickly get a
con appearance that nice nice nice I
hope you get to speak some Thai let's go
Flex those skills yeah Flex
I apart from my streaming schedule I
don't have anything I have a club with
biboo next week
is it wait yeah Tuesday Tuesday
yeah a chat where we're going to talk
about the first night that we spent
together yeah
we will so please be sure to be their
typical time at 8 PMC team
look at Larissa's song covers yeah yeah
like about my song covers so I can
release another one
yeah that's all for me yay
ladies being busy with putting out
things so support us yeah yeah
everybody's working hard to give you
guys cool stuff so hell yeah yeah thanks
for for supporting us and what are you
trying to talk to him again
you're funny
oh man let me fix my little sensor image
keep it right in front of me
such nice weather
nice weather we're having today
oh wow Will's telling me his life story
and oh wow there you go you can have
will mm-hmm yeah I guess they go for
will or Gail when Everyone likes me more
he's horny just like you
what
yeah
I mean horny as and he's got horns now
good morning girl
I heard you were making fun of me in
your stream in your member stream Kiara
I always am
I believe dude I I don't know who leaked
you that information anyway I don't know
I've just heard it oh courtly Dan he's
gonna Court you yeah
what's up lizelle
sorry that no one's talking to anybody
lonely
[Laughter]
it's about the Dragon Rider we met that
thing's important just leave
wait no I said did you hear about it or
are you a member
anymore
yeah right I don't think we can we can't
join we can each other's memberships
it's a shame it doesn't let us I mean
you can have a private accounts
the farmer's dearest fruit naturally was
no apple no Peach but a daughter oh we
can learn a lot from fairy tales
don't you why is he acting like this
I mean the dude just got transformed
like I feel alone
yeah and given the circumstance
I do it again
my soul was a necessary price to pay for
you know I can't say more
oh I can say this sorry little guy I had
but one road I could travel
for now you have a dozen the hundred
a thousand to choose from
a road that leads to a devil yeah this
really wants to make you this makes me
want to play more on my own I know right
now let's see all what happens to all
the characters and stuff exactly yeah
it's just such a different game playing
with everyone yeah it is in the river of
blood emerges finally someone approved
of something I did it's a lot like that
yet
[Laughter]
be my mother what do you see oh
quite the handsome devil it's because
you know the heart lurking under the
horns the people oh she's trying to
raise them up
[Laughter]
do you understand that she is also
teefling now yeah like what are you
talking trying to lecture
and I'm like hello
there's so many there's so many he
approves every time I talk to him
yeah
he's getting those points up well yeah
yeah I gotta get gotta get my approval
up hunting even though we can't check
because we can't put them on our team
child crying out from a lone Farm yeah
for real I found him in the fields
flanked by goblins you just gotta
believe his mother's corpse bled into
the sword you know what if the approval
only goes to Mori open but I remember
blessed
[Music]
with some kind of special magic
[Laughter]
is friendship tomorrow
angry at myself and it took so long for
me to see the coast suffering I still
want to understand why there's two of
gails
don't question it I I am questioning it
don't question it and it's nice to meet
someone this is the thing that he does
having a worm wriggling in my skull
sometimes in the days ahead no with you
as my Ally the future looks a little
less oh he's sweet yeah it's a nice
possibility that's kept me countless
nights if you want to play the hero and
be the nice characters
play her games
which is why don't you take will
laughs
it could well be she could clone herself
wouldn't you what a good argument I mean
yeah but what would you do with the
clone of yourself if you had one make it
do your chores what if it has a mind
you'll have to let me out you want to
make out with yourself Kiana I would say
he would man piano what kind of he's
standing here with nothing but the
clothes
I mean you know yourself best don't you
I'm sorry one of my jailbirds just said
something funny and I need to repeat it
to you guys but they said you should
have turned a Starion into the Monster
Hunter and gone the full young daddy
around oh my God you can't
that'll be pretty funny actually we
almost turned it man
yeah maybe next playthrough yeah next in
Another Universe we can I'm sure of it
no I refuse I would never it's okay
every single one of our one of our
things what are the companions I'm too
attached to all of them I don't want
anything bad to happen to them we should
go out we should leave the camp amazing
yeah let's leave let's leave yeah let's
go kill the hag
yeah long rest leave okay there we go
okay I gotta learn how to play it now we
go
oh yeah yeah let's go
foreign
do you do you say you do feel the same
see I cloned myself and do you already
if you remember yeah yeah what were you
making out with yourself
they weren't they were they were raising
each other up yeah it was like a mating
dance like a bird exactly oh my God
no you were Rising me up you were asking
me if I did I remember I remember was
she talking about she's going crazy can
someone calm her down
okay waterfall
be careful
obnoxious oh is this the bug where you
don't see them
because normally I had that bug before
do you see the fumes girls
Flames okay that's nice actions have
both
yum
can't find we should save after we get
down here we can uh throw things onto
the noxious fumes thingies where's Kelly
I I just figured out how to jump ah
no okay thanks
just just point point
wherever you want to go often they will
just find their way try to learn how to
use the cameras you're like a little
baby bird yeah so the camera checks I'm
getting used to but now I would not
change my format I'll play for anything
oh what's this event
yeah yeah we can like throw something on
it that's normally we should we have a
like a graphic glitch right now I think
normally we should be seeing like fumes
oh yeah the thing wait wait wait wait
wait don't go away
wait for everybody do short rest before
we didn't we just do a long oh yeah
short rest and then heel or uh yeah all
right now let me see God I hate this
fight okay
F5 F5 and hit F5 okay yeah okay
oh and Cali yeah if you want to see like
items press alt and you see what's lying
around Alt
yeah alt currently you don't there's
nothing really around them got it I'll
remember that
okay all right onward okay ready this
fight sucks let me tell you that yeah it
does the cage you want me to kill you
maybe
do we care about her I mean it would be
cool to save a life but I mean we don't
have to
trap yeah yeah we don't wait we can just
you know
go with the flow yeah
I see The Hags hello eggs
hello I'm gonna attack her
wait wait wait Molly's in a country oh
I'm sorry I thought I thought it dragged
everywhere I'm sorry no no no no I'm
wearing it weren't it wearing it
[Music]
yeah
I'd like to see you try to keep you
alive until life
I'll bring you back
you can shoot several people
[Music]
I killed your brothers why do you care
about me
shut up Rando she doesn't care about you
yeah but she says just get out of here
please like she has any kind of concern
shut the up
she does
that was like half my health yeah
even though I killed the fan that cake
uh I guess I guess I'll save her here
you go
so we gotta figure out which one's real
I swear I had a boat get rid of them
maybe I don't there's more Frenzy
someone want to attack one of them I
already did I got rid of one clothes
[Music]
oh gross okay I won't do that spell yet
then
and turn oh is that the real one
okay
uh they're so far
making clones
yeah I can't launch
what a cute birdie is that yours Kiara
yeah I brought a raven into the party
yeah
oh my God it's like yeah there's a
murderer
right a group of is it always and only
crows is there a difference between the
group of crows murder of crows yeah
it's an unkindness of Ravens and I'm
kind and yeah
group of animal names so funny I wish I
knew
let's see I wish they weren't oh wait no
wait it's the one that's not wet it's
the one that's not wet is actually her
because I I made actually beat up
no the one that's not what you can beat
up oh okay the one that is the one that
should not beat up yeah the one that is
what is the one that I saved okay
yeah so let's see where is the other one
oh yeah right uh-huh
yeah the one that's on level one versus
the one that's on level five yeah oops
that's not what I meant to do but all
right actually I didn't need to do that
either
wait
um oh
well I made our decision easier yeah
happens to the best of us it was the
other way around it's time it's fine
brain empty
she's really not that helpful anyway
yeah inventory okay there we go
inventory and then my I have a bow oh
yeah cause like when you save her she's
like super ungrateful apparently oh okay
sucks
um I mean validly
what I mean well yeah because we did
kill her family so I kind of feel her
yeah
like when you find out her motivations
she was here by her own you know choice
so who didn't really want to be saved
yeah
so you kind of interfered and then you
know
for something she didn't ask for sure
anymore anyway oh you're right
I'll use an action equip
ment they need help not letting me
well no oh I don't have what's going on
just kidding I don't have any more I get
it and turn
guys
oh let me take the damage let me be
useful somehow yeah
that's a bit much
oh she's going up there
annoying better with big weapon you know
I hope your soul is in good hands
oh
what no nothing big dumb dumb Go Raven
go sh
[Music]
oh
let's go we're doing it guys our
figuring it out
it's all coming together
ah man I need to get on a high high
ground
yeah
yeah me and your Raven are beating her
up it's sick
Raven didn't do no he's trying his
best stick your eyes out that he is
[Music]
good luck
I agree
I mean bro
made her really
not reach
yeah now you're bleeding oh my god oh
whoops
she's wet right now yeah guys you just
realized the girl that we killed there
was a child inside of her body
Ah that's no good
well we'll keep that in mind for my
personal playthrough I guess
he's kind of forgot about that oh
kidding me
it's a waste of time I'll find a way to
return
double kill then you wouldn't be begging
for your life
right
so how about we be civilized about this
hmm
I have something you want
um
what are you gonna do Memorial Day
you want to be stronger tougher smarter
done
just let me go ability scoreboard
that's pretty cool I mean that's kind of
cool we can just beat her up again if
she comes back to life
give me power the more the better the
more powers
here
that
you have to yeah
I couldn't set up shop elsewhere
people always need lotions and Potions I
mean
get out of here before I change my mind
if I ever see you again you'll be
fertilizing this swamp if I ever say
human you'll have a tentacle for Tom I'm
glad no understanding peace
I think
yay I'm taking her the marina necklace
strength yeah maybe it'll be useful
someday
foreign
big smashies
I don't know what these are all these
potions potions potions take them
free potion everything what's that
what's the mushrooms sir I got her staff
I don't know take it
pick everything
is inspired
it teleports you if you go there
all right then shall we get out let's go
you guys got everything all right
yeah okay let's go probably
yeah nice oh that sounds interesting
hey where could we be
back in the swamp
yay
oh coffin uh that's her her guy
Marina's that's rough that's rough buddy
can someone talk to the dead yeah maybe
you gave me a thing that helps me talk
to the dead right yeah you have you
should have a talk to the dead necklace
it's a necklace I think yeah you're
wearing it so you should have it in your
skill bar yeah it says rare speak with
the Dead
um in my skill oh yeah there it is
let's go all right speak to the Dead
hold on let me turn it turn it around I
bet I can oh yeah narissa also has the
ability now because she read the book
that gives her the speak to the dead
ability yeah
but he is dead uh I wait no I said did
you get the the one it's called bitter
divorce I do have bitter divorce can you
use it on him I don't know how to use it
past Bell
oops okay did I eat it must be playable
character
I don't think I don't think I did oh I
think it's because the girl's dead that
you can't continue this yeah
um that's rough
buddy I mean I understand though it
makes sense
that's okay
I have her necklace should I leave it
with him no just wear it nurse it
doesn't work on it if I wear it maybe he
thinks I'm her yeah no I'm dead not dead
so apparently he's a zombie and that's
why we can't um
foreign
that's that I guess what do we do next
what do we do next
ladies I'll leave it up to you good
question something short It's relatively
short oh I guess we could go to the
underground didn't we go there last time
yeah but we didn't finish
yeah
we'll definitely want to get some health
back maybe a short rest sell United yeah
sell cello night
um how do I quick travel
don't go so fast Cali is not even here
oh I'm just gonna grab a weapon and then
I'll be back okay
it's a Bard sword
the one that's right by the entrance
just don't get into trouble
I'll try
maybe I might fail to get it
there it is she's taking dick
oh the sword
it's in the wooden crate oh my God
everything even grunt for us narissa
I'm gonna get it
yeah we killed that dude to the Minotaur
I'm not gonna go in I'm just gonna look
at what he had oh nothing just kidding
she got it yay
Bard sword
sword am I solo play for what came to
the underdark from a different place and
I I wasn't able to enter where we're
standing in right now I just explored
everything outside
you need to collects like three pieces
or something oh
from people
I think
there's a staff of the Moon made and
what's that that sounds cool fancy
all right
well this is beautiful I think I know a
good place where we could go here in the
underdark okay okay take us lead the way
the Mushroom City
I love
oh that's I love mycinium and it's not
what it's called but the oh my God
whoa earthquake
we just gotta get down I don't know
where the weight goes down
here
oh wait it's shaking isn't that a sign
of the that monster oh oh yeah oh yeah
was it oh
uh let's get out of here let's keep
walking let's keep moving okay okay okay
through here
I don't know what I'm seeing no yeah
oh that's on your mind
there's a voice talking to you I
okay he's done
now we can go yeah big deal they're
coming who cares I ain't afraid of no
ghosts
oh
whoa
that wooden chest nice stuff
let's see Heavy test whoa A lipid Powers
I haven't actually used these yet
um
yeah I haven't used these yet either oh
yeah there's a Minotaur up there I've
used one
oh I just used one oh yeah remember we
also I think we'll share them yep yeah
use more
oh I just used one I only used one yeah
uh
click click click on your inventory
and then you see the little things in
the Middle top of the page that opens up
click on the one that says a lipid
powers
and you can you can you can manage a
list that it'll bring you to a brain and
you can clear but there's one thing I
thought
yeah we we had three
but we can find more there's a lot of
them in the game
okay so it's okay for me to use yeah
yeah use one we used one we're all gonna
share
yeah help check which one do I pick
they're not shared yes they are
they absolutely are shared I used I mean
we don't all gain the same but we we
collectively all have the same amount of
brainworms there's Minotaur up there
cookie
I don't know where I saw it said three
and I popped one thing and then I heard
people say I used one and now there's
only one left
I know I already ate the hair guys look
at my inventory
wait wait up here look look up here it
has been consumed
there's bags
well you did your best
um
okay we can do a ranged attack that
should be fun just kidding it was not
fun difficult position to start in
we'll get through it
look at do it where is the second one
I'll find it
oh I'm surprised I hit I only had 55
percentage
you're gonna go to bed
I'm fine I will die well maybe we will
but it'll be sick
oh he doesn't have that much health this
will be fine
yeah we'll be fine you know the middle
doors are not a problem
oh yeah
that's awful
oh oh there's another one a raven it was
just really started
Force tunnel
I want to try it
okay
yeah back up
okay wait I'm gonna put something
here don't walk past it oh okay
nice
[Music]
it's so broken I love it so much
laughs
oh he dead now oh yeah he's super dead
all right then next we just got the
other one yep just one more left
burn
nice cool
oh
yeah yeah just stand right there yeah
did he get hit by The Cloud of daggers
yeah
the teamwork okay here's a question of
something I haven't figured out how do I
turn off that
what is this how do I turn it off on the
right side concentration something
something Amulet of the unwell maybe in
your hot bar somewhere
like sounds concentrating on you want it
I have the amulet no I don't I don't
know someone who does that what was it
bludgeoning yeah
vulnerability to bludgeoning damage if
someone wants it
you can just take it from my inventory
I also got 100 gold so nice airing your
inventory yeah well I mean it's all our
inventors the party's inventory yeah
okay
how about disarming first I disarmed one
if you would just wait can I take this
hat in your inventory Cali yeah shaken
okay okay you want something you can
probably take it whoa what happened
there
they just they're prepared
critical failure of disarming a trap
yeah no it's a walk through it oh attack
she doesn't care about God did you just
I broke it I broke the Trap nice
guys why did you crawl up
the room was going crazy downstairs guys
yeah
I know I can't we can't go yeah you can
there's a thing over here a mushroom
jump on the mushroom Mario
yeah there you go there's stuff up here
though if you want to look
yeah goodies
I know this is
it's looting time
[Music]
mercenaries and Cutthroats useful
friends
oh everything's lost everything is
locked yeah what if we attack it just
stay on fire
oh
yeah I can attack it
okay aren't there keys around here
they're there for the taking
oh nice
Alchemist fire
it's raining
[Music]
on fire
you girls being aggressive
oh my God
I cannot believe I can't set wood on
fire
I know what if we didn't break it
salutenberg attack
I'm disarming it oh it's got a track oh
I got gotcha gotcha I didn't see it had
a trap on it
I just disarmed it okay yeah here you go
eh okay where I disarmed it but now we
need a key
ah classic
um
lock picker do your thing
oh there's skulls in here nice
I'm such a ring of fire ear warm today
I like that song I don't blame you
you just break it over Johnny Cash good
man
oh it's pretty sturdy
lock pick
oh this should totally be possible
yeah there you go open sesame
he opens it open
well that's a good idea all the good
stuff Arrow of darkness and arrow of ill
model look oh there's an elevator here
but it doesn't work yeah it's broken I
already looted everything here okay okay
it's like we got all the goodies
all right let's go down
to uh mushroom land
yeah I like mushrooms
me too
okay
a mushroom sauce I think I can still I
can still eat but just mushrooms that
are not pasta
don't make me hungry I'm gonna make you
hungry you're gonna feed me and there's
the people wait wait
yeah you talk to the people oh okay yeah
hello
careful mushroom people
listen
wow they look cool are these little
mushroom villagers
the harmony
oh he's got a funny face
they all look so shiny beautiful
is he the choir fades
oh all right
you see a
visionless body wrapped in fungal
tendril no the sovereign
[Laughter]
yeah right
welcoming
yay
well do you want to live in a mycinoid
company
no matter what a soft right yeah you'd
have to live here underground that
reminds me of
that's the that's the Sovereign yeah The
Sovereign reminds me I wouldn't want to
live here but it's nice to know about
this Village shiny like you
oh yeah
Laura Village but follow one person yeah
who wants to lead the way I want to
follow people go okay
hello
oh is this a shop it says shop on the
map yeah
hello
oh blurg what a name what letters
Cali someone in my chat is saying Cali
taking a compliment is she feeling okay
the spools connecting trying to learn I
can't see my face yeah that's a big old
hand in your face
at your service
oh
is he is like us
is yeah does he have a worm is he a true
story
um
curious to find a surface dweller here
what has brought you down so deep
ah
just want to chill looking for shrimps
uh I'm lost a common phenomenon in the
underdark I'm afraid could I ask what
you were searching for to begin with
mushrooms
uh explain the whole story
here's my life story
infected my related tadpole
it's a miracle you're still intact you
must be worried sick but have no fear I
have a friend who may be able to why is
she so nice
is
detention it is this Adventurer has an
enlisted tadpole inside her head but she
hasn't turned we're special
yeah yeah
it's him
is this the one that is he the one
oh
he's the last one a nice one yeah let's
have him take out our tadpoles ah try
um help open your mind to
he seems friendly yes
it's kind of sad
yeah totally let's do it uh okay I trust
you
all right wait a minute let's see if
it's that easy
Squidward it feels ten times its size
alive oh wait
is
the incubation
as should your transformation I think it
seems nice huh
[Music]
it appears to be in some form of stasis
wait is this the one you can beep
no ah okay sad what a shame
uh can you help no
no it appears to be Shield
physical and magical influence
the extraction would involve severe
cranial trauma
cranial
that doesn't
house I have healing magic disrespect
but one can only heal so much of their
own brain tissue ah man
but not to worry
should you transform oh well I don't
want to transformed that's the whole
point new examination
damn
I have never set foot on one myself
they were our warships during the
greatest eras of the illicit Empire
the entire astral plane from their decks
his design was lost when the gift
rebelled
out
interesting oh that's why they were
dragons or something
okay thank you I guess
I am sorry I cannot assist you in its
huh well Big Ups anyway
yeah
an idea yeah
[Music]
stasis
there are many alchemical substances
substances
[Laughter]
I like that
spawn
why you sound pretty surprised
you ruined it no I don't like it anymore
can be quite dangerous
cause confusion in those that approach
them
tongue is
planetary we have to eat a tongue you
um oh they're mushrooms okay lovely so
where do I find these mushrooms the
underdark of course although they are
quite rare and their Discovery perilous
I imagine Lenore would have them in her
possession she served mistra as a cleric
uh all right where's she living the
Southwest when I last saw her although
her Tower does have a tendency to move
weird it's alive interesting okay
continue she is quite fond of her garden
Lenore has always been a lonely sort
nature was her only companion I honored
another chance to join the society
buttons who asked you her experiments he
knows a lot priority right
okay
um
I'll I'll come back when I find them I
guess your travels be safe I like this
too
don't don't steal don't steal yeah I'm
not gonna steal
but does somebody need to sell some
stuff oh yeah people is very full on her
inventory yeah
I think
I think we've done like like we can
explore the city a little bit more and
then we could end it yeah okay yeah it
seems like a good a good place the proud
member of the Society of Brilliance At
Your Service oh Cali's talking
I mean I thought this was the shopkeeper
but he's like going through a bunch of
weird stuff right now yeah he first
wants to talk
shopkeepers always so talkative why are
they so talkative but I can I can sell
him stuff
do you have anything interesting to
change
to your liking
sell all jewelry that isn't useful
correct
yeah jewelry and all like
um
you could sell a lot of your great
swords and stuff can I throw the great
sword
yeah I might want to hold on to it then
put some armor you want to know a fun
trick yeah do we still have the girl we
killed
no menthara I don't think yeah okay
because what you can do you can collect
dead bodies and keep them in your
inventory and then you can eat dead
bodies for big damage because they win a
lot you gotta say what the heck what
about these masks we don't need the
masks anymore right no okay no I'm away
with you that would be pretty cool I do
like that that is deadly
I enjoy that yeah
um I'll sell all these poisonous
difference
in my own playthrough I've been
collecting dead bodies
bringing them at my Camp so I can look
at them and remember my spoils
when the wearer gains lightning charges
they also gain three temporary hit
points one of you guys might want that
oh does lighting charges help me because
I'm lightning I think so we should grab
that um I also have a weapon that gives
me Lightning charges automatically
so oh nice now you could really use that
so maybe you should buy that after I'm
done in here
oh is somebody selling I have lightning
charges on my shoes actually yeah he's
selling something called the lifebringer
it's like a tiara looking thing
two hour 40 hour Tiara for Liara oh
letting charges gives attack and damage
bonuses to anyone so it's good in
general
I have to do math oh gosh okay
oh no you can you can just press the
button at the bottom to to balance it oh
I see
yeah there we go wow that's so nice I
didn't notice that okay
all right I'm done
go ahead okay
do your shop stuff
lurg
what a dude silly name what a silly
little guy
I'm such a silly little guy indeed wow I
can't look at what's in the chest
without like opening it and stealing
right
no you will you will make everyone here
fight you don't do it not great
that's not great let me save really
quick I'm not gonna do it of course but
yeah yeah of course
you're just thinking about it no it's
good because honestly here
I kept accidentally clicking on the
barrel stock and they will all attack
you if you do that because they think
you're trying to steal
not pleasant
oh
mind flare can remove your tadpole if
you talk to them
yeah but why would I want to do it
also didn't you just
okay I'm good
okay I'll try again really quickly too
that is not true really quick yeah no
they're lying don't listen to them
oh one guy the head could have removed
it though if you would have not tried to
kill her really
from it yeah which is why I kind of
don't want to give it up
yeah yeah but she would kiss your eye
and it would give you a special skill
too that you can only get from the hag
had you not intimidated her right away
yeah
sometimes we just got to be true to the
characters we play
you could have looked even cooler
the trader has no more no more money
okay ah wait oh no more money okay if
you need to get rid of some stuff
although your weight looks fine you can
still carry it I know but I have an
Ingot I wanted to sell there's another
Trader down here oh
oh they're both merchants
oh
um
I'm on my way to becoming the richest
person why don't you need to trade
yeah I okay
can I talk to you
[Music]
he's cute what a cutie
hello little buddy
read if you can tell animal talking
wait I have animals oh yeah
oh are you guys killing people
we're casting
back he treats me
doesn't kick me oh
yeah he doesn't say much
the lightning thing
yeah I guess I'll buy it if you still
have that I can double your inventory
space that's wacky oh
yeah sounds tough though and complicated
I think so should I wear it guys
yeah wear what
the tea Wawa yeah it's Yara for Liara
this one
how'd you grab it
uh
uh grabbing now
okay I own it yeah yes
it can be useful for your lightning
stuff
yay
okay now he also got some money back
good for him
now are we all done Trading
this way
up here you go up these um
there's a guy like this hello
what you doing
why don't you ask him
silver and stick fingers stroke
here
sparkly
watch
a violence
oh no no
[Music]
no
[Applause]
not the babies
right this is how I killed those chicks
in my anniversary video flows to the
PACE
yeah that was crazy the kill you saw it
yeah
of course
survival in the wild
oh we got a
Village we gotta beep up some people
uh
uh sure why not yeah it's over here we
can help yeah
oh except this gift
nice mushroom powder
mushroom does The Sovereign gifts you
want people your girl's so pretty
you think so I like the Buns I like your
eyes I could stare into them forever
just like yours
Circle
um what are you doing
kill him don't do it don't do it don't
do it oh I wanna how do I do that I want
to learn
oh all right he was honest
at least he's honest yeah he's real for
that bye bye
um but you know if there is a mushroom
you might want to kill I can lead you to
one
we want to kill a mushroom yeah a
mushroom game okay you mean the
wait the dwarf like here one uh yeah
the fat one
ah that one why why kill him we bring
him with us
yeah he's talking to me
sovereign
hey all right that's not bad shaming
he's cute
he is not cute yeah he's cute I want to
give him a big hug yeah it reveals it
the other one the other one's beautiful
this one's cute no no the other one's
cuter
you better be nice to him narissa no
he's not cute he's an ugly bastard
oh what's wrong with you why is so much
anger
is there something you want to admit to
us Marissa no he's gross secret
projecting
what she's really protesting quite a bit
she might be hiding Mario hey do you
have a problem with me see he wants to
join us
but he's not joining me
yes join yeah yes you let him let him
join you yes he will be my new pet yes
your new pet
[Applause]
and
um
why do you think he's cute are you okay
because it's always cuter friendship
lovable
I mean yeah but he looks he looks sticky
and slimy yeah the others do like the
mushroom in your fridge that you've left
it the Slime is fun though
yeah but not not rotting slime he looks
like he'd smell bad
like he's riding
oh
when have you ever seen a slimy mushroom
and been like that looks tasty I should
eat that oh I don't like slimy mushrooms
as long as we stay in here
yum
yeah we just can't leave the on the dark
then he's gone yeah yeah okay but we're
staying here so all is good yes
what else is there to explore I don't
know much more because this is where I
ended my solo play for a recently
there's just a little oh it's just a
village basically there's not really
much here though to be honest hmm
should we like ended them for today
yeah
fine yeah just about we're trying to
find uh West thing yeah we made good
Progressive
yeah there's still so much more yeah
yeah yeah
never ending content also I might not
like stream every time that we play by
the way I'm thinking also because I woke
up so early and was like yeah yeah
that's how I felt last time if if you
were on the early turn it's recommended
to not stream yeah definitely
if you run out but it was nice to hear
your sleepy voice yeah
yeah
morning
it's a mushroom pasta
pasta something in my further isn't just
water you have to wake up it's still not
awoken that was that was fun you guys
nice yeah
very effective today efficient I mean
yeah yeah I'm gonna show my Evie again
check out the description Link in the
description and in the chat grab the new
EP it's for sale and we probably won't
restock it so go grab it
um and yeah that's all I have to say
thanks for coming today
we haven't had a date for the next
collab but it will probably be at an a
morning time again like the first time
Monday morning okay so I might not
stream that one oh okay
all good all right let's see let's
discuss after those three months if we
can find a date that works for us yeah
let's do it okay okay guys thank you for
watching thanks for watching everybody
and for supporting us we'll keep doing
our best still lots of fun things
happening
see you soon see you soon everybody
hi
friends
[Music]