[Music]
um
me
[Music]
[Applause]
it
[Music]
me
uh
[Music]
me
uh
[Music]
um
me
uh
[Music]
bye
hello
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
huh
[Laughter]
[Music]
what's up
hello everybody
everybody
wow oh whoa
[Music]
wow monster sword let's go
well well well hello
my dear friends
uh today we're playing the wind waker
once again it's been a long time
yeah a nice butter knife shut up
it's not my fault they made this so
shitty
i mean the original designers
roasted
um
but
uh
i
i know
that we are
very close
to the ending
but
i don't think we're gonna finish it
today
because i
um
[Music]
so as you remember maybe
you maybe know that i still need to read
a [\h__\h] ton of supers chats
and
i don't want to leave them on the back
burner for too long
have a backlog for too long
it's just like four to five hours left i
don't know man somebody said yesterday
that i probably have six hours left
now four to five hours okay i could
maybe do that but
um
uh
[\h__\h] hot why is so hot
i also have a problem um
it worries me a little bit
you know how i often often
have
um
problems with like breathing
and the
problems as in it's not so bad i just
sometimes you know have
something like asthma i don't know if
it's asthma because i never went like
never got it confirmed by a doctor oh
but
uh you know i get like
a tight feeling in my chest and now
today
is similar but a bit different because
i think if i try to remember back to the
last time i had that
shortness of breath
um i it just felt tight but i don't
think it felt painful
now
since i woke up today
um the very moment i woke up i i noticed
that when i
tried to breathe in deeply
uh
i sense
i feel
pain
uh
in my
in my um
testicles ha though in the
chest thingy area up to the
throat
um
so of course i
looked it up and it said something about
lung infection
and that worries me deeply
um
[Music]
i don't know
you say don't google your symptoms but
i mean
it's different from you know usually so
um sharps i don't know if it's sharp
it's
every time people try want you to
describe
what kind of pain something is
i find it very hard to
describe it
go to the doctor now
i agree i would like to go to the doctor
but we have a problem
it's the weekend
so the only doctor i could go to is a
hospital
and
that would mean i have to wait for hours
and hours and hours probably
i don't have the time for that
and
next week i am incapable of going to the
doctor
so
you know normally i would say [\h__\h] it
let's wait till monday
and then go to the doctor but yeah
i don't wanna i don't wanna exaggerate
and feel like yeah bye i'm gonna die i'm
gonna [\h__\h] die i don't wanna be like
that okay i'm gonna be dramatic and say
oh my god it's so yeah bye
uh
yeah
[Music]
see that that hurts just now i mean not
like incredibly painful
but i definitely feel a pain
there
every time i do a deep breath
yeah yeah yeah i did it again
[Music]
time for rebirth
um
yeah i'm so [\h__\h] i'm so [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
i'm so [\h__\h] [\h__\h] man
i don't know
[Music]
yeah well my first
thought was wait until tomorrow
we'll see if it's still there tomorrow
and if it's still there tomorrow i guess
i'll go to the hospital
would you would you say that if
uh pain in
my
chest consists for more than 24 hours i
should go to the hospital
but
what if what if they say
we must keep you
overnight
um because i i
i i can't i can't stay too long in the
hospital
oh man oh man
i'm worried i'm worried
but
today we shall
fight
in windbreaker
it's very friendly
it's going to feel a sign
[Laughter]
genma is sending me pianists
dead mom me too i'm so oh
i don't know i don't want to be dramatic
you know i've had like
troubles with breathing every now and
then
before many times
but i don't think it did i ever say that
i ever say it was painful
because i don't think i ever said it was
painful
it was just like ah there it stops i
can't breathe deeper than this
that's it
oh
um
[Music]
did i
yeah i'm i mentioned shortness of breath
and tightness but not pain you know i
think so
well
i just want you to know
that that's what's going on maybe i'll
go to the hospital tomorrow and then
[\h__\h] up everything
[Music]
wow
so anyway i don't think
see i don't want to leave the game at a
like chutohampa state
um
like
with only one hour gameplay left
so you guys are gonna have to help me
uh
[Music]
as
what's the word
assess the situation
did anyone here ever have a lung
infection before
um
is such a thing something you can
wait to go to the doctor for maybe like
for like two weeks or so
or is that something where you have to
go
immediately
several times
what how do you get that several times
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay well let's play em
let's play this game
[Music]
it's okay
at me
okay i'm okay i'm okay i'm not i'm not
stressed out i'm not stressed out
okay um
what were we doing last time
uh
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] hell
[Music]
can man stop shooting at me for once
i'm suffering here okay have some
sympathy empathy something anything
really
[Music]
oh you know that okay okay okay it's not
like i'm looking at the google results
and i'm like this is it this is exactly
what i have but i feel like googling
your symptoms itself to get a rough idea
if that is something that i can
completely ignore or maybe should go to
the doctor about i don't think that's
too far off okay
i also think everybody everybody does it
uh can you guys know uh remember what i
did last time
cause i don't
um
we
went in here what was that was that um
[Music]
where are we how do we play with the wii
u again
uh
i just beat the wind dungeon
beat the wind temple awesome now you
have to find the triforce shards
and those are
everywhere
let me look at that wasn't there a map
for them
incredible chart or tingles chart or
beatles chart
incredible chart
oh yeah i think that's the incredible
chart
okay
right the incredible
are you okay are you killing you're
shaking you nervous me too
incredible charge so for example
if i if i found one that's on the
incredible chart will it disappear from
the incredible chart because because for
example on the top right of the map
there's a triforce sign
how do i know if i got it already
is there a way of knowing
oh and there's ah
hey there's one in a ghost ship
i have to fight the [\h__\h] ghost trip
oh no
oh all right
take the try to tingle it stays
it will be crossed out
they mark it for you
oh okay
um well
then i guess because somewhat close
let's go that way
i think you need to get tangled to
translate your first child
and i will show you where all the pieces
are
i mean how many are there
i see some i see like
three triforce
he says uh how do we do this again oh
yeah
[Music]
uh yeah tingle yes i think i have there
are eight one two three four five six
seven eight okay i know i do see on the
bottom of the map uh one is ticked off
so okay okay
okay i'll kill okay i'm not a photo
that's
[Music]
yeah yeah german german german
welcome to
german channel chihuahua which will
probably
be
not used until after my birthday or like
or until july
first
first week of july maybe
um
so supposedly there's a triangle over
there i think triangle try try force uh
i should be capable of getting
everything now
right oh yeah what was this again
what's this island
oh
okay shall we try to take this dude down
because he's gonna be annoying me
i don't know how to fight these people
properly though
all right i can do it i can do it i can
do it fire
no miss
oh i'll come here what ah i'd flew over
to me and then i swam away oh there's
another one
[Music]
and you're
[\h__\h] what next [\h__\h]
well his aim is not very good generally
oh [\h__\h] mine is not good even now can
you stop moving
nice okay
uh
oh yeah come to me baby thank you one
anyway so here should be
a triforce
i feel like we were here before
definitely
look shot on the tree at the top okay
thank you
um if it's really
like if we can really manage to clear
the game in four hours then sure i guess
we'll clear it but if it's gonna take
longer than that then no
oh thank you
no nobody got time for that uh on it
coke shot they say
look
i just showed up
hey
now i thought you trolled me
hi
oops
where's the triforce
ah
i'm impatient
oh hello oh my god
let's see if i remember how to play this
game huh
oh my god blue chew jelly the first time
we got it
wow
[Music]
can i go into that window it looks too
2d to be able to go in there
well i guess we'll go here
i hope the other tri-forces won't be too
difficult to
to get
hey
ah it's just that is a hole
what is up there is that how oh
can i get up there too where where do i
want to go
i could go up here too
huh pretty
money
uh
okay no um i also got to go into the
hole
yay
hold time
[Music]
at least today the whole starting of the
game was smooth
no audio issues or capturing issues
you go in there don't run away from the
whole link
no you want it
open up what is this this is like a
temple
please tell me it's a short temple
oh many doors
when this one is open maybe
oh i found the ghost ships right there
ah
hello oh how do i find this again how do
i even fight
[Laughter]
ah how do i use my shield [\h__\h]
ah
[Music]
just fruit voice it
oh yeah oh yeah i always tried to kill
them with the hammer but then we
realized i don't have to do it with the
hammer right i'll [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay one down
well not bad not bad
we're warming up still
ah
you
[Music]
let's go let's know let's go let's go
that bits are dead
[Music]
so does every room have like like a
challenge like this
okay
nice nice weapon
nice with this you make a really fine
schnitzel no honestly this would be too
brutal
nice weapon
too brutal your schnitzel would turn
into schnitzel
please laugh for me even if you don't
understand german
please laugh for me
tenderizer
thank you
oh no
i don't know how to fight them
you just run after them like i said
come on calm down not come up come down
[Music]
i'm on fire i but they're dead
i killed him
no no no no he's still around
okay he's dead
right
nice easy peasy lemon squeezy
so today supposedly i want to tell you
stories
uh because we haven't talked much
but at the same time recently i've kind
of been missing out on writing
everything down i've written some things
down but not everything so i also forgot
a lot of things ah
surprise did you just hit your buddy
i think one of them just hit their buddy
how did the dancing go oh
so yesterday sparks
uh i got pretty far like i would say
see
the good thing is
uh
i can i can i can cheat a little bit um
like there's
there's um mastering a song so far that
you can dance it while still looking at
the reference and then there's mastering
a so a song so far
that you can dance it without looking at
the reference ever at all but even when
i say looking at the reference i just
kind of like like to have it open
for a few moves to like check
that i'm doing it correctly but most of
it i would know by heart
so anyway i could uh i could totally
like still watch the reference that's a
good thing because i'm learning all of
this in a very short amount of time and
um
being able to still rely on the
reference is very good
yeah
i think ah [\h__\h] that was the
entrance i think
you must not underestimate okay it takes
quite a while to learn you know that
kind of
detailed choreography
so far that you have like absolutely
mastered it by heart even without a
reference video it's pretty difficult
um
[Music]
oh there's bumps here uh i don't know
how okay
one is dead
[\h__\h] too late
take this
your hands and dance yeah did you see
the the video that i posted on twitter
yesterday
i like that one
what a
coincidence you've been dancing all
along
i love it it's so funny it's such a
funny german accent i think it's a
german accent could be like i don't know
a lot of different european accents like
maybe swedish even swedish act swedish
people speaking english
sounds maybe a little bit similar
to german people speaking english
hello
it seems i have done every door possible
oh oh he already saw me um okay
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
wrong button
[\h__\h] hell man
oh no you didn't
hit me
yes yes i don't see anything but i don't
need to see anything
i can fight blindly
they slice up each other
you know what even i i can feel even the
gun on fight will be easier than this
these ganon fights are known to be
kind of a joke often
i say that but then we remember back uh
our the time we had
the time of our life that we had during
a skyward sword final boss yeah
but that was mostly because of you know
being tired i guess and
and frustrated and stressed and on the
time pressure
yeah right
[Music]
but i would say it was still one of the
more difficult ones because of the
[\h__\h]
um
what's it called this movement
motion controls yeah if it wasn't for
motion controls that would have been
really really really really easy
we're going for here
the sky would strike yeah
today
must have been really depressed when we
were playing skyward sword because i
always say said i hate emotion controls
[\h__\h] the motion controls
man he must have gotten so much hate
okay you want me to play some music here
wind music
uh
how do i do music again
what do we want to hear
when's requiem maybe
because there's a wind sun below me
i don't know all the winds gods wind
god's area oh oh no this was correct
oh
that must be
even the charge or the triforce
please try force
[Music]
oh let's go
now you only need six more oh
[Music]
where's the chart someone said there's a
chart in this
in this place
but i'm done
it seems like i'm done thanks for the
membership welcome
seven parts for a free fourth hahaha
yeah
uh that was a chart that was replaced
over oh
gamecube headshot this in in here uh-huh
ah
okay okay okay then we're done here nice
so that wasn't so bad that was pretty
fast
okay
i'm just here for gemma yeah you say
elvis is back yeah yeah yeah is that the
same elvis
i thought maybe it's a new elvis
i remember it in elvis
you know uh hyper chat currently is it
the settings doesn't show me down
i hear user badges i i had to i had them
turned off
let me turn on the images too
all right why is this [\h__\h] ship back
yeah
can we leave here now we're done here
right
it's alves
yeah flex your badges
this is what happens when you
when you step ah god damn it when you
step when you look at the chat
hell this price lies back yes yes
incredible isn't it hallelujah
the king of
king of what rock
king of
rock
was that rock music
like sometimes things are
called rock genre that i personally feel
like that's just pop music no but okay i
guess it's just
i don't know
sometimes things are rock that don't
sound so much like rock
let's get out of here
rock and roll okay
okay so next up well let me look at the
incredible chart
ah there's so many in one line of the
map why is it so uneven
there's one at the very top of the map
one at the very bottom of the map and
then there's one two three four five
things in one line
i should teleport there to tear i should
teleport tear
god
is it the win con
[Music]
[Applause]
this one
[Music]
what's wrong
gales
i wish i could write like a notes like
renamed
that would be nice if i could rename
them
[Music]
so i think it was the second from the
bottom
trying to sit straight at least
i don't know maybe here
[Music]
i don't know you're such a little [\h__\h]
man on twitter too
yesterday
there was a comment i think you said why
would we watch
a stream of you
again or so i'm like you little [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
cause it sounded so genuine you sounded
so genuine in that tweet i'm like this
little [\h__\h] i'm not even gonna give you
a like for that
see i see
i see matt all of your tweets but i just
don't like some of them because well
they don't impress me enough
yeah
uh-huh he has a point lots of facade all
right yeah but it sounded so mean
in that tweet you could just say oh i
saw that one already no thank you
yeah oh no instead you're like why why
would i why would i
you
oh you know what let's
pay him back and just say tsunamu to him
now
that's your new name
ah okay
um
oh [\h__\h] so i think shut up
shut up
hey
wait is one when are we even here now
all right we're going um
i guess there's over there
there's a map i think
i am here okay
lol in reality in reality they're crying
i hear it i hear the cries like oh no
oh no
oh
she completely destroyed me
[Laughter]
[Music]
uh
looking for a map
what is the map just in the middle of
the ocean all wet
i'm sorry i don't wanna you me you may
bully me but i feel bad when i bully you
guys so i apologize deeply
[Music]
no it would wouldn't it be a beam of
light if it was something important
but it could be
i don't know i'll check i guess
hi
maybe it is maybe it is something nice
huh
um
[Music]
[\h__\h] it wasn't anything nice
uh wow where is the man
let's look around is it on is it on land
or is it is it over there baby
is that still on this map here
okay it should be here
lots of birds
oh
okay
[Music]
okay i don't think i can go for that
door but um
[Music]
i can
no wait doesn't work
no
what
that works
need the seagull oh get tingles pear for
this
i have i have oh yeah wait now remember
you can fly with them or or so
right what's the goal though i don't
want to waste too many
uh i only have two
is that enough
for what we're doing
uh kill the birds first oh okay
good idea can i do it from here
what a question
i'm talking about
all right all right mate
[\h__\h] oops that was accented
that one is even a bit more further away
i don't know do we go higher or lower
let's just test it out
okay
huh
[\h__\h]
that's so close
it's drifting
oh you ah there you go
wait you meant these birds not those
birds right kill kill these bones right
well you're too high
good morning sunshine whoa and this
one's fine that one is tough
um
whoa
[\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h]
amazing
i didn't think i would get that one so
easily
what
hmm
amazing so now um i just want to be
prepared do i fly to the very top with
the bird or what
or do i what's the what's the goal here
you know
the very time
prepare
and prepare
uh
hits the switches on top of every rock
hit the five diamonds on top of those
rocks okay
i feel like
yeah is it motion control or
no right
[\h__\h] ah go up go up go [\h__\h] how long
does this work
ah
[\h__\h]
it's inverted it's no reset i don't know
it's not no it's kind of inverted
what the [\h__\h]
i'm holding the
[\h__\h] i can't okay chill chill you can do
it
you can do it until i get hit okay
that's good oh there's still a bird left
here
oh
what is that
[Music]
okay
where did that one come from
huh
i wasn't there before i was i was going
back to the nest
[\h__\h]
no
i can't reach it
let's go
i need to kill okay i think i can reach
from here
[Music]
too high obviously
oh
wow get in the boat to shoot excuse me
you know who you're talking to here
do you know who you're talking to
[Music]
all right
now we just need to get better at flying
okay
what
nunny
come on you have to bump into it
this is nice though i'm a bird
valor sense for flying
yes
ah i'll just start with the higher ones
uh
i'm like
what do you
[Music]
what are we doing
ah okay
what about the others though
huh
that one before i certainly bumped into
that one
okay all right
have to do it more aggressively i get it
[Music]
at least it doesn't have to be a certain
order
ain't no stone gonna stop me
yeah
i'm bad
i love this can you like go really far
like really off the map here i wonder
or will they stop you eventually
imagine just flying across the whole map
of the bird
[Music]
yeah i did it i think
one two
three four
and i did i did them all there's no sign
of anything happening i know one left
there's a range unfortunately oh no
arranged it will disconnect you oh
that's sad
okay
ah
[Music]
are you good bird i'll just leave you
there
you can figure it out yourself right
okay so i think we're gonna get a map
here and since outside was already quite
the challenge i'm hoping we get it right
away
yes
money
oh yeah
oh
red roo b rupee rupee
play window yeah yeah wait i'm first so
i'm gonna
get all the money
uh
i had this weird dream tonight
about uh like staying in the hotel room
and then they were [\h__\h]
idiots so i wanted to speak to the
manager you know but they deserved it
and then some i had my cats with me and
my cats
this movie ran away
outside the hotel so i had to chase her
and no
it was a weird
weird dream no the thing is that
there was more to that you know the
hotel room like i i came to my hotel
room in the evening
and then i wanted to staff to i wanted
the staff to close the the curtain
rolos thingy the automatic ones and she
just
for five hours she kept me awake
not doing that little thing i asked her
to do kept me awake stayed in my room
and like i don't know wasted my time so
i was still awake when the when the sun
came up so i was like [\h__\h]
what are you doing do your job
unbelievable
so anyway
uh we're doing wind guard again
no wait are we doing one's recreation
right now you're
your flower crown is so pretty thank you
very much
i like it too
oh yeah let me tell you about this
outfit
maybe
um
so i
i started
uh working on this quite a few months
ago
and um
i gave hooker papa like photos
references of
the endless
uh and different colors and all that and
i was like you know what the color i'm
gonna kind of leave to you whatever you
think is best so i like the color he
chose it's kind of my my secondary color
naisu
yeah
and
but the other things like you know i i
also gave him some reference of
references of what the
what the blouse normally looks like
underneath
and
um what the
what the the aprons look like and so on
now he did keep the apron relatively
simple like as in no
no particular um what's the word
uh
what's the word
lace and stuff around it
but i think all the knowledge
it harmonizes pretty well
um
and um
yeah the ribbon while the ribbon is uh
unfortunate
but
no i guess you know when i stream like
this most of the time you don't see the
ribbon anyway
so that's okay
that's okay
um
[Music]
we're gonna go straight ahead now
we're going this way
yeah
and um oh yeah uh then i gave him a lot
of uh suggestions with the hairstyle
with the hairstyle i was really
so
so exact like for the clothes
not so much as for the hairstyle like he
would send me a draft
and i would normally i don't like doing
this but i wanted this to be um i wanted
the hair to be perfect
so i
would like draw on top of the draft
to because no it's actually like
[\h__\h] hell not so much that i wanted
to do that but it was just easier to
explain like the staff asked me if i
could
you know give
an image as an example
and to get it exact i just drew a little
bit on top of it
um
yeah i wanted these braids and updo i
was also thinking a little bit about
shorter hair because i know you guys
want me to just want to see me in
shorter hair too
but oh here
yeah
the thing is
uh it's just updates are pretty common
for daniels like braids and all that
so i thought now's the chance for that
we can do short hair another time one
day
yeah
it's here
is it really here that island is isn't
that
[Music]
what it
what was that again something about this
island was like i can't do it now
what is this again
don't touch me
this cabana belongs to the monster
monster alone you grimly you you grab me
trespassing little scoundrel away with
you and i i think i had to put something
on here
money
um
no
ah
gotta trade joy penance
the teacher in windfall
you need to get the dead from the main
island he'll go back to windfall to get
the deed the deed or the dead
it's deed from the lady wind phone 20
joy pendants
i have 22. okay okay
windfall
windfall windfall wait i have to be on
the boat right
to teleport
okay i'll go go go go go go we'll do
that
and yeah so very exact for the hairstyle
and the flowers like i gave pretty exact
um
instructions which i think he needed
because you know
obviously he wouldn't know
what exactly
a dandel
has to look like and i wanted it to be
more accurately
drawn
because i am from austria
so i feel like it would be
just weird if
since i am from that country if i made
it look like something it's not
um
needed to be perfect yeah cause i mean
it's my 1 million subscribers
um
present
so
i think
i i am allowed to
say everything exactly the way i want
now uh
i think i really i really like the hair
with everything on it i really like it a
lot um
because i gave so many like even the
strands that the banks originally the
banks were like for example
at some point they were like fully
um
had to stay filled up like no
no empty strands in between you know
what i mean
so i i went in with a
with an eraser and made these really
fine
strands
in between the bangs
to give it more of a natural not so
filled up feeling i don't know how to
explain it yeah it was one big chunk
so i would like
uh make some really thin
thin empty
strands in between yeah
um
yes
[Laughter]
very very exact and then you see you see
that the the few
highlighted
lines on top of my bangs that go across
even that
was a tiny detail that i drew exactly
like that on top of it
so whenever i draw something
as a reference hukapapa usually
recreates it very accurately
um
yes yes
[Music]
actually whoop
first official eu veto
the way you form that sentence doesn't
seem very accurate
and for the jacket i know a lot of you
guys preferred without the jacket but i
just felt like it would be a nice uh
accessory that with the jacket it makes
it look um
like it can be used for a bit more of a
serious serious
serious
occasion
uh gales
like even for whole talk perhaps even
i feel like maybe with the blazer i
could wear it for whole talk maybe
maybe maybe maybe maybe i'm not sure yet
i'm not sure
oh yeah it looks a bit more formal i
would say um
because they uh
for dandel uh
sometimes
for like if you want to wear it in a
little bit more formal way you would
wear this kind of like
what's it called like a
not the not the smooth leather but the
one that's a little bit like rough
uh
what's it called suede
i made everyone think it wasn't at the
end
suede ah i actually got it right
yaya
[Music]
outfits between the daniel and the
empress one huh
[Music]
thank you i'm glad you liked them
dan
which lady
are we going for this one
probably not
my skin loves you
school teacher school school teacher
that's nice being back here
[Music]
well what do you think about my outfit
you don't see clothes like this often do
you aren't they so cute i could say the
same thing about my doodle you guys
don't see this very often do you isn't
it so cute
a friend of mine who lives on outside
island sent this outfit to me she's an
amazing girl she can put jars on her
head and walk around like it's nothing
at all you have to see it to believe it
the one inside the house near her oh it
wasn't her
inside the house near ah
wait she wasn't the teacher oh
ah you look like someone who would want
to join pendants
oh welcome to mrs murray school of joy
i don't think i've ever seen your face
around here before my young scholar are
you a new pupil
do i just show it to her
look at this
we need to talk
i know i might look a bit flashy for a
teacher but i assure you i am one
how long has it been since i opened my
school here on windfall island oh
20 years
so yes i totally started it when i was
just born because i'm no older than dad
20 years
ever since then i have been teaching the
children of this island about the true
joy
but you have a rather joyless problem
there's this delinquent gangle for young
boys who never listen to a word i say
even though i wait patiently for those
boys to show up they never come it's as
if they don't want to join their hearts
could you please catch your leader that
little boy named ivan and talk some
sense into him for me
please young man for me
young man
young man oh thank you so much you're
such a dare there's such trouble some
little boys i'm at my wit's end over how
to handle them
they won't be so mean to a boy their own
age will they i should think not
okay
i like your hair
looks like you're
kode
[Music]
this is a pretty cure main character
40 years later
this is how they age this is what they
never show you
they want you to think
that they're all so young but no no they
get old at some point
how do i catch this little bastard
[Applause]
oh my you got a problem with us killing
people
don't tell me it's that annoying hang of
a teacher again is it
you came here to give us talking too
because mrs mary asked you to write tell
us not to skip school right but tell us
not to be tardy right bud
[Laughter]
it's it's so sad when you say it like
that
where the rest man
where are the others
[Music]
i love the songs so much
um
i love them so much
they're so they're so fun
what was that what was that old one
again
um
what's that really old one
[Music]
no no no no what was that old one
no no no
no not that old
was it already uh no not the one with
the two girls it was i think it was four
already in like the freddy ending
you make me happy
[Music]
that i will tell you
something special
i was very young when i saw that ending
for the first time
and
that was
that ending
was the first time
that i learned one of those you know
anime whatever dances
the first time
i tried learning that ending dance
yeah
it was the very first time
[Music]
very very nostalgic
the first choreo i learned yeah you
might say so besides
besides stuff like that
are great yeah i love them because like
after i think i think after that one
after the fresh pretty killer
they did that for like every single
ending of their animes
they had they always had these 3d
endings
with the girls dancing to the really
upbeat nice songs and i loved them so
much i loved learning them um
yeah in a different dimension i was
a particular and my name was
uh
cure orange
yes
ah okay no actually i was cure orange
phoenix or no no i was cure
i don't know why i can't remember i seem
to be mixing up things i was indeed cure
orange
orange fire no not orange chicken orange
soda i love that uh wasn't that like a
k-pop group why am i going crazy now
it was this orange something
k-pop group
was like made up of other or
made up of other members like of another
group orange caramel that was the one
yeah
orange caramel
duh
[Music]
oh my god okay okay okay okay okay
too much we're going too deep again
we're going to deep
uh
to nostalgic yeah catalina yes
yes
good times
sub unit of after school yeah yeah yeah
yeah
oh the kfp k-pop tangent
it just goes on and on and on and on
[Music]
i never asked you if the volume is okay
i'm raising rising raising it right now
[Music]
i love you forever if you saying
catalina you know i remember the title
but i forgot the melody
[Music]
ah that song
they had some really funky clothes on
[Music]
oh
they're fish
and fish
at the supermarket
[Music]
i love them they had like the cutest the
cutest outfits ever
the cutest the cutest [\h__\h] outfits
ever and the cutest makeup
so cute
is the game louder yeah it turned the
game louder
should it be quieter
anyway so when where were we
ah yeah i want to wear outfits like that
ah og k bob you're so old man
it gives me recommendations of girls day
i loved girls day
eight years
ago so old
now i i don't mean talking about prick
here i meant about the game
where the mighty an invincible gang of
the four killer bees do you think we'd
listen to a jump like you but i'll tell
you what but if you want to challenge us
to a competition and we'll think about
maybe listening a little bit
what do you say bud you want to
challenge
what kind of challenge is it
frankie versus salmon
oh i actually watched prickier
more than sailor moon
but prickier
even that i didn't watch that much i
mostly um
i watched uh
heart challenger
[Music]
heart
heart pranking
heart jump heart challenge
hot cats
hard catch yeah i'm playing on the wii u
yes heart gets really pretty killer
and then after that not so much i just
followed all the all the music that they
released mostly and i always looked up
the designs and was like oh that's so
[\h__\h] cute i love it
anyway i took you on whatever it is
whatever it is
we're so simple
i gonna hide somewhere oh easy
try to catch us we won't hide indoors so
we won't leave this island okay
okay oh well it feels like i already did
that at some point
most dramatic one
where'd you go
probably here
yeah
this is what i'm gonna do with you buddy
when i find you
smash you
into little bits and pieces
how do i catch them anyway
just bump against them
he's not here my body would be here
maybe
oh my god
not already little [\h__\h]
don't run
and now of course the camera makes me
wait like a full four [\h__\h] million
years
i'm gonna kill you don't worry
i don't have time
i don't
oh
[Music]
triggering me so hard
okay i got you
little [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h]
first it surprises me like that of
course it did
and then and then
the others getting in the way
unbelievable
um
yep where could they be
don't be scared of my bright ass sword
don't be scared
i see how it is
a little [\h__\h]
you're too young to jump off that cliff
but he did it anyway
your little [\h__\h]
you little [\h__\h]
got him
all righty alrighty
uh
maybe
down here
well i would be too close i think
because
the other one but maybe i don't know
around the corner no
up the tree which one that one
how do i can i even climb those
or maybe
from above the house go on top of the
house
i'm so stupid i'm so stupid every time
man
i just can't
i always need to fail before i can
succeed that's just life
that sounds so philosophic
yeah yeah
what else was there about the outfit
that i wanted to tell you guys
[Music]
i don't know i feel like
most of it i told you was just very very
very exact the birds however
were
ah
something that hooked papa
decided on
to add and this time we even have two
birds instead of
one
they're getting more and more and more
and more
which i'm not complaining about
maybe next time i'll have free
on my head
here we go
i think i have two left
two
i see can
[Music]
the darkness has overcome link
welcome to the dark side
[Music]
that must have been a headshot
wait how do i ah
yes
the younglings why not what about the
younglings
this is what happens if you don't go to
school
[\h__\h]
[Music]
shut up
i don't have mercy for you you're not a
youngling
yeah
got you oh that was it oh i found one
more i know there were four not five
[Music]
no more killer bees
uh-huh what am i what am i getting oh
piece of heart
not bad
no it's ben ninja do you apologize to
mrs mary for us all right
how about you just go to school
i think that would be enough of an
apology for her
is that them
cute the self portraits
very cute little girls the girls are
probably in school ah
they look cute
adorable
awesome i need to talk
i did it yeah
i watched it all from the shadow of my
door you really are there you fill me
with joy i have to reward you so here's
a little spare change
uh-huh
what's next
[Music]
oh when it comes to children my eyes
never deceive me someday dear you will
grow up to be a fine young man and your
name will go down in history
how the [\h__\h] do you know
wait what about the
talk to the children
oh
yes i did it's her birthday soon oh
yes how about 20 joy pendants because
one wouldn't be enough i think one would
be a good present but i guess she wants
20.
24 a birthday present
yeah yeah i have them already
um sparkling 9000
i already have enough don't need to tell
me where they are
so wait did you just give it to her
[Music]
no wait i think they actually want me to
get that one specifically
oh my rain where do you find them are
they just laying on if we could just
[Music]
now that i think about it when i saw
when that when i was climbing trees that
i saw some sparkly night up on top of
some tree in town
i can just give it to okay okay okay
what do they mean with the sparkly light
did i already get that
so uh happy birthday
my dear that's a joy pendant
to tell you the truth i love julie above
all else and that my dad is extremely
rare and hard to come by
it's the hardest thing around here
oh my gosh i will happily take a single
one from you no no i insist only one to
tell you the truth i'd actually like
about 20 of them
but that would probably only happen in
my wildest of dreams
oh look it suits her so well
that tacky huge ass pendant
oh man
you know i've been a teacher here for a
long time it's tough to put one past me
that being said i'm pretty sure i know
who put you up to the stair
it was my chat
those little sweeties hi there she calls
you sweeties i'm so joyful it's the best
birthday present i could ask for
i suppose i ought to thank you close
your eyes dear
[Music]
and now you shall give me more
oh wait
what's volunteering
although i might be school teacher i
have a certain fly about me don't you
think and let me tell you i love jeremy
more than anything else in the world huh
oh
why not it's not like i can't afford it
why i have so much cash i can even
afford my own oasis cabana
but i happen to be after a very
particular kind of jewelry
you see lately i've been ravi taken with
collecting joy pendants those are very
rare trinkets that you can't buy at any
store they're quite amazing why their
color and their shape i feel as if i was
destined to cover them
it's okay
i have more
take them
and give me your cabana instead kabana
21 yeah yeah i finally only needed 20.
eh
[Music]
yeah okay she'll take precisely 20.
but then in total you need a 21 no
because you gave we gave her one first
and now she takes 20.
so in total she needs like 21.
[Music]
ah the cabana deed it's written on
yellow parchment wait so she gave me her
cabana
[Music]
you see although i'm about a mere
teacher i owe my very own cabana i know
you can have it
it's all right dear you can stop gaming
in the basement now now that you have
this deed the cabana is all yours you
own it so whatever you do don't lose
this piece of paper
i'm getting all uh getting on an agent
seat travel it hasn't exactly agreed
with me i'm so late no i can just stay
here and relax as i continue my work
with the children
and just so you know you'll find the
place southeast of here it's on a tiny
lonely little isle near the triangle
islands
from now on it is your own little
bachelor pet good luck finding it i
already found it long time ago
amazing
i want
i want an island like that
or just a house on an island doesn't
have to be the whole island
[Music]
how much does an island cost
just kidding no i just want the house
how much is a house on an island
don't we all
one million oh [\h__\h] hellman
all right finally
um
here we go
[Music]
off yeah
sad
can't get to 1 million today huh
i guess
i guess i'll get there tomorrow
uh
unfortunate
because i'll have to wait with my
purchase
is it
this thing always there
looks so scary
i like sad
in that place
[Laughter]
[Music]
i wish i wish getting an island was as
lazy as getting you know stars because
you can't buy stars right
and named them
unfortunately getting an island is not
that easy
very sad
thanks to inflation it's gonna be 1.5
million tomorrow ah no problem
no problem
am i right
is there someone there got it
wait where was it
i know it was one above
one above i'm in the wrong
wrong
line i think
almost like that one
i think
[Music]
two million subscribers my word yeah you
know what if i if i ever get two million
subscribers i think um
i might want to ask for an outfit again
but maybe like for a 3d outfit because
like you know when i was like
asked like what do you want
i wasn't quite sure like what is
possible
[Music]
uh
but now i have a few more like a bit
more of an idea of what what is in the
range of possibility
yeah yeah so i think cause normally
getting a 3d outfit
just like randomly
not
[Music]
not really something you just decide to
get randomly yep
uh
but maybe maybe for 2 million
subscribers one day
one day this is my place now look at
that holy [\h__\h] this is so nice
this whole thing the belgian waffles
on top of this little
pond in the waterfall oh look at that i
can reach that chest after going through
a cabana whatever i never noticed that
but could i have not reached that
that
before by hanging onto the tree
oh
hey
so what do i get from getting the cabana
if i was always able to get up here
anyway
[Music]
there's a chat for
four
for the triforce
charge right yep
right
go in and find out
is this my butler
poor butler he's a door
i own this place now
i have to show it to you huh
um
how
what
that's
why that star are you are you the new
master are you my [\h__\h] wow oh i'm so
pleased to hear that name because all
butlers are british obviously monster
queen well please be gentle at this
point
um i would i i i had no plans yet with
this door but now i must think about
what to do with this door
door
you sure let me in
let me touch
that's your hand
your door handle
oh
he has a door butt
nice
butler in the maid
my camera don't do this to me look at
him
[Music]
oh here he has proper clothes why does
he just wear made out of been in that
one
oh i see okay
i just wanted to test out the flyer if
it was real
how do i get those up there
[Music]
wow
oh [\h__\h]
it's disappearing though let me go let
me let me how do i
[Music]
ah come down money all right i don't
need that much anyway
i don't need that much
i was like oh it's already completed but
no okay okay okay i guess we'll have to
do this puzzle
even interesting amusements of nobility
oh very much so
i don't need your explanation i think
wait what are the knobs though
[Music]
uh what are in the uh there's my lives
not the amount of moves i can do
oh no it doesn't seem to change
all right hmm
[Music]
this will be a pain in the ass
i have to do this right
i'm gonna
absolutely nail this
cute already have his cute face
pretty cute
[Music]
dun dun dun
i hate these kind of puzzles it's
optional
[Music]
so all i
get in this island is a treasure chest
that i could have always gotten before
and there was no need for me to do that
side quest
there was no need for me to do the side
quest
is that what you're saying
i'm i'm i'm going to do this i started
it
put out the fire okay
no i am going to do this though
whether you want it or not
[Music]
dedication
so close
look at it his huge ass face he's like
he's photo bombing
[Music]
i hate slider puzzles
uh if i wish i could move the whole
thing
upwards
there's no
i'm meeting inhabited having it finished
so early already though if i stop does
it like stay where it currently is
like can i look at the other picture
[Music]
the the finished one can i look at it
again
what yes does it go back or does it stay
[Music]
we've got all the different wrongs i'm
just trying to
put something together first and then
move it all together
[Music]
it stays
what are the knobs
[Music]
i've become faithfully aware of my
existence as a door
yes you are a door
aha
ah
let's continue no no we're not quitting
i just wanted to check
oh [\h__\h] no don't tell me
[Music]
let's go
i don't know
wait
[Music]
so i think that one indeed should be up
there
right the top left would be correct now
[\h__\h]
[Music]
ah
yes
oh
i can do it
i believe
[Music]
which one is on the very
right ah nothing red because the top the
top right stays empty right wasn't that
it
okay
the top last since i think that had the
end yeah well damn it
[\h__\h] right no no no no
i'll figure it out
[Music]
um
lucio
ah i don't wanna like rip everything
apart again
you actually are smart have faith in
your brain wow thank you that's
something carefree never says to me
so sweet
where was i
[Music]
well
whatever is in the
second row
right
the empty one right now
would be nice to have it close by but i
don't know what that what would be there
right now um
oh [\h__\h]
i just i'll just
randomly
do it eventually
we'll get it right
right
that's how it works right
um
[Music]
and that would be there
yeah yeah yeah i mean it's taking shape
but
uh i want to dub triforce
no brute forcing it
would have looked up the solution i mean
the solution is obviously on the other
side of the room but how to get there
this nail
okay so that since that goes there we'll
just keep it up there that's a good spot
for it to be at
have to bring that down
yellow jumpsuit
[Music]
and then yeah okay okay oh oh
the bottom left ones look correct to me
[Music]
oh my god
i'm doing it
i'm actually doing it
yeah
uh-huh that goes
did i bring it there
[Music]
finally
maybe like that
no
no it has to be
has to be
inverted
this will take a while
take a seat
everybody take a seat
i'll just do a i don't know
[Music]
something
yeah get a snack um i have a snack here
by the way i have some
some fruit that i will maybe eventually
eat how long has it been now one hour 42
minutes
i don't know uh brain horde
brain horde
[Music]
now we have to get those over there
anyway
[Music]
oh damn wow
oh look it's getting so close
oh
skye
yet so far
[Music]
bring that one in
leave that there if possible
[Music]
oh my god what's happening kfb what's
happening
but how do i get that
[Music]
i'm so close
yay you didn't believe in me it didn't
take that much time but
it's still like i want to
[Music]
i know i like
i get that there
[Music]
everything will align the way i want it
to be eventually on its own isn't it
just stop let's just ignore the left
side let's try to not move the left side
anymore at all is that possible
can we solve it
[Music]
oh
i think
[Music]
that's how i want it
no no yes yes
yes yes yes yes yes yes
yes
[Music]
i am
incredible
one light turned on are there more
pictures
[Music]
to solve like 20
wait there's more
[Music]
use it wisely
ah
it's not even that much
oh my god i'm so impressed by myself
what are these lights though
are there 16
one two three four
four five six seven eight are there 16
riddles like this
leave them come back oh no oh hell no
anyway
[Music]
uh what
what can i not use then
um
hey i want to use the leaf
to blow it out
isn't that what i'm supposed to do
what can i use
stomp it now no
i need water
look at the ceiling bro oh
ah
[Music]
that looks familiar
get down
oh
if i let go
does it immediately turn on no okay
wow
[Music]
i left okay
what is this
leave get out of here can i enter the
weather
yeah
okay it looks very disgusting but this
is not
this is not what
the underground of this island looks
like i don't believe it
it's a [\h__\h] dungeon
unrealistic mate very under unrealistic
underground system
i don't buy it
[Music]
baby
yes baby
left
no i don't know what am i looking for
here
huh
i'm scared
wait i hear a shiny sound on the other
side though
there's even more money down here what
incredible
how did she make so much money as a
teacher but that's the most unrealistic
thing about this game
she's a teacher
unfortunately teachers don't make much
money
as far as i know
i can't go right
oh i'll go i go strong
i go straight lit strong
what's with the controls man
she became a teacher when she was rich
that seems like a odd choice of job
after becoming rich
why would you torture yourself like that
i'm sorry but
teaching is a tough job
especially like such young kids
we're all little shits
[Music]
those relaxed kids
but then she could just get some of her
own seems like she doesn't have any kid
not wait that one
snotty child is her child
or this is just one of her students
i wonder is that her child
teach her a day fever at night
thanks for the membership welcome
i feel like i missed something
strange
about here
[Music]
ice
no that's where it came from
all right let's go i guess that is only
there's only money down here let's go up
and see
what we're actually dealing with
oh wait don't maybe you want to go
outside like uh
we'll get out on that side of the
underground
[Music]
the other ladder what
more leather
there's only one ladder here
okay i'm going in again
put down sard
b for android
by the way we need to play minecraft
again sometime because i saw
um our server was updated to 1.19 or so
or 2. i don't know what that is but
there's frogs
frogs guys
yo
build id portal
i was told like when the
uh when they're in doing that and i
think i'm not gonna be around for it
so
i don't think i can help with that ah
why am i here
you mean walk around huh
[Music]
i land in a circle
fight against wardens oh yeah i saw a
little bit of piccolo's stream
where she found the warden ah this way
she found a warden
freaked out about them they're really
[\h__\h] strong stronger than
the if i understood correctly
stronger than like the
uh end
dragon
and the whipper
right or or some
something
[Music]
which is terrifying
and
if i understood correctly like they slow
you down when you close by
yeah they do a lot of damage like pick
what i was wearing all that uh i already
forgot what everything was cold in my
breath but she was wearing that
and never elmore
and he still did half of
her health
damage where the [\h__\h] oh this is
confusing
but i opened this door
home
this is where i came from
[Music]
oh
no
all right
i never write never write it
i mean never right
put it away
they're right armor what did i say never
armor let me never write
are you supposed to be so dangerous that
you try to avoid them rather than fight
what do you get what do you get if you
kill
one of those
is it
like once you kill one you can still
encounter more right
nothing
no way
and then then there's really the only
reason to fight them for
purely for i don't know it's streaming
entertainment
regrets
[Music]
what is this hole you can't get back up
if you fall into that one
it seems
but it also seems like i have to fall in
here
bragging rights y'all
were fit
could do it with a group at least so i
don't suffer too much
but at least from the wither you get
something
and from the ender dragon when it did
not give you anything what what did they
create it for
we don't get anything out of it
that's just decoration then scary
decoration
[Music]
stop hugging me
every please
does this work i feel like yeah i tested
it out before of course it doesn't work
the sponges and the bills to make a
price marine
[Music]
[Applause]
ah
[Music]
terrifying
absolutely terrible ah
here's a hole
a coffee or your free hugs yeah people
in anime conventions be like you want a
free hug yay oh my god oh you're also
wearing a free hug shirt yeah
that's exactly that stream
scream
i was never one of those people who had
free hugs
signs
but i would sometimes
give them free hugs
sometimes when i was younger now i'm
like
i avoid these people at all cost
don't even think about it
don't even think about hugging me your
free hug
we don't need a hug charity
not an anime convention where everybody
is so [\h__\h] touchy anyway
get out of here
most of them also wear cat ears have you
noticed
glomp
all right uh is it the winds wick
requiem
[Music]
it's always the same kind of people who
do that hug thing
sweeps
just want to take pictures and shop
please don't touch me yeah yeah
oh my god
triple shot five more
[Music]
wasn't so bad in here it's just very
like design wise very depressing
not interesting to look at
unfortunately
ah this is much nicer
the money is back
it always comes back
eyes empty this time
wait a
it's my minute sister
[Music]
oh
little sis puzzle
give me some of those
unbelievable
[Music]
okay oh look at her
well i can you know i don't want to
solve anything
anymore because this is the best
possible picture to have hanging here in
my home
yeah
yeah i'm happy with that
[Music]
let's go
dry bath
[Music]
i had boomerang i forgot
okay
i still wonder
yep what are those things for
decorative object
[Music]
i remember something
about them
but not anymore
oh god
flowers
[Music]
all right
time for more traffic shots this is
pretty tedious isn't it
[Music]
yep
yeah it used to be worse i know
i guess they improved it
where are we going next let's look at my
incredible chat okay we're going
straight ahead
two
uh
thingies away
this wait that means one two three four
five does that mean something
do you guys mean something
can i fight something here
they just show me where a fairy
thingy is right
whatever
i killed that big octo already okay okay
you really know this game very well
don't you
it feels tedious because collecting them
aren't full dungeons so they are as fun
but you mean if it were full dungeons
would be more fun
i guess so maybe
what is this
that again oh this is just blowing up
because i gave that thing that thing
okay okay
now don't hit me
now don't talk to me
escape escape
escape
so next up is over there
that they couldn't make all dungeons
needed so this is why this quest is
moving
you mean they ran out of time
development time
could just delayed the game
oh
here
my map says it's here
higher ups breathing your neck yeah
[Music]
but that's not not on the same map
anymore
is it one of those things where it only
shows up at full moon or whatever
that
[Music]
was i'll just go over there maybe the
sign is not so accurate
[Music]
i can't be there
it's a triforce icon
but it's not here
the icon icon
is at a very specific
corner of the chart thingy
so i would think it's not here
this is it
it is here really then why is it so
awkwardly like you know all the other
triforce charts
the icons are like in the middle of its
um
what's the word
in the middle of its
quadrat
and then this one
is on the in the corner
of its tile yes in the corner of its
tile
as if
it's not exactly centered
so that confused me you know
[Music]
well okay
it doesn't matter we're going to lift
this
easy
[Music]
in german we say
square is quadrate
round
and the phone
one
with the same
design
what does it
okay
[Music]
actually pretty work pretty well in
numbers
they do make funny sense
[Music]
synchronized dancing very synchronized
what's in in here oh
oh you guys are easy
no match for me
[Music]
you make me laugh
and that makes me happy thank you
talking of laughing oh i'll tell you
something
now
i have a
really good recommendation that comes
originally from from my mom so you're
gonna put more weight on that aren't you
guys
when i tell you about some random ass
netflix or disney or whatever show
and i'm like oh it's so good i like it
so much you guys are probably usually
like yeah yeah yeah sure whatever
but this one comes from my mom and i
checked it out myself and it's actually
really really good it's not a netflix
show it's something on youtube
last time when my mom came by
um
uh
we were like okay well it's evening time
you want to watch something
and my mom told me right now
i'm watching this
and so she pulls up youtube she tells me
about this
first she tells me about really
excitedly she tells me about this
british
kind of a game show
with comedians
uh
says it's so funny it's called the
taskmaster
does anyone know
it has several seasons and uh full
episodes on youtube or like legally like
they they uploaded themselves
and i've been binge watching it and it's
so [\h__\h] good first of all it's really
funny
and second of all
it's kind of inspiring me too
because i feel like i could get some
ideas from these tasks that they do
basically for the people who don't know
what that show is
it's like there's a moderator who's a
british relatively old guy but he's cool
and
then there's five comedians and there's
a helper for the moderator he's cool
alex
um
when the five comedians they change over
the course of
the season like after one season they
will have a new set of comedians and
then you know
they
get some tasks to fulfill in funny ways
they come up with some
interesting ways of
talk
wait
what's happening
interesting ways of doing it
uh bending the rules and all that and
it's just really funny tasks
it's like a game show kind of
and at the end
they get a kind of a reward not really
not much of a reward but yeah
[Music]
and my mom recommended that to me we
watched one episode together and then i
was like dude this is actually good mom
i'm i'm impressed mom
yeah it's been pretty entertaining for
me recently
[Music]
i recommend it to you guys it's really
good
really good but yeah i was thinking
maybe some of these ideas ideas could be
like implemented into like vr streams oh
it disappeared
we are streams
not
definitely by far not all of them
because a lot of them need you to do
like
things that don't work in vr or with
live 2d or whatever sadly i wish i could
just do all of them
because they're so funny let me pour
some water
[Music]
i've been trying to pay attention while
i'm watching it
if like if i can use that idea
for a stream um
for example a task would be
they enter a room they they see a cake
and the task is
um
destroy this cake
in a beautiful way and then they would
do it in all kinds of different ways or
or a task would be
try to shoot this basketball through the
hoop without touching
uh
the basketball
or
uh pop these balloons
these like 20 balloons as far as as fast
as you can or
um
draw a portrait of the person behind the
curtain without looking at the at the
person
without looking behind the curtain and
just by describing having them describe
themselves with yes or no questions but
then one of them you know there's always
likes one or two who think around the
whole way the task is worded and then
one of them
he i think he was
disqualified for it for this one in
particular but uh usually they're quite
open
but
uh he would like open the curtain put a
mirror
there and then look at her like image of
that woman behind the curtain uh through
the mirror and would say well i didn't
look at the lady directly i looked at
the mirror and it turns out his portrait
was the shittiest of them all anyway
even though he got to look at the lady
so
it's pretty funny
it's pretty [\h__\h] funny
yeah they like to stretch the rooms and
that's that's also what makes it funny
yeah and the comedians have really um
nice individual personalities
yeah
there's like usually there's some
younger comedians and then there's some
older comedians who
are kind of like
like
you you can sense they're they're
too old for this [\h__\h] so they make up
their own rules
i uh hide this pineapple
on yourself yeah yeah that was a task
they were like you have sewn so many
minutes you have to hide this pineapple
on your body
uh and then later the the assistant will
guess where you hid it so they would
like slice it up or like puree it put it
in a smoothie mixer thingy and try to
drink as much as possible some others
would just cut it up and then put it in
in their pants and in their shoes and
and everywhere
yeah and and then there was one stupid
task that was funny uh they
brought in they like to bring in the
swedish guy a swedish person and use him
for tasks so one was um
try to make this swedish person blush
you have 30 minutes or so
and then most of them
would try to like flirt with the swedish
guy
and get really close and lick his face
or whatever but then
they all failed they could not make his
face go red they couldn't make him blush
because they they literally measured it
by seeing how red his face got and then
there was one one comedian who was
really smart you have to think around
the task and she just told the swedish
guy to um
uh
what's the red word bend over
first of all that sounds
very edgy again very sus but she just
made him bend over for like um two
minutes or so and then he would lift his
head and it was completely red because
all the blood shot up in his head and of
course she won the task so
i was [\h__\h] smart
yeah
i wouldn't have gotten that idea
i don't know how i would have made made
them um blush and then there was a funny
task it was like uh you have like i
don't know
30 minutes try to sweat as much as
possible and then
basically almost no one got any sweat
out of their bodies but they did some
funny things in order to try to sweat
that's really funny
really funny but i keep on thinking
about like how could i
implement this into a stream
because this needs me to use my body or
like show someone's face or whatever
it's like it's bigger bigger than a
stream like i would have to
film a whole video
i don't know
most of them don't work what's the name
of the show task master look it up look
up taskmaster season one and then go
from there
there's clips too but you should watch
the full episodes uh i hear the sound
crackling to them
okay
try to trick someone to say us oh yeah
yeah stuff like that
but yeah yeah that's that's a simple one
i guess um they have so many original
ideas i don't wanna outright steal them
either but
ah they're so good
they're so good i wanna think of
challenges like that
[Music]
one is trying to get two pieces of
clothing as far as from each other just
called yeah yeah yeah yeah
often they also yeah do something like
get this thing as far away as possible
you have 30 minutes and then one person
would just try to hide it
like
or shoot it up with a balloon one person
would take a taxi one person would take
a a
a train one person would just give it to
to a person who's on a bike and say take
this as far as you can go
and all that
yeah yeah yeah yeah
it's always interesting to see how they
handle
the tasks given to them
it's been a lot of fun watching that
um
i'm glad some of you guys know it
those shows have a whole room yeah a
whole room and and the whole group of
people and yeah they have
um like things too like objects to work
with
but i feel like at least like some of
these should somehow
be able to be implemented somehow even
if they're just changed a little bit
that makes it better if i can change it
shut up i know what to do
where are we going
there's um
i think there's a chart to find
let's see in
the one next
doors
a chart
i haven't used the charts at all yet to
find
i have yet to find one with a chart a
triforce
[Music]
or or does this mean when there's a
when on my incredible chart i see you
know triforce icons and then i see map
icons
does it mean i will find a map here or
does it mean i already have a map and i
shall look at my other map
to find
the triforce
in this
square
[Music]
you'll i find the map here okay
okay
[Music]
where could it be
where could
[Music]
you need to go to a6 to get the ghost
shot first
oh
i have to do that first
a six
[Music]
one two
three where is
[Music]
where is asics
before a ghost ship
ah you just mean before getting the
close one okay okay yeah no no i'll i'll
try to find the map here first
where could it be
over here up there is there a chance
it's up there
what's up there
oh it can't be that easy right
a is done okay
tell me that again later
and that's not here
i'll kill you guys anyway
this is fun
[Music]
i don't like you
hey
without you dropping
nothing
wow
that's just normal chest
for a moment i fought oh my god big
brain
[Music]
skull necklace
nice shot bus thank you
emotional damage
wow
so painful
yeah but you say it as a joke but
honestly i know if i would say that
seriously to you guys
it would break your heart
it it does actually give lasting
emotional damage if it comes from a
person that you like
you did change your name
hallelujah finally you're true to
yourself
finally
wait we like you of course you like me
guys don't hide it i know it
no need to hide it
i think i'm gonna start snacking on my
um nectarine what's nectarina
nah
what is this
ah
oh it is nectarine
mmm
it's very juicy mm-hmm
[Music]
one thing i don't like about eating
fruit
like that
is that
there's not much
flesh
to eat
it's like over so fast you know what i
mean
um
and um
and if it's one with a big core big seed
in the middle
then it's annoying to eat around it i
don't like it
um
i ate a little bit of the seed
how did i do that
and now when you eat like half of it
then you don't know where to touch it
anymore
because you need to eat the other side
but no you have to touch the wet parts
oh
um
i like plums do you have hmm
[Music]
and i love cherries but cherries trigger
me so hard
that the the the ratio of seed to flesh
is so unbalanced and then there's like
barely any flesh so you have to eat a
million cherries but it's really
annoying to always like spit out the
core i wish cherries were bigger so that
you could enjoy
like a big amount of cherry taste in
your mouth for a longer amount of time
you know what i mean
hmm
i mean the pits
and you're expensive too um
[Music]
i mean that reminds me when i was
picking cherries as a
elementary
grade kid
elementary is elementary
i think it wasn't even elementary it was
even before elementary
okay i think i'm done not much left on
this one
nice
[Music]
i think the way i look right now fruit
suits me very well
i look like a girl who would eat fruit
[Music]
i had a i was eating it with a tissue
around it
okay um
and where are you going
where are we going we're i'm looking for
the map here
can i go buy
traffic here i have a traffic strike
this map must be interpreted ah
who the [\h__\h] has to
i get a map and then i even have to have
them interpreted are you kidding me
[Music]
eh
what do you mean it has to be
interpreted
where do i tinkle
where the [\h__\h] is tingle tingles chart
tingles chart
is this where you are up there
oh but but then wait before i go to
tingle then i want the other chart
that's around here
[Music]
before i go to him
i shall collect the maps
where is it
maybe over there
[Music]
oh no that's already
outside
territory
oh wait this one
is that a ghost [\h__\h]
[Music]
no no no
he's bugging into it
how do i how do i enter this
wait i have to make a hole in there
probably
but it's much too much
uh
huh that didn't work
get down
oh my god
that didn't work plump the ship blocking
the entrance okay hi bob
[Music]
brutal
oh [\h__\h]
this one oh i thought it was like
bugging into it
there we go now i'm hitting it
out
should i ignore that
i want to kill you guys too
even though
it's looking dangerous oh my god
[Music]
i'm being bullied over here
okay go around go around go around go
around
alone
[Music]
almost almost come on
there we go
oh
oh wow
it's right there it's right there
[Music]
no probably not
[Applause]
[Music]
talking about just before
what was our topic
ah taskmaster
very good
friday
on wait on my incredible chart on the
very left
there's a golden bombing ship
if i kill that i get a chart is that
what that means
so let's go over there too
yeah fruit and tuscan
let's see i'll come up with a new topic
in a moment
how about ah the animation well i don't
know what to say about that
there's not much to say i guess because
like it's not like i have
any input in it or
but it looks nice
looks like i mean it's teasers i'm like
i'm just like
when are you making it into a real anime
how long are we gonna keep on teasing
the people
let's make it into a real anime
these are cheese teases so much teasing
always but it's nice that we were
included
as well as id
first gen
it feels nice to be
included in these things
just like the link your wish concert
nice isn't it
oh there's ships over there
oh wait i should maybe get my health up
[Music]
maybe i can do that here
somehow
get off the boat
yeah
like uh
i feel like in the first year
of being in her life i feel like we all
kind of
oh oh
heal me yes thank you
there we go
we all maybe
just didn't
it didn't feel like something was
missing it just felt like hey we're all
live english why would we why would we
be included with all the stuff that
whole life japan does
i i don't think i really saw it as
something that
um must
happen didn't quite see it as a
possibility
it's like we're we're our own department
you know
[Music]
how can i like
yeah
all
it's not fair
uh
i i don't know how to do it while
driving but even then i feel like i
wouldn't be able to control it better
good
oh nice hell william
whole myth big success uh maybe maybe
part of like them including us
is due to us
doing so well and then i must say i'm
proud of us
we're doing so well well enough to be
included in these things
[\h__\h] where am i
does this one have more help than the
others
oh my finally took me down for a second
oh my god
what just happened
don't despawn please
huh what
what
what hap
what am i getting is it these signs
[Music]
is it this one
no there's so many
behind me it's one of them
[Music]
that is not it
let's try this one
i thought the one where i was taking
pictures was really cute
that is
um
i guess quite accurate like i do take a
lot of pictures
when i'm outside like
of both myself
and the food and the scenery
and honestly when i was showing callie
around
i took a [\h__\h] ton of pictures of her
i was like don't you want some some
pictures there's a memory and she was
like yeah dude thanks
definitely so i was taking some really
cool pictures and i showed it to her and
she was like holy [\h__\h] you're really
good at this yay
yeah she was posing for me and i'm like
yo yo yo at least you got good poses
going other people they just stand there
as if they were zombies or whatever but
callie poses really well
really um
she poses so
girly actually and she does a lot of
girly pose and i was like hey where's
the where's the rapper pose man
so then she would do like more a more
cool pose
yeah but she does a lot of cutesy poses
i was very surprised at that
yeah like lifting leg
lifting one leg
oh you know what i mean
cute
very cute
well yeah she liked the pictures i took
so nice sue
hey
they don't take off
it
they don't take off the charts
that i found the maps that i found
but i did find those two didn't i
did i find the one on the very end of
them i think so
so maybe it's time to go to tingle
i'll go to the tingle i got all the
chats okay okay
let's go to the tingle then
head south to get the ghost run wait
what what south new orleans
where
where is uh the ghost chart a6 was it
six
one two three four one five six
oh it's right down there
right there
just do that last is it difficult
it's supposedly
over there
that one
diamond step island
how many charts have i found uh
all of them
except for the ghosty one
that's it that's the ghost one
[Music]
oh no that's uh something else
nice uh
that's good too i'm happy about that too
uh
wait can i
lift myself up from the boat
oh no
um
[Music]
i guess i gotta go higher
what is this stump here doing here
yeah i hate the camera
here
onsen
i
oh i wanted to tell you one thing i took
with me
you know on the day i arrived i went to
have a
tonkatsu with a
group of my friends that i didn't see
for the rest of dokomi
they kind of disappeared after that and
hung out with other people
um
and uh
yeah we had tonkatsu and then
uh you know this this again
it literally was
two couples and me so i was the fifth
wheel
uh
and then
there's one girl
from
the couple
one of the couples
um we know each other for quite some
time so
she knows
you know that i'm a youtuber
and without me telling her though
she
she kind of finds out what when like
what's going on roughly uh she doesn't
really watch my streams i would say but
she gets to
she knows about the important things i
guess
so
she
knew about the valkyrie connect collabo
and
she pulls up her phone
and shows me
that she has
she downloaded installed and downloaded
the game
just because of me
to support me even though she already
has so many other guts or games to play
she downloaded it and she's been playing
it actively she said she maxed out all
of us
but yeah it says um
that i always got the mvp and then she
showed me like some fighting
scenes and
uh
yeah
that was i was so flattered that like
my my friend would do that
i was i was pretty flattered about that
yeah she was showing it off to me and i
was i was like oh my god thank you for
for doing that that's so sweet that
you're actually playing it actively
um
wow
so sweet playing valkyr connect right
now
yeah
i'm i mean i i expect that from
fans you know i didn't expect that from
a friend
for some reason i don't know i have a
feeling it's like
yeah they're like supportive and all
that but are they gonna go that far to
download
like some gacha game
and then max the character out that
you're
playing
yeah
i was pretty impressed
what am i supposed to do i didn't
ah go through here i guess
didn't realize ah it's like a riddle
there's so many of them
[Music]
how do you kill this dude again
just wait for him to
scare me
they're not that scary they're not that
scary
i was scared though
ok
[Music]
thanks to your guys support
apparently they will do more
supposedly probably i'm pretty sure with
other whole life members
so not with me anymore i would guess but
that's nice anyway
right they announced they are going to
do more
and you're back
which one did that come
from where's that
hoping for today the next banner
there was actually um you'll see this
eventually but there was a certain
official program
uh that i you know did a recording for a
while ago and then
the producer was like oh [\h__\h] producer
was like hey kiwa
is there anyone else you want
to like have
uh
join you
in this program and i actually
recommended reina
and
then she did end up joining
the recording
which oh god
you may have seen a while ago that we
have ended our recording at the same
time on the same day
i think we tweeted out something
both of us
yeah you'll see eventually what it is
one day one day
i'm happy i got elena to join it but she
was like really really nervous about it
like she was like you want lucky one
when it's my first time
to participate in the official program
like that i'm nervous i don't know what
to do help me help me
so i was like ah yeah yeah
well it's not don't think too much about
it just read for the script once and
you'll be fine
[Music]
you'll be fine don't worry
just read for it once
yeah yeah
they you know it's not my first official
program i've done so many that you still
haven't seen yet as well
but they usually provide us with like
really long
really really long scripts so i can see
how they could be intimidating
[Music]
just do it as the script says
is this like if i do it wrong i go back
to the beginning and it seems soon
you did see you could break thoughts
with your sword
oh sure i like i like lifting them
is this the right one
consider considering there's a right one
and the wrong one was this the right one
no it wasn't
okay let's try to remember then
i figured it out
[Music]
memory game okay
um
this wasn't it this is it
maybe
the lap link
this one
was this one i think it was this one no
it wasn't
[Music]
i didn't just i came out of that one
where i just came out of yes yes
[Music]
why didn't i get surprised by that i i
heard it
[\h__\h] hell
i killed it before oh yeah so yeah there
was nothing to continue on here
[Music]
sounds like a mouse suffering
a casper in my ceiling when i was living
in japan
well i feel like i tried every single
one of those
okay
okay and then i tried this one i think
what did i
which one i didn't try for sure is this
one
that
please please please please please
yes okay okay okay okay that was lucky
we have this one
[Music]
um
i
[Music]
this one
incredible
but wait that
is that what i'm looking for
[Music]
ghost chip chad yes i'm done
hallelujah
[Music]
is the water flowing stronger than
before
maybe not
yum yum yum
i'm just winning i'm just winning so
much it's almost been three hours don't
you
let's um let's go get uh let's go to
tingle i guess
[Music]
let's go to tango and after getting all
the shards is it just killing ganon or i
suppose maybe a dungeon and then ganon
or is there way more still
just so i know
there is a dungeon
[Music]
yeah that's so short
but if even if i do all that
that's short on its own but i have to
read super chat and i really have to
cook tonight i have so many ingredients
that i haven't been using
[Music]
i learned japanese konnichiwa
yeah definitely if we separate it which
is currently my plan then i'm open to
doing like more stuff next time
um
yeah i'll take more time then because
next time will be
after
i have recorded
everything that i need to record
for my birthday
so i think most of the pressure and
stress should be
off of my shoulders
and then we come we can go back to
normal yo
[Music]
i i felt
like recently this whole week
i've been trying to not feel stressed
out but i feel like
looking at it objectively i should feel
stressed out because there's
a lot going on and you know becoming
sick at the worst possible time
and still having to learn the dances and
i've been recording
yesterday i have to record some more
today
then tomorrow
yeah there's a lot of other things i
have to
do but i can't say
[Music]
but yeah
shark
voila
birthday
[Music]
does your chest still hurt
yeah wait
i think it does i'm not sure
i'm not sure
it's definitely not easy to breathe in
deeply
what's this again do i just go to the
top tingle are you up there
uh this morning yeah
immediately when i woke up oh [\h__\h]
that's really creepy
that's that's supposed to be the ferry
right
that i put in my bottles
why does it look so [\h__\h] creepy
and what's with the tea of
hi tingle
who bought harry
i've been looking to see you sir
why should we play what do you want to
play what you're not here to play huh
that fragrant musty set
sir
you found the chart
splendid splendid show me show me
why you can't read that chart in its
current state it's impossible sir
you like me to decipher it for you for
your 398.
i have that money but isn't it expensive
is there can i not haggle
is that haggable
i don't even know what musty means guys
don't call me musty
good morning
it was worse than the juicy really
i have to pay that for all three
well thank god i have like 10 times of
that
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h] scam
[Music]
probably he's probably the one who made
it unreadable in the first place
would you like me to decipher another
chart for 398 rupees
[Applause]
[Music]
one more i guess
the ghost one is already readable maybe
because the ghost giant
readable as in
it's just invisible
thank you
i like his moves he can do a flip that's
nice
you must try very hard to find the
treasure
when you select and open
um
[Music]
i guess let's get all the shards
that i can besides the ghost one i'm not
in the mood for a ghost ship right now
i don't like those kind of shits i
didn't like it in skyward sword neither
yeah it's my birthday happy birthday
a gamecube version was even more
expensive that's a lot
that's a lot
light map is bright and so free oh
oh
[Music]
okay
travis chart number one and where the
[\h__\h] is that
where is that
maybe actually it kind of looks like i
could be wrong but it looks like the map
close to me the chart
that's relatively close to me over there
i'll take a look
otherwise you guys have to help me
because i'm
i i still don't have my map filled up
there's still some
empty ones so it's hard to figure out
but there should be one here if i'm
correct
focus
[Music]
oh yeah
shark's still following me though
danger zone
and a bit more
[Music]
here
if i go up here
something else to get here
it's been a while since i was up here
what
let me um
i'm gonna go up
[Music]
look at those sparkly stars oh wow
island across
i mean
over there
there's a that chest that's where the
hot pieces may be
away
[Music]
orion that's orange oh that exists
actually cool
great orion i feel like orion is
a sensitive shop that i've seen before
maybe only in austria but
i feel good
[Music]
i think
i don't know what the cow i've never
don't have the patience man
what the [\h__\h] is this island
such a mess someone cleaned this [\h__\h] up
nam that cuckoo
spiral island what do you mean someone
said something's here
sorry i'm freaking out i just i should
do these things next time
with a guide
with a guide this one you mean this
yeah
hello you little [\h__\h]
i'm not gonna give you water
yeah
blah blah blah
not going to help you no no
no
[Music]
what do you get out of this if you give
all these trees ah
forest water
heart piece
i forgot about that
forgot that was a thing
[Music]
uh
this is really hard to see right now i
think
this way
uh
great
i see so much
but could be all right
why am i here
where's the heart piece
i'm here now what now
didn't you say something about you know
sean you said you wouldn't float
you mean float to the other side
not this one
what's that tiny island for
do i float over there
this seems ridiculous
[Music]
i can try
wait are we aiming for that island that
one that split into two one
because i don't think it's realistic to
try to go over there
yep
what
oh
i'm gonna land here
[Music]
music in my ears
yeah i see it i see it i'm not [\h__\h]
blind i see it
right there
i don't know
from the tree
no we're not going to call me blind junk
kakun
it's not funny
almost died
yeah [\h__\h] it
i don't care
okay we're gonna lose another time
not finishing today anyway
uh
all right uh i got that triforce chart
number two
where is that
that is
that could be anything
where
where is that i'm trying to compare it
with the ones that i do have
uh maybe that one
oh that's that's that looks like it
that's also why are they all so close
because
oh wait
they all form on the whole map
they form a triforce
and then the temple whatever the dungeon
will build in the hole
in the middle
of the map
in the middle of the triforce
that don't make sense
you probably don't quite get it if you
haven't played this game before and you
don't see my map that i'm looking at
it all makes sense and all makes sense
nice
yeah
that already happened yeah now it's
happening again i guess
when this might slide this much
one day
i'm gonna outsmart you guys
so much
that you will kneel
all right guys where is it thank god
it's night time
[Music]
i went too far i think i went too far
ah i never go too far
[Music]
ah [\h__\h] i'm going i'm gonna come back
you know this gotta happen with
smooth feeling
[Applause]
[Music]
do you already do that with your secret
projects
i'm smart
wow
two more
gosh then let's see number three this
map isn't open yeah yeah okay so by the
logic
that we've been going with
it should be
um
wait no let me look at the incredible
charge
could be up
here
[Music]
i know
could be
no only
yeah
ah there's a couple that i don't know
what they look like yeah
ah no i see it i see and obviously that
one okay
at the very edge of the map there's one
oh yeah yeah it still kind of hurts yeah
um
oh well
after this i feel like today i won't get
much dance practice and
[Music]
i probably won't get done with super
chats anyway we'll just read it until
like what time is it now already 7 p.m
yeah
i probably won't really be able to do
much
tomorrow's the day
because i have to cook but i don't want
to cook it takes time
[Music]
yesterday i really wanted to cook
because i had the day off
but then i wasn't on standby for a
recording
for like two hours and then while i was
on standby i was making use of my time
by recording something else on the side
um but then i was waiting and waiting
and waiting i was like yo i have to do
this sometime soon otherwise i can't
cook or shower anymore
and i did take a shower but i didn't get
to cook
because it was already like 2 a.m i'm
not gonna start cooking at 2 a.m
for the poor ingredients um yeah so i
ended up eating lasagna yesterday
i'm gonna make yourself i actually have
some gills out
yeah i do have some gyoza i bought it at
the supermarket yesterday
some in the fridge i want to
heat them up in the frying pan
later
maybe i can do it quickly before the
super chat reading
ah
we should make it night time
[Music]
have you used your f right oh i have uh
once with my mom we tested it out to
make schnitzel
but
it wasn't
the greatest schnitzel
but i feel like
one can go from there and and do other
things that work better with an airfryer
um
yeah my mom was not impressed
i think i told you this already though
but it's okay i don't mind repeating
it's just some you know obviously
there's viewers who don't hear every
story i tell them
and i feel awkward about repeating
things too
but then when i do repeat things until i
know you already told us that yeah okay
but not everybody heard it and sometimes
after two years of streaming can i not
repeat some stories
[Music]
i feel awkward too like i always say i
already told you this before but but
let me tell you the story
again because i feel like there's
interesting stories that i that link um
i told you guys in long streams
like during fire emblem for example
that
people haven't been around for back then
and i could repeat them now
is that the ghost ship
did i just find it without looking for
it
on it
well
i wasn't even looking for it
i i don't really want to do it
ah it's gone
how do you enter it i guess there's
ah music
i guess there's a key to do it
a way of doing it
check to check
i like the music
yeah i don't really want to do it though
it's been three hours i should probably
stop considering that i'll take uh i
read super chats at least for two hours
it would be 9 p.m
it won't take long really okay
oh is that where the last chart is how
do i how do i get inside i try to try to
charge your treasure
what does that mean
ah
at some certain time of the day
i can enter
maybe
just phase inside
oh
okay
i [\h__\h] because once it disappeared when
i got close that i can't i have to make
it like
stay what is this
you uh
can i touch the ground
there's a light over there
what is that
flowers
i think they just woke up because i shot
them
give me the shine touch ground
the mushrooms
[Music]
[Applause]
okay let's fight him first
don't i have to steal their thing
[Music]
again
stand in line
oh get out of here
get out of me buddy
[Music]
i hate this
at least we get rid of them like this no
okay okay okay
stop it stop it stop it stop it stop it
don't need the light shield i'm done
with them almost
[Music]
standing in the light kicks to my emilia
going up here
that's it
you guys were right it looks really
short i thought there was more to it
i guess the real quest was finding the
ship
finding a map and then finding the ship
i guess
ah they kicked me out
that's okay
[Music]
that's a good way to end it
[Applause]
[Music]
um
ah
well done
with the shards you have collected that
was not really his voice that wasn't
quite it then i don't know i don't
remember
well done kiwawa
maybe like this
but the shards you have collected the
triforce of courage is now complete at
last we must make to hyrule quickly
[Music]
yeah i know we're really really close to
the end
but we'll just take it easy next time
do some more possible side quests feel
free to tell me on twitter
uh what i can do
to make the episode longer next time
mm-hmm
and yeah i'll be reading super chats for
a couple hours now i guess
but i feel like i should
heat up my gyoza maybe
how hungry am i
maybe not that
i think i'm good
no i think i'm good no need for kills
huh i'll eat it tomorrow i think it's
still good tomorrow
welcome thanks for the membership mm-hmm
okay uh uh
save don't forget to save
no saving
to title screen
yeah
it was good that was fun i got to tell
you guys some things that has been going
on recently
oh not everything i still have stories
that's good
[Music]
is
did this change now that i have the
triforce
was it always like this
wow
it's taking us places
bird mode
[Laughter]
[Music]
two more episodes no no no no no no
no no next one will be the last one we
won't separate it any further that
wouldn't make any sense
yeah pajama link cute
all right then let's go to my office
or
yeah now let's go to my office
[Music]
all right let's put this away shut up
switch you can
go now
switch
[Music]
all right
and then make myself appropriate size
nice
looking good
do i need an idol meeting
it's not so bad yet
but maybe it would be smart and i can
get a snack
do i want a chocolate or a salty snack
[Music]
maybe i'll take both
and i'll pet the kitty cat
oh my cute soft babies
[Music]
i'll be gone for two minutes but i'll
leave you with some music how about that
um
favorite knight remix
what do we have oh this one was good i
linked this one
uh
on my twitter
or on my community board
wait i don't hear it why do you guys
hear it what the [\h__\h]
why do you guys hear it and i don't hear
it
i hear nothing
i want to hear it too
something messed up again with my sound
settings
let me check
[Music]
where does youtube go huh youtube
chrome
[Music]
wait out put output
output
music please
oh there it is
oh
i know you guys don't hear each other
now you guys on yours so i have to
change this to
that that could work
yeah
um
[Music]
i posted it on my community board the
other day
i'm tired of the same song okay enjoy
[Music]
can you make
new
[Music]
me
is is
[Music]
[Applause]
don't look away
[Music]
baby underneath
me
[Music]
don't care
sorry had i had smoothie in my arms
and it's moving in my arm so i couldn't
couldn't put on my headphones but i
heard it through a little bit
whoa hello hello
hello hello
[Music]
back this movie already escaped it's too
late
she doesn't
see what you're saying unfortunately
bangor yes good remakes there's actually
been quite a lot of remixes
for fifa night
which i'm pretty happy about i feel like
we didn't get so many for sparks even
and sparks was doing pretty well in this
film i guess but yeah didn't get many
remixes
is it because did we release an
instrumental for spikes
did we not and that's why we didn't get
remixes
i don't know
what
y'all
okay
[Music]
spock's just perfect the ladies right
yeah yeah
now all my songs are perfect the way
they are but you know now it's nice to
to hear a twist
of it
yeah
[Music]
all right what are we listening to
let's see let's go for my precious audio
stock library
[Music]
which one do i not use so often um
i like this one i've used it a couple
times before but
what
now i don't hear this one either
let me fix this
everything's going into different
sources on outputs
[Music]
i love this one
what are we reading this time only the
outfit reveal right for now
[Music]
sounds like hot dog ladies not the first
time someone said that i get what you
mean
[Music]
one from today i know it's from you
uh but now we're reading uh outfit
reviews of a chance
that's where we left off i think
[Music]
and this is the biggest one we'll have
to
get behind us
all right are you ready
[Music]
for
oh wait i need more water
also for snacks i only brought chocolate
i brought i bought
in the country because
for a while i've been craving kindle
country i think ever since
we were asked like for a subaru senpai's
stream like can you guys recommend some
snacks from your countries
and then
i think it was ame actually
who recommended kinder country and i'm
like
i think we are supposed to recommend
snacks from our own countries amen
but ever since then i was like oh can
the country
wouldn't mind having some
kinder country sound it's so german but
it's not from austria so i didn't
recommend i didn't suggest that either
actually the things that i suggested
was i think because austria you know i
recommended um the mana wife waivers
waffles thingies
those are
definitely from austria
um
not the best most delicious
snack but
it's
popular for a souvenir as well
what else did i
i think i i i suggested oym dudla
as a drink you know our herbal
herbal
soft drink that we have
oh yeah yeah italian why did you give it
a german name it's so misleading i don't
understand i always think it's austrian
or german or whatever
but it's not
mamma mia
it's because we're just that close you
know
or just buddies me and italy we're best
friends
[Music]
yeah and uh
i think one more i probably suggested
mozart um
those mozart chocolates the round ones
i did think i do think i said i don't
really in particular like this but it's
just popular
as a souvenir and it's like you know our
chocolate
i don't really like it though
yeah mozart cougar and mozart balls
that was the snack exchange
oh you liked them there's there's
different types though
so i think
it depends on which one you get they can
taste a little bit different
yeah marzipan i just don't really like
marzipan yeah
marzipan we like to use marzipan a lot
in austrian
uh cakes and chocolate
patisserie
um
[Music]
i just don't like it
i don't know why i just don't like it
i could probably eat it
forcefully but
not really
my choice
[Music]
bonjour
eh you're in paris now
oh this is an overlay
a a transit in paris oh
are you at
joel the ghoul
most horrible
uh traumatizing airport i know
[Music]
i was so [\h__\h] big
but then like i don't know i've been to
a lot of big airports like the one in
dubai as well
and the one in
istanbul
and so on
but the one in paris i don't know what
it is about that one i think it's just
not as well
organized as the others maybe i don't
know
it feels like
it's
not so easy to get around that one
as and maybe i i will give this to the
dubai one
it is
even though it's huge it's at least like
uh
obvious
to see where you have to go
[Music]
jfk in queens no so i've only been to
america once in my life haven't seen
much when i was there
and that was uh
san francisco
but really
didn't see much like you could almost
say i've never been to america
[Music]
which is crazy i've traveled so much in
my life
on the european and asian side
but
yeah america canada so and so on
even to brazil i've even been to brazil
so i've been on that side of the globe
but i haven't
gone north
[Music]
america
is
[Music]
which product no i said i've never been
to canada
which state which state would you like
to visit in america i don't know
i don't know there's like so many and i
guess there's a lot of good places to
visit it's like really hard to choose
i don't know kind of overwhelming
i would say that if anything i would go
to
states that are on the ocean side not
like in the middle
it feels like
the cool places are there
[Music]
broadway show oh
can i see a broadway show anywhere in
america or does it have to be a
specific place
see the giant hole oh you have not you
have a hole
well now i'm interested now i'm hooked
[Music]
what
oh broadway is a place in new york city
ah
i thought you know broadway shows they
go on tour and you can see them in
different places you know
[Music]
certain broadway shows monster in new
york studio all
well i won't be going to new york city
anytime soon
[Music]
but one day one day then
is it like in the theater
or is it outside what's that like
well how's it different from a theater
it's a fear though
[Music]
who here is from america
who in the chat is from america
[Music]
new york is
oh my god very early as always
thanks for watching
[Music]
you know even though i speak the
language fluently going to america
like that thought
overwhelms me way more than for example
going to
england
i don't know it's scary somehow so big
and
oh i don't know it's big
[Music]
i'm not sure if americans are
like the people who are outside running
around on the street not the ones who
are in the chat
how nice they are
[Music]
one thing that intimidated me it was you
know i'm very straight edge and all that
and then in san francisco i remember
walking
down the street and i smelled a very
distinct
smell
like
throughout the whole
the whole
area there like it was
it all smelled like that and i felt so
intimidated by it just by the smell
hmm
yeah i know i don't have to consume it
but i don't know just smelling it
makes me feel intimidated
i'm just very
very very very spurious um yeah
this scares me
[Music]
smell isn't even the worst part
i don't know
i did like the
[Music]
how to say
i did like the scenery very much though
um
wanna go again
[Music]
from audio stock
it doesn't have a title
ah comes on for the membership thank you
yeah i should start reading super chats
too many hills yeah yeah that is true
that's true
[Music]
maybe someone can show you around
but that's again again it's like america
is so big and
i don't know
who is where and where is who
and
even outside of holo
i supposedly have some
old friends scattered across america
probably but then when i try to think of
them i can only recall one person
where is everybody else do i have more
friends in america than i'm forgetting
about
long lost friends there probably are
some but do i want to meet long lost
friends
[Music]
often
these
past two years
one and a half years i don't know people
message me for the first time in a
million months and they're like hey
[Music]
how you doing
most of the time that's
anyone who messaged me messages me in
the past 1.5 years for the first time in
a long time
is
usually a bad sign for me
i mean i don't you know not everybody
has to have bad intentions and all that
but
well i don't really have time to
you know
make more friendships and all because
then you know there's always these
people currently with my current friend
circle
it's all good but i used to have friends
that would be really pissed at me if i
didn't message them
once a week or once a month or so
if there was
like if it was too one-sided that they
would message me more than i would
message them
they would be pissed off and all that
but
it's so annoying like i don't have
it's not like i don't like you but i
like friendships that work even without
talking to one another
uh
like just because you don't talk to one
another for like over a week or two
weeks or three weeks doesn't mean you
don't like one another anymore and you
know we just have things to do in life
especially now
we have things to do
yeah
and that's just put so much pressure on
me
when people are like this i'm like okay
dude
i i can't do this friendship then sorry
[Music]
i can't too clingy and not really clingy
but just if sometimes they're like
they don't even message me much
themselves either but they they just
they get mad when i don't do it and
expect me to message them no dude
no
no i don't have time i'm not interested
even with my bff we barely
um
we often have times where we don't talk
for like two weeks
but we still love each other
right you i think you guys can relate to
that
[Music]
no that doesn't happen to me that
doesn't happen
[Music]
hmm
us chickens are very lucky to have such
a hard-working boss like you you're
amazing i think you will look cute and
your new outfit sadly i'll have
to miss today's stream i'll be bald gang
[Music]
i probably got spoilers even before
watching the vaughn didn't sound
yeah this is the problem with uh being
vlogging on streams like this
like the outfit reveal or something like
that 3d reveal whatever you could spoil
[Music]
that's life men true mate
yeah but i hope you enjoyed it anyway
thank you kenzie
[Music]
oh
extremely disappointed with the new
outfit being fully green with few sparks
unacceptable for hinotori like i
suddenly had a favorite last night
really still fuku papa's superb design
should challenge my heart right until i
fade in life keep on shining my legs
yeah i know that the pump nail was kind
of click bait wasn't it you expected a
fully green
kappa kiwawa with sparkles
sorry for the clickbait
i'm still kind of green though the
reason why i made myself green in this
thumbnail is because it's kind of the
color of my dress
so
wasn't so much misleading
it's your neck you don't want it
it's like turquoise yeah
thank you chunky chunk
really happy to see you around still
thank you for the love and support
[Music]
hope you liked it even though i wasn't
in the green screen soon
[Music]
thank you
for watching
hype for this but you look good in
everything cats are staring at the
screen from their bookshelf the humming
confuses them
humming
was this already when the stream started
[Music]
i thought we were still in the waiting
room i guess not now now
oh
[Music]
did the cats like my new outfit it has
ribbons
you know when i when i every morning
when i put on this dial
and i
uh tie the ribbons in front of my chest
my cats come to play with the ribbons
with the ends of them because they're
pretty long
they nickel punch the ribbons
trying to catch them they love these
kind of
long ribbons
the thin ones
anything honestly anything that's long
that you can play with
[Music]
[Applause]
what is that name dude
thank you for the rest of the chat
hello killer it's now an exact year i
subscribe to your channel oh i
discovered myth by curiosity late
december 2020
i am now addicted to euphenox
phoenix city
how you convey emotions and feelings
your sparks and your attention for
carefree jenkins i salute them wish you
the best thank you very much i think
that's your first ever super chat i
would remember that name
thank you for watching for such a long
time
i'm glad that you're hooked on kiwawa
now
i appreciate it thank you please
continue watching my stuff i'll do my
best
i hope i can keep you
hooked for a long time
[Music]
a chocolate insomnia thank you for the
pinky
i love your profile picture that's pake
monogatari
okay sorry i've been missing and have
not been donating i've made a career
change and recently just finished a
difficult class now i'm in search of a
new job i promise i'll get back to super
chatting in the near future regrets on
the outfit thank you no don't worry
about super chatting i'm just glad
you're still around
it's nice to read your name again thank
you
actually just yesterday
i was watching some old stream footage
[Music]
for a future cow carrot video
and
you know i was looking at the chat from
like back then long time ago when i was
still in japan
i saw so many names of people who are
not here anymore it makes me a little
bit sad but
yeah
but then there's all these people who
also stayed
and i'm really really really grateful
for that but it would just be nice to
know
uh like
some people may not be active on the
chat but they're still around that would
be nice to see if you guys
you guys could say hello
you know like hi i'm still around
thank you thank you
[Music]
i'll always be here
and new people too
thankfully
[Music]
ah
no so fast
chat
you're not alone
i asked her for the instrumental because
i really like it i want to sing it in a
karaoke sometime soon
i feel like i listened to it so often i
could already sing it
thank you guys
oh my humidifier is out of water again
okay that's fine
[Music]
i've seen you
on twitter so often recently what's
going on
hello
[Music]
oh thank you for saying hi
nice karen dankeshen kenshin 491
vanishes
[Music]
knows what's up took the words out of my
mouth truly seeing chaos tummy and
thighs and hips and bubbles are more
than enough reason to work 1000 everyday
potential
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah i see you got the spirit
you're motivated just like the chicken
in the video
[Music]
yeah
i get it yeah um i bamboozled you guys
i said i was gonna put on clothes that
are not so distracting yet here i am and
fully aware that this is
not
better in in that sense at all
but that was never the goal
that was just trying to baboozle you
guys
[Music]
yeah yeah that's how it is guys don't
trust me
[Music]
i already have an amazing idea for
the next
outfit
if i get one again
i just have to see
what management and hookah papa says
about it
but i feel like you guys will love it it
will just take a long time
[Music]
see there's so many things i want to do
but there's a limit to how many i can do
per year
so
[Music]
i want to trade it very very carefully
and i have a good idea
i think i think i think
i don't want to waste it but
there's one thing
that i
i feel like i need to do
hmm
my
[Music]
did you catch it
spiced chicken taco
froggiano pyjama oh
yeah i'm not gonna waste a whole you
know once in a year new outfit
claim
on a frog pajama not yet at least
there's still other things that i think
are more worth it
[Music]
according to my apron i am a wife so
it's kind of legit that you call me that
now
i guess
thank you dragonfire also thanks for the
thinking i'm dead god oh no wait
do i need to
do i need to go to the police
and
put up a missing person thingy
where are you dragon fire
where are you
oh no
i killed him
[Music]
loco
where are you
let us make you dinner later oh man that
would be amazing i wish you could i wish
during these busy times
[Music]
yeah just checking which hand was there
well i hope
you're not completely lost i hope you'll
come back dragonspire
[Music]
chat oh so god damn cute really got me
with the office trailer still hoping for
a suit down the line ahead
maybe maybe maybe maybe yeah
but i'm glad you liked it so much you
seem with the cops look you seem very
excited about it seems like i've made
the right choice
[Music]
in storageland
thank you for the red super chat nagal
is also one of those people who
haven't been showing up that much
anymore
calling you out right now i'm sorry but
i'm just saying because it makes me
happy to see your name thank you
ribbon signifies married i went
wait this wasn't in the contract we
signed this is a break of of of jiggly
bouncy
seems like uh
you need to focus a bit more nagel when
you talk to me i don't know what you're
talking about
focus focus focus
look at me focus
[Music]
don't waste my time
i'm having a conversation here
but here's a kiss
maybe that will help you focus
eyes up here eyes up here
[Music]
thank you and we're just taking down
questions
thank you for the rest of the chat
thank you very much it seems you
were at a loss of words
you didn't know what to say that's okay
[Music]
beautiful and less injuries means less
work for me right oh
because you're legally
probably not because you're still
stunning enough to keep frying at an
all-time high
might be slightly more distracted now
but trust me legal will still keep kfc
in line just how how is my boss this
feels just how
maybe
do we have some cafe scientists who
could
find out why and how
calculate
things
you press and enter by accident before
writing the message oh
you were probably also kind of
distracted then
won the wine
i'll take a break for chocolate right
now
and we need a campy science team i'm
sure some of you guys
know a thing or two about science
[Music]
my accent that doesn't sound like a very
scientific answer to me
you will have to investigate further
i watched railgun it should be qualified
yeah yeah it's
railgun very very scientific indeed
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
yum
this chocolate is so good
oh have you guys ever had kinder country
before
[Music]
it seems like you can get it pretty much
everywhere so
go get it if you haven't
[Music]
kindle country
there's several different kinds of
kinder chocolate and they're all good
i love them all
but in the country is one of my
favorites
no kinder is like
there's like different types there's
kinder bueno
[Music]
in the country kinder
chocolate eggs
[Music]
come out tonight
foreign
[Music]
yeah you guys don't have kinder eggs in
america
what if i bring them
is is the airport security gonna take it
away from me
chocolatings
[Music]
the chocolate egg dealer
illegal chocolate egg dealer
you got the goods yeah yeah i got the
goods
[Music]
eggs are kind of my thing you know
okay last bite last
[Music]
go to bite do not pass gold not calling
two hundred
[Music]
arrested chill
prison jaw
prison
breakthrough
running away from country jewel
landing in switzerland joel
hiding in switzerland joel
never getting out of switzerland joel
someone come and
rescue mitchell
[Music]
forever launcher
swiss jaw
swish chop cleanse
my destiny has been fulfilled i'll i'll
turn into swiss chocolate one day
embassy cho yes hide an emphasis
[Music]
embassy is my new home chill
go to plastic surgery ritual
change my face jaw
become
someone else joe
[Music]
then new youtuber debuted
everyone's gonna be like wait that's
kiwama
[Music]
same voice joe
you're gonna dox me john
i'm gonna be arrested again sure
[\h__\h] you
[Music]
keep my secret job
i don't know what's going on
[Music]
it's fanfic chinchou
okay
[Music]
super chat
oh my god that's so shiny what what you
see are you playing pokemon are you
playing pokemon
we spot us so much kiawah
we love the outfit
but i'm afraid the accidents will
increase in the factory
that's okay
it happens it'll be like that
accidents
there are no mistakes only happy
accidents right so
[Music]
happy accidents small price today
thank you
wow
have your thank you for the rest of the
chat
thank you so much pretty bad it's too
cute
are you
from germany or australia
yeah
i hope i hope like german and austrian
people in particular
felt
happy and proud
that i chose
to wear a dindle
for my new outfit
austria
yeah
well i hope i hope you're feeling
particularly proud or like flattered or
whatever like it's you know this looking
at this must feel like very familiar and
like oh she's one of us after all
she do be austrian yes yes
yes yes
[Music]
thank you for a red super chat
i mean i just how can i not we have such
a cute goddamn cute
traditional outfit
yeah
thank god if it was ugly as [\h__\h]
i
probably wouldn't have gotten it as a
outfit
probably wouldn't have considered it
thank god it's such a cute one
not proud of you yeah you love germans i
guess you don't wear that
[Music]
you should at least feel
a small connection though
spider danke hikoto
thank you
[Music]
um
you know i really need to get back into
my korean studies oh my god
i completely stopped because too [\h__\h]
busy i swear
after my birthday
i'm gonna take it serious again because
i have to because i want to go to korea
in august
sometime in august
the gym
the gym currently is on break too
because i'm dancing every day i'm
sweating quite a lot so
now be cool out before the trip
yeah
even before or during the trip
or both
will you meet nabi mama yes yes yes yes
i want to talk to him we're still doing
it
dancing is a workout yeah yeah
but once everything calms down i want to
go back into the things it's not like
it's not like i completely gave up on it
it's just like too much at once
happening
[Music]
i suddenly see korean people popping up
in my chat again hi
sorry mia
for
not studying
but soon again fighting i will continue
[Music]
sorry
for
not studying
korean lately
i have been so busy
with
my preparations
but
i will learn it
again after
my
birthday okay let's read this and sound
smart
[Music]
i'm so excited for korea
i was already looking at hotels and
stuff didn't book anything yet don't
even know like when exactly i'm going i
was just looking at random dates
looking at what kind of hotels
there are
it's actually pretty cheap i'm surprised
hmm
i expected them to be more expensive but
they were all like relatively cheap for
nice nice rooms
yeah
i was surprised
maybe it's because there aren't many
tourists i wonder how many stars enough
enough stars i'm 16 years old last three
years my manual was about to kind of go
to school but i keep in line with your
stream my goal makes people happy right
directed me to phoenix thank you
[Music]
you're welcome
are you back
in school now
i hope so
[Music]
foreign
not sure
[Music]
i know that like you know
i've heard for example i don't know if
it's the same in korea but i heard that
in in japan for example bullying in
school can be pretty bad
if it's like that kind of problem i
understand going back to school can be
very scary
but
you have to go it's important for your
education
and don't be don't be scared of like
speaking up to adults and teachers
asking for help worst case change school
um
yeah
bullying in any school can be scary yeah
definitely of course of course
i got bullied too and you know i would
change schools
[Music]
not
because of the bullying but i was glad
to get away from it
we had continued continued on
i was just always like unpopular
unpopular kids no one liked no one
wanted to have that kid in their
group in whatever
the sports class
yeah physical education
always always the last one being chosen
not all i will give them that tell that
it was not only because they didn't like
me but also because i was just not good
at sports
yeah that is true
[Music]
i would have chosen you first no
thank you
that's the dodgeball you're best at
dodging until the end where i've dodged
so much that i'm the last one standing
and then i'm really [\h__\h] stressed out
because everybody is [\h__\h] aiming at
me
trying to get me down
and then that's like the last
when i'm the last one standing that's
the only time when the other students
will cheer for me
and then you feel all that pressure and
then eventually because i just can't
throw back
or catch catching is also not much of my
strength
then i i'm eventually
losing anyway and then everybody's like
ah sasuka as expected kiwawa sucks
[Music]
dodge chol yeah
i am
[Music]
and i didn't keep you down
and go to school on monday
fighting
let's go let's go to school school
school yeah yeah school can be fun
sometimes you know thinking back some
parts of school i miss too
and you guys wear uniforms don't you i
wish we had uniforms back in the day
korean school uniforms are cute too
[Music]
korean school uniforms are kind of
fashionable
um
you know
you never had universe no i didn't have
uniforms
no austrian schools don't have uniforms
i never see people running around in
uniforms we also don't have any private
schools like i've i don't i never see
like i've never i don't know um i've
never seen
private school
before in austria i'm sure there are
some
but they're not like especially like for
high school and all that
most of them are just public
uh
yeah i and even the few private ones
i would say
also mostly don't have uniforms maybe
there is some but it's really really
uncommon i've never seen
in my home life in austria i've never
seen someone in a school uniform besides
you know
cosplayers
[Music]
oh you bought school uniform
oh
nice probably looking very handsome
[Music]
hmm
oh what was that one word uh
[Music]
what's that one word that i said to the
korean
diverse snorkelers that we've met in the
maldives
uh i was like wow
so cool right
[Music]
one word i remember
it was really short
don't remember
i don't remember i forget everything
[Music]
it will come back to you i'm trying to
figure it out it's not
coming up on topical
[Music]
impressive
no
[Music]
something like cool something like oh
that's so cool you know
[Music]
oh that's cool
no
not much
[Music]
okay i give up
i just have to study again and then i'll
remember everything
[Music]
[Laughter]
awesome cool
is it the best
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
i want to say something
the korean snorkeler couple that was on
honeymoon
but when we were like snorkeling in the
mall beams and i was like pointing at
the water
and then i was like timbuk and they were
like oh yes debunk
yes
[Music]
flexing that one word i can think of
okay where the hell were we
where where we are here i think
el silab pentagon j swagbuck thank you
for the red super chat
i like your profile picture by the way
so it's really just j with the hat on it
very important
it's like it looks like an umbrella
the modest office lady bit actually got
me for a minute
another smart chicken cute outfit
hilarious reveal no i wouldn't say
which i'm eroding my mind i don't know
what that means i wouldn't say not smart
because of that
it was very misleading that was on
purpose
let me change
the pgm
[Music]
something chill
now i want something new
i have so many
i always want something new
how about
we're going audio stock
[Music]
i want something with a guitar
but
something calm
[Music]
um
was hoping for
nice job
[Music]
hmm
there's a voice
what's this
like
immediately like
makes me happy
why it's like an rpg music let's go
until we rise up
[Music]
this feels like athena raiza
sounds corporate um
[Music]
let's go
wow a new town so many things to collect
and mix together
in my alchemy thingy wow
so much fun i made a bomb
oh my god i can help the people i'll
take this quest and this quest oh you
want these stones or you want these
herbs i'll make it for you yeah let's go
until here
this is beautiful
it gets quieter here
[Music]
kind of like it
don't download it
with
these oh
by the way why is it not saying audio
stock anymore
in the previews it's not saying audio
stock
[Music]
oh
yes baby
jazz me up
oh yeah
[Music]
oh
audio stack
jamming
i want this one
it's not loop though apparently but it's
at least three minutes long
but it doesn't loop
[Music]
here we go let's go thanks j swagbuck
mwah kiss for you
danger brett dankeshan
here's a korean name choto mate
[Music]
thank
you
that's that's
very very sweet i'm happy to hear that
and yes
holds for the hooter indeed
wood in front of the house means boba
big boba
it's a funny
saying
you guys should remember that one in
german we say
lots of wood in front of the house
means
big bubba
thank you optimus prime
absolutely thank you for the rest of the
chat
and die gone reduced right at homes at
homes items you're freaking gorgeous
kiwa oh god
[Music]
you guys are so charming thank you
carpenter i'll give you a kissy
[Music]
well put me in the fryer already because
i just died from cuteness overdose also
who is the lucky fluffy bird besides
kotori we should give him a name huh
to be honest i'm not even sure which one
i guess the the one of the closed eyes
is kotori
[Music]
would you say it
that one is kotori
i'm not sure
[Music]
the bigger one
right now rat looks more motivated i
feel like koto is like you know too old
for this [\h__\h] by now
[Music]
i would say that the happy one is a girl
that one
is
um
think about it can't make such a simple
important decision so
quickly
[Music]
how about kiana i know
it's very original
[Music]
okay no no
no no not yet we're not going to decide
it now but i'll think about it thank you
tony tell them
thank you jacob 47 i'll thank you for
the words of the chat honestly it's
amazing i was definitely expecting some
more formal maybe for her talk but
something like this is lovely it's been
really sweet seeing you go from being
shy about your culture on w to embracing
and also nice jokes
bristle thank you
it's not so much that i was
i mean i was always shy about talking
german i still am
but
in the beginning i was just i guess
trying to protect my privacy by not
immediately revealing that i'm from
austria
because
you know
there's not many people that are from
australia
and um
yeah
just trying to
stay safe because because um i think
other girls were doing the same
still continue to
try to be very vague about where they
are
and where they're from
you know for the japanese girls is like
pretty obvious you know we know pretty
much
you know where they're from and where
they are
but for the ian girls they're
scattered over the globe or they could
be
so
they could be anywhere
so it's
more reasonable to try to keep the
security and privacy protected
and just not
say it but you know how long that worked
out for me especially like i can't debut
and then
not mention the fact that
i speak fluent german and then you would
hear from when i talked that english
isn't my first language so you would
probably assume at some point
then
yeah my first language is german and
then whole i wonder
if her first language is german then
there's not much choices of where she
could be from
yeah
it goes on like that
it was yeah just
it doesn't
you guys would have found out at some
point but
i just still felt like an obligation
of having to
kind of hide it anyway
it's not that i was shy about it i don't
really
i don't really care
where we're not you guys know i'm from
austria or not i just feel i don't know
austria is so small and
um
we don't have that much
like famous things famous people and all
that
um that comes from austria except for me
um
so i would
i don't know it was just not something
that i would feel like is something i
could brag about like hey i'm from
austria
we don't even have an ocean
but yeah no no i just don't know the
whole australia thing also
wasn't because
i i don't know
it wasn't because i was still trying to
hide it it was just a joke at that point
once i misspoke
it was just a joke as you know from the
video about the kfb lore as you must
know
[Music]
but at some point the joke just you know
got too deep and people
thought i was really from australia
which can only really be the people who
don't watch me much but yeah
australia
like blizzard
i forgot about that completely
[Music]
very dense yes yes yes yes yes
it's gonna happen with bonkers it
already happened people immediately
japanese people immediately thought i
really have a raccoon
i'm just
too believable
stop believing me
oh yeah
yeah
thank you jacob
option
alex hedges thanks for the pinky and
your outfit is so cute it fits you very
well
thank you
maybe there is a lot of people who saw
the angel for the first time in their
life i wonder are there any here
who sighed in the for the first time for
[Music]
yummy oh that's quite a lot
so that makes me happy too that i'm able
to share like look this is our cute
traditional clothing appreciate it
don't you see how cute it is wouldn't
you want to wear one too if you were a
cute girl maybe or even a boy i don't
know but we have lederhosen for the boys
little zen
i've never worn lederhosen before so i
don't know if they're comfortable
but if you ever go to an october
festival or something like that
feel free to
wear it
to fit in
[Music]
they're not they're not comfortable
oh man
really
oktoberfest
unit in the future yeah i saw that meme
ah
we have no idea an energy and me
yeah but i should be in the center for
that idol unit
as a joke for whole for oktoberfest
would be funny maybe
uh time to face my pinky
i won't take my meds tonight it's so
amazing eleven hundred percent sorry for
not being here all the time but i'm
working to get kiwamo merch next month i
like it so much so go on mioshi i mean
birthday merch yeah it's coming up
it's coming up and by the way i did
record the voice pack
i did end up recording at some point i
was actually inspired
it ended up
being pretty long i think
um
because i found a way to make it very
long
uh
yeah i recorded it actually like on
monday or tuesday
i think
tuesday maybe
[Music]
that was one of the things that i was
recording
um
[Music]
there's even gonna be
versions of the voice pack now i'm not
gonna say too much but
yeah it's gonna be two versions
[Music]
um it's so soon how many days
until birthday actually looking at it
might stress me out oh [\h__\h] at the
calendar it looks like nothing not even
three weeks
one week two week two and a half weeks
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
wow that stresses me out [\h__\h] that [\h__\h]
that don't look at the time take it take
it day by day one by one
[Music]
a lot about this birthday was very
stressful
like even getting an artist for the
merchandise
everything's so stressful oh my god
so stressful but i'm so happy when it's
over and i hope you're gonna like
everything that i've i've been preparing
and behind the scenes
[Music]
yeah
after that big relief oh my god
we gotta celebrate
i think this year i'll also do the
countdown i don't know if i did that
last year but i think i want to do the
countdown too
with collins
have like
the collins in the countdown
and then you know the 3d birthday
because that one will obviously be
focused on performing
i didn't do it right but i think i think
i also questioned like if i do a
countdown like what time zone am i
counting down to but i guess my own
my own time zone
[Music]
i guess i'll do that
so we'll do that we'll do two birthday
streams basically
maybe even a third one
[Music]
i have an idea for something but i don't
know
where to implement it
that reminds me
[Music]
24 hour birthday endurance
okay
[Music]
you guys can go on a 24-hour endurance
not me i'm too old for this [\h__\h]
and the white wing
[Music]
here
oh yeah
and tracy i think
no wait i didn't finish no no no i did
finish el canal because merchandise
thanks for the tangent jim tracy thanks
for the pinky you finally got your
daniel it looks amazing here i made you
up still look at papa thank you
i wonder when was the first time that i
talked about wanting to get a dandelion
does anyone remember you guys are so
good with like archiving those kind of
things
when did it first become an idea
a long time ago maybe already when i saw
an energy's new outfit
maybe because like i compared it to
daniel i told her hey this looks kind of
like a dandel somehow with a lot of
fantasy and imagination
when noah got hurt no that was probably
just by that time
i was already
planning mine i think
but i was just probably just on stream
saying more more clearly i want a dandel
too
ah when mama luna drew it oh yeah that's
also a long time ago she did draw me in
some kind of a dental
[Music]
i can say with confidence that the task
to not distract those chimpkins failed
successfully yay
reminds me of taskmaster if that was a
task then i guess i would have gotten
no points unless unless the task is to
distract you guys
[Music]
then i would have gotten full points i
think that was the real task
wow
[Music]
you know as long as you guys are
distracted by
from me by me
then i'm happy
if you're distracted by something
besides me
none we're gonna have a problem gotta
have a talk
down
[Music]
okay now i'm distracted
speaking of distracted i got naturally
distracted by
some behind the scenes talk
sorry
[\h__\h] us focus
kevin again
thank you for the rest of the chat flip
the model and your ribbon will be on the
right left side okay couple of you guys
said that i don't know will it look
weird because
um almost everything is pretty
symmetrical i mean birds will be flipped
around
but my hair and my eyes and everything
my feathers
most things are symmetrical so it
shouldn't look too weird let me try
are you ready for this
[Music]
flip horizontally oh
my hand looks mostly the same
it's just
confusing me right now because the
movement is
uh
the other way around
[Music]
yeah it looks
i think you can get used to it it
doesn't look too off
[Music]
but that seems like a weird solution to
flip my model the whole time
divorced arc no no it doesn't mean the
voice now now it just means
single
and
maybe not ready to mingle
oh no just single
it's confusing that the movement is
just look straight huh look straight
okay
hello i'm kiwawa i'm wow wow
[Music]
wow
i like
fake no not fake no no very real
oh i can get used to this if only
if only the movement wasn't inverted
because when i look at myself and i want
to do like a cute pose or so it's hard
to control
when it's the other way around
how
i'm so cute even horizontally flipped
[Music]
all right
eh thank you kevin
do you still like me flipped
[Music]
thanks yoli off
pinky you're right about the tweet
because i'm falling in love again you're
so gorgeous i'm curious
dad you're so sweet
you're so sweet yuriya i love you
so sweet so charming
[Music]
david asked you too duncan for the pinky
as well i'm so happy that your new
outfit was revealed to us on my birthday
oh you look so beautiful kendra thank
you it was your birthday oh
happy belated birthday dan
[Music]
nice birthday present yeah yeah exciting
okay this is amazing very spicy top but
overall still extremely cute lovely
outfit overall very modest for sure work
safety will surely improve not
yummy
[Music]
spicy
but you know you are from germany you
know what tandems look like
you know this is just how it is
um i'm actually i feel like i still look
very say-so with my pretty flowers and
my updo
[Music]
nah not spicy no
sweet
[Music]
but a deal on kiara what
that's just
it has to be spicy
got no choice but to be spicy
but no i'm sweet sweet
no you know you
[Music]
she calls everything spicy
thank you you need to chat
can you meet me thank you for the rest
of the chat skype uh skype
skipped out of work to see my beautiful
potential outfit review let's go love
you kiara don't worry just an extended
break
yeah you better be getting back to work
immediately
huh but this is work watching my streams
is work so that's okay
[Music]
my skype is so old man skype still
exists i'm sure it still exists
just nobody uses it sadly skype was fine
thank you very much for watching and
skipping out of work just for me
thank you it's a very important occasion
very hype this reveals always very hype
so
and you can kind of guess that even if
it's a one hour stream that it
the reveal will be at the very end i
should bamboozle the people one time
and just reveal it in the very beginning
and then turn back into my normal
clothes until the end of the stream so
only the people who who were there
probably from the very beginning
we'll see it i know there's so many
people who just come at the very end on
purpose
and just do a reverse outfit review
no but i can't do that because that's
kind of sabotaging myself the amount
sabotaging the amount of people who
could see it
you know i want to bamboozle them
[Music]
so
i'm glad that the river's during the end
i was on the autobahn during most of the
reveal oh gas gas gas um
[Music]
so cute love the hairstyle so much thank
you
i actually like i can do like these kind
of braids um
that are like the
that stay close to the scalp because you
keep on adding more strands
uh
i can do that
what i'm not good at is doing an updo
like this by myself
i
i'm very bad at it so every morning i
let a hairstylist chicken
do this for me
when i want to wear my jindal
i'll let you guys help me but in reality
i know how to do curls i know how to do
braids and all that but updos
i have like no skills with that
so thanks chickens for helping me
[Music]
you deserve a kiss by now so many
pinkies thank you
maxwell the first package in the
satisfied ancient maple leaf two five oh
one thank you for the red super chat
dino quiago was a long time coming and
it's 20 times cuter than what we could
have imagined
looking beautiful tangel and it's okay
if you're married to the job okay if we
love you lots let us keep kfb buy you
some non-alcoholic drinks next option
fest love the outfit
non-alcoholic drinks that's hard to find
just kidding actually i've never been to
an oktoberfest before
just like similar kind of
[Music]
gatherings festivals
where people wear
this kind of
traditional clothing but not the legit
oktoberfest
just because i
don't see a reason to go there and
yeah
don't feel that comfortable there either
i guess
i know
i to wear a candle out some time this
year though would be nice
[Music]
yeah
this is my inside only dental i can't
wear it outside when i step outside in
this dinner
[\h__\h] i can't say that because my stage
is outside
never mind this is my
youtube only channel when i step outside
youtube [\h__\h] i can't say that either
because i use it on twitch
this is my streaming only dandel
when i step outside a stream
or video
then
the candle dissolves
and
disappears
so i need a separate dental need to buy
one
to use it for other purposes
there we go
[Music]
took me a while thank you maple leaf
for pinky the cute person dankeshan
thank you
visual novels fan charlie duncan freak
fire thank you for the pinky whole life
d is deutsch
a is austria and ch is switzerland
dark and german means um ceiling and not
ceiling but the thing on top of a house
uh
[Music]
you always wanted to deal it looks so
super cute and amazing yes i really
wanted one
i'm so happy to have one now it's girly
and cute and feminine i love it
and tidy thanks for the pinky as well
again
another kiss for you too many pinkies
big swig thanks a little uh pinky
big sweet thanks for the pinky if this
is why chickens keep getting hurt and i
don't mind losing a wing or two because
goddamn my tantrum is the cutest one
there is also kind of glad i was right
with the dinner i was gonna eat a spicy
pepper if i lost that but really
you bathed with someone who
is it
does that mean someone else uh ate a
spicy pepper
[Music]
i wanna know
i'm gonna laugh at them
i wanna laugh at them
a bunny from college and i want me to
visit and that sounds fun
did you make them eat a pepper
or did they back out like the chicken
they are
aren't we all except me
i saved myself
[Music]
he ate a habanero isn't that like
something like a pepper too
nice
they actually did it all right
[Music]
fun you're doing like bets like that
with your
with your irl youtuber friends youtuber
watching friends that's fun
[Music]
will you still do german lessons on the
aeon channel
um i think yes
what i would like to do is like uh
german karaoke but
even unarchived i'm very restricted like
you know most german songs are
like they have this gamer thing
behind them
that makes me unable to sing their songs
um
but what we could do again is a anime
song singing in german
karaoke that's possible
that
could
even be archived i think
um
so stuff like that i might wanna
to fill up my german channel i might do
there and just
it really won't be used that much it's
just kind of to say hey i have a german
channel
maybe find some people
uh have some people find me who
specifically look for german speaking
youtubers and then i'm like oh
hello nice to meet you um
i want to play
like maybe
sometimes play a game in german
yeah i'm just i don't know german
whatever i don't know just sometimes but
not even weekly probably not even weekly
i don't think i can squeeze in
a german stream
weekly
but
maybe once every two to three weeks and
it might even get less in the future
when i'm thinking about it realistically
but yeah yeah
you guys maybe have to remind me
sometimes like hey kilo you haven't
i haven't streamed on your german
channel in a while
you have to remind me what i wouldn't
mind doing there is maybe fairy tale
asmr
i'll just say as asmr because i guess
you could call it that
just
reading grimm's fairy tale german
stories
there because
[Music]
you guys have been asking for me to do
it again for a while and you know i
don't feel so comfortable doing it here
on my channel here because it didn't
let's be honest it didn't get a good uh
how to say
interaction
it just felt like it wasn't there wasn't
much of a demand but on a german channel
it would make sense
reception yes reception
[Music]
stuff like that yes yes
we'll sit by a cozy
fireplace
and read some stories
[Music]
welcome to the membership thank you
thank you thank you
[Music]
yes yes yes that is true when i stand in
the bavaria the hotel girls actually
wore something like this so it still
comes as an office outfit yeah i think i
mentioned this if you stay
in
like countryside hotels in bavaria or
austria uh chances are very high that
the off like the attire of the staff
will be
a toned down
version of a dandel
uh
that's so fancy as the one i'm wearing
but the angelus yes um or even in like
boutique hotels
in the city doesn't have to be
countryside but some boutique hotels
or just uh hotels that are more um
orientated
to catering to tradition
and restaurants too
often have staff wearing dinners
so that's why it can definitely be
professional attire
[Music]
thank you you look so cute then we'll
kill it looks amazing and gorgeous oh
thank you i know
[Music]
really happy like it thanks for coming
and supporting me on that important day
thank you
i'm flattered
thanks also for a red super chat
this is also exciting it is this outfit
the rails are always so exciting
i'm happy so many people came
check it out i was nervous about that
too but thank you everybody
naked chicken dancing skye duncan
pinky so cute
you're cute too in your helicopter
so cute that helicopter chicken
i want to see that image in big i don't
think i ever saw it in big
it looks like the perfect fit
custom made helicopter so cute
gigi duncan random collusion thanks for
the pinky best wishes for your
healthcare i love the outfit thank you
yeah since then
my health has been like changing every
[\h__\h] day
uh but currently it's
more or less stable
thank you very much for your kind words
ah it's on sale the helicopter is on
sale you can buy a helicopter at studio
neko maga whoa
you look utterly stunning kiana once
again my heart pounds and refuses to be
still in the presence of such entrancing
beauty
the outfit and you are both so perfect
thank you for this visual treat i'm very
blessed
oh my my my mind you're welcome
yes thank me thank me
thank you very much for your support
very sweet glad you like it but how can
you not like uh an outfit like this
again a pinky
did you just not want any kisses this
time because you keep on sending the
pinkies
you feel
feel embarrassed
to get a kiss from me
you've been running away
escaping
trying to escape the kisses no no you
cannot
god oh thank you
[Music]
you probably feel better about sending
two pinkies and one red because you feel
like you spent less money than when you
get a red one
okay isn't it that's okay i only sent
her a pink super chat it might have been
five pink super jets but that's
better than five red super chats or so
[Music]
now even if you know deep in your heart
it just feels
feels like you're spendless
[Music]
i would assume maybe
like
somewhere in your mind
[Music]
congratulations you made it you make it
if you fall in love with you and we felt
pretty damn bad
thank you
as expected i i knew it i warned you
guys i said you guys will follow up in
fall fall in love again
[Music]
i can see the future
yeah
thank you joe knight see us paulie thank
you for the red super chat ma
painting your new outfit is so cute the
best part i love is your hairstyle the
flowers viva luciana thank you yes
that's also i think my favorite part
yeah that's why i was so
so
um
accurate no not accurate what's the red
word canal
so picky so
[Music]
specific
precise yeah precise that's why i was so
precise about what i wanted to look like
oh for example also the you know those
slightly curled hairs on the side of my
face
originally hookah papa drew them
straight
and i said i want them to be curly like
this and have some loose strands
to make it look more natural and cute
and
wow
[Music]
yes
good call
i like the i'm still mirrored yes
[Music]
i like the curliness
yeah
nice touch thank you
i would agree
[Music]
so thank you cs
thank you
thank you mr casper
look at her powerful fun fact i actually
assumed this was a deal because of your
answer to an old super chat of mine so
ribbon lore
guess when you say you've married when
you say you've married a cutie in a
video game or collab like he said he
would literally mean it
i wish she was real
i wish i wish
[Music]
if only she was real
she's such a gorgeous
inspiring amazing woman
[Music]
yeah
we have to accept the reality
unfortunately
but thank you glad you liked it
[Music]
yes please draw more
tai chi thanks for the pinkie thank you
every other called thank you for the red
super chat time to look so cute but i'm
worried virgin youtube kun won't be able
to handle it great after canada and that
video was funny didn't expect it
you think youtube is a virgin
[Music]
i heard
youtube
has
been
involved with facebook and and then
cheated on facebook with google
and yeah now they live happily ever
after
youtube then google
yeah have you not heard
it was all over all over everywhere but
of course they control everything so
they
um deleted everything damage control
yeah i'm probably going to be um
deleted as well from the surface of the
earth for saying this
[Music]
spilling the tea
yourself
[Music]
how old is google
23 years okay well that's a little bit
um problematic okay
i don't know this funny is literally
says
netflix 24. netflix 24 years no [\h__\h]
way
no [\h__\h] way that
netflix hasn't been around a year longer
than google what is this why is that so
inaccurate
[Music]
um
that how old is netflix
what do you mean 24 years
because netflix male dvds they used to
what
i didn't know that
[Music]
that's their origin
that is interesting wait a second
[Music]
netflix is an american subscription
streaming series important launched in
august
1997 it offers a film and television
series library
[Music]
launch as male based rental business
until 2006
transition to training streaming
services 2007.
oh the logo looked so different before
[Music]
netflix offered a parental model for
each dvd produced monthly subscription
concept in september 1999. never heard
of netflix before that
it was it well known in america
i have the mailing service
[Music]
i used to run dvds for netflix what
it i think that's really only like n a
though
it didn't really
make waves until
after becoming a streaming service i
think
wow
pretty niche
not as popular as blockbuster
they still mail them now
that is so interesting i thought that
was a mistake by google
[Music]
well that explains a lot that explains
about
you know me hearing about netflix and
youtube having something together uh 24
years ago but i was like that must be
wrong because netflix wasn't even around
then
that must be wrong
made up
fake
[Music]
another pinky
thank you
anton m thank you for the pinky what
belated congrats on one million subs
[Music]
that's really late it's almost as if
you're slowpoke
did you forget to change your name to
slowpoke or something
thank you joe like
you could have just you know
congratulated me on more recent things
but no you you try to catch up to the
very
most recent
well not forgetting about the previous
things
wow
oy schneider
dun
[Music]
that's true
and you're loving off it suits you very
well this seems to be my second favorite
outfit for you nothing beats the empress
outfit can't wait to see you use it in
your future streams thank you yeah i'll
be using it a lot a lot a lot a lot
thank you very much
i guess you had to save up money or
something that's totally fine thank you
for your support thank you
paul ginda thanks for the pinky we're
getting closer to the end guys by the
way
more or less
even though i expected the dental to
look absolutely divine exquisite even
i'm really blown away right now and we
even get more german kiara content which
is an absolute win as well oh yeah
you're german speaking so you're one of
the
one of the people who are especially
happy about that i think
even if you don't need it because you
speak english too
i'm sure you will enjoy
my german content once it ever
is created
oh yeah one more thing i wanted to do is
like translated clips
um from my main channel
translate it into german
put it on my german channel
[Music]
and you guys can still watch them even
if you don't know german just because
clips are nice to watch
[Music]
thank you for the rest of the chat your
new outfit is so cute you have really
been on a roll lately i'm proud to call
you my aussie
okay
thank you very much i'm happy to be your
oshi it's an honor thank you
[Music]
looks insane with you congrats on the
new channel as well super hard for it
thank you
yeah yeah i i i won't let it be
forgotten for now it may be forgotten
but i'll eventually maybe i'll even do
like a actual debut stream i don't know
if i feel like it
because i did do a german debut before
it would basically just be repeating
that but maybe
maybe this once
i could actually get like new assets
because the thing about the real debuts
is i keep on using the old
original assets
to create a re-debut feeling
but for the german channel we could do a
debut
but like not a re-debut like a proper
new debut
with new assets new background
stuff like that
and yeah debuting a dinner yeah that's
like
one thing i was thinking is on my german
channel i am only
going to wear
the dandel and nothing else
that will be like my official outfit
over there
my default
yeah might as well do a debut i guess
yeah yo yo
i'll i i might do it um
fred's grow another red subject thank
you 10 to the work accidents for this
month have just doubled already
everything is on fire
now that i'm complaining of anything
that new dress looks amazing on you
especially the um button is it's very
cute very satisfying thank you
thank you oh [\h__\h] well then pull out the
[\h__\h] fire instead of sending me super
chats
what are you doing just standing there
typing
and looking at me
oh pull out the fire
action itchy thank you for the rest of
the chat my mouth is getting really
tired from moving
huh
bubba also congrats on the new outfit
kiara new channel
love you and i'm very excited for your
birthday stream thank you
i'll take it as a promise that you will
be there
thank you very much looking forward to
it
please don't everybody already you know
who has high expectations i feel like
and i feel in the end it will be great
but for now please please don't have too
high expectations
for now
because i feel pressured
actually
i'm scared to disappoint you guys so
please stop
expecting so much please
also like about my dancing
i didn't have that much time so
like some some
choreo is literally just like fiber
night and sparks
were literally just created by my
choreographer
like
in the past one month
[Music]
yeah keep your expectations low please
i'm nervous you're making me very
nervous
thank you though
actually
[Music]
there's still so many
you're so pretty i will watch your
german channel tend to talk in german so
cute thank you even though you don't
understand german you'll still watch it
thank you
i appreciate it
maybe you will
learn some things
take some german words with you and flex
it to other people
thank you mwah no i can't stop i'm going
to finish this
hi chiefs with the pinky dominic
thank you for that
yes time to learn german
maybelline thank you for the red super
chat we'll see you for a dance at the
may potential stay awesome
[Music]
that's already over it wasn't that on
the 1st of may if you're talking about
that big
big long
pole
[Music]
you'll have to wait until next year then
may paul
maple oh wait
i'm talking about the maple because
canada maple ah
he wrote on purpose probably
m a
y
p-o-l-e
i thought you were talking for some
reason i don't know why
when you were talking about the big big
polls that we put up on the 1st of may
and climb on top of
[Music]
it looks really cool though
yeah one of our cultures this on the 1st
of may
could put up it's actually called a tree
because it's just a really long long
long long long tree thingy with no
leaves like they cut up for everything
it's just like a pole but it's a tree so
it's called matri
[Music]
and then people will climb up there
and then there's also a tradition of
stealing
other villages
may trees
poles
and yeah
run away with them
hear people dance around them with
ribbons i don't know they might do that
here too
i haven't really seen one in a long time
because they're more on the countryside
[Music]
and i think it's more like children and
families like their parents and all that
really make use of it like the people in
between for like adults but have no
children
don't really do anything with it
[Music]
we dance around with ribbons here in the
uk that's cute
that's cute
[Music]
176. thank you for the pinky
hello boss thank you out for this
fantastic and extremely cute but i fear
that accidents will increase before i
miss the damn series
channel oh
that sounded like perfect german
do you speak german
[Music]
thank you sorry i'm losing my energy
but i appreciate every super chat thank
you
gd thank you for the pinky mate thanks
mate
love love the outfit so suit very much
so we gotta have a lot more accidents
now love you kiara viva
thank you love you too
no you're gonna be fine you guys are
invincible chickens
it's getting late yeah
i have a feeling i'm not gonna be
cooking huh
[\h__\h] it's sunday tomorrow [\h__\h] stress
me out
as long as i'm streaming i feel like i'm
in my safe bubble
[Music]
now
[\h__\h] someday
[Music]
foreign
you make me feel like the saddest drake
song out there
[Music]
are you a part of your safe space yes
yes
safe space yes
about
1 million terabyte
of safe space
i try to keep it empty
so that you all have space in it
miyako thanks for the pinky comment to
the nearest love yeah thank you love you
too
let's go
[Music]
that was funny really
jones you have such a cool name
such a cool name man thank you soon
thank you navida mini thanks for the
rest of the chat
oh my god kiara you look adorable i
freaking love the pastel colors yes
turquoise light blue and pink is one of
my favorite combos oh thank you wow
i'm happy you finally got the dental
outfit you always wanted i'm a big fan
of how it looks without the accessories
look even cuter oh really oh yeah right
now i actually am not wearing the the
hand cuff thingies
i forgot about those
[Music]
oh
there they are
yeah but no oh no no choker is nice too
no everything is like this oh i feel so
naked
i feel like
i'm at a farm now
this hairstyle
looks like i'm a milkmaid or something
yeah
[Music]
so common i'm like a commoner i'm like
an npc
i'm a [\h__\h] npc no
how low i've become
no
i'm pissing me
oh man
neck is weird without anything oh
maybe i'm glad that hookah papa just
like me
seems to like chokers
he adds chokers onto everything he draws
for me even even when i don't ask for it
[Music]
oh yeah the shadow doesn't move i just
realized i might want to get that fixed
[Music]
the shadow
of my chin
like it should move with me
didn't notice that
until now
[Music]
not so problematic though cause i'm
gonna mostly be wearing this anyway and
then i won't notice
this looks nice
actually
i guess i have to get used to
no flowers in my hair hairstyle
when i first take it off i'm like what
is this
naked
[Music]
anyway you look so proper really
anime grill necks are kind of weird
without something to distract from it
ah
keep swaying
i prefer the new flowers look
well too bad for you because i prefer
the more flowers
thank you
wait one more time
with hands
these ones
[Music]
nice
rob dankeshen william oliver 11 thanks
for the pinky so happy to see you in an
outfit dripping with your home culture
you look absolutely stunning in it and
congrats on 1 million you deserve it
thank you wait what 1 million oh wait
now i understand why people this is the
second person but now i understand why
they've been saying
congratulations because it was my my 1
million subscribers okay but it's like
ages ago
now i get it
ah
now it makes sense
[Music]
no i didn't realize
oh thank you merry fitness function
neo invisible mouth boosting every
number called thanks for the rest of the
chat
yeah legally not allowed to leave if we
keep super chatting you know you are
making me suffer right now abby
thank you
[Music]
i wrote this whole paragraph but i can't
just condense it to kiwa cute
i guess at this point i prefer the
message to be shorter
amazing new outfit also don't worry
about the ribbon
yeah okay thank you at least yeah most
of the time i'm not showing it anyway
[Music]
i am just ahead
thank you cruza
eric newstone
[Music]
i'm so close to being done
i'm curiosity do you know what the
others asked for for your muscle if
you're not to say it um like
i can't i'll leave it to them because
some of the things um
are not like done yet have been in the
works for a long time as far as i know
i think it's like really only me and
ahmed
who have gotten it
already
yeah so you have to wait for the other
ones
[Music]
hmm
i'm not sure i forgot what inna even
requested i don't remember
i remember good on kelly but i can't say
and moose thanks for the rest of the
chat
[Laughter]
you'll you'll understand i guess
probably once they show it i
think loving you outfit love you tantra
thank you moose thank you very much
yes love you too
[Music]
i mean why yeah whatever and stop
talking no
like even this outfit took like
quite some time
to prepare everything takes time guys
you know that's the ps5 no
ah she really needs a ps5 though
well i'm on years it's just as i said
takes time and kuda is just that fast
that they can't keep up
just can't keep up
i think sometimes
i think i've heard of like japanese
members even asking
for like um
music videos or something like that
and then
they don't even announce it as the one
million gift so
that might be what's happening too
like something could have been released
and you don't know it's that because
they didn't clearly say
that's what it was for
[Music]
and jake read for
foreign
[Music]
outfit and thank you for the german sub
channel thank you too
for your support i suppose you
subscribed already thank you very much
we're done
hallelujah
[Music]
i'm distracted sorry
thank you for the clapping wow it feels
good wow wow wow
thank
[Music]
without the feathers uh feathers without
the flowers in my hair it's even less
noticeable that i'm flipped
[Music]
because i think the hair is
pretty much
symmetrical
[Music]
okay
i
need a break
guys
and
[Music]
this was the last stream of the week
tomorrow no wind waker
it do be
a busy day for me tomorrow
and
um
yeah
i will
see you next week
at some point
not on monday
either i think still busy
i don't i don't know to be honest when
i'll see you again
it will have to be a little bit
spontaneous
so
[Music]
schedule
i don't think so
i think no schedule
[Music]
okay
please just yeah stop my twitter
uh
yeah keep notifications on
have an open eye everywhere
have eyes on your back everywhere on
your feet
you must put your eyes everywhere
chicken eyes
become one big chicken with a million
wobbly bubbly eyes
like jimmy
yes
[Music]
become a tower
make a chicken tower
with eyes everywhere
[Music]
but it was nice it was nice today
hanging out with you guys
chilling with wind wanker
hmm we got some we got some stuff done
and when we go very productive in those
three hours
next time we're going to finish it
and yeah become sauron
thank you sharing my beloved chimpkins
for
waiting for me during these busy times
i know it's rough for some of you
no
it's rough for me too
oh
but then we'll be back to normal soon
enough so
please wait please wait hold the line
please
i'll see you in a while
until then i might be putting out some
videos
here and there
uh
yeah i have a cow carrot video coming up
so wait for that too
it's gonna be good it's gonna be good
all right then and in german we say
alf
[Music]
wow
thank you for watching today hope you
had a good time
what's up
[Music]
oh i got used to this hairstyle now
i like it
[Music]
it grew on you yeah literally did
because hair grows on my head
huh
[Music]
funny
do
[Music]