[Music]
hello
[Applause]
[Music]
hello Mary marry Among Us among Among Us
wait I don't want to get married to
among welcome every everybody to the uh
Christmas or Holan holiday Among Us
stream we have gathered here today with
so many lovely cute girls and we're
going to have fun choking and stabbing
each other
right let's go awesome well we're going
to um do it without proximity chat by
the way guys uh because you know we have
some first timers here I think it's
Advent girls's first time among
using first timers
that's we're not yeah we'll find out how
they act when when they're imposter we
can't tell yet like for others maybe we
already know a tell but for these
newbies we don't know what is their tell
maybe that's maybe you could tell us
would you be so kind your introduction
to tell me what your tell
is please nah you got to find that out
inform classified they need a little
cash money up front first I'll try well
okay then let's start with introductions
let's start with the only one who's a
real astronaut here
Amy h Hello Amilia Watson number one
astronaut
detective yeah I like Among Us so I'm
excited to play Let's Go
can out because maybe there's some new
viewers at this point who don't
understand why is am able to wear her
own clothes in the game and why am I
wearing P's clothes and is wearing man's
clothes am do you want to explain uh yes
we have uh we had a collab with Among Us
where you could get a few uh Hol live
outfits and items in the Among Us shop
but I don't think it's available anymore
was kind of a li time
thing time too bad if you miss out me
and are P right
now was a keyboard slam you guys are
actually you guys are in a room
okay okay I thought you just slammed the
keyboard the code do keboard slam I know
that's what it looks like code looking
like a slam no you're giving them hints
you and slam welcome to the slam jam
please join there we go
who is calm
spam all right well I guess
[Laughter]
that's oh you have color
too yum she had a Spam color that was
amazing nice box oh while we're at's uh
you know bullying her for her name k we
please introduce yourself so we know
that's really you okay if you insist me
it's me Mory Kip hold live english's
hardworking
Shinigami uh I'm in a place with very
terrible internet so I can't stream my
POV but I'm very excited to be here with
all of these lovely ladies as the
sheriff completing my tasks and making
sure that we win the day let's go yes
you wouldn't kill
anybody
Cal I
guess but yeah I'm so happy you're
joining even though you can't like
stream properly thank you so much dead
beats they trained me well I wanted to
show off my new skills that the dead
beats have oh yeah Meers fairly recently
oh we got a watch out she's good at the
game oh W only thanks the dead beasts
you just ask us how you kill people in
this
game do that okay I guess I didn't help
at all that you played it recently it
was
unhelpful well okay moving on to funa
where is she where is she I can't find
her oh hi you can't vote me as the
Imposter if I'm hiding
right English promise hello hello I'm
here and I does it feel does it feel
like normal now like it still feels
weird to me to hear that introduction
promise yeah I think so fresh still it
is it is still pretty fresh but I like
it fres boat yeah fresh off the boat not
boats I feel like everyone's traumatized
by boats recently
true what's with this current Trend in
the whole life English of watching
school days what's going
on why why is
everyone told me about the tree and
there's a family
stair why why do you like it there's a
staircase did you know there's a
staircas I know there's a stair I know
now
narissa
I have no idea what these girls are
talking about good I'm so confused I
wish I didn't know it's too cursed yeah
it's nice that everybody is having fun
school days and all that fun a jolly
season it is great pie of Cinema yeah
yeah all right Iris our number one
Christmas lover hello yes you're number
one Christmas lover here hiis it's Iris
from H live English promise
your
uh I love this game but I I I really
suck at being imposter but yeah so so
yosu yeah but I'll do my best do you are
you really bad at it I don't remember I
I was horrible imposter last time I play
this cross her finger she gets imposture
maybe you just need a better mate to
work with cuz you're dumb d m oh
bit of a poopy
head I think there's no use what you
talking about the lobby will fall apart
it's no problem but let's take our
time okay yeah by the way have you guys
speaking of Iris have you guys all seen
the yesterday and today's episodes of
the Holo Ian Advent calendar cuz Iris
was very involved in them I was very
involved in them
yes and they were both in
3D both in 3D
space y so Iris why did you do it uh oh
it's cuz you know we needed some light
to bring up the Christmas spirit you
know mhh what better light than actual
fire right yeah oh that makes sense you
know it was my whole plan so that I I
could become the Christmas tree in order
to become the Christmas tree you needed
to burn the actual Christmas true true
wait what's this about burning Christmas
trees that's kind of ir
it is a master plan it's pretty lit
yes it was
fire indeed fire fire light the fire
fire fire light the fire fire light the
fire fire fire light okay uh everybody's
uh joining in again in the lobby I think
I'm coming I got my name I freed Cal
spam he doesn't exist
anymore she's real spam I'm sad is it
going to hide the code if I have
streamer mode on I'm scared yes yes yes
hidden for me it does people self
introduction please hi uh bom you I'm Co
you sparkling Gem of Hall English Advent
and today I'm a space Rock but that
doesn't mean you're allowed to Stellar
Stellar me out of the ship so I am not
sus I am
nice wow okay
good you can be
nice no no that doesn't work here
doesn't
here man so you have to prove yourself
prove the truth you can't fool us people
you're sus dang already you're already
sus all
started I think I think it's her yeah I
think it's gu it's it's definitely
it's okay let's move on
to
[Music]
pleas your voice okay
moo sometimes I become a dragon
sometimes you know but as long as you
know I'm not Chihuahua I'm not Hua I'm
Mak there we go and together we make the
best crew mate you know dogs create not
it's kind of unfair it's kind of unfair
yeah if you imposter it's to
it's extra
imposter I think I think we should vote
them out right away every
time place well let's not but indeed as
a crew mate they might be very helpful
cuz it's two brains for one I guess I
guess who's on the keyboard who's
controlling I'm the legs you're the
brains the pointer
finger yeah nice looking forward to
teamor I'll be nice to you one one day
they will play separately but today is
not the
day isn't this game a mobile it maybe
somebody could play on mobile
I I there is is work on
this well okay and then then we
saw imposter hi
darling devilish Diva RAV C cute I'm an
impostor today because I'm pretending to
be M and I
guess oh my go fake it till you make it
fake it till you make
it we're we're a nice couple n aren't we
how ironic I should be running away from
you I don't want your child
nevera
Lu even if honeyworks made a song about
our child I don't want
it okay and
then
please this is
oron from H live English Pro what H live
English
promise um please don't arrest me I'm
going to be a very good egg for today uh
cuz even if I want to be an impostor I
never get it I ever get it so you can
trust me I believe her I trust her 100%
I trust yes I trust her 100% I trust
every what are the chances that she
going get imp I look so kind pretty none
of none of us will get imposter probably
yeah probably none of us that's how it
works how many how many imposters are we
doing I set it to
two cuz we're n Deputy I don't know
should I do free I don't
know
good and I I have in case you're
interested uh two long tasks and five
short tasks uh as well as two common
tasks I don't remember what common tasks
were that's
suspicious why you you don't remember
are you
impostor oh yeah cuz imposters don't do
tasks well I it's it's long they added
rolls or something right like can do
stuff now or
something like rolls rolls oh yeah
wasn't there something besides crew mate
now like um uh like those are like the
Spy or something like that
not this okay I don't know how does that
work though I don't I've never played
that
before wait yeah there's four rols there
I don't know you girls can probably see
them in the settings uh on the on the
computer here there's a scientist who
can access a portable vitals panel so
they can check at any point of time if
there is somebody dead so they always
see the status of the crew and then
there's an engineer who can use the
vents even though they're not an
impostor but then you might be sused and
you have to be like I'm not the impostor
I just vent because I can it's pretty
cool and then the guardian angel uh is
the ghost of the very first one of us
that
dies is that how it works the first
person that dies yeah something like
that the garden the G Angels the ghost
of the first Dead crewmate they can
temporarily shield and protect other
living crew mates oh so I guess if
you're the first one that dies you
become the guardian angel and then you
can protect somebody else so that they
don't die yeah if you do it properly and
well timed you'll be able to prevent
imposters from killing their victim
sounds amazing me throwing so that I can
become the guardian
angel
a already
are wow and then there's a shape shifter
who can who can change the appearance
and disguise themselves as other crew
mates Shape Shifter how did you do that
though that just confuses everyone is
the shape shifter The Imposter or are
they different supposed to make the
Imposter harder to find too because then
you know the impostor can say I'm the
engineer oh no I'm the shape you know
please I promise I'm not a murderer yeah
it doesn't say that it's only impostor
but why would a crew do this I don't
know let's turn that one off but I like
the other ones yeah should I should I
keep them or should I think Shape
Shifter is impossible them oh it is okay
yeah it just doesn't say so there's only
one imposter is only one impostor The
Shape Shifter is that how it works oh I
can set how many there will be I
say I can say we want two or I can say
we I want one or zero I can set it in
the
settings but if I do one then only one
of the uh imposters will be Shape
Shifter but only 50% chance the one will
be oh yeah I can I can make it higher
too that we have one for sure I feel
like it's the default is good right it's
probably bad the default okaya okay okay
default then let's keep the rolls then
let's go we're going straight did you
introduce
yourself before
we before before we go um can we have
the visual tasks off because if we have
it on it might be too easy visual tasks
off yes very good okay and before we
start I'm Tak I organized this thing the
logos and the thumbnails are
commissioned by me so
thank don't kill me because I I pay for
this okay
don't we we mute right we M oh it closed
your chat byebye byebye
byebye okay I've closed you guys wait
I'm a scientist let's
go I love
science everyone's okay oh I I don't
know this map at
all
there's o
o wait I don't remember how to play
Among
Us everybody
okay there's mushrooms what's
this oh
wait I changed the
outfits I am so very
confused I'm scared why is
what I'm I don't trust
you
moo the M oh I can't go to the mining
pit is anyone dead
yet we can I not check the vitals am I
not the
scientist
anymore this is so scary I just want to
run away from everyone and do my
tasks
what no
[Music]
no I'll miss you byee the really she the
only real astronaut you know what that
means we don't have a chance of getting
back to our own
Planet no unbelievable so who saw Watson
I didn't see her at all I didn't see her
I oh I didn't see her while sheive who
reported just now me I did tell us about
it did tell us about it where was the
body so I was going around
Communications um trying to figure out
the mushrooms and what not and I went
down uh the the little zipline and then
in the storage room Amy was dead the
storage room storage
room we saw around the musroom
you saw
me oh wait so F was also in the storage
area no no we were at the mushrooms and
we were having problems with that and
crony Senpai was around and then crony
Senpai went down but Senpai was there
too Moco was chasing me around and I
left I don't know what's going on I have
mushroom problem yeah I had like a meat
problem I don't know like I suddenly
turned into like a a lighter pink and
there was like a chunk of meat chasing
me didn't get the puff and then they
change into people or something like
that do is that just an effect to freak
you out or does it do something I don't
I don't know I think it I think the the
the mushroom like if you touch it or
something something um it hides the the
people so you can just like kill them
and run away and they be my skin or
something like that
why oh did why do you know that hot yeah
yeah my skin got swapped as well yeah me
too skin a wizard and then I had a
little worm next to me for a moment and
then poof it was gone and the light was
back
on but I I don't know what what goes on
in this m I don't know I feel like I
trusted crony Senpai and now I feel like
I don't trust crony
Senai I will say I passed by and I was
actually running away from crony cuz it
felt like she was chasing me see you
where were you you
[Laughter]
[Music]
wait
wa
there Viking okay bye everybody bye okay
goodbye I I don't know the fact that she
had like her own like
um oh oh oops oops oops oops
oops okay now I don't trust anyone who
voted for
crony what is this where is this Arrow
leading me
fix
it I don't trust
FM okay this that's nor I don't know
what I can do with this
information where am I if I just hide
from everyone and never see anyone I
will be fine
right I'm a
self I'm leaving don't trust you
don't trust
you
oh wait wait iisa like 5 seconds ago no
is in the South part of the map with the
lab in the hallway I don't know this
map um wait how do I look at my oh I saw
narissa around like next to the
greenhouse when I was oh yeah yeah yeah
Green House yeah she's above the green
house I saw her walking around I didn't
see anyone near I didn't see anyone else
yeah I only saw narissa when we went up
to Communications and that was the last
time I saw
her we didn't see anyone except senite
and I think she's good scared us I ran
away instantly cuz I will be honest I
don't trust anyone who voted for crony
in the last round seems like the
imposters were trying to get her out
because they knew she was wait wait wait
wait wait is
dead there was a double
kill K us tell us before huh huh that's
something important when we're going to
start yeah I'm about to kill her who did
it there's only there's only three crew
mates left among
us two
but crony could have been an imposter
though honestly like I don't know did
you guys turn
off oh it doesn't say oh yeah I wouldn't
put it behind her if she self-recorded
because look at her look at her um her
icon like why why are you so suspicious
of her for no
reason I feel like you wouldn't be this
suspicious unless you were the impostor
and you're sure I'm not I swear to God
I'm not I I I I said out right that I
saw like narissa passed by just 5
seconds ago before I I didn't see you
when I saw narissa I didn't see you
though oh no I was I passed by her when
she was going greenhouse and I I'm
currently at the meeting room I went the
opposite direction that's why I think
she was like stuck that biu and Iris
Senpai are suspicious I think so too
wait why SAR what were you
doing I was walking around I was in the
lap the lap wait where's my the lab and
then wish it was on like the top 10
seconds I'm vo
bio I don't have
enough I
IR I swear it's not me it is not me
uhoh oh my God was
enough did we get him yeah oh my God
no that was so fast
that was a sweet I thought we won yeah
tomb oh no man you didn't even notice I
was dead
guys literally P me and biu killed me
immediately
a good team report good team you two
that was pretty
funo Tombstone impressive I was
surprised well you know what we learned
from that because call was pretty quiet
Su out was the quiet quiet
on always theet fooled me cie fooled me
too I was just confused cuz like my
voting was super rush I was like wait
why am I suspicious all of a sudden
every just literally just the Spider-Man
everybody pointing
at it was peer pressure peer pressure
you don't have the vote
we don't have toot I just F like I need
toot Iris out that was
so I thought it needed to be like
majority vote to even get anyone off I
thought only two people vot to kill
me was only a little bit of us left so
two was enough yeah cuz people had
already
died we're strong at this we're good
pretty good doing our tasks weren't you
the ones
who
I guess we're S no matter what we can't
be
helped well that was a good first round
let's let's try to be should we turn
extended voting time on oh sure of
course yeah uh it's currently 90 seconds
should we do
120 at least a little at least 120 120
is the
max good says apparently we can vote or
skip the vote if you're not confident
like who it
is pretty
confident talking certainty there pretty
confident voting out all the pretty
confident well now you should now you
know then you maybe cannot trust your
confidence yeah true
enough all right then let's start
another
round
even though this is really fun here
thank you crony for finding
this see you on the other side bye bye
guys bye I'm my crew mate again oh I'm
besides again
yay just got checked everyone is still
alive let's go over
here I don't oh no am I about to be
murdered did I do it how do you do it it
oh no oh
oh I've done
it oh wait there's one down here that's
a and Iris I know to where I've seen
people
Pizza did I do
ity it's just like out of
wild it's ready it's ready it's ready
it's ready it's going to
burn okay there Isa bi
boo we're gaming
together how many do I have to
destroy okay I trust bioo implicitly she
did about the same time that I did
oh have I done that I'm
sorry I'm sorry for what I've
done let's go to the
reactor is it bad to just be by myself
oh
no a is dead should I report this
probably
again a has
died oh
no uhoh how do I where's
the where's the emergency
meeting but I don't know where she
died I did see
[Music]
her call it how do I call it
oh no not again come on yeah
come
pleas what I'll break it down for you oh
please I did all my tasks you guys could
see me I think some of you saw me
watering things in the the mushroom
place I moved some storage around
roasted some marshmallows went up to do
my tasks in the communication room and
what do I find Watson dead middle of the
floor I didn't see anyone leave though
was anyone near Communications
recently communication top right you
take a little like a what is it a wire
zipline zipline I
see I'm far from it a little bit but we
didn't see much I
just yeah I was just in the jungle
area yeah I know there was there was
like oh oh okay these white white things
are oh okay yeah the line you can go up
and down but yeah I wasn't there yet um
in the bottom right um there was a lot
of shape shifting I don't know who is
who what happened with that the mushroom
is that the mushroom stuff working well
everybody everybody got a skin shift
right yeah it's confusion so that we
don't know who is who and then we can't
prove like oh that person was there or
whatever but we all look different like
not like each other right was not sheep
shifting yeah no it's just the mushroom
power is that somebody doing it or is
that oh by the way yeah I just want to
say I haven't used it yet but I am the
engineer mushroom it does it
okay I can vent but I'm not the The
Imposter just saying I didn't use it yet
though I wonder recently was anyone
around upper engine Lookout or mining
pit because the impostor may have tried
to escape by going down the ladders I
will check it out I was walking that way
but I didn't see
anyone okay I've been down over in the
left area for the whole time doing my
tasks so I haven't even gone I haven't
been up there yet I have Tas and
communication like I was going to go up
I'm currently passing I was passing by
the green house I was going to go up
but you didn't see anybody run past no I
didn't hard to tell still hard to
tell but people was kind of
quiet just saying actually bio passed by
me and didn't kill me
so me this is the first time I'm doing
Tas I can tell you I've been doing water
with narissa and then I did the
marshmallow thing
and the video game I shot
asteroids and I haven't been up there
yet so I I do have TK up
there okay we'll see we'll see evidence
inconclusive but keep your eyes open
yeah maybe don't don't go alone don't go
around alone guys I don't trust
anybody we don't need a
buddy all right on the other
[Music]
side is everyone going down here I guess
I have a task in the lab oh wait it's
over
here I feel like I'm too single-mindedly
focused on my tasks and I'm
also not telling anyone that I'm the
scientist cuz I'm afraid they'll think
it's
suspicious mushroom mushroom oh I can do
this
Crystal
vitals okay
just
checking hey hey
hey I don't trust anyone who wants to
stand so close
ah
ah oh there's Kiara there's
Callie
oh
oh everybody looks different now I can't
see anything
who is
this oh it's
Callie how are the vinals I feel like
someone's dead
oh I knew she was innocent she was the
only one I
trusted was a little suspicious though
she was I passed her going down the
ladders from communication to the lower
part she I her maybe went up the
communication where' you find her so I
was going up the ladder to the
communication and I didn't really see
her body but um I saw the the vent which
is the plant kind of opening up and then
closing so they vented to vent yeah they
vented to wherever it is from
Communications oh does anyone know where
where the vents from Communications
connect they go anywhere
right I think all vents can only usually
I don't know in Old Maps usually vents
only connect to certain other see I
should have checked and then I could
have told you but too bad no
idea I I can kind of say I think crony
is not self-reporting at least because
like I feel like I was I was running
around with her a little bit alone she
could saw yeah and she didn't and then I
saw Cali running around I I think we
were alone for a little bit but she may
have been on cool down as well but she
yeah she was coming down from that air
she was she was coming down from that
area yeah I told you I crossed paths
with her oh yeah okay but yeah and Cory
said someone vented
[Music]
H where were you a good question we were
at the the beach we're just kind of
going around but we don't really
understand I don't know what's going on
the map here we're just it'll show you
where you are oh tab yeah hit tab the
map will pop up there's also the map
icon on the top map icon right yeah the
top right a there's a settings IC map
but I don't understand it it has a lot
of marks on it yeah a lot of marks that
is that is it exclamation
marks h a lot of marks on it it have
some x's on it um I'm curious
not the marks I mean I don't see so many
marks on my map yeah what does an
imposter see maybe does a previous
impostor want to tell us what they saw
like Kelly yeah KY I saw some x's with
circles on time I click them
[Music]
sabotage a lot of marks on the
screen marks
I'm do you have anything to say to
defend yourself we just doing our
tasks if you were doing your task there
wouldn't be so many marks on the screen
would there
be goodby could do it I couldn't
theer b b by
[Music]
B
oh I hope we don't regret that yeah they
could have just been
confused notable crony skip the
vote uhoh what's going
on oh There She Goes me
too this
02 9 6 9
8 9 3 5
29 office is not
active
POA
how don't kill me don't kill
me I don't
understand okay off it's not itive do we
have to do both or
something
uhoh we need
power I guess these are just my tasks oh
I'm doing
it office not active oh I can't use my
vitals oh wait is someone going to the
one down
here maybe I should should go back up
narissa I hope you're not the
impostor oh 02
oh mining pit hello
everyone
oh oh you
can my FPS gaming
who who's dead cie
wait I just saw her like yeah I saw her
I feel like I just saw her too I feel
like there were a bunch right underneath
the the
ladder the the left
ladder you can check the map you can
check the map and see exactly where the
greenhouse like close to the green house
yeah wasn't she just with me at around
like yeah I saw everyone at
communications and I was getting some
stuff done there and the and also the
lookout and then I went down and I saw I
gu she moved
fast and then
died is there anyone around there I'm in
the lookout right now I'm in the mining
pit I was around I think when everyone
was
around oh we all went to Communications
home yeah everyone like uh everyone
except uh who was it like R Rissa and
FAA uh I think they were around like
Communications and like Lookout and then
everyone else went to the other coms
um I am sorry FAA but it seemed you were
being just um you know a little very
cautious I don't know if you were
careful about being stack killed but
moved away from the the radio like where
everyone was trying to fix it oh that's
well you needed to go do the other thing
right to fix it I was the first one
there in the radio and I tried to put in
the code but I think you have to put in
a second
code yeah also I had two tasks that I
did in
Communications oh okay I went over and
did them cuz I was I was in Lookout I
was putting the code in I think it was
the first who arrived and then nothing
was happening so I I thought I would go
to the other one and I saw cie was like
doing the code at that point as well so
she was like she already arrived and
then I left her alone there and I was
about to go up to the other
communication thingy but then uh it was
already fixed so then I went back and I
saw I think I saw crony again or so yeah
but I didn't see fauna and I didn't see
Iris all I saw you Kiara lad saw all of
you guys I don't know I I saw all of you
guys' Communications I I was I was with
fa alone for a while and she didn't kill
me yeah I saw Marissa go down go down I
didn't I was going to the green house
down where are you right now um I ended
up in the lookout because I got lost and
I was very
confused aren't we
all I'm a little suspicious of crony cuz
she didn't vote for Fu moo she
we have time and we're running out of
but I don't know if I'm suspicious
enough to vote
yeah I don't know either I'm going to
skip you're going to skip
but skipping no
we good luck crew
mates we got
this is no one going to the mining pit
oh no
I need to do my my
tasks
uhoh I don't know if it's good to be
alone I feel like I'm very
suspicious maybe I should be using my
science Powers there's five is that
normal oh my
[Music]
goodness
oh
Kiara I say a respectful distance
away I go to the
mines oh it's here it's
here and
here back in the M there's
more swinging arm pickax from side
to no
no don't kill me oh there's more maybe
she's just doing the same
task oh creepy it sounds like it's
laughing I was so
sus okay I'm done
you
stuck hang out with
Iris everyone's still
alive I hope she doesn't feel like I'm
chasing
her she might feel like I'm
chasing is she G to call oh oh
[Music]
uh hello hello help I think n is trying
to kill me ah you are so I can't believe
you I was not I checked everyone's
vitals and I decided to go back to the
meeting area canell and I saw her and I
got a little scared so I ran back but
then she chilled so I thought it was
cool but then she hit the emergency
meeting button much my surprise no the
thing is there's a little bit of a
backstory I was running around and the
only back
story my T what do you mean
backstory I was running around I was I
was you know I I I was running around
crony alone she didn't kill me I was
running around fauna alone she didn't
kill me and both of those I kind of
fought were sus and then I found you and
you kind of followed me and now I think
if it's not cron if it's not F I didn't
even follow you what do you mean I ran
into you and then I ran back to the
meeting area you are so fake
K I was also around crony and she did
not kill me either yeah even though she
could have and as I was doing tasks I
could have killed crony too and I didn't
which I would have if I had the
opportunity to if I well tell me
everybody tell me Iris uh and tell me
FAA what are the remaining tasks that
you have I'm done with cks and I
was yeah I saw yeah like I was chasing
you Iris I was kind of scared I was kind
of scared you were like stick to me like
little time yeah I have I have a task to
do at the dock okay and I have one at
the cafeteria then do it and then we win
task win let's go guys we have to do it
also I think people who are done with
the tasks can um follow let just wait in
the meeting area or follow yeah I mean
we have to do the tasks we can't just
wait in the meaning area no no no like
people who are done with the test can
follow
can I I think I do think narissa is a
little bit Nissa you and me Let's Stay
Together if I'm de with you no we're
stay together you or not we're staying
together now I'll actually tag along
with you guys that's okay just to see if
you okay still safon is there wait then
maybe you two are the imposters no I'm
done with my tasks it's a thing so they
want to kill me it is kind of scary oh
my God I didn't kill you when you were
around yeah what the oh you two didn't
kill each other because you're both
te you could come with me and IR why you
pending it on the blue women yeah let's
just all stay together and we'll see
what the blue women do follow Iris does
anyone else have task no I'm all done oh
yeah we should follow Iris we should
pressure her follow Iris yeah let's
follow yeah yeah you can totally follow
me nice hey who voted for me H me you
wait am I getting okay okay good
good you better you little love you
k please don't kill me
okay
okay everybody's here are we going to
stack kill don't stack kill but you
know okay why is narissa now following
wait I'm it's fine maybe
H is she
stuck
oh oh we did it
y task win who was it my T excuse me I
was it was
task who was the
impost though I wonder who was
it was Iris and
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
Iris doing I'm sorry I was supicious of
you fa so I'm sorry I was suspicious of
you Iris didn't kill Iris why didn't you
kill me we together for so long I wanted
I wanted to keep someone on my side I
see and because crony was susing fun in
the beginning I was like maybe I should
keep her on my side and kill crony
instead and like I I saw that Iris was
uh going into the same room as uh
narissa was so I was kind of waiting
outside the room to see she saw I was
like oh I think she's S I was trying to
kill I was trying to kill you actually
um I when you were inside the lab I was
I was following you and I was going to
kill you but then I noticed you were
moving weirdly and you were like running
away and then Rissa came comes in right
away like oh never mind I can't kill you
here up went back I think I was playing
a little bit too cautiously but um so
difficult there's only there's only me
that's all I saw I was I was worried
like it was still pretty good
yeah that was still impressive yeah I
can't I can't believe you suspected me
I'm was
panicking
panicking well it ends well hopefully
when we're together alone in the males
nothing I won't kill
you don't drown me in the ocean please
we're missing moly Mo
yeah oh sorry I was stuck let me just
I'm here sorry join us um
I don't want to like you know make any
hard rules because you know you just
kill whoever is conveniently there but
please do not kill am right away next
round just poor taste you being a
ghost no no no we need our we need our
space so out to do her job kill me first
I love being the
ghost ghost is no pressure yeah no
price okay we complete I changed one
thing I changed that the votes uh you
can't see who voted
for trying to vote someone
El oh boy let's
go see you later
bye
crewmate there are two imposters
imposters Among Us I'm not the scientist
anymore
no anybody go in here yes we
are it's so
heavy who thr away tungston cubes in the
trash
Oh don't kill me Kiara don't do it don't
do it don't kill me don't kill me don't
kill me don't kill me don't kill
me
is that a task should just by the Herman
Miller
chair oh what's going on over
here okay no funny business happening on
my
watch no funny business all
right
bioo and am were
together they're still
together I guess I'll
go I feel like I'm so suspicious cuz I'm
always
alone I'm so shocked every
time hello oh for a moment I thought you
were dead
again no
no well all right hope is dead I just
saw her alive like less than 30 seconds
ago so it must have just happened I just
found it in the meeting room but I was
up in the drop ship you looked at the
map and then I went down and I found her
body there and biu was up there and
fauna was up there and biu looked like
she came from down below so I'm a little
sus austral you because I knew no one
would kill you so I thought it' be safer
with you down I like the story but fun
was following the both of us so so I'm
kind of s ofun I was just making sure no
funny business was going
on I saw Iris alive like less than 30
seconds before she was found dead like I
it felt like like 10 seconds before so
I'm I'm like What's Happening that was a
really fast like pass by in that area it
was like bioo and fauna and that's it I
think in that area specifically you see
anyone like coming from that
direction I
saw storage room and then I was using
the zip line and like wasn't taking the
zipline up with me
yet oh Well B would you like to defend
yourself
why I was following Amy because I no one
was going to kill Amy so I thought Amy
was the safest bed saw you didn't she
not following her but coming from a
different direction no I was following a
this entire time you follow you
entire I was running away from you so I
didn't always see you but I was
following you the entire do you want to
kill her why are you follow
her this okay I've T I've done one task
so far it was asteroids I haven't done
the rest because I was following yeah
the asteroids the video game you do
asteroids in the last one to yeah I have
what is the as
like maybe she has her fa I went
straight to Communications I mean I will
do
my can I skip for please I I don't know
the last time too I don't want to die
again by the way Iris I don't know if
you know but you mut oh it's because
she's dead oh never
mind
but she is dead I just wanted to make
sure she joins the conversation you
know could help us out if I die it's or
fa Su one of them out if I
go not me bye bye boo this is the last
time I'm following I didn't vote
for I didn't her I voted I just
skipped didn't vote for you people it
wasn't me oh thank you I just
like what you mean byebye
people we
bye I feel like it could have been an N
self-report I saw Iris alive like 2
seconds ago it felt like but I don't
know I feel like I'm chasing
everyone I'm not
sus I can't it can't be slow
enough who else is here cron is
here it's VA I watched her kill FL oh
oh
knew I knew it what me I knew it
dead maybe a shape shifter maybe that's
a shape shifter no that makes it so much
worse I know it's not bi boo because I
went down because I saw bi boo pass us
we were both waiting to get into the
kitchen because last round Fu Moko and I
were frying fish together right so as I
was waiting I went to get cuz I was like
Advent together strong
and it was right in front of the
the where the death just happened and I
saw someone running up to the spash zone
so where was everybody and don't
lie wait you found which which of the
two bodies did you find I don't I don't
know where I don't know where okay then
I have something to add I was just up at
the very top of the
communications and there was crony and
there was fauna first there was FAA and
me and was joined I left
there was only crony can you confirm
this crony um after I was uh doing the
ladder task I went down to the zip line
again after that was done so I didn't
really see you saw K up there yeah I saw
Kiara and fauna up there and then after
I was done with the ladder I went down
the
zipline and I couldn't see anything else
aside from that maybe someone vent I'm
not sure cuz it's kind of
maybe youed
oh I mean I
know I my Ali really quick and I saw bio
and we were alone and she didn't come
after me or anything but I was in the
Splash Zone in the beginning I collected
shells and then I left okay where were
you though at the time of the
murder I went up to stor it just
happened I reported it immediately yeah
I I know I went to Splash Zone and I
collected the shells and then I saw bio
and she didn't hurt me and then I went
back to storage okay and then crony FAA
and kiata were over in Communications
yeah so Watson where were you I was at
the
laboratory laboratory I I am SS of am
because Iris was around I'm also of and
am yeah I am too and now so now I'm sus
it's trying to vote someone off no cuz
the last the last murder the everyone
who was present we that it wasn't fa now
and obviously iris is dead so it's only
you or bio but I know where was the time
of the murder foret that the first round
I reported the body and both and F were
with me and none of them said that they
B even said that she was following me
the whole time but she didn't see me
kill anyone
huh for cron trust me me
for I
trust who are we voting
for selfreported
no I don't think that's enough to vote
her out vot oh my God imposter G let's
go
byebye says no I don't know Kiara's
really suspicious right now oh sorry
okay ghost
chat hello
hello crony got voted out I didn't
expect that I know K is oh she's here
ghost is here she's here yeah oh why why
is why is B oh can I haunt oh I'm
haunting her what does that
mean I have no idea where did all
go it's she
deserves okay but I need to do my tasks
too oh it's cuz never I know why no
nothing nothing when I joined the dead
people child sending your fugie became
humous it was only
you yeah it's cuz we're in different
channels yeah okay I have to care be
careful about that okay I'm I'm a I'm a
guardian angel who do you think is the
other impostor I should probably stick
to them
um wait I shouldn't probably knows I
think it also might be am I think a was
suspicious somewhere wait did she not
kill you though I don't know I got
killed big so I don't know I don't know
who it is yeah I feel like she killed
you cuz I saw you alive and then like
literally like 10 seconds later armed
you dead so I'm like who could have been
there definitely it's definitely am me I
see I see I think it's Am Me I'm Falling
on me right now I should also do my
tasks while doing
that
okay I think it's am I'm going to follow
am not know about this the dead people
chat that she
could maybe she's not joining cuz she's
ashamed she maybe she maybe maybe oh
what what is the code how am I supposed
to know the code for this uh where like
the right where I'm where um at the is
it at a
little ID card yeah in your pocket oh
you're right
oh I kind of like just doing the tasks
It's Kind me too okay I've finished I've
finished the task I still have a lot
actually oh God I need
to okay I'm haunting Amy okay I'm
watching does haunting just mean you
follow her you automatically follow Auto
follow oh okay okay okay I need to see
who you can
haunt other ghosts as well ooh
oops I canun
you okay
let's see this oh wait did anyone die I
wasn't pay attention oh someone did die
okay okay let's go back then oh
yes uh oh I'm too
slow I think Kiara is safe yeah cuz we
just did the emergency thing together
yeah and then I'm a joined right when we
finished I ran away both of you guys are
I thought both of you guys were the
impostor you kill me
no I I really because the first death
was Iris and me FAA and Iris were the
ones that were closest to each other
and yeah though that's and now I'm
scared I know it's not Kiara because
Kiara didn't kill me or anything so yeah
I still have three tasks left by the way
but wait so why did why did you just
call him meating because I was wondering
if anybody di we're about to finish our
tasks and you don't want us to finish
our tasks I was it was too quiet and I
was scared if anyone was going to die
and I thought like might as well chat
and write Kelly what were you doing I
went down to mushrooms mhm and what's
the last task you did the Sorting the
mushrooms into the jars and the crystals
okay Kelly has been quiet yeah she has I
mean ask me any questions you want but
if you talk too much you get sused out
too so just ask me any questions and
I'll tell
you what's the last task you
did um I don't remember I was in
the shoot I can't ask chat too cuz I
can't even look at chat um I know this
sounds suspicious but yeah I don't
remember I'm I'm going to vote for a I
think yeah you're the Imposter you're
just you called the meeting because
we're so close to finishing our tasks
that you're scared no I'm scared of
dying aren't we all I saw Callie and she
didn't kill me and I was running away
from you guys cuz I thought you guys
were going to kill me so H that's my
defense yeah okay we voting okay oh you
guys if you guys vote for me you're
wrong just so you know uhoh oh I'm GNA
vote for
Kelly
or call you us cuz I saw you I saw K and
bi together and you guys didn't die so
unless you're both the impostor no we're
not uhhuh that's exactly what an
impostor would
say
well two imposters alive we would lose
by now so there's only oh okay true so
one of the previous was well crony I
guess was the one that got knocked out
right so would that
yeah I don't know I don't know I don't
know I we Skip and continue doing our
tasks unless you guys are if I was the
Imposter I'd try to vote one of you guys
out right now and then I'd probably
win I'm going to skip you guys are wrong
regret your
decision I'll miss you yeah
right no she's
burning are we winning please what they
didn't
win how many more oh
sorry I I thought it was am I thought it
was am was it am apparently it tells you
on the haunting men was it beu then I
was following after I died is it C it
shows you if you haunt them sh just
shows you who it is oh my
God
no wait oh my God how
did
gacky it wasn't me god well played well
played well
I was wild I was
sh so actually I turned into again
that's her tell she was quiet you turned
into fa I see we thought Kell quiet too
but I'm so sorry how do I ever
redeem myself to you it's late
s believe
me I'm not a real am
goling
I tried to protect her and now I'm the
one that killed
her yeah I can't I'm sorry I can't
believe I got imposter twice Believe get
why is everybody so good at lying I've
been watching professional Japanese
Among Us players
recently the whole time had practice
that's
what true
you didn't listen to
me damn it and I still didn't get
impostor single time
man maybe next time we still got more
time
right yeah there's a little more time
then let's go next
round oh I saw I saw by the way the
ghosts uh were going in their own
channel did you have fun yes yes
recommend it it was fun I don't know why
cron was probably too guilty to
join oh wait there's a dead voice chat I
didn't even
know voice CH I was like why isn't she
joining I was like probably cuz she
feels guilty oh no I don't feel guilty
at all you don't
feel Abol feel shamey just randomly get
voted off too cuz I don't even remember
like everybody yeah I got v no Kara was
giging reasoning for that
what Kara Kiara knew yeah cuz I told you
yeah yeah I told you to believe me see
oh it was actually good what I did she
was right you were so
right way to tell easy way to tell if if
cie is imposter she's quiet when she's
imposter I'm talk imposter so I don't
know bye you are the Imp wait scientist
yay although I don't do anything with
this information I just like
science
I'll go over here I'll try not to die
wait where's my task oh it's
here
easy the gamer chair where's my
task oh is it down there what down here
I'm acting
suspicious don't kill me the
pizza what's the goal here give me the
pizza
kitchen oh oh spin is oh no my spinning
is like Amnesia water monster all over
again okay everybody's alive good to see
it
ah it's an impostor roast them alive is
that too
morbid what's
happening oh this
fixed I haven't seen anyone I'm I'm so
suspicious but okay everyone's alive
still
okay I could report and be like I'm the
scientist and everyone is
alive I don't know oh if that's
useful cron Nissa
Callie I broke
it it's
disabled it's not act how do you
activate the office you have to wait for
the
others
maybe where's the
office well what are you
doing it's active
82 okay
oh wait I didn't even see I didn't even
see I didn't even really see I didn't F
wait I didn't even really see wait she
was just there wait wait wait what what
happened wasn't that wait who did I see
no no no no it wasn't me I where were
you where were you when you pressed
it who pressed it wait I I pressed it I
was oh my God I was so in my tangent oh
my God I went up to the top ride to the
communications and I was just Tangen
thing and doing a task and suddenly I
see a dead body but on the same spot I
think I saw at least one more person
maybe another maybe two people I think
so it's Kiara Iris H and then I just
came into the room and I saw C
outside I just
the all of a sudden I was also in
Communications well I didn't with almost
the same time and I was trying to go in
the way to the mushroom door but I got
rid of the mushrooms but uh maybe you
killed by
accident maybe it's just am him by being
silly uh-huh wait
what wait I'm you were there right when
I reported right no I I just walked into
the room like after cie she was already
in there like alive and you guys were
all doing the power thing or whatever
and I was also starting to do the power
thing putting in the code but then you
guys finished it and then somebody
reported Callie's body so I didn't even
see it wait so you're saying besides me
there was cie and you I was
the communications
the we all in there no one was on the
other side of the mushroom wall so I
don't think they could kill her on the
other side of the mushroom wall but I
don't know yeah I just went up the
ladder was how it went and then all of a
sudden report there might there was one
other person in there but it was hard to
see cuz everybody was bunched up I think
I saw purple yeah purple was was was
Call's dead body no no purple
we do have something to report
yeah we
heard okay you are the and the
M we were thinking maybe being Sil you
know that's good thing that we do that
oh I heard that too I thought she was
saying it to someone else and now trying
can we have someone who has a talk talk
please me me me
yes so um I was at communications I saw
a bunch of people there and I was trying
to like uh do my task and like I was
still on the task when it happened so I
didn't really see anything oh so you
were also in Communications M until this
report okay you were there even now when
when I reported you were still
there um yeah yeah oh so you were one of
the other people I saw then but I wasn't
sure who am I seeing Oh
well I remember this I will
remember
this but
oh a
joke
um oh
no that's not
good do you think Army is actually the
Imposter do you think she failed to
mute is that man
gaming
oh who was
that Nissa and C that's so fast wait
what so
fast
yeah there was like a crowd of people at
communications wait did you
did oh my God you kill my
gosh
yeah wow see The Quiet Ones it's always
the quiet on I knew hasn't said anything
but itive last
[Music]
round
both innocent I'm
sorry was too B sounded
but susing for was susing Amit right
because of her statement but it
wasn't
[Music]
purpose the two imposters would of
course vote for Fu moo because
you I'm sorry oh my God this is what
happened okay next we we
got don't give it to the blue
people I'm the crew
mate I'm the crew mate I'm not the
scientist it's okay I never use the
scientist information anyway
sand don't kill me don't kill
me crab wait is this a crab is this a
monster it's so hard to dig in the
sand one time I dug a wasp out of the
sand and it stung
me be boo on asteroids we're FPS gaming
she waiting she waiting for her cool
down she's judging my gaming
abilities we can hang
out oh wait oh our our map is
offline I
see you can
go
okay
I I ran up because of the communications
thing was down and she was right there
in Communications in front of the the
thingy I don't think it was was at the
other I was at the other I was with fa
but I didn't see her body I was down by
the dock I was in the
labs oh me I'm oh yeah I just met crony
in the labs yeah
Iris and I are doing the other task the
power thing didn't kill each other so I
think we're
safe some Li what what narissa Fu were
you I was down by the dock I I figured
that you probably all were going there
and I wanted to keep doing my tasks so I
just went down and I was doing a sand
castle and then I was checking since
yeah don't the um I passed I passed yeah
they disappear but if you pass them you
can still do them oh okay yeah I was
checking manually okay yeah or if you
just still like remember where they were
before it went down
yeah
reactor
reactor what task what are you doing at
the reactive we're doing our task we're
just trying to task what
task doesn't want to use I like the map
I like finding the little yellow mark on
the the screen is now you
know is
marshmallow sizing
yellow what I actually haven't done that
yet the yellow there's a yellow so cute
little Among
Us uh the marshmallow the marshmallows
yeah um so inconclusive but what task
were you
doing
yeah the marshmallows are nowhere near
the reactor so what were you doing that
was yeah but what were you doing today
huh we doing a bunch of in the reactor
what were you doing what were you doing
in the reactor yeah what were you doing
in the reactor kind
[Laughter]
of for now I'll give you guys a benefit
of the
D please don't kill
us
you
[Music]
live okay SL Place
suspicious of bow
bow I don't think it was B
boo oh where you
going where she going where's she going
oh where's she
going oh oh oh 2 80 6
2 okay I do tasks I spin the
wheel I failed to spin the wheel I
getting over it has prepared me for this
moment we got a s man Mr Sandman bring
me a
dream we got a sandman situation over
here any dead bodies here no b no
B
okay 25 6 2
4 okay everybody's here okay
we're going
down I would like to go in the
greenhouse oh take it
off of course I should remember
oh I should remember my tasks so I can
tell
people okay she's going up there I'm
going
here
648 oh is this you can spy on
people I don't know how to use that well
though
oh it was Kara it
wasara Ked watch it don't believe her do
you see I saw people kill am I am medic
I am medic I can see people's vitals
yeah and I can see you kill am is that
how it I I am Med I can see people's vs
I have three battery charges every round
to see how many people are alive this is
the first time I have medic I saw kiar
kill no people no no this is hard for me
because I had just I had just seen bibu
and but I did not see kiata and I was
going down and she didn't follow me so
she might have realized she was alone
with a but uh bioo also when she killed
me selfreported and then immed this is
literally the first time I've gone this
scientist and I have this is the first
time I played it so how would I know
that I have three charges of scientist
to check
vitals where is the body time in a while
uh the body is up this
communication I saw Kara who wanted you
probably just looked up some guide about
those no I didn't this is the first time
I have whatever scientist whatever I can
check people well I was I was so often
alone with others and I didn't kill them
so why would I you know can somebody
vouch for me cuz I think I was a little
alone together with a lot of
people come on
uhoh I was alone with bio for a while
but I was not alone with Kiara yeah I
Kara for like a Split Second I saw I
several times alone and I saw crony
several times I think alone and I saw
narissa like maybe one or two times
alone yeah it felt like um either Kiara
or fauna was going to kill me cuz like
they were just kind of walking around so
I stuck around one of them to make sure
I didn't get killed um it would kind of
check out if Kiara was the instantly Ved
I saw the kill I
believe wow
okay
sorry good bye forever thanks forever H
what was it I I love you or I'm die
thank you for I die thank you
forever
well somebody's not voting oh yeah the
other I just accepted that you guys are
voting me me out but I guess you'll
you'll no you're running down the clock
it's so sad I I was always with you
guys it's so
[Applause]
sad goodbye goodbye I will go up like a
phoenix and I will rise like a
phoenix
H
Iris
IBU Iris she's running
somewhere a knife slice it I love
cooking
mama excellent just like
Mama is that how cookie mom is I don't
know when she became
Italian can I go this
way
okay
good oh is there a thing in
[Music]
here what's going
on is this the wrong
thing oh there's be
boo I don't think it's
beo I mean she definitely could have
killed me here
oh Pal's
disabl is this
vitals oh but it's
disabled
okay we're
together where we where we
dropping so
scary Iris so sus it's right there in
her
name is there a dead body up
here is she going to the other one
probably
oh okay everybody's here foku is not
here
notably they are not
here I'm not even trying to do it I'm
just keeping an eye on
people oh I wonder if foku
is going to murder people
okay no no body was reported that's good
I just have one more task to
do and it's all the way down
here down here it's over
here should I stay with bi boo is she
going to be
okay
can we go this
way I have one more task
[Music]
oh
hello no I I cuz I I I believe it's F
what why like when we were going to when
comms were down we were going up I see I
see like um many of us were going up I
think it was like
I think I saw fa beu um I also saw I was
also with crony and narissa alone none
of us killed each other um and we were
all going up to comms but then I see F
coming down from comms ignoring the fact
that comms is well you have to do the
bottom one first right we're just trying
to do the tasks and you know at the Top
If you were at the top you would do the
top one right but we just counting we're
focusing on our task yeah you can't see
the tasks on the map when comms are down
yeah yeah yeah you can't but if you walk
around
you that's what we did last time
[Music]
too that's why I decided think
soing I can't get
anything that's how we play
a me tell me aask you did this time
what's what's a task you did what's the
task you diden
house where you are we doing yeah why'
you you you come came back down from
comms even though comms is sabotaged all
the way back down to the greenhouse the
greenhouse is
pretty green is
pretty you got
[Laughter]
a who are the cutest puppies who are
wow look at the Little Liars look at the
Little Liars
oh cute little liar
about bowing
[Laughter]
it
bye come on cast
your yeah don't don't um delay your
death it's yeah it's inevitable time to
go what excuse
me like a p byebye
[Applause]
[Music]
puppies that was really good sussing out
Iris that was
impressive good from the reaction too
even the last round when when we almost
voted them out cuz they didn't know what
they were doing at the
reaction that made me 80% sure and then
I saw them going down from P oh yeah
yeah why say we're crew we do
the
yes I'm so sorry it's okay
you were just trying to survive I I
think out of this whole group of people
me and foku are like the worst Liars so
it wasn't a good
[Laughter]
combination your
B we were so bad
[Music]
harda makes me
laugh IA laugh too you you see see I I
had the good the good B you know I did
the marshmallows and then she goes oh we
did that last
[Laughter]
time oh my god well at least I finally
got imposter do we don't want to do one
more round yeah hide and seek for the
last
game hide andek hide and seek hide and
seek hide andek
it's like hide and seek like how you'd
really think hideand-seek
would for hideand-seek wasn't there an
actual setting for hide and seek though
yeah there there is there is computer uh
you might have to make a new room though
maybe um if you can't change it in the
settings um on the computer yeah then
you might have to make a new room where
is it yeah no I don't think you can
change it
here okay then I'll make a new
one okay okay it's kind of like it's
pretty much like playing tag yeah
cute um any preferred
map let's do the original oh yeah
yeah
okay
nice I'll send you the link in the group
uh the the code in the group okay there
you this one's chaotic but really fun
thank you I've never done it before oh
it's fine and it's a short game too so
okay let's go
perfect man this is scary this one this
is like the only time I actually want to
be imposter hide and
seek I never want to be imposter ever
again for this same we don't have to
mute for this said oh no I don't think
there no reason
just try not to give away your location
on accident I guess we can mute if we're
done uh we don't have to right move to
the I'm
noty wait we can we can hide in V oh is
there only
one oh is this like
zombies
better really slow you do tasks the
timer goes down
quicker we have 3 minutes to hide
left is 3 minutes to hide she's in the
meday I'm I'm
here engine she's coming for what wait
what oh man is she green that was who
knows what color I might
[Music]
everybody's clumping
together you better
hide she right
now my
God is that
Callie wait how does this
work
name tags do your best the Music close
to you when she's close by
that's crony where's
crony don't say it
yeah oh that's fun that's so quick too
that was so another one another
[Music]
one again
for both the impostor and the the the
the crew
mates can we increase his speed for both
crew mates yeah I want to but also I I
uh I think I have to make a new Lobby
because I don't think I can change the
amount of uh
Seekers there's only one one oh yeah
it's fine to leave it on one we just
need to speed up we're all running
really fast wait okay
W this is how it should
bee we got
this yumy let's
go I get
to I think so oh I hope so I'm going to
be Unleashed for
my honestly why are okay oh God where do
I go don't forget to do your task do
your
taskas there's Tas oh God I don't see
them I see tasks but I don't know what I
really want to finish that
sorry it's all
[Music]
good why do I
have I'm scared I'm scared I'm scared I
hear I hear the face we got to win we
got to win this I can't find you guys
what the heck
[Music]
everyone got her I'm going on a vacation
with
her I'm not even near you oh my
God
[Laughter]
gave all of us
[Music]
on terrifying screams
here
louder this is so much more chaotic
louder yeah it's so chaotic
when you hear the guitar you're
[Music]
like oh God my eyes are spinning 20
seconds 20 more
seconds I
believe oh you're going to be even
faster the final round I'm alive okay
should I do tasks no no no it's fine
it's
fineing chicken wait there's get one
more
minute don't stand still because it's
going to show your
location it shows do you guys know where
I am location it show there's a there's
a red dot uh that indicates where the
crew is have it on me I shouldn't have
moved I shouldn't have moved I shouldn't
have I see dead bodies I see dead
people does she see me from the MCH
or only when she gets closer oh God oh
[Music]
God
so was impressive virus amazing I don't
know how I just didn't really see her on
the screen that often so thank God
everybody was so
fast that was close though teleporting
across couldn't even keep track more one
more
[Music]
who is it this time let's go who is
it knows today I think everything r
r does doing tasks do anything like we
put an early task wi if we do if you
finish them all yeah then we could get
lucky and finish proactive with the task
hide is
this I can't die oh
no wait okay got to go got to go got to
go I was about to the thing I'm sorry
I'm try
I'm
nice she
was oh no what color guys guys damn it
I I do wonder if doing tasks is even
worth
it she ran fast she ran
fast going to the cafeteria wait can we
tell
her it might be a little
unfair oh okay I felt that was the wrong
direction okay you know what um let's do
our
tasks I'm too scared to move around at
this point I die whenever I use do tasks
it's
[Music]
just
4K only only three
left what is the danger met there come
on guys one more one more
minute such a good hiding
she's going at a good Pace very good
Pace
[Laughter]
oh that was a really good hiding spot
yeah my so loud all the time oh no
whoopsy you guys are slippery yes
everybody so
fast is there overtime she's in now you
have a minute so fast
[Applause]
I
survive
I'm no pressure oh
[Music]
man just go you have 30 seconds left do
it
what you do you're
Phoenix the
wall you have 10 seconds 10 seconds
just she won't get you she won't she
won't get you oh
[Music]
no oh my God the last
second
many oh my
goodness wow how many seconds was left
one literally one
second
mcch though that was
amaz that was the ever
what Escape time at the end of the day
but was really slippery yeah really
slippery yeah oh my God that was
exciting I
mean I'm I'm pretty exhausted from that
but we can do another one if you want
I'm down for one
more actually actually you know wait
wait oh no before Oh I want to I want to
speed so fast yeah it's fast oh good
okay
you want how how do you kill people the
whole time um there's a kill button so
don't you worry okay oh my God no way I
don't want to be here no the monster is
unleash she has awakened I'm coming for
you nobody's using my hiding spot right
oh oh no good idea don't use my hiding
spot might go use it was that your no
that wasn't your hiding spot
shoot oh my God she's on a rampage there
were two people there I only saw one
person
overlapped does the music get louder for
me too I feel like it
does he someone really even for
imposter get out of there get out of
there you little
what's going on
[Music]
Noy
where are
[Music]
they that was my hiding
spot
I she's checking the corner
where oh no that's okay that's the step
I still got time I still got
time I saw someone where is
she that hiding
[Music]
spot that mean
soly
oh my God that was no no I haven't found
anyone in my CES you passed by
[Music]
somebody someone's here no oh
where are
you hello I'm all
alone no hints no help oh was that there
was some button popping up there the use
button
yeah in
[Music]
time I didn't even see you that's lame
what the
he see you I saw you that's all that
matters oh get out
turn around
[Music]
[Applause]
quick oh one more one more one more
run no no
no still one more
minute they're literally right
run
run you can throw it through a loop just
run just run
[Music]
[Applause]
rle good
[Music]
job p
p
[Music]
wow my doie
doie did that was clutch again pretty
clutch I would say get into the last
foring after Mama Mia that was
wow that was fun that was merry I'm too
excited to say anything so let's start
with the with the goodbyes from anybody
but me
um please no yeah this is really fun I'm
glad we could get together and have like
a little Christmas Among Us
C perfect holiday SE holiday game right
yeah just red with toy and some blood
when I think of Christmas I think of
Among Us and violence and death us
ornament yeah it's pretty festive the
colors you know this makes me want to
play this makes me want to play on
Project winter yeah we should
play yeah I know
[Music]
C
wow thank you I'm sorry you died so
[Music]
often but that's okay it's still fun
Callie what about you you had some good
good kills today it was nice getting to
dust off the old Scythe for once and get
back in the game for a little bit that
was
nice yeah I had a great time with
everybody here everybody here is fun to
talk to fun to argue with in a fun yeah
really in a fun way yeah in a fun way I
guess that's about it we should argue
more often yeah yeah let's do it let's
do it no no I can't maybe not yeah no we
just stay TIY but within among us we can
argue as much as we want right and then
outside of Among Us you know we're
different people among us changes us but
only what happens in Among Us worst of
us yes exactly Among
Us
[Laughter]
all right and fauna please please tell
me about your experience today science
Rules that's all science sence what did
science do science science Rules and
statement than
great interesting interesting I don't
quite understand but I agree oh I don't
think Kiara knows about Bill it's all
right don't worry about
it
wor tell lat oh it's a okay
Iris Mrs Mrs Santa Claus Mrs Christ yes
yeah no this was fun I'm glad I was able
to lie better this
time yeah you need some good lying yeah
we need to learn from IR
some never suspected everyone everyone
was great love how bad fle was at L
yeah their first time convincing
moment it was the same as me when I
played for the first time
worry always like that it's great I love
it thank you very much that was fun they
were so lucky cuz like in that one round
they were about to be voted off and I
thought I was going to be alone but then
somehow somehow they survived
couldn't save
you no it's okay we couldn't save each
other even if we wanted
to yeah well thank you Iris and then
people what about you I was happy to be
able to kill people I wish I was able to
kill more people but I was satisfied the
amount of people I was able to kill this
time that's the spirit thank you for
your service that's the spirit that's
the Christmas Spirits let's go let's
go it was
solid good job again I'm so sorry P it's
okay
Trail but what stays in Among Us stays
Among Us
[Music]
exactly we a lot of things to do we
really good at lying right that
was
and uh we have fun we we yelled a bit we
screamed a bit and we did a lot of
lying yeah but most importantly we had
fun so
true when I saw I was imposter with Fu I
knew I knew that you weren't going to be
good at
lying
no
face we sweet yeah it's all good true
it's
funny I had so much fun thank you so
much for putting it together
kiaha I'm sad I had to be the impostor I
don't like it brings me no
joy murdering me no oh but so good
though you were good at it was over
right away that's true yeah you guys
were Mur blue women women are scared
women blue women I always say it it's
the blue people the the avatars I always
say
it yeah thank you you're welcome I'm
glad you had a good time that's that's a
continue this in the Mal Dives yeah
peacefully the other blue
yeah it was a lot of fun I'm kind of
surprised that I actually got impostor
twice um because I never get imposter
yeah I never get these
roles yeah and thank you for organizing
this it was a lot of
fun I
love I guess you know there was all
sorts of drama but like we said earlier
what happens Among Us us stays Among
Us wow
beautiful well said thank
you well yeah that's pretty much it um
but Christmas is not over yet I think
there's still members that have like
special streams upcoming so check them
out everybody and I just want to make
one quick announcement about the whole
Ian Advent calendar some people may
already know but the last day the 25th
day will be delayed a little bit so uh a
few days uh it's out of my hands out of
my power now but please check back on it
next week we'll all tweet about it when
it is finally up uh so stay tuned stay
excited and thank you for spending
Christmas with us viewers I say to you
viewers thank you for spending it with
us and thank you to the girls for
spending it also with us thank you for
getting together at this time thank you
Merry Christmas Merry
Christmas
Merry
H had a lot of fun that was really great
and I hope everybody has a nice nice
holiday season e some
cookies y Yum Yum Yum Yum okay I have
some protein milk in my fridge oh very
christmy
Sant May s Santa will come to drink your
milk oh protect your
milk yeah all right I don't think that's
going to make Iris like Santa
anymore already does not a lot oh no
Santa is iris is literally the tree now
okay the tree I'm not yet don't let
Santa drink the protein milk we can't
let him get any stronger than he already
is for Santa no don't give him the power
no the
cookies isn't I in some countries Santa
drinks beer or people give beer to Santa
really something sounds German Santa
gets drunk I don't know I think so drunk
he drinks a lot and then he drives yeah
oh no oh
no makes it worse that doesn't really
sound like something I would want to
tell my children over yeah okay with
that I think some people already gone
like fle is gone already so I guess
let's go
everybody
[Music]
byebye