[Music]
he
w
[Music]
no
n
[Music]
fire
ah
uh
ah k gety key
I'm
tired
hello
uhoh
e
EP a it's so loud make the music
quieter it's so
loud maybe I'll mute it for now on my
side ah turn it off I don't want to hear
it oh my God it's giving me like uh it's
a really cute music but it's like over
stimulating me right
now um no I woke up at like oh for
[\h__\h]
sake what's going
on my obs
yes but I think I think that was only
OBS are we
back tell me I am back yeah
okay yeah I woke up like an hour ago and
I rushed to get something to eat some
breakfast it took longer than I thought
but at least I went outside
supposedly supposedly the fresh air
should have woken me up feel like I
haven't gone out outside in like 3 days
besides my
garden uh life W I miss you so much yeah
hello to the people how many of you are
weren't able to watch the recent
streams because of
time
problems raise of so many
[Music]
Wow Wow have you guys been watching The
V
vs cuz it's been a lot of fun honestly
like and they're not too long at least
the vods aren't too long like I mean 4
hours is not that long at
kfp you did did you watch the V watch
the vs trying to catch up okay okay okay
okay take your
time sometime eventually I'll take a day
off after all this is over and then on
that one day you can try to try to catch
up with everything
uh wow 48 months let's go thank you uh
my voice doesn't feel like it there
Mirage is such a good song Thank
you where are we right now with Mirage
let me check my my brain my head I'm not
feeling up for this challenge right now
but we're going to do our best uh oo
almost
500k oh almost there honestly could
probably could reach it before I go to
sleep
probably could work could could happen
very possible Mirage Mirage
Mirage Mirage Mirage Mirage stream it
stream
[Music]
it I had like such insane like I I
didn't sleep so well that that's
probably one of the issues I slept kind
of badly I had
nightmares and I
had good dreams too but it was a weird
mix and I kept on waking up because I
just couldn't feel
comfortable
um
yeah yeah it was a weird mix
uh and yeah
blah blah blah blah I wanted to squeeze
this in because I had an eye on it since
I saw they have a myth update myth and
first ID
generation but I don't
think I think we'll have a
problem with getting any of
them we might just have to appreciate
the Silhouettes only
because for okay so in order to get waa
I have to set CI in my deck trim my deck
and Achieve nine chains n nine chains of
what what does it nine chains
of wait nine chains of what what does
that
mean just
what oh oh uh oh what just throwing
[Music]
like ah just ah like um merge something
nine times in a row so not just throw
something in and have it not merge it
has to oh okay that sounds kind of
doable but then in order to that that
has to be done with cie so in order to
get cie I have to make the biggest
treasure two times in a row in free gaml
and you know I've never gotten the
biggest treasure
before never and now it says do it two
times in a
row in free what does that mean in
free two times in a row in
free game wouldn't it be two gamep
playay
sessions see that I also don't
understand but
um two times
what two times in a row
what
six
what what the [\h__\h] the ENA score 4,500
three times in a row I don't know how
difficult that is in free game
play three times in a row in three
gameplay sessions so
nine how much is how much was I always
scoring 4,5 I think that's you need the
biggest treasure
to get that
usually and for goba set all five
members of Gen 2 in your deck and
combine characters 1,000 times in to
what what
1,000 see but I don't even have all of
Gen
2 and am needs this no she needs 35 but
but gen one and I don't have gen want if
fully they want all members of that
generation so first I need to get gen
one and gen two
completely I'm not getting any of
these I'm not getting any I thought it
was just a free update and you get them
for
free I'm going to cry I had this
realization earlier though before went
before I went to sleep I was like oh
[\h__\h] for [\h__\h] sake oh I already have
them too
and then there's first ID set your deck
and make the
big set in your deck for
Mauna and Achieve 5,000 points in a
single
play
O
to wait it's all of their like kind of
like connected
sire cute achieve a total of 60,000
points I don't know if that's a lot I
don't know
but I wouldn't even be able to do that
either cuz I don't have tokin NOA Senpai
uh P Senpai I
have and konet I don't have I'm pretty
[Music]
sure where would you
be where's cor ah down
here ah in order to get coret you need
OU in order get to get Uka you need
combin character okay this is like we're
all we're almost there we're almost
there 200 more
times but okay I I think okay let's try
to focus
on let's try to focus on okay what's the
most realistic nothing none of these
none of these are realistic for me but
um we can try did no there's no way I'm
doing
that there's no way there's no way what
there's no way what does this even mean
I still can't fathom what this
means what did YouTube die again Mama
Mia what's wrong at this moment [\h__\h]
this internet what I'm going to kill
them the [\h__\h] is wrong with them
[Music]
[\h__\h] the
[\h__\h] I'm so mad at them what what the
[\h__\h] okay please tell me you have calmed
your titties
ipan please tell me you are okay now
because I will otherwise kill you
please
mhm okay I I think it's
fine knocking on
wood is it is it it's probably it's
hopefully fine yesterday too I had a lot
of issues in that uh stream in the
beginning but then but then it was fine
after a while after a few crashes it was
fine anyway
so we could try to work towards getting
like gen one first in order to get gen
one okay I have two of them so I need to
do a total of 250
chains a chain
is just any what's a
chain what's a chain a chain is just any
any any kind of combo like any kind of
merge like one merge is one
chain
okay well okay we're getting there we've
been doing it it's 131 out of 250 okay
and then combine characters 4,
times I would say we're getting there
too but with my uh steam says I've
played this
game 4 hours so far which was in Japan
I think so in those 4 hours I got
[Music]
1,800 we're not even going to finish the
first gen
probably this is this is actually uh I
would say a a little bit too tough
divs a little bit too tough I would
say like this is not making me happy
this is not sparking
Joy right now it's a little bit too
tough It's a challenge and it forces
people to play for a million hours it's
a little bit too
tough but sure okay uh the window size
by the way is not
very very much
there let's just do something like
[Music]
this whatever okay I guess we'll just
we'll just grind a little bit U I'm not
going to play for too long because I
have my other stream later of course
yeah I forgot how to play this game oh
thank you for teaching me again I think
it's giving me a tutorial cuz I'm
playing for the first time on this
PC uh
how was I
playing space or
enter or uh uhhuh uhhuh
okay wait what
was oh okay all right uh
well Lami is
always some something I like to see
right hey one combo hey two combos oh
threee combos oh four combos oh and it
ends it breaks my
combo I don't even know how do you play
this game well it's been a while I never
played it well but how do you play it
well
H I think a lot of
times I was just like not careful enough
and it just I I didn't shoot it far
enough and it just fell off right the
cliff like right in front of my face H
when more than one merch happens in the
throw oh that's a com to me that was a
combo it's a combo to
me I want to see me this is not fair I
am
my how can you do this to me so that was
a combo I think
I mean that's going pretty well so far
it's pretty smooth but will we ever get
will we ever get the biggest treasure
which currently is set as peka Senpai I
don't know I don't think so maybe even
today is not the day although who knows
maybe they nerfed the game a little bit
in the
meantime we already got to
S is this going well
you still can stream it more until yeah
I guess so maybe if it doesn't annoy me
too much if it doesn't frustrate me too
much
maybe is this loud enough for you guys
or do you want me to turn it up or down
because currently I have it almost
muted all the yapping that the girls do
is so cute but at some point I think it
makes you go
crazy I want to hear what voice lines
they have for
me how can you take this away from me
this this this rights to hear
myself I have rights to hear
myself okay okay I see it gets me like
you hear them Yap and you just want to
repeat everything they're
saying they pick cute ones and did you
hear it already did you girl did you
girls did you guys I generally say guys
to everybody did you guys hear it did
you guys get myth does anybody have
myth I'm guessing no a lot of you guys
were like surprised by me putting up the
stream you didn't even realize that myth
was already
available no I
yep I have myth give it to
me I don't even have the game
we have myth at home myth at home myth
at points at nander roids of myth at
home
takanashi do the
[\h__\h] my at home be like [\h__\h]
unpainted waa after four
years surely surely the time is coming
guys the time for Wawa to
shine it's it's it's there I feel it I
feel it guys we going to be released
from the
suffering just
believe if if wa neroid finally happens
will you guys get
it say
yes
yes really
[\h__\h]
internet [\h__\h]
internet ah why why why why why why why
why why why why why why why
why why are you like
this internet what's wrong right now why
do you annoy me so much you've been
stable before but I guess I could say
I'm glad it's happening now and not like
during my 3
live if my internet would have died
there I would have also
died okay Aki sire into the
[Music]
middle any Aki Senai I don't have any
Aki Senai right now or is she hidden
somewhere no then go here see I'm
already having issues how am I ever
going to get to P senpai
never never never literally
never can she fit in there how big is
she smaller than smaller than Kanan
and try oh God that was close that was
close oh it's not looking good you must
believe what's there to believe there's
nothing to believe anymore no why didn't
you go further back I wanted you further
back I guess even that wouldn't have
helped
me okay that that's a good fit if she
fits she sits must be a
cat don't tell her I said
that um we'll turn into can so next to
can is
good hey chain
let's go okay save that was
[Music]
close guys recently with the 7 Days to
Die streams I haven't really been able
to communicate some much of you guys and
pay attention to the
chat uh your voice too loud for the game
I need to put down the volume my voice
too
loud wait why did I
[Music]
I think my internet died
again what the [\h__\h] is going
on what the [\h__\h] is going
on I'm going to tag them on
Twitter I'm I'm so close to tagging them
on
Twitter and be like what the [\h__\h] are
you doing to my
[Music]
internet I hate them the the funny thing
is there was a non interet related issue
I had with them with my
ISP and
uh like I called them I was like
hello I can literally not make any
calls in like I don't have a phone
connection
in my
area I need to step outside and go away
to get a connection what's up with that
and they're like oh yeah um there seems
to be
some
problems uh it will be fixed until this
date date
arrives guess what it wasn't fixed it's
been but but I could I have didn't have
time to like bother with it I usually
don't make calls anyway so I just uh
have been waiting a bit more for it to
resolve itself but it hasn't resolved
itself um so after the date where they
said it would be fixed it's been like
over a week now since then as
well so in total I think it's been quite
a while now so I should give them a call
for that anyway but maybe it's all
connected guys what what happened I
didn't even do anything
thanks I guess
thanks but we have a no to stand
by oh oh oh oh interesting interesting
should I I have three nanas on which
nanora do I want to throw
this Nan becomes kanatan ah okay kanatan
is like right now between uh two nanas
so one of them but this one scares me so
maybe the one over there like next to
no should I aim for that
one outside edge middle outer
one they're going to tell you the same I
know I have a feeling I legit think that
they were messing with me they told me
there's like an issue and they were also
just H hoping for it to resolve itself
gave me a random date a couple days
later and we're hoping that I wouldn't
call them anymore and it would just
resolve itself I I don't think they did
anything I just think they gave me a
date said said wait for it and were
thinking to themselves uh if it's still
not fixed until then then they she this
[\h__\h] will just call us again I doubt
highly that they did any effort to fix
anything I [\h__\h] hate
them I had so many issues with them when
I moved
remember I told I think maybe in the
member stream I don't
know that's so many a [\h__\h] them just
[\h__\h] them [\h__\h] them I'll make my own
internet
company where do I throw
it ah well I'm hoping that if I throw it
into the middle those two will merge and
then she will push back into the middle
a little bit too
but where do I sign up you'll have to
come to Austria my ISP I cannot do it
internationally yeah with black check
and cute girls black check and
is that a meme why are you guys saying
that can you switch thre the switch um I
don't know I think my contract is pretty
long it's a futur f Futurama meme did
they say they'll make their own
internet was there such a moment black
Che and hookers well blackj kind of
suits me you can keep that I do like
Blackjack it's one of the few card games
I can play
oh wait so what where should I throw it
in the middle let's
see oh okay was see see she did go back
into the middle I predicted it it
[Music]
happened okay wait uh turns into Kat
currently no Kat but whatever I'll just
throw it here I don't care brain empty
good good good good good another one but
maybe we can get p in this run see my
best score is
4,400 I think the one that they want
what was it 4,500 and then probably like
10 times in a row five times in a row
okay okay sure sounds realistic to me
too mhm
mhm does that sound realistic to you
guys no no
oh no n right
now if only those lamies would push
together are you for real I I'm getting
another nura right after which turns
into a kanatan oh so let me try to throw
it like lay it on top of
them that's notop okay well that works
[Music]
it worked somehow so yeah I was going to
say before my internet died um knocking
on wood I uh is there like anything you
wanted me to like talk about recently
and because you weren't able to watch my
streams or because I wasn't looking at
chat most of the time on 7 Days to Die
we weren't able to talk about um throw
it at me throw it at
me how have I been
how am I doing I don't know the the
sleep schedule is kind of weird but it's
it's working it's it's kind of working I
I would like to not do this for my whole
life but uh for a week it's okay I was
sleeping doing all these 3D but I saw
her new 3die outfit and holy moly it's
it's so [\h__\h] crazy it's so insane it
looks amazing what are those shoes and
those bones and wow it looks
insane but I'm not going to lie I mean
I'm I'm jealous at everybody who gets a
3D
outfit because for me they are doing the
typical Japanese company thing where
they're like um no no we cannot do
anything that we haven't done before
whatsoever we cannot bend our rules in
any way you used your 1 million wish for
something you could have gotten
anyone cuz I didn't know I didn't know
that I could get a 3D outfit back in the
day cuz there was no example of it I
thought it would be too expensive to ask
for something like that I didn't even
consider it because we didn't even have
3D at the
time ah so that it wasn't on my mind and
when I asked oh can I like the I got I
got the dandal
dress if you remember I got the dle
dress back in the day and nowadays I'm
like I have so many life Tod outfits I
don't really I can't even I can't even
think of what else I would want so I was
like hey can I maybe like this year skip
out on a life to D outfit because we get
one per year now skip out on One reverse
my wish in that way say the dandle was
for this year for example and get a
Fredy outfit instead and they were like
no I was like why and they were like I
don't know I just
know
mhm okay guess I'll do it myself I'll
get my own fry outfits the which is fine
and like I'm glad I can do that for the
music videos but it's really limited I
can't use it for the fredd lives I can't
use it at F I can't use it in the Ian
concert I can't use it in our app and
stuff like
that
yeah so
I don't know 2 million would be my next
wish
but you
know but
yeah I'm not going to pretend that the
um I'm not jealous I am jealous I am
jealous but it is what it is but they
look
[Music]
gorgeous
gorgeous this is be a problem I think if
I if I can land it exactly on her but
then N I feel like it will turn into
cown and then fall
down don't you
think like look how far on the edge she
is I mean she's kind of laying
comfortably there but if it turns into
kanatan you have no idea where she will
go we you don't know where she'll go
it's too
risky next is another oh okay wait then
right okay then maybe I'll do it over
here and then combine the canot
dance or I'll do it on top of a
different B no never mind no never mind
no no no I'll do it here I'll do it here
uh maybe on top of aidos but or like
I'll try to squeeze it in
here left or
right left or right left or
right right left
r r r r r
okay
okay nice internet what do you
mean internet's fine right now right
don't scare
me it's looking pretty good
sh H oh two fukis I have Aisa in there
get in there oh whoa whoo whoa
[Music]
whoo my camera pushed her I was actually
I was trying to push her inside but it
pushed her to the right side off of The
Thing Man
wow it's only
me
2,000 see I'm never going to get
anybody I'm never even going to get the
first
treasure this game is not sparking Joy
with me right now they're dangling myth
in front of
me and they're laughing at
[Music]
me the deps hate me
this is not fair I need like some kind
of buff or bonus like they need to bring
us some items or something they need to
bring us a shop oh you know what they
could do with the more scores you get
the more coins you should be getting or
something some kind of currency and with
that currency you should be able to buy
like a
buff I don't know what that buff would
be maybe um like a safe one save or or
like a resize or a change switch switch
to like a one time only per game switch
to a different like if fubuki is coming
up I could uh I could roll that into
something else for
example but one time per game if I
activate that buff like with my if I buy
it from a shop they could Implement a
shop where you can buy these little
things doesn't that actually not sound
too bad a little bit of anist assistance
come
on please
who
[Music]
please yeah nice change of pace right I
think so
too we Holo cure now yeah I love Holo
cure the items are fun the shop is
fun where do I throw
you just here
thank you thank you ah ah I need to
sneeze again maybe no
no what's this mess why is it so
messy
col oh what y thank you nice nice nice
nice nice so many good ones in a row for
once you're being nice to me
this
game uh wait did I just throw the subu
Senpai there why did I do that oh well
can never have enough subu senis in your
life
o
o hey hey
hey the devs heard my
cries I don't know I think they're like
drinking my tears enjoying them this
whole ocean around you think that's a
normal ocean no no that don't are my
tears that I have shed is there
something in the middle that I'm not
seeing or is it just
empty H I think it's just
empty
H yeah okay so I told you about the
about we talked about Ollie we talked
about my sleep schedule anything else he
wanted me to touch a PA wow no okay
pretty early under a thousand already
know how are the C Kos are good I really
should take them to the vets cuz I
haven't taken them to it's not like they
have something right now but just
thinking
generally
um haven't taken them in a while and I I
actually really need to
uh update their vaccines I think their
vaccines have
been like dead I don't know how you say
it outdated off probably not working
anymore for a while and I've just been
too busy because I've been traveling the
the whole summer and before that I moved
houses um so you know need to find
different vets and stuff uh expired yeah
forgot the words
pretty sure and then even before that
before I moved I there was you know
times where I went to the vet for
example because of the whole scratching
thing cuz of their allergies seemingly
they have some allergy both of them and
I can't figure out what it is and at
that time they were like okay yeah the
vaccines are outdated but right now
let's do the vaccines later because
we're gonna like try to figure out this
issue first they didn't want to do both
of them at this both of these issues at
the same time because the vaccines can
make them kind of weak and stuff for a
day or so I guess and they said like
just bring them back for the vaccines
you know when when they feel better or
sometime I don't know
something a [\h__\h] I thought it would land
on
Luna
oh all according
to any plans for spooky Mo spooky stuff
uh well I I think
conveniently 7even Days to Die
fulfills quite a bit of my
spooky
uh uh what's a good
word spook spooky like you know uh no it
[\h__\h] does COTA yeah yeah yeah it does
it [\h__\h] does there's [\h__\h] zombies
in Apocalypse all the time and I'm
screaming here and there it [\h__\h] does
but uh I have one game planned that I
got perms
for it's quite
Niche um I'll play it probably on
Halloween night but besides that I don't
have anything spooky planned besides
that but I would say my quota is
fulfilled okay leave me alone leave me
alone alone I'm old I'm a foure standby
I'm I'm old I'm a grandma okay leave the
horror games to the Younglings leave me
alone leave me alone inscription maybe I
don't know what I could look at that
probably if it's not too crazy bad
scary Leave Britney no leave W
alone I old
to I don't want to
play but yeah I think the game I'm
choosing to play on Halloween is really
Niche but there's a there's some there's
some reasons why I chose
that um I hope you will like it I'm
really interested in your reaction and
if you know the game at all
[Music]
I don't know get in
there touch yeah you too why not
touch Metal Gear so how is that horror
Resident Evil no no
no no I don't care I never played a
Resident Evil game I know a new one came
out or a remake I don't know but not my
fa
W okay okay I don't know with my luck
I'm going to [\h__\h] it all up somehow but
this is a good chance to get to our
first treasure
ever wait the getting Muna has something
to do with pekora right having pekora in
and then doing something but probably
some [\h__\h] again like three times in a
row or what was it was it maybe a
specific score we might be able to get
Muno you could have a bigger combo if
you thre Luna
faster oh oh
well no way she'll even touch Resident
Evil or Silent Hill yeah I I mean in the
past you know free years ago or so there
were certainly things where you guys
would say oh there's no way ki's going
to play that and then nowadays you would
be surprised you know I am playing those
things that you maybe wouldn't have
expected
before you
know but yeah currently I am not
interested
in uh those
games tapping up the that would be a
good horror game horror under
exclamation e uh not exclamation the
other marks I don't know what they're
called uh really is that something
fitting is that going to fill up the
quota not sure about that
one uh can she fit in here like in
front oh
okay fine stay there I
guess kind of
dangerous oh
really really Luna say
p three of you right next to each other
what's what's wrong with
you American American me
Alice wait which one did I play I played
one of those scary Alice
games is that the one I played yeah yeah
ah no I played Alex madness
Returns I played Alice madness yeah that
was good times good times if you haven't
watched it guys how long is that ago
like 2 years
ago two years ago Halloween time or no I
think I played it like kind of at a
random
[Music]
month I'm on my period
yeah I recreated that
Meme three years ago no way then
actually I'm going to I'm going to take
it back don't go back to watch my
archive because three years ago WWA I
don't know I wouldn't be able to listen
to myself for 3 years ago what is this
pile of [\h__\h] man what am I supposed to
do with this
everybody's like
somewhere I don't want to put any more
on top of here otherwise I can't reach
him
[Music]
anymore wait let me I get another Lamy
let me try to throw it next to Lami
please stay okay wonderful this could
work this could
work yes a cleaned up a little
bit nice nice nice nice here and here
what super come come on thank
you I was trying to watch every H move
ever archive so I will okay okay how how
much more have you got to
go oh wa was are so cute thank you I
love three years ago wa there wasn't
anything wrong with you're so nice
you're so nice for saying
that for chains that was actually better
H
okay well honestly I don't know if I'm
even capable of of like looking so much
or aiming so hard for those achievements
when I can't even get one treasure One
Max like final treasure out of this and
I'm not even there you know I'm not even
there how can I do three times in a row
free games stuff like
N I had that motivation but the way
everyone keep streaming it won't happen
uh but wait are you trying to watch
everything of every member or everything
of every myth member everything of every
myth member might not be so
difficult we're maybe the easiest gen to
achieve
that honestly
[Music]
okay why do you hate me why do you hate
me really really why do you hate
me there we go
chain I was gone
again bro
[Music]
I preferred her for years ago you prefer
her what am I supposed to do to make you
happy now I'm not going to go back to
that three years ago
W just a second I gone just a second
really only okay well that still sucks
still going to sue
them still going to sue the [\h__\h] out of
[Music]
that my life depend depends on my
internet yo like
[Music]
literally uh
wait yeah let's Place her like here I
have no ly right now but let's Place her
close to a sub sen anywhere really okay
are you comfortable there let meai H you
look so comfy good for you
oh okay never
lety K oh good good good there's a lot
of katans
around yeah
[Music]
okay okay okay I got another fiki right
after
that maybe
like here so that I can eventually
someday change that subu into
something oh actually the a I'm going to
put her here too okay somewhere else
then she didn't want to go there maybe
they're not on the
friendliest uh path right now I go back
to Old archive K so I can listen to you
singing
maros that is valid that is s valid that
is like self valid though
thank you for appreciating my old kadas
I I appreciate you appreciating my old
kadas
um oh
no damn I don't know the order by heart
close
um I don't know if I want to throw that
Fuki over there too it's getting kind of
cluttered but
okay and up
here and then over
there ah stand by don't separate them
they want to be together selfcest
selfcest selfcest
selfcest okay okay
oh you
guys you guys are you know you
know you should
know Wawa has a thing for self it seems
just kidding just
kidding just
kidding of course
[Music]
any a lying around no maybe over here oh
God damn
[Music]
it stay
stay stay
[Music]
stay it's getting so messy
and my internet died
again I'm going to I'm going to lose it
what's wrong with them before the next
stream I'm going to restart my router
but honestly that [\h__\h] never works for
me restarting my router never helped me
with
anything this island is going to
collapse I know I know don't
foreshadow everything about this is
already foreshadowing we don't need any
extra
foreshadowing just get in the
middle lau
lau no no
no
what did you see
[Music]
that it went from right here in front to
right over there right on the I didn't
even know there was something there she
could combine with
what God's hand supported me just now
very acrobatic God's hand LED that to
happen
wo
wo waa this is dangerous this superent
but very
dangerous everything here is very
dangerous why did I don't know man I
don't okay something something will go
wrong now watch it
happen I'll try to throw it on
Top push I pushed it I pushed it I
pushed it back I pushed it back I pushed
it
back go back sub go back go
[Music]
back
um let's throw ly over there yeah so
that she can merge with nanola later
when she becomes a nan when she grows
big
uh hope you don't play Goa cuz you used
up your like no I I I used to play Ark
Knights
but ever since I started this job I have
no time to play games especially gacha
games outside of my streams
anymore cuz gacha games you got to play
those every day man
every
day I don't know if I want to merge you
because you're going to be too big what
am I going to do subu
Senpai I have to do some bigger merging
first wait there's a subu senpai down
here which oh wait that turns into Lamy
and Lamy is right there
too I was going to throw it and then
quickly go back to push some
[Music]
I I can't even be happy about
this
[Music]
man okay wait we got two things
hat they give her that hairstyle cute
wait was that her default I don't know
anymore like I see haima with different
outfit more often than with her default
cute I guess that is our
default I guess we got two things from
that let me go wait did they did they
put them into my deck did they trim my
deck oopsy not rankings
no no I know it's just me I'm I'm I'm
playing this game
alone oh yeah they're in there
okay um I don't
know uh if I
want well I don't have gen one or gen
two complete yet so there's really no
point was there anything with h doing
something with Gen
five gen five gen
five you can get M zai for a really
crazy cumulative score okay is this 10
something with Gen five
no wow
okay these are pretty
simple what was this one achieve over
5,000 points in a single play yeah if I
if I get one treasure like the the the
biggest treasure once that could be
achievable
but okay here we
go okay let's
go ah so
cute it's nice to have something new in
here oh
cute right so hotas will turn into yummy
and okos will turn into
hachama
interesting okay will take me some time
to get used to that I think oh there we
go they're so
cute everybody's so cute I love these I
love the designs I love the style the
art style they're so marshmallow so cute
so
bouncy so round I like the face on the
waa
one I want to get the waa why do they
not let me get the waa
it's not
fair hey what's
[Music]
up the diamond face the diamond
mouth so cute I wish I could do
that here recreate
myself cat cute cat and another cat
[Music]
oh my God there's so much yapping cuz
I'm playing kind of fast right
now oh no okay wow that's pretty
clean pretty clean pretty pretty
fast not
[Music]
bad good start good round
but you know I'll mess it
up why I should have thr that to hot oh
well ah wait let me keep her
here
[Music]
a y y y yep is there aai yeah
you could have merged into
katas by now they're probably merged
what do you
mean try sing in new Mirage s we might
help you with this mess no I will I will
lose my focus I will not know what to
thr where I already don't know but you
[Music]
know you push her further inside thank
you thank okay okay oh chains
chains oh yeah we like them
chains pretty good having a t sire there
next to a n
sire actually not pretty good run what
do you think
guys let's not jinx it though that was a
weird bounce can you calm down
[Music]
stay
no okay here is fine
too I get I can get for if they
touch okay okay okay okay okay push no
[\h__\h] they won't get pushed
[Music]
Focus W Focus don't ruin it now your one
chance I don't have any can right now
but it's okay it's okay
[Music]
[\h__\h] lock in I'm trying to lock
in but I'm so stupid I'm so
stupid a Thea is so
[Music]
dangerous that one's so dangerous but I
I if I create her here if I'm lucky the
can of with touch with but with how far
away they are right now chances are low
those two the Nan that will turn into
kada and that
one but I have to
[Music]
try put her on top of
Canada
okay guess we'll fix that later here
another one oh my
God uhoh okay okay that was relatively
calm I was hoping for it to go down
honestly but they're so they're like
they're hit boxes or whatever I don't
know they're not as fluid they won't go
down there they're not very
like
flexible
hey okay so it's really [\h__\h] messy
now it's so
messy wait should I throw it over there
oh uh let me become n uh-oh okay okay
okay okay okay
[Music]
okay or
there doesn't matter they are all too
far from can but I'll throw it
here what just happened I don't know
what it's okay it's
okay okay is it is the hat that was
bured down there gone now okay okay okay
okay here comes a big combo yeah and
maybe a big explosion with everybody
falling into the
water I have another idea for an item
that they could Implement if they were
to make a
shop uh an item to remove one thing in
your pile just poof without even getting
anything just because it's in the way or
it's blocking something like I would
want to choose for example like I don't
know this some something in the middle
that's just keeping things from
combining that would be a good idea
right poof away with
you that's a good
idea let me should I try to put her
there I I'm scared she will fall down
but I could also put her here I kind of
want to put her there I'm hoping she'll
stay on Oka on top of Oka but can't
really trust
her I'll just squeeze her in here which
I'll regret later because she'll be in
the way of something
[Music]
I hate this I hate this it's so messy
it's so
messy there's no way out of this I think
I can't fix this this is so bad this is
so well who knows who knows who knows
who knows where would I put this hatch
in m
a I don't have any hatas right now I
have a million things but no
hatama next to Nan what up
[Music]
here up at the top stacker on top
okay um this should be
good okay
[Music]
one you ah there's one stuck in
there I'll just no I have to ignore her
there's nothing I can do oh nice
for okay okay okay
[Music]
I have a loveh relationship for this
game that is growing stronger and
stronger and
stronger let's try to be more clean but
also more faster for
combos wow great great start in being
clean it's okay it's okay I had no
choice this is just the
beginning it's not
like I have a choice it's just the the
things they're giving me to work with
are just not that good okay here we go
here we go
push push
[Music]
push bounce
bounce it's so frustrating yeah it feels
so good but you lose so hard for real
man what's what's this what's the
point what's the point when I can't even
play this with me
[Music]
maybe it would hurt less if I could play
M
death okay
okay but then if I play so fast and I'll
make a million mistakes again and
everything will be like face palm
moments did you guys see the the clip
that I
retweeted that was not a face palm that
was a face slap I really just slapped
myself really hard on my
forehead but it's a face palm I guess a
face slap
Palm it was so loud I know it was really
strong I hit myself really
strong stop hitting
yourself stop hitting
yourself
oh I'm not going to get my hopes up I'm
not going to get
my I'm not even going to be happy about
that
doesn't mean anything getting annoyed of
standby early on it doesn't mean
anything is this even early on maybe
it's not even considered early
on but I'm
fast
wow faster than the speed of light I
call that a SOA slep what what does that
mean where'd you get that from
[Music]
okay now we're getting messy
again
still
[Music]
acceptable okay now it's getting
messy can you realign your gam does
grave bar on the left oh I didn't see
that
oopsie
sorry two people telling me at telling
me that at the same
time one brain cell kfp one brain
cell
okay no not there what that was too
much too much I uh
momentum not quite the right translation
but
enough [\h__\h] [\h__\h] looks Messy as [\h__\h]
again
no uh maybe close to AI
[Music]
Senai no not close
whatever it's
fine people try to tell me I know you
always do it's like
hard especially in seven days to die you
guys are seemingly telling me a lot of
things and I'm just I as I have this I
wonder if I'm the only one with this
problem I ask a question like in terms
of streamers I ask a question to chat I
look at it for a while but the delay is
like a few seconds then I get distracted
or so I look back into the game and then
I get distracted and then I forget to
look at the chat again to get the answer
which comes in the moment I look away
often times and then 10 minutes later I
ask again I wait a bit still don't get
the answer I look back into the game
that's when the qu the answers come in
and I missed them it's like it happens
so
often it's an endless
loop there's a Lamy down there and
there's a Lamy over
here but maybe here is good yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
wa
W for once I'm doing something good with
my
life let's go nice chain two
noers so now I would like to have that
item to get rid of canata in the middle
here but that doesn't exist and now I
would like to push those Hamas together
but I don't trust
myself
oh I think I'm ready to play in the
Austrian football team cuz that was some
sick ball
[Music]
skills not really where I want to but
okay
[Music]
the middle is safe but then I'll bury
UK coming next
though oh
wow maybe I can
still almost almost had the back one
that wasn't too bad could have been
worse
um ly no [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] they're playing right now and
winning what there's something happening
right
now ah what's happening right now who's
winning what can't wait for the next
football watch along just the other day
I re-watched um I just like looking at
my shorts and I rewatched the um
football short that I uploaded the you
know that one clip that was drawn and
I'm like oh my God like I rarely
re-watch content of myself and
especially also I rarely laugh at myself
doing stuff that I did in the past but
that one's just so funny especially with
the animation it's just so funny and it
made me feel so nostalgic already even
though that's not so long AG go it was
just like a few months ago and I feel so
nostalgic about that time I was just
really
excited yeah he touched the ball with
his
dick he blocked the ball with his
dick that clip is so good man good times
I was like in a good mood
o I will not be in a good mood for much
longer
o it's over guys this is a sign that
it's
over I don't know about that Lamy in the
back I might just do something over here
wait canot down no there's a wait never
mind there's a canot down here
what [\h__\h] wait but two lumies two
lumies let me just try to do it on
top oh oh oh okay that worked
surprisingly well not what I had in mind
but
sure stay
there bro look at that that it's so over
it's literally so
over it's so over it's so over ah I'm so
scared it's so over over let me just
throw that in and and
pray oh I think it went back a little
bit oh God it's so
over oh what the [\h__\h] was
that oh it's so
over it's
so oh go back go back go back go
back I saved this Lamy seemingly
oh oh
oh what if I just throw that straight in
there into the other Lamy what do you
think will
happen bad things will happen something
good might happen if there was a nan
right
behind but there isn't do do it do
it it should
[Music]
what h she somehow reseted her position
and made herself comfortable
there
oh I saw her falling down and I saw my
my life fading in front of me and
showing me all the highlights of my life
and the flashback I saw
it holy [\h__\h] ah she got pushed by the
next ball a nice
nice emotional support
physical support uh
hat there's actually a good amount of
space here but do I want her there uh
yeah maybe because Lamy is
there oh
[\h__\h]
here should I throw her should we try to
repeat this and throw her right on nanoa
like one of these or throw her on the
top
here would be a kind of D there there's
a oh maybe it doesn't matter as long as
if I throw her right over there she'll
combine with the c down behind her I
think or I go for the center
one I'm scared like if I don't use it on
the front one if I use it on the center
one I'm scared it will cause an
explosion that will cause this one to
fall
[Music]
down you know that's why I'm thinking
rather than top to go for this front one
but you guys all say middle okay
okay I get another one I get another
one wa if I squeeze her in here nah they
will never they will never touch like
once it turns into canatan I have a
feeling they won't touch not the way I
like them to
touch what should I
do let me on top of L
me I wouldn't I'm not sure if I want to
do
that yeah it's a good
setup be a good setup though I
guess oh the yeah the V are next to each
other what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh I could try to like push them
together you know by pushing nanora onto
nanora and with that impact maybe the
vamus will
touch I mean we did this a momento a a
moment ago and it
worked I wonder if I should do it
again don't risk try
it some dark magic happened guys
oh my
God oh my
God oh oh shoot no no I stand by please
please please go back inside it's not
time to leave
yet
um it's pretty good so far this this has
potential even though it's a little bit
messy
maybe on top of Lami but I don't know I
have I I don't know how to throw it so
that she will stay there cuz you know
this Arrow this
line like if I throw it here it will
just the throw will be too straight and
there's a high chance over is that it
will bounce off and fall down so I need
to throw it higher but if I throw it
higher then there's more like momentum
and it might like bounce over there to
the back side it's just a a hard a hard
thing to figure
out up from the other
side I want to I want to be there to
support push n
in
how how how would I do
that but wait there's a fubuki coming up
fubuki turns into OK let's just keep her
like somewhere there I don't know I
don't even know
o o o o what
[Music]
okay no dangerous no
dangerous okay let me push let me push
let me push P yeah yeah yeah yeah oh I
see some some realignment has
been happening
okay this is good everybody's pretty
comfortable and they're grouping I have
two
no h and and enough to us to make
another enough enough uh can making man
like there's some good stuff here but
they're a little bit far away thank you
for the membership
welcome oh n for kind of done so maybe
close
byi is stuck in there in the
middle but I'm just going to thr oh all
right I should have looked at at that
getting another one another one another
one and another one and another
one okay
okay please ST stand
please
tou did you guys see um I I I've been of
course like
Indo like I've been updated I know that
there is like oh thanks for the MIP
renewal I know that we have we have been
like you know making this card game for
a while but yesterday I saw a
tweet um that like in Japan in Tokyo in
Akihabara I
guess there was like a whole life card
game get together battle thing and like
500 people showed up were and were
battling there the tournament yeah but
they already they're they already have a
[\h__\h] tournament I was like what what
s since when are the cards out anyway
that people can already have tournaments
your deck is good I've heard
[Music]
so yeah it's it's so nice to see them
like actually like have a [\h__\h]
tournaments like they're the the game is
the card game is doing well enough to
have tournaments I'm happy to see that
but I guess card games are uh I don't
really play them nowadays but in Japan I
guess they're still quite a lucrative
business huh people will jump onto these
kind of card games especially when H
life is uh
involved um I don't know if that was
officially
organized uh but I don't think it was
organized by fans it may have been
organized by the shop or whatever the
venue I don't know
I actually don't
know I would buy them just as collector
items
really yeah I guess if I don't know if I
was a I can't say cuz I'm a I'm part of
whole life if if I was a fan would I
play the card game I I probably wouldn't
have anyone to play it with but in Japan
yo yo wouldn't it be cute like for next
Fest um if if like there was like a kaiy
overseas fans meet up with Japan fans
meet up like a a mixed International
Tournament if you guys get yourself some
cards I think the moment you're in Japan
you can probably buy them somewhere
easily and cuz you don't need language
for card games right although the cards
are in Japanese huh is there English
cards yet I don't know even if that's a
thing already
[Music]
not yet oh damn H okay then it's a
little bit difficult soon when is
soon but in the future wouldn't that be
nice to have like cuz a lot of uh
overseas fans come to Japan for Fest if
you guys battle it out there that would
be a cute little activity for you
guys
a to argue rules of cheaters ah they
wouldn't cheat Je Bros wouldn't cheat no
I don't think they would cheat I don't
think they would
cheat I don't think they will
cheat give him some credit
[Music]
o oh God I want the hot there but I'm
scared no will pop off
[Music]
no when I played MTG playing with people
with spoke a different language was a
pretty common thing right I would
imagine like with chess
too I don't know why I'm bringing chess
up but I'm thinking of that Netflix
show sometimes people cheat in card
games without even knowing it's unint I
had it happen a lot of in Yu-Gi-Oh well
in Yu-Gi-Oh I can't imagine don't people
come up with a lot of [\h__\h] in
Yu-Gi-Oh I you know I don't I never
played it I never watched it but I I
just think of the
memes yeah misunderstandings are common
huh like not pot of greed I draw two
cards I do this I do that I don't know
what I'm doing
[Music]
pot of green I don't understand
but so where do I throw hat guys what do
you say do you think no will be safe if
I throw it from here or should I try to
throw over noo I don't know she's kind
of
big don't you mean don't from
where not over no yeah cuz she probably
will be blocked off right okay then
please be safe oh okay she kind of went
more inside
actually all
right rather than falling more outside
she F she she kind of rolled towards the
inside thank
you um
oh gu I don't want you to get lost in
the middle that's my
issue but I'll throw you up there you're
still reachable
so oh
nice I have this feeling that any moment
now I will do a stupid
mistake and everything is over uh any
moment now I feel
it yeah yummy
but we have a f we have a nor this is
pretty good I don't want this to end
badly when we have three nanas I don't
know which nanoa to combine it with but
Nan turns into Katon so any of these is
good what this
one yeah it doesn't matter that was okay
that was
okay aim for the
hidden no
oo let's throw oo there and here and
here and there and there and there
yeah I saw that
coming okay now we going uncomfortably
messy again
sorry oh okay wait let me throw that up
there so she can oh oh something will
explode I'm so scared I'm so scared I'm
so scared push push
[Music]
push my first
time oh my God wo wo wo wo wo wo
oh oh [\h__\h]
holy
[\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] oh this is is this a
dream is this a dream can't be real oh
my
God oh my God is this
real this is real can we get to 5,000
then we can get Luna I think not sure
anymore [\h__\h] I'm going to mess it up but
at least we got big
but the first time I get the final
treasure will I get a reward like any
any new member for that just for getting
the final treasure
once I must get some kind of reward
that's the first time I ever got
that
please you get Co oh let's go yeah right
right some said something about
coyot coyot Senpai no what what what's
wrong with you
okay that's
fine you weren't supposed to go there
but happy accident am I
right okay wait I'm almost at 5,000 so I
get K and Luna maybe
ah p is so cute over there she's
sleeping giant
sleeping um
maybe just here I don't know I'm scared
I'm scared to [\h__\h] it
up no go more
down I I'll have to thr her
here please let me get to 5,000 please
please have mercy on me
o is that oh
God safe to
go is it safe to go yeah
okay
took L of people are excited to play
whole life TCG I personally will build
your deck thank you what maybe ah he you
know what would be super
cute cuz you know
MTG I love magic G but can never get
[\h__\h] uh perms for that um but if
there's an English version coming out
coming out we could have off collabs
playing cards playing whole life cards
against each
other but honestly I think it would even
work without off collab if we both set
up our hand cams whoever else I would be
playing it
with I think that would work too but as
an off collab it would obviously be such
a great
idea I need to ask them when they're
putting out the English ones the English
cards good thinking I know I
[Music]
know okay there's stuck down there and
I'm getting an OK next so I don't want
to like clog it up too much uh Nan
there's no Nan
around should I throw it over there I'm
scared about Canan so maybe not I maybe
I'll throw
it so scared I'm so scared I'm so
scared get
there wait I'm scared if I I want to
push her in but I feel like I'm going to
push her to the to the outward maybe
from the other
side I'm too scared what do you think
can I push her in or is she too too far
off and I
will rotate over and see if she
set oh okay okay she's fine I wonder if
that pushed her in a little bit maybe
maybe maybe okay be careful Canan don't
fall over I will
cry oh
God okay okay okay okay she's still safe
she's still
safe what's that is that a is that a hot
M there
I think
so she fall she fall do you no okay now
legitimately I'm not sure if I can push
her in
anymore but I'm right before 5,000
points those
you
please can I I mean Fuki is relatively
small so maybe I don't know if it
matters what you're holding
[Music]
but uh place it by the open area you you
think nothing will move I guess
so probably nothing will move
but a bit go small get the
points um touch C first I want to touch
I'm not sure what will happen
have you guys had a case like this
before when she's so far off the
edge push from to side really it feels
more dangerous
here
sh we look at points for just placing a
thing or do you only get points for
combining things I don't remember I've
never paid attention oh
okay will how many points do I get for
the N
combination
[Music]
uh oh she didn't move she didn't move
even a little bit she was totally
unfaced over
there bro don't
do it's like her star is keeping her
stuck in the ground like it's like fixed
like an anchor 5,000
5,000 she's anchored in she's locked in
okay I'll continue a little bit I guess
but now we now we could risk it and try
to push her in
but I don't believe in that side I think
if anything it's the other
side should we
try oh wa okay see all right all right
she's more oh thank
God is there any points after 5,000 for
any achievements or is it like safe to
like die
now
um let's
see think it's I think it's okay to die
now wow now I'm fine with
dying goodbye
thanks yay oh me said bye make the
biggest stretch oh okay make the biggest
stretch once for me and then for K too
right like as long as it's
p
ma we get a new one at least one new one
finally aqu as well ACH a score 4,500 in
single play
yo and what I have accumulated score
50,000 yo yo yo I'm getting so
many let's go wait coyi what's with
coyot I don't get
coyot what was the what was the thing
with
coyote yo
y they swapped out some other ones that
were new still but wait do I have the
full
[Music]
first gen yet wait that game
is gen two do I have wait let
[Music]
me let me
get no I'm still missing Matsui sampai
I'm still missing these two ah man and
I'm still missing col
[Music]
Senai okay Dallas what does uh if I need
need two
times aha doesn't have to be in a row
and doesn't have to be in the same game
though so if I just keep P Senai in and
do it
again [\h__\h] I said it
again
[Music]
again oops I Did It Again
okay
um combine Char well this will just
happen eventually
okay you don't have any of
these ah okay mik Senai for two more
times treasure Max
treasure this isn't that far off this
isn't that far off achieve eight chains
what do you
mean a
oh chains as in yeah eight combinations
in a row eight merges in a row
okay oh I did a seven chain when I made
Pico wow
okay got
seven 100,000 oh my god well these also
seem to be pretty automatic like they
will just happen
eventually um
ah I could get Kon if
I make the biggest treasure with OKO
Senai and then with coron I could make
uh I could get
lisu we're not getting any of Myth today
it
seems
um make the biggest treasure two times
in a row in free game that's that's
insane wait I I got one out of two so
what two times in a row in free game
wait I don't wait what wait what what
does it mean like I have one of the two
what does this mean I still don't
understand if I in the next
game I two out of free
tries so in the next game or in the next
next game I could fail it in the next
game as long as I do it in the next next
game I think
mhm that is a
achievable that's manageable and then
nine
chains when my Max is currently
seven but with C you got to do with C in
your
deck okay
okay then I don't know let's do it one
more time with um pekora Senai as the
biggest
treasure just because then I can maybe
get coine I don't know I wouldn't have
coine or should I do
yeah yeah yeah let's do that because
otherwise yeah that's that's still
achievable right now I think
um
but let me swap
out some of the ones that are still new
with the older
ones yeah that's kind of it
okay we have Mona in here
now that's
exciting MAA wait I want MAA maybe
here and oh we should bring all the
purple ones together for fun uh we
should make a
rainbow oh
yeah oh
yeah oh yeah oh
the
wait wait
OCD OCD is strong right
[Music]
now I look at that isn't that
pleasing it's kind of
pleasing person in the smallest that you
won't hear voices for oh okay okay okay
suddenly F zai very small smaller
smaller F zai
looks good I like this we'll have to get
used to
it okay let's hope we can win it again I
doubted that I can do this two times in
a
row but we'll
try we'll try I want to play like have I
want the stream to be maximum 3 hours
maybe so that I have a chance for a nap
if I
[Music]
want why do I why do I feel the need to
always take so naps I just don't have
the energy if I don't take a nap
man I'm such a lost
cause you got this wa thank you 3 hours
Short 3 hours is very short 5K views
until 500k oh guys open another Tab and
watch Mirage music video do it just do
it oh nice W wo okay w
feels
good I don't even know what I'm
combining yet what's happening I don't
really know I'm just letting it
happen I by looking cute with her only
mask new voices in my
head they're not so
familiar new voices joined me in my head
how nice of
[Music]
them I didn't even watch look
ma she's so pretty
oh I'm not even thinking and things are
just going well for me right now if only
it was always like
this there we go oo that's pretty close
already holy [\h__\h] and it's really really
clean but obviously it's still going to
take a while it's not that easy we still
need a lot more going on
here stream after the stream that's fine
that's fine thank you so
much sometimes you're more effective on
autopilot sometimes but I feel like
maybe in the beginning it's fine but
then later we really got to lock in
otherwise stupid things
happen are you guys going to try also to
get myth it's a long a long road but
it's a Time killer it's a good game as a
Time killer and then you'll feel so
happy when you get myth
been trying okay you've been trying
right now next to me sweet let's see
who'll get there faster but I I
literally will not get there today
because obviously not enough
time another little
oneoff uh short game that I want to play
next week if I can squeeze it
in
um I don't know if it will be in the
beginning of the week or the end of the
week I still have to make a schedule but
another game I want to play uh still is
the the voice voice mimicry
game I want to play that that game is so
unfair like even when you make something
really accurate it can score you as
being really shitty at
it so
Savage but I definitely want to play it
yeah it's so
funny seems seems quite entertaining to
make stupid voices and you know I am the
creator of
M so you would think I should be good at
this
game I am a s can you move more towards
the inside
[Music]
please there goes my effort to have
something two times in a row
three I feel like three of them fell off
or
two it's okay for the one with cie I
think we still get this one more
chance I think that's how I understand
it I'm pretty sure that's how it works
now because he said one out of
two this is a good beginning oh my God
[Music]
one more chance one more
chance oh W
hello hello hello such a clean beginning
this reminds me of the sua game right
now like when you have a clean beginning
like this is always the best feeling oh
wow
[Music]
what was that oh F
sire the blondes are confusing me maybe
it's better to have all kinds of
different hair colors hey y' hey y' heyy
y'all what it's so clean
[Music]
I try to keep the hair color separate
yeah but sometimes they force your hands
if you want to get specific
achievements cuz like I think which gen
like second gen I think or
first one of those gens has like a lot
of
blondes there's generally a lot of
blondes in h live
[Music]
lot of shades of purple too true yeah
and of course a lot of
silver silver
foxes still playing pretty brain
empty it's going
well will it stay like like that will it
stay
well I
am not what I would want right
now
okay yeah I know it's slang for like a a
hot old
man not that old though I think usually
oh two
moas two
[Music]
Mo Two Moons don't we have two moons
right now I heard something about that
in theory we have two moons even though
we can't see the other Moon uh Earth is
or is it a different
planet was it a different planet in our
uh star system no is it was it Earth I
think it's Earth but um yeah an asteroid
is technically our moon right now
because why why does that make it a moon
I'm not
sure can anything be a moon as long as
it circles
Earth why is that a moon
yeah until November 25th yeah it's in
orbit is with anything in our or really
but then are we all moons to the sun
like like all those planets that
are circling the sun are we all moons to
the
sun yeah we are technically oh we are a
moon but to me the Moon is just the Moon
but I thought the Moon is just the
moon it's called satellites what
satellites are satellites
[Music]
so that German song German singer song
English song
though I need to listen to that again
that's such a good song you don't even
know what I mean uh What
[Music]
uh the classes of Stell objects are not
really logical they developed over time
when stuff got discovered a moon and
that moon are different things
what MOA feels a great distance in the
force after what you said you mean a
disturbance they change definitions all
the time remember what happened to Pluto
got
downgrade yes L my land rout the EUR
vision
yeah I really like that one hey you're
not supposed to go
there Germany did really well then
thanks to Stefan Rob discovering Lena
may I must say that is not a good artist
name but didn't she change it to Lena
officially by
now just L now
[Music]
where [\h__\h] why is it so messy I hate it
thanks I hate it um maybe close keep her
close
[Music]
toot
yo Miracle still happen
[Music]
what do you think of this
guys there's a real case of folks in
chat just talking about stuff they don't
know anything about what else hey
hey they're chickens okay they can't
know everything but also they seem to
know more than me some of them
defending you
guys can't allow this kind of chicken
slander
[Music]
yo any astronomers in the chat I was
watching some um like binge watching a
few like Universe
planets videos do you to
day but damn [\h__\h] gets complicated and
confusing and just my brain zones out
that those videos were too o o those
videos were too much for
me they need to use simpler words for
me like how long it would take to get to
each this planet and this and why why
this planet is the hardest to reach in
Fury even though it's like not realistic
going there but why it's difficult
because of this and that and these
factors and you know those kind of
videos cuz this planet has this kind of
like stank to it it's
[Music]
stinky it's just
stinky of course no that's not the issue
but that really not where I want her to
be
EUR europa's Clipper is launching
Clipper I'm just thinking of like whole
life Clippers I'm guessing this is
something
astronom something related to
[Laughter]
spaceships Moon Clipper satellite what's
a what's a Clipper
satellite does it clip onto the moon
oh it no it's a the name of the of the
satellite ah uhhuh
uhhuh hey it's so over it's so
over the beginning was so good okay
kimori
goodbye I never had a chance of you
anyway did I
I'm really worried about CI
man her
voice like she got permanent
[Music]
damage hopefully hopefully can be mended
because this is her job like singing and
all that but I can't [\h__\h] believe I
have to scold her like she has this
voice issue this fro voice whatever
issue and she still does like two
streams in a row like relatively long
ones too like she played Dark Souls and
seven days to die when I saw that I was
like girl I literally wanted to scold
her but okay like if she I'm sure she
wouldn't risk it if it was really
dependent on that if that would really
have an influence on it I would hope
that I I I will assume I willum that she
knows what she's
doing yeah I I I hope so
I I don't know like
if I just want her to take care of
herself there was no need for her to do
two
streams says me who doing two but I
don't have broken voice glands or
whatever it is right
[Music]
now yeah scarring in her lungs like that
sounds pretty serious to me
but I don't know maybe maybe I'm not her
mom I'm not her manager in the end it's
you know her choice of course but I I
hope she gets I hope she gets well and
better and fast and I hope that scarring
somehow
heals the doctor said to fully
rest Callie I'm going to strap her to
her bed and not in a kinky way
I'm going to go I'm going to go to
her put some handcuffs on her and cff
her to her bed and not in the kinky way
[Laughter]
[Music]
I guess the doctor didn't tell her
complete vocal rest but I mean it
wouldn't hurt probably to rested a
little bit for like a week or
so or MTH
even at least no streams try to keep it
at a
minimum she doesn't even consider that
option does she oh wait oh sorry I I I
fought oh God I F
ah [\h__\h]
okay I thought that was you know two
silver haired ladies I thought I could
combine
[Music]
it h yeah streaming is her job but like
you know there members take time off
here and there especially if it's for
help and especially if it's for your
boys then your whole job depends on it
so the more you stream the more you risk
it
and not even for a biscuit like I don't
think you're getting any biscuits except
from herb would be nice if she gave
us you know how Taco daies want cookies
from Ena would be funny of um herbs fans
with theand
[Music]
biscuits maybe they already
do or scones sces would be funny
[Music]
too I don't even like sces scones are
too dry and
like give me quol give me Spong cake
give me anything but a
scone even just a [\h__\h] normal bread I
prefer over scone but why do people like
scone so much that's why I don't like a
lot of afternoon teas that much because
at least in like England it's always
scon scones here scones there scones
everywhere
sad British noises sorry con are better
when warm I had them when they were warm
and I still didn't like them I would
still prefer normal bread if I'm putting
jam on something i' still prefer normal
bread with cream and jam nah I'm sorry I
wish I would like them I would feel more
sophisticated if I
did sadly I'm not sophisticated
enough yo yo yo
I'm getting better at this at
least it
[Music]
seems o o where you going where you
going too much momentum
[Music]
lot of combinable things lying around
but they don't seem to be willing to do
it there we
go yeah F almost fell
out well good night thanks for
[Music]
watching if I saw a lady at a coffee
shop with a cant C I think she's
sophisticated really just having
a wow it's simple to someone
sophisticated
huh then I must be extremely
sophisticated I eat quel all the
time but I don't look very sophisticated
when I get them in my [\h__\h]
pajamas with messy
hair waking up at 700 p.m. no but today
I didn't get a quo today for breakfast I
got myself
kaash
Ka love
Austrian dessert I want to like be able
to cook it myself I need to maybe do a
cooking stream where I just teach myself
it's in FY really not that difficult I
think I just I just in my mind it's
engraved in my mind that it's difficult
because in my childhood whenever my mom
would make it she's probably listening
right now
but five out the 10 times she would burn
it because I don't know she lost track
of it
like she was doing something else on the
side
so I would still eat it like scratch off
the burnt Parts because it went when
possible sometimes it was really really
burnt but my mom literally told me like
it's not that difficult it really isn't
your childhood memory fails
you okay
see about that I feel like fi putting
her here is kind
of let's put her close to no IDE do of
anything oh
nice wait in this position upside down
she looks like the the the the the the
fub fubuki fub FUBU Zilla from here just
upside down
and yeah it doesn't even look like
fubuki anymore
in this shape and
form I guess just from behind she
doesn't even have to be upside down from
this
angle
nice wait why won't you touch what's
wrong with you there we go just a little
bit of a
push oh uh how about here oh
God I'm chilling guys I'm
chilling I'm just chilling right now
looking forward to seven days to die
later oh
[Music]
thank you thank
you hey it's going pretty well wait
almost a like 4,000 okay not really but
like you know what is that over there is
that F yeah it's F come on I can't reach
her come on come on bounce off of fubuki
bounce off of land in the middle yeah
yeah yeah yeah
that's is
good that's is
good all right but nothing small left
now only big things I'm going to squeeze
this here so it doesn't get
lost IAM turns into
fuk let's land her over there
oh
freeas could have extended my chain but
okay I guess you hate me MAA they hate
each
other they totally hate each
other oh my
God triple Luna we got free moons now
who would have
[Music]
thought this just looks like a hot pot
right now let's cook it let's get
cooking come on see I'm I'm actually
doing a bad thing squeezing all these
smaller ones in between the big ones
making their chances to merge even even
smaller this is my
[Music]
fault [\h__\h] what
are you feeling what I'm
feeling this could be so good but they
hate each
[Music]
other oh my God oh my God
oh please calm down no momentum no more
too much
momentum careful kiar and other Hol
girls
[Music]
no too much
momentum not the other
thing all right we're we're combining
things they're growing bigger and it
will be the problem of future
Tak she'll have to deal with this
[Music]
I hate my
life I'm so close to another maximum
treasure future
now
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] past w cursed me
inde [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I could have been so good
I hate
this why why why why why why why why
[Music]
why are you guys doing better on your
side the ones who are playing on
their on their
[Music]
own tell me
why not particularly okay I'm glad we're
suffering together it makes me feel
connected to
you I unlocked T finally oh let's
go good job
[Music]
I got a million points waa in not in one
go I would
Fain cumulative
[Music]
right what that's so dangerous that's
like comparable to the moments in sua
game when something randomly goes like
pH into the
[\h__\h]
universe and then everything is ruined
all your efforts are just
[Music]
ruin really really really go over there
why won't you go over
there go over
[Music]
there a little bit too cozy
again I my MTH was wrong I thought that
was going to turn into Fuki but okay a
for
chain fruit getting yeated out that was
always such a I hate my life kind of
moment and why does life hate me
[Music]
indeed very wrong very
weird I I seems to be my new is she by
any chance in a position where Lami
originally was because like she seems to
want to get me in
trouble is
this I don't know
like this this pay Payback revenge for
something H talk was I
to
like
extroverted I thought we got along
pretty
well
[Music]
man I asked the color of her pan she
knew that was coming it was in the the
Google dock
[Music]
sheet no excuses she didn't have to
answer
it I didn't force
her but I think I'm really getting
better at this like I mean I think I am
I think I am am
I those were some stupid moments with
things falling off
but it just wasn't
fair it was just like too much momentum
I wasn't even that involved in those
moments when things fell
off
cop no I'll praise you once you get cie
o that's not happening
today not happening
[Music]
combining things feels so
good OBS yeah not OBS ISP
CH what is wrong with
you I thought we were through this I
thought we were over this I thought we
were done with this
[Music]
wow a nice
chain we're back welcome back was it a
millisecond well at least it's fast but
still messed up
yo look at this it's pretty clean it's
going to get messy from here
even with sua game I wanted to be good
at it but I never really got good at
it I
wonder
why even at these simple games I can't
get good I'm just not gamer girl enough
I need cat ears on my headphones
[Music]
my cats were involved in my
dream and I think whole life members
were also involved in my
dreams the horror part of it I don't
remember all of it anymore but they were
like ghosts or zombies or like an in
between thing of zombies and ghosts
maybe an Onie honestly
honestly um was like I was like yeah
trying to hide from it some somebody was
with me some ho I remember I
think and she dragged me into this
closet I think this is like me reliving
my memories from that one
um uh horror Escape game that we
did and we were in the closet and I
like at the corner of my eye I saw the
Onie going
around and then the person that was with
me was like all uh like Whispering do
you think they're gone and I'm
like thinking to myself shut the [\h__\h] up
it's he's still there don't
talk um but then she said something
louder right after that and then only
got us opened the door ripped it open
and I had I was so scared for my life
and the only took us and dragged
us and then it felt like the Onie
dragged us into a different part of the
dream
basically but for that moment when the
Onie had me I was living my reliving my
PTSD man from that escape
game so scary when we were hiding
too it was so
scary I
think never mind
but that was so scary I was screaming so
much back then if you haven't watched it
it's up on the whole live official
Channel some of you guys may have missed
it the Ina CI
Wawa in Japan horror Escape game and
boat
[Music]
Adventure Cali and Ena had a good time I
was
suffering um Fuki Z kind of
dangerous yeah yeah yeah okay okay
[Music]
okay can't miss the twerking lava plus
yeah I was I made the plushy dance Chima
now I need to make the plushy dance
Mirage but very difficult because the
plushy doesn't have fingers and the
Mirage
um Dance challenge you know I don't know
if you know this but the for me the
dance challenge is not the full chorus
it's the it starts
from basically the part that I did with
crony um the solo dance chart is a
little bit longer because I was like
because why not but officially I like I
would like the dance challenge should
just be should should just be that part
cuz I think it's really
caty and yeah
I want to show off those finger
movements surprised to captur it so
well are there any okay where are my
K-pop
fans in the chat I need to point out
something and I need you to agree with
me
um that was so unnecessary deaths I want
I want want a
refund I want a refund
now that was a sua
moment orbit we now have a earth now has
a third Moon
congratulations who who flew off who was
that that's our new
moon no stand by
right what a beautiful
moon I don't mind it but yeah Kpop fans
where you
at did you see from black pink Jenny's
new music video so I'm generally not
like a fan I'm not a hater but I'm not a
fan of like her but did you see did you
see yeah you saw now what I want to
point out is her outfit that outfit
where she's wearing that really really
really short mini skirt and like dancing
around the car the mini skirt and and
you can see like whole tummy like oh my
God and I look at that mini skirt and
I'm
thinking this is like the accurate size
of how my skirt the length of my default
outfit skirt would be if um people
cosplayed it really
accurately which I was looking at that
Alfred and I was thinking yeah no wonder
everybody cosplays it with most people
cosplay it with a much longer
skirt because I would not feel so
comfortable in that personally but it's
my default outfit so I have to wear it
but on a real flesh
person it's a little bit
more yeah so so like oh there is
there's no coverage of ass
provided ass will be
out you cannot bend down you cannot like
if you sit down on any surface it's just
your
ass your bare ass sitting on that
surface good luck in summer sweating
with your B like there's something about
let me tell you when when you wear mini
skirts or
whatever and it's summer and you sit on
some kind of plastic or steel or some
kind of seat if if you were wearing
pants or so you wouldn't be sweating but
I don't know what is I need to learn
about this science why do you sweat so
much more when it's your actual like
flesh touching the seat and touching
each other why would just wearing fabric
break over that prevent that I
wonder it needs to breathe why does it
breathe more when it's
covered I guess I guess you do sweat
more but it just automatically goes into
the fabric but that I feel
like I feel like I would feel that why
is
it so much more extreme when you're
naked
there Fabrica breathing skin is not
M the metal doesn't let it yeah I guess
so it's really
uncomfortable sweating
on yeah I feel I I I I feel bad of
course also for people who would sit
there after me and I was always feel
nervous when I'm supposed to get
up and then I
wonder will it look wet when I get up
oh so when I get up I like slowly scooch
scooch scooch trying to drag if there's
potential wetness there I like to like
try to like I don't just get up I like
try to move around to like maybe bring
it with me or like you know what I mean
I I don't know how to explain like I
mean I'm not sitting there completely
naked there's a certain amount of fabric
somewhere there right so I try to wh
that fabric maybe wipe it away if
there's something there I can't see it
but I
I I assume there's something
[Music]
there yeah so
anyway do you enjoy these annual sweat
it's not even summer right now thank God
actually
[Music]
I earn
iron what
what what's your problem you have
something to say to me
uhoh get in get in
[Music]
there I wrote oh
God I wrote a
message after that stream to crony I
just sent her an emoji of an eye and an
emoji of someone
running I don't know if she understood
what I was saying but then later a few
hours later she
replied and she was like what's up and
I'm like I don't know I just want your
attention and she's like a and I'm like
every every crony attention moment en
lengthens my
lifespan she seemed flattered by that I
mean it
though who's lying there I no
[Music]
Senai it's
true
Ian I'm surprised though I saw a
compilation after that uh I think it was
from C
carat uh of many moments when you guys
already pointed this out to me and and
moments where crony talked about it in
her stream
alone and I didn't realize this
yesterday that We There were already
moments where you guys pointed it out to
me in the past didn't
realize before
Gore a long time ago now finally we had
this interaction this realization
together I'm still baffled I don't mean
like I don't want to I don't mean to
insult her but I'm I'm just really happy
to find some it feels like validating to
me that she says it that way
that's validating to
me I don't know this is too risky is
it
here oh God there's something small in
the middle I don't want to cover it
up it's F Senai but I have to I'm forced
to cover it up now can't throw that I am
Senai anywhere else oh and now I get the
F really get in there
it's so
over it's so
[Music]
over try again get okay combined with
the other one
fine that flare is forever lost in
there is it ironic that crony took it as
a disc she she only took it as a disc
that's a joke I think I hope
so h
[\h__\h]
[Music]
internet
bro
[Music]
bro oh finally back
bro I'm so
mad I'm so mad is this going to happen
during seven days to die too look at
this [\h__\h] pile of
[Music]
crap it's looking really bad I hope it
won't I hope so too but at least it's
not
fortnite but the problem is it kicks me
out of the game completely each time and
I have to restart cuz like I can't start
the game normally through the normal
steam start button I have to go into the
server window and then open the server
put the password and everything it's so
annoying it it takes so
long it takes so long to get into the
games oh my internet messing things up
like that would be really bad and of
course I I just mean I don't mean The
Sire of
course h
H where do I put you where do I oh this
is this okay this is really bad this is
really really bad this is really really
I need some serious merging happening
now
but at this
point it's so
over something will pop
off you're not even you're not even
merging
okay not going to do that I'm not going
to do that M Senai I'm not doing
that [\h__\h] [\h__\h] don't give me these small
fries
um I think it's so over
yeah that was so obvious that was that
was going to happen because at that
point any big merch that I would need to
clean it up would also result in this
kind of
explosion it's rough
man wait the two P
clears are two in a row
right maybe I should just change it to a
different one at this
point no I mean the coyote ones not the
C ones I think the coyote ones are two
in a row
[Music]
she thank you for watching good night
you guys are going to bed so early I'm
so proud of
[Music]
you my head
hurts just one clear yeah I'm thinking
about it maybe if I fail quickly I'm not
going to force it now but if I fail
quickly soon then I'll switch
[Music]
toai that might be a little bit more
realistic to get one clear of something
at the coin
yeah we're getting to the free hour mark
soon I think at three hours I'm going to
just forcefully end
it cuz I have
to if I want a chance to wind down for a
nap usually my body
will happily take the offer of a nap
all
[Music]
right the chain thing see I have idea
for another another buff
item um extending the time window for
chains by 2 seconds 3 seconds or
whatever so that you can get longer
chains easier and when you activate it
it will only happen like once in the
Run yeah yeah yeah wow I should they
should hire me for brainstorming new
ideas for this
game I should just make my own game
become game developer put my cat's
images into every corner of the game see
now if I had extended the time window
that would have added onto the
combo wouldn't that have been nice huh
that would have been nice
[Music]
blackj black check game I don't know if
I were to make a game it would be a
jrpg but that's very
ambitious I my dream used to be uh being
a character designer for mm RPGs or
jrpgs like any kind of cutesy oops
cutesy [\h__\h] sorry I don't even those
silver ones they blend
together no like I legitimately dream of
something in the quality of tales of
games okay let's switch it and give it
one more try and hope it will work out
um um we keep what I guess we can keep
her although those ears I wonder if the
ears
ever uh get in the
way I
wonder they do seem to or do they are
they all just round hit
boxes are
you not sure
try sting by actual head size like m is
larger than flare maybe
swi what do you mean actual head
size doesn't really matter they change
in size depending on what position
you're giving them
right you think they have the same it it
would only be fair otherwise the The
Meta would be to only put girls in
without
ears no no ears girls
only that would be the EAS
[Music]
way superai would be very popular then
although the cap a little bit there's a
little bit of obstruction
[Music]
there I've been watching this Survival
Channel
recently the past two three
days really good filming and editing
honestly so this guy he goes to places
he usually what he will bring is like
just his camera stuff
and maybe his canoe if PE go to a place
where there's a lot of rivers and stuff
[Music]
and and like a
machete maybe sometimes sometimes a tent
but sometimes no tent sometimes really
amazing like he will build a whole
shelter from
scratch with the
machete like he did it on like deserted
Islands but he also sometimes he's from
Canada it
seems and
so uh the deserted island ones are like
very interesting of course but they're
not the like most of his content most of
his content uh seems to be filmed in
Canada and so in Canada it's more like
mountains and cold stuff and so on and
and then he will bring his
canoe Cano is it called
Cano in
[Music]
English no it wasn't Bear Grills was
someone else I need to look up the name
again yeah yeah and so I've been seeing
a lot of the
Canadian
wilderness mountains there's not much
not many animals running around
actually very
vast mountains and and Fields very
pretty though very
beautiful very calm very
Serene I'm going to tell you
channel name when I get a a hand
free cuz I think the videos are really
well filmed and he's not like I've seen
other Chanel I had a streak where I I
binge watch someone else's survival
videos um that guy seemed to be a bit
more skilled and knowing a bit more
about stuff but this guy that I'm
watching right now I don't mind that
he's not like on the level as some
others I feel like it's a bit more
realistic and
relatable like he still [\h__\h] up some
things and still learning some things it
seems but but at the same time it's
still impressive what he
[Music]
does yeah remember when I was watching
stuff and I was telling you guys about
about um spare fishing that was so
[\h__\h] cool I was like I want to learn
how to spare fish
but then this guy the Canadian guy so in
his like uh he did one video on a a
deserted island like kind of
tropical and then he did one in the
jungle in the
Amazon uh
rainforest and so in those videos he
says where he gets those survival skills
from which I don't see other people ever
crediting the people who taught them
them really um but he shows that there's
like this like course that you can take
in these areas there's a jungle survival
course from some YouTuber person and
there's a there's a deserted island
course from a different person there's
these courses and I'm thinking to myself
yo this is so sick I want to take one of
these survival
courses so
cool I want to learn
that so interesting yeah if it's
somebody who's extremely experienced and
tells you how stuff works and is
together with you and maybe a couple of
other people that
is I
byebye why you hate me
why oh oh my got something you keep that
by cute sure come in join us
ow my elbow
one more try one more try we still have
[Music]
time
okay
yeah maybe one day I'll take one of
those
horses I want to learn survival skills
it's just you know those kind
of Basics that okay you will probably
not need them ever in like you'll never
really be in a situation where you need
to survive in a
jungle unless I actually wait there
might be I travel so much on
airplanes knocking on wood but if if I
ever happen to crash
somewhere in a jungle or on a deserted
island and I would know how to
survive if I survived the emergency
landing or
crash
D that would save my life
possibly no no no I could
survive hey I I I there's there's
circumstances
in some circumstances maybe I will
survive you know they don't always crash
the same
way chances are not great but yeah
hopefully I'll have my camera with me
and then be able to document my survival
just
kidding just kidding but um yeah
realistically this will never happen
thankfully I guess but I still want to
learn it it would be so cool honestly
just because like watching this guy do
that um especially in Canada that felt
like
so refreshing
and feels like a nice way to get away
from the internet and all that toxic
[\h__\h] for a few
days and I thought of a genius
moneymaking uh business
scheme let's say you are so good at this
survival
stuff that you can easily just you know
go into the Wilderness find some food
yourself go fishing Grill your
food you can easily go out there for 5
days or so six seven days even
maybe and basically you
are not
um
wow you're not spending any money right
cuz you're just like living off nature
and
stuff
so how
about you rent out you wait you rent out
your place in on Airbnb and each time
you get someone to rent your place
you're like okay I'm out you take your
survival stuff and for 5 six days you're
making money with your Airbnb your home
that you will get back to after but in
the
meantime you're surviving easily
comfortably and having a nice time out
in the forest or in in the jungle
wherever on the
mountains and you come back and you made
money just by being away for a few days
and and you didn't spend any money
either though cuz you're just eating
nature just enjoying nature having good
time I like this
lifestyle I I think that's
genius why
not write that down write that
down yeah like I think that's that's so
genius just rent out your place make
money when somebody Rents It you leave
your home for a few days you come
back live comfortably then you don't you
don't need a [\h__\h] job either
maybe probably just live off with
that I don't see any flaws I don't see
any flaws
either it's a perfect
[Music]
plan that's called being a landlord yeah
yeah yeah but the thing is like then if
you if you rent out something on Airbnb
normally you have a different flat where
you
live uh uh but in this case you don't
need a different one you just keep the
one that you're renting out and then you
just go into the nature for the
[Music]
meantime it's
different one the help when you stuck in
the w
[Music]
n they can help
themselves you you'll just put an
automatic lock system into you don't
even have to do the check in check out
you just put the key
somewhere worst case you probably have a
friend in the city who can for worst
case maybe take over if they I don't
know if they're [\h__\h] toilet breaks or
whatever or you just send a technician
but don't have to do anything can give
them a contact number for technician
case normally nothing
happens no if you because you wouldn't
you it's difficult to live in the
wilderness for your whole life life and
you still want some home to go back
to but every once in a while going into
the Wilderness is
nice why don't you understand this plan
stop trying to find flaws in my plan
it's
perfect but first I have to learn these
skills I'm saying as if this is my end
goal maybe it is maybe it
[Music]
how's this going so far guys I've been
yapping so I don't really know if I'm
doing well I think it's doing okay
yep yep yep wa it is doing
well is doing well let's keep her in the
middle that's actually middle is perfect
it's good that she's positioned like
this right
now perfect I could just Place someone
behind her and keep her pushed into the
[Music]
middle me
com yes is
nice
roll in the middle is the best
ever let me Place her right next
[Music]
to this could be
good 2,000 points and I'm still alive
let's go up to
5,000 I want to see big cats and that is
not allow that is OU sampai in
big that's the big cat I want to
see nice cleaned up that one too okay
okay okay where do I put
hat I guess I I might have
to I might have have to throw her in
there she's pretty big
turn to oh well
okay I hope it won't get too tight here
I hope there's going to be space enough
but as long as Aqua SAA is in the
middle this is
ideal oh
wow this is like the most ideal run I've
ever had in terms of
[Music]
positioning wait
don't know where to put her either now
the the the the the lineup is kind of
bad right
now oh
[\h__\h] uh are we back man I put Fuki
simper in a really bad
situation oh
well oh well regretti
spaghetti oh I'm pushing I'm pushing oh
nice nice nice nice
um I what do you think fubuki turns into
no no is right next to her could this go
wrong or will this go
well do it should I do it kind of from
an angle or maybe not necessary
yo yo yo no what are you doing she's
right
there she's right there I should have
done it from an
angle she's right
there the sharks are smelling your blood
nowhere to stand by please
go oh no maybe if I put the there there
should be space for an a sire right
there yo okay nice w
[Music]
get things a little bit more messy but
oh
well put it up here
o I'm I'm why are these sub not
combining hello do you think if I make
this IM man into a fubuki sfire she will
push oh it just happened on its own
thank you thank
you oh oh I think get in there come on
mingle don't be so shy why is she she's
so shy she's like they're having a party
here and she's standing in the corner of
the party looking at her
phone standing there all
alone this is pretty darn
good we have a TOA Senai next to an aqua
Senai literally they're touching
H where to put iism but this is kind of
messy here with the small ones and I get
an auki next
so I don't want to mess that
up I don't want to mess that up over
there I don't want to squeeze anything
on top of the F yeah here looks like she
could land quite well here but I don't
know how high to froze
I'm
scared oh okay that
worked get in get in
yes don't bounce so much they're
bouncing so much I hate
it oh my
God oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my
God oh my God oh my
God oh my
God just run
[Music]
hello oh my
God I died again but it's going so well
no I please [\h__\h]
you look at this you're missing a lot of
good
combinations ah h
[Music]
I have a lot of space in Fury but then
again I
don't this is such a good
run and this will be my last one put
hatam on
flare
really I don't want to cover flare up
you know I could put her next to her
hopefully I don't want to put her on top
Stay Stay okay okay just be visible just
keep keep flire
visible I am on a fubuki would be good
but here there's the danger that she
will fall down and cover F Senpai I want
her there okay okay okay okay
[Music]
okay
okay is there space for an i in here
thank you
yeah help
it I'm scared
chat I'm not in Japan I'm in Austra I've
been back for a while
now on AI ah yeah true true thank you
thank you oh oh no
okay oh I
don't what if I is it bad to squeeze her
in like here
[Music]
who who to who who to same
spot
okay
okay okay nice nice
um please don't please don't do anything
weird okay okay okay
okay now I can't reach the hot but uh
maybe
okay I mean we'll figure that one out
eventually no no no is around right now
that's
okay whoo whoo wao C
perfect it's falling into my
lap I'm winning I'm
winning I'm
winning oh my
God going to cry
let's go where do I put the small
fish maybe just here
then H oh wait
's not really that much space I think it
will be fine as I am goody gitty
like should I combine with the hatama
this it's probably fine bit I'm a bit
scared but about the consequences
but okay okay I pushed her in a little
bit more wait wait wrong I thought it
was FL
Senai [\h__\h] probably was looking at the
top right there oh and there I go
messing it
up oh that's
that's that's pretty
bad but okay she she she angled herself
a bit more towards the
inside no that is better placed here
here right now I
think
[Music]
oh okay okay
okay cleaning up once
[Music]
again okay all
right why don't the subar ever touch
should I try to squeeze in here or there
here
risky
Hat's
relatively big not the smallest
one I mean we can just let it happen
naturally I guess but to the right of
the shoe buuz not that much space and
they don't
really budge budge
H next is
azuko so might want to make some space
for H and AI together next to nor maybe
although maybe on top is
better on top of one of the
noas maybe here possibly that will push
the TOA and the TOA will push the Subaru
eventually
you want her here I don't know like
there's a lot of space here I could just
build another person
here but then I'm cutting off the
Subaru's
Lifeline the Subaru Twins and cutting
them off when there's still potential
for them to just
touch yeah let's not split them on
purpose I would say
she
here I'm more leaning towards here
but feels a bit more spacious here in
the
gap
[Music]
between nah
sh should probably avoid potentially
blocking
Aqua
AA
okay that was a decent argument ah
there's another hat coming up so I don't
really need to build the
auki right
there
but two hatam turn into one I and we
don't have an right now we don't have a
fubuki
[Music]
either [\h__\h] now now now it's really
detrimental sorry it's just it's it just
looks oh no whoa W whoo whoa whoa are
you sure about that I are you sure about
that I'm not so sure about that
[Music]
I'm not making good life decisions
anymore
[Music]
possibly nice block I
know
[\h__\h] well I
guess I don't know man there's so much
space here but I don't want to block
I'm insisting on
that
um probably going to combine with this I
am the good thing is that that fubuki
can then merge with that n down
there yeah the one on top is safer and
then ah you're going to grow so big it's
going to be a
problem there is a fubing coming
oh it can
fit yeah for
now maybe
but okay no explosion I was a bit scared
those moments are very
important now this hatot I I can't I
can't trust
her I better place her close to I
Amai like I'm going to try over I
Amai no no
no
yo she blocked the ball of a
stick Sweet Lord nice say I just moved
her over there while she was
falling if I wasn't paying attention she
would have
[Music]
fallen oh wow wow wow wow wow wow oh
[\h__\h] now it's looking a whole lot
Messier cuz of all these random ones in
between
fub [\h__\h] it's it seems to be very
difficult to throw over I am it so I
have to throw by the side but the angle
sucks the angle
sucks save of the
year it'll chain once Amma comes on top
of yeah I want to put her there but I I
I I don't know
like if I throw it here it'll be like
weird with auki
s and here it will just probably roll
over to the
[Music]
right thanks for the membership gift
it's very nice of you I'm just going to
do it I'm just going
to here what do you think
here here
is yeah and then I'll move I try to move
over to I right away
okay it was fine it was fine and we got
an IR right away I should have seen that
coming literally because it's right
there but
okay that was scary that moment
of
moving very
scary oh God we're supposedly really
close to something
uh
fukai I don't want to block the asuki
[Music]
Senpai but we got another one right away
which makes a norer but I don't have a n
Senai right now yeah close to sha
maybe yo stay [\h__\h] she's moving [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] s wiggle
wiggle are we good we're good I wiggled
her well enough then I can land this
fubuki hopefully on I hope it roll to to
the
right nope it didn't and it blocked my
auki
Senpai God
lord everything's moving that hota is
about to be the end of
me yep yep she will end
me should I try to push
her those two those two
I'll
[Music]
just should I go for this one or that
one very very dangerous very very
dangerous left or
right top one safer
brisket on ah you mean Fuki Fuki no oh
yeah okay yeah but how do
I I don't know if I can throw it over no
it didn't work last time with the other
ones and no is bigger than what what
whatever whatever was there last time I
think I don't think I can throw
over may like oh God
I'm okay okay
[Music]
okay I was so close to it that was the
most ideal thing
ever ah Mama
mia oh was so
[Music]
close good try
though good
try I
guess
ah what can I do besides trying two more
for Ena what do you mean two
more
damn damn
I'll I don't know maybe I'll try to play
this game again on stream in the next
two weeks or
so one of those
weeks it's so frustrating it's like so
regretful I tried so hard but got so
far yeah it's already past 11:00
p.m.
um yeah I guess I'll see you guys for
seven days to
die probably
today I wonder if it's going to be 4
hours
again
um
oh not joining
today
so okay I wonder how long we're playing
cron is sick too
[Music]
no oh oh well like at least the the main
gang probably will show
up everybody's getting sick
no be
careful be careful
girls don't go outside the outside is
dangerous yeah Calif M well certainly
also gigy
gigy gigy can't leave her wives
alone she has a family to
protect Austrian Norway 5 to1 what what
some kind of
European soccer football thing going
on the things you were talking about but
like what is it what what exactly is
it she has trees to plant trees to plant
and trees to destroy yeah where found
Nations leag
ahuh cool 5 to one against Norway I
don't know Norway I guess not so
good did we see Norway in the European
Championship I don't think we saw Norway
at
all there is no way that they're making
it anywhere let's go Austria
wow yeah this Austria once again popping
off
wow they didn't even qualify yeah Norway
not good wow damn feel bad for them
Norway at least they they have a
beautiful
country go Austria go Austria not
Australia
Austria same lineup as
UFO cool feels nostal
iic okay I guess maybe maybe I'll take a
nap I'll be so tired though when I wake
up um yeah thanks for watching was fun
was fun was fun A little bit of yapping
I could let out some yap
yap then I can't let
out too much during Seven Days to Die
the reason I mute myself so often
yesterday is just because I don't want
to clog the voice chat with my personal
questions and problems too much like my
self
conversations um anyway if you're
curious the Survival Channel that I've
been talking about was someone called
Xander with X sander
Budnik almost 1 million subscribers
like you can tell most of his videos are
more like Canada survival guess it's
really hard to survive
Canada but every now and then he does
some kind of like jungle stuff or Island
stuff but they're all nice I I haven't
watched so many of his Canada things yet
but there's so
many oh you like his channel too baby
sander baby Sanda grew up and is now
doing YouTube survival
[Laughter]
[Music]
stuff xanda grw up so fast yeah wow
maybe xanda can teach me things
[Music]
now yeah Mirage 500k soon yeah and until
seven days to die feel free to give
Mirage another click if you want I would
appreciate it and we can get there
probably tomorrow I'll upload a video
tomorrow
then yeah why not throw it out there
right
away thank you thank you thank you so
much for the support
and see you in free oh God three hours
in
say thank you and don't worry Europe
gang soon soon soon next week next
week we're going to have more European
uh friendly
streams although I don't
know that one 6 a.m. sponsorship stream
it's not very European friendly
but that's a sponsorship can't be
helped I don't know if I can put out a
schedule tomorrow though I'm still
waiting for for the reply if I can put
the sponsorship stream on my uh schedule
on my public schedule and I probably
won't get a reply until Tuesday possibly
because Monday is a public holiday in
Japan and it's like our department our
sponsorship whatever department has to
ask that
company and if they're not there on
Monday then it might take until
Tuesday to get an
and I don't want to I could yeah I could
just put in sponsorship stream I might
do that but
[Music]
mhm I'll probably do that cuz I am
impatient as
well yeah Canadian Thanksgiving what oh
is it already Canadian Thanksgiving
time no has nothing to do with
me I'm not Canadian I wish I
was tomorrow oh how nice hope you have a
lovely Thanksgiving then to my Canadians
if there's any in the
[Music]
chat Happy Thanksgiving see you later
guys German
re I'm
tired you could drink
[Music]
Coca-Cola CH chug chug chug ch ch
M
yipp it's a fortnite on drink AA yippee
[Music]