[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
currently i
am a little bit
not amused
because of the
annoying
stuff that i tried to do for like two or
three hours
um
but
welcome to the iron beats stream
i had this idea a while ago and i wanted
to
um make it come true yeah because i
i love um
i like i like doing you know creative
type of streams especially with the hand
cam
because i don't know it feels
more
uh
um
it's [\h__\h] hot it feels more
i know it's nice to do something with
your actual hands you know
now before we get started
and i want to get started because i
realized when i was testing
um
that it takes a long time to place each
bead perfectly
uh it takes a long time so
yeah it's uh finicky very finicky
um but before we get started
i wanted to open or like show
what elena sent me
oh i'm not gonna be using gloves i'm
gonna be using these tweezers they sent
them
you'll see you'll see what i have but
yeah and anna sent me some stuff
recently and i wanted to kind of like
show it on stream first
before you know i want to kind of open
it
on on a stream to have my reaction i
guess so that also dana can see my
reaction
i didn't tell her that i was opening it
uh today though
yeah
because
reina invented keyboards
and for my birthday she made a a
keyboard for me
and then she sent it she showed it first
in my birthday you remember
and then she sent it after that
and she didn't only send the keyboard
she also sent some snacks
so those are indonesian snacks
interesting rainy laughs yeah
so i want to take a look at that
uh
[Music]
my webcam is being very tender
i don't know why it's like a relatively
new one
and still
it's like
being [\h__\h] swinder okay let's start
there's some snacks in here so let me
show you those first
okay are you good webcam you're good
yeah yeah yeah okay so
oh we start with some
indonesian instant ramen
there's a
no it's it looks like ramen but it's
called me goreng
i know
nazi
i think i've had that many times in my
life
oh you put a fried egg on top
interesting interesting looks yummy
i hope it's not spicy she knows i don't
like spicy food so
i think she's aware of that and the
other one is jumbo
it's a bigger one but it's the same
thing in theory
[Music]
i wonder where the difference is besides
it's
like
i don't know what that means but that
wasn't on here
there was a legendary those are good
indonesian that's national treasure i
see it oh
it looks yummy i wonder
maybe it's like ramen that tastes like
nasi goreng
maybe
i'm curious
maybe that will be my dinner tonight who
knows
[Music]
oh
another thing is in here is
what is the east east valley cashews
wild harvest is harvested cacao cashew
nuts oh the cocoa powder on top looks so
soft
you see that focus
camera focus
it never does when you want it to
is that all you can do that's actually
it is focused
gently rolled in dark tropical cacao
oh that sounds yummy
i will eat these
n-u-ts
at some point
danger is dangerous dangerous maybe
maybe dana was aiming for that one she
wanted me to say that
i will lead teams and
yes uts
something else there's actually quite a
lot of snacks in here something else
that's in here is um
this thing
four delicious taste with
in one bite ah four delicious different
taste oh
maximum bite bang bang max
oh there's like some
rice puffy puppies
something that looks like caramel oh
yeah waiver caramel crispy chocolate oh
so good
oh wow
oh yeah it looks very crunchy
also says
um right here
yeah yeah
extra delicious long
interesting
maximum bite another one is
silver queen
chunky signature milk chocolate cashews
oh cashews again are cashews very
popular like
very common in indonesia
[Music]
cashew nuts
not my favorite type of nuts but maybe
it will be afterwards
it is oh
[Music]
indonesian snack box it i would say
although maybe
maybe it would be enough to do a whole
snapbooks review
compared to how much they put into the
other snack boxes that i ordered
actually
nah although like instant ramen you know
it's not uh i would have to like you
know
it's a bit different it's a bit more
effort
to make that on stream and also what is
this
what is this
[Music]
the taste of home that's the only word i
understand here
what is that
[Music]
the taste of home you always come back
to
is that so
i am not sure what to expect from this
snack from egg
[Music]
that one is a little bit intimidating
hey you guys saved a whole stream on
this but now i already started i already
started revealing it should i stop
revealing
[Laughter]
do you want to see the keyboard or
should i
oh god damn it
keep going
keep
[Music]
you're gonna see the keanu boy i know
right you want to see it yeah
all right let's look at the other sex
thing
what's this
this looks like a children's snack
fantasy stick ours is like the nutella
one where you dip it in
this is like the indonesian version
because i love that one the nutella one
it looks like it tastes like these
sticks here it's very tiny though very
small
very small
those aren't bad
my childhood
yummy
[Music]
conduct
i think that's what it is
nostalgic snack
ancient category
ancient
magic
[Music]
wait there's another one from the same
maker
oh
yum yum bubble puff
does reina like this i wonder
there's a bubble stick
this is like a
[Music]
cute cute
stick in there with a star shape
how does this work
this is a strawberry flavor a bubble
crops and
oh
interesting
interesting can't say much about it
right now what is this oh
uh-huh
[Music]
white coffee
you know i don't like coffee but is this
really coffee
oh yeah then there's coffee bones on the
image here
but it's what
does it taste like white chocolate
[Music]
instant coffee
you guys know i don't drink coffee
but maybe my mom likes it
yeah yeah my mom loves coffee i wonder
if she would like this one
white coffee i've never heard of such a
thing
[Music]
pour the contents of sachet into a
coffee cup
add boiling water stir and enjoy
oh
when my mom comes by soon
let's give this a try
let's go
okay okay
we have
oh
i love this type of melon
i love any kind of melon actually
oh this is
what is this
it looks
if that is what it is it looks so fuzzy
it looks fuzzy
cotton candy
it does feel soft
wait you can't you can sell caught some
candy like this
[Music]
how's that work there's cotton candy
inside
what that's crazy
i've never seen that before
yeah
[Music]
we don't have that here
oh my god
that's that's revolutionary
[Music]
you just package it but
and i'm really curious about this one
this is so interesting i've never seen
that before
i've tried so many snack boxes you know
from other countries
no one had cotton candy before that's
impressive okay and then we have two
types of chocolate oh that looks really
fancy
indonesian finest
chocolate mango steamed oh
and milk chocolate coffee novak
and number one in the world
milk chocolate with a cute cute animal
and cute it's like what's this one
called again
what is this little
little boy called
apokut
[Music]
what is he
but he said lubac
it's not a red panda
lumak
it is that no like english name
that's just what i feel like i was
thinking of a different animal but like
more of an english name
so cute
it does have similarities to a red panda
but it's not red
[Music]
oh chocolate they're like very thin
compared to other chocolates they're wow
they're so thin
interesting
[Music]
oh i love chocolate i love chocolate
okay but now
comes the real deal
the important thing
actually she sent
she sent a card
oh on the back she wrote in german
what i what she probably learned from me
you have to sleep i like you
cute
let's see
[Music]
i don't know if i can show the content
of the card to you guys maybe it's the
receipt
of the
parts of the keyboard
[Music]
let me take a look first before i show
you
what is it what if this is a love letter
what if this isn't i can't open it
gloves please gloves don't don't do this
to me i need to open it okay there we go
whoa it's so long
oh oh okay now this seems uh
[Music]
oh
let me read a little bit
hi kiwala
[Music]
i wanted to put in a card but i can't go
outside at the moment so hope you don't
mind the letter
contents kiki keys
your keyboard the extra keycaps and some
indonesian snacks enjoy
kind of not sure what to write now lol
you always work so hard i wish all the
good things to come to you smiley face
i'm so happy we could somewhat get
closer last vacation and i'm excited to
visit you in austria
with my tongue
love peanut
cute
spicy
[Music]
a little letter
sweet thank you raymond now we can take
a look at the keyboard yeah
take a look
and then tom joked the keyboard
it came with indonesian
newspapers
[Music]
oh well why is it so heavy oh it's a box
oh what the [\h__\h] what's so heavy
what the [\h__\h] is so heavy
oh [\h__\h] i need a scissor
ah
i didn't think of that um
we are be getting a scissors
[Music]
okay
i got a scissors
i
really
um appreciate the new keyboard because i
have um
i have the same keyboard for a while
and it's uh
it's really dirty i mean i could just
clean it but
[Music]
it's in this case you know a good
opportunity to get to get a new one
[Music]
it's packaged so nicely
oh [\h__\h] like i guess there's like
a base to build it with
and that's probably the box
yeah from the base oh
[Applause]
i don't know much about like making your
own keyboard actually i know nothing
about it so
this is the first
wow
why so heavy
it comes in this pretty big uh box that
says ki chrome
q1
a 75
mechanical keyboard an open source
customizable keyboard for peak
productivity
it's so heavy why is it so heavy
what's inside stones
oh
[Music]
i did ask her for like if it's possible
oh it's really happy
if it's possible for um a japanese keys
and she did do that oh here it is it's
heavy
look at that though
look at that
the camera is currently in a position
that i don't really want to move it from
because it's optimized for the
uh thing that we're doing next but i did
show you guys a picture on my birthday
stream
whoa
cool
now i have it in reality
she did send some extra keys right
[Music]
oh yeah
oh
there's some extra keys in here are
those maybe the ones that were in on
there originally
maybe
oh no those are also japanese though
[Music]
press it
[Laughter]
you want to hear the tonjap and i remove
the microphone closer to the to the
keyboard
[Music]
sorry
oh
did he hit us
do you hear it
it's an interesting sound not quite what
i like when i see keywords that uh have
the size of this
like that are where the keys are dead
thick
i kind of remember them sounding a bit
more um
disrupting i don't know how to explain
it but this small like
gentle look at the clock
[Music]
i don't know how to describe it because
i don't know a thing about keyboards so
there's like um
there's a this one the escape
button is a kotori
from the kfb logo
and then here we have
a sparks shift
yeah those are the special kiwa related
buttons on here
and then i think i think i would say
that the
this stuff around is inspired by sparks
as well since i mean the key is also
then that shift keys also sparks
i i can see the sparks in here like the
the yellow
and the black reminds me of the sparks
music video
oh it's all
in the back like it's all all covered in
that
pattern
oh it has like like golden
golden shininess when i like
i see it like reflecting
in the light wow
[Music]
pretty hey
thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
keyboard asmr
[Music]
ah
but do you want to hear them about the
music
[Music]
keyboard only
it's just me doing business
doing office work
sorry camera really shaky but don't
worry it's it's fixed
it won't fall it's just shaky
wow
and you know there's a really special
feature
with this keyboard even it's it works
even if it's not connected
even when you don't connect it it has
something really really really really
special about it
wanna know what happens when i press
sparks
[Laughter]
three two one
see
so smooth unbelievable
i'm just joking
i did that myself
did some people actually believe that's
what's happening
[Laughter]
ah you guys are too easy to convince
them to lie too
too easy all right then i will use this
keyboard starting from the end of the
stream
and get rid of my old keeper and i'll
never use it ever again
and thank you for the snacks too
they look yummy let me put them
back in the box so i have some space
oh
snacks
[Music]
okay
now we get to the
actual
stream
today actual uh actually what we wanted
to do
oh thank you for the super chat so far
guys thank you
hopefully i think i can read some super
chats today uh after we're done here
so i will put down this
i think
it's a microfiber
kiwawa
towel thingy uh
but i'm using it to make it so that this
is not so
[Music]
clear
so i've been i i got
the
um
agreement and judgment of
three different managers
so whatever you see has been deemed okay
just
don't make a big deal out of it it's
it's you can't the only thing you will
see is that i have a head
and that it's the shape of a head
um but i'm wearing my omo cat
uh cap
and uh yes i am
i have the i have a head oh my god
unbelievable
shouldn't be a big deal right i think we
always knew that i have a hand you can
see it
like literally
over there she she has a head
she
she has a head over there yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah hi hi kiwamo finger hi
all is okay there there's no like
clear features
but in any case
what we're doing today is you guys maybe
have done this in your childhood
um
let me show you what i got
i
got don't drop it don't drop it
millions and millions of sparkly shiny
new
beads this is just one of the boxes i
have two different colors uh color boxes
these ones that i just showed you were
are more like neon colors and these are
more
they have there's like i got some skin
color
[Music]
ish color too
so these oh they're so sparkly on the
camera
wow so yeah i have
a lot of colors
putting them down again
i don't want to drop anything if i drop
this [\h__\h]
i it will take me a million years to
collect everything again
we shall okay
okay and i'll be placing those on top
of here they're really tiny spikes i
think everybody knows this kind of thing
you know there's these
tiny spikes
and on top of those you put the beads
yeah
don't drop don't drop just go your own
way and then once you're
once you have something that
you're happy with
i always used to use i don't know some
sort of like baking paper or so i think
but this these ones came with like some
paper that i won't show up to like
there's like this kind of paper that
apparently you put on top before you
iron it and then i bought a little tiny
baby iron
it's so tiny
it's like
it's like so tiny
it's such a baby
i'm gonna iron it um
what we're making with this baby iron
it's such a baby and then the box it
came in was also so tiny
yeah
so um
i am prepared i am prepared and i also
have
i'm not gonna just be randomly placing
something and hope that it looks good no
no no no
as you saw in the
in the um
thumbnail i got some new cute
uh pixel art from dakoma
to use
as a reference and she even sent me
uh something to like um
you know uh like see a great so what
i'll be working with now is let me show
you
[Music]
wait a second
so we have
this
cute stuff as an option
and you know i i don't think i'll be
making all of these because i realized
you know it really takes a lot of time
surprisingly
um
but maybe in my private time too because
it's pretty relaxing
so the other thing i i requested
uh
these ones here as well
and nancy
no
no i i
we're i honestly we're lucky if i can
even make one of those happen
oh by the way the glow here
is from like an rgb um razor
headset stand that i'm using as a tripod
because i had uh nothing better a real
tripod was actually taking up too much
space so yeah
anyway cute right uh you guys are
welcome to use it yourself maybe as a
reference if you wanna and then
screenshot it now because i'll be
getting rid of it in a moment
three
two
one
okay
[Music]
wonderful
um
[Music]
i um how many we can do ah let me turn
the bgm on again
this will probably be um
this will probably be a very chill
stream too i don't know also i'm nervous
because of you know
this these handgun streams are always
making me nervous
how about we start out with elena
because she made me this lovely present
oh i can if i ever meet her again or if
i just send it to her
she can have the
this what i'm making if it goes well if
it goes well we should maybe warm up
with a chicken i don't know
should we warm up with a chicken
by making a chicken
i'm not sure
maybe maybe make a chicken although to
be honest the chickens look
only 20 percent less
like
work
but
i'll make
i'll make a chicken
first
[Music]
now whatever i'll go all in i'm gonna
make rain
egg forma i did warm up a little bit
because um this the set i bought it came
with
uh some
like um
it came with some how to say
guides
and i tried making one of them but then
i was too busy uh preparing the stream
so yeah anyway starting with lena
i i guess i shall start with the bottom
um they have an outline and we should
also decide
let's let's see what colors
her
[Music]
for her skin
i have this color
[Music]
ball
yeah
wow
i'm just gonna place it at the top here
and we have a shadow for the
skin
yeah
[Music]
oh god
so guys can you tell me right now you
don't you don't see like
you know anything in particular right
now right
right
what you're doing there's nothing
good
i'm
oh good i thought so i knew it yeah i
don't see anything either
[Laughter]
yeah
enhance no don't
and then
okay well her pants are gonna be white i
have a beautiful
white collared bead
just as reference and putting them in
the corner
and we will need a yellow a yellow yeah
i have so many yellows um
i guess probably
damn it
we lost one overboard
i will go with this yellow
for
her scarf
and then there's also some browns in
there
[Music]
you know i thought this was enough beads
and enough colors but you know you can
never have enough colors i will go with
this this brown
beat down beta i think there's a chance
that i actually ate one before the
stream
perhaps maybe
um but i'm okay
[Music]
i'm not sure
there's a chance i ate one but i'm not
sure i hope i didn't eat one and then
there's like an ah
an outline that in the art is not black
it's like a
slightly
slightly brownish black but i don't have
a color like that i'm just gonna go for
black
it will be a little bit less of a gentle
color but that's okay
[Music]
i think it will look good anyway so
black on black looks like this
[Laughter]
yeah
and then
[Music]
like
what color is that
[Music]
i guess we can try this color yeah you
don't know what i'm talking about oh
wait that's the same color as i want to
use for something else yeah yeah no it
actually is anyway even in the pixel art
reference
okay there's some red going on which is
that's her mouth
is that your mouth
[Music]
i'm not sure we'll just uh do it
some relatively dark
red well where are we here here we are
gosh they like they they're like little
bugs jumping around
and her eye color is
oh i have a good color for that
i will be using this color
wait you know what i'll i'll put elena
on the screen
so you know
um
even the people who come
out of nowhere we'll see
what i'm working on
[Music]
let's put lena on here
okay
[Music]
yeah her pupils are white but i can't do
this uh in this in this particular pixel
art
[Music]
and uh some dark blue
i have of course yeah bye
i think we lost another beat
dark blue
[Music]
and
we have all colors yeah her hair color
her hair color i'm thinking now this is
difficult i have this very very
um
pale purple that actually i think looks
the closest actually it might be perfect
don't you think it's absolutely perfect
holy [\h__\h] i'm lucky
the other colors would be like it's just
gray and white i think this is good
spot on actually yeah
damn
okay
okay then
on top of this kiwawa we will be
building
uh lena
and let's see so the base let's start
from the feet one two three
four five six seven seven
outline
blacks
let's get started
[Music]
this reminds me of the time
when um i built that uh where should i
start
does someone want to count from top to
bottom how how high it is but i think it
will fit into the circle
reminds me of the time when i built a
pixel art monument with guru
all right where's the let's see here's
the middle
[Music]
ah
where did it go out here
nah where'd it go
right here
uh i said seven right one two three four
seven six twenty seven thanks for
counting
thank you 27 i think that's
one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten okay yeah easy it's gonna fit
into the circle pretty much
are you guys seeing what i'm doing oh
it's not very focused is it
hello we are here please focus
let me do an
let me do an auto not not audio auto
focus i want to turn off the auto focus
and focus on myself
um
[Music]
no
here is it around here it's hard to see
well
it's fine
it's fine right
[Music]
ah the gloves no the gloves are not so
much the problem i'm just like the thing
that makes it difficult is i can't get
too close with my head because i'm like
scared that you know it's making me
nervous i tested it you know i tested it
i took videos and checked it
tested it with my measures
but i should
i want to get closer to it like really
close
to get a better look
[Music]
is it okay currently is it looking
tell me when you can see that um
in reality
um
i have no pupils
just kidding
tell me when you can see i have free
eyes
in reality
let me know
okay
first line first line down
okay wait this is too many one two three
four five six no it's correct okay
[Music]
okay second line
oh
okay it's free
does anybody actually like still have
something like this at home
i remember always doing it like after
school
um
like before going home i always went to
like something we called
um
it's like a like a kindergarten but for
what the school that you go to after
kindergarten
so you go there after the school
and then there's like something like a
teacher someone like a teacher like
taking care of you and giving you like
activities until
you usually go home around like 6 p.m or
something like that
day care yeah i guess you would prob
maybe i guess you can call it that
and there i used to actually me and the
other kids too we used to do a lot of
this
[Music]
but i never made something as intricate
as this back then i think oh i got two
at once nice perfect okay and then i
fill it out with
ah wait one black one in the middle
[Music]
they are hard to grab sometimes because
you have to grab them in the right spot
i used to do it at home but it's been at
least 18 years
oh
so so little boys like to play with this
too huh
it's fun
[Music]
okay now we fill it in with some skin
color uh i said i was gonna use this
color
[Music]
the thing is like when you put them on
here like it's very easy to like mess
everything up and throw them over and
like you know
mess it all up so you gotta be careful
because they you put them onto the
spikes but it's not like they're like
completely poking through they're kind
of just like
chilling on top ah
i'm just chilling on top
and they're not
not uh not perfectly secured
thank god i have a tweezer
where's the
[Music]
my hands are too shaky for this
that'll be extra precise yeah
i remember that as a kid i got one of
these beads stuck inside my ear i had to
go to the toilet
wait is that is that like a result of
being bullied someone like putting it in
your ear or did you do it to yourself
i i said i almost accident or i perhaps
maybe ate one before the stream but like
how do you get it into your ear
i was a dumb kid ah not a horde
i see okay we have the second row down
we're going pretty
well we're doing pretty well
okay next row is
[Music]
one
outside here one outside here thank god
they're like
pretty simple what we're working with
and then two of those brown ones that i
wanted
although maybe i should
uh maybe i should go for the other brown
[Music]
maybe i should go over that yeah
yeah okay i have changed my decision
i'm going for a brown wait that's the
brown i went for anyway never mind
that's the brand i wanted to use anyway
i'm going for
a little bit less saturated brown
is that properly in there okay
[Music]
okay
you know i see sometimes i see um
i see these
like creations
also being sold as like merchandise
at like conventions and so on in the
artist booth and i have to say like
i think it looks so good it looks so
cute
[Music]
like i think it's actually desirable
and what i'm making right now
i think if i give it to reina i think
she'll love it and you can make like a
keychain out of it you can there's like
uh i didn't buy that but you can
with these sets you can also buy
something to make a keychain out of it
it's too much work it is too much work
yeah it's like really small ones
you can maybe make a few ones like if
it's the size of this arena a few ones
are maybe yeah manageable but
it does take a lot of time you can see
how much time i'm taking if you know it
by heart
if you know the pattern by heart after
doing a couple maybe you can get faster
because you will already know our next
one i know this is a black black black
skin color skin color black cinco
skincare and so on you know
[Music]
that's what makes it special that's true
too
but you know
uh i was joking that i should
um
i should make
some
next birthday merchandise i should be
making these keychains for you guys but
better to just
not hand make it and just
create a keychain that looks like it's
um
iron beads
you know just make a normal pixel art
keychain and everybody's happy then
oh
where are we oh yeah the full row is now
black until
until the end okay until it's filled out
[Music]
it's going to take a while not sure if i
can make all of turducken
i do want to make a chicken too
[Music]
it landed on my table i dropped one and
then landed on my table
[Music]
yeah they look like pixel art that's why
it's perfect to make like pixel art uh
merchandise out of it
[Music]
be careful yeah
it takes patience yeah
[Music]
but it is relaxing it's like you know
like making a puzzle putting together a
jigsaw puzzle or
i don't know
okay well done
uh next roll
okay
on top
another black one
[Music]
here you go
the other side as well
actually
i think i'm pretty fast
you guys watching
my appearance in fauna stream where we
were playing una
[Music]
did you guys watch that last night
yeah
thank you
for sure
it wasn't so bad
[Music]
i i won like one time or so but honestly
even if i lose that uno it's not like
it's not really like something you can
say
oh that's
because you suck it uno
oh really game rng man it's it's just
rng like literally no one can tell me
it's not
okay brown one
[Music]
90 chance exactly honestly
the only thing you can really influence
is
remembering to say uno and challenging
others to that they didn't say uno
but even then
i swear i was pushing uh uno
and those times were
you know right after fun after i
challenged her i swear i was pushing it
but somehow the input didn't go through
so weird
[Music]
believe me campy
thank you for believing me because it
wouldn't make any sense literally one
second after me challenging her why
would i not
say uno and then repeat the same thing
again
five seconds later like how
i'm not that stupid okay
i have my stupid moments but that that
was not one of those
[Music]
relaxing
dropped it there it is
oh come on
[Music]
okay
run row
down again okay
oh it already looks like like her
feetsies it looks like what we're making
it looks like the thing over there
[Music]
oh
okay now we add a roll row
one pixel wider
[Music]
isn't this so cute
i saw like in the tweet replies some of
you said you were gonna um go buy some
and
do it on the side as well
[Music]
like you only do this really when you're
a child but
i i thought i was a genius when i had
the idea to do this on stream as a
handcam
stream
i i might be a genius
[Music]
like i find all these ways to do
creative streams
to do something like an art stream
without ever doing an actual art stream
it's like i keep on running away from
having to do an art stream but that ah i
do i know different kind of creative
streams
[Music]
this is art
this is crafting [\h__\h] see now now i'm
[\h__\h] some things up because
[Music]
yeah i have to fix it
it moved
[Music]
very finicky okay i'm gonna get back in
the line
that's so hot
the gloves are so hot
i'm turning the fan all the way up from
my good
and i'm wearing a cap it's
i don't know if it's even helping at
this point do i really need to wear the
cap oh my god
with it
i don't think the air is reaching me
though
so i turned my back to it
i made a table today
i'm so proud like i ordered a side table
so that i can do these streams properly
on my next like in my office
[Music]
huh
oh thank you you watched me draw new
ears thank you
where was
i oh okay black
i ordered a height adjustable
removable like with with um
wheels
little side table
and now
basically my office desk is basically
l-shaped
yeah
and it's it's perfect i love this
so glad i got it
it's really helpful
and i was worried about building it but
it was very simple and i was able to do
it
one of the
maybe
three
maximum free pieces of furniture i've
ever built myself
i can't even remember the others but i'm
i'm thinking that there must have been
something else
before
something
well here normally i get help
but this time i i was like this should
be simple enough so i'll be able to do
it
if i can't do this then i can't
live alone
so
[Music]
gosh i'm feeling so hot
okay here we go
another row done
oh it looks like her feet
let me let me um move the
oh the fan a little bit
[Music]
tight space now
okay
how about this
[Music]
making green progress yeah i think so
too
cute
lower abdomen complete lower coming well
her legs are her legs are complete
because this is where her crotch starts
um
okay
oh let's start from the right let's do
um basically one black one and then like
a
chess pattern
almost
of those colors repeating the brown and
the
brown and the yellow the brown and the
yellow
easy
i know it's true but damn quavo excuse
me
i'm just
i'm trying to be a professional
bead
uh iron beader okay
uh look at that and look i'm so proud
where am i okay yellow and another brown
and then three whites
[Music]
yellow another brown and three whites
yellow
[Music]
you know yesterday when i was doing that
valley hair relaxant
you know
i was having fun you know but i was
worried the whole time
that
history would repeat itself remember
that one time when we played uno on my
channel
and i did some babu babu talk
i got like i got like so much
so much [\h__\h] for it
so
now i'm always like kind of worried that
if i commit to something
people will get
annoyed and must [\h__\h] on me for it
oh
my gosh
it's like
i'm just committing to the bit you know
but it seems like for the valley girl at
least
it was okay
i didn't see
complaints in particular
oh yeah and i'm glad i didn't get the
ooh look
that's the game because i feel like that
would have just turned into baby talk
it's basically the same thing
so i'm glad i didn't get it
[Music]
i mean i i enjoy doing little baby talk
but i feel like people would just [\h__\h]
on me again so yeah anyway that's just
some real talk
there's something that was on my mind
okay
why is it sauce um
so unfocused let me fix in again i don't
know why
i don't like it alan we have a lot of
detail going on here i wanted to be
focused
[Music]
i don't think it's even able to focus on
that
[Music]
ah
i think this is the best i can do really
apparently what the hell
i'm using the the logitech stream cam
it's maybe a little bit better
[Music]
too small
okay okay again
next row next row next row
i'm so cute i love it i want to make
millions of those if they wouldn't take
so much time
i think we're going inside and one pixel
inside
so one less width
and that's for two rows
[Music]
let me prepare that already here there
you go
ah don't mess it up
there we go
and then
uh one brown
brown yellow brown yellow
surprise surprise
[Music]
brown oh
okay
this could be my new go-to gift if i
meet another home life member
you know how i always bring them like
austrian chocolate like austin chocolate
cake and so on
maybe my new go-to gift will be
this there's a lot of time i would put
into that
but i think they would have really
really loved it whoever i would give it
to
how could you not
[Music]
one more row of white pants and then we
see the tummy
[Music]
yeah very personalized very cute
you know another thing i was
uh
thank you james oh i just want to talk
to her
oh you like sick or so get well soon
please
another thing i was
uh
occupying my brain with
a yellow brown yellow brown today was i
i finally
um
started
like a kind of like a how to say
a prototype
prototype
i don't know maybe not even prototype
level maybe already more advanced than
that but a prototype plan
of
um
my
taskmaster inspired game show
you guys know i've been watching that a
lot
i'm currently at season 10.
thank god they have so many seasons yo
and wait i'm i'm thinking
you know vr blah too much work [\h__\h] that
so
i i thought of some
some tasks that are possible without vr
and just by basically voice and maybe
drawing and so on
and i got a couple
oh no this is for yellow okay
[Music]
now i'm just uh today
today i made a plan like an outline
[Music]
of what the tasks will be
i want to do it in like end of september
or middle of september
depends on
i guess the timing of who wants to
participate
now i just um
i asked
everybody who wants to be part looking
for like
five to six people maybe
[Music]
i think
so i'm saying prototype is because i
just want to see how it goes and how
how manageable it is and
i don't want to like it and like
a lot of
special
extra
assets for it like a new background or
whatever i'm just gonna be reusing a
background i think like one one
background i never really use is the one
for the outfit review from
um
from my fancy dress and i think that
kind of fits because taskmaster also
always happens in this
beautiful big
uh
venue
that looks kind of like classical
[Music]
i don't know like a
like a concert hall almost
[Music]
so i think i'll just reuse that
and then maybe get like a
uh
how to say what you call like speaking
speaking um table
podest
something like that
for me
[Music]
now here we have the belly button
and with the belly but [\h__\h] with the
belly button in the middle
come on
[Music]
there you go
with the belly button in the middle
we have the belly button
belly button
i've been getting a ton of taskmaster
clips in my recommended that's probably
because of me
because you're subscribed to me and i'm
watching it so it's recommending you
what i'm watching
yeah i'm watching
so much of taskmaster
okay next row
oh we're getting we're going uh one more
inside
dropped it
come on come here
be a good bead easy
i hope the ironing goes well because
that's one thing i haven't tested but it
should be fine
[Music]
what's your favorite task for stuff yeah
there's so many i've watched 10 seasons
i don't remember
don't remember
okay
uh outline and then we have
one yellow one skin tone and then fill
it up with all black
one
[Music]
yellow
come on
be
[Music]
one nice tone
fill it up with black
[Music]
we will have enjoyed the time regardless
of what the final part is thank you
[Music]
we confirmed it aha
you see
you get recommended when we watch
isn't that kind of cute
don't you feel like connected to us now
by watching the same things
[Music]
if you ever get a
don tendo
video recommended german german youtuber
then that's probably because i'm
watching it
you can thank me for that
ah where did it go
i hear
[Music]
kimaritonjo
i'm also making beat creations at this
very moment only depends on making
cuphead characters oh cool
hey what are you doing on this side with
me noise
we have like
45 percent of her body
yay her head is pretty big though
how about next
get some water
[Music]
big head
hey they're all the same color
i don't know if that makes it really
easier or more difficult to count them
you know if they're all the same color
okay next row
we have
one less again
[Music]
i'm so glad i joined kfb ah
i'm glad you joined here with me too
welcome
welcome to king
ah
[Music]
uh what do we have one skill skin color
and then uh filled with black okey dokey
[Music]
i'm so excited for the result holy [\h__\h]
this is so cute
[Music]
if we ever do that charity stream
i will make one of these as a prize the
charity raffle
or whatever
i should i'm gonna remind them about it
say again i wanted to do this when are
we doing this question mark
[Music]
wouldn't you want a handmade
super rare kiwa iron beat pixel art
keychain
[Music]
cause they're also really sturdy like
once you iron them
they're so sturdy like it's basically
it's plastic
[Music]
custom made it to the to fit the chicken
that won
[Music]
i don't know about that
if they request something difficult or
complicated i don't know but whatever
it's um whenever the time comes we'll
see
[Music]
we'll see what i can do
next round
already next row is gonna be like a
little bit transparent um
so like kind of like a
brownish color
there ah which is
it's the same color as the scarf right
in this case or is it
it looks like the same on the pixel art
but maybe i'll use a different one what
do i have
ah i'm gonna use one since it's like
you know it's supposed to show a little
bit of the skin i'm gonna go with one
that's a little bit more
skin colored
i guess
it would be here
and if that looks weird to me i'm just
gonna change it but i think it's fine
oh good night
[Music]
the ones who go to sleep
sad
you leaving me sad
[Music]
you know what i saw today was really
cursed
i saw something that has
hurt me deeply
left
mental damage eternally
i was just scrolling through twitter
and i saw a video
of some apparently
a rapper
standing in the middle of shibuya
uh
in tokyo
being like confused why nobody
recognizes him
and then
i was like i don't even know who he is
what the [\h__\h] is that
what was this thing little
um
[Music]
the gucci one
little pump yeah you know him huh
so since i was curious i was like i
don't know who the hell that is you know
what maybe i'll go for it
maybe i'll go for a gray instead
let's change that
dark grey
i don't know what that is so i looked it
up
yeah nobody knew him and i didn't know
him either so i looked him up and i saw
like he has this one song
well he keeps on repeating gucci gang
gucci gang gucci gang gucci gang gucci
however instead of watching the original
what was recommended to me
was like meme videos where they changed
up the song
[Music]
and then there was one that got me
laughing so hard
it was like
every time
uh
every time he says gucci gang the song
gets faster
and it's so funny because it was like
and i'm like this is so stupid and
hilarious
oh man
had a good laugh at that one
now i know who he is not that i give a
[\h__\h] but
yeah
surprise you guys a lot of you guys know
him
apparently
[Music]
i'm around her neck now
yeah whole life song should be
known
as more than the gucci cat
i don't know him only from the japan
video oh
[Music]
you also only knew what that has been
making rounds huh
my video
[Music]
and then after watching that video i had
this this gucci gang
speed up video in my head for
an hour
as long as it's not the original
it's so good
once again good again
[Music]
why did i remind myself
she's
almost done
[Music]
is the red
wrapping her mouth
[Music]
i feel like
it's her neck huh it looks so red
[Music]
should i maybe just make it like a dark
dark brown
or i can i guess actually i have a good
color for that
i have like a like a in between color
it's like a red red brown that i haven't
used yet
[Music]
wait she had a red choker
she has a red choker is that not just
her like i don't know that gonna tell me
no she doesn't right
[Music]
no she didn't okay then i guess it's
just the skin color basically
shadow
for the skin color
[Music]
okay so three in the middle
once again
[Music]
it looks good like
as a whole
especially as pixel art if it's small
when you make it big you question some
things
well yeah that's her neck yeah yeah
yeah and now
i'm gonna
do the hair
i'm so glad i have the perfect color for
the hair
[Music]
yeah oh oh i dropped one perhaps on the
floor i know it's it's here oh my god
i'm so lucky
keep on dropping it in reach
[Music]
[Applause]
you know my day today didn't start very
well because i woke up and then i
actually had like a [\h__\h] nightmare
once again i only have nightmares these
days a lot of like
dreams where i'm being followed or
someone wants to kill me
um
it's not very nice
i've been having a lot of dust
and um
[Music]
and then so after the nightmare i wake
up and
i check my phone and immediately have
like some
urgent
annoying
work-related
matters to attend to
yeah couldn't even
get breakfast first
[Music]
not the best way to start the day
well
what is important
hmm
if you're too hot when you sleep you
might have nightmares
i i mean it is pretty hot in my room
when i sleep even you know
[Music]
uh
well i don't know if it's because of
that
i just
i'm also just really stressed out
and
i have some
[Music]
concerns and worries
at all times
oh is that her ear that's so cute
oh my god
ah ear
hair
[Music]
nothing i can't talk about even if i
want to talk about it
[Music]
hair and then like a blush
oh so cute it looks so good
this is such a genius
honestly
honestly if i didn't have a reference
from dakuma
i would be lost
the lost lamb
liking the cult of the lamb
[Music]
that's your mouth right i could even
make the mouth pink no
i don't know
i don't want to risk it
i'm just gonna make it the skin color
again
what can it kind of because the the
shade is
red it kind of looks like
that's her
mouth maybe
[Music]
yeah it would be really wonky
you know what i want to try
[Music]
adding
adding my personal ideas
i'm gonna
[Music]
i have this cute pink color what if i
give her like a smile
nah but her nose is there
it's gonna no wait there's no nose
that's her mouth what if i give her a
smile
that look weird
[Music]
like
diagonally above
[Music]
yeah i know girls have no nose that is
true
did i use the wrong one
that's the wrong one yeah
like
so
[Music]
it's just three pixels
but yeah i don't know if you see what
i'm doing but it will give her maybe a
smile
maybe
dakuma is probably
shaking their head furiously like what
are you doing
you're ruining it
[Music]
it might work
it's gonna look great right next to the
eyes
yeah
maybe
we'll see we'll see when we get there we
can still fix it
once we have the whole image
[Music]
or
i mean okay that if that looks wrong
then i'll just change the color of her
neck to a more brown less red color but
right it's already kind of like a
more brown color
okay where am i now i kind of skipped
something here uh
there okay two skin clowns
or no one more
one more
[Music]
tomorrow we're playing ross by the way
but i scheduled it at an early time and
right now i don't know what to do with
my sleep schedule because i don't know
if i should go like backwards or
forwards with it
um
because of popcorn
because i have to be
awake
at 4 00 a.m or so actually probably at
maybe at 3 a.m like be on standby and i
think the panel is at 4 a.m for me and
afterwards i have like two hours of meet
and greets
so i'll have to probably be awake until
like 7 8 a.m or so
so if you consider that
oh
[Music]
do i wake up at free
or do i
stay up until 8. you know it's it's the
worst possible time
oh
wait a great school till 9 00 a.m oh
that's even worse okay do i stay up
until nine
or do i wake up at four
[Music]
ah wake up nah but that's actually with
my currents i don't know it's both
let's both have
it's both tough
ah
because of you know the una colab
keeping me up
i was awake and because i had to eat
dinner and then shower i was awake until
like 4 30 or so last night
um
so if you consider that at this point it
would be better if i just stay up longer
but then i can't do the early stream
tomorrow
because the rest stream tomorrow is kind
of early which i can totally move it
around but i scheduled it around that
time because
um i wanted to
maybe
be able to do something with ina i
didn't tell her that that was the plan
but
i'm overlapping on purpose
hoping to run into inya
i don't know what to do it's a dilemma
it's a dilemma
it's both terrible
[Music]
stay because of what i mean stay
oh damn it
yeah where's case melatonin can help but
[Music]
yeah
it can help but
[Music]
sleep early
yes see i don't know if that works today
because today's stream started late
and if i want to read super chats it's
also gonna end late
i don't know man this week's schedule is
really good in terms of like content but
time-wise
not so much
purple
skin
slow down i'm talking so much
[Music]
no slowing down no slowing down
also getting kind of worse at grabbing
them
[Music]
i although yeah definitely after rest i
can read them
because i have the whole day
whole day in front of ahead of me
i'm starting with her eyes
[Music]
mega
mingle
[Music]
i've seen this before in pixel art where
the mouth kind of is on the same level
as
the eyes it might not be that weird
wow
see i don't i barely even see her mouth
like there's the color difference isn't
even strong enough you know what
let me ah grabbing something in the
middle
is hard
let me try an even pinker one
[Music]
there you go
yeah
do i want that for the whole mouth
though
whoops where is it
[Music]
ah nah there
one feet down beat down
i repeat
beat down
sergeant
[Music]
sergeant beat
me
left the chat
[Music]
we will miss him
oh
interesting
uh
purple skin purple black purple skin
[Music]
don't feel like that
purple
skin
[Music]
don't beat like that
ice oh another round
okay okay okay okay
okay okay
now the neck really bothers me in my
version
creative freedom
for kiwawa
i
am just gonna use
the dark skin color for that part
[Music]
sorry dakuma
i'm going rogue
going rogue
tomorrow contents for rask by the way
eras rests speaking of
a rogue
that's better
maybe i don't know we'll see
what if we give her hair some shadow
yeah i can give this hair some shadow
too
you can do it on the same kind of purple
but darker
[Music]
will i regret it
we'll see
[Music]
uh
yeah i'm adding my own thing to it isn't
that nice my own little
taste okay
so
uh what was i saying oh yeah yeah yeah
rest i'm thinking maybe you saw her
i saw amis rust stream she looked inside
my house and showed the updates even
though i wanted to be the first one to
show you but it's okay i love amin i can
never be mad um but maybe you have seen
if you haven't seen it yet then don't
look
um but i i added some planters
and i want to figure out you know i
waited to actually plant something
that we could do it together
are we going straight up now where we
are
and um
and
yeah i want to do that and then i don't
know um i i want to show you
what i've been
working on on my skill tree
and i don't know
i don't know
[Music]
maybe try fishing and if i can figure
out how
one two three four five
[Music]
okay
that's that
[Music]
just gonna do it this way now
maybe
[Music]
soothing and relaxing isn't it
yo
it's like something from your childhood
rediscovered all over again
[Music]
but this time like your brain capacity
and your creativity
is
has expanded so much
that your potential
to make something
really great that you actually want to
use
is so much higher
fascinating
[Music]
potential yeah
i can't wait ways to use my tiny iron
okay um double row
three three
three purples
[Music]
i hope it works i don't know how strong
it is or how strong it has to be
to
iron the beets so that they melt but not
over melt
i mean there is the paper in between my
mama definitely safely
another three
[Music]
iron
fire
[Music]
that's the iron on a few random beads
oh
night we'll be fine
[Music]
the instructions didn't even say
anything about how hot or so
we'll be back
[Music]
i said iron normally really
i thought it was the same
i didn't hear a difference
[Music]
oh
that's a different skin color
then
the blush
and the belly button
i
don't have one like that so i'm just
gonna go for the same or am i maybe for
maybe maybe a gray i guess a gray would
work
a gray works here
and then a black
yeah
oh
cute
incredible fascinating 10 out of 10.
would do again
would beat again would i run again
can you like
can you double iron
i think i think it should be fine like
i'm wondering like if i were to attach
like a keychain to it
and i have to do it afterwards i think i
don't know how they do it but i think
maybe i need to add
like a like an
extra section
of iron beads to make a hole like a
circle
at the top of the head
and i want that yeah you can iron it
multiple times right yeah okay in order
to attach those two
all right i guess it would also work
with just a
hot glue
burps and i have a belly button
well because we're in our human form we
have a belly button
would you prefer us without a belly
button would wouldn't that be weird and
creepy looking huh
[Music]
don't ask for things that you're gonna
regret
[Music]
i'm gonna say it though
as a proud
inside belly button owner that inside
belly buttons are
better
i'm gonna say it like it is and i'm not
scared of saying the truth
[Music]
sorry sorry to the outsies
i'm sorry
please don't lose your confidence
[Music]
for sure
okay the mouth looks
weird
[Music]
changing
it's gonna put
i i don't think that however me too me
choosing a very pinkish color for the
mouth now makes it look more like a
mouth
as it stands out
more
as such like i have i have different
colors now
this one the mouth is more pink and the
neck is more brown so i think
um
it will
give off the illusion better
[Music]
um here we are next to the eye four
four purples
[Music]
ah
where'd it go i don't see it
it just snapped off my thingy
put them in
we might have lost him
i need to uh
use the vacuum cleaner
afterwards
[Music]
that was a loyal beat waiting to be used
by me
it was like
his destiny
and i took it from him
[Music]
how could i
okay
yeah yeah my cats yeah that's the pink
although
they probably wouldn't even find it but
yeah
[Music]
and i don't think they would try to eat
it or so but but it better be safe what
was that there it is
you look just as beautiful as the second
ago that i lost you
[Music]
okay where are we now
and she looks like i don't know like a
pokemon sprite so cute oh my god it's so
exciting because that takes so much time
oh my god
[Music]
every time i look at her the more i look
at her
the cuter she looks
you know what if hollow myth ever meets
again together in japan
i give every one of them one of these
i'll make one of them for each of them
we'll all have matching kiwawa made
keychains
wouldn't that be lovely
[Music]
everybody will talk about it they'll say
okay wow made me this super cute
iron beads keychain it's so cute
she's so good at it
i'm totally using it
[Music]
oh sure
i'd buy that
need to write the credits on the back of
the iron bead
[Music]
with a sharpie
okay the rest is
[Music]
yo did you guys see
you probably did did you guys see
elena's new outfit oh i never talked
about it but it's so [\h__\h] good
i already saw it before you guys saw it
but
it's so good i love it so much oh
i love it it's like
so edgy and cool
i love the hood i love the hair
i love the highlights in the hair
really really cool
matches your sparks outfit oh
perhaps a little bit
[Music]
where am i
oh skin color black black and then
purple okay
[Music]
yeah i'm sure portsy mama worked really
hard on it
she uses it a lot yeah understandable
honestly all of her live ids new outfits
uh hold up by the second chin your
outfits are so cool like ollie
ollie is just
incredible
anya was to me very unexpected but um
maybe if you watch a lot of anya
maybe she
maybe you would know that she has
interest in steampunk i don't know
looks really cool too
[Music]
maybe that's her
like preferred style
it reminds me
[Music]
i don't know steampunk but also
i don't know when she doesn't wear a
mask
it has other vibes too
which i like it's uh
it has
potential
for a lot of different types of
occasions
[Music]
my head hurts why does my head hurt but
like as if someone's
poking the top of my head
stop
stop poking
[Music]
now we do the dark blue
here one dark blue here
[Music]
she's almost finished
oh [\h__\h]
it's taking so much time
[Music]
ah
okay one right next to it
and then one on top and the purple in
between
[Music]
how much time have i spent on this
already
[Music]
two hours okay no half an hour of that
was um
keyboard and snack reveal so one and a
half hours
oh my god
[Music]
i don't know if i can do it if it's
smart to do another one but i want to do
another one
i want to do chicken
[Music]
i want to do chocolate chicken
i will
i will i'll just try to be a bit more
speedy
damn it come on
don't be a [\h__\h]
[Music]
one
more chicken
chicken
[Music]
oh the rest of the line is purple okay
okay okay
now here are mines i might be getting
faster because i think
um
[Music]
shouldn't be too difficult now i don't
have to keep on checking what i'm doing
[Music]
guys tell me when the music has
successfully brainwashed all of you
[Music]
oh
one two three four five
[Music]
okay
i see yes yes
two skin colored ones
[Music]
i wanna use my baby iron please
and the rest is purple okay
18 months ago
brain's still working okay then my b2m
is not working properly
your brain should be out of order
already
[Music]
i'm surprised
so many of you guys are watching this
i hope it's not boring
let me see what can we talk about
what can we talk about
[Music]
you guys have any
wishes
[Music]
favorite dinosaur
favorite season oh i don't know
[Music]
i already talked about elena's outfit
what the hell
what
recent cooking successes none new twice
music i did watch it today
uh
i think it's some
i mean i like it and the song it's a bit
weaker than their other songs i would
say
but maybe if i listen to it a few more
times
maybe i'll change my opinion not that i
don't like it at all but like compared
to the others the others are a bit more
catchy
[Music]
yeah i just cooked the other day but i
wouldn't call that a success like in
particular
i mean you know what maybe it was i
failed a little bit
but
i guess it's a success to have done it
in the first place
because
it was actually tasty i ate it on the
second day as well
with some
salad oops
that's tasty
lentils
are not bad
no lenses are such a cheap food
and you can keep them forever in your
closet
and they'll just
you need to be more more appreciated
too much
okay
oh
the top of her
[Music]
i'm on the top top of the world no i'm
on top of her head
[Music]
one more
i've been watching a lot of like
kpop related videos talking about like
all kinds of like
um
[Music]
in problems industry
but like not not necessarily industry
but like in certain agencies and so on
it's interesting and kind of sad
[Music]
um
but i want to talk about it because i
guess it's like um especially the ones
that i've watched
is one that was especially depressing
about some incident
with four minutes that's all i'm gonna
say
[Music]
okay
purple the rest of it is purple
[Music]
yes it's raining i'm collabing with lana
right now this is her she's she's here
she just she just doesn't want to talk
she needs a break
[Music]
this stream so far is like
it's all about layna i showed up the
snacks i showed up the keyboard
and now i'm making her
keychain
[Music]
i should put rayna on the thumbnail at
this point
[Music]
my back is hurting
uh
[Music]
i need a massage i haven't gotten a
massage in a while
i'm gonna get one next week how about
that
[Music]
finding my back there's a it's a little
bit like
yeah
because i'm like
trying to be close to the
thing
and it's um making me hunch a little bit
i need to look closely at it
[Music]
oh i've done yoga once and i was like
this is not my thing don't like it
[Music]
the art is sunshine
oh
i want that vina you know ever has like
back problems but i feel like since
she's doing it
as a job
[Music]
i mean she doesn't like to sleep on the
floor
well no i don't know if that's helping
or making it worse
[Music]
i know that sleeping on a on a hard
surface
can be good for your back and and if
it's a too soft surface then
it's bad for your back actually like if
your bed mattress is like way too soft
that's too bad
and then sometimes
chilling on the floor
will help your back
too
but i don't know if like whole
naps or like hours of sleep
on the actually wooden floor
is counterproductive or if it's helping
what do you what do you guys say
hi
surprise
oh i showed your uh keyboard and the
snaps in the beginning of the stream and
now now i'm making you
isn't it so cute
i've been working on this for one and a
half hours
i'm almost done
and i'm gonna i'm gonna make it into a
key chain and if we meet i'll give it to
you or i'll send it per post i can do
that too and it will be earlier probably
[Music]
not put water in it what
soak it right
i know it's so cute
i love it i'm so in love with what i'm
making
it's a miracle
what's the [\h__\h] miracle are we going
up oh no one more black
i'm almost
done
i can't believe it i thought i could
you know i requested
document was like hey what do you want i
can't help you and i'm like oh yeah how
about um turducken and nancy and some
chickens
uh
and and then takuma added the cats
on their own that wasn't my idea but how
do i think i could make so many i
underestimated how much time this takes
[Music]
i'll do it again
we can even do it as a member stream
super chill members hand cam stream
get some work done
if you guys want
you know what i'll put some in my hand
i mean it's faster
[Music]
but i did do my best for the setup today
like not only the camera because i had
to
you know
had some trouble with uh
camera
but you know first of all building the
table
and then cable [\h__\h] and tripod stuff
i tried my best to like make everything
optimized for the stream today
and i i set up my
my
camera
in a different place i'm using the the
stand from aniplus
the charging stand
you know i was i thought i couldn't use
it on my iphone because um
it has a
um
what do you call it like an android
charging thingy
um
on the side but
when i put the iphone on top it charges
it anyway
it doesn't matter if it's like if the
slot for the charging itself is android
because it charges just by like putting
it on top of it
fascinating
[Music]
i was like
yo this works let's go
[Music]
sorry guys um i can't look that much at
the chat i hope did layne elena say
something because i i have to focus on
my beads
[Music]
if it works it works yeah wireless
charging a yellow
i'm so surprised she says she loves me
really no she said ah hey you made that
up alfie and dean
you made it up
your little [\h__\h]
okay okay so just what i
already saw okay
i don't know she cares about me
i care about her
[Music]
extrapolate what
what
man the lady that was taking care of me
in the
after school daycare
she would be so proud of me
for what i'm making today
i think even back then
it was already obvious that i was gonna
be the creative kid though
ah now i really dropped one sorry
i was always the creative kid
always has been
[Music]
what am i
uh until that row right until
until that black one here
okey-dokey
[Music]
oh my god
it's like i'm i'm at the end of running
a marathon oh
speaking of that and some collab the
other day
you guys were really shocked when i said
i ran a marathon before
but just because you run a marathon
doesn't mean that
you know
a lot of people participate in marathons
and
you can be very slow
and i was really a child
um
but
back then um
why am i here okay
my actually my father was a very sporty
person
and sportsy
and would take me and my brother to
those kind of activities
[Music]
uh
and as a child i guess i
i i think i enjoyed you know i i i liked
running
and i liked inline skating
okay i know i don't talk a lot about my
father
when i say was it doesn't mean like he's
alive okay
just to make that clear he's alive
[Music]
we don't want to get too deep into that
anyway that doesn't matter um i also
remember like we would go
inline skating for like i don't know it
was i don't think it was a marathon
but there were like a lot of people
inline skating and riding their bicycles
on a big big big long long long long
long long long road like it was
occupying
a whole
um
like not a highway but like some kind of
fast
big road
and i really enjoyed that because like
inline skating i love inline skating i
don't do it anymore these days but i
loved it so much and it's like
even more fun when it's just a smooth
straight
um
smooth wait
wait
smooth straight road
it just feels so smooth like butter and
you go straight and you listen to music
you don't have to think about anything
you just you're just
like a skater girl
she was an inline skater girl she said
see you later boy
inline skater girl
it was me
[Music]
excuse me i wasn't in line skater girl
not a skater girl
an inline skater girl
[Music]
very specific
after a while i grew out of the inlines
and when i wanted to do it again i
didn't fit in them anymore and i didn't
have money for new pairs so
yeah i stopped
and now it's like
i don't know
to be honest i don't feel like inline
skating ever was like a proper workout
for me anyway
i was going fast i was going places but
i don't think i was really um
using
[Music]
calories or anything burning calories or
anything that much
i don't think it's like that much of a
workout
it didn't feel like a workout
wait i'm done oh
one more outline
oh my god
hey yo
[Music]
yo i'm so excited i can't grasp the
beads anymore they're all just flying
away
when i try to squeeze them
one two three
yeah and whatever i just have to close
it up no need to count it
ah
i can use my baby iron i can use my baby
iron i can use my baby iron yeah yeah
yeah yeah i can use my baby iron i can
use my baby iron i can use my baby iron
[Music]
baby iron
baby
[Music]
what are we gonna name the baby iron
i know you guys have no good ideas
what it means backwards what do you mean
it's backwards
[Music]
half
a hairpiece
look the herpes is fine eventually it's
fine
looks the same to me
what do you mean she actually is the art
meme rod
oh wait maybe it's mirrored because uh
when you iron it you actually
oh
will it get flipped
[Music]
okay okay so doc
dracula smart how come i was thinking of
that
do you flip it
is this the back side
[Music]
well that was a big brain then if
if this was considered
it works both ways
okay whatever yeah you can look at it in
both but on both sides
okay time to turn on
baby iron
iron
yeah
i got it came with this little
uh cat cat mouse pad cat pads
uh yeah put it on
and it has like this
[Music]
this funny face i think you put water
somewhere and then it goes like swoosh
but i don't know i'm using it without
obviously
and then
[Music]
oh
for some reason one of the papers got
kind of dirty but i have another one of
those foils
[Music]
all right this one's clean
no no the other one got dirty
i need water no i don't need water are
you sure you know there is and that was
an instruction
it was an instruction
um
where'd it go
where did the intersection go
[Music]
i don't think you need water
um
[Music]
i need water
no you don't need water
oh okay here here's the
um
cover with an ironing 8 paper iron
evenly it says nothing about water um
please use the iron on the parent
supervision
please turn off the power of the iron
when not in use to avoid children's
burns please use the fuse beads with
iron and eight paper when ironing each
iron and eight paper can be used
repeatedly with iron time on each side
depends on the size of the work one to
two minutes please do not over iron to
avoid burning the model of the convex
grain what
okay just be careful
i am not the iron in close
okay i've placed
the thing on top
i don't know how hot it is
how fast the iron gets hot but
are you ready i'm scared
[Music]
i think it was pretty fast
oh
okay
we're just do i move it or do i
let it stay
you know we used to use like some kind
of baking paper using this kind of
plastic feels kind of weird but
okay i feel like something's happening
[Music]
no no no i'm not uh there's there's a
foil in between i'm not putting it on
directly oh but i see i see i know it's
happening i guess i just peel it off of
the paper
[Music]
just make sure
that the edges
as well
[Music]
yeah they're definitely melting oh
oh
[Music]
it's sticking to the sheet but i guess i
just peel it off
i don't know how i would
over i have the bottom ones are not
really
how would i know that i'm over ironing
it
[Music]
okay i think
uh
after it cools down okay
i think i got them
[Music]
and the bottom row is doesn't look very
melted
[Music]
come on
now it looks more
melted and this this side doesn't look
properly melted
[Music]
it's like a pokemon character
little blue thing's so cute right
okay
[Music]
okay it should be fine right
i think it should be fine
i think i covered it well hold
[Music]
on the edges i'm not sure if it's
if the entries are done probably but
okay it's probably fine okay let's wait
and now we wait
okay
[Music]
you can see how the the holes have
pretty much closed inside the outside
ones are like they still look some of
them look pretty open that's why i'm
wondering
but then
they definitely changed shape a little
bit so
really fun
[Music]
circular motions some will stay open
left side looks under done left
um those those are fun
[Music]
just just for good measure maybe
if you can look through it's not good
okay okay just for good measure i just i
just don't want it to like be too much
how do you know it's too much
one more okay a bit more
i turned it off momentarily
[Music]
but oil
the other side
no you don't do that
i can't because it's sticking on the
on the base
[Music]
circular circular circular shooting only
an iron
i'm iron woman
not iron man i'm iron woman
[Music]
circular motion circular moisture
circular motion
i choose you
i definitely smell the um plastic
i smell something a little bit not too
much though
slightly
[Music]
it's all coming together
gently gently stroke and pet the pea
fowl
and she will reveal her love to you
perhaps she might even show you her nest
if you're very careful
okay
now we wait
and now we wait
look at that
[Music]
[Laughter]
iren
babudon babylon
[Music]
hi kobo where is kabul
why are you saying hi
[Laughter]
[Music]
is not
here
it's like
just saying
hi hoping hoping for her to be here
secretly
[Music]
mom
i want to see themselves how long do i
have to wait it's still hot when i touch
it it's still hard to touch
[Music]
drink water
hydrate
[Music]
starting the next one
um
i guess i have never
one of those spaces but
there's a start of something i
started to make
um
that i'm too lazy to take off because i
have to
carefully put every color back to where
it was originally
i was trying to make a cat face
and it's still on there so i'm just
gonna wait for this one
[Music]
ah but it's still hot
interesting
[Music]
but that at least makes me think that i
did it properly
[Music]
and i want to see it does it come off of
this one i wonder
that's the other side
[Applause]
[Music]
what if i can't get the plastic off
you see here there's this paper
and i put on top
put it into water like hot steel
i don't i don't think that's
that's maybe that's the life hack for
iron for iron beads but no never heard
of that
classical please when it's cool though
enough okay okay okay okay it's already
separating
[Music]
well i hope
i hope me elena will never separate
okay let's change the music shall we
[Music]
i
oh
[Music]
okay
ah wait it's not charging well enough
apparently
and just told me low battery mode no
no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no
no now
[Music]
come on
are you sticking to that there you go
[Music]
what
how
spoofy
when did i do that
that is because i clicked something in
the app i guess on the phone yeah yeah
weird weird [\h__\h]
[Music]
now i look like your grandma
i am your friend
[Music]
i make cookies for you
can i peel it off now it's um
warm it's warm still
okay i still have to wait
i should read super chats
[Music]
now grandpa grandma
screaming little [\h__\h]
you little [\h__\h]
get into the top five of the try it's
just kidding
[Music]
me
for the sake of my sleep schedule
yeah maybe maybe i'll just do the
chicken in a member stream
i thought we could do more
in before lena's gonna ask am i not
enough for you you are
you are
it's a good first attempt definitely
like it came out perfect
[Music]
it's passive practice i think not much
faster but
a little bit perhaps
[Music]
now i know how long it takes
and now i have everything well set up
i'm just petting my people
[Music]
we're talking about the rooftop episode
of scrubs i have to get a sleeper for
you i'm trying ah
he's trying to
um
help me memorize with wow why otherwise
your super chat would sound really weird
now
[Music]
i'd like to see this again publicly
really
really is it not too boring
next time i'll bring more talking topics
then i'll bring more and more topics if
i can
[Music]
i still want
that i want so many
maybe i'll do some in my free time if
i'm really bored
but there's a lot of things i should be
doing in my free time
she's she's pretty cooled down do i have
to wait until her body is ice cold
do i have to
like a dead body
what if i put her in the freezer
it should be okay now
it should be okay
okay let's go i'm peeling oh it works
[Music]
wow
will it come off of the base
[Music]
how'd that how did i take it off
see maybe with the tweezers
oh
[Music]
i want to be too aggressive
oh damn
[Music]
okay
holy [\h__\h] did i did i iron too much
[Music]
i can i can see it coming up but
might be easier without gloves
i'll do it here
close to my face
[Music]
flip and smack
hot dog
[Music]
it's um
pretty
uh
i don't want to break it i'm scared i
don't remember how much
strength i can apply to this how much
strength i applied to it as a child
let me let me take off my gloves for a
second
[Music]
i do feel like there's a child that may
have actually done the
topping
trick
[Music]
uh let's feel it oh there we go oh there
we go
eyes it's easy with
when you're able to use your nails
oh don't break it please don't break
i'm scared well
the middle part is like really
really stuck
i melted that one really hard oh
the pins no the pins are not melted the
those are fine
i hope i don't rip off her head but no
it seems
it's working
oh i got it i freaked
it
[Applause]
wait wait like putting
she's free
freedom
okay
[Music]
may they reveal
outfit reveal
alpha's reveal oh we gotta start from
the from the feet
how do i do it this way
[Music]
okay after the reveal
feet oh my god what is feet yo let's go
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
armpits let's go oh short hair what they
have short hair
let's go oh it's so cute on her face
oh it's a shortcut
wow
cute what the hell oh my god aina you're
so cute oh screenshot screenshot
screenshot time oh shiny
other side oh i see the other side looks
uh
worse um so maybe this side should have
been mirrored after all if it was really
the other way around i don't remember
but it's okay
oh cute
[Music]
it's relatively thin i really flattened
it
the side is right it's the right way
around okay okay
the mouth turned out fun
[Music]
cute
so cute i love it it's a masterpiece
flat elena yeah that's unusual
[Laughter]
[Music]
i see like here it's completely closed
and here there are some
some holes
but uh overall
i mean i guess you could iron it a
second but i think it's fine
[Music]
it looks so good
i'll take a photo and i'll upload it on
twitter in high quality
[Music]
second layer of beats
that you don't
i don't i don't i mean that would i
guess work with hot glue but you don't
normally do that
[Music]
i need to show you this
they're under a heavy book
yeah i'll sleep on top of her tonight
[Music]
cute
i'm so happy
i feel so
satisfied and accomplished
tons of tons of tonsils
[Music]
okay
sorry i'm too excited
i don't know what to do now doing
another one feels like
too much time
will be used
[Music]
and i'm kind of tired because of the
heat
weird
[Music]
yeah maybe i'll just read some super
chats and then we call it a day
and then we do it's another time again
or wait um
oh let me see
[Music]
let me see
uh
where's some
relatively small ones i mean
yeah but still
like
and then the egg chicken
seems really simple because it's like
barely any colors too
but
one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten eleven twelve
thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen
seventeen eighteen so eighteen bros so
it's significantly less but
i don't know
yeah but then once again i wouldn't read
super chess probably so that's that's
not good now let's just read super chats
and then
read them for an hour and then i can try
to sleep somewhat early tonight and
reverse my sleep schedule again
let's go backwards instead of forward
uh okay
okay thank you for watching you're
welcome to say
uh let me move my phone
to
uh
all right i'm going to turn off the
camera too now
uh
yeah
it is a big success
and they were diva
a phone goes
here
[Music]
i accidentally moved to the whole talk
screen anyway we're here now
okay
let's see
okay let me get everything in place
okay well it goes here
[Music]
um
oh i can take off the hat
and the gloves
let's go
[Music]
chat is there
okay
everything seems uh in order
i'm here you're here everybody's here
[Music]
okay then now i shall
move this a little bit
okay
everything's adjusted
yeah bgm btm what do you want to hear
[Music]
so i'm super chat reading
music
we can of course just do this one
yeah the only
why not i like it
i should close the iron bead um
chests uh
[Music]
i should close them up
probably
so that i don't knock them over and have
iron beads
everywhere
24 colors each
no wait they don't close
come on
okay i feel like such a child now
having this but
hey yo
sometimes
we have to relive your childhood
it was worth it
okay
there's no oopsie
you didn't see my third eye did you
thank god oh man i thought this was the
end of me
crafting can be fun definitely
[Music]
found another way
of doing a
unique
path cam
the queen
of uniqueness unique
[Music]
it's me
hey it was a lot of fun
maybe i inspired some of you guys to try
it you can order one of these sets like
on amazon or whatever
and make your own cute pixel
keychains or whatever
just do it don't let your dreams be
dreams
upset where is the
why did i stop breathing
[Music]
what does that mean
too short
look again hell no
even when [\h__\h] was a thing i never used
it i always used photoshop
inspired me to iron my clothes i need to
do the laundry
oh
if only if only that inspired me too to
do my own clothes
i think i'm going to build a keyboard oh
a pre-packed bead kit where you can make
your own kiwana ah
it's like
you wanted me to make one of those for
you well you'll have to make it yourself
at least i'll provide everything for you
have fun
the lazy
the lazy merch
you do your job
i just lay back and watch you
doing it
oh wait the fake tunic finale you're
saying that that was where i have to
continue reading oh yeah yeah
okay let's go
go make the mercy
it's so
what's the word effect efficient it's so
efficient
self-assembling
wait i like i thought i should put up
the thumbnails
[Music]
how much is some well you will have to
try it out and see
[Laughter]
oh the first one the first one
um
[Music]
having completed this game to the
fullest i'm absolutely blown away the
game does so much with so little and
gives you all the tools it needs to
letting you free to explore and
experiment even up to the 11th hour of
the game i was still surprised with new
secrets
the final puzzle was also an amazing
journey's end for the whole game thank
you kiana for introducing this game to
me it definitely goes on to one of my
all-time favorite games with so much
love and care put into it i agree same
for me
i didn't expect it at all
i went into the game with
not so many expectations i didn't think
i was gonna be blown away that much
and love it so much
if anything i thought i would like
suffer much more
because of you know how
people say it's a really difficult game
but yeah
it was it was such a pleasant surprise
so glad i chose it and
really deserves to be streamed more
it's a great game and i don't even think
it's a bad streaming game it's just
people need to give it a chance
[Music]
but it would be a cute telecom but it's
so much more it is yeah
i mean the visuals the visuals are
so
like they remind you so strongly of
zelda but
there's much more behind it
oh my gosh gets a kiss though
tunic case
he's me thank you soon merry christmas
fellaini thank you for the red super
chat oh you're eyeing me
why are you eyeing me hello you're
trying to say hello without standing out
too much
thank you thank you felix
[Music]
he's
a kiss for you felix
hope you enjoyed the
very long tunic finale arc
thank you so much
it's heidi also read super chat thank
you as well
for being there
i hope you liked the game maybe you can
give it a try yourself
thank you skye danke channel pendant
[Music]
i have returned back from europe and let
me tell you i'm having you out
withdrawals
i now understand european bros payne
after having been subjected to a
barrage of 1 to 5 a.m streams on my
timeline you're truly you truly are the
saving grace of the eu time zone
wait what you were you went
[Music]
you're back in the u.s now and now my
streams are at bad time for you is that
what you're saying
gomez
oh maybe go back to europe
maybe better to go back to europe
oh
no no no he says he has returned
it's not about me going to korea
[Music]
i'm in the u.s and the streams are good
for me oh yeah there's obviously there's
gonna be some people who even when the
stream is early in the day actually i
prefer that because of how
they work or
you know
how they're
uh
sleep cycle is good time for everyone
else to streams in europe
yeah yeah yeah okay
everyone else has bought mine
which is fine you didn't need anybody
else's streams did you
but it is true that uh na prime time in
europe is one to five a.m
so it's hard to catch anyone
like really hard like unless you [\h__\h] up
you sleep completely
forever
and mr empty blocks
[Music]
yeah lots of world it was really great i
wanna call again i barely saw stuff like
we weren't there for
a few hours and stood in line for an
attraction for like one or two hours
probably two hours
so
ah i need to go again next time i go to
korea i will go to la the world again
yeah i want to try the ice ice rink ice
skating too
yo there were some some pros down there
especially like in late late late
evening when things were closing down
and people were leaving
the only people left in the ice ring
in lots of worlds were like professional
looking ones
like they did like tricks
they did pirouettes and like some jumps
and [\h__\h]
yeah
we were watching that for a while i took
like a video
pretty impressive
we were watching from like
two or three floors above very high up
watching what they were doing down there
so cool
yeah
they did some cool stuff there
hmm
yes
i
i remember there was a zamamito moment
but i don't remember what exactly it was
but yes
i love i love the phrase summer middle
thank you
[Music]
i'm gonna take a throat candy for some
reason
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
okay
protein
[Music]
another pinky thank you by the way lot
is actually a fun company as is it's
founded by a korean [\h__\h] yeah i read this
one already
korean japanese stockholders are mostly
japanese
it's staffs and ceos are mostly korean
interesting so in japan people call it a
korean couple and in korea people call
it japanese coffee it's so weird how did
that happen why
why hmm
need to research lotte the company
because like you guys remember i told
you about that really famous chewing gum
that they made
that everybody in japan knows but in
korea apparently it's pretty unknown
navi mama didn't know it and i didn't
really see it in the convenience stores
or so either
yeah japanese ads for it
yeah i wonder
why
i guess they make some products that are
like supposed to be focused on the
japanese market
[Music]
honey butter chips
nope
i don't know what you mean dastia thanks
my pinky
thank you no message though why
talk to me
dastia what's up
what are you thinking let me
let me unravel your brain
thanks for the pinky though
comes on for the pinkie i'm korean but i
think that tanz you enjoyed it more than
me i'm so hungry
[Laughter]
[Music]
wait something specifically the hot dogs
maybe
uh i want to eat them again the corn
dogs i guess you call them corn ducks
right that type of hot dog
it's a corn dog i keep on saying hot dog
but
i mean corn dog
don't really have those corn dogs here
in austria i've never seen it anywhere
before
yeah the ones on a stick
i saw them in like japanese convenience
stores in their hot section you know
where they have like fried chicken and
stuff
they also sometimes have corn dogs so
sometimes i would
uh
take one home
corn dog yum yum yum yum so good
really want to try this corndogs you
mean any corn dog or the korean corn dog
found a recipe for it that's relatively
easy to make at first glance
well if you make it and it was easy then
share the recipe with me
they're everywhere in the u.s
why why are they not popular in austria
they should be they should be popular
here too some things i really don't
understand other things i understand why
they are not popular because
the taste
is not quite something that i think
everybody would love in in my country
but
corn dog the taste is
i think
very very
very
easy to love
[Music]
not really corn dogs i was so
disappointed when i tried corn dogs in
canada though
hoping would taste similar wait what do
you mean what are you comparing it to
good korean corn dogs use yeast gel
corn bread oh yeah oh yeah yeah we don't
really do cornbread here
it's not good
not good anyway
[Music]
different though oh
well i mean it definitely like seemed
very different from the corn dog that i
had in japan that was i think more
american style
more simple
[Music]
yes
definitely
ketchup on top
[Music]
or some other sauce
yeah yeah yeah
black fruits and vanquish and pepsi
thank you
that's right
anthony webb thank you soon cursed boy i
are dancing thank you all yes
thank you soon
tickets
oh from pearl i'm saving to buy some
merch thank you for inspiring to become
a youtuber as well you're welcome and
good luck
[\h__\h]
action
uh squeaky mustache oh wait that's me
she was a pinky thank you
chicken
oh my chicken who are you talking to
someone
someone in the chat i guess
not
me obviously
couldn't be me
but i i like seeing my chickens be
supportive of other chickens it's really
really sweet
what a wholesome community
isn't it
ah sweet it makes my heart melt
thank you action itchy
swimming mustache duncan
skye duncan pepsi duncan captain
jerkbait thank you
thank you for the pinky
you will always believe in your kiwawa
you definitely got this
which boss was this the scavenger
probably because in the first tunic
finale i think the only boss i did was
scavenger
thanks for believing in me
i wish i could have just cheesed him
ah
but that would have been
too
too boring too simple too easy
even when there's an a really easy
solution doesn't mean you should take it
because you you learn
nothing by it i'm trying to be poetic
right now
i'm philosophical
you do learn something
if you look at it at a perspective of a
speedrunner you learn how to do a
speedrun
but in general
if you just cheese them throw them down
and let it be an auto kill or whatever
nope
let's just exploiting it
exploiting life
and getting nothing out of it
it has a philosophical things
but cheese tastes good
well too much cheese isn't good you need
a balance you know
oh thank you mimas
oh
that's sweet thank you for the feedback
you're welcome to
come back anytime
i'm lactose intolerant i can cheese you
know what you will come out so much
stronger than all the teasers
so
you should be happy and proud of it
being lactose intolerant
hell yeah just tolerate it [\h__\h] you
don't say that to him
that's just stupid advice
it's like saying to someone who's sad uh
just don't be sad
[\h__\h] you
honey sore duncan
oh happy birthday's birthday
oh i didn't know this earlier i'm sorry
eden excellent
quickly
47 out thank you
for watching spicy chicken
i did it
apparently i did it
it killed the boss i know a tank is
[Music]
my favorite parts of the stream are
listening to you pearl and listening to
your mom come along to perfume songs
oh really i didn't know that
they mentioned how more perfume songs
that from gamescom
oh
how was it
did you see something interesting
with your super chat cats hey yo
hey yo what
hell yeah
my chunky wonky
very nice
you enjoyed it
good
happy for you
[Music]
jonker's is spanx new or she
no well i mean understandable to be
honest
they are so lovable
if you guys saw them irl
ah
you would just
ditch me
immediately go for my cats immediately
they're just so
so
irresistibly adorable
no way
it's okay i wouldn't even be mad
i'm also like so happy every time
someone appreciates my cats and they're
like oh your cats are so cute oh my god
i love you cats
it makes me so happy it makes me so
proud too
like i raised that kid
that cat hey
[Music]
no kelly didn't actually try anything
but she she loved my cats
understandable
i love champions movies but it's their
mommy with my auntie
okay you passed the test
thank you
and thank you for the rest of the chat
spanking here's the kiss
thank you soon
[Music]
that was a super chat about
seeing me as gyeongbokgung palace which
i don't know if you really did to me it
sounds like a joke
but maybe you didn't
if you really did and if you're here and
tell me what the oh i guess
never mind
i think that could be cheated
telling me what the color of my hanbok
was i don't believe it
[Laughter]
i don't believe it
tell me the amount of sweat drops i had
on my face
you counted them didn't you
don't tell me you didn't i would be
disappointed
buckets
very much
so many
uh
i i'm i'm i'm really
i think i can confidently say
i strongly dislike the summer
i have a strong
dislike for it
same same oh same whoa
pasta relatable
yeah
[\h__\h] some woman i mean there's truly
like some countries where summer is
actually decent
but it ain't here and it ain't there
is
[Music]
summer only looks good in
anime
[Music]
oh
i was looking at my beets and i just
remembered
i said as a child i had like um
sparkling
a lot of seafood
sparkly beets those were my favorite
i made everything with sparkly beads
they had sparkles inside shiny spy
phones
oh
now i'm really into beats
extreme sparkly
sky thanks for the winkie sorry i have
to rest i hope you can race your finale
today if you feel you need some rest i
would love to come for finale part two
let's reach the ending
sky
i didn't do it but you were there in
part two as well
[Laughter]
i right so hopeful i thought i could do
it but nope
longer than expected thank you though
for being there as long as you could i
actually i didn't play much longer after
that anyway it seems um
thank you
thank you soon
[Music]
ah you were waiting in line while
watching my stream huh uh it was like 5
00 am there
south side in korea thank you for
working hard to solve the travels that
occurred it's all popcorn and family
thanks i love you guys you're welcome
yeah i have an eye on what's going on
behind the scenes and
i'm gonna help
not just look away and pretend i don't
know what's going on
[Music]
i i would i probably would have like
if i would have gotten to the end within
the first stream
probably would have said oh guys i'm
sorry i'm gonna do the true ending
privately
yeah and then probably would have never
gotten to it so it's good that we did it
on stream in a second stream
yeah
anyway thanks nemo
i hope you enjoyed your time at the
aniplus cafe
[Music]
space waterfall thank you and brandon
danke
i'm done with the first tunic uh finale
super chats
now
next is rest
the first rest
last last
rest
easy peasy yeah it wasn't so bad what is
it
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] no i didn't second time
thank you and george sandoval thank you
shane jim tracey
ah yeah i had some microphone problems
in the beginning oopsie uncle thank you
nowadays
do not mess with the kanata you might
find yourself getting killed by her mama
suse
well just be careful around susan you
might get killed interesting
um
you know what i realized there's a lot
of stuff going on on the weekends like
i'm like uh kind of
uh busy because of soul popcorn
the other thing is though
uh
when is that oh no wait when is that
pink fight gonna happen in rust
because i guess
the 31st is wednesdays
the month is not ending this weekend
so they're not gonna fight yet right on
the weekend
i don't know when i need to schedule
my stream if i want to be part of the
fight
do i even want to be part of the fight
i have no chance i think but
last day before the wife
so the
31st of the 30th
or didn't they say i'm thinking i think
we were told that on the first friday of
the month is when they reset the server
but then i have a bit more time but okay
that's uh good to know elisa it's not
this weekend so
but
i was suddenly reminded by seeing uh
pikulas tweet with the
trailer
that
that summer festival is happening
on
the weekend
um
it's like
i don't know it's kind of
i think because people aren't playing
minecraft so actively anymore
it kind of went under a lot of people's
radar
and now i don't have anything scheduled
to participate in that
no it's on the 28th i think
wait it's on the 29th
is it on monday
because on monday i can
schedule something
that's it's a shame
i wouldn't mind it being like it's
coming back in popularity though
29 okay okay okay ah
well then
i think i can do a stream on it i didn't
build anything though and i don't know
what exactly is gonna happen
maybe maybe i can um ask another member
to
go to the festival with me
yeah
because i think last year i was just
wasn't i just like
hanging out with a second kind of like
somehow
but
i didn't have like one specific partner
or anything
[Music]
oh was that
i couldn't feel that
yeah yeah like we built some stuff
was that
the same day
was that a separate thing
we filmed something
i think it was a separate day with
separate streams
the one where usa can build some stuff
the slides
yeah
and then the other one was
where i guess i was like a little bit
with myth but not quite because ina was
with lamy
and the rest of mip i don't know i guess
we were like a little bit scattered but
i remember like i was
i was alone around the time too because
i was i remember walking through
an attraction that the horror horror
house alone
and then being a little bit lost
and i was like uh where is everybody
where the hell where should i go
ah then i translate a little bit yeah
well maybe
maybe this time
i can
hang with someone
[Music]
no i was alone going for the house
i'm pretty sure
i don't know i'll see who has no plans
i'll check
after the stream
[Music]
you may not want to gather or attack
things near safe zones if you hit the
wrong thing they'll go after you
thank you
yeah yeah now i already know
the most basic basic things
but i still have a lot to learn i guess
thank you
for trying to teach me i didn't see the
super chat at the moment though
unfortunately
thank you though
not lou thanks for the thinking
you got this helper just think of it
like a more violent minecraft
yeah yeah yeah
yeah that's uh
somewhat of a comparison
hmm
i shine
and scratch functions
oh
i think your your dream is telling you
to stream sparks
thanks for the pinky
the house is too small show the dignity
of kfp if you're attention okay okay
okay you see after the wipe i'm gonna
build something big okay
this time i started small because you
know i'm just gonna start like small so
you can have a good like you know
overview of it
yeah
but
i might just try to build something big
next time
because i hear that you know other
people also making big things like gooda
i still
i'm gonna talk about it tomorrow and
rest i guess but i still don't know who
the hell was that who took that crate
away from me
i didn't see them they're like like a
like a ninja
they move in the shadows
but apparently
i heard it in ahmed stream
but apparently the the counter
when you're
like about to log into the server
is this correct is it it's not correct
that tells you how many people are
online it's not correct
apparently
[Music]
i think she started afterwards no i
checked um
i checked the whole schedule and i
didn't see anyone streaming
[Music]
count it for two days straight
oh man
i hope i get it one day
i'm scared of like confrontation
i just want to get it once like when
nobody's online make use of my of my
time zone you know
but i did find crates elsewhere i didn't
realize that those would show up
elsewhere too
saw them for the first time
that the other day when i played offline
just shoot first to intimidate them
right you can't show that you're scared
you have to be the one
to assert dominance by shooting
[Music]
but you know i don't really i don't
really play fps games either so i don't
have that confidence and the skill
i don't know if it would go well but
should first ask questions later never
heard of that
never heard of that before
nah
i don't know i don't even know how
different types of guns work
[Laughter]
which ones
uh shoot
fire and which ones should
and we're gonna shoot fast and which
ones shoot slow
anyway anyway we'll figure it out maybe
this is my gun learning arc
uh
you have to be an fbs pro training
artist that's what i'm saying maybe
maybe yeah
[Music]
np153 garlic stain cushion superhuman
blue duncan
thank you
charming
christmas thank you i have attention let
me let me skip those sneak shots often
ate dankeshen
matsuli was very friendly when amy and
iris met her flair mostly just fishes
watch out for moomin though
and mommy
i don't think muma has the balls to
attack me though i'm her i'm not only
her senpai
i'm also her bird senpai
within horotoy
i i don't think she would do it
but she's welcome to surprise me about
it
and then she'll forever be on my death
note
black kitchen thank you very much
[Music]
what
no way kim song did the guy who despair
wrote another stupid potential there are
people impersonating me on the internet
i didn't know that the job of holding a
heavy spare in the scorching sun and
guarding the palace in five hour shifts
would be so popular
you guys think he's
like really
well then i want him to tell me
something that he would only know
okay i would i would ask
which
there were there were three
arches
one big one in the middle and two on the
side
now you would have to tell me which one
i went through with navi mama
which one did i walk through you would
know
if you're really working there
yeah or pixar didn't happen
[Laughter]
picture of you
in the uniform or so i don't know
you better come back and report to me
with which gate i went through
yeah the chance of getting it right even
just by guessing is pretty high but
still
i don't want to know
[Music]
unity chad thanks for the pinky the heli
was visible for a bit right before it
opened fire so i probably saw you if you
wanted to go away you must unequip your
weapons or not
oh wait right i keep on forgetting
i mean
i mean i keep on forgetting i was told
maybe once and i acknowledge it once but
so when the helicopter flies over you
and you don't wear any weapons it won't
shoot you
is it that easy
because i forgot about that when i was
playing offline and i was running from
it like an idiot again
armor too
oh
then the wolf killed me
unexpectedly
a wolf killed me instead
less than three pieces oh you can wear
three pieces
but is is even just a shirt considered
armor i guess so cause like all the
armor in the game is pretty much just
dead
straight this fight i'm kissing
i'll try to remember it though
might all be removed for a hot time
yeah hmm
bit annoying but manageable
um
space wonderful thanks for the pinky hi
kiana today i had a cake and got gifts
because my birthday
the second one where you might ask me
glad i get suspended with you for over a
year where you were the biggest
emotional and motivational booster for
me and made my life better thank you so
much
happy birthday birthday space waterfall
oh
i'm so happy
[Music]
congratulations
i hope it was a great birthday the
second one already damn
it's really crazy when you think about
how much the time passes and how long
some of you guys
are loyal
kfp chickens to me thank you so much
it's an honor
thank you for letting me be part of your
life
thank you thank you
i appreciate it
happy birthday
i made it
remember a first cake
no
you guys grew up
look at that chick i raised that chicken
oh
yeah i
i definitely thought you guys would
leave me
but now
sometimes i feel there's more old
viewers than there are new bjorns
which
it's fine too like it shows that people
want to be loyal to me and watch me for
a long time
but it's a bit sad if you think about it
that
there's no
no new people
wanting to check me out that's that's
that
we work hard and do our best to see
growth
i started watching in february thank you
thank you
my nose is itching i keep on scratching
it
[Music]
yeah yeah korean bros that's why i
appreciate them so much too like
i have to
appreciate the little growth i get you
know
jayce wacko thank you soon cyrux thanks
for the pinky haven't had the time to
just kick back relax and watch the kiana
stream in a while so that was really
nice especially since it's a new game eh
is rust itself new though no right no it
isn't
watching you grow while playing is
always a treat that and watching you
panic like a headless chicken
like a headless chicken
or rust has been around since 2013.
why is it
why is it popular now
is it like
some whole life members being a
trendsetter once again
maybe like who was the first one piccolo
miku senpai
yeah i guess yeah we have to wait for
the prims too but i wonder how long
how long people wanted to play
yeah and i did see like en members in
our discord being like when can we
stream it can we play it can we play it
no please wait for server okay
oh
hold the snare
well sirek you're welcome hope you
enjoyed the stream
and hope you can come to more streams
more often
just relax and watch wawa
my question also thank you for the pinky
the stream was so damn good quinara
i'm so glad you liked it i don't know if
you're that hooked but i would love if i
saw you online during your stream times
like gouda
you know i think one reason
why i've been playing it um more than i
thought i would is
it makes no sense but it feels
a little bit like an mmorpg to me
um i mean obviously it's an mmo but it
gives me
slightly gives me a little bit of the
feeling i had when i was playing mmorpgs
a little bit even though it makes no
sense it has no rpg elements
but for some reason somewhere deep
inside i i could slightly have that
feeling
it's not like i even like saw that many
players while i was online like i saw
maybe two people like
and anya
and and uh
katrina who was that
who's it again
theresa theresa
yeah but
something
something really really slightly
reminded me of it
[Music]
i wish i could just play a proper mmorpg
though
but for now
for now um
i'm
i am
enjoying
it i guess
a little bit but like i'm still like i
don't know
i don't know about the pvp aspect um
i don't know we'll see i'll i'm
gonna try it but i'm not too confident
about it uh
[Music]
but so far building my base was fun
and
but i did have a little bit of a trouble
to figure out
what should i be doing
like
if i'm not doing pvp
what am i supposed to do i kept on
running between the convenience store
and my home
and then i ran around
to a different convenience store
and i keep on going back and forth and
trying to get as many scraps to to build
up my skill tree
but then besides that it didn't really
like
there's not much outside like and
like i only saw a few bear boys
there's not many enemies
it's like not that much going on so i
was like what what okay what what now i
just keep on repeating the same things
it was a little bit
[Music]
okay for now i guess
yeah i know about like tunnels and ships
and all that but that seems like a
little bit too
big of a quest for me at the moment
when i'm still building up
too much too big of an endeavor right
now
i feel like there's like no
not much like before that
do it with other people
[Music]
maybe maybe i can
get on that ship with someone else how
many people should you get for the ship
because i think the ship from what i've
heard is really really really
tough dangerous
yeah but i assume that they already had
like
more experience than i did and more
items and stuff
well
what i did find really interesting i
watched the bakula senpai's dream of
sniping down the helicopter
she built this whole base to shoot
through
to be protected from the helicopter
i was
pretty cool but then what you get from
the helicopter was so
as they like to say in japanese
i didn't know i didn't
so [\h__\h] like she
it was
the loot was not worth the effort i
would say
just uh
the feeling of having it like the proud
feeling of having shot down the
helicopter
yeah but the loot is so underwhelming
what the hell
not worth the effort at all
unless you can
repair the helicopter
and then use it but then the map is so
tiny
it's not like you can fly to another
island with the helicopter
it's not like you can do that much with
the helicopter
even if you repair it
ah
but if you have the helicopter
then i guess pvp
you would be insanely powerful
oh [\h__\h] is piko not gonna do that on the
last day
[Laughter]
is she gonna use the helicopter to
kill everybody
[Music]
i don't think we stand a chance um but
let's see what happens
[Music]
oh my god
oh dear
oh man
make an alliance with her to save
yourself
yeah i gotta pull the usaken card
say ah
poor i am fine remember i'm i'm a member
of usual canyon yeah yeah
remember
we have an alliance
yeah it extends to other games too
yeah it was in the contract
please
be nice please
and i i i
i keep i give um english translation in
exchange
yeah remember the light drop the bunny
house i built for you yeah yeah yeah
put down the helicopter
ah
it was fun boss thank you i'm glad you
enjoyed it
[Music]
oh come on
thank you i'm sorry i'm backstage
driving you today see you next time if
he doesn't no problem
um
uh i i as you saw like i i improved very
fast i i in rest like i got the basics
down very fast thanks to you guys and
thanks to amit
although i think i learned more from you
guys maybe than from america
but um
for me really i
i soak that [\h__\h] up
that kind of backseating i'm asking for
it
i want you guys to tell me it drives me
crazy to not know how to play the game
so
any game minecraft same thing
i need to know i need to learn
and i sometimes i am i feel like weird
about asking so many questions but you
know
you know you guys seem to enjoy telling
me
yeah
myself i'm i have no no problem with it
thank you for helping
vaccine aoe oh
well yeah did you see colorful landed
what
when
nani
my chicken tweet
doko
today
[\h__\h] my [\h__\h] twitter doesn't load new
[\h__\h]
huh don't they have a verified account
it's not my
verified accounts but maybe it's just
not loading
you know i got tagged in some
like in my verified tag i see some
verified accounts some like news outlet
or whatever
tagged me in a post about a different
kiana
i wanted to point it out to them but
whatever
attacked the wrong kiana
they actually also attacked the right
kiana but uh
yeah when did they reply to me
how how long is it ago
i don't see it in my recent replies
how many hours ago
yes yesterday morning
what can someone
ah thank you skye
the art gods rumble mysteriously wait
that sounds like they are on it
the art gods rumble mysteriously
doesn't that sound like they're on it
[Music]
oh my god the power i have is
unmeasurable
[Music]
but then i should stop playing right now
and get back to it only when they
release the chickens
because i'm not gonna play the second
time
maybe probably but no
[Music]
is my reply
thank god they saw it
i was hoping they would see it
they're gonna have an update soon
[Music]
but
the chances of chickens being included
then
would only be
if you know
if they already had that idea before i
would say it can't be that fast
unless i don't know
yeah
i pushed out a twitch patch last night
was playing
oh someone was playing this game on
twitch
oh
chickens
i want the chicken
it would be so perfect
i want to check them
[Music]
um
chicken
[Music]
anyway
please give chicken
please
i require the chicken
ah
how'd the craft go good i'm gonna i'm
almost done like actually i'm gonna end
super typewriting here because i'm
almost done with this one and i'm gonna
upload it on twitter
thanks for the pinky i tried once while
you were playing oh not sure if i'll
keep playing or not and did you play on
like a public server
it's fun but everything disappearing is
going to drive me nuts love the
strongest asmr so far nothing has
disappeared for me
um keeping my
upkeeping my home is easy so
my body also i was able to retrieve
several times
oh
it's not a big issue but i don't know
i probably wouldn't like playing it on a
public server either with like really
like serious pvp going on
scary too scary
um
other reset well yeah it's kind of
stupid but
in the end
it's like live just shorter
it feels like
yeah
at some point you die but you still work
hard try to create something big in the
meantime right
hashtag philosophical phoenix
oh just giving up because you know
there's an end
i know it's such a like ah i question it
too sometimes you know i question it too
even though i'm a phoenix i question it
too at times
is it really worth it
but
i mean what else can you do
yeah make the most out of it make
memories
passion fills up with phoenix
apply that logic to rest
[Music]
thank you for the pinky
the game of great
and there it is that's the end of the
rest of the chat um
i'm gonna read more tomorrow
but you know it's uh 11 p.m now and we
did say kiwawa needs to go to bed early
today
let's see if she can
gotta find the melatonin
melatonin melatonin
how did you know
how did you know we made industry oh she
did a stretch you were a good baby today
because you did not disrupt my stream at
all good baby
now you're gonna get many many cuddles
yeah
yeah baby
bubble wrap oh my god no don't eat the
bubble wrap from lena
no
time she's already
already doing
cheeky things
[Music]
you walk in the room and immediately go
for the bubble wrap no don't shoot a
bubble wrap no plastic no no no
it's your breakfast
she's on my on my lap now oh she's kind
of wet i think she
cleaned herself
[Music]
yeah i'm gonna close the office door
it's okay as long as i'm not in the room
i can close the door and they don't give
a [\h__\h] about it they won't try to get in
no no no no don't dab
down and immediately she goes to the
buffer
it's like she's like a magnet
or like a zombie automatically going
towards
the enemy in the game or just like the
protagonist yeah
holy [\h__\h] stronger are you good
a girl's coming
okay i have to
clean or kick her out so i'm gonna end
it here um thank you guys for watching
i'm glad it worked out in the end
we're gonna do more
more iron
[Music]
beading and in german we say
avidazine
[Music]
thank you for watching
last
[Music]
i think
oh baby baby stop
no it's itchy
bye-bye i'll be dancing
[Music]
you