in. I'm in. I'm
dee
.
2 I'm
in.
4th day. th.
Dee dee..
This folder will be
held on 19mar ignition
around web super expo
2022 and follow live surface wink
screws back row  by Weiss This
is a pre-program where we try out various projects to get everyone excited about Schwarz.
Yeah, yeah
[Music]
Well, we've got a lot of international
members coming.
First of all, please click on the
jp button.  Thank you,
Iraya -The flower outside the national line is the four -white button  I would like to
tell you that this
is my first time in life, Mr. B.
Latest
Hey, it seems like you are going to stick out. ai,
boober, and eni,
please rise up. Kei, also english, the
wind of the first generation.  It's sad that I got a notebook in c tone and a game sp.
Thank you very much for listening to Japan and cheering me up, and also for chatting with me.As expected.  I ca
n't say it.
Hello, I'm Ice Walker. Thank you
very much. As long as you don't have Shima-chan, you're all
welcome. But everyone, please feel free to
leave as many comments as you like.
Thank you,
Hahn.
Lastly, today is Expo and
Beth's Serious Hanyu.  I'm
getting ready and I'm dry. Please sleep at the end. I wonder what's going on. What's so
weird
about singing a shop name? I
want to do anything, Uraga 3.
Boo-boo-okaa-marker-chan, it's like the
sound society is the most important thing. Ah, we
have to start with pretending. I
want to go to ``Nyomotomo'', but oh,
well, everyone remembers the title of the third festival this time.
You
remember Taito Solfe I
remember how to match this Audi. It's
okay as long as you remember it.
Yeah no
baby yeah
one more
movie ra
re
re 4
p
However, it's Karchandu, Inka,
Bill, Fish, what's up
? Well, please go outside quickly and google it. I'd like everyone to
try their hand at a project with the theme of links, that is, connections.
Yes, it's not a fish, it
's a link.
el What's going on? Yes, it's not happening, it's not happening
. That's why there
's so much light. Why is it a radius?  I'm
planning on having people take on the challenge without being recognized, and I'm going to do a hood that
connects them with the theme pink cards, m
car,
A-
chan Alba Cru Papado Battle.I don't
know if they're doing it,
but I think it's a good advertisement for the enthusiasm of those people.
Wow, are you going to
do a new device shorts on this day?
Hmm, I'm not sure if I'm going to do a matcher. I
thought I'd tie up the device today, so I'd
like to do it another time, but that's it.
Booby iPhone Live  We have prepared cards
with the members of jpi den written on them,
and we will ask you
to choose Unhoronmen from among the cards for various questions that we will be giving you.Members
linked to Umba themes  You
can choose a card up to three times for one theme,
so if the card you want with someone else
ends up costing you money,
that card will be shared by both of you.  in hand
3 people who don't fit in. It doesn't say you can't get any of the 3 people who wear the hat.
[Music]
Housework is exactly like that, making sure to draw the right eye according to the theme.  He
explained it beautifully in one word,
but when the motor matches it, it transforms.There
is also the Mars 5 Spicy Noodles so that you can't get rid of this, but the
pattern is to link the five machines.Well,
select the members that match the theme.  That means please.
No
hi Which combination of soldiers is the best?
He who is linked according to the theme in this version
is me, my friend A, and everyone's comments.Looking
at the comment, I
would like to have a meal for Chan.He is really an honorary archer.
Please, I drank something like this.
Thank you very much. I would
like to entrust the announcement of this important announcement to the person who was judged to have been able to link the jammer to the stand.  rl 2
Sekiyama Thank you very much. I want to see the photo. It looks
delicious.
Des ponds mere feeling. I
said "I have a masher." If
you would like to tell me about it,
please send me the link.
Yes, it's better to try it.  That's what I think,
so let's get to the comedians.
First of all, here's the topic.
[Music]
Horo Live This is a unit. Oooh,
old man's iye  Lychee is also a movie,
isn't it?
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah The
three of you are so weak, well, you're still alive, it
's a light light train.  It's
abnormal, isn't it?
Fuji City M3 is great.The front race is also
various.The government, where most of the live performances are, is a little bit
different.I don't like it.I don't like Mac.
So,
there are members here who say they should wear formal clothes to the Horo Live, but
there are members from all over the place, so
uh, there are members who are really warlike, and
of course the unit should be shut down from accidental drinking and production.  It's
Nemahoroba, and I'm going to get into people's hearts and
clean it from head to toe.I
think there are a few people who have no choice but to do it.
Yes,
that's what I wanted to say right now, so
let's take the money away from the Ministry.First
choice, super and choice cards are
here.The
one who thinks it's a war from among the others
is an avalanche that spits out units.  Today, I
see that I have a car with Irohasa sealer.D It
's Mr. Moore.Hmm,
yes,
I have 5 children and 2 children, so it's illegal.  I
can't read it, but Ai 102 Pariah
's Muna is no 7 Cleaning is the one who is neat and clean
Misa Iyo's sound anchor is 2
Nhaa
That's right. Both of them have a neat appearance,
but the Karon head is
not so good.  I think it's an okay band style.
No, I'm watching Live Rush, which I don't watch anymore.
That's right. I wonder if it's even in the comments.
Yuki wa Papa is in that pa-pan.  That
's
right. Hey, this is a fashion person.
Te Salmon. It's hard for a newcomer like this to join.
First of all, everyone is probably at war. You're
not lying to that three-person rider. I think you're
playing this psychological game.  I have
n't finished deciding who to choose yet,
so I guess I'll read it first.I'll
have to choose from them, so I'll
have
time to think.
Hey everyone, gc
If you think of that message,
please find me pretending to be asleep. Don't put pressure on me.
There's a lot of pressure on me.
Ah,
noon, that's what I'm talking about.
choose Noon. Don't say Moaha. Well then, no.
Yes, let's make rice as a hobby.Ah, there
is a possibility that it will grow or not.You
say it's completely rough and rough.It's
summer.I'm
going to send it to you.How
big is it?Please send it to me.If you decide,
please understand.
Please don't change. I hope it doesn't rain this much.
My love is barely enough to tell me that it's good for my teeth.
Please hold me
back. It's so warm that I'm scared it's going to fall.
Player. So, have
you made your choice? Yes, that's
okay.
Yes, that's Photo King I building. Paid.  Is that so
?
222 new Yes, it's
a little late at night. It's gotta rain, everyone.
It's gmail. There's
a problem.
Will you be able to announce the air thermos today?  It seems that I
can announce it, so I would like to announce it in one match. Please
announce it to Ise. Click here to
choose the carpet. It's a
shame. This
is the apb of the one. In August, that character island,
Hirofy is a bit of a reverse character.  Ah,
that kind of visual game horror has to be reversed.
Then, ahhh,
boobah,
shake,
yeahyeah, human.
Well, let's take a look at each one one by one.
So you've
chosen Porter 3, Anlucia.
Mayahony I
don't know if I should clean the original tank, so it
's a shame. Is it possible to clean it? I'll
sublimate it as a story tomorrow. It looks hot.
If I sublimate it as dance teacher data, I'll probably
become a soul senpai.  It's
not a broadcast.It's a
policy.That's what I expected.Ah,
I'm so happy.Ah, I
heard Bush senior's songs and a lot of hotpots.  I felt
like I was watching Dart's alter ego.I
never thought I'd see him playing with a Nendoroid, but I'm grateful.He's
probably a big performer.He
said he was going to eat it, but he acted
like it was entertainment bait.  Yes, that's
corrected.Fenty, who said it properly, and
Rescher-senpai, I
see.Yes, I thought
so.Ah, thank
you very much.  Noaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa”  The
reason is that only the store is at the bottom and the rest is because I'm a wife haha ​​4 I
understand, but I get the impression that the government
isn't everything, especially now.  I
thought it would be okay since I can't play,
but I always said yes, but for
some reason I was asked to do it,
but it was just like that.Yes,
thank you very much.
Yes, I mentioned it a little bit earlier,
but I have
n't done any collaborations yet, but
if it ends, I'll probably have just made my debut,
but I'm still p.
That's how you say it's still a technique down.  For a story  I
feel like it's not sublimated, hmm, maybe it's
time or outside activities,
but it's not because I don't have it.
There's number 4. It's okay to pray, then.
Marner, it's not like we're in a war right now, so it
's a lecture, but
what do you think?  Hey, let's take some shots.
There's also soccer, so let's watch over each other, ladies.
The future is scary. Well, I'm looking forward to it. Just a little bit. So, my
areolas and areolas are about to fall apart.  The
first chair means everyone's success.
Thank you.
[Music]
A Everyone read the atmosphere, and you
chose a slur that mixed the atmosphere reading. That's great
.
Now then, let's move on to the second choice.
Here's the second choice card.
Huh?  Let's chant "Hello"
No,
God, an oxygen baby is the perfect ideal
Hey,
maybe look at his politics
This is
[Music]
Boober  It's
been a long time since Ayabe Zoze taught me.
Well, this is crazy.
[Music]
Buber
But it's so shiny and unexpected. I'll
write a long story about how there will be a 5th place advance.  Some
people are crazy about it, but I guess it depends on the price. I
don't know, but ah, yes. Well,
everyone, if it's a paradox, then who is the one who doesn't respond? No, but if it's the
secret best, why not?  The
owner was fired from the main building
Booba
Diary Ahtaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah
se
with p It's Spain Boo
Boo I don't know if you're saying Nesne or something.Okay
then, it looks like everyone has answered
Nagayama Shaking I don't want to do it.Let's
all work together.Looks
good.  I'll
match it, but I can't
answer it. I linked the answer, right?
Yes, that's the president of the wholesaler who announced it on the scratches.
Mar
hae, let's do this, Luigi. Yes, then,
Ori. Well, the red is cracked,
but.  Hey, I
'm going to booby. First of all,
Mako-chan, please
take a look. Well, I'm looking forward to it. I don't
think anyone can deny it. That's true, isn't it
?  I
still have the impression that the value of Jeongjo hasn't fallen even though it's a washed up country.The more lucky Jeongjo is, the more
expensive it is.Well
then, let's play around a bit.Yeah, let's
go.Well, I
originally
put it in B.  That's right.
1 d It
's okay. I have to be honest with myself. Eh, do you want to
join Chinama Race?
Well, that's not the case, so I thought I wrote something.
In the second season of Tero 1 Brother Honjin, I
think that fur in particular has the image of being the government,
but the way he talks is like a war
after all.  If you
do that, there's that
back side, and
there's a hole between the mirror and this hole.Ah,
I already knew about the chance, so I changed it.I
thought the karma would disappear quickly,
hi-fi Yeah, that's right, a little bit at the end.  Yan-en  Even if you think that
Miyane has accumulated so much that you know even if you leave a feeling,
I
was the one who wouldn't suffer either way. Well, it's
very interesting to read.
J No, it's true that peace jp also
has the image of cleaning.  Yes, yes,
John's play is so-so. Mr.
Angelo is certainly strong,
so there are times when I wonder if it's a political party.
Hi Boo Baan
[Music]
pro Producer is a stylish guy. I won't reveal it,
but you're not that kind of person. You're the one who cuts your fingers to see how much you've grown.
But you're strong on the inside, and your fingers
don't wear out.  Yes, I
'm saying cert, so yeah, that
's the theme. It's a theme in the fee. The
accuracy and the content is a little bit. The content is a
little like the opening of the ad song.  I'm
not talking about that, but I don't know what time it is from Liu Xiu's point of view,
but
it's an interesting point of view from a producer's point of view. It's okay. Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.
I think there's more than life, okay. Ah, I'm
a little worried if I'll see you, but I
feel like I'm a deucer. New Sardar.
Looks like there's a possibility that I'll be
swallowed. I'll be lured in.
Moon, I'm looking forward to it.  However, I didn't get a
second chance this time. So, I
remember that. Wow, I was
waiting for the university. Yes,
that's why I would like to go to the third choice.
Yesterday's last lap.  It's your choice,
so please think about it.
Shiina, I think it's good so far. That's
it. Here's the Dodgers card.
So,
yes, a river. Hey,
yes, this is Naylor. Hey, Mr. B, what do you think?  Let's
do it. It's difficult. It's garbage.
Let's go. It's finally
time to call them. Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa didn't have been the children of last year It's neat and clean, but if you don't understand it, it will come out
Arthur Yes, that's right, bring the voice Naru
this one
Sancho Who will you go to after the low wage?  It's a 5 start.
From my point of view, I don't want to meet someone who seems like a good match for me
. I'm
in the country of renarena.  It's
okay, you can trill, right? It's
not the same, I want to be the boss, beam,
cannon Eval,
pin poster. Do you
think Nature
AI, awareness air,
Tabool? This is so
cool. I don't want to turn it into a third person.
Hey.  I'm a little confused about how to use that white.
Depending on how you look at it, you
could say they were all cleaning. Hmm.
Hmm.
[Laughs.]
Yeah, I might have had my own money too, but I
was just chasing after them.
Thank you again. So, what did everyone give me
? I took a picture of it. Well,
then.  Thinking time is over.
Hello.
That's it. I would like to make the presentations all at once.
I would like to ask Ise to make the presentations. Please
Rucker
par.
So I told one person, and only Mr. B got it. Well then, it's
okay if I don't say it. I didn't think I'd choose.
Well then, I thought you'd choose the Hi pattern. I
don't care how you feel about having a big Rangun-chan. I
don't know what the point is from the snakeskin afterlife.
That's it,
Anne Year
Epward. After all, she doesn't look like that.
After a little while, she looks cute, but she
looks like she's wearing an air conditioner, but
when she talks like that, she looks like a crazy little devil.  I
feel like it's possible to make a delusional comment about shipping.Somehow, I
learned about Nesobe-senpai, but
I'm stuck up to 1 slot, but it might be a morning.If
Raijinja continues, I'll share it earlier in the fall.Navi
Mall will be there.  Congratulations to Bin-san
for running so well. That's
how I ended up wearing it. That's great. I
put this term on my back on the stocks.  Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa, I
would like to ask each of you
why I did this to everyone.
But I
guess it’s because I recently heard a song by chan that was included a little bit.
Since there was a council meeting, I
thought it was a war with the booing now, and the
song was bitter for the first time.The unit was having a hard time with that image, so I
guess that's why I added that color.
Noyone's miso administrator, etc. are women.
Hey, the launcher is not an illustration.
But it's
neat and at the same time, after all, it's the same time.
How can we do the war and leave the bunker behind
? Hey, it's like a family. The
distance between Iiyama and the team of 6 people will flow.  It doesn't seem like it's something
like that. I do
n't think I've ever had a
good relationship with a lot of people. Ah,
that's interesting. There are people who think that way, but
Chiara was chosen by my peers.  It seems like they made a mistake
in choosing it.
Well, it looks like everyone in this is neat and clean,
but in the end, you can confidently
say that it's a cleanup. Even if you don't have a lot of people, you can say that it's the countryside of Piron. That Ina-
chan.  I
want you to be a little bit strong about yourself, so I'm
going to press the good thing, but after all,
it's a sweet mud.
If you want to play a musical instrument, that's
why I'm going to make you a senpai.That means there will be a difference in points, so only Mr. 8 p will get it.
Let's take a look back on how the unit was formed, one by one.
Well then, let's start with Mr. Button's neat
unit.
Janjanaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa's's not even a year.  I'm
totally fine with it, just on the stage,
because I can be a cleaner all the time. Yes, I don't care
what kind of talk I have with Ya 1, but then
in the book, Lucia has quite the same personality, so I'm
as rich as I am.  Hey, I don't do diapers,
right? I'll probably teach you tomorrow if there's a sky. I
bought 4 of them and said they were
cool.  I
don't have a jar.It's about time for my senior to
do the cleaning for the two of us, so it's Aaron, and
Aratanjins, so Yatsuda-san,
hey, that's
nice.I think it's good.Thank
you, and then let's move on to the next one.Let's
ps  It's 3 -This
yacht is here. Ah, oh oh oh,
winning Arthur,
I have an impact. Midfielder is like you.
Main Isono part It's all over with the tax revenue. I
wonder if it's a raaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh.  That's what I thought.
Yes, it's neat and clean with gaps. Well, that looks interesting.
Thank you. And I also like Mr. Kiura's cleaning uniform.
Let's go here, this is the highway,
this
is the house, it's all about Mitomiya iPhone, but when I
look at it like this, it's clear whether it's a win or a loss, there's
one more person missing, so I
'll take your place. Ah,
wow, I'm so excited. Yes,
my emotions.  I think it's definitely possible for a two-song unit,
but since there's one liar and four award predictions, I don't think it's
fair to say that.
Ah yes, that's right. Ah yes, that's right. Ah yes, that's
right. Yes, it's in.
By the banner saga
Well, it's parent and child. This color is the participant,
surfer
Jack Aoya. Hey,
yes, that's that care.  I
would like to be the producer who will take the haiku, not the room fee that I want to use to make it more concentrated.
Please let me know in the comments who you were most able to link to when it comes to love. Thank you very much for the unique
car last week. I
appreciate your comments.  It's
arigato, and it seems like it's
becoming more and more famous with its composition.So, I
tried it a little, and what was it like?I
tried the cleaning unit of the first one, and it was a
difficult police car.I kind of
worshiped that war, for example.  The
idea of ​​adding that slightly devilish rider element that would be present if it were an off-line story was really good,
so what is the next question?  I'm
sure it's
something like that concept,
but it's too late.Okay, well, that's a bit good,
so I think it's time to wrap up.Okay,
now I'm going to make a presentation based on what I'm thinking about.The
main topic this time is a link.  Those who were able to
Congratulations, it's Kiura-san! Nyaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa I I
’m not sure if you’re asking for it there, but
if you say that Asaba Shun is of the opposite sex, these two would
be the wrong person, that’s for sure.
But when you do that, you suddenly feel
a lot more neat and clean, but I
don't think it's a loser's dialect.That
sounds interesting.Congratulations on the campaign.
Amero a I
'd like people to create their own favorite units while imagining their own units.First of all, I would like to
announce the next theme.
Here's the theme. It's
not a new secret agent in the Ahorekku Sentai costume. I
mentioned it before.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa with with
Aaaaaaah I wonder if more and more layers will come out
Hey, I'm looking forward to it Well
then, let's go
to the word choice first. Let's say bar and
two here.
Macha
ase face el Jean
de
belarus
onoa
Loss, right? This is singing.
By the way, it's not long, but how to counter it.
Why is it weather resistant? I want to throw it now.  I wonder
what will happen to my anxiety if I get hired, and what will happen. I'm
young enough to be eaten.
OK, and I've decided that this is the person I feel
like. I'm
becoming Shoda himself, but in Spring 3D, I
asked him if it was time for me, and the pass app was
wrong.  I'm sorry, but d used it,
so I'd like to ask.I saw the role name in the story.I wonder if it would be
better to give it to each other.Luigi is a god,
so
in the case of Fox, he was also the commander.  I'm wondering
if I can
do the work I'm waiting for, like cleaning or something.The same goes for these four
people.I'm thinking about what I can do.I
decided on the 9th stone.Good luck.  I
hope I don't have to pay for it.The Hanamae Village atmosphere makes me happy.What will
happen to Iyo Mitten's battleship?I wish I could have some Goishicha tea.Now
that thinking time is over,
aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
So, let's all announce it all at once,
please.The temple of literature
is ah, the government has done it, it's
amazing.Above 8p,
on the other hand, it was left behind.I
wonder if the tourists couldn't take pictures of it.It's not like it's in the summer mood.  I thought it was possible to do something like Rosol,
so I spent a little time on it, and then I
came to Hyun Jae Babu Button, Sui-chan.The
image of a secret society is simply a squadron flame.
Since I imagined it, I think it's okay to use the color.
Well, after all that, I want her to have
blue hair. I
want to see her hair grow, so go ahead and get it in that color. If you're going to go ahead, Yusa, I'll go ahead and
do it.  Japan, why did you come in? Well,
then p Saan Ah
means taking care of yourself
Tat try this a Oh, what's that? Ah, I was
shy,
Tatai ja na is also a bit raw.
Senpai is a bit more of an arm holder. I
think it's English now, but it's
still a preliminary secret society crazy.
Ae
Gaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa4a
Since it's a fantasy, it seems like they can use magic or something like that.I see that it's
painted well, so I'm
looking forward to your future choices.Thank you very much.
For one reason, I think Shion-senpai would
be stronger if he could use that magic.
Yes, that girl once. The two companies
respect the Chinese New Year,
but it's no longer King's Packy.  Is that
clear? Well,
there is already an empty house in Horo x. It's
true that my
grandmother does it,
so I think all my rivals will do it, so I'm actually thinking about it.
Senpai is definitely active now
Who do you think that crappy kid from Horrocks is? He
doesn't do anything at all to chan,
but Ross
[Music]
Summer anime is good!
Hahn
Summer Vanes I guess you can guess it now,
right?  Actually, when I got home, I
looked forward to seeing what happened at that time. It's
like an alternative version of the battle that happened one day. I
want them to fight me. That's true.  Wii
Na
Na's
very similar -like -chan, it's
definitely a bit of a crew, but it's a little bit of a crew.  I
said I don't understand, but
Parker S is a success. Congratulations. Thank you.  Let's
do that in the room and go to the camp's choice.The
members of the second choice are
here.Akariope-san, the
chateau is walking fast.There are so
many shutters that look good.I wonder
how to take them.Mr.  I
wonder if I'll take the booba or not.I'm thinking about Natsumi.Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa It's a
simple sound that makes me want to read it like a reader
I can ride it.
So, I don't know if it's going to be a little bit off
or
what should I do
? Well, I don't know what to do. I'm not sure what to do. I just need some time, so please
stop by. I'm thinking about a serious new book.
Major 7 tons, everyone. What kind of book are you going to write?
Hey,
come on
[Music]
Seeds idf asm 4 id
Please tell me, of course, the secret you want to make inside
Who is it?
OK, I only saw you, so I decided  It's
really hard to decide which one is the boy. Hey, I'm
confused.
Now that the dentist has successfully decided on the birth cycle of the power, I
asked Masa. It's been 7 minutes. Have you
decided on everything?
Okay, that's the end of thinking time.
Asan
Now, let's announce it to the front line.
Please, please, please,
babara. The
big time choice was also a success. Yes, yes,
okay. Let's take a look at Wa-Waru. Let's take a total of
3 characters. Characters.
Algiano is going to hunt Ano in the same city separately here, and it's
not that most gloomy Aso Yuurin,
but it's a
new connection to the theme from earlier,
and it becomes a rival to that digging x. Is
that a rival?  I was really worried about that
change-chan, who has a weapon, so if you
look at the number of people who can step on the cover, the one who has it is more than a child.I
see, they can fight each other with weapons.  I
think I'd like them to be rivals. I
have an image of them as being very intelligent,
but I guess it's like a head vs.  It's
a joke, big brother, it's not finally,
that's what it's like, it's 40% 30%
after that It's like a samurai vs.
Yes, this is because daddy's book Sophie has a weapon
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, but Hanabishi-san did the resuscitation cleaning.I
watched a little weapon showdown, and it
was a little anime-like.By that's right.I wonder
if the showdown between the Jump King and the others was that big.As a result, I ended up drinking from time to time.
Oh, I'm running a shop,
so I understand. That's really interesting. Thank you. I
'm a member of the committee. Well then, I'm going to pay for the money, and
that's fine, woman 4 b. Come on, come on.  I wonder
if it's a team of two dogs, what is it? I
want to cooperate in love, so I'll lose weight.
Boober-chan
Noon Boyz Lost 4
[Music] I'll
go to Apo Island for a minute. Caliper. It's as easy as Earth to
protect. I wonder how many times I hear that sound. I see.
So, I'd love to
know what it's like to be born in Saga from the perspective of Mr. Kiura, who is like me.
From an image perspective,
he's an interesting kid. It's
so
cool.  It's a
little funny and Lung Maru is interesting
Booby If it's Rosa, English 4 Australia ah ah
ah ah
there's loss, right?
Rosasen Yes, shhh I
think Kancolle's yes
o Among the 2nd generation, it's missing and rate without permission
That sugar chain that I think is cleaning
Yeah, I'm sorry, but I can't say anything about
Komahane, so let's start with fashion.
Thank you very much.
And finally, Mr. Button, Daigo Urushi was attacked.  Um, I'm
definitely thinking of making various shapes and materials.I was
at a loss, but
since the Kiya staff is here, I'll go and buy some products and rollers.
reus It's almost time for sodomy polo I'm ah
ah
[music]
noon Additional members are coming and I'm already making a series of
lures
lazy to
do ah ha it's the same uh it's possible
Hey, that's the third choice.Next is the
last one.Last, a few thirds, let's go to
9.Here's the card.Also, the
passer power.  The
expression on my face
is like, oh yeah, just a little bit. There are
a lot of layers to the power,
and there are many different
colors. Hey, you wouldn't choose Kagura, the God of the Dungeon.  I'm
not going to choose anyone. From now on, Baka Hina-
nee-chan, the tone will be great. Maybe there will be another actor.
Hey, the
color is also a little strange. I wonder what will happen to the road.
So this is it. If the eyes are delicious, the
volume is
node
aether. Well, that's it.
Maybe, out of desperation, there
will be two people in the sabre car. It's the
famous sky of Jamisan Grassin Club. There's a
lot of blue. It
's a good road. I thought it would turn red.
Surprisingly, it's Opochi-kun. I was a little
scared, thinking that the station manager would join,
but it's true. Surprisingly, he didn't get the job
. He got angry at Gesan and a lot of money. He
touched the baton. A
Ah, the
racer was round.  Well, I
'm so happy. Well, today's a good one. It
was cool on the second floor, but
what do you think? It's all decided. I'll do it now.
Well
then, thinking time is over.
Okay,
Disney.
Now, please announce the last rath and the number of wins all at once.
Please.
Hayume Kobucha is Habusha.
Yeah
ana rank can
dj ra etc. a
her a What's that? Oppelia I'll
ask you about it later. First of all.  Button 3 di
But this is the head of that head, right, the
feather is a bit more money, or the head of the head.  If
Rescher-senpai and Sky-senpai were able to
do it, I think it would probably be a good fit.
If it's logistics f, then hahaha, well,
it's a step, so I probably won't win if I write a masterpiece. I see. What's the
pattern? It's an annual. I wonder if
this will happen.  They attack each other with an all-out attack.
In terms of power,
sea lions open up ties. It's a bit of a familiar
setting in the sky, right?
Summer. And then, let's support those two a little.  Around
that time, Paul Oras Boss
's hair was also dug up in the sumo section.
Thank you very much. I think we're an interesting
unit. That
's how the two of us ended up having the same problem.
Why is Glaster so good?
Chosen Hour
38  Are you a fan of ck one team? It's a
bubble but it's definitely good. Come on,
come with everyone, and it must be dark.
That Sana-chan and Sakura-chan will go to that castle to
support you. A. With such big waves.  I
guess I'm lucky in my later years, isn't it? It's nice to have bread. I'm
sure it's good to have rain, water, sea water, etc.
While I'm saying that, I want sea water. It's
not perfect.  Well, I thought everyone would choose the eyes,
but
then I made a reservation.Reaction
Hosouma Rival Theme Arjaan Rice Grass
Chang is Kuro A-chan's Rival  I do
n't think I'll get the nickname, but I
'm under pressure from my seniors, so Tenpai is the thick Kansai version of plastic surgery.
Well, that
's it, it's easy to understand,
so that's all, but at the same time, there are
new secrets to fight against Horrocks, one by one.
Let's see if the union has been formed.First of
all, I'd like to ask Mr. Button.Eh
, this one
is good.I'm thinking of
inviting you,
so there's no next time.The
listing on Iwata City also fell flat in Iwata City, and there are two 6th generation students
and 3rd generation students, so I'll kill them.  I hope they touch it. It's so
thin that it looks good. If we win,
this is the unit for summer 4 ep 3.
Amaran Anagrasan should have been included.  That's
right. The
Shiira team, who I'm a big fan of, really
wanted to make a Kachari. If you
join Laban, you'll be able to see it,
and you'll be able to join Pantaji, and you'll be supported by Gigas. It's
love, as expected.
So, how to enter third party?
Thank you very much for all the children.It
was Kiyuna-san, and I
was here with Asano-kun.Ah,
yes, and he lives in Aburachan.If
that magicianism had come to meet you.
Yes, I thought it was a good idea.
Well, there are some measures I'd like to
take a look at, such as anime that look like fun. So,
everyone was watching
and commenting and linking to the most popular topic.
Please let me know your comments
Hi, let's
get into one and move forward
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa-Bus Change Boy Reach, Bus Change Boy
Reach, Zazu Tomorrow Team and Pon Shufu were the best,
but I don't need them because they weren't there, I do
n't need them.
After trying it twice like this, everyone came
up with a concept and found it interesting.Ah
, somehow it seems to have come to life.It made me want to go to bed in the early hours of the morning.No,
everyone had fun with Mr. Near Future.See the
bottom part.
I also have to think about it a bit,
but those two flights were also included, so I'd
like to conclude with this.  I
'll announce the person who was able to link to the theme the most this time.
This time it
's Pen Button. Congratulations.
[Music]
Of course it's been done,
but it's a battle.
4th place Hmm, Hue Bar
[Laughs] Boo
Bar, I'm so happy!  I thought it might be
Ozone Kit. I'll
be representing you.
Thank you very much.
Station
me2
So, I've linked two different topics in a little while.  There
were only two people who were able to link to the theme, Mr. Botchan Toshikiura.
Congratulations.
[Music]
Oh, that's good. I should have fallen in.
But hey, there's nothing there.  That's why I wanted to drink it. Well, I'm
sure it was really good, but I
think we both had two more drinks.
It's good under the fair, Abe Tan. I'm sorry,
but I'd like to try it on another machine. I'd definitely like to try it again on another machine. I
think so. Thank you very much, Maa-
chan. Well then, that's fine. 10th generation
Kahei.  The person who wants to go is going to make an important announcement, yes, I think. It looks like he's here.  I
'd like you to do some reading as well, but
since it's such a cold day, let's
meet up and play the culprit. That's
all, please.  It's so
lewd
What
Maxo
Ah
rar
Yeah yeah aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaatanshiptata
Uwaaaaaaaaaaah
rar
[Music]
All the event cats
me
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
in The mountains around the stake have decided
a
rar boo boo
anoano
[applause]
Day
I'd like to get it, but 8 p I'm sure it's
a guess, so please let me know.
Well, I think I've finally made it to him.
If it's his sister, there's
a lot of big things going on in Void. I'm
really glad I was able to participate in the event. Let's watch the
4th episode where we can be together.
ee 2. Reru's character tanto is delicious. Hey, we're
together,
right?
As you would expect from Mr. Moss, Mr. Miura, his wife, please give us your impressions. Yes, it
was Ito's afterlife, but
haha, well, I don't have to watch it first.
Well, I guess I
saved up some money, but I didn't launch it.
Um,
Chiara has done
a lot of follow live
concerts, such as that broadcast and the same implementation, but I've
endured standing on the same stage for a long time,
so I was
really able to do this.  I'm so happy, and I'm looking forward to showing everyone what kind of
performance I'm going to do,
and everyone's amou
sensuality is full of excitement.  There
was an announcement made by Zhang Jin,
but in conjunction with this announcement, I would like to release the
t-visual of the spot surface that was
released earlier, so it's
not revenge.Here
is the key visual for the expo.  The
members are Kasuga Onna Air
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.  I had no
choice but to become Hippo's Needs, so I'm
happy that they're now the all-stars of the main team.Next
up is the key visual for the third festival.Here
's the key visual.Here's the serve.Here,
hey, here's the announcement
lol Hey, it's not too early.
I
Amedei
Hi, I'm a little happy. We're all
lined up like cats here.
It's delicious to drink, but I'll
be participating in the key visual this time.
Follow Live Production
Follow Live Polo Live english  The
stars of Horo Live Indonesia Posters will
be performing live as the key visual for the third festival.Follow Live Kono Live
English Miss Polo
Live Indonesia's 1st generation members will be appearing in this
very gorgeous key
visual.
[Applause]
Okay, well, let's talk
a little bit about the Expo. Hey, in
Projectioners, it's
gradually becoming clearer how we'll be participating.
Everyone, please look forward to it.
Yes, and moreover, this is not the only thing.
Holodot is
making a big appearance, and we
have also released information on the goods for the Saa Ikeposa Third Festival.
1. This is important. 1. The real identity of Ngya
Minutes are Furataru Live and A
Eyepatch Night So speaking of the general section, it's Penai and
how many chapters I want to take I want to pretend I'm definitely in love, so
naturally I'm also ready for battle Ahahama I
press it.
But since I've bought it, let's support it together at the Hashinya Bar Horo Live.Thank you
very much.  It has a
built-in logo that lights up.It
has everything from the image of the Mamo-san Busu performers, so it is an
indispensable item for cheering on the management's live performances.Yes
.  I don't
want to hold a hula and hold it and shake it, but it doesn't become a memory.
And the
t-shirt is also a must-have for live performances. It comes in
two colors of work and fight, and the
words to choose from sizes M, L, and XL are very friendly.
In some cases, the back is prepared with the name money of the performers of the live performance,
and
Storm Hatachi's name is haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.  Thank you very much for your support.
Large
and muffler towel. This
is an item that boldly uses live logs. It
goes perfectly with the Hetto Live T-shirt and has a beautiful look.
Thank you very much. It's cool. I
really want it.  It looks
like there will probably be another one
next time. Let's go next. This is a little love.
That one wasn't that either. It
's an iPhone. It's a windbreaker.
It's a tote bag. There are so many amazing live performances by the master.
But in the
morning, it
still
feels like a small bag.It's a light bag that can hold my closet-colored
Moonlight for concerts and my sister's tickets,
and
now it's designed like a Windraker Ronnie with a round second floor.
The windbreaker has a
logo designed not only on the chest, but also on both arms.
Well, it has the
names of all the talents affiliated with Ore Production
written on it. I'm
so happy.
Hmm is perfect for around March.It can
also be conveniently used as a coat for Ra.And it has a
design that can be worn anytime,
so I feel like I would like to use it on a daily basis.Hello,
and a simple tote bag.
However, when you pull up the zipper, it gets a little
bigger. It's
so convenient that it's 14th place in the amazing expansion. Back
then, it was designed with icons of live members,
and the
capacity can be adjusted depending on the purpose.  It
's a tote bag that you can change the design of. Well, it's small. It
's a shredder. It's in the comment section of the summary section, and it's posted as a copy comment on the internet, so there's also 3rd place for 10 people. And it's too late. What kind of outfit do you wear?
Simple is the
best. It's Sakoshi. It's
perfect for holding small accessories, so it's
recommended to accompany live performances.
So, at the end, I'll be releasing the penlight colors all at once. It's under
construction, etc. Please take a look.  Let's
enter rar
Feminism is color is color decay is yes
yeah character is not like
that signal 9 eia county second step in
file fain holding white 2 is
Ito The
members who will be performing like this are
obvious at a glance  So, I guess it's a bit
good, everyone, please practice so that you can change that color.
Thank you Patty Leaf
Peony I wonder if I did a firefly I
arrived at the button that carried me on my back.  I
felt like I was reaching the button that said, ``I'm going strong,'' and I said, ``
Thank you, I don't have daycare.''
Even if you have a ticket to enter the
Expo, you
can buy goods on-site without having to enter the
third pace car. How to purchase, regulations for infants, etc.
Details will be announced at a later date, so please wait for more information.Car
aa 4 e
aCongratulations, I'm going to use the melting hinge in my defense.I'm
a little excited today because it's the year of the year.  I'm
going to end this here, but everyone, how do you like it? Let's
do a new project. Well, let's
get some weights. Hey, let's
eat again. It was fun. It
was great. Thank you so much.
Nao. Thank you very much for coming.
Please do your best in your regular lessons as well. There are some lessons that are
a little rough. I'll do my best in the lessons.
Hello and Tia's comments.
Thank you very much to all the viewers and to all the viewers.
Thank you for your support.Yehre
re
rb dia
aria
and penis
ex 4 third pep information will continue to be
reported on official programs etc. Please look
forward to it.  The
person I'm talking to is my friend A Building
Shihaku Button.
Ellery and Fee Center
Takana Seki Arbi.
Thank you
very much.
Thank you very much.
jr
ran
[Music]
[Applause]