[Music]
[Applause]
hi what's what's going
[Music]
on what's going on
everybody I think I'm preparing to play
Minecraft I think that's what's going on
I'm a little bit confused about what I'm
supposed to be doing in this very moment
I feel like I'm supposed to be preparing
myself for
something like a bonk on the
head and maybe after the Bonk in the on
the Bonk on the head I lose my memory or
something get a little Amnesia something
like
that maybe but what would cause the Bonk
on the head
I'm pretty sleepy I'm pretty
eepy I'm a little
sick but that's okay because maybe once
I have
amnesia myself and my body will forget
that I'm sick and I'll
be I don't know what I'll be what would
I be with
amnesia I never forget anything so I
really have no clue
anyways there's a black screen that's on
purpose I don't really get what I'm
supposed to do honestly I think I'm
supposed to within a minute make it not
black
anymore perhaps I'm supposed to appear
somewhere let me double check that
that's what I am supposed to do
instructions are a little unclear how
will I Bonk my
head how will it happen people are
saying many many things okie
[Music]
dokie I
see okay
everybody I'm going to prepare
myself to to lose
everything I'm ready to lose it all are
you guys oh I got kicked wow okay hold
[Music]
up
uhoh oh you guys can see see
that what the heck is
this what is this oh why are the where
why is she staring at me f wait why are
you staring at me f what what did I do
what did I
do am I
muted what is
[Music]
this okay are people using this right
now they are
[Music]
oh are we supposed to lose our memory
already wait hold on hold on a
[Music]
second
ow ow what happened where am I
what happened I think I hit my head what
happened who are all of you
hello what makes you think you don't you
hit your head
too wait I don't see any cracks though
are you
sure wait wait oh you do have a
crack don't worry about it
I wonder if you can hurt people
here can I hurt
you am I hurting you am I hurting
[Music]
you in my bones oh my
goshes this doesn't hurt where are you
[Music]
from
okay um am I can someone do a little
check I I I got banned I got banned for
trying to hurt a lost confused little
rat oh
dear am I the only one experiencing this
oh nope I'm not this is a universal
experience what does this mean I don't
remember how to read
everybody I forgot everything except how
to speak
English oopy doopy oopy doopy oh the
game was muted was
[Music]
it it's okay you guys are on whatever
whoever I am's point of view all you
need to know is what I'm
saying you get what I'm
[Music]
saying all right let's see hold on a
second hold on a second am I streaming
is that what I'm
[Music]
doing what is
are we all still
confused are we still asking God
why voices I'm surrounded by Voices why
do I feel like I was just surrounded by
Voices within the last 24 hours as well
with
that this one's seems very put
together you look like you look
fine like fine isn't nothing
wrong thank you you look good
enough yeah
I can't hear anything well that's not
true I'm lying
[Music]
hello how would you know did you recover
some of your memory I don't remember
anything crazy is that I feel like I've
heard that before why are you so quiet
why is everyone's so loud except
you everyone's L except you too is this
reverse proximity chat wait back up back
up no it's
okay
hello I don't think it's reverse
he going to stop
eating I'm trying to get you in my right
ear she going to my corner
hello why would you get that
impression supposed to be a cute girl
righten of
you adjust oh did you adjust it like in
your
head I think I have to do the same for
you I don't know why but
I'm please please speak hello oh Wonder
am I
speaking you are but why who why is B
also in my
ear I mean who the heck is that she just
looks like a ba she does maybe it's the
letters floating above her head oh those
letters is that what those
are seems like your your dele went
pretty deep I forgot how to read we need
to go back to the elementary school
classroom I think so I hit my head
pretty
hard the alphabet Cirus
circus you know I'm having faint memory
of like those little paper pamphlets did
you have
do you remember
those there were lots of paper
pamp I remember oh my
[Music]
gosh Echoes of Forgotten
memories is this my
Lord press what the heck is a sneak key
what is a sneak key what what
what is a
saky okay it shift
[Music]
apparently Who I Am the world I live
in what was the word say before
that and more than
[Music]
anything the people I hold most dear I
have those
or I had
those faced with Oblivion I feel empty
wait I can
read okay I guess I guess my ability to
read is coming back no plot holes
here I feel
empty
relieved what is this pacifism or
something no no what am I thinking of
I don't remember I hit my head really
hard I feel it I feel a bump forming on
the right side of my head perhaps dist
draw these are all kind of different
[Music]
no I do not
know why do I feel like I've said this
sentence so many times in my life I do
not
[Music]
know so much I don't know I didn't I
just say that didn't I just say that and
yet and yet that bright light it calls
to me that
one wait that that
[Music]
one is that the Moon that light there's
a lot of lights am I dead this
is oh my name is Jonathan spelled with a
G cool Jonathan
I just saw heaven light where shall we
head are we the fastest
readers yes I think
so
fast it was in my head oh even faster
thinking Ice Ice Baby I hope there's
food over here
ooh someone's hungry
careful is this a hole oh my
God it's not a hole it's not a hole it's
not not a
hole not a
hole jump quite to make fun of one when
you meet for the first time where the
heck are you
[Applause]
from okay is this the sweet release of
[Music]
death is this
one
what the best still cast
what what are
those what
the breaking the fourth wall here we
have not seen any of this I have no clue
what this is back in back in what did
they say they said hey there
hi you have the look of Outsiders about
you I feel like that's not something you
should say to
somebody yes wait wait could it
be could it quick send a word to his
mates there's there's a
Majesty the the heroes have arrived at
the
sanctuary me right
[Music]
away roal audience chamber what are you
why is it so cute are you the Majesty
welcome Heroes this is the kingdom of Le
bestl and I am its king the Majesty
that's the
Majesty the guards who brought you here
have informed me that you remember not
but your own
names no my I I was thinking that I
think the my name is it's like on the
tip of my tongue it's like it's like
Cleopatra
Eisenhower da Vinci the great thei or
something coming it's coming back to
me a side effect of travel between
worlds no doubt it wasn't for me hitting
my
head
oh this must all come as a surprise to
you but hearken well it was I who
summoned you
here wait are you so I didn't just fall
asleep and hit my head you you sent
someone to whack me
you see an unprecedented Calamity now
threatens our
world this
world it has sell the Earth with
corruption and driven us from our
homes oh how how
Dreadful this blighted land now gives
rise to creatures of Shadows known as
stains
stains this Kingdom of lisal and its
surroundings are now the only safe place
left to us theist
am I pronouncing all these things
correctly I'm so excited to hear
everybody else pronounce these things
but should the Calamity be left
unchecked is only a matter of time
before it consumes the entire
world oh it's so cute I want to I want
to hit
it I want to throw it across the room I
want to hit it against a wall and it's
going to squeak like a like a toy face
with the prospect I scoured the ancient
to ooot okay the ritual of hero
summoning
I'm a
hero you who hail from another world
have been summoned here by me to become
the saviors of the
bestl only you have the power to save a
world I knew I was
special only me so not the other 18 just
me right and so I ask Will
you your majesty
what is it he's so tiny compared to the
guard a great host of stains has broken
through our defensive
line
no oh
no we are rushing to mount a defense but
the situation is dire Your Majesty we
must get you somewhere
[Music]
safe oh he noticed me how did you not
notice me before you're not a very good
guard there's a stranger here standing
before your king and you just passed by
as if I wasn't here I could have had so
many opportunities to kill him what' he
say oh he's asked like what who are you
strangers including
me what what say you Heroes will you
accept this
Destiny there is great power within you
will you use it to save us to save this
world but
can IOP
you
hi
hi is that the only thing you say oh hi
okay no about be brok in this one a
little just a tiny bit little broken
this one over here kind is that kind
that's what I
[Music]
asked we don't
remember don't remember don't we don't
[Music]
remember situation is so funny to me I
have no
[Music]
he oh my gosh she stting her
I am no
hero the King has made the great mistake
wait the king said you were hero to
propose to me he
said then got cut off I think we were in
the same Squad you were in line for the
Thro I did not realize I'm in the face
of royalty your Hess yes honestly your
your highness could you maybe go back to
the king and get him to change his mind
because the bab is I am not I just want
to find a cabin in the woods live a
quiet life for the rest of my days I
know I understand my my little cousant
[Music]
however you I was going to be crowned as
Queen but like I said I was rudely
interrupted by one of their servants but
promise you after we save the
world I will make you have a good long
retirement oh your hardness you most
generous I would you in distress we got
to go sa I regret that you must face
such danger so soon after danger no why
did I feel like I was listening to a
customer service phone call just now oh
dear
Majesty his majesty know oh I
should why does this this using so many
difficult words I don't understand these
words I come me come from a land of
simple
words too late to save this world from
destruction this is our duty to defend
King it's your duty not my duty this is
not my king Brave World Heroes let us go
forth without
defeat I'm waiting for like a teacher to
say 1 2 3 all eyes on
me wait it's fight time already oh my
goodness I can fight I can fight I can
fight I can fight
purple bar what does it
mean oh
de why doesn't he why doesn't he feel
any
damage may we have to kill the this is
pretty op somebody died you can die oh
what's that H it Hur it Hur it h it h it
Hur it hurt it nice hurt this one hurt
this one hurt this one uhoh see now I
feel like I'm contributing remove the
what the oh God where he
go wait he's going to kill the king he's
going for the king he's going to kill
the king I'm going to kill this one
though this is on me this is on me
ow oh my gosh I'm out of
there oh I'm going to die oh dear oh
dear oh dear oh dear please please small
one help me but I got a big head a big
heart I have red I have red I bread I
bread I
bread why is he why ises he like me so
much oh thank you thank you my beautiful
Knight if that's what you are
oh oh dear am am I oh dear I'm I'm
sicking hear you
you I'll help you it hurts I'm going to
prove that I'm the best hero the biggest
best hero has you lost any
XP ooh this this way stranger oh oh
death
again shout
Revelation hold your weapon and left
click
Revelation Hold Your Weapon this weapon
left cck revelation
[Music]
Revelation Revel
Revelation
reev
[Music]
Revelation put your heart into it who
are
you
Revelation revealing
ration
re
Lian
[Music]
re this what is that what I was supposed
to
do Revelation no
worky I bet somebody wasn't saying it
and that's why this happened
somebody wasn't screaming it somebody
was just saying it in
[Music]
their why why is there a voice in the
back of my head that just went bow bow
but in all over
[Music]
G in response to the lack of Revelation
just a a lower case bow bow
[Music]
oh my goodness my head is
spinning just spinning oh it appears
that revelation will not return for
about 5
minutes and it appears that I have to
now
sit in my lonesome and not listen
to what word am I thinking of oh dear no
the English it's slipping away from
me I can't to get back in I never
thought I would miss all the voices that
I
[Music]
heard especially after yesterday where I
just have a hunch that I was again
surrounded by the voices of a Vilan cute
[Music]
girls and then here I am again with no
recollection of it but being
blessed to hear it again AL be it's
different
voices was all a dream was
it was it
now that fair Maiden with the blackish
bluish hair that was
[Music]
shortish she had a nice voice
the chick with the
pigtails that are
uneven and the loud red
hair I'm kind of worried about
her I little worried about
her the Majestic giraffe looking lady
with the silky green
hair adorned with
flowers she seemed
[Music]
fine
anyways I don't think you guys are any
closer to understand no I'm not any
closer to understanding what's going on
than you
guys also
who Who I Am Me
Cleopatra Eisenhower D Vinci the
great the second or the
third doesn't
matter doesn't matter
me what about
me oh I'm not
sick I'm normal this is how I sound
normally this is how I behave normally
[Music]
normal
actually the eyelashes feel very
[Music]
sticky normal actually
normal I will make an attempt to join
again I was unable to perhaps a little
voice in the back of my head will tell
me when it's
[Music]
ready
perhaps I hope I hope that I am not
expected to count it down the 5
[Music]
minutes I wonder what my future has in
store for
me I wonder what will come to be from me
being here
today not being dead I thought I died so
many
times I was so ready to go into that
good
[Music]
night I'm feeling kind of self-conscious
was I not saying Revelation very
well was I was I really bad at
it did I ruin
this for
everybody it cannot be it cannot be
there has to be someone worse than
me out of 19 people I could not have
been the one who was the worst at saying
Revelation it's not it's not
me it's some external
Force I am at my Peak State there's
nothing for me to improve on your
criticism is not needed and not welcomed
before I do
not I I don't have dang it I'm going to
say need again even though I just said I
don't need it but within the same
sentence I'm going to repeat it and
that's not very good
English however no one could form a
better
sentence it was still the greatest
sentence that could have been formed to
convey what I was trying to
[Music]
say so again I don't need any criticisms
where I don't need any advice
[Music]
is they should have told
us oh it's just
me wait it's just me am I supposed to be
here wait am I supposed to be here maybe
I'm not supposed to be here I'm in a
room by
[Music]
myself am I am I not supposed to be
here uh-oh perhaps I should wait see I
got very oh wait let me eat first let me
get ahead this isn't
cheating let me make sure that whenever
I get back I'm at full
health they'll never
know n n
[Music]
see I knew I was the main
character all right I am going to leave
myself unsatiated okay I'm going to
assume that I'm not supposed to be here
so I'm going to I'll see myself out for
a
second perhaps I am supposed to wait
until they tell us to go back for
absolutely nobody else is in there it
was just me hopefully I didn't hold
anything up by
appearing I
hope what if behind the scenes the gods
of the world are going why the heck is
she here why the heck this we were so
close to being finished fixing
everything and her showing up ruined at
all it's was going to be another 5
minutes what if what if that
happened back in the Box why do I feel
like I was just within the last month
inside a white box that looked so
similar to that one except it didn't
have that kind of logo in it oh how
strange how
queer I
wait oh the voices the voices in the
back of my head that appear on my
screen they're saying
things but they aren't saying to go back
but I'm going to do it and happen oh
people
humans oh my God wait so is this like a
different timeline
IES have turned back the time
your yourness maybe we you can go back
and his Hest finish the and you can get
me out of here voes they're not telling
me to do anything I don't know what to
do they're giving me no commands I don't
know what to do
to save the
world
from I'm not going to off my we're going
to call off this journey oh thank you
what about my sword do you have you have
a nice sword too thank you thank
[Music]
you take me
back take me back to that wonderful
place
the place where you
died you look lonely I can fix that I
find it absolutely adorable that you and
the King you similar vocabulary like may
have or not
yourness I will stick by your side until
this L finishes your highness you're
quiet
no need I don't know how to fix it I can
fix
[Music]
you the is fine your I I'd like that can
you fix me please I'm fixing you there
is a v in there someone fixing you
you're fixed thank you all hold on I
need a fixed B I mean that that hot babe
over there yeah that hot babe over there
yeah I need to fix fix her you are so oh
my sword sword oh my sword as
well good thing we haveing all
us haha you're crazy she called you
crazy
crazy let me help
[Music]
you
stand out of these walls man oh are we
working together to escape hello
[Music]
the what
what why is that
breakable why is that breakable
what did I do get me out of
[Music]
here I broke a dimension didn't
I oh God what did I do hold on hold on
hold on hold on don't look don't look
don't look
[Music]
is everybody still in the
box oh dear what dimension did I break
this
time I assumed if everybody I did I do
[Music]
that they're in the night sky thingy
they rid it oh shoot me leaving made it
so that I
skipped was that just insane
timing I'm supposed to see the dialogue
if I open okay well if I open up my mind
back into consciousness of that world it
it does not take me to the
[Music]
dialogue that is ridiculous
what the
heck okay
um let me see I might okay I might get
spoiled but you guys probably won't
be well because I'm not showing you
anything yeah I'm not I'm not supposed
to be here I I'm not supposed to be
there
[Music]
oh
wait hold
on hold on I think I'm waiting to be
picked up I'm waiting for somebody to
pick me
up let's see oh I'm being picked up oh I
got picked up nice okay okay okay cool
all
right echo of Forgotten memories
yeah who I am the world I live
in yeah
yeah Deja Vu moment here and more than
anything
yeah yeah the people I hold most dear
yeah
yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah face with a blo I feel
empty yeah
yeah yeah
relieved
yeah yeah yeah yeah perhaps
distraught
yeah
yeah I I do not know yeah
yeah I don't
know I don't know so much I don't know
and yet
yeah yeah that that bright
light it calls to be yeah
[Music]
yeah oh dear are we all is everybody
doing this
[Music]
again what are you doing to look up
the have to look up
[Music]
the on second I can't see
chat ski a skipper how do you skip a
skiper I can't Skip
[Music]
Skip it's him the cute guy the cute guy
that I want to throw and have animal
retrieve
[Music]
am I breaking it oh spam okay okay okay
okay I wonder what the others are
[Music]
doing I'm going to drink water while I
do this
[Music]
wait where's
everybody
huh where is
[Music]
hello
hello it's just me
I went too fast wait the others all did
the same thing am I just waiting for
them is that it I wait here I'm the main
character I'm the first one
done wait
where where's
everybody everyone else is here but the
but they're
not they're already there
why am I
alone I can't do this alone can
I it's just me
hello me
[Music]
you
oh I can do it oh no I
can't what the
heck he doesn't even take any damage I'm
going to
die what is this what is the skill
difference ow just touching him did that
look at this look at this look at this
look at this look at this I dodged
it it's like a Souls
character I know this is rigged maybe
I'm supposed to
die maybe it's part of the
plot it adds I mean it definitely adds
to the story somebody ought to die that'
be crazy oh my gosh that' be crazy if
all 19 of us survived
until the
end oh he has a
beam what the
heck his aim got worse I feel like I'm
wasting Bread on this apparently I have
to ENT oh it's been 2 minutes I was just
had to entertain him for 2
[Music]
minutes
hello what shout Revelation and hold the
Revelation
Revelation oh my
[Music]
goodness the St host has been
routed I did it and I got my dagger I
mean a dagger that I've never seen
before
hello look at them are these the
different houses Celesta oh my you
fought bravely kind Heroes just me here
I pray you're not
inured pray harder I'm hurting real
bad rubius that Mighty armored one must
be their leader the stain King
fascinating Most
Fascinating AR Arin well I see why they
call you
arrows we'd be in a right pickle with
them without your El
that what is what is that supposed to
be AOS we sustained a minimal damage
thanks to your Bailer our kingdom is in
your debt thank
you I must hasten Hast hasten to inform
His Majesty of her Victory will you
accompany
me I suppose I
will l
just shut up I was team veiler in
Pokmon
go I heard the news though we called
upon you suddenly you Rose to the
occasion you have my deepest gratitude
what interested me most however is
strange power you manifest during the
battle with which you were able to
defeat the stain surely nobody else had
some really cool op move it's just me
right just me and my dck who am I
talking to
and power May well be the key to saving
our world from
Annihilation oh dear fuzzy M was slain
by stain
King oh dear according to the heroes the
power came to them like a forgotten
memory when they spoke the word
revelation wait oh multiple Heroes not
just me
okay no one's they used to to root R the
the stain hosted
s well that's bloody brilliant in no way
so we always must to the next time St
talk revelation we must uncover the
secrets of this phenomenon if we are to
Prevail against the
Calamity many questions remain but one
thing is certain the kingdom of the
bestel still stands today thanks to you
me that he notice that they didn't say
y'all they just said they said you me
me here here show Heroes this is me here
I asked for you once more will you lend
us your strength to save the bestl from
R I guess so I have nothing else to do
right now I nod yes
yes marvelous on behalf of all the bes I
thank you we're blessed to have your Aid
kind hero
singular allow me to introduce the four
Great guilds which are responsible for
ensuring the Kingdom's peace and
prosperity
The Haven for the Curious where
knowledge and creativity creativity
creativ
creativ what was it called I can't go
back the home for Glory seers with
ambition and vision where closest allies
become fiercest Rivals the Amber coin
the sanctum of healing with the spirit
of empathy and devotion thrives the the
[Music]
the beacon of the righteous and loyal
where great threats are faced with even
greater courage the day
jange one of these gills will become
your home during your time here my
[Music]
house Beyond this door lies the room of
Truth therein the will of the ancestors
shall decide your guild fear not
introspection is a vital step on the
road to enlightenment Excel exceler as I
always say ever higher time to roll the
dice oh wait is this the British one eh
be seen some look down at the coin cuute
hole let us save the world together the
room of Truth await to go forth with
[Music]
VOR am I am I where I'm supposed to
be the room of Truth let me double check
am am I supposed to be in the room of
truth I ask
[Music]
God are chat are you
God everyone's catching up
oh wait okay okay yes I am I'm supposed
to be here okay cool okay cool needle
step on the platform and receive the
will of the
ancestor is this a liquid do I drink
it oh I miss the countless sparkling
lights seek Enlightenment with
with
Scarlet Scarlet not that's that is not
fever what does that say
[Music]
okay wait what amber
coin done the
cloak how do I do this
again ooh
armed with an unwavering will seek to
defend the soul of
Jade am I wait am I not all of
[Music]
them hello oh my gosh I have a recycling
bin and and I have an egg and I have a
radi I thought it's a radio and a map
and an
axe very
cool it's me
m oh what's
this oh perhaps it's time for me to to
to do something hold
on one second wait I think I got if you
if you get stuff in the game you get
stuff in real life oh my gosh I got I
got stuff wait this is the game this is
this is true this is life no
okay A C another cave a second cave
oo oo
o
shiny shiny shiny
[Music]
oh this is all I can show you for now
otherwise stuff will happen ttle
[Music]
drop
hello
oh hello
weirdo uh don't tell me are you in the
same Guild as as me is that what this
means is that why we are together now
uhoh please to make your acquaintance my
name is the bay I still don't know your
name unfriendly
stranger I will tell you I'll try to be
friendly from here on I will need to
force yourself I don't believe in
changing character for for friendship
it's called character
development dummy my name I think is
Cleopatra
Eisenhower Da Vinci III no the great
thei I'm just going to call you three
from now on all righty oh oh my goodness
that was the cutest entrance I've ever
seen hi now how come to hello oh hi I
done something to you
three you weirded me
out H where are we okay I think we I
think were we supposed to talk to the we
all in the same Guild do I really have
to be in the same Guild as this okay you
do righty you've been chosen to be with
me that's not where where where is the
lead oh the lead is the leader over here
oh orin's over here hello you we have to
go Orin who is this who are you do we do
we oh I think I'm standing on or do we
have to
oh I want the table on the table on the
table hello there
hii oh wait it's oh it's our Guild sorry
keep you waiting oh that's perfectly
fine oh what the
got you also got a recycling bin why
I've got to to recycle where we've got a
map oh yeah we got to recycle for sure
we do got a m how do we talk we got to
speak to the Gil Master how do we talk
to the master wait we have the British
one oh we totally
do oh I I can talk to him you speak
British yeah right click he says water
this air is the Amber Corn's little den
of
operations uh name's aurin and I'm the
closest thing in charge around
[Music]
here Orin we have the British
one liore straight away after you were
summoned but we appreciate it now you
want of us meaning We Fight Together
against some stains maybe do a little
well saving while we're at it eh perfect
he's Canadian
[Music]
too Canadian you to get
Town we're in learn how to accept and
perform quests see there's a quest
bought out in town with missions get
posted might want to take a bches out
and see what the quest master has to
say I don't understand are you because
you do it this so well I don't
understand either I'm trying to catch up
here we completed the quest that me that
was that was the
M skill Master next go to the quest
board we have a quest
stranger wait where is the quest Master
honestly that conversation this is the
quest Master but don't worry you needn't
bother him we fulfilled the quest oh go
to the quest
Bo we on to the next Quest slow down you
what was your name
again the bay I follow the bay okay and
what's your what's your
name me yes what what's what's your name
I am uh nice to meet you I'm Takara of
the oranges of the oranges your
name your name your names what is your
name my name is
[Music]
panta P I already aded nice to meet you
nice to meet you both my name is the B
and this over here is three very nice to
meet you that's not my name that's the
lazy version of my
name no it's Cleopatra Eisen divin she
the great the
third for short three just call just
call just
call the number three she's not very
nice so try not to get on a b no I I
just treat people the way that they
should be treated that's
all this are very nice I don't think
we're going to get
along yeah oh what I think that I think
that there'll be a Twist in this story
line and we'll be the bestest of friends
I hardly doubt it I don't I also don't
know where we're supposed to be going is
bookie the quest guy
perhaps isn't it a
board sorry I think the first thing you
need I'm not going to touch Quest board
do you think that's the quest board
everybody we're going the wrong way
we're going this way where are we oh
you're right we're not supposed to be
here well yes we're not supposed to be
here we're not supposed to be there oh
no we're going to get in trouble we're
going to get
expelled oh no we just got here expelled
like is this a school or what I'm just
taking I'm taking gues right now please
just leave me alone I have an egg you
guys also have an egg I have an egg I do
have an egg it's cuz I'm running out of
bread oh would you like a piece of bread
no I I still got two but like just
wondering for okay well sure if I can
eat the eggs well I have five
so five eggs or five breads
five eggs I have five breads wait we
lost our cat not
to we lost our cat kitty kitty kitty
here kitty kitty kitty Kitt Kitt Kitt
Kitt Kitt Kitt Kitt kitty kitty kitty
kitty kitty kitty kitty kitty kitty
kitty three
what I guess we got off the wrong foot
um
how what Lovely weather we have
today how would you know it just started
[Applause]
all
right uh we found our kitty
cat we found our kitty cat please leave
me alone with
three need to be on a leash it seems no
can we request one God can we please
have a leash yes we need a leash for all
cat kitty
harness guil cat I am fine
free CS where are we going the
bay uh according to this map I think the
quest Master should be right over here
that sure looks like a a board that sure
looks like one I think this is the
board that's a good board nice
board let's see look pretty empty oh you
must be one of the heroes then you
master told me about you I to here is
the
quest JS and
requests oh you
from what the heck Hello Intruders
Intruders Intruders
[Music]
Intruders kind of people are
people they're not oh wait there's a
pool down oh shoot oh my God your sword
is way bigger than mine know are you
honestly that's really think
to if it's for the sake of improving our
relationship know I've never I've never
felt special in my entire life wait you
think I don't want you to feel special
you think I want you to feel like a
loser I mean I I I've awoken only an
hour ago I don't really remember what
what I feel and how I feel but I mean
same
here you
understand I
do we're more alike than you think the B
perhaps we're not so different after all
perhaps hey are you what team are you
perhaps we
are oh hello there we part of the a
where the heck did you get a horse what
I I don't know I just have to
you must have stolen it where do you
check the where do you check the quest
it don't burn my horse you're going to
kill it horse me horse meat creature
horse me yeah yeah Taco
Bell it's
aall wait we got to the quest board
first we're
winning where is the side quest we need
to go to tired of my now
hey this looks
like
matal The
Apprentice next Quest the side quest and
then speak to the quest wait
what Master what is our side
quest
click toate but I hope you have the time
for some CI
Runnings
can quest
Quest the Smithy we got to find the
Smithy and get the stuffies together
I've got the map we can go to the smiy
let's go let's
go
Scarlet he W the
oranges oranges out the
oranges we are going on a quest do you
care to join us I shall join you of
course we are join us except now I'm
lost I don't know where they they left
us we'll catch up with them yeah may may
I actually uh receive one of your
remaining breads you may because I have
more than you thank you I have zero at
this point wait I can't give it to you
oh we may trade oh how do I
accept like this yes like so okay one
one bread for you did you did you get it
you are you are so kind uh oh wait no
this here we go I bring it wait I can't
what I can't I can't put it in your
box
maybe I must
exchange oh wait H lock in trade we got
to uh click the r
thing in the at the bottom I need wait
you one more time stand still do not
move I take you my
party
huh below the golden icon the red icon
yeah you missing the bread
yipp yipp thank
you
I are we going let's
go we can go with the horse
too oh you wait what the heck how'd you
get the horsey you right the egges come
from eggs they come from the
eggs oh my gosh oh we're so
fast oh we're so fast get up gety up get
up get up gety up get up get up get up
get up Apprentice the blacksmith is that
The Apprentice oh we go it's up there oh
I see oh my gosh wait hold up what
where'd she go you can get off with
shift oh okay shift oh you're killing
your horse you're killing your horse oh
my God
horse hello cuz
I it's over here we're in the wrong
house oh I don't think we can get it why
do you get the sh sh sh you shift okay I
shift all right it's this way how did
you disappear you disappeared into the
house I was just it's just the power is
St it
makes gave me endless speed is it an
air in air it's just that's a chef I
don't think he's
there the problem I think it's up there
what's the problem yeah it's over here
so this is the smithing but I don't know
what materials we're supposed to have
materials needed I think he's yeah we
should ask him we need 10 oogs bunch of
trees we can
oh okay okay it's a good thing we have
axes
girls oh let's us go trees how far do
you think is far is this far I know how
far is that right here can we take
this can we take these trees I I don't
think so I don't I don't I don't think
so not maybe we can go a little bit like
further out yeah yeah yeah yeah further
the horse like outside outside what did
you say your name was
Cleopatra Eisenhower D
Vinci the great the third okay let's
go oh they fo I shall remember it this
time I believe in
you I'm trusting you I'm trusting you
the bay this is your chance to prove
that you're not
weird these trees look like they won't
be
missed
right
right but I don't think these are oak oh
those ones are
[Music]
oak I don't think this is out
enough loock broken there they are but
not okay this is not out enough yeah
this is not considered outside this is
not out it responds right away why are
these trees here then F here who even
wants
these yeah these are not retrievable
trees maybe we have to
go even further this
is a
maybe outside the walls
perhaps are these different horses every
time outside maybe can they go
upstairs can we
[Music]
go I I was told that I did not accept
the quest actually you didn't accept the
quest
is there fall damage yeah there is fall
damage
uh-oh those must be the trees right
maybe I need help what's wrong what's
wrong where are you I'm in a dangerous
situation oh my goodness here how did
she do that I might die no don't die I
I'll try to go step by step yeah yeah
yeah I will parkour parkour
I've just realized I've been muted in
the game this entire I've been muted
this entire time oh my gosh we've been a
mute this entire time then what voices
did I hear before oh my goodness where
did she respond I don't know perhaps
there's another staircase closer to
where these trees are and maybe there's
an exit I'm assuming these are the
trees how do we leave hold
on I'll figure it
out I'm on the
missions going jump on the roof or maybe
not I'm trying to find another staircase
see if like it can go down to a gate or
[Music]
something maybe not maybe we should go
back they are so fast what the
heck is there one around here I don't
think so not let's go back to the
staircase and let's just go go we should
get
where is she where did she respa I I
think she respawn in the
guild let's see I think so this is that
was really the only
staircase there was no other
staircase whoever designed this wall
didn't think far ahead in
in in efficiency let's see look this is
this this looks like the gate we oh go
to another location wait where are
[Music]
they
comrades comrades comrades comrades is
it time for me to go be a main
character
comrads I use this is this the gate yeah
there's a gate
here where is the Lady of the oranges
where the heck is what the heck hello oh
where did we are we are
scattered cat you go here is this the
gate oh
yes oh my goodness we oh my gosh and
there's more people here ignore them
pretend you don't see them ignore
them ignore them Revelation I got him
it's a
ooh the tree has consumed me
did I not get anything for
that oh that's silly sir
ma'am I will take this I will take works
it
works do we need 10 each do you think
the Smithy seems a little bit desperate
for wood I you know what just in case we
can do ten we can go a bit overboard
and that's way we we can also sabotage
the other
people or is it respawning does it
respawn yeah oh never mind no
sabotage I'm going to use
my um I've got eight I've got 10 already
do I have all the what I mean there's so
many
speeds she she Tru really stuck to her
word she she went and she used her
horse I'll get these
wait this isn't Oak never mind that's
not Oak I made a mistake it's not Oak um
we we've gone outside the game wait are
you hearing the voices of our
kitty no wait is it through the radio ah
still be dum how do you use the radio we
outside hold on we are defeating oh
[Music]
owie stop it you should be able to
teleport outside the city Gates you in
my are they talking to them oh I got
money oh they like
creepers was a
creeper
ta we need more
wood I got all right here we
go don't worry
I'll protect you dang
it
owie raw in the
N it's making very sad noises I don't
like
that not a fan I want to hear something
funny
honestly ooh
Deary do you think we get extra for
defeating you don't we get coins do we
extra coin
how many how many blocks do you have I'm
ready to go back to the smithing and get
another side quest we need more money I
have 10 but don't we need like what if
we need 40 though why do we need 40 if
um we need 10 each well the the other
two are coming to to get to get to get
their wood anyway but we could just get
the wood for
them you would do that three for someone
else well overall it's for me oh speeds
up the
process You' be wrong about that I would
like to come make it to your make make
it known that I am protecting
you thank you the
B you're welcome
three see the be
so yes what is it do you think that if
circumstances were different we could be
friends
cuz I
don't honestly I was about to say
something
heartwarming
[Music]
but what what p phone
call and I scared the bashel the out of
me no one's calling
me yeah three maybe if you were a bit
nicer to people maybe call you I'm nice
to what do you want kitty cat where are
you
[Music]
hello that's this is so sad they wait
you get money from them you say
something about a dog that changes
everything huh oh never mind they give
you
money F kidy you made me lose 10 years
of my non-existent life
hello everybody absolutely no reason
hello I am back from the dead living
again welcome back we have enough wood
we can have a we can leave now oh I
don't have enough wood it's okay I have
wood I have 30 you want to trade once
again I can do
this yippe hold on yipp
yippe take it wonderful would you like
would so generous I don't know how to
how do we
trade y accept yeah how do I accept
press T then then click on
accept oh yeah okay done okay marvous
let's go back and get that coin oops
oops Co we finished the quest yeah there
you go take it thank
you how do I get it thank you click C
the red the red block oh I think okay
yeah thank
you wait actually I haven't got it oh
you should have I'm going to oh no no no
he's on the chest yeah
oh all right let's get out of
here let's go wait ladies should we
should we create a
party is a party leader right now she
would have to invite you oh okay can't
invite me to the party please I invite
tree as well there you go hey hey hey
hey hey hey hey no a all right let's go
back oh is that why we can't hear
anybody
elsea oh wait she can hear me never
mind what are you looking at let's get
out of here let's get out of here let's
let's get out of here
H yes yes okay all right we made it we
made it we got back to
the let's ride boy I mean
girls
yeah
C Sound of the Hooves click CL click CL
click
[Music]
CL made it no you got to buy things
there's people wait there's people
there's people I don't know in here
there's people I don't know I don't know
people um I don't I'm not
comfortable I feel very unsafe right now
I I don't feel comfortable with these
people I do not know who they are
there's major stranger danger here
should we should we should we come back
another time I don't but we have to be
the bestu ourselves be the best making
more aliens and more friends can they
hear us Co we might not us hear us the B
farted the B
farted I don't think they can hear us
morning
coming how do I make a
pickaxe one you have toy bring the
material
can mine was made immediately do you
have the required
materials wooden
pickaxe wait what see my master where
where's the
master completed we can go to the quest
Master where's the master especially if
you need coin do I have with
them where's the
master she gave you oak logs right this
the master I think they're in the Box
still right yeah I open it
okay failed to purchase you do not have
the required mat what we got to make
planks and sticks okay I made okay we
need PL I have planks and we need sticks
all right I thought I planks and sticks
planks and sticks I forgot how to make
planks
I remember how to make
flanks
[Music]
flanks and
sticks my nose is so what would we have
to do now complete give me what we do
now that's the way that cost
money
great completed the log thank you so
much see my M over there you the
materi cobone
cobone to many people are speaking to
him
[Music]
at wait is this all of our money am I am
I using all of our money okay I do not
think so my money has not decreased I
think that's your money okay I'm rich
your how much money do you have three c
a wooden picka now I have 93 points I'm
richer
[Music]
than3 well I'm richer in a life
experience ha
ha you just brag about being old three
it's not really no that's not what that
means that's so shallow that is so
shallow you what you think you think
just cuz someone's older or younger they
don't live that's shallow the B
shallow in my ear but you know three C
stone is here I'm three I'm just
sometimes I
wonder what are we suppos materials need
it is it is a nightly time where many
danger awaits Us in the outside Fields
what is the what is our current uh Quest
here Cobblestone oh
tan tan
Cobblestone Cobblestone do all of us I
still don't understand do we all need to
Cobblestone okay all right got take
cobone us needs like I don't know how
many 10 10 Cobblestone 10 Cobblestone
okay okay oh that makes oh I'm sorry
that makes sense because then we can
upgrade our tools I'm predicting the
next the next thing that's going to
happen so every time if we get if they
ask for ter we collect 20 you know
that's the what you know is always about
about get to think ahead you got to
think ahead
plan for the future I think you're very
smart to
B thank you three was that a genuine
compliment coming from you it was not
I'm I'm going to get extra extra CS I
really don't think we're going to get a
long three if we
don't I think we will stop fighting you
I I think we got a slowburn going
on it's morning
morning
righty I've got enough I'm ready to go
back are you ready to ready I'm ready
I'm ready I'm ready how much how much
you need why just need 10
right
yeah
[Music]
okay watch out watch out watch out watch
out watch out watch out watch out wait
step out of the way watch out watch out
watch out watch out watch out it was
already
broken above your head but you aren't my
[Music]
friendsa please don't get us in trouble
with other guils oh hello there you are
you're my friend yay where you
going what you say what you say what you
say what you say what you say what you
say what you say what you
say something something def you must one
those legendary horse girls we're doing
things you you'll be hearing from my
lawyer for
that I don't think that's a real horse
anyway I am no longer rich I am no
longer Rich all right I have 21 coin I'm
poor what what do they
want bless you bless you thank you what
now do I have to craft anything what
supposed to do now what are we supposed
to we have to go back to the uh maybe
the the
quest okay maybe what kind of armor
would suit you best Quest Master let's a
quest Master Quest Master Quest master
master of the
quest it's somewhere you know what I am
I'm Master of the
pastor past no
pasture is here hello can you guys hear
me we
did oh thank God hello who the heck are
you I have no idea who are you why are
there so many cute girls around me all
of a sudden are you in me lady oh I I
don't know what I'm doing you sound like
someone I want to get my nails done
with you're right true I haven't gotten
my nails done in ages my name is Iris
and I don't know anything else besides
that name oh Iris you sound so helpless
and
[Laughter]
weak honestly it makes do you know what
cup you're
in a cup what do you mean cup I got a
new Quest what what quest what do you
mean cup what group are you in my dear I
I seem to be in The Blue Team oh that is
the seruan cup that's what I was asking
oh goodness all righty another one I
don't gold I don't remember the names of
the other team The Blue Team only ours
matters number three I haven't said it
do we have what have I done to these
people I don't
understand you know perhaps you should
reflect on yourself it might be a you
problem hey did you not get a quest that
build something you're asking the right
questions what have you done what have
you done everyone think I've done I
don't want to know what I've done we all
heroes but I'm the biggest hero I hope
we here suppos to be the special one The
One and Only They said that to
me were talking to you come to post jobs
and
[Music]
requests well best of I'm so rich
have B I mean the
bay
the um no I got the same question though
okay I'm so rich can I sec I see to
finish the quest I don't know if we're
close enough for sure
TI I'm only mean to you because I'm
insecure
three I have a lot of toxic masculinity
that I'm
just suppressing wait no I don't
know
[Music]
three I am s can you tell me what what
I'm supposed to do with my
Cobblestone can you give me some of your
money I don't think I can give you have
you gone and and gotten your Cobblestone
tools yet no I didn't know that was an
option oh go go back and talk to the I
I'll come with you it's going to be okay
honestly I knew that was something I
need I need the
stone I have stone I I honestly it
wasn't me oh okay that makes me it's
it's also it's kind of both like it can
be two things at
once do you want me to help you on not
three honestly Mia this isn't the right
place this is this is definitely not the
right place um I I don't I think we just
barged into a family eating dinner wait
why did I join our
party I don't know Iris you're not
enough
[Music]
do you think these two are
happy honestly they seem pretty
happy you know the king talked about
some great Calamity but these people
seem to be living in peace I know this
is a really nice nice neighborhood I
know right all right um do you know
where the blacksmith is cuz it's no
longer on my map um no I think we're
just going to have to go into a bunch of
different
houses I don't think this that's a
it all right can you pull out your map
please let's let's stock this person she
might know I think oh you were wrong
this isn't where you're supposed to be
wait I'm just
kidding oh hi what's
up oh I think it's that house three is
that one I think it's that
one let's go it might be
this did we just steal a party member by
accident we might we might have it's
okay we were this one we were lacking
anyway I think everybody else had five
we were the only ones with
four all so talk to you got it right
this time good job are you a
shopkeeper oh I can upgrade my weapon
how come I can't upgrade it won't let me
upgrade have you talked to talk to the
blacksmith first The Apprentice or the
blacksmith Sher apprentice apprentice
apprentice hello great you brought the
cop brought the call if you talk to my
real okay wait what wait I missed it huh
it's still not working what did he say
shoot babe what did he say he said I
could upgrade but I can't really like
fting maybe I don't have enough sticks
oh do you have yeah do you have money
and sticks how much money do I need 50 I
have 90
okay do you have
sticks oh wait I got it I had a I had a
fresh
Shi what do I want I want a better sword
stone sword wait it's 100 coins oh but I
have 100 coins a stone pickax but I can
only
get I have a
sword I'm going to go outside and make a
phone call three I'll be standing right
there all right I'll be coming with you
okay
a hideous hair you
have my
go what what what wait that's not my
name
Kitty did we just steal another party
member where is
she why is there another party member in
our party are we clausing Guild Wars I'm
so proud of you oh she hung up on me all
righty um how'd you call her uh you you
have a radio oh private call I see okay
okay um Iris why did you hang up on
me
peasants the heck you call me peasants
oh my goodness I'm not three I'm not
talking to you I'm talking to kitty cat
I'm talking to
Irish yes oh oh oh oh that's what the
that was m i mean whoever you are brown
brown cute cute brown owl the name is
Cleopatra Eisen Howard D Vinci the great
theii are you on our team now what's
going on I have no
idea I have no idea cute brown
owl okay my name is Iris and I'm
curently I'm curently yeah nice to meet
you what is your name
are you talking to me no I'm talking to
someone else I'm going to hang up now
give me
out what' she say I don't know she she
like said things but they aren't very
helpful oh I see all right well now that
you have your Cobblestone we can go back
to the Gil master and you can get your
coin and we can be rich together three
okay yeah I still have I still have a
lot of
cobblestone that's all right we'll need
it later maybe crave the coin I mean I
only have 43 coins now because I spent
them on the sword I got a cool sword and
I I don't want this but I have
anyway I have a good sword and I have a
pickaxe you got a good sword that's
great I'm so happy for you three
honestly uh you know seeing you like
this makes me like you just a tiny bit
more you like me here you like
this well that doesn't work wait hold on
TR request for
what come find
out all this I
bet you accept you you click on accept
yeah I want to fight in the dungeon with
you guys see how good you
are did you pick up another
Quest you can only have one after to
trade Okay click on click accept
[Music]
I was going to pick it up after visiting
the
shop from him why don't we
the now click on the red
block I'm a little confused because it
just gave me the option of getting
another Quest un oh the quest Master why
do you have a raw pork chop because I
killed a
pig I'm so proud of you go talk to the
quest leader now
[Music]
okay
hello
hello hello there
fuzzy up in the and in the oh fussy
that's
500 sounds like me FY no one said hi
back moved away from me
have you got the 500
three what have you got 500 500 what 500
what
coins yeah why all right now we can go
buy stuff oh wait I'm just kidding I
don't I thought that was a trick
question what I need to go to the I need
to give my where who do I give my
Cobblestone to him no one just talk to
him
okay hail hero I see we you you've gone
and finished the quest our citizens are
in your depth I know you get the grave
duty of fighting the Calamity but I hope
you stopped by the quest Bo from the
time time to the com if you for time you
have look around
[Music]
town nice nice I got the coin
B let's go crazy yeah
woo oh look who it
is oh hello hello sweet little lady
hello there hello my name is Iris Iris
hello there hello Iris hello what may I
call you
too my name is the bay I'm the B I am
Cleopatra Eisenhower divin she the great
thei oh well that's a very very you can
call her three
three you can't you you can't do that
but what am I to do about
it you're right I'll I'll just call you
three and there's nothing you could call
me mumi or something like oh that came
randomly where' that come from I think
it means no name so I'd rather you just
call me that instead of a number no name
I thought you had a name I thought you
had a really long name I do but you guys
are acting like I
don't oh not a h
okay I'll call you I'll call you
mooms okay just to shorten it you know
we need even shorter than
that just to shorten it all right oh my
gosh wait what are those called I feel
like I want to know you as three so I'm
going to call you three for now what
that's fine what are you have the Naruto
thingies they're not Naruto thingies
what are nar I was Naruto no no they're
not shurik I mean I don't even know what
you're talking about I don't know what
shurikens are no they're they're Stu STS
they're they're the power of the of my
angel devil uh they're my halo it's my
it's a part of my halo what Halo what
Halo did did you understand that I don't
understand I don't understand she's I
think she might be the town Looney or
something I have no clue what she's
saying see I thought she was like the
cute sweet little weak girl that you you
were going to do on but no she's just
kind of weird she's like why they why am
I being
wait am I just supposed to admit that
these are shuriken or something is that
what I'm supposed to do I mean what do
you mean Halo you think you're an angel
ha honest you just got to tell the truth
we value honesty in this group well do
you think sure can't do this what I mean
honestly yeah yeah I feel like they
totally could do that what else I could
totally see that happening in Naruto
what what else did they do Nar what is
Naruto what do you exactly what it
sounds like what does I don't know what
it sounds
like the first thing that com your head
your this is my Revelation my Revelation
isn't
farting yourness no
no would never oh my gosh wait she's
from that one movie she's from that one
movie where they sing and make dinner
for the pretty girl hey Jan yes I
thought you were about to say do you
know John Cena I'm sorry I'm who John C
exactly what it sounds like is he around
here I can't see him I John C who is
Jonathan John Cena Jonathan Jonathan is
to kill the
king Jonathan Jonathan inside that that
Jonathan is or the other
Jonathan we have to get
your are you going to make him gathan we
we have
swor no it's no it's Jonathan a I know
but if you kill him he'll be gathan but
your highness oh yes yes be gathan I put
my my name on the line us am a coin have
nothing to do with Amber you on the
Amber team are you of Amber she's of
Amber I'm not she
is what's wrong with them misunder
understanding you
what are you talking about I'm in your
team I'm in your party so you are on our
team on our team you shut huh huh I mean
you you shut your humble
mouth what did you just almost say to me
I did not say anything I thought you
supposed to be a part of the empathy
team huh you too you guys have any fire
do not yeah I I don't even they they
they're the ones who reached out a
helping hand you're supposed to refuse
it man you're aan cop oh was know you
guys okay I appreciate it I appreciate
the we should we should we should remove
ourselves from this you
me I'm not I'm not of the Amber we want
to go crazy oh yeah we have money to
blow let's go yeah let's go before they
ask any more questions I don't want to
answer does anyone want does anyone want
me to stay in their party or or does
nobody wants you except
[Music]
us let's
go all right I think the shop should
just be around
shop shop oh thank you for saving this
town welcome to my humble little
[Music]
shop what can we get what can we all
right all right just give give me the
gun give me the gun give me the gun give
me him I'm a free deer I didn't ask for
wait you think I'm a free what the heck
wait why do we have to talk to a kid I
just want the goods assuming we don't
have money to
spend the way we're dressed I'm sure
funny yeah okay this is a little too
much a little too much uh Small Talk are
you looking for the I see on
what the he is ARA I just want to buy
stuff see
child now and then I'll do if you have
some time yet why not visit the GU what
the heck he's just he's there what do
you he has nothing he's just he's just
maybe the child has something for us get
crazy buy the child you think we could
buy the
child you want a child can we buy the
child I mean I don't know I don't know
what kind of world this
[Music]
is oh dear what's going
on the gardens oh the
child keep an eye on scway birds and
stuff goly you're one of the heroes boy
this is my lucky day this
[Music]
is building
P you when you Heroes can build whatever
you like to build a scary birds what the
heck why would you do that build a
gardening secret is a place called The
Pit mom say but I you can play a really
fun game there you're here I've been
that you maybe you can check it out tell
me when
it's building or the pit can I tell you
a secret did you know there's a place in
town called the pit is that where Amber
coin people go pit the P AR is so far
away
let I'm going to follow you oh
[Music]
okay where's kiaha of the orange
and where are they oh wait it's over
[Music]
here this ir's left but she's still
there feel like I belong yes you belong
here now yay you'll never belong
anywhere
y wait where'd she
[Music]
go
hi oh sh too fast for me too
[Music]
fast
see oh excuse you lucky lady lucky lady
I've got a game for you your new face
stop stop it stop it you're one of them
arrows what saved the town aren't you I
want to get rich I getting rich I want
to get rich I want to get rich I promise
there's nothing Shady see how I run with
the Jade sword before I join the Amber
coin with the Gil Master took us out to
UNT some stains and T us how to work as
a team just point yourself at your mate
and right click and then you can select
where to invite your oh
what
huh he's just teaching us how to trade
and Jo parties realiz we're way ahead
we're we're so far ahead can you keep
keep up with the program pit Dorman
please ever feeling too l or too heavy
maybe come down here to the pit and play
around or two and if you ever see some
por that s walking out of your penis
don't worry about it that won't happen
to you a you lucky oh is this
gambling it is there's a gambling thing
in here please meet him at the jadea
Guild Hall all right where's the Jade
old Guild Hall oh goodness it's really
having us going around in circles a't it
is it is it is it oh she
[Music]
off where the
hecky where I supposed to
go this way the
verish that where I'm going the the
book why am I by myself
again around
here
no maybe I should call her should I call
her is it in here or is it not in
there
he
baby I think I think I think it's here
I'm not sure G is it here is it oh
there's the members where's the king oh
there he
is I mean not the king the Guild Master
this one I see you returned Brave hero I
hope you familiarized yourself with the
town and learned about venturing we all
lament what has befallen the lands that
s our kingdom the clamity in stains it
has born and turn most of the world into
a wasteland you must be shaken to
suddenly find yourselves in another
world but I pray you will Aid us in our
fight I pr is a way for you to forain
your powers of
Revelation for that end I have just
received word from one of our Scouts
regarding a possible lead I'll
investigating the Calamity near the pl
or comrades ched Upon A mysterious
ancient whatever they observed from the
r and light to the the Revelation which
we used to rep the staying King
station the for
fation I
ask to go for
with exit the Town Gate head to the
plane and speak to H of the chain
sword all right I feel like we're speed
running this eai adventure are we a lot
of bread where did I get
this say
I'm why do we have so much bread I'm
going to
call
somebody I'm going to call see I'm going
to let the other player is in a call she
send me the
voicemail all right speed run it is all
right we go to a what do we have to do
go to a we go out outside we go okay we
go outside all right outside the
gate how where where uh is it this way
what the heck where'd you go where'd you
go where'd you go where'd you
go is it that thing the purple thing in
the
corner
[Music]
oh
day you think I remember where the gate
is where'd you go I'm here
where I hear your voice cuz I'm calling
you long
distance um I don't know I'm back at the
I I can go back to the guild the Amber
coin
Guild where the heck is that I don't
know can you uh where are you I'm in
front of where we just were together oh
okay
oh no oh I've reached the gate okay hold
on where are you we are supposed to go
to the gate so it's over yeah yeah yeah
yeah
yeah okay so it's along here somewhere
okay oh oh oh there you are there you
are hello hello the gate is over here so
we're going back to the gate owie we're
going back to the gate back to the gate
okay here we go all right all right
all right all right all
right b b man get out of here get out of
here look A Lost
Child we will help
[Music]
you uh you're
welcome that's the last time I'm helping
anyone right where the heck is my
validation absolutely ridiculous all
right head to the planes is it the right
is this the right oh I just realized
we're still on a call together oh even
though do we get charged by the minute I
[Music]
wonder just stay on call all the time
somebody's hurting you oh no I hurt them
back wait my power is so weak that I
can't even kill a
cow I think mine is I'm getting money
I'm getting money I'm getting money I'm
getting money I'm getting money I'm
getting that's not very much money
[Music]
well wa what's our Quest
again we got to go speak to H of the jam
sword oh yes okay
okay okay we both got money I think if
we work together we get more money oh
I up upop up here okay let's go okay oh
I don't know where I am burdened with is
that
gold Wait no that's art that's three we
got we got three
[Music]
iron want some I
do nice nice to
have can use it later all right all
right we get all right well we've
reached the fork in the row three I
don't know what to do here we go left we
go right uh we go this way right this
way I
think I I
think we really we're going all the way
out here really oh we have to we're
going to but we can get stuff in the
water it's
okay the people kitty cat what the heck
what the heck we found you why didn't
you answer your phone I was so worried
cuz we're on the
phone why you guys have been
the because sometimes we're not next to
each
other I tried calling you I love how we
we thought like all righty we got to
talk to you our initial for determined
that the portal has been yet to be
sealed there's no way to enter the ruins
where at last when
I I'm remember part hearing a strange
voice but we don't know what to I don't
know why the St the way anyway I was
saying um I was done with the quest it
appeared on the
bottom
the have you guys completed the quest
guys we're going to go kill people we're
going to go kill people
now well they're not people but we're
going going to kill I was muted by
mistake it's okay have you completed the
quest yeah we we're doing the one with K
now and then we go to the dungeon are we
going to go together yeah we got to kill
stuff
[Applause]
[Music]
too kill kill you I'm
hungry I didn't know the private
call so that that counts as one right
doesn't keep do we have to count
ourselves I think so ah I killed one I
am done with
it I kill
more please
respawn I need enemies over
here what the heck you
[Music]
cheated these are the thingies right I
don't know squid hurts squid hurts squid
hurts okay we I can make a party co one
sec I think I think you guys may need to
accept I'm I'm coing you
guys I'm not getting any
call
[Music]
weird I'm just going to kill as many as
I
can I certainly have killed 10 by now
[Music]
ooh I didn't even hit this
one thank you for the
[Music]
help I don't think I killed 10 yet
n get him I need one
more no it's mine
it's it's ours ours kill
kill dang it dang it yeah yeah
seems
um more do
[Music]
I got flowers do you get money for those
got 10 I
don't slow
hey this I I have
pride I did
it the reason the reason was just
because um like I probably killed way
more than 10 but like you participated
in some of the kills so that made it
like your kill and not my kill
a didn't count together weird oh my gosh
no my vision I see it know perhaps this
K is what will open the portal into the
ruins you want to take it with you hero
we shall secure the surroundings and you
may proceed undisturbed the secrets of
the ruins
await oh is this the dungeon we're
dungeoning now yeah D dungeon Time
Dungeon time the quest finished yeah
let's go
okay you you have you all proceeded in
the quest right yeah yeah just a double
check it says investigate the underworld
dungeon right yeah okay good we can go
then let's
go okay
ow let's go oh it's actually right there
huh
yeah battle cries
Yi no
okay let's go time to fight time to
fight are we ready I guess yeah let's go
we're ready we're ready
Amber
[Music]
oopsie jumpy
jump Jon ready yeah I'm ready wait oh
wait enter oh ready ready yeah I'm ready
yeah are we clicking ready I clicked
ready I'm I'm click I clicked ready okay
standing by to enter dungeon okay oh
enter dungeon no players standing by
what what do we just click enter
now it says no player standby it says no
player standing by
though I think could it be uh L can you
like in your party settings cuz you're
the party leader can you kick wait wait
wait wait
wait wait click out and then go back in
cuz then it says that I'm waiting now oh
wait wait
wait wait I click
[Music]
what do you see it now wait how do I how
do I get
back how do you know how do you do that
ready noing again well well I just walk
back and then walk closer to it
huh he says no player standing by um
wait do you want to disband the poty is
it CU iris is in it I think it's because
iris is in it so SP and we can remake
the poty
Irish
Irish how do just B the party now oh
here right
click and
then
uh invite fail wait you k away from the
party yeah oh oh I see I see I see I see
I see I'm out I got kicked out okay now
I'm out as well all right let's make a
new party yeah your
party back you guys yeah where I see
your say l and m think B need invite yep
I'm in okay you're in wait hold
on the party or ready to oh what I'm in
the part
okay we wait wait is this one out of one
is that okay
okay ready I'm ready okay ready oh now
now it's working now it's working yeah
I'm ready too okay ready ready M press
ready press ready ready yeah it looks
like you didn't
press hello
[Music]
M dang
it me what happened three talk to me it
appears that I did not accept the party
invite and I entered the dungeon by
myself
ah she's entered the
dungeon okay we got to enter too all
right we're entering all right but you
may not you may not be with
[Music]
me oh hold on hold on hold on can you
not exit the dungeon I don't think
so maybe if I kill
myself oh I'm I'm calling her I'm
calling her should I kill myself
uh maybe do you respawn back at the
dungeon I lose my stuff I don't
[Music]
[Applause]
know hold
on
huh what's
[Music]
here
uhoh uh
uh-oh maybe I should leave the
game I'm going to leave there's
footsteps I'm going to they're m i I'll
be right back all
[Music]
right ta oops yes she
is nice to see you once again hello
mistake had been made missed you yeah
miss you very much I miss all of you too
am I in the party now about this you
always in a party you need to be ready I
was ready I was not right now but hold
on hold
on don't click the sword I'm ready we go
y
ready oh my gosh I'm not alone this
time all right guys I don't ask why but
go here to this door the
Underworld the domain of boundless
oppressive Darkness as fear it is
unavoidable it holds the final resting
place for every creature that walks the
Earth yes even in this realm of the Dead
those are who live and call it home oh
my this feels like it was written by the
hands of death oh my goodness what we
going to do he must
orange
juice orange juice ooh uh I don't think
that's orange juice um which way we
supposed to go maybe we go this
way maybe this is not the kind of fire
you like there's a thing over here I
like any kind of fire you can do it
there's a
crystal hard to reach oh there's a whole
castle over there oh dang I don't know
how do we get to this
fly have you tried flying I have not
tried flying can we
fly I usually can but it seems now I've
been restricted maybe we have to go a
different way
yeah but this all looks like
Islands
parkour parkour oh oh there's one over
here over here over here parkour parkour
oh I see ah you teleport from Stone to
Stone
okay probably we lost the
others that's okay we're too good new
checkpoint unlocked oh checkpoint if we
die we spawn here I think
so very nice very convenient let's go
this way okay parkour parkour parkour no
parkour do sometimes dream about
flying three where are you someone's
calling me sorry it's the voice we're
here we're over here we're over here
really want to where's over here you see
them okay okay okay over
here follow your heart over here over
here is always a good way to let people
know where you are
exactly over here let's get ahead of
them let's get ahead of
them where's the next checkpoint
[Music]
there we go they're catching
us
nice nice nice okay but from here
honestly I'm not sure I think that it's
through
here are we just exploring he if we
brought our own blocks I wonder can we
place them all we can
try I have no we can't are we just are
was just walking around I think it's
this way cuz there's a checkpoint up
here
oh yeah oh yeah there's something here
hello
locked yes I I'm not sure where we're
supposed to go from here perhaps towards
that castle oh that would be that would
be a marvelous
idea hope I don't
die
okay oh yeah
jump
here Dam too yeah careful
careful be careful oh I messed up I
pressed the wrong
[Music]
buttony
Daisy I pressed shift instead of
control I was out of
control here I come
[Music]
I was so worried that I have lost you
before I heard the answer to the dream
question the dream what was the dream
question if you ever uh dream about
flying I don't I wish I did don't I
don't maybe try flapping your arms when
you as I fall asleep yeah May okay I'll
try
thata dream dream
[Music]
dream dream dream dream dream dream
dream dream dream dream I forgot how
that song goes that sounds that sounds
like a song I should release dream dream
dream dream dream dream that's not how
it does no someone from the Lava Girl
Shark Boy movie no checkpoint oopsie oop
oops oops you been checked not again no
it was a shortcut look shortcut let's go
let's go to the castle okay let's go
over here
Castle
[Music]
time can you girls be
careful I don't know which way I think
we go this way we go around that
one we go up maybe oh know oh goodness
um yes and then you run you a run yeah
let's go
okay I'm right all right
do up up up up
up
up up
down up up
up down up down up up up up up up up up
up up up up up up
up three we did it they did it they
should just kill themselves so they can
come up here that's the Strat speedrun
Strat wait is it is it is it group is it
is a group checkpoint yeah oh it's all
right they're there I see them they can
do it you can do it
look at them go look at them go she
could not do it it's all right but look
look she'll here behind us
here yeah you figured out the strap good
job it's a group it's a group checkpoint
let's
go just die just down
die jump I don't think she can hear us
hold on let me call her real quick
you can also try Pro just jump just jump
into the lava she hear me through your
phone jump into the
lava jump did
it jump further
yeah there we go
hooray are we ready the orange juice
after all right I'm ready let's go let's
go we
oh
[Music]
oh let's go wow wow oh wait I just
realized weren't we told to go and like
not just our group in dungeons weren't
we told to go with like two groups um I
don't remember they only said like
there's a maximum how many groups can be
in D at the same time oh okay yeah we
don't need anybody else just the four of
I'm still on Co I'm
[Music]
sorry of the
orange yes
[Music]
nice nice the corners check the corners
are we're doing
go nice next time I have's stick to each
other because we're going to have in
this dungeon
yeah wait what is this we found
something what checkpoint oh I got a
triangle
some I got a triangle I can take it well
why how did you take it you filled it up
or I I think we I think the zombies are
going to dropped those we got to kill
okay so we need to find a star and a
circle oh I found the circle I found the
circle what the heck stop it stop it I
got the star too they immediately
brought it to us okay need a circle now
I'm trying to how do I put the circle in
how do I put the circle in right click y
let go we we have several
circles
[Music]
yeah remember to
eat remember to eat everybody
friend
wow what does this
say another life expired leaving behind
a tiny flickering light a soul repres
presing both a legacy and an ending
I read for us read for us the veiled
figure cradled it in her hands and with
a hint of melancholy she whispered is
this the right thing to do it's if you
need to ask it's never the right thing
to do
okay that that a crazy thing to
say amber kind Amber kind Amber kind
Amber coin Amber
coin wo there's so many stairs I don't I
don't like there so many why are there
so many stairs I know my foot
owie what is this what's this is this a
a puzzle pu rub Cube time I'm going to
be absolutely useless all righty um one
two what what Chang is it I don't know I
just touching it how what are you are
you right clicking it oh okay okay well
uh maybe each each person takes charge
of one side or so yeah wait I was
supposed to put all the lights onto onto
the front face
maybe I think you just want the whole
thing to light up no yeah I think all of
them have to light up I see I I love
these kind of riddles wait these kind of
riddles yeah I hate him too is this okay
hey oh oh wait mine was full for it's a
each each side affects the other side
like it's not just one face ah I see um
wait hold
on that's a we should just observe for a
evit I'm not sure if this might not
actually be the to stop every guilt from
proceeding it's just a
distraction is a distraction that would
be funny I really have to go to an idol
meeting it's just not this is probably
not the best time
maybe try to figure out one
side I think I can't change anything
anymore huh did I use up my
tries okay
[Music]
oh I can't do
anything it seems like a good time is it
a good time I do need to okay I'm going
to go to an idle meeting and let you
guys figure this one okay I'll be right
back
[Music]
I I can't oh oh I F I F I F sorry I just
got a little bit
[Music]
frustrated light I don't understand the
the way they
changeed I think it's like it's
um okay so it's
two I'm just going to keep pressing
until something works oh my goodness oh
wait I think I think I understand can
someone go to the other side and follow
my instruction yes okay uh up on the top
top top top left click on the top
left okay nothing happen no it's the
adjacent ones it's the ones next to each
other that turn on and off okay I got it
oh I I was able to cck it before what
like maybe it's better like if two
people just do that CU maybe like we can
I'm not sure oh I have also lost the
ability R you on your
run
no God
okay are you run
you okay I I'll try I'll try let let me
do that
[Music]
[Applause]
press too many
times I pressed it too many
[Music]
times you are of the
orange of the
orange no
I don't understand based on what they
they I'm trying to I I I try to regain
oh no it still doesn't
work still can't press it I I am trying
you're doing great I am
[Music]
trying okay this
one you have any kind kind of strategy L
up no I'm just like trying to understand
the pattern that's how I would do it
honestly
so if you have any suggestion you're
doing
great they can't use it anymore either
do we have to make just one
[Music]
line okay one side is light oh nice
I hope it stays like that I hope it
stays like
that looking good though looking good
looking
good I know if it's
changes oh left side is still safe and
full okay okay let's what's going
on we're still at it and La is the only
one able to press things what oh yeah I
know you want to I can press things the
way they are are on the left side we've
got one face down we just need the other
two to
go three I feel like just
indiscriminately pressing them without
communicating is not going be work what
do you mean amazing oh oh it's
working it's
working it's working what's that this is
just like one come on come on Kitty one
of
them doing great
[Music]
Kitty I'm trying to
understand oh no we've lost the side
no wait it's it's changing on itself oh
no I think I think three is also
pressing oh it's my bad my bad
what do you want me to
do I don't know I I feel like everybody
working on one side maybe doesn't
work
ohed send
help send
help maybe they deact like the deps
deactivated our power so that only one
person I wonder how the other is going
cuz otherwise it's 2K I wonder yeah one
group apparently solved it so far oh
wow what like you just
got well I wish we could press it yes
not good you guys can't press
it is that like maybe a specific way to
make it I'm not sure another group made
it
apparently no
a there should be a a reset button you
mean there really is one or are you I
mean you just got to hit the reset
button just got to see which one
is wait
[Music]
what okay the same pattern at the
opposite yeah let's try actually can you
tell
me okay let me see we probably need to
the
[Music]
other sorry I know this is like so on
you no can do it okay let me check this
spot actually let's try to understand
the logic of a like this so I
mean I don't know there's a simpler way
of just like being like Oh you clicking
see oh you're clicking again you can
click then okay let's I can click
yeah let's do
[Music]
together oh oh I can't click anymore
almost almost almost
now I you I can't click anymore yeah it
looks
good
oh okay on this side no on this okay now
I I I got an idea
o mhm she can do
it adjacent blocks adjacent
blocks keep on clicking
keep on pwing at it oh nice nice nice
you got this one oh
wait you had decide if
oh be careful cuz you're going to get
the logic of this
game it's just if you wait so now this
starts wait wait wait wait wait
don't do inside out of time because you
can if you I don't know how to explain
this very
well know why you're not not able to
click it though maybe it's a bad there's
no way that it's a limit because you've
been clicking it the most yeah yeah it's
probably bad but it's probably better
than all four of us doing it at the same
time so yeah but the way to do it is
like you just keep track of like what
each like when you click one block what
it
fills but you just got to be mindful of
the ones that are on the side because
they'll affect the ones that are on a
different
face yeah so like careful touch like so
here's good
this is probably good but it's like you
can't can't touch
[Music]
these there you go there you
[Applause]
go pretty much good job good job all
right you're doing
[Music]
great oh looks
good something like
that I feel like you're you're very
close you're doing doing so good
got nice nice nice nice nice good
job she got the
[Applause]
[Music]
power she did it she did
it
MP y go
the goat cat time to be useful
again let's
go
sington oh my
God look at that chandelier my
goodness as can you
see oh my gosh care watch out for the
lasers watch out for the laser eyes oh
oh my
goodness this the way we should I don't
know if we should have gone this way
maybe is he getting rid of the whole
bridge I I I I feel I feel that might be
what he's doing we should have gone the
other
way no no no no wait what a checkpoint
oh this is a new checkpoint okay oh that
supposed to happen Okay scrip to
death what is this don't eat it it's a
mushroom um um um um ooh
um let's try
kill just decoration is it just
decoration oh yeah I know what to do I
know what to do what you do oh wait
someone someone received bone
meal yeah oh yeah for oh we got it oh
nice nice nice and then ow more we need
more more bone meal oh more more bone
meal can we make it
biger we have hard to
come here come here die on this
altar if you have B me please use it oh
nice nice nice nice I guess are you
supposed to kill him or go a bit more I
think we can
climb yeah kill kill him on the thingy
kill him on the
thingy nice nice nice nice nice nice I
don't
know I got
you nice nice nice oh it's so big now oh
it's like spawning the
the
[Music]
okay a this is so cool fire oh get them
get them to die like on the tree can we
go now you can I know can we maybe that
it yeah maybe I might die
think there's a button here how do you
climb button the
tree just press press space jump into
it this is not I'm doing but I said I
wouldn't
do
no I think this might just be stairs oh
there you
go are you going up yeah but actually we
might oh it's already reaching the top I
can see from are you sure
you don't need more yes reaching the top
I can't get it oh I got up here where's
the from
[Music]
here I don't
know oh wait wait these
thingies it's the vines right yeah I
forgot how to climb them
[Music]
there's a button
here I don't think the buttons do
anything oh it's just there you're just
there okay wait yeah she's
there it
doesn't I
fell
a can I climb okay oh no this one's Pap
for
then which way is made it oh okay
up here and then up here up
here difficult buttons okay the
buttons
okay I wonder what this
does those buttons the
[Music]
buttons I wonder what those buttons are
oh you just follow them I think oh you
just follow them
yeah oh
okay oh we're here
[Music]
no oh you're right oh you're right oh no
I'm good you made it yeah welcome oh oh
more okay follow me follow me hello over
here I feel like maybe wouldn't we only
need one of the trees to grow I don't
know is there two platforms
where did my oh my bone meal disappeared
oh it's over there okay have come
here I mean why would there be
two get
more are you collecting bone meal in
your inventory or do you have to kill
them on the thingy oh I you have to kill
them on the
thing I
see me
[Music]
nice I'm behind you
ah
w we need to also do this
one not enough though not enough is
there only one skeleton at a time this
is pretty difficult dungeon wait wait
wait it has to die on the tree it has to
die on the
[Music]
tree this one him come here always
fallowing come
here tra him oh wait wait wait wait wait
don't kill him ah he's going to kill me
heit doesn't drop the bone me hey he's
going to kill me no no it's a DI on the
tree a he's going to kill me oh
okay I thought he was going to get
me oh no way this is the
no
way where's the butt no I go the vine
first
[Music]
really roll roll roll
okay how come it work last
time
[Music]
hold oh my God
oh here we go here we go I see I see it
worked last time from there didn't it or
did I not do that
yeah I think welcome back I think this
should be okay
now let's try W they're holding
hands uhuh huh whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoaa whoa back up buddy hey buddy
hey buddy pow buddy pow get out here I
see it see
it okay do it
[Music]
where do I go from here I
think no get her oh she has to come back
[Music]
now okay does this then connect ah okay
wait maybe
not
um oh up here up here up here up here
okay uh uh wait and then wait no not
this way this
way oh God
um I am confused uh oh maybe from here
up here up no oh follow the buttons wait
how do I go up from
here here maybe
oh they the buttons they speak to you
buttons oh my God I'm just seeing I see
red uh no we can't there's no way up
here
no uh maybe on the top go back down go
back down go back
down oh
here where yeah here wait wait where
oh
oh and now I don't know uh uh uh oh do
we have to go to the other tree do you
think
probably I don't see the other yet oh
maybe down there is it down there yeah
you can do it I believe let me go to the
go in front of you in front of you
there's one over there can't you make
that one the one that's there well uh
hold
on no this one over here not this one no
the one to the right wait B can you
jump yes I will not be able to forget
that I feel like this is this is just
not taking me me down or should I go
this way I thought it was this way and
then we go around I don't know I'm just
going down now maybe there's multiple
paths look there's it seems as if there
is one path and that is marked by the
buttons ladies but there's multiple
paths for the
[Music]
buttons whichever speaks to
you is only up really the
way this like this way then that way did
I see that button
I didn't follow the but okay now these
patterns are confusing me yeah that's
what I
mean found you got it do you have to go
down to go up no
what oh she's being I'm scared I'm going
to miss this oh you got the checkpoint I
can just kill myself we can just die now
could lame feels lame I want to figure
it
[Music]
out you guys made me feel like I was
being stupid for think you got go down a
little bit oh no that wasn't so hard at
all woo I'm going to read the next part
okay I'm going to read this you read
okay yeah I
read to the
den denance of the
Underworld the
light emanated by S was
vetal vital you got this you got this
doing you're doing so well
okay now I cannot read anymore for some
reason H I cannot read anymore I don't
know click on next page it doesn't work
no it doesn't
work I don't know yeah you can be the
other the other ESL will
continue they needed it to survive in
this ever cold and dark environment yet
among them there was a heretic who
called their Customs into question do we
really need to take others lives to
sustain our own
stain no there has to be another way and
so she stepped into the plane above oh
plane which plane This
Plane let's
go is
the oh oh your power of Revelation has
grown strong
stronger
aah you've recovered a portion of your
memories have
I what
portion click here to watch
video
yeah yeah oh yeah you made it the video
did they give us a better way to play it
oh oh hi Ena what the heck Intruder
Intruder Intruder Intruder Ena what the
we need to we need to put a
video yeah uh just be care the way they
want us to play the video is not a very
smart way to do
it I think we need to play on
stream uh let me see if they did what we
asked I just need to download the
video okay wait
oh so go I'm going to at you instead of
doing what they the thing in the
Minecraft you download the video do you
see it yeah okay yeah download the video
and play it I'll do now okay I download
video
wow okay I mute the I'm going to mute so
we I can watch the video okay I'm going
to mute too yeah yeah yeah mute
too mute
too hold up everybody I'm getting the
video ready hold on a
second hold on a second hold on a
second hold up we got a video to watch
then I then I need to go I'm
dying okay okay
up video
[Music]
where is
it all
right think I'll put it here you guys
ready for a video we unlocked a
video ready
Freddy here do this how's the background
music been don't worry don't worry about
it ready
okay I think it's going to play if I do
this oh wait a
[Music]
minute I can't hear it a Reaper's job is
to end people's lives and take their
souls that's how it's always been the
spirits of the underworld need their
[Music]
sustenance but I keep
wondering this me these are my memories
this is me
is this the right thing to
do no it's not I want to like the
eyeball
[Applause]
[Music]
what's going
[Applause]
on look at
that turns out we can also use people's
emotion we don't need their souls at
all return to the dis to die should help
the living
reer not take away their future if the
others can't accept that that's their
loss
wow she how
cool more is really
cool oh
wow it's over oh are people waiting for
me wow they're chewing so
loudly hello
yeah she called me a horse girl what a
weirdo I'm her fan now when I see her
again I must talk to her yeah meet her
that's it we've done the first dungeon
let's go I'm so happy
Yoo I'm dying good job every bu good job
good actually GG's how do we return is
it is that light up ahead where the Moon
is I'm going to return by leaving
oh I think hello what the heck hello
hello traveler pleasure to see everyone
are you leaving or are you incoming we
are incoming
incoming I
wish this isn't the right way it's not
the right way you have to fall off this
Cliff yes that Waits you
otherwise have to jump yeah it's down
there that's where the dungeon is I
promise promise as the member of the
ceran cup I trust easily yeah yeah yeah
all the way down get down there you
don't want want that now you want this
death there's a l move move further move
further S I think it means you're not
ready I can't jump oh it's not allowing
me to she's not ready
oh ready to to face the dungeon what's
under here oh my my weapon is so cool
actually
nothing w w all right sorry we're
pranking you s we don't want gu Wars
regret to say that the bay may be
crashing all right is everyone so is
cleop
Eisenhower you want to head back to
let's go back to yeah let's head back
let's head back wait where's the cat
wait kitty cat kitty cat party kitty cat
give here kitty give kitty
kitty up get
up Crush path red lady we just saw we
just saw you pink lady
this no we just saw you were doing
something oh yeah I just saw your most
inner thoughts your de saw the inner
workings of your brain I know what you
are I don't know what they're talking
about they're making me really I know
what you are I know what you
are I know I know everything about you I
have issues with people
please all right good night I'm going
home goodbye I shall as well hell
maybe we should get out of the call can
I get a
signature we saw
you I will return home my goodness I I'm
hor
hor we have to wait do we have to speak
to the we have to speak to do we do we
have to speak to the oh we speak to the
guy oh my goodness
I should get out of here what does he
have to say what you guys doing to my
honorary gu M I have nothing but the
utmost respect for your Valor hero Valor
all right well
me that's right I'm in the toilet so
challenges with courage go in should we
go
inside oh hello I'm live now
hello what's your name are you also a
puppy I am not a
puppy oh she got she went in goodbye I
am a big cat very one of the dangerous
one she says her catchphrase
is just the saddest
eation witness I'm I'm a big cat sorry a
big cat goodbye goodbye they make a
goodbye goodbye goodbye I'm in front of
a dungeon
goodbye was that that oh hi those
interesting sounds you were making oh no
that's my horse oh your horse excuse for
misunderstanding yeah I don't I don't
speak words have you given back your
quest already I suppose
not what we have to give it back you
give
uh oh damn it I
H damn
it wait
what wait what we have to go back
apparently oh
where is he wait he's not over here he's
not over here where is
he where are
you what wait no we don't have to go
back what
hello stay here or don't stay here we
here here
St where is he I caught up I caught up
oh I see I see I
see
we what' you say what did you say hat
what did you say what did you say oh
hello ladies what say that hat say
[Music]
greetings I am the appointed
point point get it are you now of the
skylet
wand I
speak we had a side quest and she took
over leader of our Guild wow that's
cool it looks like you're we with a hat
like this it looks like you're wearing
like a red velvet cake on your head what
is your name blue
creature it um
um I don't know the leader youg don't
know point of the SC hey you aren't you
the one that hit me with your horse oh
my God I don't there's there's lots
of her and you are the one that drowned
her
this wait who don't worry I'll kill
whoever what what they do they hit you
you hit me with your horse no no no no
no
no no no who her right what what Guild
are you a part
of is this way it this
way where are
they oh they're in here
what this way this
way all right which one is it the middle
one
right
the yeah yes you want to read
awesome read
read which one is she who's this it went
away I didn't see what she said
oh I see to think the ruins held such
secrets a crystal deep within that when
touched returned a fragment of your
memories to you memories which awaken
the power of Revelation albeit at only a
fraction of its potential mhm that your
summoning and the discovery of these
ruins should go inside so closely there
must be some connection between the
ruins and the power of
Revelation oh Brave hero seek rubius The
Guild Master of the Scarlet hand wand
what it gu has also been searching for
strange ruins in the lands of listol
weaps can't take them seriously when
they say mayhaps they've discovered
something I don't know what he said
speak to the I like that word scarlet W
Guild
Master all right sounds good SC well go
to rubius rubius yes please Rubi is free
me
this is a shortcut shortcut my horses
swim is there is there a bridge near
here wait where is
he I don't need the
bridge there she is oh my gosh you're so
fast yeah it's the red velvet cake
people oh can you can you speak yes oh
good day to you hero returned from
investigating those ruins are you I've
gotten theist from V's
moress yes I now sense within you a
trace of the power of Revelation wait
fascinating most oh go ahead go ahead go
ahead Most Fascinating one might hsize
that those runes are the key to
unlocking your powers we of the scolard
W have also been investigating near the
plains Irish superglue fell from a high
place and wouldn't you know it just off
the coast we as
Pi a light with a striking resemblance
to Revelation her blood flame was doomed
to
fall good hero would you be willing to
travel to the coast and Aid in our
efforts there oh is that where like
we'll see Atlantis I don't
know me members of our Guild are already
there hard at work I'm quite sure they
will appreciate your assistance good
luck and Excel all sounds like a spell
someone would
cast and speak to the corun of the
Scarlet how long is getting
tired yeah I mean I think maybe that's
just like the continuation of the main
quest is it and it just goes on forever
forever until like the very end oh dear
not sure and did the did the did the uh
I don't know if she has a different name
uh the the red one the B the B I think
she did oh okay so it's just uh us and
the lost kitten now I think I think I
got a head off though I'm I still got
sick brains no worries you made it far
traveler I hope our Guild will find much
success in the future if there's
anything I may help you with or be
assistance of uh let me know at any time
we'll do and to you
Smooch smooched your horse what are you
GNA do about it horse of course yes my
horse only I see you have an interest in
horses no that's not what that means but
go on it's okay go on comrade I'll join
you again goodbye goodbye Cleopatra
goodbye goodbye farewell farewell adios
all right everybody I thought I'd only
be here for two hours but I was here for
three hours I'm going to go
die I go sleep thank you everyone for
watching you just missed kiaa I'm going
Kia I just saw a m I'm m i mean no I'm
not oh there she
is take her I was talking the phone
take her I go goodbye yeah bye-bye
goodbye goodbye I need to talk to this
until
tomorrow until tomorrow
byebye oh
Deary all right everybody I am heading
off I'm
EP big EP I feel like my congestion is
better today though
what am I talking about wait no I left
the server
so my congestion from yesterday where I
was having congestion it's better I
think
so I also didn't nap
today but I am I I I'm
done I'm checked
out I don't know when I will be playing
again maybe tomorrow maybe Monday maybe
Tuesday I'm not sure sure I'm just going
where the wind takes me the wind being
the amount of energy that I
have but yes this was day one of Ian r r
r it was
fun I go
now I'll see you
guys I think I did I send a special
ending I think I did did I you'll find
out we'll see anyways by my byebye
byebye byebye byebye byebye goodbye bye
now bye-bye byebye bye-bye CA Eisenhower
D Vinci the great thei signing out
[Music]