foreign
[Music]
oh yeah
you know
look at this okay okay
let's go foreign
[Music]
laughs
hi
they're just starting uh for everybody
who's watching the archive I just
started in the middle of the
whole ID cup because my games are at the
end
um
uh so far seems like the other group has
been winning but
um it's unfair because we should have
won the potato sack race two of our
players went in first but okay
well well let's uh gambarro wow hi hi hi
hi
I'm second team right yeah you're you're
a okay
you were so good I was watching you
while I was cooking you should have won
honestly I was just I
don't know
you were legendary
that was incredible
yes yes
practice
[Music]
oh God
I will shinjiru yeah
are crazy at this game who knows
I don't know you guys practiced a lot so
just don't worry I mean
also if you
if you strain it just shout like a real
sport
[Music]
oh okay I believe let's start right away
who who has the first yeah
okay okay ready ready guys okay you got
this they have a problem
okay
let's go
they could shoot any moment now okay
there we go yeah
oh nice nice nice Kayla's always nice
best backup
[Applause]
that out good job good job good defense
[Music]
[Applause]
that was so weird it's out okay no
problem
[Music]
where is it
oh
okay my eyes
on your side it's on your side I don't
see it
I'm so nervous don't worry you're doing
great
[Music]
nice save okay
don't worry don't worry don't worry
it's out it's out it's out
thank you
yeah the X's because it's going towards
the wrong side yeah
you have to hit the like
the opposite side for the first hits
after the first hit you can hit wherever
you want basically ah I see
I'll take it okay thank you
okay thank you
thank you that was on the line
don't worry
oh okay totally winnable
hey
[Music]
Google
number nine
again
will there be an interview
please win
those teams
[Music]
I believe
wasn't ready
okay okay
wait
oh yes
looking good hey wait okay
[Music]
[Applause]
okay okay in real life
something you would do
don't mind don't mind
do you pass in badminton in real life do
you pass to your teammate
we only can possibly do like one one
okay we cannot pass
ES
okay okay okay
I'm enjoying this too much
when it feels good
IES
okay okay
that's their problems
[Applause]
[Music]
we sweep
congratulations
you guys caught up the city yeah really
of course Point wise we did
yes oh oh my god let's go you guys are
10 points ahead right now right now oh
yeah thank you thank you so basically
after this soccer will be like the what
is it called the
it would be the deal breaker yeah soccer
designs at all yes yes okay so if you
want to win win the soccer if they want
to win they have to win the soccer do
you guys think you guys got what it
takes to win soccer we will win we will
win
of course we have to know because
winning it just felt so good right now I
want more of that please
but like seriously you guys are like
really good at like uh hitting the we
are thank you
[Music]
was a great backup to have behind me
like she was managing the backside and I
was managing the front but they normally
shot a lot of like shots to the very far
back so you know Kyla was always there
to support me thank you
[Music]
seems fun but seems also very difficult
yeah
it's very strong
support support office support and
um that uh I'm team Wing yeah
[Music]
can you keep the server online so I can
play more badminton for the coming
months please
thank you all right then soccer next
leave it to me
okay yeah give it back yeah yay nice job
okay so they said that there's 10 point
difference and soccer is gonna make the
big difference yeah we are leaving but
we still need to win the soccer yeah
okay
but the soccer is 20 minutes in total
right so oh my God
should I maybe try to stay in a certain
area like close to the goal or so any
any uh I think
uh striking right yeah
let's forward while the uh the others
can I think at least one tries to stay
back and guard uh without you somebody
has to stay around the goal like at
least in the area roughly around the
goal otherwise
okay yeah before EOP okay okay second
goalkeeper yeah yeah no okay
no no foreign
[Music]
okay
foreign
the pressure
y'all better not bring the ball to me
okay
[Music]
do we automatically run
we're automatically running by the way
are we automatically running no I think
you always have to press okay yes my
little finger gets tired from it after a
while but I'm pressing it nothing's
changing so it is
you can jump as well but but it's like
oh
[Music]
wow
don't worry don't worry boy we have 10
minutes
okay okay hold hold okay
don't worry
don't worry don't worry
let's go it was close it was close
okay it's okay it's okay
okay sometimes it just disappears
it is
[Laughter]
can she be that close okay
get out of the cold Zone
[Music]
Watson's a really good goalkeeper
we have so much
yeah okay who is it who is it okay okay
yeah okay go go go go go go go oh shoot
that was so far
okay okay what does that mean okay don't
worry okay don't worry
okay go
okay you need to stay back a little bit
no you no you don't take the ball
all right I don't know
[Music]
where is it okay I gotta redo
okay okay
go go go go go
no
no no
no no no
[Music]
the defense okay okay I'm gonna take it
to the left okay
okay go go go go go go go
oh Watson
[Laughter]
I'll be just staying close Okay please
sometimes I'm not sure which direction
it went
let's go
Jason
[Music]
it's not fast enough okay
ladies
and take it to the left too again all
right all right yes it's like a real
soccer match
again go go go go go go take it take it
okay
wow
job
she's gonna get distracted at a certain
point
okay
[Music]
no
um
nice okay
um I need to stay close I need to stay
closer to here yeah I'm gonna go into
the right side
[Music]
is she gonna
send it to us from here
I feel like it always goes further than
you might think
okay
okay okay hey wait hold on
good at least I'm gonna turn around
yeah they're turning around is difficult
yeah
I don't even know if I'm running or not
am I running I I don't know yeah you
feel like you're running I don't feel
like I am but I'm not holding control
come on
I'm sorry it's holy God
[Music]
it is
is
nicely
close close close one
eh wait are we already in the second
half what no no no no no no no no no no
seven minutes
[Music]
okay here we go don't throw it kick it
you're ready all right
where's the bowl
oh there there it is let's go
wow wow it came back to me all right
I gotta stay back here in case they in
case they end up getting it
yeah go back go back this oh what the
[\h__\h] where was that
okay let's go come on come on come on
come on ladies
[Applause]
[Music]
nice nice okay
yeah I did I didn't know soccer will be
this oh yeah
get it
[Applause]
toys
[Music]
yeah no definitely do that oh that was
that was nice that was a good night
it's okay it's okay it's okay no problem
okay
is
yeah maybe describe yeah
we can bring it back in the second half
yeah yeah yeah oh my God you have to be
maybe a bit more aggressive more
aggressive yeah
I wonder if maybe I should not defend
that I should strike it no I think it's
good that you're defended okay okay
you're good okay I feel like I'm doing a
bad job no you've been doing a good job
okay I think we need more defense though
more yeah
can just kick the ball to the front we
don't need like that much of like you
know we don't need much of the attackers
oh okay defensive yeah so if we got the
ball just kick it yeah
[Music]
yeah
then it might be hard it might be hard
to get points yeah sometimes when the
ball finally goes over to like the goal
side the red goal side I feel like then
often there's like only coyote Senpai
there and nobody's helping her I should
be closer to the goal honestly so yeah
[Music]
no
hold up
[Music]
yeah
they're going to be more defensive 100
because they're winning so we we really
need to be aggressive I think okay okay
um
I'll get it
all right
okay they were interviewing the glass
Empire or what yeah yeah I think I need
to be more in the central area
[Music]
nice nice
um
Empire
[Music]
let's just be Senpai yeah
I said she's been streaming like at
least for the amount of four years even
though she's only been around for 1.5
years videos
[Laughter]
bad weather by the way I really hope I
don't DC oh don't worry it's over soon
just 10 more minutes okay just gonna
tell Kubo to chill out
chill chill out stop
making rain
it's too good of a goalkeeper yeah
I need foul options
option
I want to kick them
I wanna I wanna make them stumble
yeah
and have a guess
okay yes
if we have any strategy yeah yeah okay
okay just just leave it to Lady Luck I
guess maybe there's a miracle combat
yeah
[Music]
stronger
aggressive everything stronger okay
let's do better let's go
okay
[Applause]
mm-hmm
just take a deep breath
okay nice nice kick it off
[Music]
all right
I don't okay all right
get ready ladies here we go
all right
okay
[Music]
um Watson day no Watson yeah she's
really good I'm Watson
where's she gonna where is she gonna go
okay
right over my head I wish I could jump
better
right here
from there I don't know if we can shift
I don't think the rules are that
realistic
better to try
again
it's so aggressive I think we need
somebody doing what pekuda is doing over
by the goal can we just follow her
okay
nope away
I also still have to turn around every
time they're already looking in the
right direction we have to turn around
so difficult to get around the ball oh
Matt come on there's no way I'm sorry
but I'm sorry
it's
not your fault
good try good try
guys no worries
you can surprise them they're gonna let
their guard down
[Music]
my aggressive aggressive guys so right
where is it oh no oh no Kelly Kelly
protect me I'm ready I'm ready
she might go sideways yeah but nah
nah all right she wants to go to gouda
but she failed she failed
I'm gonna be tactical about it okay okay
[Music]
all right
don't we love each other
it's fun
oh yeah
all right nope
okay got me effed up over here
Watson's too good
yeah
oh God
[Music]
okay okay
all right
oh okay okay
[Music]
all right nice
oh
foreign
[Music]
okay
she wants to confuse us
all right get ready ladies we're here
we're here let's go let's go
[Music]
[Applause]
come on
if we can tie with them we just need to
tie with them yeah
that would be good
no no no
okay
okay I decide it's fine it's fine
defense defense right yeah defense
I'm here
I want to do a penalty kicks they're fun
yeah
what do we gotta do to get penalties get
ready
[Music]
defense
okay
what are you gonna do couple
what are you going to do
it
okay
oh
[Music]
foreign
go
no
I had to save it
that was close and can we get extension
you cannot expand no like 10 minutes oh
yeah
um was it good momentum
momentum
thank you thank you thank you guys
huh imposter does fly
it is it's fly still I'm gonna get it to
the left all right there you go
two door locks
nope nope nope nope very nice
nope nope nope nope nope
whatever happens this was a lot of fun
yeah
I
have the best team
[Music]
okay
I know
Donald Donald
Trump
okay
definitely they needed her to be there
my team's the best my team is the best
my team is the best
[Music]
we didn't even have penalty yeah
hmm But it was good
that was great that wasn't good
we did our best a good match yeah yep
at least it was close it wasn't like
they completely destroyed us yeah yeah
not not like Pokemon unite or anything
like that
yeah
but
there was literally do not get gas lit
into thinking that we didn't do well in
that tournament because we did okay
it was great even though I was watching
it was it was it was really awesome
thank you everybody worked the whole
time
good thank you
yeah dang I meant too strong I mean it's
a good I'm Amazed
[Music]
yova and Cali also like
um what is it yes
[Music]
look at our bodies were all the same
not even wrong
[Music]
I had fun
games are just like also so much fun I
really enjoy all the games even the ones
I didn't participate in so I would have
loved it yeah
but badminton easy
I think the map is open until
um
yeah I think somebody said 21. 20
something something so yes everybody
wants to try it yeah if you want to ask
someone to play with you thank you Kyle
I'm not asking anybody to
I'm still trying to get a friend to play
the taco 4 because I really love that
one
is crying
I'll play against you Kyla anytime yeah
you know what we have to uh Kiara we
have to play uh like two two versus one
oh okay versus Kyla what wait what no
no no no
don't worry I can maybe do it alone
again
I will just die but you know
um
it's good games yeah just a game and
that's done
thank you
[Music]
did I look cool
yes I was watching
we should have been cheerleading where
are your pom-poms
oh
you mean in front of your heart
is too strong that was wild yeah the
movable wall yes
how strong are you now though getting
punched like this yeah
she likes it she likes she likes it you
sure about that just like back in the
day
thanks thanks I'm not abusive to my gym
it's pink slap
s
everybody gets stinks
wow
really give me a five stars
Emma did you play soccer in real life
before or what I have I have oh
there oh that explains everything
never had a prayer
bye everybody
[Music]
announcement time
are you announcing your wedding with
someone
oh
congratulations
[Music]
it was intense and well after all of
those intense games will be announcing
the winners
yeah so first of all from the bending on
the capture the fourth
with 40 points
and then we also have the sack race with
30 points yet again three candy wins so
that brings us to a total of 70 points
what's the next one the next one was tug
of war
in which it was a blue versus pink team
OMG
[Music]
four how many points
exactly 40 points
and then badminton again two matches
both won by perf Theory so 20 plus 20 so
another 40 points for party
after three candy was leading pretty we
managed to catch up by 10 points and
then that's where soccer came in and
became the deal breaker yeah
Watson too strong we are happy to
announce that the winner of the whole ID
cup is the
tiger
[Applause]
[Music]
I don't think so Crystal
I don't think so are you gonna spanking
for that
um
one team gets like a better medal that's
awesome
I'm a loser
top two
is hard
[Laughter]
[Music]
going to be awarding the medals right
yeah okay the theme captain please
distribute the medals to your teammate
hi I love distribute
oh yes
[Music]
let me see hey what if I just put on the
gold medal anyway yeah put it on
I have access to the gold but maybe I'm
gonna put on where it is
[Music]
all right
my medal now my metal let's go
I'm gonna take your medals
thank you so much
[Music]
think better
does everybody have their medals
[Applause]
[Music]
just like the opening we will be asking
for a few words by each team captain
starting from Sri candy teams
[Music]
yeah
wow that was it that was really fun
really really fun and
um
can we do oh can we do the
um the the yellow together again
let's do it again yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay let's go okay okay okay
speak again
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
everyone everyone did there everyone did
um everyone did their best doing the
games
[Laughter]
thank you so much
[Music]
opportunity thank you for playing with
us as well
please
[Music]
first I would like to say thank you for
all for dating to uh to actually make
time for this and also I love birthday
thing because they are all
um hardworking so they practice too and
they they like oh my God I just I just
love the team so I love you too
[Music]
we put a good fight yeah
thank you so much everybody thank you so
much for inviting us so I thought this
year was really fun thank you
so let's do it again next year again
please thank you
next year again please
guys yeah yeah
let's go yeah okay do you want to do the
cheer for one last time
[Applause]
thank you
thank you thanks to you
[Applause]
[Music]
lastly yeah
pushing
[Music]
you mean going small is a shift oh me in
front of a cute together yeah we do yeah
yeah
[Music]
three
two one
[Music]
thank you
look look at me look at me okay okay
okay uh
[Music]
again
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
he wants to take pictures
I'm going to party VC I don't know if
they'll get the memo
[Music]
hey we're the real winners let's go I
got the pink medal the cute metal yeah
where should we go for the picture
[Music]
should we just go fly up so we can get
like all of them
oh that would be cool
one of the balloons to ships
how to fly in Minecraft wow
please yes
let's see creative mode
and what I can't get the
how do I fly
you need wine
our game has been updated to creative
mode there there it is I haven't I
haven't
go up again
anything
today my hands are a little strong
ER
ah double jump Oh I thought it was just
one jump okay double jump what oh sorry
it's okay it's okay it's okay I'm fine
[Applause]
um
[Music]
let's go this is a good dragon ship it's
so pretty
are you taking um
I'm flying all right let's go let's get
in the dragon in the dragon dragon's
mouth and [\h__\h] uh yeah there we go cool
dragon's eyebrows
yeah a dragon's head pool
yeah yeah
[Music]
um
so please make sure that I'm in the
middle so I can get like a better
picture
okay
can go in front
um right
here I'll stay here
we can go a little bit in front
yeah yeah
or is it good enough like this name
oh hi okay
okay
this works
this one's nice this one is nice
you know
here I am okay okay bye
oh hi everybody
okay got one
we got two
um
okay we look at us everybody yeah
everybody look up how up is
[Music]
perfect
perfect okay get my chocolate sandwich
please
okay get my good side
you look good okay okay I think it's
done okay
I will send it
yeah
[Music]
thank you
I want to see what's in this ship this
ship is cool yeah
yeah I ate it in Indonesia oh and the
other one I don't remember the other one
she's ready
wow I'm an Explorer
I'm gonna send the pictures
[Music]
I wonder when the Japan
sports festival is
and then there should be an announcement
about that Japanese
I I got it okay wait wait wait I need I
need to close my stream first okay wait
was it invitation
My Stream too we we can stop the stream
now yeah okay okay okay thanks everybody
let me go talk to my viewers really
quick and I'll be right back me too yeah
yeah guys okay hello
it was uh pretty short wow uh what's uh
I'm pretty
pretty awake still but I I think I'm
gonna crash now I have to sleep
um I made Burger before stream or like
during during when this was already
going on
before and half in the middle
was an okay Burger
um I don't know about Japanese
did I get info on that
Japanese Sports Fest
did I miss something what the [\h__\h]
uh maybe I missed something
[Music]
what's the idea
um
search Discord
s
[Music]
August that's now yeah no no
I don't know ah no okay I see it but I
don't think
I don't think uh
oh wait
that's 2022 yeah I can only find the one
for 2022.
why it was hitting me was it
[Laughter]
oh [\h__\h] I I was
next week with not cracking anymore in
case you saw the community post for
Members Only
ah yeah
yeah okay they were probably thinking of
Summer Festival yeah last
um Japanese sports festival was November
2022 apparently what do you want because
[\h__\h]
was uh November 2022 so it will probably
be around that cold winter time again
yeah I don't know um this was a lot of
fun
um the games were awesome I really
enjoyed them and I did great at
badminton
um and soccer I don't know be careful
you what I'm what
I'm what be careful I'm what I'm only
looking at
at chat
I know I'm still in the VC but I'm muted
completely I can I can leave to BC
you got the only goal yeah right the
only soccer girl they were like
they had a they had a great Amelia
Watson who was protecting the girl so
well and who made the most uh creative
mode who made the most goals I think was
a pickle now on their side
she seemed very very well practiced and
and and aggressive in the game so
um
one and three pickura damn how's pecula
MVP and literally anything she does damn
see that sounds bad I don't like it
doesn't have a good ring to it in my
opinion
um
what's his last name can we not just say
pecora and then his last name instead or
or pecora Ronaldo pecora Ronaldo sounds
so much better
Lando
Lionel was it Lionel Lionel Messi really
was Messi the last name last name okay
what's the first name then
what's the first I think pecora Ronaldo
sounds so much better Lionel pecora like
I don't know whatever
but yeah
I am it's like 8 A.M now as you may know
I stayed up
um not even that tired right now but it
will probably come to me in a moment
um
so I'll try to sleep now
and uh
I'll try to fix my sleep schedule from
now on actually yeah it's Sunday now so
within Sunday when I wake up I'll try to
make my schedule for the week there'll
be another
oh so
unexpected uh collab with a kohai
it's cool still asking for my attention
does she wants to get in the boat with
me
okay but I don't want to be the one who
controls
okay why is she so cute what the [\h__\h]
the [\h__\h] is her problem wait she's in
voice chat alone
I win
cool why Why you wanna go somewhere with
the boat where are you where are we
going
I'm celebrating my win
um
[Music]
but but but but but you lost against the
pink girls
I was pretty weak Kobo
um yeah what do you say about that was
it really your win or was it your team's
overall win hmm no I just we just we we
just that fine wait what was the other
game you played
sucker right um
yeah and badminton
ah and I won against you in badminton
too see
so we won and soccer okay I saw you I
gave you one goal that's that's you I'll
give you that you got one goal in soccer
yeah and I have a good asses for pequful
Senpai
I mean obviously you girls did amazing
in soccer yeah good job
badminton player but I have to say I was
a little bit sad when I first saw the
teams and I saw you were in the other
team I was sad
yeah I got separated with my parents yo
what the hell
why they wanted to see blue Power Team
with Gouda and pecora is that what they
wanted to see maybe I think they want to
break our family yeah
we have to support and protect Family
Values
yeah
but it's okay I still win yeah
I'm still waiting yeah did you hear the
other day when I said instead of
bokoboku I said
did you hear yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah I hear I hear that I I did it for
you feel free to use it
are you still streaming
no oh I am oh yeah thank God you didn't
say anything oh bad
I was talking to my viewers you kept on
like you know poking me all the time
out
come take mommy for a ride
thank you
it's actually amazing that even though
you didn't know I was streaming you
didn't say anything yeah bye
of course I'm not yeah bye
everybody
no I mean just like you know Secrets our
secrets
ah like like yeah
oh yeah
like the that story you're dead
family secrets
next week your outfit reveal
and next week right
I mean it's two days
well it will be in two days in two days
it looks very very big and extra very
complicated again
uh but it looks traditional oh
yeah I thought I follow because uh the
all the other Generations gen 1 Gen 2
they all have traditional style outfits
oh it will be nice I I think it will be
very difficult for Cobo cosplayer to
make yeah
do you hate cosplayers do you want them
to suffer
no but I want them more extra yeah I I
understand me too me too I want extra to
hmm my newest outfit is a bit extra did
you see mommy's new outfit
the the night one yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah you like it I saw it I saw it
it's so
I don't know how to describe it's so
ah confusing me confusing you
you mean it's cool right
yeah it's cool yeah it's cool I mean
it's confusing in a good way of Phoenix
but then you're a knight no but I always
my lore was always that I am a part-time
Warrior that's from the beginning that's
why I already have I always have a sword
in the shield cool but did you forget
oh so that's your now I'm full time
before I was part-time Warrior now I'm
full-time Warrior
[Music]
you'd get more busy then yeah you know
have to protect the world and stuff not
a big deal you know so are you still
running your business
yeah it's running almost automatically
just automatic cash income you know easy
okay
here it is 8 A.M
in the morning I am right there
I stayed up the whole night
sleep no
I go to sleep I go to sleep
well mothers often don't get sleep
mothers always don't get sleep because
of their children
lack of sleep because of you
no no I'm not the children
you don't know me you don't understand
mother
go to sleep all right all right I will I
will stop getting your pocket money done
if you think you're an adult
[Applause]
eh can be you can be like that ah what's
up the stream that that stop talking
stop the stream oh I was I was saying
bye anyway I was saying goodbye I'll
continue saying goodbye I love you Kabul
oh okay
oh they're so cute I love her my cutie
patootie
uh I was just like roasting her because
she was so cocky you heard it in her
voice right she was like
[Music]
yeah somebody has to bring her back down
to the ground
ground her I am gonna ground her
one week no computer
Gremlin no I love her I love her
attitude I love her gremliness with
everything about global anyway I love ID
Indonesia did you hear all my flirts too
Dana
caught her off guard
yeah that was a good important
opportunity to also get closer with some
ID members and also talked a bit with
Sona Senpai and coyulin
not really with Luna unfortunately
um we keep on like you know missing each
other
so holotalk will probably still be the
first time where we properly talk yeah
I'll close the game
thank you
they said I'm but we but I am number one
in Your Heart Right may have lost but
I'm one number one in your heart
oh well okay so I will hopefully fix my
sleep schedule until next week until
Monday meet me
[Music]
um
yeah
I wish you all alone and
[Music]
um
thank you for watching
and if you missed hello talk catch up
with hello talk that was big success
everything went pretty well
um
yeah and now this was a week where I was
streaming at n a evening
a few times but don't get used to it
because I'm never coming back to na
prime time
sayonara and a prime time goodbye
see you never again unfortunately it was
uh one time only occasion
when I was you know asked to participate
in Pokemon Unite
I was not told that it would be
at 4 00 am for me because they needed us
together at 4am
I was also not
I think I wasn't told right away that it
would be the ID thing it would also be
so early but 6 a.m is still okay but I
had to already
like frick frick up my sleep schedule
for the other thing so you know same
week might as well
keep it like that yeah but at least this
time I wasn't tired you know
hmm
I wasn't tired
easy peasy lemon squeezy
yeah yeah but um I don't know did any
more people than who like Anyone who
normally can't watch me who got to watch
me thanks to the late streams
I wonder
anybody
yeah really whoa
whoa
thank you well I hope I hope that you'll
continue to catch up with my archives
then
even when I stream at bedtime for you
please because I am still still doing my
best uh with you know
still doing my best every day every day
when I stream
[Music]
so I'll see you in the world gang okay
archive
um
yeah
anyway at least I'm just happy uh that
this was a lot of fun that I got to
interact with some cutie patooties and
that I was not
um bad
that's what I thought what I was doing
and it all came like pretty naturally
like
it's right like right off the bat
right off the bat
if you know what I mean if you catch my
Dorito
drifted around that pun or right into it
uh yeah if you watch the practice you
you could see even on first try
things were you know easy
yeah
I wanna play more badminton
badminton champ that's actually
difficult because like
you can't really take the time to turn
around and run back to the back of the
field walking backwards is too slow so
you have to rely on your teammate
who's behind you if you're in the front
and the same with soccer it was so
difficult because you know I felt like
80 percent of the time
um
they were like repeating the same
pattern
the same back and forth and
you know when eofi would shoot the ball
to us
the problem is we have to like
see where it's going to
but then
even if we're lucky and the ball lands
where we are we then have to like turn
around and Pew shoot it
in the other direction that's so
difficult like because the turning
around takes so much time
Tricky Tricky Tricky
um
clunky I mean it's just like
honestly pretty decent I think it's
better than
uh expected
soccer on in Minecraft
[Music]
um
and yeah in the end I at least got one
goal I would have liked to shoot a few
more goals but Ahmed was correct
and and I feel like the ball just was
wasn't on our side that much
unfortunately
yeah but everybody did well and it's
just difficult turning around the ball
quickly
yeah but makes me want to play a real
soccer game
like FIFA or something
ah
what reminder for what sorry my chat is
really small right now
reminder for what
remind me what did you remind you of
remind me of my Q hour reminder write
that again
what what
you reminded me of Hulk here
we might
okay I know I don't know what it was
yes Sunday this was my Sunday stream
basically now I have to sleep sleep yeah
fix my sleep schedule
um
on Monday I want to do two streams
though one Holo cure early in the day
and something in the evening
not on my channel
my evening
maybe maybe
she posted it okay
you already know okay and there is
of course of course
I wouldn't
I couldn't accept it if she would collab
with someone else first
because she knows yeah yeah
comfortability collab because we have so
many uh similarities that we already uh
found out about while talking so much
recently
and I'm like what the [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
um
hogging her all for yourself no I can't
no she's been socializing with lots of
other people too so
um I know all of her other plans already
that's okay
but she understands
she understands
she gets it love
mm-hmm
[Music]
okay now I'll go
yeah yeah yeah yeah no no it's okay like
she can do her own thing you know yeah
of course
I I I told like we talked about it we
talked about it you know that we would
love to of course do like a million
things together like she's she asked me
if I want to play Terraria with her and
I I told her no you know what no you
should play Terraria with other people
um first of all because I'm not so
interested in Terraria
and second of all because
um you just you know you need to
I don't want I shouldn't be involved in
every one of your collaborations so yeah
at least you're honest
no I bought I bought Terraria for Malin
Senpai in 2020 when Martin Senpai asked
me to be part of a Terraria group collab
project
and then I bought it and she asked me to
test it so we tested it a little bit and
then it never happened which is fine
because I wasn't that into it
um
no it never happened but it was like
planned behind the scenes
so I think I still have it on my Steam
account
hmm
[Laughter]
yeah yeah to be Minecraft bosses you
know what I want to play and I I got the
perms for it when I requested it uh the
Minecraft games the Minecraft RPG games
there's like two
that I got perms for
um
yeah don't Vibe with it it's a fine game
and all that but you know I don't vibe
how my game permissions doing huh
how are they doing
waiting reply
too bad
awaiting reply
they're cooking
oh I'm cooking something by the way
I'm already cooking another a half a
cooking side to side to the whole talk
I've been cooking another
um Advent collab
it was gonna be a mix of Advent and
Council but now it's just like full
Advent
because like I was like hi who wants to
play who wants to be in part of an
episode of unbelievably believable
um and then immediately all of Advent
replied
and then you know
yeah
so now it's uh I'll be hosting I don't
think I'll even be really participating
I'll be hosting though yeah
time is
uh on the
literally next week is
um
[Music]
17th on at 4 P.M jst
which is 9 00 am for me
it's because in the evening or so uh
um
uh Dana and ID have some stuff to do and
this was like literally the only day
where everybody had some time
other days was like not me I can't be I
can't be there no no
um
yeah
uh we're still deciding on the game I
gave them some suggestions and I let
them vote
what day uh 17th
but maybe it's 16 night time for n a
um
[Music]
boobs when's full Ian Among Us
are you asking this to me because you
think I will be organizing such a thing
nothing has been brought up until now uh
I was thinking a little bit about it
like how many people can you do in Among
Us Now 15 20.
like officially what's the number
15.
we're basically 15 minus like one
because uh fuomoku are one person right
Moco plays
so we're 14 then
she only won't play it according to a
previous stream what
was there a reason
does she not like the game
super anxious because
but what because a big amount of people
oh deception yeah you know I don't like
that so much either because I'm really
bad at that too
yeah that's understandable
I think for their senpai's reason is
different though she said she doesn't
like big uh group collabs that are that
huge
um
yeah no I understand
I'll ask her anyway but if she doesn't
want that's fine I'm gonna invite her to
girls talk though sometime because she
likes girls talk I think Larissa told me
um I have my ideas
I have my ideas for everybody oh yeah
I wanna I wanna you know stay close with
Advent
um
cooking
I wish a blue protocol would release
earlier though there is a hi
[Music]
I was I wish blue protocol was uh
release earlier
hmm
ah wait what's the maximum I guess it
depends on the game
we can't all play a cardic phone uh not
got it from uh jackbox games right
that's like
not for 14 people
I guess 14 is too much
ten
six to eight and it really depends on
the game
it's not all I want to do Jack box with
like completely mixed
um Generations
um
yeah and you know what we could do
though now I think en only Mario Kart
tournament maybe could work I don't know
but wait One race is 12.
uh
Maybe
maybe with okay wait so we could do two
hosts
12 racing
which one of them is
watching her and backseating her yeah
Amy said before I think that she would
prefer to
just host something like that
um but um
how long is that even gonna be with just
12 people
not that long right just
how long can we drag out a 12 people
Mario Kart tournament
an hour can we drag it out to an hour
she wants to shoutcast hell yeah
I I personally wouldn't mind not
participating because I I don't have the
patience to
and the determination to teach myself
Mario Kart for hours to even be relevant
at the race
uh you can drag it out infinitely yeah
but that's stupid
[Music]
okay see now I'm getting tired this is
good
[Laughter]
nah nah Mario Kart is just I hate the
pressure but that's maybe just for the
big Mario Kart tournament that wasn't by
always organizers
uh maybe with an En I wouldn't feel so
much pressure
I don't think I want to participate in
the next Mario Kart tournament because
like it's always at a bad time for me
and it's just so much pressure and I'm
so bad at it anyway and so what the hell
if I want to get good I would have to
spend like a whole month practicing and
even last time I was actually practicing
really hard okay
and still
it's no
foreign
[Music]
versus one
or several four people matches
yeah but then still like brackets
that should take a good amount of time
with
uh
well maybe we can make both of four more
play actually
then it's 15 minus one host how about
that so 14. uh
14 plus a host
oh
can't always
let mokuku do everything
and I need another person to
um you know make it an even number
eh no
you're the person the controller I mean
they probably have at least two
controllers right so let's say in one if
they like
end up becoming part of the same match
and have to fight against them then then
they just have to use two controllers
easy
their package deal
yeah but I want to see who I want to
play games too
so it's more Coco playing the game
flower has to play too can't always hide
from gaming
hmm oh oh it would be cute if they play
Ice clam boys wait can you play Ice
Climbers together
can you do that is that's not possible
Right
that would be like its whole
own like thing that you have to program
yeah it's not programmed like that
would be cute though
they should play like the og ice climber
you can play that together can you I
don't know I actually don't know but I'm
just assuming because it's two
characters
like the real game
ogs or they should they like old games
anyway right Islam is pretty old
um
no okay I think I should go I'm getting
tired
[Music]
no nobody wants to see that trust me
there would be too much suffering
too much amateur
chess see no no there you go plenty of
nose
actually I had this one idea keep on
saying I'm leaving and I don't I had
this one idea what was it I think I was
gonna
um what was it something about cooking
uh a cooking challenge
but I guess not ah it was more like a
everybody does it off stream they cook
something like a burger or so they I
wanted to give everybody the challenge
to make their own Burger
and then cook it and then take a picture
of it and share the recipe
and then like we would uh
just rate it but I don't know if I would
maybe make it myself recreated to
actually get the taste of it but I don't
know
like everybody makes the original burger
and I just judged by presentation and
recipe
um
I mean I feel like from a burger you can
kind of tell if it's good judging by
judging by the looks and by the
ingredients
because it's literally just like those
ingredients stacked on top of each other
the only thing is maybe that yeah hoping
that you didn't over salt your burger
patty and
or or didn't season your Patty at all
for example
um
and then the price is the best burger
becomes part of the imaginary Carefree
no real KFC menu
real before and we can do it again
um
twice
kfb became real twice already
one said that uh anime convention was a
was a Crunchyroll or something was it
quenchable convention thingy and then at
the fourth Fest fourth Expo
um
right yeah that was really cool
I read the other day like a real big
misunderstanding but if I
I would assume that most people are not
misunderstanding this I got food
poisoning shut up no way did you
well it's not my responsibility
so listen uh because Mr standing segment
yeah they uh Crunchyroll back then this
was last year I think uh they labeled it
as kfp takeover or something like that
um which was just a label
there were no actual kfp members serving
or making the food right it was just
named like that but then I saw like
somewhere I think on YouTube in some
comments somebody was like you know
talking about how kfb even took over uh
like you know at a convention before and
made the food and this and that
and they like truly believed in it
uh
but it's not true
that's trueing
they just called it that
do you think many people misunderstood
and thought those were actually kfp
employees
and actually food made by us
I didn't even make the menu
they just like sent me yo we're doing
this and that and this and that I'm like
oh cool cool I love it absolutely
amazing
I love it
um
that's all I did
yeah that was my misunderstanding
segment
uh
phone game
so we're still discussing what to do
all right I think I'll go now maybe I'll
talk a bit more with never sound then
I'll sleep
can I just say like I honestly don't do
this normally
I don't know why even after whole talk I
quickly called her before her stream and
we were forced to end our conversation
because she had to stream
um
she may be waiting she wrote me a DM
ah
and mokuku wrote to me too
oh laughs
thank you so much for everything today
and for even coming to cheer us on it on
in our karaoke too it meant a lot to us
especially when you must be tired and
it's late in our time zone
it's usually like you know they share
like an account mostly for interactions
but I think even when mokuku writes to
me it's like whoever also kind of
writing it together
um but they always write like super long
paragraphs
we hope you had fun and that you get
some sleep soon too thank you so much we
hope to spread more and more whole life
love around the world as well as make
whole love English song altogether that
they're they're so uh wholesome
they're so wholesome
yeah because I watched all of their
karaoke
[Music]
it was a good way to pass some time
and they sang hinotoli and when I asked
me from I actually knew they were going
to sing it because they asked me for
permission to sing it and for the
instrumental and I sent them all of my
instrumentals I was like huh what you
want Hilo Tony instrumental you know
what here you get all of our
instrumentals so that in the future
you're always ready you could always
sing it whenever you want nothing is
holding you back have fun
all of them I think they would love to
sing a heart Challenger like it would
they like cute songs right they like
cute songs so they should sing Heart
Challenger yeah
[Music]
and I think they like my new songs that
are upcoming as well but I mean
everybody will everybody will there's
something in there for everybody in my
opinion hmm
yeah anyway
um yeah I love you guys
I love you guys okay
I love you guys I may be looking very
um cold-hearted right now and
Untouchable and all that you know with
these glasses and my cowboy hat
unreachable but the truth is I'm just
like you and I love you I'm just like
you um but I am a phoenix
um
I was a bit scared of going for this
week but in the end all went okay so now
next week
ah
I will work on the schedule after I
afterwards
[Music]
oh my God by the way I watched Pokemon
unite Championship quite a bit and uh
na1 and N A team one and then second
runner up with someone else I think
maybe an sea team and then uh third and
fourth was Japanese teams
Peru Peru in their own block had free
wins and they got pretty far um because
of those free wins but then yeah the
next fight they lost against the
Japanese uh group I think
but I was quite surprised there was some
some drama there going on with one of
the Japanese
uh groups they got like
two penalties
they got like two penalties and it kind
of escalated but if you want to know
more about it look up
um
uh what was that
foreign
[Music]
look that up
yeah
okay okay I need to go look here next
week of course of course of course maybe
twice
um
how do you get penalties in the video
game that's the thing it wasn't anything
during the game
it was
you know I think they called it bad
sportsmanship
for one of them at least
[Music]
um
and then the guy eventually ended up
not being part of the team anymore
Midway through and their Reserve had to
come in
and play the last two matches Maybe
and the penalty was like you know how
they were they were they would be free
matches if first one team wins and then
next round the other team wins then
there would be a third one right and
they had them start
twice with a
handicap uh as in they would start
so that the other team already won a
match
and they had to do that twice
oh my God so it wasn't a best of free
anymore it was the best of two
it's cool waiting for Cooper's not
waiting for me
no no no what do you mean what do you
mean
that's big oof yeah and they they won
through it because that means you have
to win twice in a row otherwise you're
out so they did it once they they won
twice in a row and they thought oh
penalty over let's go now a little bit
back to normal but then something
happened again because like they won
twice in a row right and you're really
freaking excited because you win in
conditions where you know it's very
stressful and pressuring and then so one
of one of the uh Japanese guys he gets
like really excited and apparently he
took off his headphones very
aggressively
I didn't even see that but yeah and
because of that
because of that they got another penalty
but then I was like waiting for the next
game to happen but they like had endless
waiting screens
and then suddenly came back and I think
they switched the order suddenly because
they had to discuss more I guess and
then
um you know I was I was looking at the
the guy's Twitter who took off the the
headphones
I was looking at updates because he was
like updating his Twitter quite a bit
um
and then uh they read okay we have a
penalty again for next match and then
like five minutes later he wrote oh it's
over and then five minutes later he
writes sorry I'm not in the championship
anymore
um
yeah he never like explained details
but he apologized and was like sorry
because of me this and that I am I'm
probably never gonna do this ever again
probably never gonna be uh part of this
stuff again they were going to be on
stage ever again this and that like
seemed pretty pretty dramatic
and then he got replaced
yeah
man
damn
and they still got pretty far that team
got fourth
um
no they played really good though
on the first the first penalty
you want to know why they got the first
penalty
they won a game and then after you win a
game you get interviewed on stage with a
translator
but apparently there was
miscommunication and they didn't show up
even though they were still in the same
room I guess
uh and they're still in the same Hall
um
and because they weren't there they got
a penalty but it's like weird because
they were saying yeah misunderstanding
they were saying misunderstanding
they didn't know it was happening or
something like that and then I saw on
Twitter that the guy replied to them on
Twitter the interviewer replied to them
sorry we were waiting for you on the
stage with a translator I'm sorry that
was so miscommunication apparently like
the he also didn't really know what
happened Viva blue you know
um interesting but they still did so
well even even with all those
setbacks
um
no
but it made me feel bad like I didn't
even know about this group before but
it made me cheer for them
like seeing how they were dealing with
so many penalties it made me want to
cheer for them even more
um
chewing on The Underdogs they weren't on
the dogs though they were so good yeah
they were so good
well it was exciting though
watching the world championship was fun
I will go now
you have to let me talk you know I
haven't had much time to talk in this
week you know
many many situations where I can't
tangent
how can I sleep without talking about
this
you know
yeah okay I'll go okay see you guys are
practically booing me off the stage
right now
okay okay okay
I go to sleep okay fine
then
uh I'm getting really tired
when we say happy dancing
[Music]
[Applause]
la la la
I think that's a German song or do you
guys recognize that
[Music]
it's not ragtime
it's sleep time
[Music]