[Music]
so
do
[Music]
hmm
do
[Music]
[Applause]
20.
why do i wow i hear myself so loud today
hello everyone
[Music]
what's up everyone happy new year not
yet not yet
i mean i guess uh i guess there's uh
a few countries where it's already
2021 but
not yet where i am which is uh why we're
doing the stream we're gonna wait
together
you're gonna spend and give me some
company because
otherwise i would be alone
[Music]
but
christmas i spent alone at home
streaming and new year's eve
i'm also spending alone streaming at
home
and
i uh i don't
i don't wha what what do we learn about
me
what does that what does that say about
hey i'm putting i'm putting some honey
into my tea right now i made some tea
because the only thing i
i don't even have alcohol to drink
because i just don't drink alcohol
[Music]
okay
you have us well yeah but like no that's
virtual
it would be nice to have someone you
know right next to me that would well
would be nice
would be very nice but it's okay
it's okay it's okay oh i don't know what
kelly is doing
i have no idea i kind of wanted them
to for for new year's eve in japan every
year
they uh they play
a program called gaki not sky
and i really want to watch it but i was
busy
i think it's already over anyway they uh
played before midnight
and i i think um it's already over
but i was streaming on the whole live
official channel
so i couldn't watch it anyway now i'm
not sure if i i have a tv
but i don't think i can uh receive
any of
[Music]
foreign is a really really funny program
they do it every they do it every every
year
at 24 hours gaki not sky
[Music]
neeta
everyone in japan knows this program
because
it's a tradition for everyone to to
watch it
at new year's eve it's a it's a
it's a a laugh laughing comedy program
maybe you've heard it before when they
go like hamada matsumoto
auto and then they get like
slaps on their butts
[Music]
i watched it a few times before but i
don't know about this here it's not
happening i guess but they i think i
think i should be able to catch like a
re
re-re-um
how do you call that when you when they
play it again and onto me
anyway what you guys know what i'm
talking
about don't you have you never heard of
that
it's 24 hours don't laugh like if they
laugh they get
they get like everyone yeah if they if
they laugh they get kicked
on their butts and every year they have
a different theme
[Music]
but
this year's famous las vegas wow
oh my god guys it's only 20 minutes left
oh my god okay guys so
uh first of all did you guys watch me
and kelly on the hello live english
official
live english hold on the official
channel
[Music]
my chat is going crazy oh my god
yay thank you guys it was um mostly just
us
watching videos of 2020 and talking
about what we think about it uh
and only in japanese but i'm glad you
watched it anyway thank you guys that
was fun
i was so happy to be invited to
that um thing
a lot of people yes because someone
asked it in the chat right now a lot of
people
thought that i was live translating to
kelly because i was looking over the
whole time to her
and apparently i don't know maybe i was
moving my mouth or something but i
wasn't i wasn't i wasn't
before the stream i was translating some
things to her when we were preparing it
[Music]
i was surprised because whenever kelly
speaks japanese
she often tends to call me kiara chan
and i was caught off guard when she did
that at the end of the stream she was
like
me and kiana tell them
[Music]
people even notice my reaction to that
you guys are watching too close
well yeah that was fun of course um
the the the the clip that there were
that there were three clips that each
couple
a couple uh chose themselves and the one
that me and callie chose
was the one with piccola but i want to
say
i want to say i mean obviously that was
my suggestion
but i want to say that callie didn't
have any suggestions in the first place
so it's not like i forced uh my
suggestion on to her
okay i just wanna i just wanna you know
make that clear
that i it was my suggestion yes but it's
not like i forced it on to her
but i know it's pretty obvious that it
was my suggestion because it was a
stream from piccolo
i
[Music]
when i had to think about um
a special stream of 2020 that really
stood out to me
uh my brain went like super blank
but the only thing i could really think
of at that moment
besides my own streams obviously
it was the piccolo stream where she told
her mom that she's a veterinarian
that was the only thing that came to my
mind uh
not that there is no other content with
my my mind just went
blank i couldn't think of anything else
and that was actually quite recent
reasons too
uh and yeah to me was very special it
wasn't it was
a huge moment yeah yeah i would agree
with that
um
also i just had a phone call with my mom
before this stream
she called me she's probably watching
the stream right now
hello mama she called me wanted to talk
to me
you know what i just found out about my
mom
this is unbelievable she said that one
month ago
she started playing
[Music]
minecraft and the first thing that comes
to my mind is oh okay yeah i guess we're
playing it together eventually
on stream because everyone is going to
ask for it
and she was like uh she was like super
proud and boasting about
that that she builds two really nice
houses and then she's gonna send me
screenshots
i did not expect i you guys know i told
you many times before you guys know that
my mom plays games
like mmorpgs like at least in the past
you did a lot
but i i did not expect her to play
minecraft
i did not think that she would enjoy
minecraft but she's uh playing it a lot
apparently
that is adorable isn't it it's that's so
cute
but yeah i guess i'm gonna play
minecraft
with my mom eventually there's probably
gonna be a collaboration one day
but i don't know maybe maybe only
only chat no voice chat no discord
because
i don't trust my mom when it comes to
saying things that you're not supposed
to say on stream
i don't trust her
so she will she if if we're ever gonna
do that thank you for the super chat
thank you for the red super chat if we
were ever going to do that
it would only be chad i think i don't
trust
[Laughter]
[Music]
whole live official channel appearance
did you guys watch the last
part of my uh collab with kelly of a way
out did you watch it guys it was on her
channel this time
uh we finished the game it was
yeah you did of course you guys did
thank you guys oh my god my chat goes
i'm watching it on the on the actual
chat window not here by the way
um it was
painful i actually cried
i did cry
i did cry at the end um
it was i was very angry
i was i was very angry man it was
i did not like it i thought you could
i thought there would be maybe a choice
to you know
have have both stay alive but
um
[Music]
it was very painful
uh so that was not played or anything i
was actually really upset
and i screamed there was um
the part where i think it was when when
we were reaching for
the gun i i screamed i started screaming
a lot at that moment and
never in my streams have i ever screamed
[Music]
never have i ever screamed so
i don't know so extremely out of the top
of my
lungs while i was screaming it was
actually
painful but it just came out of me i was
screaming so much that afterwards my
my my throat was actually really in pain
which is why i'm drinking a lot of tea
today i screamed
like i like i was really really like it
was about
that life or death like i was so
passionate about it i
it hurts so much it was so intense i did
not want to
like die
i have never screamed so
so i don't even know how to how to
describe that
that scream it hurts so much
and before that stream i did upload to
my
channel and the 2020 kiara highlight
video
did you guys watch that one as well so
busy
so much going on of course you watch
that as well
kiana rewind yay if you didn't
go watch it after this stream please
and i have uh commissioned someone
called nixon i have commissioned someone
to uh create a compilation uh
because first of all i was uh too lazy
to do it myself
second of all i wanted to help the
community by
uh commissioning the community and
giving something back to them
uh something called money
[Laughter]
and i think i thought that it would make
the community very happy if i would pay
them back with money
and involve them in such a project and i
also thought that it's probably a good
idea to have someone else make it
because
like obviously a channel that always
clips my my streams
would know uh what moments are special
so i
put a lot of trust into next set for
making a nice video
uh if you haven't seen it please watch
it out watch it out check it out watch
it
uh um please watch it it's uh from
it's supposed to be a 2020 review but
i've only been around for like almost
four months
so not not quite the 2020 rewind but
for me 2020 is pretty much only those
four months forget about everything that
was before that
it's only those four months okay
uh oh my god there's so many people
why is there's why is there so many
people
checking why is there so many people
watching
the countdown of me it's not it's
probably not even your countdown it's
probably for most of the people it's
only for me
[Laughter]
yeah everyone 10 minutes oh my god
that's um
[Music]
i've left so many things um
unfinished like i uh in 2020 so many
things i wanted to do i didn't do
uh so i'm a bit panicked that 2020 is
ending
but whatever thank you guys for the
memberships and thank you guys for the
super chats we will we will be reading
super chats after
words because uh tomorrow's stream
thankfully
starts uh in the evening time around
this time right now
a bit a bit earlier than the stream i
think
[Music]
tomorrow fourth generation fifth
generation
are doing like uh uh a relay
of everyone getting new outfits new
year's outfits
so i wanna
what time is that starting in japanese i
don't know like i want to wake up in
time for that and watch every little
stream of that
i think all together it's like six hours
or something nanjing has
when is it starting 1 30 p.m for
japanese center time
ah 1 p.m thanks guys
[Music]
oh i wanna watch it all okay one o'clock
that's good i often wake up at one
o'clock that's that's my
that's my usual time when i wake up
but oh my god for a way out today i was
barely sleeping
i i i got four hours of sleep because i
was so stupid i took a
super long nap yesterday regrets all
those regrets
and then i couldn't sleep at night and
then i only had four hours of sleep for
a way out but after a way out i i did
some things and then i went to sleep
for another three hours and then i did
the
the stream on the whole life official
channel and now we are here
so but all in all i'm okay i'm feeling
okay
we might be able to sleep somewhat early
today
busy woman yes business business woman
verb
ah i'm so excited for the new outfits
are you guys excited are you guys going
to watch it it's it's the 14
the full fourth generation and the fifth
generation
everyone except nina which is super sad
but then leonard john is getting
a new to explain what's hot what
happened there and then
john is getting a new redesign her whole
main outfit
uh is getting a redesign uh at the end
of january
so that's the reason why she's not
uh getting the new year's outfit
which is super sad but let's support her
i wanna i wanna support
so i hope everyone can support her
because nana i really i really really
like nina
and i want to support her so at the 31st
of january
i think is when she gets her new design
and i want everyone to go to her stream
and support her
i know
but i'm looking so forward to her new
outfit
ah i saw the silhouette and it already
looks really cute in this
silhouette she has like ribbons on her
legs i think
and a really short um fluffy puffy skirt
i'm really excited to see it oh my god i
hope that her main
uh color frame stays orange doll because
i'm also orange and
what would happen to odenzu if she's not
orange anymore
i'm looking forward to that i can't wait
for a new outfit
but first of all it's the new year's
outfits i think probably everyone is
going to get like a kimono
themed outfits japanese traditional
clothing
themed outfits i i want to see
whole live english i like that as well
one day but
um will that day ever come five minutes
oh my god
oh my god wait wait no no no no wait
what the [\h__\h]
why is it oh why is it almost 20 21 what
the hell
oh my god oh my oh my god
[Music]
oh my oh my god
oh my god oh my god
[Music]
my tea already cold enough to drink
it is and um one more thing
but there's more and more people coming
everyone comes to my countdown yay
happy do you guys see this
[Music]
i already reserved the premiere for this
i already reserved the premiere okay
uh it's already reserved on my channel
so go to
to go to your subscription box turn on
the notifications okay
turn on the bell okay because in eight
hours
eight hours from now this is coming out
okay
this very special maybe even more
special than the new year's countdown i
want everyone
to listen to it when it comes out and i
want everyone to be like oh my god
yes yes
it's i might be sleeping i don't allow
that
it's literally like only three minutes
it's just one song
so you are going to turn on your
mezamashi
your alarm clock uh for that time so
that you are awake for that premiere
everyone in the middle of the night i
don't give a [\h__\h] you are gonna be awake
and you're gonna watch this it's just
three minutes you can go back to sleep
right away
[Music]
i'm not really planning on being awake
for this
but you guys have to i mean maybe i will
see
i will try to i mean
[Music]
okay i was i was not awake for the for
the highlight video because i was sound
asleep i had to get a little bit of
sleep i got only a bit of sleep
i was not awake for that and i tried to
watch the
i wanted to re-watch the the live
premiere live chat but my youtube is
[\h__\h] around is it only for me
when i open that that live premiere live
chat for
uh the highlight video it doesn't load
for me
does it load for you guys for me it
doesn't work so i can't
see um what you guys were writing while
i was not there can someone test it out
but not right now okay not right now
priorities priorities
[Music]
oh my god oh my god oh my god okay guys
by the way
uh do you realize you you hear nothing
uh like no background noises that's
because i know this is surprising but
even because japan loves fireworks but
they're they don't do fireworks uh
uh they don't do fireworks for new
year's eve in japan
because they like it to be quiet isn't
that surprising because they really love
fireworks you know how
in in animes i know you guys are weeps
and you have seen
uh animes where there's like summer
festivals where the girls are in huge
yukatas and they walk around and then
they look at fireworks
i know you are reefs so you know those
those kind of stuff
um and they love fireworks
um but they don't do fireworks at
midnight which is i don't know
don't they do that in every other
oh my god
ah
[Music]
fine arts
oh my god it really says 2021 first of
january happy new years
happy new year oh thank you
in japanese we say um
[Music]
i can't believe it i can't believe it
happy new year
let me make the sounds of fireworks
because there's no fireworks in japan
for whatever reason
actually no wait let me play my my the
video i recorded last year
uh when i was okay listen to this here's
here's five eggs how much
you hear uh the ambulance too
[Applause]
did you hear that
thank you for your new year super chats
and everyone else too
uh oh my god it's 20 21 what
on earth is going on this is this is
insane let me drink my tea
my my first sip of my tea and 21 is 21.
ah um video that i just played
last year um let me tell you how i spent
new year's eve last year i
worked i had a shift
and i i worked i think until 11 p.m
and my roommate actually uh
works there as well and she came in
for the night shift uh so she started
her shift when i ended my shift
and then um the night shift
at that time was kind of empty because
every everyone was celebrating outside
i will not tell you too many details but
um so i go to my
i stay i actually stayed um
at at my workplace and went over to my
roommate
who just started to shift and was like
do you wanna you wanna
do you wanna do the thing and then we
did a thing that is
that's super secret thank you for the
super chat oh my god
don't tell anyone but we we worked in uh
i don't work there anymore but we worked
in a in a very big building
uh one of the biggest buildings um
in in the area and we went
to the top
uh how do you call that how how do you
call what do you call the top of a
building
do you call that the roof the roof we
went
up to the roof at midnight
and watched it was extremely cold
and we watched the this is what the
video was just from
we watched the the fireworks from the
view of the roof and um
it was uh in secret
we maybe did not possibly didn't
have permission to do that
but i have to say that was the most
amazing view
that i ever had for new year's uh
fireworks that was that was
amazing that was the best view in my
city that i could have
ever had i was that was really really
nice i took a lot of
videos and photos back then but it was i
was basically watching
the fireworks from above and they looked
so so so so so much smaller
than looking at them from below
they looked actually what i said i said
it was the best view ever
that i had for new zealand but when i
think about it
the the fireworks themselves didn't look
so
special because they
looking at them from above was a little
bit lame
they didn't even look that big
anyway we were pretty pretty high up
there and then she went back to work and
then i went back home
to my kitty cats but that was a very
special
very special new year's eve and now here
i am
sitting not not on the roof of of one of
the highest buildings in my city
but i'm sitting in my rundown house
which is falling apart
sitting in front of my pc and talking to
a bunch of people who are not actually
there
and just drinking my tea
that is quite a different kind of new
year's eve
casper i don't know about casper i have
to say i heard him
uh when was that i heard him in the
night
uh doing a little bit i thought but like
really quiet i think he might actually
be dying because
um i don't hear him for 24 hours but
then i hear him like
a little bit normally he would be like
super noisy always but i heard you like
i i told you recently he's been i don't
know
he's been very very quiet super super
quiet
there's so much so many things i want to
talk about oh my god but um
yeah so what time is it for you guys
everyone
[Music]
what time is it 11pm 10 11 p.m
where are you 10 a.m
or what australia is what
two a.m four p.m
oh my god so fast 5 p.m eight days
four am four pm ten am
so many numbers
[Music]
so many of you are living in the past
and i
am living in the future
i'm living in the future
[Laughter]
but for some european countries i think
uh wow wow world i think for germany
and so on i think this is coming out at
midnight
am i right or am i right because eight
hours this is eight a.m
for me it's an eight i 8 hours time
difference so it should be midnight
are you guys even you guys might not be
able to watch it huh
damn it i'm i'm so smart with my time
scheduling i'm just so smart and doing
such a good job
stop it you better watch it right away
after you did your countdown and your
new year's kisses whatever
anyway um
i talked about the official channel i
talked about the club video i talked
about the
its outfits tomorrow i talked about wow
wow
world and i talked about how i spent new
year's last
i i'm looking at my i actually made my
own uh post-it note i'm looking at my
post-it notes
so the only thing i don't wanna i don't
want this stream to be too long okay i
wanna go into superchat reading and
have it really that simple and that
short but uh i want to talk a little bit
about
2021 goals and stuff
new year's resolution i suppose yep
um
yeah and by the way i had a really nice
members only stream yesterday if you
missed it and you remember
you're welcome to check it out we had
some fun we talked a lot about
2020 and all we we went through every
single stream that i did
and talked about it in detail and that
was fun we also watched
the the there are some whole live
english clippers
that did a whole live english rewind
really like 11 channels uploaded
clips that are rewinds of a whole live
english members streams
that was fun we watched that together
with them together with the members as
well
thank you guys for the super chat thank
you guys thank you thank you thank you
thank you
so anyway that was talking about 2020
and but i want to talk about 2021
[Music]
um
i didn't think about this i should have
written something down
should have written a letter or
something um
the counter yeah because it it this is
uh it's after midnight it's counting
this is the actual time now it's
10 minutes past midnight
yeah it's already over it's uh first
january
2021. um
so well 2020 is over and 2021
is beginning
uh well what is my goal for 2021
my goal is i want to
i want to obviously continue streaming
uh for her life i want to stay in the
whole life
and and and be part of whole life
english
for as long as possible um and i want to
i want to release more music
i want to release a new song maybe
in february
and possibly i want to release a whole
album
in 2021 a full album of course
so that i can one day give a concert a
solo concert maybe
and have more you know repertoire when i
perform at anime conventions that's a
goal for me
i want in 2021 i want to be invited
to an anime convention anywhere in the
world
be it europe be it america i want to be
a guest at an anime convention and
perform live there and meet you guys
probably for a screen but still good
enough
[Music]
yeah and i think you all know
that i am leaving japan in two months
time approximately and
i am personally looking forward to that
because
i miss my cats very much and some of my
friends
and my family but most of all i miss my
cats
and i also miss the food and everything
i mean japan is amazing and
i love i love japan i've um
i've spent a big a big part of my life i
spent
in japan
[Music]
i miss my family and um
generally i miss a lot of things from
home but
yeah obviously japan won't go anywhere
correct
japan won't go anywhere so even when i
move back to my home
in 2021 soon
the time is passing so quickly thank you
guys for the super chat oh rainbow
a rainbow nice one
good job thank you
beautiful thanks for the membership too
yeah so even what was i saying
what i wasn't saying damn it
damn it what was i saying what was i
saying guys
japanese oh yeah yeah okay okay thanks
so even when i move back to my country
i'm planning to go back to japan many
times
to visit kelly and to do some things you
know i wanna
i wanna visit japan every now and then
um first of all will probably be
whenever
if it's ever gonna happen whenever we
get a 3d
uh version of ourselves that would
probably be the next time when i will
visit japan
and after that after that once that
happens
i want to go back to japan like every
two months maybe
uh so that i can do 3d streams every two
months
and visit cali every two months so
it's gonna be an expensive hobby but
worth it
but for now i'm just really looking
forward to finally get back home
because actually this whole year 2020
i was planning on going home like three
times
to visit my cats the only purpose
was going to me to visit my cats
i wanted to do it three times no matter
how expensive it would be
but i ended up going at zero times so
i i i wonder if my cats forgot me
if they still remember me you know i'm
pretty worried about that but
i am it should be fine i'll i'll go back
and oh i reunite with my kitty cats and
i'll be the happiest person ever
i think i can personally like there's
just
i'm really happy ever since i
there is one thing in my heart that i
feel so strongly
is missing and that is my cats
even though i'm so happy with her life
[Music]
there's this one thing but i think once
i get back my cats
i can finally reach full happiness
[Music]
soon yep i think my cats are going to
the
uh guests uh a lot in my streams and
meowing a lot thank you for the super
chat thank you for the pinky
thank you hmm
[Music]
and besides that what else
i want to
[Music]
what are you guys goals what's
everyone's uh
resolutions for 2021 tell me
mi no no mo quila
tell me
new job good luck on that
survive what why is there so many people
saying that what the hell
uh what uh start learning japanese
if i didn't get a better job i want to
learn music production become a
vegetable oh
survive survive survive uh
finnish university
[Music]
good grades hashtag hashtag yes
to never go into the usual room drinking
routine get back to me in japanese going
to japan at the end of the year oh
i think that should work draw more fan
and potential yes
[Music]
do a single push-up
travel japan that was my goal too this
year it didn't happen
work more in programming
[Music]
you didn't
get the rtx serious free zero
to see caddy and kiara wedding mm-hmm
watch bloom live oh yeah that's
happening in in
february get a healthier lifestyle
oh yes that's also one of my goals
because
in japan uh especially especially since
i joined whole life
i didn't have much time thank you guys
for the super chats thank you
what birthday oh happy birthday your
birthday is the first of january happy
birthday
well the first uh what what am i saying
the thing is um
ever since i joined the whole live i've
been kind of busy and
and also other reasons but i barely have
been cooking i
actually haven't been cooking at all
maybe i cooked once in the past
two or three months
one time one time
so and everything else was ubereats or
frozen food
or something from the convenience store
that i warmed up
so i want to in 2021 once i moved back
to where i came from
once i move back i want to cook for
myself again
learn a few new things to cook
cooking stream yes we can do that
i think we might do that eventually
although i probably miss all the amazing
ubereats options and i will miss the
convenience stores in japan because
where i live
there are no convenience stores
[Music]
i could make my own country where i can
have everything that i
i want from every country i can combine
it and it will be one amazing super
country
i wish i could do that um
[Music]
i mean there's supermarkets but on
sunday they're all closed
on sunday there's nothing and also
during the week
they close like they they're not open 24
hours
so basically in japan
doesn't matter what day it is doesn't
matter if it's a holiday or whatever
it's everything is always open 24 hours
which is amazing
i mean i feel sorry for the people who
work there but that's amazing
we don't have that where i come from
things
close on holidays things close on
sundays
what was that about what
what would it take you to get to eat
hachima's cooking
i mean if if she would actually
follow a recipe and cook something
proper it's not that hard then i would
eat it maybe
then maybe i would eat it but right now
i'm planning a collab with hatama
and where i cook for her
that's the plan but uh
i don't know if it's gonna happen for
sure because i don't wanna really cook
in my house but i guess it's gonna
happen probably i'm gonna cook something
actually edible
i'm going to cook something that you can
actually eat okay
[Music]
um
yeah offline collab of course because i
have to cook and she has to eat it so
i think she'll be visiting me actually
she'll come over to my place i hope she
doesn't put casper into the dish
[Laughter]
i don't know yet what to cook it should
be something simple because
i don't have a big kitchen and we're
gonna be streaming like in front of my
computer so we'll be cooking in front of
my computer so i'm bringing
i'm gonna bring like one of these um how
do you call them
portable portable
uh stoves stop stoves
hot plates whatever i don't know what
what you call them
i'm gonna put it in front of my pc and
then we're gonna cook there don't give
her ideas
yep i shouldn't have said that you would
probably be up for that
[Laughter]
a portable stop stove is that what you
actually call it a portables
great what i don't know
something that you just plug in and you
can put it anywhere and cook anywhere
i i think you guys know what i'm talking
about right
okay so yeah my new year's resolution
is uh taking um
more time to cook for myself
and move back to my country reunite with
my cats
achieve ultimate happiness continue
working for her life
release a new song in february release
the whole album
eventually become 3d
and then visit japan every two months
to make 3d streams
[Music]
am i forgetting about something i think
so yeah that's pretty much my goals
ah alrighty
so i think without further ado
it has already been one hour anyway i
think i'm gonna start reading super
chats
while having a lot of talks with you
okay
[Music]
so
i hope that also in 2021 maybe
kyogre can get a new outfit too
today all the older senpais are getting
new outfits
so i hope kiaya can also get a new
outfit
eventually i have absolutely no idea
what i would imagine what what kind of
outfit i would want to have i have
absolutely no idea
um so i i will leave it to
whoever is working on it eventually and
i will let it happen eventually it's not
i'm just gonna let it happen i don't i
don't even know
but one by one step by step chicken suit
no no
well i guess we can also uh get can
should we leave the new you count down
here
so people know it's over while i'm
reading the super chats
because i'm gonna go over to readings
super tacos wait wait wait
a swimsuit would be nice yeah eventually
a pumpkin suit huh
why because i'm orange stupid
what you know what i have to say to that
you know what i have to say
that
[Music]
did not deny
no way a dandelion
[Music]
traditional clothing from australia
can you read um the sentence
this is the time since friday first
january 2021
i'm sorry but a few people ask this
question and i wonder
can you can you read that
i have already i am in the future
for me the countdown is already over
but it is now it is after midnight
do you understand sorry sorry i'm not
trying to roast this person in
particular i'm trying to roast everyone
who is asking this question
is
[Music]
[\h__\h]
what i just said something in japanese
so
that doesn't need translation i will not
i will not translate myself i refuse
i refuse i refuse i refuse to translate
myself
[Music]
okay guys are you ready for the super
chat
we stopped at where did we stop
[Music]
ah thank you so i did read the shadow
face streams or i did not read the
shadow first super chats
did i or did i not
did i stop right before them
i did not okay okay so we have to read
shadowverse
minecraft and everything after that okay
that's gonna be fun
it's gonna take a while
if you would like to hang out with me
until i'm done with them i would be very
happy
ah wait let me write in my in in the
whole live english discord
happy new year
from the future
and then i post my smug face to some
in the future and some of the girls are
not
in the future
happy new year
all right shadow very super chat let me
put it let me put a thumbnail here
so that you know if you're watching the
archive you know
where the hell i am right now um
[Music]
nails uh shadow verse
nice thumbnail isn't it what a cute face
[Music]
and so we will be reading that let me
get rid of the wow
super chat reading let's get started
yay it's so weird it doesn't feel like
it's 20 21 it's so weird
it doesn't feel like it's 20 21 but okay
let's get started
[Music]
both sent me super chats for new years
[Laughter]
thank you
[Music]
wait a second
the baby's name changed
you know you know the baby which usually
always changed the name every
every day to one day less
and it said a crying baby
[Music]
crying baby that dies in a few days
and it now says
[Music]
babies the baby is gone
maybe maybe come on come on send me your
usual super chats
tell me you're still alive
[Music]
this baby has been super chatting me for
a month every day
several times and each day in the first
first
day it was i think like uh crying
in the night crying baby in japanese in
the night crying baby that dies in
in 31 days or something like that and
each day
and each day it has been one
one last day and we were worried so much
about the baby and now the day has
finally come
and the baby is gone the name says
farewell farewell crying baby
the baby by the way has a twitter i want
to check it out
where are you singing let me check out
the twitter what happened to the twitter
[Music]
is that it
is that the baby it always tweeted me
but it's kind of
oh
[Music]
i don't understand the last tweet
actually it's still tweeting
i don't know is that the baby
it looks happy on twitter
[Laughter]
oh no
baby
[Music]
[Laughter]
i think the baby maybe will be revived
and eventually returned to us
anyway
of course it's dama what the hell
ah
[Music]
you you uneducated wrong taste excuse me
excuse me not paddle it's
bottle room uneducated weeps
[Music]
i'm talking about white cross wig sauce
whatever you call it
wickudosa is an anime card game
card game anyway card game slash anime
patrick
foreign
[Music]
please tell me i'm not the only one
suffering from piano withdrawal syndrome
i think that was um when i
the shadow first stream was after a one
day
break was it is that why everyone was
going crazy
that i that i was that i was gone for
[Music]
what for the fto muramasa
happy new year whatever you mean i
brought you luck
for for fgo or what do you mean thank
you for the red super chat
i'm glad i could help
[Music]
and i already uh back then uh wish you a
happy birthday for someone else but once
again happy late birthday it's really
late now but
happy late birthday
[Music]
so
can't believe i'm going to hatch for my
accent
[Music]
the red super chat
yeah saying it's my birthday ooh
and i want to say thanks to the best
boss ha uh
slash imaginary girlfriend in the world
you collabing with aculator is a present
for me oh i'm happy to hear that
that's great i hope you enjoyed the
collaboration
thank you thank you thank you happy
birthday belated but
still i hope you had a great birthday
i hope you enjoyed the the collaboration
thank you so much for your support
i am happy to be your boss and imaginary
girlfriend
which is one of the one of the key
promises
of a membership thank you thank you
also still thank you guys for the super
chats that are still coming in thank you
thank you thank you is that a red super
chat
are are you in the chat and can't tell
me if that is a red super chat because i
don't understand
this this currency
it look i think it is is it
i'm sure you are in the in the chat yes
it is okay i'm perfect
good that you are here
gotcha fun and congrats on 650k subs oh
thank you thank you for the red super
chat thank you for supporting my gaza
funds i did
actually not spend any money yet on
shadowverse so
i am i'm not
spending any money on that just yet
[Music]
yet no no no no never going to happen
never going to happen
anyway the money will be spent
wisely brazilian
if you still have a credit card you
could borrow mine
let's see some pulls i never really
railed on this game but there's a ton of
art from other games that i wouldn't
mind seeing again don't get too addicted
thank you yeah i have spent a lot of
money on
a different gotcha game called
um architect i've spent a lot of money
on that one
but i'm not planning to spend my money
on shadow verse okay
no no no no no vigorously eleven
thousand tiago tdm thank you
improve your
[Music]
i can only use money on real physical
goods
i i only use my oh well that's a that's
a that's that's probably
good that's probably good
[Music]
thank you for the support
thank you for the red super chat big big
mike
thank you lately happy christmas kiana
my dear phoenix you are always shiny and
smiley
your optimism always encourages me feel
sad for your homesickness
me too hope your whole life family and
kp staff can relieve your homesickness
oh they do they do
please stay safe and keep your sweet
smile love you thank you that's a very
sweet message
indeed um whole life does help me to
keep my mind off of the homesickness
but soon as i said i will achieve
true and pure happiness because soon
i will be back in my country
and i will probably also miss japan
and then i'll be like oh i want to go
back to japan
[Music]
foreign
thank you for the red super chat hey
kara i wrote a message with
actual text this time nice hmm you got a
kiss for that
i just want to say i love your streams
even though i can never catch them all
live
sometimes also here's some gotcha funds
for your category
i don't have a gaza addiction i don't
have a gotcha addiction
but thank you for your support and thank
you for the kind message
it will be used wisely i will invest it
in a good way thank you so much
thank you thank you soon and i'm glad
you like my streams even if you can
mostly watch them in archives only but
really thank you
sure you don't completely believable
it's true what the hell
what the hell
why are you doubting me
[Music]
i don't spend money on gotcha games
anymore i don't do that i don't do such
things
[Music]
i'm literally not doing it though i
haven't spent money on
a phone game on the gaza game in months
wait whatever don't believe it this is
ridiculous i don't understand why you
wouldn't believe it it's true
stop it
raven 201 trevor g dankeshen watching
you stop me from railing on gotcha
glad glad to know i'm is inadvertently
still wailing for you attention oh yes
you are
also congrats i totally never i totally
believe that you could actually win
i never doubted you for a second dot dot
dot
[Music]
thank you i gotta say i was slightly
interested when i saw cute anime girls
and i saw extreme carrot and became
extremely interested
what the hell was that extreme carrots
what a weird character but it's a fun
game i really like the shadow louise i
want to play more
mr queen i love you wishing you the best
in the new year to come with the
kikiriki gang and holiday season thank
you for all you do thank you thank you
[Music]
this is my first time watching a youtube
streamer keep up the great job
wow thank you your first
time watching a youtube streamer and you
sent me a pink super chat thank you very
much for your support
i hope you enjoyed it and i hope you're
still watching
[Music]
h what up thank you
now
yeah i love you thank you i love you too
what does it mean when you say kikiniki
and duncan oh wow
you don't know well well kiki is my way
of saying hello to you guys but
it is um it's my greeting it has a
background but uh
it's just my greeting okay and then
danke chun is german for
um thank you
is german so i say uh thank you after
each name
by saying thank you soon after each name
takes monkey kitten spider and then
night owl
oh my god yeah that was a big one darren
wait thank you for the 500
red super chat
thank you with the text saying the
following
uh a mere three and a half months ago
she appeared
oh is it is this a poem a majestic
bird brilliant even to the sun on the
eve of one of my darkest nights
she sang the beautiful song lion on
color okay oh i did
a friend knowing my darkness threw me to
her
oh she has since brought me light hope
and cheer as my birthday passes i thank
the sweet bird
for sharing her heart yeah okay i i do
remember reacting to your birthday
at least life but i couldn't thank you
yet properly for the super chat
thank you so so much for your support
it's interesting that
um a friend showed you my stream
and then you apparently became a fan
because i was singing
lion thank you thank you lion is a
really fun song to sing always
so i'm glad that that was the one that
dragged you into the kiara hole
you are welcome thank you so much i hope
that your birthday was nice
and that you spent it with someone maybe
and ate some cake hopefully
and uh thank you so much for watching my
streams thank you so much for being part
of kfb
thank you i really really appreciate it
way too generous but thank you so much
honestly i don't know what to say but
thank you soon
looking forward to having you in kfp
in 2021 as well happy new year and happy
birthday
jake monkey thank you soon meister thank
you and also with a red super chat
thank you saying your place
show potential yes see it wasn't that
bad
perhaps you were an egyptian pharaoh in
your past life i don't know why you
would get that idea
hope you get your deal list all because
of yugioh okay now i finally get it
[Music]
i was wondering about this when i first
saw that super chat and now i
finally understood it oh
because of yugioh
10 more minutes um no
okay okay i'm gonna get rid of this
because people are so confused
my countdown is already over
oh my god
oh for a different country you mean ah
that is quite possible that is that is
indeed possible
yeah people don't realize that my
calendar was going up
actually i'm also i don't have anything
to drink right here damn it i ran out of
drinks
and my throat is hurting is it okay if i
go quickly uh to get something to drink
my my my throat is like
what the what is that super chat
[Music]
thank you for the pinky i'll go get some
water i'll be right back
water water and need some water get me
some water
[Music]
oh no no no no no no don't don't stop
stop stop
i'm already back stop flushing don't do
it i'm gonna i'm not gonna read those
flush chats
i'm not reading them i'm not reading
them
[Music]
i only got my water i only got my one i
told you i just
literally went down to grab a bottle of
wine i'm trying to open it right now but
i'm too weak
there you go
[Music]
um
don't use my name in
[Music]
went away in the middle of that super
chat oh my god i'm so sorry you were you
continued writing hope you got your
duelest memories back
and i'll see you in master rank someday
i wonder if that day will come but um
thank you oh you're welcome you're
actually there i'm so happy when people
are actually uh there when i read the
super chats because
that means that me reading them is not
going to waste because they're actually
like
picking up you know like like it's it's
like they're it's like they
didn't order a takeaway order at a
restaurant
and the takeaway order took three days
or actually it didn't even tell you when
to come back
but you're still actually there for
for the takeaway i i respect that
thank you for picking up your order of a
super chat reading
thank you thank you thank you thank you
shirt
six minutes left until it is new year's
where
in which country
cea singapore philippines melissa oh
coolio nicer
almost there ooh all right i'll
celebrate with you i only wanted to
celebrate my own countdown but okay
while we're at it
tell me when it's happening i'll
continue reading so meister
thank you for your support i do want to
continue playing shadow verse so
please give me advice
jake gets
and had never watched it before either
even still it was really fun watching
you play this game just uh don't get
addicted to kacha
don't worry about me i have i don't feel
the need
to gotcha and even if
um i'm i can control myself
i can thank you soon
[Music]
ah
it's not a cute thumbnail i know
christmas was already over but i wanted
to
use uh that art anyway
because it's cute and it was still close
enough to christmas christmas
cute thank you for your lovely items
all right let's continue with that
[Music]
monkey looking for the top thank you
soon
i know exactly who you are you changed
your name
well i know that this is kazuma killu
i know it
and i it's funny how you guys are
laughing
i literally just recognize it because of
the
something i don't know the profile
picture
[Laughter]
i know you guys the people who always
send super chats i remember them
by name and by the peripheral picture so
when the name changes or or
when when the name stays but the profile
picture changes i sometimes i'm like
hey you changed your profile picture
why did you change it what the hell what
were you trying to accomplish with that
what my lady would you please grace us
with your bird cry at the end of the
countdown to welcome the new year
you mean your personal new year
you're sending us dollars what's your
i already i already uh welcomed the new
year
but hey here's a countdown in one minute
so
i can't i can give you a bird cry for
that one
[Music]
one second let me prepare something
one second
okay i'm ready
uh 20 seconds left four
uh cea countries i prepare
i prepared for this red super chat from
high dow hey dao thank you soon by the
way
i prepared my battle cries okay five
four
three two one
[Music]
[Applause]
come on
[Music]
[Applause]
never done that in a while
[Music]
that's that's pretty much my my way of
doing fireworks
so it's a great way to get fruit
those are my bird cries
it's like fireworks happy new years
everyone whoever
uh just came into 2021 you're welcome i
live in the future i welcome you in the
future
[Music]
yokoso happy new year
once again
[Music]
welcome to the future
[Applause]
welcome to the future at it
[Laughter]
[Music]
you have successfully
entered the year 2 0
2 1 what would you
like to do first press
a or marry
kiana press b
or eat fried chicken
or press c
for
[Music]
getting raped by cali ope
choose now
[Music]
abc is not a valid choice
please choose again
[Music]
a c or a b
is not a valid choice please choose
again
c a is not a valid choice
please choose again bc
is not a valid choice please choose
again
you have to choose one letter
for [\h__\h] sake
eight okay you shall receive
that whatever that was i forgot it
[Music]
oh
high-tech bird
all right continuing back to the super
chats
looking for the top functions
[Music]
i have something in my throat
drops but thank you for asking
happy new year thank you happy new year
to youtube guys happy new year happy new
year
happy new year guys it's already uh one
hour too late for me but happy to
new year to everyone who just had a
happy new year
[Music]
anyway going back to super chats
or pink pink how do i say your name
thank god
also what the hell obito i am a winner
you're not telling me to go out of my
own chat what the hell
syracuse thank you for the red super
chat
all right then get out of bed and take
your toy money with you very good sirek
someone finally is on my side thank you
sarik for protecting
your leader takana
danke finally
someone who follows me
and doesn't even think about going to
the dark side
[Music]
don't go to the dark side i am
your mother i have
hatched all of you little [\h__\h]
you are not going to leave me for the
dark side
you better not understand
understand
i am your mother
[Laughter]
oh my god those
i can't
sorry wreck anyway
[Music]
oh these are partially the members only
ones so uh
just so you know guys partially
there are some of the members only
stream super chats in here because it
kind of
overlapped okay
[Music]
oh my god people just don't stop
thank you guys thank you for your
support
elias ewan patrick chandang mono chronic
dancing personally
it's a mystery thank you uh patrick
chandan kitchen
dynamite thank you for the red super
chat
my mental health takes a hit in december
and it isn't help
uh helped by finding out my one cat has
cancer
that's [\h__\h] horrible
oh can you save a cat with cancer
or are cats not like
can you can you say the cat who has
cancer
[Music]
sometimes
i hope this person's cat is okay
oh man every cat deserves to be alive
forever
why are cats not eternal that's not fair
can i give my eternalism
to a cat i i
i will accept dying forever
if i can give my eternal eternalism to
some
cat and i don't know if they actually
want it but
uh anyway
uh your streams and other content has
made this love so much better than it
has then it's been in years thank you
for doing everything you
that you do love your kiana keep up the
great work thank you thank you
thanks for the sweet message i'm glad we
could help me and the other halloween
girls but
please please let me know if your cat
feels better
please let me know when that happens
thank you for your support thank you for
your generosity
there you go i'm your cat now even if
your cat is gone i'll be your cat
i'm a good cat i can be your cat
also we have a cat in kfb
we have a the kfp cat you can have her
just take take care
we have a few cats they belong to kfp
but you can have her
[Music]
wait i'm the kfp cat yeah
i'm giving you away don't you wanna
don't you wanna be given away
i i mean this is not a matter of
discussion but
anyway let's let's continue no
discussion
[Music]
and bye bye i didn't agree to this
well it was never matter of agreeing you
were you are the kfp cat so
you have given your catness to the kfp
why what did you think you were doing
okay just kidding i could never give you
away i could never give you away your
mind forever
stay i was just kidding i was just
kidding i take it back i'll take it back
my cat my cat okay
jenna from koslovski looking for the top
thank you
[Music]
forever that's right forever forever
never forever
oh my god
i forgot that i still have the robot
infected
i only wanted to reverb an echo
forever and ever
[Music]
yes but there's no there is no reason
it's not scary nothing scary about that
at all nope
what time is it for you right now one
hour and 13 minutes after midnight
[Laughter]
as i answered someone i didn't ask you
guys i answered someone's question i
didn't ask
you guys
[Music]
um
i like your funny words magic chickens
shut up buy a novel player danke sharon
soraki blade thank you
attention all
attentional general picorin has come out
of retirement to sound
the call to arms the deaths of precious
kp employees at the hands of ina and
cali will not
stand viva
that's a very nice speech thank you
what do i hear inna and callie killed
precious kfb employees what the
[\h__\h] what that
why do i only now learn about this
we want justice we want justice we will
not accept this
who has slaughtered my employees
i do not forgive and i do not forget
you do that
[Music]
thank you thank you guys i know i can i
can rely on you in the important moments
you're always here for me
my lovely lovely chicken employees
[Music]
2021 starts with a war yep there and
there we go
[Music]
yes what i just said in japanese uh is
that i
um since i played momotetsu with solar
senpai aki senpai
and and um and then it i was thinking
of playing momo tatsu uh on my channel
and inviting
ina because her japanese is good enough
to understand the game
but i was thinking of inviting
two other certain girls and make the
whole collab english
we will be playing a japanese game but
it's easy to understand i will and i
will i will explain and
um will play it with english english
speaking members
but i want and i want to play it with
ina
so i invited ina to uh
do that with me
but i'm still thinking about the details
and who to invite i have i have a i have
a
idea of who to invite but i don't want
to 100 percent
um go for it yet
i want to think about it a little bit
more and then we will have momo tetsu in
english
it's a game that will never come out in
english but it's easy to understand so
we'll play it in english
on my channel by explaining you guys
what is going on
so you better listen in the beginning
and then and then try to follow the game
as much as you can
[Music]
the wall street journal is reporting
that kfp is liquidating assets
after the mobile texas fiasco can you
answer
allegations that we're bankrupt
[Music]
however it's just allegations there's no
truth
there is no truth about that
it's just rumors
i know where to get my money once it's
been taken
away from me i know how to quickly get
it back
[Music]
just trust me just trust me
stop taking photos stop taking photos
this is not a press conference
happy new year always remember that i
love you and i wish you the happiest
years to come thank you
as a friend what the hell dagger
stop stop taking photos
no no no
no
no no
no this is how ryzer feels oh
[Music]
nine nine
i refuse
no oh oh stop
okay are they gone are they gone
are the paparazzi is gone i can come
back up
there's one no
no no no no no no go away
stop i don't have time for this i don't
have time for this
ah
who where i need to read my i need to
read my super chats
go away
justin
[Music]
[Laughter]
stop
okay whatever i guess i'm just so famous
i have to face it it's my destiny
i have to face it
i'm just so famous everyone wants photos
of me
yes take photos
hello yes yes take more photos of me
take the good side take my chocolate
side
take as much as you want
uh okay continuing
too many tangents today thank you
account name black casper the friendly
kfb ghost
they um i can't count past four
wait what is it
[Music]
um i can't cloak past fully
but i got outside it was nice to have
attack again
but i thought i saw a big fishy
following me
i think i'll say home where it's safe
and cozy and what's kia
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you casper i still don't really
know what happened with casper
i told you guys the other day i told you
the story
that he's like kind of um very silent
these days like normally in 24 hours he
would
every hour he would make a lot of noise
but recently
in 24 hours i don't hear him at all and
um
i did hear him last night still and in
24 hours i didn't hear him before that
and then i heard him in the night before
that
a little bit but very tiny don't know so
i don't know i don't know what's going
on
but he he must be still alive because i
heard him last night
hmm casper is giving birth
how long does it take for a mouse to
give birth
let me check that how
how long does it take
for a mouse to
uh have babies
what another not exactly my question to
finish labor
what
[Music]
i mean i mean i guess maybe maybe the
mouse is pregnant maybe casper was a
girl all along
and uh maybe he's pregnant right now
and that's why it's so quiet is that a
possibility
[Music]
huh i'm very curious
pregnant for 20 days um
we will see i'm actually happy that
casper is not dead and i'm also happy
that he's more quiet than usual
because uh he's he was so noisy i was
like it was freaking me out
to a point where i was always like
casper
and now he's uh mostly silent so i don't
know what happened
i don't know i don't know if casper is a
girl or a boy
we will have to ask casper that
anyway duncan casper just take your time
you can as long as you don't get inside
you can enjoy it living in my ceiling
creepy takishan katy mcdonald cherry
dude
eric pj pj davis thank you
oh that's jordan duncan aj baldwin
doing your part to help the cave
pre-songs nicer
[Music]
thank you
well i hope not
i hope not happy new year happy new year
thank you guys thank you guys thank you
thank you thank you
thank you so much happy new year to you
too
[Music]
hopefully you'll all stick around in
2021 as well and don't leave me
casper laying eggs she doesn't lay eggs
stupid
congrats casper have you seen this
message some of the kfc christians hold
for you the biggest special party ever
shut up
[Music]
foreign thank you so much for your
support
what
[Music]
oh man
feeling dank
you guys always pick up on that i don't
even realize it when i say that anymore
i don't
i don't even notice
[Music]
m
was it really necessary to write an
english translation for
the two sentences that i said for that
german super chat
was not really necessary
[Music]
oh i got special pictures of kelly you
don't mind sharing do you oh you're
giving to give it up to me give them to
me
sharing is caring
jaywalker dankeshen bronx thank you and
thank you for the red super chat bronx
brandos diaz
what is it with these red super chat
just
writing some greetings what the hell
does this have some meaning or
punkish and bronx dias i suppose
happy new year by the way thank you for
the support
uh yeah i i don't understand
why but was talking in other languages
really interesting
interesting
what do you wish from 2021 i pretty much
already talked about that
uh right after uh i reached midnight
so you're welcome to watch the archives
but basically i want to make music
i want to stay in home life and i want
to cook for myself
more because i've only only eaten like
frozen food and [\h__\h]
[Music]
h5 thank you in action lunchbox thank
you
sword nine times
[Music]
i love your energy keeping you thank you
thank you i'm happy to hear that
equivalent exchange albedo
looking for the top 10 kashin er roy the
big boy duncan
security twinkle thank you
[Music]
yellow yellow thank you for the red
super chat hello
are you are you here are you here are
you here to pick up your
your uh take away food you take away
dankeshan
i was winning i'm always winning
thank you for your kind support yellow
as
always you've been around supporting me
so kindly and generously
gender gender gen generously yes
something sounds wrong gender genor
gender ros gene
i'm right it's correct oh it sounds
weird to me
well thank you thank you
[Music]
i think kfp is being investigated by the
australian federal police
due to allegations of heinous war crimes
and tax how do you answer that
how was it i have no idea what's up what
accent that was
i was trying to make it sound even
british or
australian british
or attention mate i think kfp
is being investigated
anyway i don't know man
[Music]
australian frederick polish
they probably don't talk like that that
sounds irish
nice it's just
[Music]
sounds scottish amazing do they do they
do like this where even though it's
supposed to be
do they say in those instances
allegations of heinous war crimes and
texturation
how do you answer to that
do we really sound like that i don't
know
no they don't god damn it
do a canadian what how how would i know
what a canadian accent
sounds like
[Music]
i have no ideas
i have literally no idea
[Music]
you say a boot a boot ah
okay well you made me curious okay oh
canada accent
okay let's go what do you got to offer
to me
a boot all the boot canadian accents
watching youtube
a boat a boot a boot away
a boot a boot
but everything else sounds normal
[Music]
house we'll say it again
house and down and ruined and soothed
tongues in their mouths
mouth is normal move i mean let's
probably not move
mount moof
[Music]
both
don't don't worry about it
[Music]
being a mom is not a boot routine
well everything besides a boot sounds
pretty normal
[Music]
they're just trolling you canada isn't
real what the hell
okay how about australian accent
let me hear what that sounds like
apparently in my head it sounds like
that
uh how to do an australian accent fast
okay go
blah blah blah
[Music]
oh my god stop touching your hair
what lork do australians say
instead of like do they say like what
like mike bark
they do it's crazy
i'm going to work by boycotts
i i like going to work with my work
[Music]
bother
where's the butter where's the butter
where is the butter
does that sound australian
where's my bork where's my butter butter
i am
[Music]
that doesn't sound australian to me that
sounds normal but okay
the end they uh they like to make the
end of the sentence go up
i see i saw i saw it
oi mate pass me the bada
because you're australian killer that
makes sense it sounds normal to me
because i'm australian
australian australian
okay continuing back to topic the game
of three eleven decision
earlier you were saying your goals was
to reach the ends of the world while it
does have an end i hope you know that
it's so far away that nobody has ever
reached the edge in
survival mode oh but
does it not happen like the the spawn
point in minecraft
when you open a new world is random
right does it
has it never happened before that the
spawn point
is like pretty close at the edge of the
world or is it always like somewhere in
the middle
is it always somewhere in the middle
[Music]
you see it's random so does it never
happen
[Music]
it's always zero ah
so you always spawn in the center oh
okay
again
mysterious user thanks for the
membership
astor
just wanted to what did i learn um
i don't know what i learned just just
want it wanted to stop
by your stream and say that i
hope you're having a wonderful evening
i think it's evening there i'm
australian so it's hard to tell
if that's australian
i'm crying yes
see one person said yes perfect
there we go
[Music]
you're getting there wonderful i've
heard better well of course you have
no why what's with these people who say
no you have no idea what you're talking
about
those pictures are more scottish more
than ever but i personally want to say
i love and i love like english accents
like british
i like british accents they're sexy
i want someone who if her life english
is gonna get a new member
on a new generation i need someone to be
british
i need someone to be british
and not fake british like amelia watson
i want a real brit give me a real brit
[Music]
exposed
thank you hughes is sending me a super
chat thank you i like your art very much
are you probably not watching right now
but thank you
whoosh what
[Music]
exposed
oh i will try to read this in australian
accent again
okay let's go by the way
i have always loved your
so much thank you for
being the light of my life i have no
idea what i'm doing
i don't remember anything i don't
remember anything
thank y'all for bringing me hope you are
the reason i wake up every day
i know i don't know what i'm doing
[Music]
everyday you are the most
beautiful foreign
i have ever seen and your eye
or look like the universe
oh i'm surprised people say that sounds
like scottish maybe i should focus on
learning
a scottish accent
[Music]
you really think we say foreign
i um i
i would like to not apologize to my
australian
merch orc
keana is being possessed by the scottish
spirit
oh my god oh my god okay guys we're
gonna we gotta get it going
thank you for the ransom for jeff kiana
kfc thank you
thank you sorry that i butchered your
super chat but
um i'm glad you wrote something really
sweet sorry for butchering it but thank
you for your support thank you for your
[Music]
kindness
thank you i'm sending you an early new
year's greeting i just want to let you
know that you have given me happiness
during hard times you're a glimmer of
light in the darkness thank you
that's very sweet kyogre yodakishan
mb737
thank you for the red super chat with no
text
why you do this again and again why you
always do this to me
thank you guys for the membership see
these people where um
they she wouldn't we would like to
recycle
someone of english i um
they heard my australian accent and they
were like wow
dab that's some good australian accent
and they were like i gotta
oh yeah they were convinced thanks
thanks german peeps they were convinced
by my perfect
uh australian accent which is why they
just
joined the membership they must be
australian
they heard their own language and they
were like
thank god someone finally speaks my
language here
what can i give kiara or mate kiara give
up on the oc
accent please it hurts or it makes me
laugh so hard or it can
break
[Laughter]
i try i'm just a genius you know i can't
tell they're back
i just have a talent for these i just
have a talent for these coins or friends
things i just have a challenge for
free foreign
this not is it you got it you gotta
admit this is how australians talk
they say foings instead of things
i know it
[Applause]
ah
shut up shut up i know what you're doing
there i know exactly what you're trying
to do by
writing that comment that's not a knife
what is it what else is it jen can i say
royce uploads
this is a knife i haven't i have a pen
i have an apple oh
a pole pen how would you say that in
australian
how do you say apple in australians
a york egg york
in the middle of an egg you have ad york
in australia
ah purple that sounds legit it must be
orbital
i have a pen i have an opal
[Music]
um
my australian buddies are leaving me
because they're disappointed for not
representing them correctly
don't leave me mate
i love you guys i love you guys
australian people
you have a beautiful accent however i
cannot copy it very well
i'm sorry
[Music]
contractually true i'm still here with
only
oh my [\h__\h] god i'm dying well that's
your problem
i love my australians i love them
i also love my canadians i also love my
i mean are there any br where are my
brits
where are my brits my brits was my
my favorite sexy accent where are you
guys
right here nice i'm british i'm nice
i'm right here nice right here nice
i was here almost nice
british people brit is here nice brick
yet nice
[Music]
i've learned some italian in the past
good in it my italian
italian thank you
[Music]
well thank
um
[Music]
do you know any finish no unfortunately
it's just i love italia visited italy so
many times
and end up in my in my childhood and i
want to visit again i love italy
italian people are cool and they really
they're really easy going really open
really outgoing
and obviously italy uh is on the border
to
australia obviously which is why i visit
italy so often
[Music]
i hope i can visit again soon
so mb737 thank you for your support
thank you for the red super chat
very much appreciated you always so so
generous
and so kind thank you
essential is a perfect english speaker i
need to
defer this question to you how should i
pronounce
kansas and arkansas
that's how it is that's how you
pronounce it
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
well you guys are wrong
well that's just misleading that was on
purpose
mate alright you australian [\h__\h]
you tried to deceive me
where are you muda
me and me and my ksp employees we have a
good relationship
i can i can i i can i can i can curse at
them a little bit
every now and then that was on purpose
because khan says you say kansas right
you were
you were totally teasing me and trying
to get that out of me
to say art i can i i i i
i okay arkansas whatever [\h__\h] it
and those feeling i kept speaking so i
had to ask there was no trick
of course of course of course no no we
australians we speak perfect english
you and me i am the real australian in
the room and you might be a fake
australian
but you and me we know perfect english
[Laughter]
so continuing
just want to say you give me hope in my
albedo
what is this this is a oh my god i see
the end
ah well let me read it let me read you
super chat
i just want to say you give me hope in
my life and make every day just a little
bit better you are guiding me to real
life and it has been so amazing so from
my heart
thank you for everything kiara are you
welcome
[Music]
you thank you founder of bluepolyuu
tankishanti
is at ted's donkey
i did not change it excuse me
excuse me
what are you be sure to get me off
i forgot the english what are you
accusing me of huh
[\h__\h] i call that
this is what i call it
i'm going into 2021 and i've already uh
sweared
so much
[Music]
what what's joe what what does that even
mean
thank you for the pink super chat what
what does that even mean
for
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
i was trying my best when i felt it
coming i've tried my best to turn on the
echo
[Music]
quickly
[Applause]
oh my god that sounded amazing
[Music]
f-o-d-r thank you for the rest of red
super chat
wait wait excuse me i wasn't full volume
thank you
thank you forever i am not sorry
you gotta be prepared for these kind of
things
a way out it was so fun and full of
emotions thanks for the great breakfast
yesterday
you're welcome thanks thanks for
watching
that was a hell of a sneeze hell yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
thanks for something thank you for your
support it's more than just something
you might just
write only something in your super chat
but
i know it's more than that thank you so
much thank you
lord cloud thank you inside quest
jackson lunch box thank you
how do i say that name
[Music]
oh i think i saw you in the chat
how do i read your name
are you are you are you actually in the
chat or am i imagining something
someone from i think singapore
how do i read your name tell me
[Music]
tell me oh my god it's almost a new
countdown
[Music]
i i guess that person is not here after
a while maybe
[Music]
thank you for all the hard work you put
into entertaining us you're incredibly
talented and deserve all the success
you've achieved and more
i'm looking forward to kfp finally being
profitable as a subsidiary of net in
productions
we are not a subsidiary excuse me
thank you for you
[Music]
thank you for the support thank you for
your generosity
thanks for watching and supporting kfp
and five four three
two one
happy new year in another country which
one is it this time is it indonesia
indonesia ends somewhere else
[Music]
yay
yes my bird calls welcoming you all to
[Music]
thank you once again
hoping for your support in 2021 as well
happy new year
[Music]
looking for the top thank you soon
trevor
monaco
wants to let me know
let me let me let me say it as he says
it
your draw droid that boat like you drove
your cart in mario kart well thank you
albion at least i don't sound as stupid
as you do
[Music]
uh
security number 6119414 here
rnd is asking what's r d
if we should have a memorial for adam
sadler
kelly's horse for the next two days also
security needs to never upgrade to try
to escape again
i don't care that's not
my problem you duck beats got to take
care of that that's not my problem
you think kfb is going to take care of
everyone's problems and worries what the
hell
carefully is here to take care of my
worries adam sadler is not my problem
thank you
stinky raven monochronic thank you
thank you and trevor g duncan
yeah we don't serve horse meat we don't
serve that
happy new year from malaysia oh thank
you happy new year to you too
[Music]
oh thank you for the membership thank
you
[Music]
okay but where is circles
we don't talk about circles
[Music]
we don't
my marketing research shows that the
target audience
is really interesting interested on this
sure
go ahead please circles was like a
brother to me daichi
shut up
maybe one day i'll go back yes you
promised to bring him back yeah
i mean i don't know i don't know if i
promised that but i'll
i can try i can try eventually to go on
a rescue mission
i love them like my son shut up
you did not have such a relationship
with my horse
that would have been really weird
[Music]
yeah you're going to change the time
when you stream once you leave japan
probably it will change a little bit
yeah
i'd probably be streaming a lot for
european prime time
i don't know what time that is for you
guys but
european prime time here i come
yeah it will probably be mostly european
prime time
between 7 pm to 1am
probably most of the time
yay i think at the moment whole live
english
doesn't serve the european time zones
that well
unfortunately so i'm glad to fill up
that spot
i'll also try to still um have some
variety
in my schedules
[Music]
i still i'll still watch your eye guys
thank you
now i think the actual problem for me is
going to be
um streaming at japanese
[Music]
wait a second let me think what am i
trying to do what is my brain doing
right now
reaching reaching my japanese viewers is
gonna be problematic i don't know about
the american viewers
but like if i stream it at european
prime time it will be in the middle of
the night
to morning time in japan so
they'll probably not be watching me that
much anymore but
for americans and canadians and so on i
don't know
also my australians i don't know about
them i'm not sure
oh well all of that we will see once the
time has come
stuff xp thank you soon well next is
thanks for the stream thank you for
watching the stream
thank you thank you very much for the
support i'm glad to have you
and watching my streams happy new year
hope you had a lovely
lovely evening and i hope you will
support me in the future as well
thank you thank you so much
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat
why would you send me a super chat um
with no text with no text what the hell
a red one with no text how dare you
unacceptable
[Music]
anyway someone asked if he'll attack
will be uh
um
affected let me see
normally normally um
i stream somewhere at 10 a.m japanese
center time ah
i mean oh wait a second dad
how much
[Music]
i i'm
it would be like 2 a.m two hours after
midnight
for me but that's not such a big problem
for me
so the time might not change
and hot time might stay the same
because um
that's if anything it might be one hour
earlier
if anything so that it starts at
1am in you know germany and so on
and 10 and 9 a.m japanese center time i
mean
my guests my japanese guests are going
to hate me for
making them stream at 9am because most
of the japanese members
are not exactly the people who like
waking up early
[Music]
oh
we will see
[Music]
we will see the times might change they
might not
everything is possible
[Music]
all japanese in japan so
the priority is uh to stream at a time
that is comfortable for them
and 10 a.m is already not really
comfortable
[Music]
gohan
okay
[Music]
casper just moved out so he doesn't
disturb his dreams anymore that's very
nice of him
he was noisy because he said goodbye
don't worry he's still all right that's
so sweet
i i'm not sure i think my
my most logical explanation is that
after we
closed that hole that he has realized he
can't get inside anymore
so he's mostly somewhere else now
but just a few times the way i heard him
making small noises
recently is when he just came back to
chill a little bit
but he's not really living here anymore
and that's why i don't hear him that
much anymore
he didn't starve to death i literally
just hurt him
he wouldn't starve to death he would
just go outside and get food somewhere
else
it's not like my house is the only
option he has
there's food outside everywhere my sorry
my stones don't eat only one thing
i'm sure stop don't don't
chop everyone shut up oh
he's still alive i'm sure i just heard
him last night
[Music]
oh yeah 2020 was the year of the rat
wasn't it
i just realized that today when i when i
was looking at the layout for the whole
live official channel stream that we did
today
and i saw a mouse or a rats in the in
the logo on the top right and was like
oh
was it was it the year of the rat it all
makes sense
a year of casper and now we will never
see him ever again
who knows though maybe we will maybe we
will maybe we won't
know i know
wild mice don't scream unless they're in
danger or dying
evil pest control put rat poison around
or your neighbor's dead good chance is
gone
well but the thing is they they came
like a month
over a month ago and put rat poison
there
and then they came back two weeks later
to check up uh and they they found
two dead bodies so they took those dead
bodies away
and put fresh poison food there
for the rats or mice whatever that is
i think it should be mice so they put
that there and they came back two
months later again two weeks later again
but then nothing no new bodies
and they told me that the
the the poison trap thingy food was not
touched so they came back two months
to two weeks later again they came like
five or six times or something
but uh once again it was not touched
but i kept on hearing casper every day
so basically
he figured out that he's not supposed to
eat that
he knew he was still alive he's just
super smart he knew that he was not
supposed to eat that
and they kept coming back in the back
and back again
and they always told me well your
mouse did not eat the poisoned food so
yep he's a big brain mouse
and that's when i accepted it because it
was impossible to get rid of him that's
when i accepted to just have him in the
ceiling as long as i don't see him
anymore
but then once upon a time a few weeks
ago
when i was streaming i was picking up my
uber eats order downstairs and then at
that moment i saw
casper running around from the ground up
to the ceiling
i saw him that's the first time i saw
him actually
that's where i panicked and i called the
professionals again
they came over a few days later and they
found the hole where he
came through and they closed that hole
so after that i did continue hearing
casper
in my ceiling very loudly as usual
but the past three days
she has suddenly out of nowhere started
to
be more quiet and i
personally don't hear him anymore at all
for um
a span of 24 hours then i heard a little
bit and i didn't hear him again for 24
hours and i heard a little bit and then
i didn't hear him again for 24 hours and
there we are now
[Music]
you've earned a new subscriber because
of that story nice
yes i don't know but um the thing is we
had professionals and he didn't eat that
poisonous food he he knows that he
wasn't supposed to eat that
so i don't know man maybe he did
i by the way that that poison
poison food by the way the professionals
told me
that it doesn't kill them but it makes
them blind
so they will eventually just die because
they're blind and can't find
find any food and so on i know that's
like really
it's really terrifying i know i know
i know i know i know i know but that's
just how they do it i know
i know i know i know it's really cruel
when i thought about that whenever i
heard casper screaming up there in my
ceiling i was like maybe he's panicking
because he
finally ate the poisoned food and turned
blind and then
he doesn't he's like panicking he's like
what the [\h__\h] am i
he's making me sad oh come on
it's making me sad
i hate it goddammit
okay let's change the topic this just
makes me sad i feel so terrible but like
the thing is like this house uh has been
um controlled and uh affected by mice
for over 20 years
now we got even more worried i know
[Music]
i seek mouse cry while they're starving
oh man don't think it's cheap too deep i
try
[Music]
oh man okay let's stop talking about
this
[Music]
properly and break bring kfc back from
bankruptcy plus i'm free from
quarantine so i can get back to work and
what's with all these super chats what
the hell
so i can get back to work and invest
more into kfp
please please don't you don't have to
really please
when you finally have uh money then
please
the first thing you do shouldn't be
super chatting it to me
it should be to use it for yourself but
thank you for your support
i want to say thanks for all the fun
streams during holiday season and more
thank you wong hang you always so
supportive thank you so so much thank
you sir thank you for the pinky i
appreciate it very much
thank you soon
[Music]
the fact that you stepped up and got the
shirt done is really impressive thank
you
plus the fact that it was done by you
makes it really special
rest assured it will soon be covered in
cat hair oh yes mine too once i go back
doesn't keep my chicken warmed up
i mean if you put the chicken
under the t-shirt yes probably a little
bit yeah
the shirt looks really cute and adorable
i like the artwork and design that went
into it keep up the cool work yeah
thank you i'm so happy to hear that
thank you
very gamer311 thank tango soon that
moment when kiara takes time to read
your super chat laughs and says she did
what you wanted but you don't know ah i
told you i think i told you
[Music]
foreign
the shirt is black and my cat has black
fur oh yeah
i know exactly what that's going to look
like once you wear it for the first time
[Music]
happy new year kiara thank you happy new
year to you too happy new year
thank you to you too thank you soon
[Music]
thank you guys so sweet
i'm really happy you're going back home
to australia canada just hope
that you that i can still catch as many
streams as it changed ours
well but you're in australia and i will
be in australia
so shouldn't we be in the same time zone
i don't think you have to worry about it
albedo the mac tron sanction resides
thank you so
saying kelly will be so lonely without
you kiana will and will you ever do a
stream with your mama phoenix
maybe i'm very worried
that she will say something by accident
something weird
some i don't know maybe maybe maybe in
the five five five for our future
also i got that whole move t-shirt as a
christmas gift to myself because i like
the artwork on it and it makes me smile
to know you made it
thank you i'm happy to hear that
thanks for getting the t-shirt
thank you i'm glad you like it i put all
my heart
and all my time and all my love into it
[Music]
how are we still in the minecraft stream
with the super chats i've been waiting
for hours
[Music]
i think i'm almost done joe star hero
thank you for the red silver chad
while i first learned of whole life from
other members your streams were the
first time i started checking out
streams regularly and it's been great
getting me through
these rough past months after i i think
i already read that one when you sent it
because i remember the sad part of this
and thank you joestar thank you
thank you i already read it but i read
it again and thank you for your support
donkey shin thank you so much joestar
it's very generous
please take care of yourself and happy
new year
thank you so
[Music]
correctly
i know exactly what part of the stream
that was
hello my baby hello my honey hello my
ragtime girl
sent me a kiss by wire baby my heart's
on fire well what what is that
if you refuse me honey you lose me then
you'll be left alone
oh baby telephone and tell me i'm your
own
wait what is that what's that song
looney singing frog from looney tunes
wait i don't remember the melody
what's this what's the name
[Music]
oh what is that
the frog
i never heard this one before
[Music]
i never heard this before
it has five million views what the hell
[Music]
that's amazing thank you san diego for
this uh
insightful super chat
thank you so much two hours late to the
party oh yes you are
late thank you thank you for your
support thank you thank you so much
thank you and happy new year to you
chimipah dankeshan just some some
stormtroopers
[Music]
stream oh
okay i'm reading the members only
superchats from this stream
quickly
discord discord you missed my
my party is always so it's already too
late but thanks for
showing uh showing up discord
what the hell this couch is showing up
so often
at my stream these days
[Music]
happy new year this car discovery
discord
discord thank you
thank you can i eat some snack
[Music]
i don't i'm not even asking for your
answer guys
i'm going to eat it this chord
always seems to show up when i'm reading
my super chats
discord is always too late
are you listening this chord you're too
late you're going to show up earlier for
my stream sorry the content is not here
i mean some people say the content is
where when i read my super chats but i
like to think differently
let me drink some water too
it's 9 00 am but you gotta get up early
if you were kiana simp
that's just how it is you're gonna get
up at any that's not an excuse
it's 9 a.m that's not an excuse you know
that
discord you should know better how is
that an excuse
oh my god beginners amateurs
oh
[Music]
hmm
um
[Music]
is this corsail watching this
um
[Music]
ah so good
all right that was your snack i'm done
with my snack
let's continue
all right
it was nice to see you put me in the
thumbnail and i've claimed you as my
baby goal therefore i am the bigger of
the two kiara
i look forward to being in many more
films
shut up imposter oh wait that was a red
super chat thank you
are you you're trying to say that you
are the the big
kiara in that thumbnail and i'm the
small one
i called
[Music]
understand
should have read that in australia okay
let me read that in australian since
you're using australian currency
karen soy sorry excuse me
[Music]
or it was nice okay that was good that
was good that
up until then it was good it was nice
to see you put me in the
bump noil and all i have claimed
you as my baby girl girl
never i am the bigger of the two kiara
i look forward to bringing in many more
from noise with you
[Music]
i don't know i don't know i forgot how
to do it i forgot to do it
[Music]
gargoyle that's also what i was thinking
about when i was saying baby coil
i was speaking of gargoyle what the hell
i can't help it i'm just naturally
australian i can't help myself
[Laughter]
thank you kiara kfc
gargoyle coconut
[Applause]
yes i've already heard the good news on
twitter welcome back
baby xander
[Music]
the way i read that name because i was
still in my australian accent
yeah ghosts sexy toes it's supposed to
be yagura
yago sexy toads okay not
you know
oh my god i did not mistreat it but i
was still in my australian accent
excuse me oh my god
change your name because my kids
[Music]
m
i hate how youtube doesn't notify me
about members only streams
yes i know right that sucks what the
hell man
we're doing 18 [\h__\h] you know 18 jared
martinez duncan
snoop dogg kfc duncan thank you for the
wonderful last quarter of this year and
with a nice community thanks to you
best wishes for another good year thank
you so much
this is a lot better than youtube
rewinds are you talking about the clips
wholesome moments uh moments funny
moments
cute anime girls how's youtube supposed
to compete yeah right
it can't danger
[Music]
kitchen lizard wizard alberto john
kitchen
v gamer for eleven time concern do you
really not recognize the how you
there he goes throwing his money at me
with a red super chat
and uh let me read it in in my british
british language
okay here you go here's how do most of
us support you
i feel like many people have said it
before and i'll say say
the rest of her life have brought a
pretty
[\h__\h] a year that was good that was good
br
pretty shitty year in pretty sure yeah
yeah to a pretty decent one so here's to
a better
year in 2020 2021 river lakia
[Laughter]
thank you you know i'm still asian yeah
but your currency is
uh british so even if you're asian you
might have a british accent
so i speak to you and you're in your
british accent language
i don't think i can read it in um
your your actual original language
logic excuse me what
the hell you guys are stupid you know
nothing anyway
thank you thank you monkey hang thank
you
i'm glad i'm glad you're part of the kp
crew supporting
me very kindly very generous
and one of the i mean you you all are
amazingly
sweet but um
i really really i'm really happy to have
you guys
so thank you wanyang for being being a
good person supporting me
i'm glad to have you glad to have you
around happy new year
thank you and congratulations on on uh
finally reaching a point where you can
super chat
already
i've actually gotten my life together
because of you i'm learning
japanese and studying to become a
teacher thanks kiara wow
good luck thank you soon
[Music]
oh dear this is when people sent me
super chats asking me to
bonk them oh my god a french super chat
from a canadian
excuse me mademoiselle kiana marco
revolution are you asking me for a dance
yeah let's [\h__\h] dance
[Music]
i don't know what i was singing there
that was absolutely random
[Music]
[Laughter]
happy birthday to me oh happy birthday
happy birthday can you do a popping
sound with my what kind of popping sound
i can do
um
[Music]
or do you want um i don't know
what what what are you what are you
looking for i can do this one
that's my frogs
[Music]
i think this is the first time i did the
frog noise
since i got uh since i turned on my my
com
what's it called my um
is my is it my uh equalizer oh not my
compressor
or i don't know whichever it is
yeah because this makes it extra loud
it balances the small the the the quiet
noises makes them as loud as everything
else
so now you can hear it so clear do it
again please
[\h__\h] up
turn on the reverb
wait wait what the hell is okay
okay i think wait i think my pitch is
back to
oh my god i can't
i'm frog
wait okay i'm back to normal thank god
i'm frog okay someone clipped that
moment
where from from when i was starting to
do the frog noises
to i'm frog only those five seconds just
cut that and upload it thank you
thank you
[Applause]
i know you're really good at roxanne
thank you
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you for always
being the best in every stream and for
the great community that is kfb
thank you for the kind words
gargling do you guys want me to gargle
an echo i have this this might go
perfectly wrong
[Music]
let me try to not spill water everywhere
all right
[Music]
the echo is probably gonna make me laugh
so hard and i'm gonna
spill it everywhere what are you singing
don't laugh chiara don't don't laugh
quite a sick
oh you made me laugh so i almost choked
that's exactly what was
going to happen i knew it okay one more
time now we now
now don't laugh don't laugh
[Music]
it almost went into my air air thingy
you know
where where your air goes sometimes when
you when you
bring it on you when it goes into the
wrong
place
[Music]
oh my god
is
[Music]
[Laughter]
huh
[Music]
drowning verb
sorry i'm low-key dying every time
point of view you are drowning
[Applause]
are you cooking a phoenix no don't cook
the phoenix
what the hell am i doing i'm trying to
get for the super chats for [\h__\h] sake
[Music]
i'll never get done with the super chat
it's always like that it's always like
that
it's just too much today
uh i'm boiling a chicken
thanks for the membership very smart
choice to join my membership very smart
all right let me get through them a
little bit quicker
29 thank you soon last of which i put in
here
let me turn the music back on
last episode for the year thank you cara
for bringing joints in my life thank you
so much for making our days my days
brighter don't stop being you and very
bottom left
thanks to you i was able to be more
productive please bonk me no
but thank you shane
this year is pretty much a mess for me
discovering whole live ian girls and
utensil gave me a reason to endure 2020
instead of giving up
thank you tanjul and thank you to the
rest of the whole life girls happy new
year thank you
[Music]
patrick stop by wasting
thank you for the red super chat i know
exactly what happened there because your
message got deleted because i
timed you out because it was an
experiment
thank you fodr thank you for
offering yourself to the experiment
2020 not ending with a bang but with a
gurgle
thanks for the membership member
thank you for the red super chat yeah
fodr thank you very much really thank
you for your support
three dimensions
for the uh omni also participated in the
in the experiment therefore your message
is deleted as well
thank you very much for your red super
chat asking to
be banned on my chat for uh what was it
300 seconds
we have successfully found out that when
i do that the money
does not get refunded but your question
your text gets deleted worth it
thank you
18 bankers
thank you for the happy birthday on
october this year has been truly rough
for me but you have made
things a lot more bearable for me i'm in
a better place now you're truly amazing
kiana i love you thank you i love you
too that's sweet
thank you thank you for the membership
unless you like hooked into your stream
during that weakness
you regret it i don't think you do
account arctic fox thank you
once again red super jets
[Music]
thank you so much mr firefang
don't worry about it
welcome
[Music]
thank you so much happy new year by the
way ah
oh yeah yeah you were you should already
be 2021 for you right
since you are in my home country
so we are a few of the people who are
living in the future
this person was also asking for it but
no no no no more
thank you for the support though feeling
navy boy kp administration officer
duncan
[Music]
thanks for the great time stands
especially through 2020 i only started
watching home live when gen 5 debuted
but
you are definitely my favorite to watch
without a doubt here's to 2021 viva
thank you thank you thank you blaster
jungle
sharon
jack pain
some clippers are here so i'm going to
take this opportunity to thank all of
you guys for the jobs you made for 2020.
yeah
thanks to all the clippers for
supporting type 91 duncashin totaling
vacation crispy duncas and rockmount
sarana thank you and thank you for the
pinky
thank you i heard some kfp employee got
lost and move out of the usual room i
appointed myself to a warden so the poor
employees don't get lost
interesting i like how everyone gives
themselves a position in kfp i like it
keep it up guys thank you soon wild
nexus thank you so much
[Music]
i'm me one more time with a red super
chat thank you
this message is not not not deleted so
that was after you came back
yeah thank you thanks for coming back
mgd duncan
thank you very much for the amazing
moments we have lived together these
past months and the many more to come a
question that has
been bothering me recently how many
chicken nuggets have you eaten in your
life
millions my friend millions
i cannot count anymore i have lived too
long and i've eaten too many chicken
nuggets
logical paradoxes
m
[Music]
thank you for making the later year of
2020 entertaining you are welcome
thanks for watching kiara as much as
people
like to mean the energy i always uh
enjoy your content because you stay
surreal with kfp a toast for a great
2021. thank you i tried to stay
you know real and not uh
i tried to show you guys my human side
and um that might
uh sometimes
put me into situations where i'm a bit
too open
and a bit too emotional but
um i don't wanna i don't wanna
hold back my feelings you know i
try to be real with you guys and
share my my real feelings with you
be it sad feelings or be it human side
while being a frog
excuse me just because i can make the
voice of a frog
i mean i did say i am frog but i'm not a
frog
anyway thank you and thank you guys for
hanging out with me
even even when i'm you know crying
or telling you stories that you don't
even give [\h__\h] about
thank you soon i love you all but you
know that
thank you soon
thank you for the red super chat kissing
[Music]
support says the message very short but
a very clear message you're supporting
me i think
thank you hopefully
in 2021 uh i can have your support as
well i would be very happy
if you would continue supporting in any
form that is doesn't mean
that i want more super jazz i just want
to have you in my audience that would
make me very happy
[Music]
kiara your first super chat reading was
where people got to know you how much
you appreciate us and for giving us
so much of your time thank you
soon owen walker dan kishan
tanju you got me addicted to shadow
verse i just won my first
pvp match what nice
[Music]
popcorn chicken
thank you for the red super chat saying
last akka spa oh i think i already read
that one
before i hit charging limit thanks
boston for making 2020 a whole lot
better you and the other halloween girls
have brought a huge smile to a lot of
people i'll be cheering for you girls
long in the future
now broke kfb employee at me you're
welcome
thank you for your support it is very
much appreciated
you are very very kind very generous
pretty much too generous but thank you
so much
thank you hopefully
i'll see a lot more of you in 2021
never leave kfb you cannot leave anyway
yot also thank you for the red super
chat
thank you ylt says kia i just want to
say a few
want to say hours before your stream
started i was feeling ah i also read
that one
i read a bunch of those already on
stream well
thank you for great sick day you are
welcome once again
i hope you feel better by now y-o-t i
hope you recovered for
from your stomach flu anyway
uh thanks for watching and thank you
for your support happy new year
[Applause]
going for the rewinds in the image and
the individual streams i stayed up all
night to catch all the debuts
slept and caught your fall guy's stream
too nice
it's been a wild ride ever since this
year has been tough but watching your
streams
have really helped me pull through oh
thank you
it also helped me too i'm feeling 10 out
of 10 now awesome
that's good to hear yeah
and um starting to stream
definitely helped me to get through a
tough time as well
so i'm glad we're helping each other
that's nice thank you
better licks thank you and happy new
year
off to a better year hopefully nagel
[\h__\h]
donkey shin i think that might be a red
super chat again
so what you're gonna kiss going to stick
with you from the start and saw
how you grew from a fairy chicken into a
true phoenix
your content is entertaining full of
energy and sometimes waking up to your
streams is just the best
so here's to you from a hungarian cave
chicken thank you yes it was
okey dokey i i i guess that was a bit
too many zeros to not be a red one
thank you i'm glad you sticked around
and
i don't know if my memory is it feels a
bit cloudy but if i
remember correctly then
we had an incident
i'm not i'm not i'm not thinking of the
wrong person right
yes okay we had an incident but
see now we are best friends forever bffs
i remember correctly okay okay it's been
a while it's been a while
but it's all good so thank you for
staying around really it means a lot to
me thank you
i appreciate it thank you for your
support
thank you it's nice to have you around
so
happy new year and hopefully i'll see
you next year i mean this here a lot too
new charge them still broke
well you brought that upon yourself
thank you sir [\h__\h] false thank you
thank you for your hard work on your
streams especially hello talk thank you
thank you i love your bubbly personality
and how funny you are i will always
support you no matter what always be
happy and see you next year
thank you for doing
thank you in swamific thank you for the
red super chat
saying this is for the members
subscribers and viewers that are both
here now and those that are not here to
say that we love you and what you do for
everyone being you and being fantastic
we are here for you and it's true thank
you for being here kiara we mean it
thank you why you guys are sweet thanks
for the membership kfb floor map
michelle thank you i'm very kind mrs
thank you for the
generosity thank you for the kind words
i really really
am happy to hear that and very kind of
you oh
olly did you end your stream i saw you
were also doing some
countdown stream
you say that in in japanese it's it's i
mean fully you
[Music]
super easy everyone being everyone will
be like oh
[Music]
i'm still going through millions of
super chats please help me
although i might i don't know i'm
probably not gonna get until the end
let me let me finish the ones from this
member stream
almost there well thank you for the red
super chat what is that about
dragon ball z i'd be goku i have
absolutely no idea
i'm sorry but i don't watch i never
really watch dragon ball
so i don't even know who google is
i don't even know i'm so sorry
unsubbed why are people pointing out
that i said dragon ball z
that's how we say it in german you
stupid idiots
how do you say it
say dragonblood sets
well you you say z
well i don't give a [\h__\h] i'm used to
saying dragon ball z
that's how i'm used to saying it god
damn it
unsubbed membership castles
[Music]
well i don't care
aussies say that well of course i do i'm
australian
i know how australians talk
i rated that too there we go
see as you guys said that's pretty much
everyone else everywhere else from what
i know
okay then it's the americans who are
trying to be
a little bit of a special flower there
it's it's only america see i should be
laughing at you guys
brit gang approves that
[Music]
nice
anyway swan fork
[Music]
i'm a doctor both real life and in-game
so
and i say i love your atmosphere thank
you
i have another doctor wait is is didn't
i come to this realization last time
or is this the third australian doctor
is this the third australian doctor
in kfp or is this the second
i feel like last time it was someone
else
not sure about the other one wow we got
so many doctors
what kind of doctor are you tell me can
you tell me about the pain in my
shoulder can you tell me about it what
kind of doctor are you
the pain in my shoulder and my neck that
has been going on for many years without
any break in between
[Music]
tell me doctor am i going to die that's
pasta
possible that's not what i wanted to
hear
[Music]
daddy issues oh my [\h__\h] god
[Applause]
i don't agree with the thing that you
said but
[Laughter]
thank you for your support yay i'm glad
you didn't dislike my my upcoming stream
i i wasn't trying to i wasn't trying to
hurt anyone
okay i was just trying to be
entertaining and being funny
and uh i get that all the time that's
what i i thought so
i thought that you must often be told
like i don't like what you're saying to
me stupid doctor
tell me something else and doctors will
would probably be like
oh once again i've heard that [\h__\h] my
patience
i hate my job
every time when you when your patients
are like
well i want you to say something else i
don't accept this
well that's great good to hear that
sometimes accurate okay
i got w and we d damn nice
and we need we the weedy is so cute
anyway
thank you
well thank you double choice that's
sweet
psyric with a double red super jet how
is this never ending oh my god
all right my break is almost over so i
wish you and my fellow employees a fun
stroll down memory lane i once told you
there was a certain point i started
watching it actively and when you asked
when i sadly was asleep because of the
night shifter i repeat it here
17th october mario kart was that my
first mario kart
thank you for the red super chats thank
you for your support
i'm i'm glad that the mario kart stream
got you into the kfp uh
rabbit hole very wise decision very
smart
thank you sir thank you for your support
it's nice to have you and
i hope you have a lovely
[Music]
that was australian that was english in
an australian accent if you didn't know
this
patrick chandang english quill danke
looking back on how far you've come i
hope that you'll look towards the future
with confidence
you've made it through all the stress
and still managed to build an awesome
community
we're proud to work for our best prep
thank you
damn the member stream was quite
emotional
uh it was a great memory stream though i
had
i had um it was nice to talk
about everything and review it so openly
that was nice
got very emotional also
cried a little bit out of happiness as
well
ah thank you thank you for giving me a
place where i can talk so openly you
know
thank you so much
[Music]
oh now there's a lot of emotional long
messages oh dear lord
it's never ending
thank you for the memberships guys thank
you
oh my god uh okay glory of combat thank
so get monkey jackets monkey again
majestic phoenix her voice cuts through
the noise standing tall and proud with
plenty of poise may she continue rising
to new heights and be our light of hope
during these dark nights
wait shouldn't it be like may she
continue rising to
new heights and be our lord of hope
during these dark nights
cave is with you that is no lie with
kiara we all fly
that sounds good thank you for the
thinking sounds good to me
i would have never been able to be part
of a community i can have so much fun
in if it wasn't for yuki at all oh
thank you honestly thank you so much for
being who you are and i will continue to
support and snipe you in 2021
thank you welcome to the membership guys
welcome
oh and the red super chat thank you
thank you soon well dude thank you
i'm glad to have you around it's always
fun to have my viewers
in games together with me so let's do it
again soon
blizzard wizard thank you
in one of the fire emblem streams you
talked about how things in life are
transistory
it hurt a lot to hear wait what what i
definitely didn't use that word what did
i mean with that i don't understand the
meaning
[Music]
of
what does that mean
i think it means that it doesn't last
forever
i think that's what this person is
trying to say because it continues with
it hurt a lot to hear ironically it's
what made me commit to watching you and
member up i want to enjoy
all this while it lasts with all of you
yeah i think uh i think i understand
well yeah that's just life that's just
how life is
yeah but yeah that's why we have to
enjoy it while everything is the way it
is right now
thank you vlad thank you for the
wikipedia
pete
thank you
uh donkey dokishan saying kiara tensor
going for the list with you and all the
kp employees
it's just confirmed that you are the
main reason for me staying in this
rabbit hole
i may not be able to catch all the
streams live but i do enjoy every moment
thank you and looking forward to 2021
i'm not sure if this is a
red one just in case i give you thank
you
i am the main reason for you staying in
the rabbit hole
thank you that's sweet
ah i'm happy to be someone's main reason
to be here
that makes me happy thank you soon
[Music]
it is red okay perfect thank you for
your support thank you for the
generosity
thank you very generous thank you
like i said i appreciate it
i hope you will never get out of the
rabbit hole
[Music]
trevor gee thank you for the red super
chat
wow saying you flipped me this stream
what do you mean i have always been a
passive slow quiet person but having
watched you
and everything you had gone through till
then it inspired me and i decided to
show my support
since then i've tried to spread my rings
and to be more open and involved oh
[Music]
oh what is the 500k stream where i went
from passive to active
ah ah you were talking about a specific
stream that we were talking about in
that moment i see i see i see
oh that's great
that's good it's good when when you can
become more open
the world will give you so much more
fun things if you are able to you know
talk to people openly
do what you want go for it instead of
like
you know holding yourself back
because the thing that's holding you
back the most is yourself
thank you
[Music]
i just read although you were killed by
chile yesterday
kelly right thank you i still believe in
the love between you i believe in it too
thank you for the devil red super chats
thank you [\h__\h] me too
thank you sir thank you i believe in our
love as well it's eternal it's eternal
love
isn't there a song that's isn't there a
song that has gentile eternal love
oh not really what i was thinking of
[Music]
interesting galaxy angel oh my god
that's so nostalgic
been here since the beginning i did not
expect it to become such a large part of
my life and i've cried and laughed so
many times on your behalf i can't
express
how much you mean to me and i've gladly
watched every stream i love you kiara
wow that is dedication thank you so much
and thanks for the pinky
thank you watching every stream
that is something you can be proud of as
a kfp member
the frock clip is up who did it was it
pudding
[Music]
frog noise
but there's the old ones there's old
ones too which one is in
the new one
[Music]
uh filter upload there we go
all ibm clips zero zero views
oh this is two minutes and 41 seconds
now it has to be five seconds and that's
it
oh it sounds beautiful it sounds amazing
that sounds absolutely fantastic
continuing
thank you for the red super chat
and my first akka spa thank you
and all of her life for making a
complicated year better for people
here is the gacha koi for you phoenix
idol chiara
[Music]
is
something like that some something like
that
it's some kind of um for idol songs
there's this kind this kind of a
supportive um
way of supporting them by mixing they
call it mixing
they're like in the audience and they're
like
then they go like yes
[Music]
and then there's like even more like
weird ones
like this one
i i like that kind of support
it's not call and response no no no it's
more like they just do their own thing
in the audience really loudly
but really passionately
[Music]
i like i like the way that japanese idol
fans support
their idols in concerts because like
it's much better better than just you
know the audience just
quietly watching and saying nothing
[Music]
saved 2020 and a big part of that was
utensil
looking forward to another year of you
all me too
i would be glad to have you around in
2021 as well happy new year mancho
thank you thank you for the support
um nice neck crack i'm getting really
exhausted so
i hope i hope it's over soon
[Music]
wait i can't read that um what does that
say
yeah what is that name what is the name
translate google
[Music]
dot
there is no names for my weapons no um
so i'm sorry i can't ask a question
i can't answer your question because
there is no answer
thank you soon happy new year thank you
happy new year to you too
happy new year thank you soon thank you
oh my god another red one thank you if
yellow wants to open the concert please
notify early i'm afraid that i won't get
the ticket oh don't worry about it i'm
sure you will be able to get one
thank you but it will still be a long
time
i wanna do a concert when i when i um
get 3d um but up until then all we can
do is
uh karaoke streams unfortunately but
that's also fun
thank you i saw when you read super
chats very kind of you
jay walker general pickering thank you
for the pinky
mama oh soy kid
[Music]
yeah i still have uh
the ones from the video left
and the ones from this stream but would
you guys excuse me for today
it's been four hours
the frog club is up on twitter again oh
i'm putting i knew it was you i knew it
was you
ah is it okay thanks guys
i'll see you guys tomorrow for an
atelier riser stream
um oh
happy new year i can't believe it's 20
21.
super chat
you guys pay me you guys pay me that's
how it works
oh and i have to notify everyone oh wow
world is coming out guys wow i will i
have to
i already made the premier reservation
but i have to tweet it out okay i don't
i am i can't forget about it
i have to do it now i have to do it now
so in german
we say avidas
you guys thanks for hanging out with me
thanks for doing the countdown with me
i had a blast thanks guys thanks for
being there with me
i'll see you tomorrow or today whatever
and everyone who's still
in 2020 ha ha loser
catch up with me when are you catching
up guys
gotta come to 2021 come on
i'm waiting for you
[Music]
come on just finish 2020 why would you
stay in 2020 so long
aren't you sick of 2020 let's move on
it's time to move on
so
[Music]
everyone please support me in 2021
as well thank you
[Music]
tracy
you