[Music]
is everything's normal now I think this
the stream is kind of a little bit have
a
lagging let's hope better now yeah okay
so this is the first time that I am uh
asking uh some Ian member Kanan Kiara
and FAA to join the uh Age of Empire 2
uh but we also have Ana and rainy to
play
[Applause]
again
so uh this time this time um we put it
into a team um since me Ana and rainy
already playing this game before so we
put I think it's wisely to put uh two
versus two versus two kind of thing
yes every team have Ian and
ID International Teams let's go yeah
yeah yeah y
yeah like like a g setting with a random
map a normal six player and the location
actually right now is randomly choose
Coastal but I actually have no idea
about
it I don't have any idea about the maps
it's okay yeah I don't have any idea
about the
map are you sure it's random Mrs Mauna
who's playing Vikings are you sure that
was not on purpose could you playing
Vikings I I put like game modes and
random M and they put the loation on
Coastal okay okay then let's I should I
don't know should I still is fine right
it doesn't really mean that the whole
map is covered with ocean right it's
just that there is a coast
right map
Pool yeah that there you can just choose
like 10 or 15 maps that you want to be
in the pool
oh so you can choose everything that
looks good to you for a big match okay
mostly oh maybe I just choose the one
that have like maybe six with mostly
they
are choose Arena too Arena and black
forest and uh in the top uh two top top
two row Black Forest yummy Black Forest
Black Forest yummy
for Yummy
chries which one again H in the top row
there should be black forest and Arena
it's alphabetic anyway Black Forest yeah
I heard that I never played it but it's
very popular I think for big
matches and then what do you want to
request
Arena I don't know I up to you put it to
you anything's
fine it'll be fine it be fine how bad
can it be yeah all right
you oh my God no no no no no the one
that is on Aran Black
Forest um which one again but they're
so look at that V majapahit Empire oh my
God wait can I sh a costum map Pool oh I
can how many maps are there there's so
many oh wait standard
there where's the big
mapish have how many Maps there's a map
called Mega random like is it is there
really like a question mark shaved water
on
it Mega random is just super random
interesting iess it's going to be
heavily stylist like everything is going
to be random it's not always going to be
the same M I'm looking at four people
yeah but like the thing is I can't
select see like I I can't see the six
people maps how do I see the six people
I don't know yeah four people now think
there
four how most
how old I mean it's just a map
size and these are just map Styles right
there's 83 maps in the
game automatically adjusted o look at
this oh now this is huge adjust it ah
you went to real world Indonesia oh my
God so much water in Indonesia not real
world not worst water in real world so
much water in the real world go back to
random too random Black
Forest it's
fine black
forest um no no I put it on random Black
Forest AR and Empire that's the three
random that I choose oh it says Black
Forest here but I guess when you get to
the game it's going to be
randomized yeah I
guess okay okay it's not bad if we go
eat cake
right cake is good cake is let them have
cake yum let them have
cake okay um well I think it's time to
start okay guys ready G kick us out good
luck good luck everyone good
[Music]
luck have
mer please go EAS on us okay
bye-bye all
right hello
hello
so I I I almost have no experience with
this game oh me too it's been a long
time since I played oh God did you
practice I did not
practice but I watched one video I
practice like game for like 30 minutes
okay that yeah and that didn't do
anything
okay I think we got
this hopefully we
do so do we need to like team up first
in game or like we're already in one
team
right yes how does teaming work in this
game um I don't know are we oh we can
see each other's Maps oh I
see then I
guess oh yeah I can see I can see your
village
mhm that's cool so I think we just build
yeah we just
built next to each other or something
mhm okay
cool hey um and I think we
Wicked
sheep this is what I learned from the
video I watched
uh-huh oh wait this is indona wait
what oh are we in
India yeah cuz I see the
flag I see the red and white
flags wait there's a Wonder right
outside our
walls
uh how do how do I go here where are you
going hey there you go Hey where's this
villager
going I'm going to your village as we
speak right now wait where am I oh
you're Scout I see it yeah there you
go
um wait I need to
materals
there so little materials
wa we need wait yeah are there
like trees I guess these are trees the I
don't see any Tree in my place bamboo
yeah I see bamboo wood but no trees do
you see any
trees no but I think the bamboo is is
okay yeah that should be
good it's still wood oh GL Stone wait
let me
build Lumber
Camp here
um what what do you think I should build
first oh who's
scouting Kara is scouting in my house I
see a blue that's crony I also see cron
at your place they're scouting okay why
is everyone
here
I think it's good to build a lumber
Camp um okay we'll do
oopsies and to kill the Sheep the poor
sheep and
then eventually you want to get
hey uh
Hey a loom
mhm do we have money okay wait how do I
oh wait how do I how do I choose
buildings I'm pressing q but nothing's
working idle
oh someone is scouting here oh it's MOA
so scary I know it is scary they're
probably like so
scary
oh I'll build a
mill n i making a lot of vill ERS Lumber
Camp
here and
then mining cam will be
good oh
I'm my Scout is going
somewhere I haven't played this game in
a really long time me but I did play it
a lot back in the day oh I many Idol
villagers I'd have to check how many
hours I haveth I feel like I didn't even
play the steam
version back then Mauna Senpai is not
leaving my
place please I'm just a little guy I
know I'm just a little guy don't do this
to
me she's not living my place what oh oh
she
left um
okay
anyways um you good I think I'm
good I don't know what I'm doing I
watched a guide to the first making the
first villagers what you should do with
them and I already forgot
everything it's okay I don't remember a
single thing to
YOLO all right
right it's still early things can't be
so bad I know
right I'm spamming Farms wait I should
probably build another house yeah cuz I
need more people that will be a good
idea yeah
uh all right oh research Loom right
that's a
thing yes I did do that oh bar who is
this
kiar kiar is here is there like a a
truce at the start of the game where we
can't fight each
other I I don't think
so I don't think so so we can fight at
the very
start well you can try if you want to
try I don't really want
to wait what if they what if they
I was about to say fight Muna Senpai cuz
she's nearby but maybe that's that's not
a good idea I don't have any military
units yet yeah I don't think anyone has
any and
unless
okay
um make a farm okay I should make more
houses
yeah hey military
building I guess I will build a
bars all right I also have no idea where
to put
anything me too I'm just putting
STS seems good yeah we should we should
try building
like
no
okay I'm growing lots of I
guess I'm spamming Farms right now for
food I guess we should try to advance
our
ASAP oh MOA Senai
place just scal thing don't mind me oh
God I feel like she music is so
dramatic feel like she's going to attack
me any time now oh
no n she's probably scouting
[Music]
somewhere go
here uh go
here bless you ex
me is this C there's one minute left in
the treaty
oh
uhoh wait how do you increase your
Villages again oh oh he just built
houses oh there you go and then you need
food and then how do I make them work
like the the people who are not
working uh you can push period to find
them and
then uh right click or whatever you want
them to
do okay h
what am I what am I what am I what am
I
um archers are archers good they did say
we're allowed to accept vac seaing from
chat oh
yeah which could save
us how do we get archers oh we need an
archery
range
um why can I not
buy
this it costs
um oh
hey oh we have to upgrade Advance the
age I'm almost to the feudal age oh
crony just made it to the feudal
age yellow villager at the
top H oh nice
uh make bunch of villagers I probably
should make more
houses and maybe I don't know what I'm
doing me neither
really I'm just Hing the H
key ah oh God I know we were talking
about hot Keys before in the Stream and
I was like wa you guys use hot
keys
I don't I don't use hot keys I don't
know how
to me
neither oh I'm going to build a market
that seems good what we doing again
right I should
[Music]
build what house is houses just
because okay there you go more houses oh
my city is looking so
ugly I don't think mine is any better
either are archers
good they should be but I don't know if
the The Meta or not okay I don't know
either we should go for the cheaper one
oh is anyone attacking your place
no
okay I don't think so
um ah but there is
music scary music is
normal Calvary is good for my maybe
here maybe here and then oh there you go
course 10 wood I love this
game I know I'm happy to be playing it I
love this game too I haven't played it
in so long me too we collab we collabed
this but that was like a year
ago was it already year I have so many
little
Meats
yeah oh who is
this wait wait wait wait wait build a
farm no I'm So Far Away fall no fall no
yes Ki is AFK in my place if you want to
come and attack should we I'm so far
away I should go back where is she she's
like yeah she's SC but she's not moving
she's not moving at all we teach her a
lesson uhoh is this does this start a
war
I mean why
not why not I don't know she's still not
moving she she's still not moving are
you fighting her I am heading back to my
place and see if I can make it in time
to my Scout my Scout what hey yo did
they
Scouts
wait what does that
mean
I might be Stu help
huh
help are you
okay um my Scout is not okay I think
mine might be dead I'm killing kar's
Scout with my
archers should I get rid of the
woods is that what I should
do get rid of
what right I'm stuck like in the middle
of
wots oh you might have to like chop them
down yeah oh oh oh oh they're attacking
me they're attacking is still alive
they're attacking me there's another my
Scout is
dead you're a scout my Scout is dead I
couldn't get
out I'm just a little
guy I know oh oh K
left I killed her her
Scout I wonder if she
noticed we're all just little guys yeah
we're just little guys okay got I need
more try our
best how do you get more Scouts again do
you need to like build the military
buildings yes I don't know which one
let's you get a scout
though um oh God more WS please I'm
building many
archers okay that's enough gold that
should be enough gold
right
um create the Villager oh not enough
food okay cool I have a lot of food can
I give you food oh wait did you build a
trenter yet the what I'm sorry did you
build a Trade Center yet um no not yet
I'm trying to work on it let me know
when you build build one
okay
um going very
slowly I need more
houses research
wheelbarrow Town watch do that that
seems
good
a oh yeah we need food
hey
um
oh oh I could get a monastery I'm going
to build a
monastery oh what does that do I grab
this Relic here unless you get monks you
can get relics and it generates gold you
can win in some mode with it but I don't
know if you can win in this mode that's
amazing
oh
okay
[Music]
oh fine
hand card yeah re I'm just going to
research
everything and hope for the best oh hi
bi
boo welcome welcome oh hello B
boo um we're playing Age of
Vampires we might be the underdog
team oh but I Believe in Us yeah
yeah who knows what will happen I want
both of them to fight and then we oh try
to take everything from behind that
would be good you know that would be
cool
um a she'll be able to make more people
build a
castle do I want a
castle why not you
know I don't see why not to build a
castle my
monk go get
this my civilization can have
elephants and I'm most excited get
elephants you can do
that that would be so
cool
the Persians get elephants you know what
I kind of just picked mine
randomly go home that's also
Fair more wood do I need more
wood I have a lot quite a lot of
food I have 23
food 23 can I can I donate to
you I should build a Trade Center
wait I have like 1,000
gold oh yeah build a trade center and we
can
trade I think it's still locked for
me okay I'm going to build the farm
first oh there's a lot of relics around
who is
this maa's scout is here can I convert
her
Scout can I wolo her
Scout I can
try she killed me so you have to take
revenge for me I will yeah I'm going to
wo her I keept seeing that what does it
mean it's the sound that the mon make
whenever they
convert go
oh that is interesting to
know I'm going to make a million
elephants I will load her
nice okay what we doing
here does it consume the monk when you w
ol I have no idea Chad might
know yeah oh everyone is
Idle okay hold on more more more lumber
Camp over
here Monk Is Not cons where did my monk
go what's he
doing oh whoops o
oopsies whe battle Town
watch wait why are
you why are you
idle we need
[Music]
food no we need
food okay there we go you over
here my trade
cart ah
oh here's my
monk oh
cool okay wait I want to can you
follow this
one and
then I to go collect these relics
oh no no no no
no
my elephants are
here I want to see put them on patrol oh
shoot
huge do you see them they're huge
yeah that's actually so
cool Elite war
elephants oh my monk grab this hey oh
there you go
no no no no
no and go
back can I Advance oh I
need a lot more
gold Lumber Camp do I have more people
more humans do I have a
m not
sure I'm very afraid if anyone starts
attacking
us MOA Senai already
did not my Village but she killed of
stuff right yeah she got my scoutout now
I have no Scout yet
Afra if we get
invaded
yeah
well when it happens it happens I guess
that's
true um did you build a tra
Center not yet wait where do you find it
again I think it might be log for me
wait how do I how do I oh you probably
need to advance your age yeah Advance
how do I Advance click on the to Center
Town Center it will say
Advance um I don't see it so I guess I
should um on your town center
uh-huh oh yeah I need more
Meats
yes can I donate food to
you no idea can we
trade
diplomacy
um and oh you need the Trade Center to
trade that
actually
you guys let somebody die
no I shouldn't have done that
right Archer
line
um I think I have a lot of stuff stuff I
don't know what to build
though we Town centers is that
good is that the
meta I thought you only do that if you
Dy more
elephants upgrade my troops
okay
cross
Bowman okay there you
go should I advance to the Imperial age
why
not more elephants oh
no what's up what's up no I I messed up
my clicking and now
it's no it's kind of messed up I live
with
it no but you need to see my
farm oh I see don't worry mine look way
crazier I just Place mine wherever they
go it's not symmetrical now well okay I
I'll live with
it
um do I what do I I
want is M here too hi M hi
M this is wait started building a Wonder
wait does she win if she does that I
think so we it's okay let them fight Let
them fight each other let them fight
each
other I see her
Wonder how long does it
take I have no idea I think it takes
pretty long like 15 to 30 minutes even
longer
[Music]
building oh
gosh moo will take care of it they're on
the same
team they're on the same team it's
over uh n it's okay they will fight each
other will they they they will
definitely fight each
other I don't
know I don't
know do we need oh there we go there we
go
um release the elephants is what what
did unit should I do
to wait do I need to build a Siege
Workshop do
you maybe I guess it's just attack
them what do you need for Siege
Workshop build a
blacksmith you have plenty of
time wait is a blacksmith a regular one
oh it
is
everybody go
help truchet plus elephants at my
elepant May should build more
elephants wait no castles also make oh
trebuchet
okay
[Music]
okay oh
there we
go
everything okay
oh I get
everything okay more
villagers are we at the highest level
there you
go build a
farm 800
huh more elephants
oh
oh um blacksmith
Market Wonder more elephant might be
good where's Trade
Center oh
this
mhm I'm going to have this I don't know
here must be packed to move unpack to
attack What will what will un do my
Treet
okay there we
[Music]
go I'll try to get the castle upward oh
I have our
elephants
do I want to skirmisher how do I get
those
elephants uh elephants are from my
civilization only oh but you also have a
unique Unit A some unique un I
see that's actually super
cool
oh
hey
J okay there we
go okay
research Town watch is that
good oh do I need to send the
treets to the to the
Wonder Elite elephant and blacksmith
upgrades are there more blacksmith
upgrades
did I not get all of
these all right well there's more let's
see
H is an
elephant a Calvary
Calvary I think we need the elite war
elephants more castles equal more
elephants okay I like the way you think
but do we have enough
stone is it worth
it why
[Music]
not how fun this game is although maybe
it's only fun not beinged
yet I mean that should be one of the fun
Parts too it's
true
oh I want to get my Elite war elephants
and then I'll send them
over start The
Siege but maybe I should leave some
units at home to defend just in
case all
right Lucky
Sevens
cool
um wa I don't have
nearly we might just have to
go oh yeah how is the wonder how is
Cron's wonder I don't know but I'm going
to go I think I'm going oh you're going
to go and
see yep I'm going to send in I say if
they're fighting each other Leaf them
be that's true we want if nobody is yeah
yeah I think it will be a good idea to
check um um I can sell wood at the
market what the heck is this stuff well
this is the
University oh
gosh murder
holes
oops oh
hey okay there we
go you can't sell wood blacksmith wait I
have so much
wood I have a lot of
wood research
everything all right I shall research
too Town
watch I don't know how good that is but
not enough food oh
no I need more
Farms more Farms
everyone get to work I should build more
too oh is it done
oh there we go oh you can send your
trade card to my Trade Center to get
gold
oh I think I have enough gold I still
have
like almost 2,000 oh but you should send
it anyway cuz that's how I think that's
just what it should be doing it'll go
back and forth ah how do you do that do
I just go to
your just go to my trade market and then
click on it with
your with your
unit
okay which one is trademark at the
G uh mine
is next to my
university oh this
one oh I'm out of
stone mining camp do I just click
my leure to
go
okay I'm going to go attack her and hope
for the best select my trade
card
oh which one is that game oh here there
we go
um cu's already in shambles is
she what's happening where will she be I
don't know I'm about to attack her
careful of Mauna
Senpai it's not going to be a good idea
to meet her
Allway I'm going to hope for the
best and I'm going to build more more
elephants I'm being attacked by wild
animals that should be
no no trouble right we are the wild
animals oh no my Tre shades are
unpacking to fight the wild
animal all right
going there we go you guys
going
a town
center University will be
nice
okay any more trade
cards
okay my units are going this one is the
fake out she's going to think it's okay
cuz there's just one and then these guys
roll up
ooh kind of want to see oh they're
fighting they're fighting they're
fighting let's go I say let them
be this is the Wonder is the Wonder
already
dead I think so is this the wonder I'm
being attacked by K oh oh is this her
Tower her
castle
I
see I think she's losing
anyways these
monks I don't see I don't see any of
Muna senpai's people so oh never
mind the elepant be fine I
think oh we're fine is actually super
spicy those elephants man
the elephants are
going oh
nice wait you destroyed her castle
castle you destroyed her
castle but it's is Kiara's
Castle she's fighting me
too oh
gosh how's everything at home be careful
be careful
k k k us going in careful oh my tret are
dead well you guys are that's fine you
guys are attacking
cron yeah my elephants are on the war
path maybe I should send them home
though yeah cuz you destroyed her castle
and one more
building I'll send them
home
okay
it's time everyone go
home
okay okay you know what I need more
Farm we have a tactical
Retreat now we
defend all right bre the New Castle is
this just
mean I feel like I'm gonna make enemies
here I think that's kind of the point of
the game yeah that's kind of the point
of the
game there's no
friendship oh no I guess
not oh no her castle got
built Oh My Elephants aren't that good
against the castle wait how do you build
military
stuffs oh more buildings should leave
yeah I see it
wait Castle Palisade
gate
Watchtower or
trebuchets do the research uh
Workshop spies you know what I should
have this
first oh and
you go
trade
um I want more trade how much gold do
they
get that's a good
[Music]
question oh my monk can heal the
elephant oh no moon is attacking me
where where is she I don't
know I don't know where your village
seems fine
though yeah it does seem
fine is it really
fine I hope
so
yeah oh oh my Scout is in her my
elephant is in her Camp why is my
elephant
here why is there's a lone elephant here
leave what are you doing my
elephant
get out of
here that's a lot of elephants okay
whatever the
elephant will just be sacrificed Hey
where's the
people he's just a little
guy I have a lot of elephant oh wait the
monk can heal
these
oo please heal these
sh have spend these resources I should
but where do I spend them
onor
okay research
everything oh I spend like all my
gold that may have been bad
oh oh
okay
I just
want
money I can cancel the
researches maybe I should how's everyone
doing is he doing
[Laughter]
it
sell the
wood oh wait we have a lot of this quite
hot wait oh my wood economy is in
shambles though look at
this okie dokie how much do
my oh
gosh oh I have a lot of idol
villagers do I need more
food I should more research
forging oh I should create Castle oh un
need houses okay you know what that
makes sense to that makes sense that
makes
sense Siege Workshop wait did I already
build the siege Workshop what oh
wait what are you
doing
house no this placement is kind of but
okay I not have a stable
either what's happening okay everything
is good for now is everything good for
now for now it's
good all right I just want more
money more gold money will solve all of
the problems right yeah how do you how
do I give you my gold oh you don't need
to give me your gold it's okay
oh do that in game I think you can
oh
I guess there is a gold
mine
okay
nice wait
so we'll build a mining camp
Mia SP
man oh you can
upgrade
cool you
that's
[Music]
expensive is it worth it
though what are you looking at oh um I'm
seeing at the archery
upgrades oh
yeah okay I'm going to do this too for
now and then Camel
Rider
hey um um
so let's
see I'm researching
everything
H Siege Tower I shall do that
too oh
nice camels counter
Calvary bow men
okay we seed
Farm oh I should get this I should have
got that a long time ago there's so
many you good
upes
yeah
that's like this click unit to
card oh yeah you do that right I
mean I'm going to research
everything if we just get a million
units we can never lose
right can never find
out I'd love to find out
who's
idle more
[Music]
Farms ooh um now what she'll make
more guard Tower I shall make even
more I should make even
more okay
okay
oh ooh I don't know what I'm
doing me too it's
okay I feel like the others are probably
like doing a
lot yeah they're
fighting they're probably doing good
things and I'm
not it's fight then considered a good
thing I guess
not okay wait what
oh cool
um
okay aggressive
[Music]
stance if you let them build it's going
to be worse that's true stand stand
ground
should I try to fight
somebody Raine maybe my next door
neighbor how's she
doing I don't
know oh yeah I could
Scout it's probably smart mhm do I even
have Scouts
anymore what happened to your scout no
they're just hanging
out
oh
um I have a lot of elephants that's for
sure not enough
units what are good units to
have I'm going to research
stuffs oh oh I need more
gold I
see
elephants R is attacking me oh no my
Scout did my Scout
die I think so there's a castle right
here
h
let's break this castle castle scary
upgrade I'm Not
Afraid oh I've got
elephants and
trebuchet my sh Scout too and
horses I saw someone said that my
civilization is the horse girl
[Applause]
civilization I'm not I'm not a horse
girl maybe I am
though you you kind of you kind of are I
I have a lot of horses oh what are these
what the heck are
these what did you find wait wasn't I
building I was building camels
though
uhoh uhoh I'm getting I'm getting
attacked oh no oh no is starting
elephants do you need do you need oh
they're pretty op oh no no I'm good it
was just my one
Scout oh gosh it was just my one Scout
oh shoot let's
go oh gosh I'm going I'm fighting
oh she's got treor Shades
too
uhoh
uhoh you good I think I'm winning
oh
nice
maybe a roll out elephants
research
H what shall I
research murder
holes murder holes sounds good yeah
sounds kind of spicy I'm going to
resarch
it
okay okay that was a good start I'm
building more
houses um how do I heal these guys does
my monk have to do
it is he good at it
it oh
no all right there you
go
houses cross Bowman more elephants more
treuchet more
elephants
AES with
villagers I being tired by rainy they
looking
fine
oh you
good is she building again oh
no she may regret this
decision
uh-oh monk get out of here get out of
here Monk go back
home okay
F oh God my go
okay
uh-oh elephants
fight where did you guys fight then I'm
F you oh
shoot W let's go
okay elephants go
home those elephants yo I I will be so
frustrated yeah I will be so
frustrated I need
more
houses
more houses for more
elephants all right more more
people
hey
a okay oh I need to build more
houses there's not enough houses
more
houses
a okay that's a
lot more houses more
elephants and everything will be
good more houses maybe more
Farms okay
cool I have a lot of resources do you
need
anything um maybe
gold
okay can
I wait how do I trade with
you I have no
idea I also have no
idea
um diplomacy
[Music]
tab I see pay
tribute weit researching coin banking
okay I'm going to research stuff first
so I can get a better
deal
um tribute is not a good
idea oh
a is more more castles are more castles
really
good oh yeah I need to build more
buildings more buildings more elephants
that is that is
right more
units time to have
this
uh more
units more elephants more units more
elephants more
houses there we
go
200 elephants no no more
trash what are other good units I should
the camel Riders seem
good what's strong against
archers I still more
this
houses
skirmishers you
elephants
horses do we just need more elephants
not beathing the hor girl
allegation I
know I have several
units here I don't even know what all of
these are oh you can guard unfinished
buildings I
see
okay my elephants are getting healed
very
slowly o I'm getting
rich notot for Stones I need more Stones
okay all
right what what this guy just standing
here
oh do you think I fight
R apparently those two seem to be fight
then so you can
try I should Scout first I guess I don't
do I yeah that would be a good
idea why is there a random house here I
guess I built it
there
nice I Shield research quite a lot of
food have a lot of
research a lot of resources
explosives oh are you guys all
now
uh-oh uh-oh
you good I'm
good supplies my
walls
build stone wall all
right I have enough
Stone can I upgrade my walls I'm running
out of stones
too Persians can't upgrade walls
more monks for more
healers
Library no defend only
attack let me do this we're just oh wait
why does it look so ugly like
this what's up we're just doing the
attack on Titan strategy where I have
multiple layers of
walls oh
yeah that's the
plan that would actually be kind of
smart
strategy I don't know if I have enough
stone for this your place looks so
clean oh thank you my place is wait who
is this wait who is this who is here
somebody's there do you need help who is
this do you need help building a castle
oh my God they're building a castle we
have to we have to fight them where is
it
what oh
goodness it's Kiara she's here she's
right outside Castle she's not ready for
my
elephants I'm going to send help she's
not
ready
uhoh are you sending your elephant oh
yeah and the trebuchet is oh
God oh
God it's a
massacre cannot esape
me they're trying to run but they
can't oh there's another
Castle whose Castle is it everybody pack
it
up this this one Haack my
treets she's got another
Castle where's my oh there you
go
I three we don't go in
alone
uh my elephant is tanking
upgrade who are these guys do they
fight oh they fight they're a little
fisty no you're
elephant
okay I need to send everybody else
in that's right pack it up pack it
up get out of
here walls walls are these yeah there's
walls over
there you know what let's
go I think I'm going to attack
rain oh my
together
okay where my why do my walls look like
this also what is even happening here
I'm going to destroy those
walls
oh why do my walls look like
what is
this was this the mining
camp open villagers how do I how do I
get the
villagers separated uh-oh uhoh wait wait
wait wait why are my TR sh here oh
someone's why my Cal is
here I've gone too far wait maybe they
should be here
okay are they sh um you guys I do the go
here uh-oh they're strong
uh-oh
uh-oh they're fighting each other
uhoh oh no they're actually fighting my
unit uh-oh okay pack it up and
leave
oh they're getting
close what is happening my trade
cards okay they
left
uh-oh you
guys
build a
gate okay I can't see what's happening
here what is this is a guard town
and Mining need to go out for more
Stones I have so many
trets forget wall you need
units how many
units which units
elephants probably elephants
okay
more
elephants always more
elephants um
H archery 2 wait who are who are these
people oh I can research something for
the
elephants you research this I don't know
if you get the effect to like you you
should
right does pH also receive this
effect F elephants receive plus one
normal uh-oh I'm getting
[Applause]
attack uhoh oh
gosh my my
Army I only have
treuchet oh they're really they have
wait they have a lot of units this is a
lot of units uh-oh oh oh they're double
teaming me oh no oh no I'm sending in My
Elephants uh-oh oh no no I'm getting
distraught I'm sending in my
[Music]
elepant
uh-oh
everybody
fight
uh-oh
more oh it's over uhoh it's over it's
over wait are they
living are they living no they're not
leaving
uh-oh it's
over oh no you can build a town center
in my city if you want if you send a
villager and we can live together
uhoh
uh-oh
[Music]
fight there's more people
inside no my poor
villagers
uhoh double click elephant select all of
them
oh everybody go are they
retreating uh-oh maybe not oh
no h oh
gosh
no who are all you
guys
my ts are my ts working
no well there's a
castle
uh-oh my poor villagers it
up
uhoh I'm trying to send in the
reinforcements
wait that's you
okay
uhoh oh
gosh oh
gosh More Everything more
elephants more elephants my castle is
alive for some reason
that's a lot of elephants that is a lot
of
elephants
no it's okay we can
rebuild we just need more
elephants uh-oh okay they're leaving I
think oh that's brutal I think my game
is is oh is dead
maybe are you okay I'm laging out no oh
I think we're okay maybe yeah we should
be okay we should be good thank you are
you
okay yes is very much lagging oh my gosh
me me and my little FIA
here my castle is still here though and
some STS I
guess oh my
go this little guy just casually farming
okay I'm going to try to attack Raine
now pack up my
treuchet everybody can I build stuff in
your place roll
out I think you
can no I don't
need where am I being attack black
Smith should have one
here
oh oh my gosh my
elephants I have so many
elephants
[Music]
what is
this
oh I
see more
everything okay okay
team
um you guys over here too oh my
gosh
me um you can focus on rebuilding I
think yeah I'm doing it right
now
okay thank God I have enough
materials
um you all
right um what do we
need good question Stone and
then all right roll out
everybody
uhoh
what I'm being
attacked are you am I where oh
[Music]
it's well that's
fine
uhoh
hey
uhoh elephants go for it they're your
best
elephants pack it
up
uhoh is everything good I don't
know can I get in do we have to bust the
door
down are you attacking
I
am oh the door
down oh
shoot let's freaking go
uhoh that's a lot of
elepant my ke are
open
that's a lot of elephants pack it
up is this the Town
Center all
right more people best elephants more
people
who's
this I don't know how to how to kill
someone how to wipe somebody out Scout
AFK in my
place oh this is
Rous um let me
see destroy
everything I'll
try
oh
gosh I need more
units I need more
elephants I could have infinite cross
Bowman cuz they only cost
wood
a okay don't leave what's happening over
there oh my my goodness oh my God I'm on
a
rampage
uh
okay more
elephants more more everything
thing oh that's pretty
amazing oh God okay what do I do with
this people
again
a upgrades are there upgrades to
get
for these Siege units but I haven't been
using
them um
okay
oh I need
more
okay how much do them do they cost the
game oh I see
oh all right
where okay
everybody pack it
up and get
ready oh my rider in her base why are
you
there that's fine you wiped the entire
place I'm sorry I'm sorry
rainy elv weet oh oh wo wo wo wo this is
actually satisfying to
see she has a castle
here uh-oh elepant gooll
out everybody roll
out elephants
okay
coolers going to do this for
now then more
houses how do you cue the
housesit all
right
uh-oh
pack it
up she's on the
Rampage I am on the
Rampage I did lose a lot of units though
what's moai and crony up to
haven't seen we should probably be
afraid
yeah
true
um let's see
you
everybody roll out here can I repar this
oh there you go okay okay okay more
elephants more trebuchets more
crossbowman pack it
up all right
everybody everybody group
up and get ready to roll out my
elephants are gone
you my elephants wait why are they here
why are my elephants
here oh no I still see
them why are they
here they already rolled
out oh
no they rolled out too
much how do I control
them they cannot be
controlled okay
no the
rumbling oh good is attacking
me where where I have no
[Music]
idea
uh-oh
um my
elephants
my
archers is this enough
building to go fight oh there you go
they're woing my
elephants they can't do that how dare
they it's more than enough let's just
get these guys to come as well I like
how they March in
formation oh wait they got a lot of
castles oh gosh
uh
right no all right get ready for the
castles I don't know if there's any
units ignore
it is it a red herring okay the
castles I
see more
elephants power Treet
Castle more
crossbowmen
more houses
[Music]
h
stable heal my units but I don't know
how it's
hard a right pack it
up uh-oh critical mass of elephants
there could always be more elephant
it all right I'm going
to
get to it already
everyone can we go in what are they up
to cron and
Mauna I don't know maybe we should be
afraid
yeah it's way too
suspicious way too suspicious that I
don't see
them
what
uhoh all
right oh God
more My Elephants can't pathf
[Music]
find are they
kill
them okay time for some
Woods send in more
elephants more
elephants
what more
archers
more oh
hey I see what did I get rid of this no
okay okay elephants good
job the elephants are ramping okay okay
you know what okay okay I
understand I
understand the gate is
open okay
fine oops pack it
up is this the Town Center how many
people do I have
now we're on the war path
no
please do your best
elephants
oh gosh what is not built yet and
there's more elephants down
here okay there you
go oh you're making a nice Army here
yeah I know right it's good defense H
okay because they're probably coming for
us eventually I'm farming
them thank
you all right
the elephants are really moving
out attack the
civilians have no
mercy going to do this for
now
uh-oh you good more trade okay
I'm running low on money oh looking oh
no what what
happened my arm is
trapped oh
no can they not go through the
gate what happened there
St oh no oh
no they could be the
defense I mean UNL the gate oh wait can
I open the gate oh I'll open the
gate I think the
gate oh wait it should be
unlocked
maybe are they stuck in the corner
game might be can I destroy your
wall
sure oh I I don't even know if they're
capable of doing it oh oh they should
be
okay I'm I'm trying can everybody group
up oh I can't never mind they're not
doing
anything oh
okay pack it up oh wait
this
one well the game is dying for me
uh-oh oh wa delete my
wall can I delete
it I mean it's fine it's only two armies
anyways okay it's only
two I may have made too many wait is
it oh I can make more people right I
need more
houses
okay
hey all right how about
thing there too many
elephants hey oh gosh it is like the
rumbling oh no C sign oh no
she's back I going too
far oh no wait what
happened I might have trampled
everything all right
everybody crony is up
next pack it up and roll
out everybody
if you need help call me
anytime okay yeah I might have enough I
don't know if I have enough units
anymore I do have
units we'll send those for
backup who
send I'm forming a nice group of alleys
right
here oh is this kar's Castle I'm sorry
so many military units I
know
okay elephant have it
here are we going take more no we should
be all
right oh goodness that elephants don't
know how to path find oh
good oh my
God okay the elephants have
infiltrated oh this is still oh okay I
see okay that's F that's roll
out all right
uhoh my archers have arrived come this
way
uh-oh roll out
everybody more
military yeah maybe I should build a
Wonder but then I need to defend it
rainy oh no that's what they get for
attacking
me
yeah I can help you are you good I'm
sending the
rumbling uhoh but I might need to
build build a Wonder oh you you're doing
good it's too late for need to upgrade
more
St upgrade them and then maybe we should
be going this
way you want to go from Luna Senpai next
I think so
yeah I can send in some guys okay send
in everything you got
okay
well maybe we should I mean we should
Scout but I'm just going to send
everything in and hope for the best I
think let me know if you're
starting I think I'm going to I'm just
going to go for
it okay hold
on you're going to Moa temp I right
yes oh the wall is already
open is it here yeah it
is I'm sending them in okay I'm sending
them where are they
hiding did I send them yeah I am it's
going to take a
while but they're heading there
oh they got
walls
ooh they have many walls it is like
Attack on
Titan
uh-oh the calvary is here uh-oh that's a
lot it is a
lot I'm sending backup troops
uhoh more
archers all
right heading
there me too woo you
broken oh
gosh I don't even know what's
happening okay
more crossbow
go oh I need more houses oh no go go
everyone
uh-oh I
hope I hope they're doing
well wherever they
are uhoh oh that's you I'm
sorry I got scared
ior I think we're doing
good I think so too
yeah I'm going to try to break
down the
doors oh I need more houses cool
me
too okay the gate is
open let's
go let's freaking
go everybody in do they have more
gates blood
gat you have so many units
too
I'm sending out almost all of mine oh
yeah me
too go we need a bus here
too pack it
up and roll
out oh yeah they have more stuffs there
yeah
uh all
right good luck
elephants go
go
go do your
best I'm coming
in oh you did it oh one more there's one
more
G where is all their
stuff is this their
stuff I have no idea
maybe
oo all right roll out all right go
go in
[Music]
everybody this is so crazy this
units it is no mercy no
mercy oh
no
all
right oh Cony
resigned is
this we
won I that a good idea I didn't do
anything I didn't do anything you did
you had so
credit goes to you thank you for the car
I I think you you shielded me you were
the tank you tank the
aggression oh yeah I guess I kind of
distracted them I guess that's something
yeah you distracted them while I built a
million
elephants do you want to move to the
yeah see yeah let's
go too strong the mother of
[Music]
n too strong that was really nice
nice yeah that was
fine k at first like K put Castle
everywhere yo I was minding my own
business and was like yo yo yo yo Raina
can you send some help I'm going to
attack cron I'm like what dude I was
minding my own business and then I was
minding my own business too everyone was
minding their own
business damn Kiara was out for
blind I mean I was just trying to get
the game the ball
rolling I guess so yeah before someone
rolls it on me yeah I guess otherwise
you know people would be just like build
like me like me
peace well me and Ana I feel like we're
playing like a farming simulator me that
was me that was me before Kiara was like
yo help me out I'm like huh what oh yeah
actually the reason I attacked crony was
because she was building the wand and I
you know you build the wand you target
for she building a w she was building a
w yeah and that gives you automatic win
if you keep it for a very long time and
as we see this game was going to go on
for a long time so the Wonder could have
won yeah that would have been a good
Strat FAA was about to attack but then I
was like if they're fighting each other
then let them
be I just did elephant strategy just bu
million elephants and hope we're the
best wait can we see the I think MAA has
to maybe somebody has to press something
so we can see the the the stats or
something oh yeah stats already here um
oh sorry is it quit game do you do you
click the turn to map there we go nice
nice nice nice nice wait where do you
see it oh my Society hi Society Statics
how do you see in the society I clicked
return to map a
lot a
lot
yeah cool cool cool cool cool
a very nice oh when it's come back to
economy I sense a lot to
crony you were
trading t t trading I had 11 castles it
was good it was
good
were yay
know very cool oh our numbers are
actually not bad yeah nice food
collected
yummy wood collected very
cool very nice if you look at timeline
you see like the graph of how things are
changing
oo I
I oh my god wow just like going up
and the tables are elepants all about
the elephants
yeah let me see I want I feel like not
attacking first was a good strategy
though cuz like we could focus on
ourselves yeah cuz we were just chilling
at the
start I was like if if they're fighting
each other then let them
be yeah I mean why not that's probably
what you should do
[Music]
but sometimes the intrusive
thoughts oh yeah I get them
too the intrusive thoughts yeah I
understand in my chat people say like
nobody stands in that
way what whatever we do n Alis
win oh well normally I would have liked
to play defensive too but I don't know
to kill the Wonder and then from the
Wonder everything was just like rolling
and I it just happened yeah feel like
aggression is good it adds the spice you
know yeah I think I underestimated you
guys honestly I thought maybe you guys
didn't practice enough so maybe you guys
wouldn't
know
yo I was a coule how do I build the
barck constantly asking yeah I don't
remember almost a single thing how do I
do this how do I do that why are people
unemployed if if I want to ask for
rematch again would you want to do it
but not now
yeah but I'm totally another time will
be nice yeah maybe this time is uh we we
make it pretty pretty easy because we
have a cheating seat in our live chat
but the next time how about no cheating
on chat
yeah yeah please sure if you can really
control that and we could we could
randomize the siths so that hope it's
not from it's not months from now cuz by
then I'll I forget about the game
already h we it just the date
immediately before we forgot how to play
again yeah what I'm
saying what I'm
saying maybe after this I will put
another date yeah but this this seems
fun like like I I'm pretty pretty I
think I underestimate a lot of you guys
yeah oh my God that is crazy I need to
play again I was scared of you Luna I
was so scared of you no I I told you I'm
not really good at this game you didn't
believe me just because I play this game
this on me that I'm
good you are
good good it's just that you are trying
to save me and I'm
sorry I think everyone need a practice
theme after
all
no but yeah thank you so much everyone
for playing this game with me uh it's
been fun thank you for organizing thank
you for organizing this I'm glad it
happen
finally it was super fun thank you thank
you it's been we almost doing this like
for like two hours actually
yeah just like I expected the game is
going to be two
hours perfect perfect timing yeah well
um for this one actually I have a lot of
uh strategy game um uh each of Empire
year is like one of them while the
others uh there is another game called
Starcraft if you guys interested I'm
it's another building game another
starting game if you guys interested I
would love to make another one I'll try
yeah i' love to but I need to learn
about the game yeah I need to learn to
yeah yeah yeah more more learning more
learning my brain is going to
explode what it is what it is thank you
so much um I we need to guys have any uh
maybe information for the
viewers I don't know oh
no thank you I don't have any being a
great
teammate thank you for bring out the
aggressor thank you for car being a
really good like we we're actually
pretty working good together yeah next
time I won't build the
Wonder not have
underestimated you need build the Wonder
you just have to figure out when you're
building the Wonder is your military
already finished
also were try something when I arve we
only have one person working on the
Wonder but the Wonder takes like so much
more time than other
buildings build with like 20 people at
once yeah you it's you need a lot of
people and make sure that uh your
military is ready to you
know take
why the Wonder I wanted to build one too
someday someday someday somay
somay wow that's all everyone thank you
so much I'm going to end the stre
then thank you so
much let's play again
hope
Bye Bye Bye by
bye man I feel bad cuz I was so
useless I got to be honest I only I only
did like 30 minutes practice against
CPUs before the collab and yeah that
didn't help that didn't help but
like but like thank you FAA yeah all the
credits goes to
FAA for being such a such a cool hard
care
thank you so much
FAA yeah I guess I I I was a mid Shield
I was the perfect mid
Shield I was the perfect mid shield and
you know what you know what I'll take
that
H just a bit more practice yeah true I'm
sorry I'm sorry I was playing SAA game
last night
[Music]
I'm sorry that I was playing sua game
last night I mean I wanted to practice
on stream but then game permission and
stuff and so
yeah the equivalent of not studying for
test you you need to ask like for the
games permission like a week before
streaming and I couldn't I couldn't
stream practice
session cuz it was like it was it was
too late to ask for
permission yeah but anyways thank you so
much guys and thank you to fa and thank
you to Mauna Senai for
organizing for organizing the
collab
H yeah it's one of those gamees games
where you need to ask like permission
like long before the stream long before
you do the
stream
anyways thank you so much everyone for
coming and that was fun I can't wait to
play more games with this group ooh
maybe more strategy game will be
[Music]
nice and gra everyone I'll read the
super chats and donations in another day
a gra everyone bye-bye
[Music]
at
a
[Music]
[Applause]