This fever's got no fall
Temperatures crazy off the wall
Get ready like stop, drop, roll
Not gonna break a sweat at all
Sparks light that candle fire
The phoenix rises higher
Frigid, frozen, no limits
Deadly cold, 10 below
支配したいよ 君の心を
(I just wanna rule your heart)
「いい子」？
「僕の」？
No more!
Fire it up, fire it up now
Hot passion, never back down
Freeze you out, freeze you out now
Not about to bend to you
Fire and ice, death and life, now
High pressure, turn it up loud
Fire and ice, fire and ice, now
This world's all smoke and mirrors
君の思う価値
(Whatever you think you're worth)
超えて超えて
(Above and beyond)
じっと息を呑んで
(While holding your breath)
染めて染めて
(Dye it over and over.)
Blazing, unchanging
No strange thing about this heat, witness me
Hit this beat, rinse repeat
These feelings got me freezing up
中毒性の愛は
(That's just addictive love)
身体中、いま かけ巡らせば
(If you just let it run all over your being)
Can't control, overflow
つかまえたいの！君の心を
(I wanna catch you, and that heart of yours)
「でもね」？
("And yet?")
「だって」？
("Because..."?)
No more!
Fire it up, fire it up now
Hot passion, never back down
Freeze you out, freeze you out now
Not about to bend to you
Fire and ice, death and life, now
High pressure, turn it up loud
Fire and ice, fire and ice, now
This world's all smoke and mirrors
うるさいその口
(Just stop talking)
閉じて閉じて
(Shut it, shut it)
有毒性の「I」を
(That toxic "I")
込めて込めて
(With all my heart...)
We’re caught up in the eye of a storm of flame
It’s not complicated, but a nuanced game
A past you once gave me something I can’t shake
The chance knowing somebody who had moves to make
So what’cha waiting for? You gotta burn it up
Cuz when it rains it pours, ya gotta earn the love
I’m never given in
They’ll never get enough
Cuz you and I always rise above
You got it?
Fire it up, fire it up now
Hot passion, never back down
Freeze you out, freeze you out now
Not about to bend to you
Fire and ice, death and life, now
High pressure, turn it up loud
Fire and ice, fire and ice, now
This world's all smoke and mirrors
君の思う価値
(Whatever you think your worth is...)
超えて超えて
(It's above and beyond)
じっと息を呑んで
(While holding your breath...)
染めて染めて
(Dye it, over and over.)
Produced by Teddyloid
MV by Kanauru