[Music]
la
n
[Music]
la
oh intro was fast what do you
mean no it wasn't it was 4 minutes or so
I had a short oh snap I was chilling
should have started the original time
then I didn't and I wouldn't have had
enough time to sleep
[Music]
really I'm
tired I was sleeping
I so
comfortably it's going to be such a good
[Music]
nap but oh God 3:00 a.m. I thought I was
doing you guys a favor with moving it to
be light but that's like the that's
that's the thing like I was like I was
like thinking M like if I would have
started at 1 hour early you know then it
would have been still I think like 2:00
a.m. EST Maybe
could it
be and you know I don't know that sounds
better than starting at 3:00
a.m.
uh what five oh oh PSD then PSD is what
I mean
then 2: a.m.
PSD yeah sounded better than starting at
3:00 a.m. now I don't know what's your
plan PST gang are you going to stay
awake for
this PST where are you it's 3:00 a.m.
now are you are you going to stay awake
from me are you
what you love me too much
guys
PST ah and then EST is what 6:00 a.m.
now or 5
[Music]
C let's
go you're going to go back to sleep what
when I hope this stream is relatively
short are you speaking from
PST go wash your face yeah I'm
like I want to go back to
[Laughter]
bed
a thank you wow I need to be be strong
for you for the people who are strong
for me I need to be strong for them
please keep it
short
Nanny no if you
[Music]
guys it's an awkward streaming time in
it it's like awkward for for the
main for my main audience which is psdd
I guess no awkward
huh no I don't think I would still be
streaming come on I I don't I won't be
streaming that long it's 7 p.m.
here uh shouldn't go too
[Music]
long it's so hot in Japan I I went
outside today and I bought this
game and bought a lot of other too
and I'm just so proud of
myself to have had the
realization cuz normally I I would buy
games um online in the shop just you
know because it's faster than going
outside and buying a game in
person um yeah and I realized wait if I
the yen is so cheap if I buy it now that
I'm here if I buy like a a physical copy
of it or even a downloadable version of
it whatever as long as I buy it in Japan
how much money am I going to save and I
looked it up and I'm saving €
20 less
USD and cuz since I bought the physical
I don't even have to install
it yeah I I wouldn't mind having more
physical copies of games than I can put
them on the
Shelf what a deal 20
[Music]
bucks that's
actually way more than I F and so worth
it
[Music]
yes and I was legit that made me think
should I buy a couple of games that I
plan to play in the future should I just
buy several games right now while I'm
here
wow I wouldn't even say it's less
convenient
honestly because I mean I have a I have
a switch case with me and where I can
put a couple of these small cards uh
game cards thingies in
there
yeah it doesn't really seem uh like an
issue to me at
all uh DLC region locks and stuff oh
okay prob we already have a yeah I got a
Japanese Nintendo account very recently
actually just for the for the recent
game the
fitboxing game just for
that ah I yes I got top 10 but that's so
I'm going to say one thing about that um
these rankings I see them every once in
a while and it always seems weird to me
because
like what wait what exactly did it say h
okay I see now I don't really I don't
know how accurate that really is because
I feel like wouldn't there be others
from Whole Life up there from Whole Life
English I guess in this case up there as
well is this really H maybe it is I
don't
know it's English speaking based on
watched hours H if and that's like what
what are months something something to
June let me see was it may
or uh I out one whole whole quarter
quarter the second quarter of the
year I'm actually so surprised
that I'm getting it now because I think
uh June I didn't stream that much in
June did I cuz I was traveling in June
that was like one of my concerns was not
being able to stream so much in June um
but I think May was pretty normal yeah
yeah but but apparently I did well
enough to be in such a ranking for the
first time
wow
ha C I'm I'm I was happy seeing that I
didn't want to think too much into it so
I wasn't sure if I should retweet it at
first I retweeted it a few
days
uh uh it was just one day it feels like
several days after
they repost it or
so I I just wasn't sure should I should
I not should I should I not I don't know
but then I decided cuz some people were
tagging me and congratulating
me and then yeah I thought
okay I'll take that
win you had your longest streams by
average in May
H H what was I doing in me it's already
so long ago I don't even remember
anything in
May what was I what was I did I have
like a did I play some
RPG in
May thank you for one
year those charts don't call yeah see I
think now that I'm doing weekly members
streams for the whole year already I
think I'm generally in like um a
disadvantage so to say for these kind of
rankings because I'm pouring a lot of
hours into member streams that won't be
counted and there's no one else doing
weekly member streams in Hol
live uh so far and I've been doing that
for the whole
year yeah so considering that as well
wow I'm happy about that cool cool to be
on a list like that oopsie um yeah thank
you for watching me to so that I am on
the watch
list y be y be I'm on the watch list
they're watching
me scared I'm green by the way wow frog
frog
um so we're going to start playing and
Lu's Mansion 2 HD actually that was a
spontaneous decision
um but I was looking for kind of like a
filler series more or less um and I
didn't think about this at all um before
but I realized why not play L smashion
2 um cuz we play Lu's Mansion 3 and yeah
I mean I think this should be good have
you played this before I'm not sure like
uh I played one with my brother a long
time ago on a GameCube
could that be Luigi Manion 2 or was that
Lu just Manion
one I'm not sure yeah but I think uh
this should take like three streams at
most so I think it's going to be a good
filler series for my Japan trip that was
L just mention too oh okay this was a
Freeds oh okay so I only played the
first one then so we going
backwards well you know I I I normally I
I never really cared about like
remasters and and ports but more and
more now I'm actually
appreciating this kind of stuff cuz it
gives me an opportunity to play it on
the switch for you guys on the
stream
so it's first time for
me yay
so even if this is not one that I played
before I think it will still feel you
know like any other Luigi masion game
right they're all pretty similar they
all feel like same same same which is a
good thing in this case I think doesn't
have to be like completely new and all
that let me pour some water yeah I I I
hope I hope for more Zelda
games to be playable on the switch
Twilight Princess specifically would be
nice although I did buy Twilight
Princess for the what was it
we so could always play it there
right okay so today I don't know how
long we're going to
go but I'm probably going to get hungry
so until I get hungry
H did you talk to crony no I forgot yeah
how far is she did she only do one
stream so far on
tunic forgot about that I didn't mention
it to her man it could have been a
conversation
topic played seven hours did she like it
did she like
it did she like
it I think if she likes it then I must
marry
[Music]
her I love everybody who loves
tunic she seem to like it you got to
like it so good no snacks no snacks not
really she thought it was relaxing I
don't know if I would have described it
as
[Music]
relaxing maybe in the beginning could be
relaxing I
guess wasn't it still rough in the
beginning though cuz you don't know
and you're weak
but okay cool cool
cool cool cool cool I'm happy she's
playing it I bought it for her didn't
I ah ah wait before we start um maybe
maybe we talk about one more thing
tangent I'm too lazy to start a
game but this
is um
I said on Twitter I don't have time for
this but I I'm going to
try um the holos summer
Bingo
exists again like last year and this
time there's also hardcore version they
didn't translate the hardcore version to
English yet but for now I have the
Japanese version uh and there's normal
version and there's
apparently a uh
reward there's rewards again but they
didn't say I think what you could get I
don't think they said that anywhere not
even
internally but they did say that I won't
be as great as last year so I don't
know how motivated I am for that
then if I can't M win 1 million yen what
the am I doing this for
but okay you know might as well like
kind of try doing it right so let's look
at this a little bit what's what's
doable and I
think last year try to have like
remember did you have
to have finished the whole sheet or just
one Bingle was enough right in order to
enter you didn't have to have everything
it doesn't say so far either that you
don't have to do anything I was pretty
strict on myself too
yeah yeah one ah one rose one entry
okay so okay I'm not clearing anything
yet but I'm going to use this as a
pointer Bento I guess Bento means make a
bentle or eat a
Bento make a Bento would make more sense
eat a Bento is too easy
especially if you're in
Japan but it doesn't say and they're
always very vague and and do whatever
the you want with it kind of style
so I guess we could just eat a
Bento justes say make a bentle that
would be nicer though but hey you're
making it too easy for me I'll eat a
Bento I already
did but not since when does it start
yesterday I think or today no I think it
starts today okay I haven't eaten a
bendo yet uh do any sports I guess dance
a sports so I will be doing that summer
test of
Courage is that something specific I
think I think it's
not I think it's just
anything did they did they explain this
anywhere I think that's just anything
that's testing my
courage I do not want to participate in
this like horror thing that they're
doing I don't know if you saw but
they're doing something horror is I am
not interested in doing that or
participating or even looking at
that I need to figure out what this
really
is hopefully it's just my own kind of
test of
Courage learn a new
skill how long do we have for this one
month new skill I mean we'll find
something we'll find something
yeah he just play
RP play an RPG and learn his skill
within well I mean that would work not
really what they probably intended but
that works write a poetic verse I
literally did that yesterday because I
would say writing lyrics is a poetic
verse in my member stream I
I I'm I sang a bald song a song about
bald
no wait let me check is it since
yesterday no it okay it's yesterday my
ball onone counts okay so I already did
this
nice play a retro game okay we'll play a
retro game no problem so I think this as
long as the test of Courage is just
whatever I want to do then we can get
this real easily summer memories talk
about some I talk about memories all the
time we'll get this conect an experiment
I can do that uh or an
event while in this one month while I'm
in
Japan it's a little bit difficult
but organize an event actually I'm I
think I'm kind of organizing an event
behind the scenes right now in a way in
a way we'll see small collapse the do
small collapse countless events we we
can totally count it as that honestly
then any kind of off collab would
probably
[Music]
count yeah it's something you've never
tried
before okay we can do that probably in
Japan relatively easily but I'm very
picky with food whatever I haven't eaten
yet I've probably just not eaten because
I assume I don't like it but I should be
able to find
something conduct an
investigation what the does that
[Music]
mean
huh an
investigation yeah what how who
what
what what would I investigate Play Ace
Attorney that would make it easy but I
don't want to play that no
[Music]
should I do it as a stream cuz anything
here we don't have to do necessarily as
a stream I I could probably like like do
something behind the scenes and just say
haha I conducted this investigation
because I I
investigated how
to what's whatever you know I I find
some stupid thing now this is a problem
though I don't have the motivation to
learn 47 prefectures
I don't I'm not I why is it back why is
it back the one thing in the Bingle last
year that seemed the most unlikely for
me why is that back
[Music]
I don't know about this
one maybe this whole
row but if I then I can't do this row
either yeah if I if I don't do this then
I can't do this or this that's what the
free space
is I don't like it watch a movie okay
picture diary cute why not do a laser
activity what would that be just any
what would that be like sh is shopping a
laser activity I think so I did that
today
then massage too okay I did that
yesterday okay complete catch insects or
fish I just saw a spider in here a small
one I could catch it
immediately H I'll find a way to do it
treat your
parents how should I treat them nicely
or treat my parent that's difficult when
I'm not in the same country as them
right
now uh I could
probably I don't know we'll figure out a
way fig we'll figure out a
way yeah I can send lunch
money have a collab easy fan
[Music]
service guess I I just gotta do another
Fever Night 3D
stream or even I don't even have to do
it in 3D I can just like show up in my
fever night outfit and zoom in
and but fan service generally is meant
to be like spicy but if we take it
whatever way we want we could I could
just say fan service is any kind of like
me being nice to you guys so
sing a sumary song okay easy we'll do it
in K confess your
sins okay we'll do it as a side thing
somewhere I guess I can do this either
on stream or I can go to real church or
I can just um confess it to jmo or so
doesn't say who to confess it to could
you could you secretly confess or even
to
myself write a letter oh okay give a
gift uh okay find a find or show a
treasure okay yeah most of this seems
doable yeah I'll try to get as much as
possible out of it and then there
[Music]
is
this this is the Hardcore
version uh I know doeses it give us
extra entries who
knows probably in one more entry if yeah
if we get a three what did I pronounce
that nice or
what so hardcore it's all in Japanese
yeah they're still translating it
apparently so this is
um concept toi so this should mean do
any kind of like call-in stream where it
has a theme it just has to have a theme
so M for example completed this today I
called into her toi and the theme was
that she would draw whoever calls
[Music]
in that is doable I wasn't planning on
doing a to
Mai just out of nowhere but uh wait we
have one month
time no I won't make it get anniversary
is like after that
then have have
to I guess just come up with a theme and
do it on at a random time
basically uh this one's easy just
sending uh a member of whole life uh a
text of message of
Love okay this one's create a new unit
and and I mean that could be within a
game like Minecraft or
so uh or just within like you know a
stream like girls talk or so I'll figure
out a way to do
this uh this is collab with someone you
haven't collabed with yet easy now with
new members especially easy this is eat
a
bug I know that like like bugs can be
good but I'm not delighted about this
but this may or may not finally force me
to finally eat a
bug uh I would think
like ideally something that can be wait
what what if I yeah like
gummies what if I eat gummy
bugs like gummy worms
like I mean I know that's up
but in the like they were
all they were all just like last year
they were like just like interpreting it
the way they wanted to I took it too
seriously it doesn't say homo it doesn't
say eat a real bug it just says eat a
bug
I I could do that but
maybe maybe I can do off collab of
someone where we eat
[Music]
bugs maybe I can even
combine three two or three of
them either collab with someone I
haven't collabed with and then we eat
bugs or make it
Ian food with like AA and eat and mix
some bugs in
there and then this is the Italian
cooking one uh and this is
uh this one's kind of
[Music]
rough this is um to like impersonate a
whole life member and while doing doing
that uh do a stream
so supposedly they probably want us to
do a whole stream impersonating
someone I'm uh the only impersonation
that I'm good at for a life member is p
[Music]
Senai oh I I I I I would say that I've
been intentionally practicing uh m
but I could try to get good at
Mugo I think I have potential
there can you for an hour
um it could be imagine I do to and the
the theme the concept is doing P or
mon uh H I'll think of about it that way
that that way I would have you know a
good concept and a good reason to do
this impersonation stream cuz what else
will I do with an impersonation
[Music]
stream can't even pick what impression
right now have you never heard it before
of course you've heard it before you've
been here for a long time you know how
it sounds like well I haven't I haven't
[Music]
really
uh come come come
come oh wow so got
[Music]
it Kitt k
[Laughter]
[Music]
who's
P yeah pretty good right but like can I
I never really tried like just talking
endlessly it was just like always like
certain dialogues certain phrases short
phrases I don't know I can do like whole
huge conversations and all
that I'll have to I'll have to come
water I just I just um I'm better it
like saying things that they're likely
to say and if only if they're like short
things but
uh I want to try for
[Music]
sure doesn't say it has to be a
convincing impression but I would want
it to be a convincing
impression
right this one is made for Liz oh yeah
yeah yeah she'll have
fun can you do a little bit of
M I don't
know M
no let me get a let me get
a Rend
[Music]
okay
M by the way I do like mango Jam I I
think it's a funny nickname
but so funny
[Music]
man uh
do you hear this no right
wait it's been seven months or so but I
if you're not
familiar my name is
m okay wait
wait can you stop this for once
okay if you're not familiar if you no I
can't my name my name is
m
o wait I need her to scream I don't
think I can do her normal talking I need
your
[Music]
screams oh
what what what no I
can't more didn't mess up right R is
moreo didn't mess up right ref no I
can't it
starts what did you say
it's maybe
wait no no I got to do I got to do I got
to
P see I I don't really I like saying
small words that she says
[Music]
but uh but what if I just the whole
stream just go
B no that would be boring if I just do
that it has to be it has to be more than
that PO
hello
hell it's time
for
by I can't okay I give
up I've been better at M I've had better
[Music]
days I've had better days
ah I bowed my last
bows but the good like the thing is like
she has also like this cracked
voice um similar to P
empai that's why I guess I I feel like I
can get
there but I'm just not good at
impersonations your Haim was quite good
during day of the diver really I did h
I don't I don't I don't think I really
could
though I don't
really I don't see potential
there no no no
[Music]
no really think I can do rden
that I want to test out I have never
considered
that
ah
to I don't I just revert to Piccolo
[Music]
I know I
don't it's all just P that's the only
thing I can
do oh you didn't hear the references now
oh well yeah okay
whatever let's get into
[Music]
Luigi yeah I don't know I just feel like
what's what's P going to think do a
whole stream trying to impersonate
her she not going to be
like why is she doing
that stop impersonating me for a whole
stream what the
what is she going to think about
that hopefully she'll I I can't that's
the only thing I can do please back with
us EMP I forgive me
[Music]
okay it all finally sorry oh my God I'm
installing
whoa let's play Lous Mansion free which
apparently in North America was called
Dark Moon because this Moon apparently
scatters now I already know that's going
to scatter I already know it and we're
going to get the pieces and we're going
to put it all back
[Music]
together I wish I wasn't whole life
member impersonation and I would have a
little bit more choice I could do toad I
could
do um
[Music]
Lo so apparently these ghosts are good
with him
now H but now they're going to get
confused once the Dark Moon shatters and
scatters do to say am
ah yeah I could do Gremlin am
hm if I can do to I can
do no wait what why did
[Laughter]
I toad toad toad get out of my fro toad
come
on MAR I don't know anymore um what do s
sound like again what does zombie sound
like
[Applause]
[Music]
again I'm I'm not I'm I'm not a
detective
I'm Gremlin
told I I'm not a
detective it's the pain
it's it's a bing it's a bing it's a
[Music]
bing many voices are mixing together
now hey why is this playing can hello
why is it automatic let me say when I'm
switching the dialogue what is this
automatic what am I playing this right
now I'm pring the pixelator
F A
pixelator young
fell young fell
no here we go oh I probably should be
somewhere
else wow this looks
[Music]
like a jackbox screen doesn't that that
look like a jackbox screen but instead
of purple it looked like it it was in
green
am I hearing several TRS later above
each other or is this just how the music
is I think that's just how the music is
it sounds wrong to
me sounds like I messed up the
sound a
weird I don't like this I actually don't
like this do you guys like
this it sounds like I have
two windows of different music's
open you like
it I hope we get rid of it
fast T Tata greetings Lui I knew her
peps would cross again you seem a bit
tense son relax We're perfectly safe
here in this imp impenetrable
bunker anyhoo it's been too long my boy
what have you been up
to I imagine you've been off advaning
with that Daredevil brother of your me
oh I've just been continuing my research
on paranormal happenings and what not y
y yab yab in fact after our last
adventure I became somewhat of an auor
in the
Feld Luigi he's he actually said Luigi
that's proper
Japanese Luigi enough of that about that
let me fill you in our ghal
predicament see that on the screen that
there is the Dark
Moon what it's a mysterious Celestial
body that has a pacifying effect on all
of the ghosts in the shade
Valley K chaa when I heard about it I
jumped at the rare chance to see to
study ghosts in a peaceful
environment it was incredible my boy I
was doing some of the best research of
my long and stored
career that is until something snapped
inside to go certainly got all
hostile it got so bad I had to escape
from the gloomy manor TI here where the
ghosts can't find me oh yeah of course
I'm not one to sit around and twiddle my
thums I wanted to know where the ghost
freaked
out so I settled in and did some
research to figure out what had happened
they should ask me to do this voice why
does no whole life member sound like
this yeah I think I'm pretty good at
this I'm good when I have a
like an immediate
reference a second before I say it you
know otherwise I'm kind of
lost that's when I discovered something
truly astonishing the Dark Moon had
vanished from the
sky SOA and on top of that the whole of
evershade valley had become enveloped in
an eie
fog now I can't be sure but I think The
Disappearance of the Dark Moon is what
caused all this
Messa and what a mess this is if we
don't do something about it to go smart
I listen
Luigi my we just R and terrorized the
whole world Beyond we still my research
will go to waste we can't let that
happen my
boy now I've got good news and I've got
bad news right here
this looks like the thing that Beed her
was so good yo I love the UniQue Ideas
she had they were so well
executed
BR so
[Music]
good like the Dark Souls fights were my
favorite
yeah the thing with the camera being
like kind of stuck uh to her so to
say was so
immersive really liked it and then KY K
coming
in really good stuff yeah I I really can
tell that 3D deuts are already
like they already have a lot more budget
and all that then when we did
ours and I noticed this are like ID for
W's um as well I think but like they
they're like worlds it feels like they
always get two
worlds I only have my fast food
place like two worlds are like two two
stages so to
[Music]
say they're really nice
looking mama M Mia
but this kind of stuff like you know it
only happens once so you got to make the
most of
[Music]
it I already told I already told UHA for
the Far Far Future like once once you're
getting into planning your 3D just make
sure you make the most out of it because
like any life after that like uh
anniversary or birthday whatever like if
it's your own project you will have to
like pay for all the fancy stuff but
this time this one time you can do
whatever you want and you pay nothing
so just do everything just do everything
and the cool thing is now uh since
Advance frd deuts they have like budget
to bring in fly in a member from
overseas to have as a guest like the
company for it that wasn't the thing
before but it's a thing now probably
because they were like well you know
otherwise the only ones you can really
invite most of the time are the ones who
reside in Japan and what if you like you
know besties with someone who's not
residing in
Japan and you really want to invite them
but like why would you why would you you
know expect from them to pay for for it
just to be in your
3DW so that makes sense that's yeah
that's super
[Music]
neat that's really
good yeah so things are always getting
better each
[Music]
year so you know Kyla was flown in for
that I suppose nice
took them four years to understand that
there's a world out of Japan no no no no
no that's not true because four years
ago myth debuted and that is that is at
the latest where they understood that
there's a world out
there
yeah anyway the good news is that I
found a fragment of the Dark Moon nearby
from be's fre
deut yes but the bad news is that I
found a fragment of the Oh Oh I thought
I was reading the same dialogue
again I found an fragment of the Dark
Moon your meaning the thing's
broken this dark moon piece seems to be
corrupted by some sort of
[Music]
energy this is just be's trash in
it yeah yeah yeah
I missed the scrappy almost DIY quality
of early H and always been my favorite
thank you I I I see how that can be
definitely charming and all that like
back in the day when we were amidst
Corona we had to you know use whatever
we could and and you know had a lot of
lot of uh Charming VR streams because of
that and I see definitely why um people
like those things it was more person
personal more personal wasn't
it had more
Soul speaking of Soul V dancing was
really cute she very very like I can
tell like when when you when you like
dance yourself or see other people
dancing a lot um you'll notice more and
more the personality shining through
from people like I think the the better
you get a dancing the more your dancing
will lose its personality actually once
you're still like an amateur at dancing
while while you're still an amateur it's
like easier to see the quirks of
somebody's
movements who's still getting to know
their own body and then more and more
when you really get really good you just
get good and I I actually do think this
is actually so true um but not not
really a bad thing necessarily you're
just getting good and in exchange your
body moves as it should so super
accurately to the choreography and all
that and then um it kind of loses that
that flavor a little
bit but you know that's not a bad thing
just getting good but I like I like
seeing that
flavor yeah yeah you get get better at
mimicking and then yeah you just like if
you're really really good at dancing
you're supposed to be able to perfectly
mimic the
choreography as it was created by the
dancer who made it the
choreographer and
then if you can do that that that just
means you're really
good that you can still like M add your
own
little little
marking I guess but I think it's very
different from when you're still an
amateur like I can't
recreate how I danced when I was still
more in
experienced I I wouldn't say much of a
own twist it's like like you can try to
add more
um what's the word
nuance like you can try to hit certain
dance moves
stronger uh with more punch and all that
but I feel like the personality gets
just lost in a way
anyway mostly cuz you're trying to dance
as accurately as
possible well when you're an am like
you're trying your hardest to learn the
Coro and you don't quite realize yet
when I was still long time ago when I
was like just getting started with
dancing I thought in my brain when what
I was dancing was 100% accurate and
exactly as what I've been uh looking at
when learning the
Coro but
then then you just see it differently
you know what I mean you just see and
feel it differently from your
perspective I I feel like it's similar
with like when you when you just start
learning to draw and you think what
you're drawing is amazing but then years
later when you get better you realize
how bad it actually
was you just see it so
differently yeah yeah using a mirror is
really important and analyzing each
single dance move that you're doing but
but yeah um I used to think I was
dancing super accurately but in fact I
wasn't but at
least uh then I still had my own
quirks when I was dancing and you get
good and then kind of lose those quirks
H so I love seeing amateurs so to
say I I say it in I mean it in the
nicest way I love seeing so to say
amateur dance and learn how to dance
dance and get better and
improve I love seeing that because ah
everybody dances differently
then really intense gameplay thank
you H like comparing like seeing KY and
beel dance next to each other didn't you
see how different their Styles and and
their quirks and their personalities
were be you had this bounciness this
cute
bounciness m
dancing each move very differently from
KY I like that it's so so sweet it has
such a huge
charm the height difference was funny
too
yeah so cute I feel like those
two that's like yesterday in my member
stream I said I don't believe in fate
but those
two they're kind of of the epitome of
Fate
H they really found each other and
like like they're like ying and
yang they're meant for each other in so
many
ways what you don't understand what I'm
mean you're asking me in what way are
you for real you mean what do you mean
what
way they both were like the noobs the
noob newest members until now well now
that Justice is here beu isn't anymore
but you know they were new and they
immediately clicked and like like
they're like The Gamers the endless
Gamers the hardcore Gamers like they're
really good and long time Gamers long
time as in long
hours and and yeah they just like match
really well even their yeah the the
whole like rock and Smith that kind of
fits well too and the fact that they're
so different though and like looks is so
funny like an extremely tall one and an
extremely small one it's just so
funny so yeah I think they they um
what's the
word uh full full fill
no they uh fall end full sounds so
similar but it's kind of different
compliment
yeah yeah not quite what I was looking
for but yeah they compliment each
other they complete each other
yeah so a nice match made in heaven
those
two I like it so anyway let's play this
freaking game man I'm
so stalling oh my God I'm just yapping
lazy lazy wa lucky for us I've got
inventions for all kinds of situations
stand back
Sony yaa yaa yaa
ya Put Your Records On tell me your
favorite song
[Music]
I've done it Luigi it seems to have
regained its original
Power what Luigi what what is she trying
to say and did you hear that whooshing
noise outside youngster let me check my
instruments criminy what crime Min crime
is that what does that mean I thought he
meant like some crime is happening no
he's like what's he mean what does that
mean is that like saying oh Shooks or
so
CUO
crimey I said
criminy like oh my God Alo it is like
that okay that's what I thought all the
folk around this bunker is
gone quick let's take a look at the map
of ever shap Valley
home
okay just some simple
Hills Luigi do you know what this means
we should be able to reach the gloomy
man now but more importantly instead
restoring the Dark Moon we solve all our
problems if we find all the Dark Moon
pieces the fog in the valley will chaa
chaa the ghost will return to nor
but until then all the SCS will need to
be contained that's where you come in
Lui with the new Dyson sponsored by
Dyson vacuum why did they not team up
yet Dyson and L Manion why
not why you're the best ghost Wrangler I
know son y y coincidentally you're also
the only ghost Wrangler no so what do
you say young fell will you help me
capture The Ghost and restore the dark
MO
he he's losing
it he's not really excited with the
prospect I'm hungry already what do I
[Music]
do oh of course you will it'll be just
like old
times but it's okay I think my Hunger
like goes away like if I wait a little
bit like yesterday also I was able to
actually live on much longer without
food and ate food after my massage but
during the massage holy moly when she
was like massaging my lower back and
pushing down she actually also stood on
my back when she was standing on my
lower back and I I was like on such an
empty tummy I was like
who this is really not a good feeling
a like pushing down the empty stomach I
don't know that really was not
good I'm hungry should I order
something I'm so hungry
now yeah like I think both extremes are
bad having just stuffed yourself but
also being completely empty it's both
bad yeah but it has to be something
that's like kind of easy to eat while
while
streaming that's kind of
[Music]
difficult no no more potato chips ah the
cool thing is in Japan I can order from
the convenience stores in Uber Eats as
well I could get snacks from the
convenience
stores and then later I'm going to order
proper
dinner and there's not even it feels
like there's no
minimum amount like in Austria we don't
even have Uber eights but with the other
apps there's always a minimum amount of
order but I can keep my order pretty
cheap when they're not going to have a
problem with it but I always feel bad
like just ordering like something that's
like like seven bucks or
so but I appreciate it
[Music]
oh yeah I can get like a sandwich a
simple
[Music]
sandwich
o
m bread
[Music]
yummy order order something you've never
tried before and bental
you're right I could immediately knock
out those two challenges but we're not
in a rush I have a whole month for
that right probably I think
[Music]
so I could order a ble but like that's
something I kind of want to
eat uh like properly you know what I
mean not just as a side
thing my side
chick m
ah sorry like now I'm stalling more and
it's still not playing the game
because I'm now thinking about what to
eat and there's choices and choices and
so many choices wait is there
[Music]
like that's why I'm here this is Peak
are you for
real game is just an excuse okay you
know we're here for you I guess so okay
that's
[Music]
sweet yum what is
this
[Music]
WOW H I think it's going to take a
moment for me to decide
side oh what about this
[Music]
though I might go with
that I might go with
that yeah that's a good
[Music]
snack should we get a nice
drink what did I have M oh
interesting oh why not add a nice little
[Music]
drink hope this is
good and now now the order isn't even
that
cheap
[Music]
hold I have Yum Yum Yum Yum food food
food yeah no I kind of want this I kind
of want
[Music]
this I'm not going to say it a lot until
I have it I mean there's like a million
Uber e orders um probably per minute in
Japan especially in Tokyo and so many
delivery people I'm still not going to
you know got to be got to be a little
little bit careful
I watched this video today from Fern
about uh that's a English version of
this channel uh that I also like to
watch they made a video about the the
Japanese and the McDonald's
machines
the where you order your food saying how
it's making you pay so much more and
order so much more but I was watching
that and honestly it really
didn't feel like it applies to me at
all cuz I don't know about you guys but
maybe if you are generally a bigger
eater then yeah but like I know that I
cannot eat more usually than one
relatively small burger with just one
Patty and one maximum is me medium fries
usually I can't even get extra nuggets
to
that I know I'll already be full and I
know that and I also like I don't ever
like you know look around all the
different Burgers I always know I'm
going for the same Burger do you guys
actually go for different Burgers each
time you go to like McDonald's or Burger
King or some
on cuz I always go for the same Burger
[Music]
depends rarely not really no no you also
okay there's a lot of people who always
go for the same thing because they were
like saying that like by putting all the
expensive and fancy looking Burgers up
to the top and you having to scroll down
it motivates people to get the fancy
expensive Burgers but like
scrolling half a
millisecond to find what I'm looking for
when I'm looking for it
specifically it's not changing my mind
and I'm
yeah I I don't and if anything this kind
of system doesn't it it motivates you to
scroll doesn't it so you will find your
thing anywhere I would say but I don't I
don't think that's really as effective
as they were like making it out to
be yeah yeah you all know what you're
going to get
huh now what about like how much do you
actually always order guys do you just
get one set and that's it or do you get
like huge orders I guess there's a lot
of people who do get like bigger orders
than me for sure I'm a small
eater so I I could see how ordering at
one of
those uh terminals what you whatever you
call them makes you maybe get more stuff
than they were saying it makes you get
more stuff than at buying everything at
the
counter I don't think so but they say
ever since they got those terminal
thingies the self order
thingies it made everything rise uh in
Revenue but I don't think I don't think
that people necessarily order more just
because they're ordering from
there although it does make things maybe
like is you don't feel as stressed out
that is true to like quickly make your
order if you're if if you're at the
counter yeah I feel like you you may
feel like you have to keep it short and
you know not shop around too much but if
you're at this like big screen then yeah
I I I would feel more chilled to like
look around at my options and all that
but I know like for me I'm a small eater
I'm not going to get a million things
that I know I'm not going to
eat hell
[Music]
no yeah
anyway let's play the
game but I like to hear that you guys
already made up your mind about what
you're going to
get confirms my
thoughts what are you scared of Sunny
it's just a few harmless ghosts well a
few hundred ghosts and they're not
exactly harmless but look here with my
brains and your uh your uh we're a bit
of a pickle here aren't we pickles are
green by the way just like you well the
only way out of this mess is to restore
the Dark Moon which means you're going
to need some ghost hunting gear
son but wouldn't you know it I left my
new Poltergust 5000 somewhere inside the
gloomy manor so now that I've cleared
that blasted fog from around the place
I'm sending you in after
[Music]
it yeah did we just take a survey for
care use it
maybe look familiar oh it's a
DS wow actually wait it's not as
shocking as I'm acting it to be because
it released on a DS and I guess they do
plant consoles into their games if it's
like a was this like was this game a
release game for the
freus I'm so hungry oh I'm going to die
I'm going to
die
[Music]
mate yeah no we don't even have to
back yet I'm sorry I'm yapping so much I
can't believe it either that I'm over an
hour in and I'm just hearing the
introduction the introduction dialog
yeah yeah oh I'm so
hungry this customize DS he says
DS I guess there's no reason for him to
hide what it is but this is fascinating
to me
somehow has an interactive map of the
gloomy manor on it sh sh it'll also
allow me to communicate with you while
you're
exploring huh
that's our communication device huh
wow oh perfect placement
yeah yeah he's allowed to hack their
consoles oh
they're not usually that okay with
this what the actually you're so
right
Mama Mia I'm late to the stream don't
worry we're still in the
introduction dialogue I have not moved a
[Music]
centimeter yeah I know in the Pokemon
games the newest uh console is in the
room that you started yeah yeah yeah but
like it's not so in your face as they
just put the DS in my face it seems to
be like a reoccurring object
wow wow
[Music]
poaha
hello doesn't this make you want to buy
DSO well I used to have a DS I kind of
still have one I
think um no I wouldn't feel like wanting
to buy one
now thees are
old oh
my I just got here how on Earth did she
y for a whole
hour well we talked about the
Bingo and
stuff and it's mighty dark in there so
you don't want this flashlight Okie doie
donkey okay youngst let's test the DS oh
my God it's they actually say and use it
can't believe
it can I just play this endlessly now
what if I play this for an
[Music]
hour you can't stop me you can't stop me
he's looking for it where the did I
just put that thing what the
hell all righty I'm going to go ahead
and Mark an important location for you
[Music]
okay that's the garage I think that's
where I left the poter G
5000 let me just
go yeah let's go let's go let's go let's
go hold on to your
mustache
yipp yeah literally standing right next
to him I couldn't make him wait for a
whole
hour he would lose his at some
point right
[Music]
wow so spooky oh my
God spookiest game of all
time let's go we're moving
[Music]
finally 1 hour 20 minutes into the
Stream
[Music]
can I do the shock thing with the no I
don't think so don't think I can do it
yet the with the
light okay
that that did get something out of me
just now
surprisingly yellow
Yello Luigi come in Luigi you thereare
young fell ah there you are I was
worried that the battery died in the DS
but the DS is so good the battery lasts
forever am I right turn the screen
brightness down so it should be good for
a while you look a little nervous
soon I like how they legit
like kind of hint that
the brightness of the screen will help
the battery because otherwise we might
run out of battery it's not like
unrealistic forever battery wow mhm mhm
you look a little nervous son try to
lose an up AIT besides tiptoeing about
won't get us anywhere you can run by
holding be while walking now get
on run so
funny wow is that like a dead cheap
Jeep I mean with that I I know it's a
stone but like the face looks kind of
freaky oh
wow
so what's here oh
X and
nothing I don't get rewarded for
checking out things so early in the
game oh oh
oh
oh it's the
[Music]
garage
Y what they left for the
back done oh no oh no oh no what are we
getting ourselves
into Mario
Mario what do I see a rat
there
too don't get the key
[Applause]
Luigi oh where did it
go I thought oh it's
smart it's so smart what it changes
Direction
immediately how am I going to catch
that how do I catch this
little
this a bit tricky you can't do
something so tricky in the beginning of
the
game oh oh oh oh
oh I got it okay you can't catch up to
it okay
okay get the hell out of here you shitty
ass
rat maybe it was just trying to protect
me keeping me from
entering this misery of
mine that's actually
nice oh a rat and a key yeah B is a key
right
interesting do all rats have
keys
oh
Knights all
right got to go this way right
where is my Dyson my new
Dyson where could it
be maybe behind this yeah yeah it's a
treasure chest uh but I have to suck
this thing off no damn
it maybe in here
no the car is really cute oh there it is
inside the car I saw a Chevrolet
Corvette today it caught my eye because
the the logo on the car didn't look like
something I knew so Chevrolet generally
has a different logo right but the
Chevrolet Corvette has its own logo I've
noticed the one with the flags one to
the left one to the right it looked
really nice it was black and it I I
looked up the Corvettes uh on Google
afterwards and it looked like it might
have been like a 2020 one or something
similar they all look pretty similar so
yellow really really
nice
special ah you found it good work Luigi
that there that there is the new and
improved Port glass
5,000 it's simple to use just hold down
that R to
vacuum before you go hunting go why
don't you test it out in some of the
junk in that room okay
[Music]
really like the older Corvettes but how
old are we
talking round tail I don't know what you
mean how old is
[Music]
that oh I can aim this of course
okay uh thing is I didn't bring a Pro
Controller I'm just using the separated
uh small controllers right
now they're not even connected with that
connection thingy
so it's not like
ideal to play I borrowed the dog from
jenma maybe I can borrow a proper
controller from
her
oh wow this is really big advertising
for the DS but back in the day you would
already have a DS if you play
this you don't need to be reminded
anymore to buy a DS at this point how
are you liking the hold the G just wait
until you catch some ghost with the
thing in fact there should be a few
nearby and I know you young fellas are
all about learning my doing but you
really should take a look at the guy no
no no no no no no no I'm assuming most
things are very similar or you guys are
going to tell me we're just very similar
to
uh we just mention
free no I'm not looking at that stupid
guy but can I just like get into the car
and drive away with it wouldn't that be
nice would that not be
[Music]
nice DS is still new oh no it is not
it's very very much
[Music]
old
suck let's
go which room should I go into first
where
money well is this camera like is is is
he watching me for
that ah what watch
Luigi
don't going to make me scared it's it's
a it's a curtain with a door drawn on it
in front of a
door
why nothing
the mud room what is a mud room is that
a common room in
houses what is
this wait it was like
beeping oh it's cute it's
cute the way it's sparkling and be
bumping how do
I what
I think I need to do the flash right
probably how do I flash though if only I
[Music]
knew oh doggle wait is doggo friend or
fo I don't remember I think
friend do how am I going to get the do
maybe if I go outside here
[Music]
it's like when I found the
friend yeah wait what did I just do I
turned on the fire does that do anything
oh it goes off again
why
[Music]
wait is this like a thing I have to blow
into it to make the fire last longer or
so wait is this blowing going into it
right it's not working I thought that
might be a
[Music]
thing okay can we go out no a it's
closed okay wait can I get the
rug oh I roll it up
huh ah
oh oh money the big
money n
nice okay I think this is for later
maybe but actually no the other room
needs a key too a maybe I'll go
[Music]
outside there was some things I think
potentially oh if I blow out all the
candles is that going to do
[Music]
something no no secret there oh but look
at
this it's hard to aim a little bit
actually no I wish there was motion
[Music]
controls that feeling when you get a
gold bar out of
nowhere
amazing oh
n why did I get that is it because of
the the the this empty spot here is that
where I got that from just
[Music]
now okay what about these flowers I blow
at them or I
suck
nether it it's hard to aim in this is it
just me who feels like that
what about this chap chep is there a
secret
here
[Music]
no yeah it's a maybe because it's
joycons I don't
know so I'm holding it with like my
hands very far from each
other it's not the best way to play
gold baby I struck gold once
again and I didn't find anything too
special though
[Music]
now H how do you run again I
forgot a b right
okay okay back inside I have a oh you oh
that key works for that door too
[Music]
oh what I found another key where did I
find another key uh-oh ghosts
[Music]
Ghostbusters I forgot the key
got the
existence don't be scared Luigi there's
so many people here for emotional
support oh
[Music]
more that scared the out of me bro
are you all going to do
this it's not funny
oh my
God
rude wait we don't have a map now
huh
no please open up the path
now you
hello could you
please I guess I just got to go through
fast
okay I did it oh there's the
map did I close the map
what huh
oh yeah I know I need a key shut
up I would hope that it's in this room
then but
where there's not really much to this
room
what about like there's some shattered
glass here that's
interesting what do you mean I got it
what did I
[Music]
get mud room feel like I looked at
everything
there a
okay check check check come on
[Music]
how could I
miss stuff when I even rolled over the
carpet there's another mouse rat
[Music]
hole wait that's interesting I don't
think that's where the key is but oh
I don't think that's what it can but
let's do it
anyway that is what it can I thought I
would just get some gold out of it if I
blow at it Gamers never look
up
no where' the other one go gone
[Music]
okay he told me to look up but I don't
give a what he says
I decide where to look he's back seating
me faster
faster open
up
FBI he just for
Bingo I don't think he Luigi is willing
to eat it he just sucks it wow cool
[Music]
well thanks for pointing it
out
funny by the way today
Sunday my first week in Japan is over it
feels like I've been here for two
already
oh low or
sh hey
yo yeah but how do I get the coins in
the picture is that where I would use my
flashlight what the do you
need we seem to have found something
very special there
Lu come in handy when you need the most
but it's just a wild guess CIA
chow what was I just saying oh yeah the
week is over um I think I can do a
schedule for this week
um I'm a bit busy I think but I'm still
going to probably do five
[Music]
streams should be eh should be
possible so relatively full schedule
it's honestly very full schedule plenty
of streams the win after might be
difficult with streams isn't the week
after already New York then you will
understand why it's
difficult but this week next
week is pretty much normal ATT tendency
weeks
so it's not it's not even as if I'm in
the only weird thing is the streaming
times hello
Yello you see the green circular panel
on the wall it unlocks the door all
you've got to do is ah there we are
you're finally teaching
me how to flash
things without uh taking my clothes off
okay wait
didn't oh
what find the
missing I thought that
what that's up there but
um W
aquarium in the door door in the
aquarium why
[Music]
no lower lower yeah yeah no oh it's hard
to
control
ah what oh oh what oh god this is so
hard to
control but perfect stay there you're
going to stay there right
[Music]
interesting nice mechanics no hey hey
hey what hey what why did it go up when
I reach
it
n that
is oh wait there's oh
there's oh there is up and down motion
controls kind
of that's okay it's
[Music]
confusing is it because of
the
candles
no is it though be fast how fast wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait I thought I could still like blow
at it from there but no okay no no no no
no okay there's a
timer there is a timer
okay and I go down and then I do I suck
at the bulb or do I blow at the
bulb I'm not sure what the best course
of action
is I tried with blowing but I guess
generally oh you press X to pick it
up God damn
it thought I just use my
vacuum run
[Music]
it was already going back up but I got
it y yippe I'm so tired I'm so hungry
maybe I should have ordered proper
dinner
already oh yeah
[Music]
ypp he's so
stupid he is so stupid it Luigi this is
why you're never like going to be the
same as your
brother you know friend don't go
flashing yourself with
[Music]
that sorry I had to think of something
funny did you guys
see man the Olympics are all over the
place and when I think of flashing I
think of like naked people right um but
now I had to think of the the guy the
French
guy was jumping over the pole and bring
the pole down with
his
[Music]
jewelry I watched
that several times maybe like five times
because I don't know the bounciness was
really
funny and then slow
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
motion
man I don't know like there's ah I just
would I personally would never feel
comfortable in any kind of like sports
outfit there's several Sports outfits
not just this one where private parts
are very visible I would never feel
comfortable in that and then this
happening to you oh Mama Mia oh oh oh
no but then I saw another one from the
same competition uh where like one
completely failed uh didn't even get
over the pole at all that was sad too
like that must feel like so
embarrassing when you at the Olympics
and you don't even get over the
pole that's that must be really
[Music]
the Walk of Shame after that man I feel
bad like it can always happen like with
all the pressure and but people
were like joking that uh he's probably
only done this like two times in his
life and he's not a properly trained
person um must
hurt to fail like that there's just so
much Olympic stuff everywhere man right
now it's actually interesting it made me
think that my original thought was you
know doing it like with the with the
football stuff just watching Austria
matches so to say but more and more I I
see how interesting the Olympics are in
a different way like just I could see
myself
watching um just like 5 hours of
different kind of
competitions you
know so I'm considering that for next
week
but um I don't know how fast I can get
permission for that cuz they want me to
like tell them part like very
specifically what I want to watch and
then they'll like check if if I'll be
allowed to do it and I don't even know
what it depends
on
MH and Luigi is listening to me
nodding I would just like
watch several different competitions I
think some are overlapping right like
happening at the same time so we would
be like deciding which one we're more
interested on together
mhm no it's not like we would ask the
Olympics
umh like directly like hey can I do this
no I think it's more like a risk
assessment kind of thing if there's if
what I want to watch is okay I don't
know I don't know
I'll I'll try I was thinking maybe
Friday next week could be a good day to
just do like five six seven hours of
just watching Olympics for hours
together I don't know where though where
can you even watch
[Music]
it is there stream is there a worldwide
stream or so what is it like with the
football stuff that there were specific
websites depending on the
country actually I have a TV here if
it's just disconnected I could use a
Japanese
TV uh but then I have to set it up in a
way
that the speakers are not Audible for
the
microphone actually I could do
that then it would be more live than
when I was watching the football
[Music]
stuff I guess I could connect headphones
to the TV and then
yeah listen to that for the
headphones you can activate any of my
inventions that feature green circular
panels okay press a to flash
okay so I will try but I don't know I
can't get permission immediately I don't
know how long it will take um so I'll
have like like probably uh any like one
game which spring r or Luigi's Mansion
on
it um on the schedule as a backup and
otherwise Olympics because they're
already ending like after a week right
so I kind of got to do it next week if I
want to do
[Music]
something but yeah I'm Legit interested
in just watching random competitions now
anything even if Austria I think Austria
hasn't won a single thing yet
everybody's getting medals I don't think
only a has gotten a single one are we
like the only ones who haven't won
[Music]
anything but where you know we're more
like um our thing is more like winter
Olympics for real for real we got bronze
for Judah okay
okay okay
okay
okay yeah we win more things and way
more things in Winter Olympics that's my
cope oh Judo
[Music]
okay Judo MH Judo that's
surprising Singapore hasn't won anything
either oh rip
[Music]
you miss Judo maybe there's still other
judo
competitions just say Australia we're
doing okay thank you can
I nah can't
[Music]
but if I do if I do it through the TV I
think the TV chooses for me uh the TV um
station we'll probably choose what we're
going to
watch uh when there's overlapping
Sports just St y
mhow
[Music]
chiao wait so
let
suck ah yeah they would probably
prioritize anything where Japan is
participating in hey it's so dark in
here and I here it
goes I'm scared
oh wait money oh my God so much
money is there
more no right oh it's in the Next Room I
guess the the the noises from the ghost
are from the next room why is it so dark
can we turn on the lights should I flash
this that doesn't that's not going to do
anything
right can't even I can't even look that
properly up
does it do anything
[Music]
no wait ah wait I see I see I see toilet
flush what what happens
nothing oh wait wait what did I just
flush was there money in there that I
shouldn't have
[Music]
flushed oh
I did not expect that at
all this ghost is flashing
[Music]
me a yo what for free what do you mean
thises ghost is that your reaction to
the ghost showering a yo for
free is that shower in like is that in
the outside
partially no there Windows right would
be cool though in the males our bathtub
and shower were both basically
outdoors in like a garden type of
thing there was a roof that went at
least over the bathtub but it was
basically in a
garden was it was nice
I liked it often the Mal Dives uh
Resorts Resort Villas and stuff they
have outside showers but outside uh bath
tops was a bit more
rare but I I like the vibe of
it it was not Breezy at all no no also
the the fence was really tall you know
so that played into
it no what
come
[Applause]
here
no suck suck there we go there we
go okay my first real suck
action is there another one what what
what's with this
now yo let's go let's go let's go let's
go suck suck suck suck
suck get him get him oh thanks for the
hearts don't need him but I'll take take
[Music]
him outo Shores are fine as last Last
Resort I wouldn't say last resort in a
in
a was that a pun in Resorts particularly
I think outdoor showers are are like
what
you ideally would want to ask cuz it's
really nice
[Music]
okay let's
go guys it's not even about phrasing
this whole game is about sucking that's
just you know how it is that's just what
I'm going to be saying this whole
time it's just the reality of this
game let me see how my food is doing
boom
boom okay
yellow I'm going
to probably mute when it gets
close to
[Music]
ringing what he's sucking me back to the
bunker what I did
[Music]
it mission complete yay yippe oh they
time they timed me wait 20
minutes did I go on tangents in between
by any
chance TW 20 TW 20 20
minutes um don't time
me it's not
fair it's not like you don't understand
this really looks like the jackbox
screen you guys know what I
mean yeah thank you it was a lot of
yapping you guys admitt it too so the 20
minutes is not
real H fan
service yeah me yapping wouldn't you say
me yapping is the fan service
though you say it's the sucking ghosts
[Music]
usual
room Neal room
[Music]
one three two two
weeks
bye you made it back and with all of
your pixels to boot good work Sunny we
might just make it out of this mess
let's see what you sucked up with for
the gust
5000 not
much no no no no just two
[Applause]
weeks there's two EGS oh
cute what does that mean Mass 4 W four
weeks of mass
what what a four four what
[Music]
what wait
unit you miss the ghost designs of the
original game well this was just the
most basic one though I'm sure better
ones incredible I start studing these
ghost post
tast wondering where that pipe goes all
the stuff you collect goes to a super
safe W but it's a good idea to visit it
often to check your progress and see the
results of no I don't want to no I SC
the gloy man in search of paranormal
signals I reckon the ghost that took the
other the Dark Moon pieces is hiding in
there who could it be who could could it
be is it the big Teresa ghost
H
boohoo boohoo you get a
notification for this stream you
mean n it's been up the reservation has
been up for hours too though and it's on
my
schedule maybe you should make your own
notifications don't rely on
YouTube put the schedule make make make
my schedule as your wallpaper
screen to always remind
you
yeah yeah we literally just started the
game but I actually yeah it also feels
like we just started the
stream what yeah this is weird it feels
weird
today ready for some more action oh
you're courageous land you know you
remind me of myself and your age fellow
those were days anyhoo I want to start
searching for the rest of the Dark Moon
luckily I've got just mention to make
our job
easier I think I should mute around
[Music]
now
that's for
[Music]
I
is
[Music]
okay I got
it thank you for the wait
[Music]
yeah just a small
snake small snake to even more not get
any ther in the
game I'm just going to eat this now okay
and in one
go okay why is it
cold what is the whole thing cold it's
supposed to be cold I think it's
supposed to be warm normally what the
[Music]
hell it's a hot
dog
H the monster has some spice to itzy
[Music]
M oh my God right it's a cold dog
now that's honestly a
[Music]
scam is that hot
dog supposed to be hot can't can't be
cold
no it's okay I'm already eating it it's
[Music]
fine it's going to be cold it should be
saying cold
[Music]
dog H I just
realized I don't know why I thought
about it okay well I know what I thought
about it
[Music]
but when I was introducing them Bingo to
you the hardcore one I translated and
mentioned every single challenge except
the one that I fought uh
[Music]
up did I oh did I did I say it I don't
know succeed
in a prank did I say it maybe I did say
it
actually I didn't did I
yeahuh only on
[Music]
Twitter no they see I
they had like a lot of choices from
other members and they randomly selected
them with throwing
dieses I'm going to continue to say
dices cuz I don't
like die doesn't really sound good to
me I didn't watch the stream when it was
happening so
I thought they just chose it based upon
which one was
best and figured mine was one of the
best I think mine was one of the best
suggestions it's hardcore but it's also
very doable and
fun and good stream content
too like even if you just prank someone
over a Discord message and just
introduce that on like your stream or so
without making a whole stream out of
it I think that would already be
entertaining I pranked sh with my
w
yeah
[Music]
what what
mhm a no it has to be since yesterday
starting from yesterday anything that
happened yesterday
onwards me in the dressing room
huh no no no no doesn't count
[Music]
no no that was definitely a succeeded
prank
[Music]
yeah yeah I think it's easy you can just
make a simple
[Music]
prank
H he could actually also
combine the concept Callins with also
[Music]
pranks can try to prank everybody who
calls
[Music]
in yeah everything's pretty easy
but the
bugs is there any way of getting them
without ordering them online somehow I
don't like the idea of ordering food for
something like
[Music]
Amazon I was just going to say I would
prefer to get it fresh but that sounds
like you guys would just say okay how
about you just pick a bug from
the floor then and then eat it
huh but just the fog of getting
something like pack packaged like food
packaged from Amazon or
so generally I don't like that
concept just thinking maybe there's a
restaurant who has
like bugs in their
menu like a gimmick restaurant
[Music]
yeah like at least crickets but maybe in
in in
France
right could be something in
France okay I'm almost done with my hot
dog
[Music]
I have a lot of crickets in my
garden when I get back I could get what
take one and Grill
[Music]
it which is actually kind of a funny
pun because in
German crickets
are basically grills
[Music]
mhm
E I wouldn't say they are cooked when I
SWAT the flies with my electric F water
I wouldn't say they get cooked for that
even though it smells burnt
[Music]
often maybe let's not do
that but that could be a way of me
catching the
cricket that sounds so cruel
[Music]
though could find a cricket in my garden
bring bring my flash water SWAT the
cricket and then Grill it maybe in the
frying
[Music]
pan then it's fresh and I I know what
I'll be eating but no no I I cannot
even fathom the
idea no somehow that's
just oh
but I
mean isn't it more I don't know
eco-friendly making like catching my own
food like in the
wilderness and so self-
sustainable to to hunt and cook my own
food
yeah I don't think crickets in Austria
would have any diseases but that's
something I was thinking about two but I
think it's probably fine
right
okay now my little
drink how do I drink this I don't think
I don't think I have a
straw tape
guess I'll just drink it like
[Music]
this so first we had the hot dog that
was cold now I have hot chocolate that
is cold but it's cold on purpose this
one is cold on purpose
[Music]
y
y what a periscope
what something stuck between my teeth I
think e them alive while the other fgs
are
watching sent a message
[Music]
I don't know if I can get like an
audience of bugs watching me eat another
bug I would have to catch them too I
guess and and create a little like
theater for the bugs to sit in while I
eat the other bug that sounds like a
whole
project go
to eat a
bug Sease me seize Bingo challenge eat a
bug
writes Discord message to n oh hey N I
haven't seen you in a while can I like
visit
you for no particular reason holy
that is a cruel a disturbing
[Music]
idea oh no could turn it into a prank
though could get like a
a fake
one probably can't find an edible one
that is fake at the same
time just like a a plastic thing and
then pretend to bite into it and then
see her
reaction and have her go check if her
real one is still in the cage and all
that and then and then she realizes it's
fake and I'm like ah pranked
[Music]
crunch what was that what the
it's very cruel it's very cruel
yeah but if you think
about accessible
bugs and that's about it they got the
stuff no I wouldn't do that uh no
her bugs I
mean obviously I wouldn't eat her actual
bugs those are huge buggers like that
that's a lot of meat in them actually
they actually would be very nutritious I
suppose cuz those are big
burgers those are some big
burgers actually we should eat such big
bugs because they have a lot of meat on
them I guess more than crickets
but I wouldn't do that to her cuz I
would also feel very disgusted like a
cricet is Tiny so it's so like something
I I could think about because it's like
over in an instant and you can barely
tell
probably yeah but I just watched um a
video the or
dang about
um what was it actually about it it was
basically saying that bug
meat is the same as crab meat I think
that's what they were
saying uh and if we were to eat like the
same amount of it on its own without all
the sea flavor that comes from the sea
it would it it would have the same
texture and feel the same and you
wouldn't be able to tell it
[Music]
apart mhm yeah yeah yeah yeah cuz
they're basically bugs yeah they're like
kind of the same
thing yeah it's just that with bug
they're too small so you can't really
comprehend it that it's the same kind of
texture and usually it's just like
crunch because it's a small crunchy
Cricket cuz that's that's usually the
way you would serve bugs to eat just
crunchy rather than you know soft so
your brain
doesn't understand it's actually the
same texture there's just too little
meat to notice that and yeah ocean stuff
usually comes with ocean
flavor that's also confusing for our
brains anyway I'm I'm so useless today
in terms of game
progress I also wanted to say I started
watching for some reason because I got
this recommendation I don't even know
why it's in my recommendations but I got
like a a
rcraft video recommendation from this
one channel who does only roomcraft
videos and I watched
one um and then I watched a few
more and the one that was really
interesting to me I think it was the
first one I watched anyway was uh what
was her name blue something the first
cartel in roomcraft and it had this
whole history of this girl getting her
smithing skill on Max and then everybody
would lying on her for years because
everybody had to go to her and you know
she got her level even higher for that
so she was always at the top of her
level run scrape run scrape esape I mean
run escape not rcraft yeah yeah damn it
confused yeah run
escape but this whole time I was
thinking the guy who narrates these
videos when he mer he sometimes cuts to
his own RuneScape Avatar and his own
RuneScape Avatar looks exactly like Ki
Mori and I was
wondering is that on purpose is he a fan
and he made his avatar look like that or
or is it a randomly generated Avatar or
like what is going on there why does it
look exactly like cie like
what like it's got the veil and the the
crown and the pink light pink hair and
the black clothes that look
cool like it was a weird crossover for
me I had to think of narissa of course
when watching that because of RuneScape
now I know a few things about RuneScape
cuz RuneScape was never something I
played never never even on my radar I
didn't even know about its existence I
don't think it was probably not that big
in Europe I would think but maybe it
wasn't I just wasn't aware of it I think
I think m
no it was it really wasn't big in Europe
I think H
anyway let's play the
[Music]
game let L what what's
Lua there's a mechanism that controls
the access to the section I saw that I
think the deaths are from the UK
pretty big in no way for our viewers oh
really TB TB I also don't know that was
big in the UK well I can imagine that
but I don't think it was big in
Austria the access mechanism is in the
for I'll give you instructions once you
get
[Music]
there what the is tiia
[Applause]
never heard of it in Germany okay so
it's not just me
right no no no no no it looked way more
I can show you I can show you it looks
like exactly like cie it looked like a
rune scaper trying to cosplay
C for
real okay we're back in the
entrance we're here to make progress in
this
game are they still going to hit try to
hit me
yes okay no problem I'm just zooming
[Music]
through oh
dear oh dear what are you
doing hey what's wrong with you why
would you do
that M Mia
bito hey they even hitting each other
what's wrong with these
boys wait was that door always open over
there wait that looks exactly like
[Music]
themi that blasted
ghost those bruts just stole the gears
from the access mechanism I told you
about I'll use the Periscope to find
them then you can use the map on the D
to hunt him down terrifi looking your
eye just gave me a great idea now I'm
going to call the DS just genius the
Dual scream wow
okay you want to open up the map in the
dual screen oh just continue calling it
The yes that's
shorter
yeah okay but
[Music]
first I
can't what where are you going with
that oh at least the light is back on
kind
[Music]
of no
really what that would do something wa
I'm going to follow that
one I follow you I will follow
[Music]
you isce to
deep isn't that a Jesus
[Music]
song
yeah thanks speaking of Jesus I don't
know if this is a controversial thing
but I think it's so just so fun
on its own and has reached absolute meme
status so I think I
[Music]
can I think I can say it
um oh that was when Sister Act okay
that's why I
yesterday I guess I was watching a lot
of things really um I I was on a YouTube
tour I I where could this be
going I watched yesterday I stumbled
across something that a lot of people
probably knew way before
me
well let me just ask you
[Music]
guys why are you gay why are you gay who
is
gay are you gay what are you gay who is
[Music]
gay you guys know it you guys know
it but I actually sounded perfectly like
him I think just now and I ended up
watching the full 1 hour 10 minutes
interview
basically I know it's old as I
watched the full thing I didn't know
about it and it was so funny the
pasta the pasta the pasta pasta please
pasta please calm calm down pasta
please this is so
funny yeah we pasta I watched the whole
this the funniest thing is you have to
watch the full version because the
funniest thing is like first she's on a
call okay so for people who don't know I
don't really want to get into the
details of explaining what this is that
that's
probably something I wouldn't want to
explain uh it's a bit difficult let chat
explain it to you but it's a interview
you know on a national
TV um
and they have a phone person there
someone on the phone who is like
screaming angry at the guests that
they're interviewing
and
um it's like the guest loses the
connection sometimes right uh or one
time at least and uh you hear that
they're going for traffic and stuff
and you would think that he's just going
to be on the phone because he doesn't
seem to be really invited but somehow
after a few minutes he shows up in the
actual studio and just sits down next to
them and the interviewed person is like
appalled because like what the
I'm not doing this and then leaves
for a bit um but comes back but anyway
it's funny because you you here this
pasta the pasta the
pastor going through some stuff right
preparing some stuff rushing to get to
the studio I guess but afterwards you
realized what he was actually doing he
was literally at the Farmers
Market buying cucumbers and
bananas and then bringing them to the
table and like he kept on like bringing
out the banana and the cucumber and then
he's just randomly starts eating the
cucumber after a while and this
is so
funny this is so funny man he keeps on
pointing the this one sausage he keeps
on pointing everything at them and he's
like do do you know do you know what
what gay people do and then in front of
the
interviewer he holds like one of the
veggies and like he does you know he's a
pastor and he just like does the motion
so in such a serious Manner and I I
noticed even the interviewer has a hard
time not laughing at that one he just
does the motion with his hands and the
Cucumber or whatever over and over and
over and over and over and over again
and oh my
God it was so
funny so
funny
can't that was so entertaining
yesterday oh
if you don't know it look up um what
would you look up what could you look up
to get to that um you guys tell tell
tell the people who are curious guys I
don't want to say too
much I I'll keep
it uh this
bag oh yeah yeah what why are you gay
interview why are you gay
a I'm doing it wrong do I blow it out or
what why is it not doing
anything what is this again is this what
what is this something he
mentioned why do I hear
sounds why is this moving
yeah it was so
Random I think I I think the way I found
it is
because uh on
Twitter in the reply section there's
often completely random right and I
don't like that there's just unrelated
random spam videos there but I found
that through that and that was
actually one of the most one the the
best thing I've ever seen oh in a reply
hello in a reply section
ever
nice yeah and the new auto play is
apparently it's only on Android so
far so you're lucky I guess if you're oh
what the hell big chunky boy lucky if
you're
W you have a
iPhone I guess you could call yourself
lucky
oopsie I got this
one yeah now when you watch videos on
Twitter it's been annoying me for a few
days I have to say something about it
when you when the video is finished
playing
once it will immediately go to a
completely unrelated video
automatically like you're watching
Youtube shorts or something but the
thing is it doesn't even go
to the next thing that would be
underneath in your timeline no it's just
completely
random completely random unrelated and
it's usually something you don't want to
see and it's annoying is there
anything else I can do in
here I feel like
no it's so annoying because often I
think this is especially the case on
Twitter cuz like on YouTube shorts you
see the previous of the YouTube shorts
but you don't like it doesn't already
start playing on Twitter it already
starts playing and you usually you
usually click into the video a few
seconds in when you maximize it right
that's the case for me so that's why I
watch it once and then usually I watch
the first few seconds again after it
loops
[Music]
oh but now I have to like close out of
the new video that
they're giving you to watch forcing you
to watch close out of it go back onto
the timeline and click on the video
again it's so stupid I don't think
there's anything else
here yeah
so
annoying
myy that's a big chunk Lo of
money
W well
that's no that's just bad
insane
but really the rest I can't
suck yeah there's some videos you you
really want to Loop because they're
supposed to be looped I guess too yeah
but no it's really
annoying so dumb oh
jeez
jeese
wait no okay you want to be St another
cheese and a rat are there rats coming
out why is this just their cover
up hello why can I not
suck okay about
this is the motion reacting
no is this enough
[Music]
no I have to load this up a lot probably
right eh
n why is this not
working I would think that would
[Music]
work what am I doing wrong
cuz I don't have the dark Moonlight yet
ah okay so this is not how you do
that I remember there being another tool
in the other games
too
okay fine fine fine fine
fine and next room upstairs
maybe or can I already return the wheel
and that's isn't there more Wheels
still I'm sure there's more Wheels
is this enough is that all you need what
you what what do you mean
[Music]
no they took it from there I saw it or
is it for here what the
all
right is it too early do I need all four
at
once I thought I could go one by
one all right it's on on it's
on yummy
bananas oh no why are you gay not the
bananas from the farmers market oh
no what do you come out when I'm here
come out why are you
gay gay g g g
come
on I'm not good at this
[Music]
game come
on I can't react so fast I'm not good at
the controls I'm
just
no
no no no no no no no see I'm really not
I can't react so fast
no no no no no Shane I'm going to die at
this
rate
please
please no I can't get to you that
fast this one's hard it
is ah ah he came out but what I'm going
to die
let just keep on running
already I don't have
to no he's already gone charge your
Flash oh
[Music]
hold wait how do I turn
around I have to kind of claw cra cra
claw claw my
controller no one I'm too far but he
won't come out when I'm the
what if I'm turn turn around no
no
no can I inspect it am I Inspector
Gadget or what oh my God that
works okay I really didn't think that
would
work
[Music]
what I can't believe that's how it was
I fun I have to shock him when he's
out okay sorry for the
unnecessary
drama uh am I not investigating things
right
now in this
game that felt like I was investigating
[Music]
it oh let's go yeah Hearts I actually
needs thank
you but money would have been fine
too open up
that's a crazy fish
man inspector gadet Mansion
wow boy okay this one's not
opening
fish why are you fish why are you fish
why are you
fish ah
I really recommend that to
everybody oh we got a key wait is
a think we get a key is it for here oh
no
no like we got a
[Music]
key and
now what
spooky
game spooky
game
Scary
help why are you
[Music]
good I I don't know what to
do I don't know what to
do they don't want my wheel yet
[Music]
I feel like I checked all the
doors back see may you
know can't get through
[Music]
here missed a wall a
wall speed
[Music]
surprise the gold coin do
it we'll make more gold coins for
sure a door a door the
hallway I missed a door there n there's
nothing on the
[Music]
map do you mean ah different hallway
okay
[Music]
oh okay let me
check
um
[Applause]
ah did I not how did I
not it's a fake door huh it's not real
there's supposed to be a door here right
here
[Music]
or
here no
[Music]
wait if I don't have the dark Moonlight
how am I going to make the door
appear and this doesn't go
away I
oh
wait this
[Music]
maybe this
room does this have a key has a
key ah
now I feel almost
stupid preview oh it's
m doing her totachi
stream all right let's interrupt her my
turn for the
call not the key for that room
huh
[Music]
uh
what what
[Music]
upstairs this one
oh what oops see by accident
wa disgusting what's is there like is
the Lord of the Ring spider in here or
[Music]
what why is there never anything in
these
[Music]
hello there's definitely a ghost in here
wait there's some cool stuff there
too yeah yeah how about you move
it move that
huh it's just a what do you call these
things again those are not something you
would have an issue with moving I would
think
can I blow over a piece of
wood it's a very soft piece of wood come
on is it the
[Music]
fire got to deal with the v ah do I can
I shock the fire and then can I can I
wait wait can I suck the fire and then
blow away
that
um
[Music]
what oh wait that's interesting
though there's a hole to look
through
peekaboo oh there's a wheel in there h
[Music]
oh this is a thing I can interact
with oh a
bed it's a Murphy
bed yeah
right no don't get no 3 2
1 wait yeah that's the room I looked at
right nice nice little secret
room
oh it's so cool music
[Music]
here I need to
sneeze it's
gone ah aim do
tomorrow I can watch the last episode of
oh of of heart of the
Dragon I wonder if if reera will meet
Damon again and he will ask her why are
you
gay I wonder if that will come up at all
[Music]
am I on the roll or what would that
meeme why are you g you will only
understand this if you watched how of
the
Dragon if you're up to date with it
sorry
sorry keep up with
me
please you always have to keep up with
me that was a great combination wasn't
it of two things that I'm into right
[Music]
now so
ah
n oh oh
hello oh I just going to turn us back
wait but I didn't take the wi
bro I wasn't ready to leave oh but
that's how you get into that room
downstairs okay I guess I'll have to
walk back
[Music]
afterwards
huh I like to binge watch shows wait
till the full series H what do you mean
you're waiting for other Seasons too or
just this season to finish cuz it's
finishing sh night I guess for na or
[Music]
Europe there's always a combination of
you guys
[Music]
huh just waiting for this season okay
otherwise You' have to probably wait
like in total maybe 15 years if you're
waiting for All Seasons if each season
takes two to three years and they want
to do like Five Seasons or so or four I
think the estimate was four or five
seasons in
total
think
that it's going to
yeah like it's so sad to think about the
fact
sometimes I think about this like I'm
glad to be alive now with all these
shows that I want to
watch but like is there going to be
something when I'm
[Music]
old that I'm like in the middle of binge
watching and and then I know I will
never be able to finish watching it
because I'm going to die in a week or so
you know how
beautiful you know do you ever think
about about that
like what about the people who are
currently dying and but they like House
of the dragon and they're never going to
be able to finish watching
that it's
[Music]
sad
oh okay how the am I supposed to
reach
that can I even
I don't think
so yeah it's so it's so sad I know that
went to being heavy
[Music]
but oh hey
yoy you don't read about you don't think
about it but reading the books is not a
solution for every case like I mean with
House of the Dragon okay you can read
The House of the dragon books but you
you
Game of Thrones books aren't finished
like Game of
Thrones later
Seasons you know if you were to rely on
the books you're going to wait a long
time who knows if you're ever going to
get all the books from that guy
huh who knows about
[Music]
that yeah
my Phoenix oi can't be more aware of
human mortality than I
[Music]
am nice light novel title you got there
who's the auor of
[Music]
that so uh hello uh give me the wheel
you already live for several of your
book series not being finished before
the offer died
what that's that's really sad offers you
can't just you're the only ones who have
the ability to finish these stories like
it's not the same if someone else
finishes them you got to finish them
before you
die make can't can't blame you if you
died by an accident or so but if it's
like
H then you really should have scheduled
it
better can't leave everybody on
Cliffhangers think
ahead if you already like 80 or so
finish your
[Music]
story right I'm just kidding but like
for real though like
time management
tole do I leave through this thing again
can I not go back a normal
[Music]
way how's this work
again oh hello I still want to go back
to the other room too though I wonder if
I can still do something there with the
jewel uh not not really a jewel I guess
but um
[Music]
like you don't even have to like write
it in like full book form at least write
some notes to how it's going to
end right you could do that at
least write it in in just small words
[Music]
can't risk it getting e at that point it
doesn't
matter how do I get that can I not reach
that now
[Music]
either that's close okay what
the what the
actual
that's messed up that's messed St
how do I use the
[Music]
Fire Light the
phone
what I'm blowing
he not doing either way
[Music]
anything something clothes that I can
use h
I don't see
anything I don't see anything
useful wait that thing up
there it's freaking American lights with
fans we don't have that in austal we
don't think about
that am I going to burn
myself the other way or what what do you
want from me
huh why does it
close why do you
[Music]
close light the
torch what
torch there's a
[Music]
torch this is not a torch if you mean
that that the floor or I know that looks
I don't know what to do with
that I can't do this yet can
I okay I believe I cannot uh proceed
[Music]
here yeah yeah yeah thank
you next room guess there's a lot of
backtracking in this
game oh wait wait wait I was about to
give up and be like okay this doesn't do
anything
there's a reason why this one's broken
hey come back down again
hello come back down
again there it
is
hey oh money Oh I thought the room would
go all the way down but I guess there
wouldn't be any space for it to land
[Music]
a I figured that might ow
summon some
GS what what's your problem you don't
like
music you want me to turn it
off it's always
you always this
[Music]
Trio hey
you got a gift nice good for
[Music]
you I got all
four
wow yeah he thinks it was quick I don't
know about that okay now we can go and
insert them but let me explore this
place a little bit
more this this clock there reminds me of
another thing I saw on Twitter which was
just you know a children's home a
child's homework where it says WR a
time in some way and then he wrote it
like that and he was like nope teacher
was like
nope yeah nothing special I've seen
stuff like that before anyway nothing
too special but reminds me of
that oh wait this makes sounds
too does this have a
[Music]
meaning Y
what anything else I can move here no
it's that
thing the clock is not accurate
No is that all in here
[Music]
hi I
hick there's a broken mirror there
though I don't know if that means
anything I just saw it when walking
out L the clock oh I guess I didn't try
that I
didn't oh I did have the beat
up there a jble
ha ooh my
first
uh
Yello doing some G gemstone hunting on
the side now can't say I blame you those
gems are
wonder you got a job to do hurry the
up
okay nah it's okay I'm in he's so so
talkative but that it's not because of
these causes you know I already wasted
so much time with tent I need to make
some progress he can't keep on like
talking to me so much
[Music]
yo don't go away don't go away don't go
away don't go
away wait is that all I can do there
when I lift the
carpet can't fall down right
okay what about these fruit
[Music]
no no okay um then I think upstairs are
good for now let's go
down let's go down
[Music]
Luigi well you don't have golden spiders
do you you need golden spiders for them
to turn into gold bars that's the issue
[Music]
ohoh that's the real problem
n what do you want yeah why it long face
Luigi oh genetics I suppose rude I'm
self-conscious about my long face
okay the tears don't fit into the
mechanism and what the why not
those bir BR ghost must fend them
something I suppose I'll have to repair
them in order to make them work so
you'll have to stall a little bit longer
do something else have
fun oh
yes why is he celebrating I'm not
proceeding in the game but you you say
that's a mission
complete no
37 I was thinking maybe okay with be
funny if it was 30 minutes this time but
37 what did I
do we not talking
about why are you gay I talked about
that for a bit I don't know what
else oh man I ate I ate
okay thank you
it's not my fault it's my tummy's
[Applause]
fault good work I knew I should have
called you first uh let's see gears
gears
[Music]
gears come up with something to make
again
[Music]
let's unload the PO 5000 and see what
kind of ghostly cies you
got not much oh but I mean yeah and I
got those I got those um other thingies
to the Collectibles the other
Collectibles are you not going to show
those huh oh you're not going to show
those I see how it is undermining My
Success missions auto complete this game
when go what are you talking about what
does that mean what do you
mean what I was right these new ghosts
are very interesting indeed they won't
be making any more trouble for us now
that they're in the vault fall out
this is this this this one of the
vaults oh how far back in time are
we was this a tutorial you
mean
N I didn't take three hours for ear no
shut
uping paranormal signatures and ghosts
also helps me find you in the Paris
schope I need to figure out a way to
make those gears work okay
byebye A2 gear up oh that's what I just
did I only got
bronze holy at the the health I
lost so much health because I I didn't
understand how to capture that one go
[Music]
oh you already finished it oh
okay that looks interesting
[Music]
uh music ah I remember there's a grand
piano in the library maybe I gohost just
playing around on it let me just Mark
where you need to head on the gold GS
map
[Music]
M this is the strongest paranormal
signal I've seen yet
[Music]
[Applause]
let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go yaa yaa
Sky I don't know what he says there
honestly
um
crank wait crank
crank they're gone why the are they
gone so that they don't annoy me anymore
at this point I've been plenty annoyed
I haven't been that annoyed by them to
be
honest Crank that
you
[Music]
you it was quite the great invention he
made there
oh
oh wow I didn't realize that that's what
was going to happen
I honestly had no
idea
rats there's rats in the castle there's
rats
everywhere there's rats
[Music]
everywhere do you guys think
alent is there a chance okay if you read
the books Shut up but do you think
there's a ah zombies
you think there's a chance that Allison
will don't answer if you read the books
do you think there's a chance that
Alison will go to
reira she's already left the castle and
she's kind of like Fed Up and useless uh
at this
point
no I wish I wish she would but it would
be a
huge a huge step and abandoning
abandoning her side completely I'm sure
at this point she's like
them all but she also can't abandon
them yeah but when she talked to her at
the church I feel like she still didn't
have you know she was still in the
council
so you
know anyway I wish I wish they would
reunite at this
point there's a part of me who can you
know kind of
Imagine a situation
where Alison at this point is like okay
I've been fired I hate my kids my kids
hate
me I'm not useless here anymore I know
the truth now and I
think I should support Rene right now
you know I feel like there's to a
certain extent it kind of makes sense
seems
reasonable but I also understand why she
wouldn't do
it that's too big of a step to like just
you know leave everyone else of their
family
behind at this point she's too deep into
[Music]
it what is she going to do though what's
she going to do
[Music]
hello rock paper
scissors very very cultured
young ghostman aren't you okay you know
what we're going to we going to speedrun
this one now I don't accept anything
below uh or I mean above 20 minutes oh
my
God got be the
spiders wait
no no no my
[Music]
score okay we got to be below 20
minutes this thing I forgot do I oh okay
o wait a second there was another one of
those somewhere
else guess I didn't try sucking on it I
only flashed it
[Music]
how can we be fast but
also look at everything properly oh what
the
[Music]
hell huh oh I like this
tune no you can't make me
up you can't make me ah what the hell
huh that's not how you sort those books
you should hire so ah no oh why did I
miss it okay don't get hit don't get hit
that's not good that's not good wait
they they're coming
back maybe one more behind
me
hello wait no wa I
miss oh my God ow my health no I'm going
to have be lost so much
health at least I got some golden
animals
okay got to go down from here huh dining
room oh I'm got to do this in style
really cool wow SC I did
it can you guys do that
H all right I sometimes do weird things
I know like this cuz the X disappears
ah there was next where did it
go probably no point in doing
[Music]
that
oh what will you donate oh I feel like
that's a hard one to find
bro cuz I normally I never look at the
freaking
[Music]
ceiling
169 gold oh you can't even see my my
gold
counter
ow stop I
freaking what's
this what is
that you want to be flashed oh
[Music]
wait the clock is
ticking oh and now I go in all right
then I guess I'm going
in now I'm a level Below in the
[Music]
kitchen not
this kitchen reminds me of that game we
played little nightmares I think or was
it the
other the
[Music]
chef
yes no hits
baby is that it you coming
again come again ah don't touch me
[Music]
okay no hits no hits no hits I can do
it
yay let's go good job
Luigi good job anything else here um
[Music]
H I don't want to miss anything
important but I feel like there's
nothing maybe the bridge re refrigator
oh okay
yeah ah we bring it to the fire don't
we wow sugy such a
riddle do you mean there's a f game
coming out there's already a lui's
mansion
free are you talking about I'm talking
about little nightmares
ooh another
one we have
arrived boss fight already wow s under
20 minutes may be possible but this
looks like it might be
rough why is his head like
[Music]
that why is his head like
that
oh is this fight difficult is there a
gimmick is there a gimmick or is it just
a trying to dodge the
books where is
he where is
[Music]
he
what
ah me
H I got
you
hey ah do I have to get him before he
does the me me me me me me me or was I
just too
far probably
not well that's not it there's another
one no what why are you why why you
making these evil laugh
sounds
watch okay get him get him get him get
him get him get him how many are
there first
H okay this one is going to die now
second time in your life baby can you
even call that life at this point
still take
out no I can't I I I think it's really
you have to do it before the me me
[Music]
me no no
where
[Music]
okay he do be
panicking
y I've investigated the
music
yippee was that a whole
chapter me worried oh my God but totally
did it well maybe you're even under 20
minutes this time possibly
so oh yeah oh we're actually getting
this is how fast a mission could be if
you don't
tangent this is how fast I could
[Music]
10 only silver I did lose a bunch of
Health but come
on I'm looking cute today you too
you know recently I've been getting even
before I went to Japan though um the
past two 3 weeks my eyes have been red
like a
lot like very weirdly red not always
like sometimes it's less red sometimes
it's more red you know the white part in
my
eyes I can't really find an explanation
as to
why I don't know why
but I'm thinking maybe I have an
infection but then it would be probably
constantly because okay I think when it
started this when I was wearing
lenses for a whole day and then I took
him out and I noticed that my eyes were
super red um but in an interesting way
it Formed like a red circle A Perfect
Circle
around the colored part of the eye right
not just like generally red in in random
patterns
no it
was a perfectly shaped
Circle and that made me feel like that's
weird they're not just
red it's around the eye and then after
that I haven't really been paying
attention that much
um for a week or so but now that I'm in
Japan I noticed my eyes have been super
red again not in that circle shape but
still no I thought maybe I had an
infection or something uh when that
first happened
though probably fine but I got a retal
around my eye when I hit my head on the
road eh what in the white
[Music]
part no no it's even like it's not it's
not even when I'm staring you know on
no it happened to me when like um during
the studio day too but then I then I
excuse it with being tired on the day
when I was in the studio the whole day
I was thinking I guess I'm just tired
but it was also when I was not tired
then it got went away again and you know
I don't know if I have it right now but
I had it when I woke up today I think or
yesterday
also I don't
know it's probably fine but it scares me
seeing my eyes so Rand
how many missions are there in this game
by the
way I just finished three four now
three third
one is all of you finally step out of
your brother's Shadow and be recognized
as true
hero did that happen after this game I
don't think so wrong false Hopes And
Promises EAD you little
okay next
please 25 missions wow wow wow
wow it doesn't happen I'm not getting
recognized as a
hero what of course I'm feeling like
finishing it but I don't know how far we
get
today 25 missions and six bosses are
bosses outside of the
missions an attachment is it the the
thing yeah it's the
[Music]
[Applause]
thing we got
it we got
it the first Manion what do you mean the
first
Mansion we're leaving this Mansion I
guess it is Tiny there's more than one
mansion
[Applause]
I didn't know cuz in Lou just mentioned
three and one it all is in the same
building
constantly I didn't
know I thought is this in the same
building the whole
time
[Music]
huh makes sense cuz this is and they
back hey you I was not supposed to
get hurt
oh what
the can I restart the
chapter I can I
[Music]
can
don't turn me immediately like
this uh W spring was definitely longer
than expected but
I trust's Manion to be um not as long
should stay around free streams I
think wait was there anything to
activate with the dark light device wait
but said find the dark I don't have it
yet well of course I have it
right I don't have no
[Music]
don't why were they gone and now they're
back
again
why okay I want the dark light device
please where is
it where could it
be why is this fire blue
[Music]
now you please the
hell why you bully me like
[Music]
that is he what is he
throwing I'm
[Music]
scared big boy is dead where's the other
one here
easy did you bring the triple again or
okay yeah as always no no no no no no no
no no no no no we're not doing this
again get out of
there I know this
time I I know how to do it this
time another one right uh
wait okay
okay four of you
go that's
new they're
multiplying beito
Basta okay guess we haven't entered this
room have we
not oh it disappeared is that supposed
to happen you just took the the you just
took it away from
me what
now what
[Music]
now
um how do you I was in the room before
how do I enter that if they took away
the door can I enter from
here
[Music]
no what I looked for the
hole
above okay I'll just go up the floor are
we on the lower floor right now
oh what
hello Lu what the door's gone what the
that's all you'll say I'm sure
there's another way to the room oh
really oh really you think
so course there is another another way
do you know the way why are you
gay well if they took a door from me
they should have put a door elsewhere to
make up for
[Music]
it oh the time changed is that my
Nintendo switch
time not even the minutes are accurate
what the
hell uh where did they where did they
just go wait wait wait the clock is
gone that's not how I'm going to get
that back
[Music]
H what
now help help Chad I don't want to take
20 30 minutes again for this
Mission I guess wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait no they went for the to the
other room next door
maybe I know I need dark light for that
but I don't have it
yet following the ghost right now I
guess so they would probably be in
here the
[Music]
file
why why happened
twice why
[Music]
do I need to check in the other room
again here wa let me check first are
they are they there are they
[Music]
there no but
maybe no wait where are the
fireplace in the room I was just in
[Music]
okay the
fireplace I can turn it back on or oh I
can go through
hello
hello oh
M
oh there it
is take wow it's
[Music]
beautiful what are you doing don't go
away don't don't ghosts and
their abilities to go through walls
oh I I thought I had to go to the next
room but I was going to try this out
anyway oh oh uh okay oh hey it's working
ah I was about to ask you guys how do I
do
this I can't flash
him just suck off the
glasses oh
yeah uh-oh don't get in his punch
[Music]
radius
uh
[Music]
easy
easy we got it is that a mission on its
own I wonder probably right that's a
mission I think getting this thing
yippe it
is feels like it may have been over 10
minutes I don't know try it out with why
okay but you're not adding that to my
mission time are
[Music]
you I have to wait
until or I don't know I guess I can't
use it there that's not something to use
it on try it out he says something
specific in here
or uh ah wait there was a door here
right okay okay
okay I get it I get it
bubbles oh wait I suck I suck bubble
door comes
back easy math
[Music]
thanks for the
raid I like how he sings
along so immersive actually that is
crazy immersive that the protagonist the
character you play is singing along to
the bgm that normally PGM is just for us
to enjoy and the character in the game
is not supposed to hear
it interesting he sings A Lot why does
he hear it why does he hear it
what is there stereos blasting through
this whole
building have you been hearing that
creepy laughter whoever is releasing
those spirit balls seems to be enjoying
himself um not having any luck with the
pariscope so it's up to you to find him
and put a stop to him in a separate
mission right no this is a longer one
capture whoever is releasing the spirit
balls well but first I don't know if
this is where he wants me to go but
it's where I want to
go okay I'm not getting that a second
time uh what was the button this
[Music]
one nice is that key for that door
because I probably need fire for that
first or is it for a different
[Music]
door is it for this door
no I've been here before but maybe I can
use the light on something here
too what about on this do I get a golden
ghost out of
[Music]
it no I don't think this is doing
anything no what about mirrors are
mirrors interesting
no what about
this oh
[Music]
M no I don't think I don't think I guess
I mean tell me if I'm wrong but doesn't
seem anything is
[Music]
there ah money money money
get out of there
woohoo what if I don't s these balls in
immediately will the money go back
inside wait there's something missing
here
obviously I don't really care about
getting it back but
okay I get rewarded Le
yippe okay I think was there something
in
here I feel like there was but maybe
there wasn't or whatever was here is
gone
[Music]
now
what oh it's just a little so
huh
[Music]
ow that's it they do have like random
surprise actions for no reasons in in in
rooms you have already explored uh in
other Luigi games too I think pretty
normal huh
[Music]
M
ah just
checking just making
sure okay nothing here who's taking a
shower I there was a ghost here before
and I think they just left the shower on
[Music]
where do I
go
ah
huh is this
new did I go here before oh yeah the
library oh that SP web wasn't there
before they're blocking me
off
rude I was was here
before I have a right to be
[Music]
here oh that makes the elevator work
doesn't it oh no no why would it it just
gives me money again
right
wait wait what did that just do I guess
it's empty because I already opened it
before and it just Clos this again where
the do I go
[Music]
dog bone they threw me a bone but not
that kind of bone that I wanted I wanted
the more metaphorical bone to be thrown
not a real
[Music]
bone door missing
oh thanks for throwing me the
metaphorical bone door
missing oh
dare aha
[Music]
y oh is that a grill PE PE what wrong
what's that what
what oh
nice
PE what is
that h
ow I burned
[Music]
myself ow wait how long does that
need oh
oh the full length no I bur
[Music]
myself what does that
mean am I not ready for
[Music]
that a tra not a thing okay what's it
the
grill maybe for ah for later when I can
take the fire and then I'll spit it onto
the webs I
[Music]
guess I wish I could suck
that I could suck that
in was that just a picture of a
different mansion that I'll be going to
on the wall far away like that could
have been something like that okay well
that room didn't help me did
it I don't think the room helped
me brazing is something I've never done
[Music]
before brazing is just not my kind of
thing help guys I need your help help
you need to go get in that room go down
okay thank
you we
[Music]
do what
I don't see a door showing up oh no no
now I
see that was not a door something's
glowing above
too why are you so far away
[Music]
balls don't don't wait wait wait wait
I'm really bad at aiming why did I
create
this for a little bit of pocket money
really but isn't there a door on like
right here is it on the on the
stairs I guess it could be on the
stairs uh oh it would
be I guess it would be
here
no no because then the map switches when
I'm up
there E I thought shouldn't there be a
door here
[Music]
the map makes me think there's a door
there in the
hallway which
Hall a that ah
[Music]
ah
here e didn't I already bring this door
back what this is so
[Music]
confusing
so oh we're outside
[Music]
again what is this another kitchen or no
it's the same kitchen but they're busy
in here again okay oh wait we're like oh
H in a nice
Garden can I do something with the
flowers no can I shock them that's what
I
bought yeah that's what I was trying to
do I think in the very beginning too but
I didn't have a flashlight
[Music]
yet that would be fun to stand on when
somebody's spinning it that fast eh no
honestly it wouldn't we had something
like that on the playground that I used
to go to as a
child damn that made me feel
sick but the frill baby the frill is
what it's all
[Music]
about need that F
baby is there one missing here yes
symmetry guys oopsie
ah symmetry is one of the most beautiful
things in the
[Music]
world
ah
ah fancy playground oh no is that so
fancy I do actually yeah not really see
this kind of thing that often
true might be a little bit F
down those bars are making clunky drop
sounds same kind of
clunkiness as when bio
walks
[Music]
around did you see she's releasing
slippers as her merchandise and Sh only
is releasing a belt
I'm Bel the slippers though they look so
cute but like I think they're going to
be small like my own slippers right
those the slippers that I released were
even small for me kind
of where am I where what where am I what
can I do what is this something oh oh
it's behind the water I thought it was
in the
water okay then that's all I needed to
do probably
[Music]
they're larger larger than the ones I
have could you compare the
measurements cuz my slippers barely fit
anybody like probably don't fit any man
feet
[Music]
usually don't you dare hurt don't you
don't you hurt me
[Music]
T slip is kind of small too yeah if I
knew ahead of time I would have asked
him to make them bigger but such
[Music]
things are
difficult to
know uh one thing I wanted to do today
in the Stream don't make me forget it is
show you some preview picks of merch I
was thinking because I actually don't
have everything yet I was thinking of
showing them step by step only one at a
time one piece of merch at a time cuz
I'm still waiting for the last piece of
merch uh to be made into pictures it's
usually always very last minute we still
have like
a where am I going what am I supposed to
do we still have like a a week or two of
[Music]
sales what I go
now where I go
now ordered the mer yesterday thank you
yeah I'm going to show you something
today before I leave you
back outside from where I came
from did I miss something thought I
looked pretty thoroughly
[Music]
going to order the merch
soon
ah
what what what did he build this himself
here or
what what the
hell now it would be a time to call me
and explain this
[Music]
Skitty oh n secret path to something oh
key but I would like an explanation as
to who built
this is a
narcissist c s with 28 enmies re SLI is
4 31 oh yeah free enemies are really not
much but at least they're a little bit
bigger like I think slippers are really
good merchandise but we really would be
nice if there was at least two sizes
like one small like female size one male
size cuz feet are unfortunately very
different
from yeah not just person to person but
especially the the biggest difference
is being
us men and
[Music]
women oh God how do I do this again uh
make him make him make him hit
[Music]
me yeah one size fits all does not why
did I let why didn't I let him
go doesn't work for feet yeah
agree where'd he
go where'd he go where'd he
go where'd he go
ah playing hide and seek
again don't you dare hide again I don't
have time for
this there was a pain to find 47 CM
shoes
really there's no point in getting
getting that again right
[Music]
when are you going to make another song
I'm working on it right
[Music]
now working on it but Kima isn't even
that long
[Music]
ago is this just for me to walk through
this door here
so why I'm here oh it's
[Music]
close
uh oh I can get that from
here wait it's The Power of fire up
there
what was kind of there
but don't think I can get it yet
huh oh can I
maybe I can can
[Music]
I if I get it to be a flame and then
suck it no
no
what what is the dump
waiter Ah that's what you call
[Music]
that that's what you call that uh
that's not very dumb it's a smart
[Music]
waiter I would call that a smart
waiter how did I make that work
[Music]
again thanks for the
memberships how does this work again oh
my
God why does it not open
[Music]
ah sorry I'm stupid
but sometimes I don't see these things
they blend in too
[Music]
much what's so funny eh
eh she a little bit tired
oh cute I love you were laughing okay
then no problem okay you can have the
Mansion to yourself you can have any
Mansion to yourself you cute I love
you how could I be mad at was there
something there just
now oh there was did I
[Music]
imagine a
should is it the the building the room
where it comes
out huh
what ah the
table thank you I forgot what you go oh
hello no no no no no no what the
[Music]
what
the what what's with them now why are
they so complicated come
[Music]
on is back boo is happy that table is
back and food is back right I did that
for you you can't be mad at me now right
why would you BL me I brought you the
food
boo
Bo
wait
booh can talk this BR I can I can spawn
all kinds of things for you
y
[Music]
woohoo I can spawn all kinds of things
you want maybe I'll try why are these
things
glowing oh oh do I want this
back yeah more food for you that's what
you want
right don't go away
B
CH see I brought you more stuff
back wait can I really not spawn
something here what the no don't
play with me what the ah oh hey
[Music]
what wait what does that mean
h oh how you do that
[Music]
wait I'm going to die does the bone give
me an extra
[Music]
life wait okay okay
okay I don't know how this
works oh I'm supposed to flash I thought
it was all about the the dark thing dark
light all the Bon is for
that
okay
[Music]
um no no no it is a dark thing isn't
it but I don't
[Music]
understand oh now it's working
what he what what no you just a ball
what that was fast
suddenly why was it suddenly so
[Music]
easy was it was hard to get to
him then he was just like bouncing
around super fast to suck him
Ino oh yeah I wouldn't say I made it
harder he did
[Music]
it it was weird you know you saw I had
him like kind of there in my light
several times not
this okay this was for minutes again but
it was a long
[Music]
Mission when you revive once does it
make your rank go down I
[Music]
wonder yes kind of a mini
boss are your lesbian vampire why are
you gay why are you gay are you gay who
is
G hello lesbian
[Applause]
[Laughter]
vampire I hope you know the meme
otherwise this is weird
I hope you know do you know the meme do
you know the
meme excellent I'm positive that my dark
light device worked even though you had
some troubles there
obviously then you is
G then who is G
cute boo are so cute they look like
cats they look like
cats his
hair ra Rising highrise full of ghost
the challenges awaits you and you fellow
ghost Huns oh is it like online
multiplay
layer it's concerning to find a boo in
the gloomy manner boo always spell
trouble especially if they G up if you
see anymore be sure to capture them
right
away I have a special container just for
boo down the funny story actually you
may have remember that I used to have a
device called the p portf
[Applause]
I think you just asked me if I'm
gay gay g h hold on a sec the Periscope
is acting up something's not right Luigi
the signal coming from the gloomy
manners all give me a minute I need to
figure this
[Music]
out ah boo boo boo
boo clean up those darn spider webs
they're blocking our progress and they
ruin the furniture and there just plain
grass I
agree
M yeah what do you what do you want me
to do suck up every last web but I
thought that doesn't work it didn't work
so
far thought I had to burn them because
they were so
thick is this the last mission for this
man that would be per
perfect if there is you I said 25
missions and every man makes five
missions and seems to be five manners
the math adds
up the math just adds up I want to check
in these rooms was there something
[Music]
to
oh no uh was there
something to put my dark light onto
[Music]
no not in this
one new Paper Mario
Boos not sure what they looked
like I know this will add to my
time but I just want to make sure I'm
not missing any secrets wait did I
never activate this BM BM machine
[Music]
surely I did was this not the bathroom
nah I have never been
here
oh oh don't go house oh look at
that yeah where'd you
go what the
hell don't run away from
me oh that's the first one I could have
gotten that way earlier because all this
needs is the
[Music]
flashlight dropped like a leaf
yeah they
open
what what is this why is this so sus why
is there no meaning to this
[Music]
H is that
all over
here ah the dog ah the dogle yeah the
ghost do right we saw him and then ah I
should have I should have gone out there
when the ghost Doo was there oh my God I
missed
him is that
[Music]
bad you B ow
that hurt
me am
I they want me
[Music]
the
no
[Music]
ah wait what exactly
oh but it doesn't have to be all in this
room R why is there an exclamation mark
there 41
freaking spider
webs
[Music]
41 a little bit difficult in between all
these statues not going to lie
[Music]
okay at least there's not one in between
these
guys does it then check this room okay
and now it's sparkling again
okay I hold di I
I exactly 41 are you kidding me these
they're even like relatively small so
that's messed up if you ask me uh-oh
yummy
is there any in
here um light could turn back
oh I wasn't
[Music]
done no not here I guess they showed
them with the exclamation marks never
mind okay
[Music]
that's a spider egg oh wait no
way how do I shoot
[Music]
it wait how do
I wait how do I shoot it surely there's
a way to shoot it shoot it or
[Music]
ah oh oh get out of the way get out of
the way oh now we're playing
with fire is there endless amounts of
these coming from there or what
[Music]
uh-oh as long as I got the fire oh no my
egg my egg I think it's is it no thought
it was maybe the solving but I think
it's
fine wa wa what was
[Music]
that another
speeder oh I think this is the way to go
you really should clear everything up
with fire here it's just too much stuff
ow oh okay bye-bye they just scaddle
[Music]
okay did I get this before no
maybe
not what's behind the cheese I had the
cheese
before there's nothing behind the Treese
there just go into this
room do you have this to do this in
every
manner later
[Music]
and like how they're just very slowly
coming
down right where are the other spider
webs am I
[Music]
blind maybe I'm done already
no I don't see any other above
me oh that one
yeah okay that was just
two I don't like the creaky sounds in
[Music]
here need to call
a something that's not a
[Music]
carpenter cuz Carpenter would just fix
the rugs not the not the wood planks
right
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah that would make no
sense huh wait wait a
second I was wondering why they're
floating now if I get the furniture back
then they will have surely some
on
oh oh
no did I scare you my names sing it with
me now
booven oh you're so
funny OMG
wait did I do it right B
P don't cry I love you
P he so cute I did it I did
it you good
B
oh I need to help
him where did you
go bo bo it's all going to be
okay you can be the bouncy ball that I
will sit on from now on I hear it's um
good for your back to sit so to sit on
Bounty
balls in your
[Music]
office thanks for the
membership fantastic I'm glad you found
and captur that to again you mean booly
again they're very elusive only coming
out when their hiding spot has been
found they may all look the same but
each has its own personality trying to
Capt
all bul
again so spider webs oh nothing left
here but this
[Music]
thing CH what is it
back I guess it's back doesn't look like
it's much back
[Music]
It's Just Books many many
books is there point to getting
everything back for sure right I'm going
to get some extra bone
or some kind of
[Music]
gem something will come out of
this was that the last
no oh
[Music]
wait at the
globe
who was that the
last really oh more
[Music]
books that's a little bit excessive
don't you think more more no
where where wa where where where where
where I
maybe
[Music]
above try spinning the glow that's
it that's the fun part oh look at that
what I do with
that burn it all right I just went there
to see what
happens that was the
trick that's it right that's all I need
to do here what about the other spider
webs where are the other
ones where are the other ones now we can
go upstairs again and deal with the
other spider webs I
guess probably now we can burn it
somehow the the big ones
above now there is a way
h no go no
[Music]
no what is
this hello how much does this
stretch huh
what
ah
fire I only see
[Music]
um can I do this room first
oh this closes again doesn't it h but at
least it's on
fire no wait wait why is it so much
harder to pull
now wait I guess I will have to
do come on don't annoy me
now oh it's like attached to that fan
okay
[Music]
ooh turn or else okay I guess I cannot
turn you like that then I'll turn you
like
this yeah I
[Music]
figured no can finally
reach the
gemstone but there's still oh yeah just
here I do it I do it I do it I do it I
do
it okay what are we going to do about
outside
though I did not quite understand
this can I not get the other one up
there the
ball maybe we'll start with the small
ones
oh oh good to start with
[Music]
this get to the fire okay what the
uh W is it going to explode like
what and we dropped the ball
[Music]
interesting oopsie oh that was another
one I didn't even see it oh yeah
yippy that was only 20 out of 4
41 is there something missing here oh
[Music]
money I smell
money okay oh
oh I was about to
leave prematurely o o
[Music]
o
oh no
I was about to dodge but he's so slow
[Music]
I wait wrong
oh o speeda wants a piece of that
cake no no
no okay um We'll Walk This
Way oopsy
can I also fall down on
purpose yeah cuz I just want to go to
the level I think anyway
no also I don't remember getting rid of
that bro I don't remember getting rid of
that spider web that was originally down
there okay now I think I'm doing
it
oh oh is also like oh W she's doing it
[Music]
wa I'm impressed
wa okay so what
wait what wait
[Music]
what where the where where oh it's just
going to oh there's nothing for me to
suck up
[Music]
may I not pass through
here these what is this kind of giant
ass unsymmetric
bike looks
fun that's a that's this bike is
kind of like KY and
[Music]
puu wouldn't it remind you
to behind this we have fire I thought
[Music]
so nice fire swing oh we finished this
room look at
that that's an easily achievable one
oh thank you how how kind of
you who just so
[Music]
tiny he actually so
small
who bye-bye
[Music]
he's a short King but Mario is a shorter
King oh wait that's not the where the
door
is three more rooms oh my God this is
long they make you get your hopes up oh
wao wao cuz the other missions are short
oh if you charge it up all the way to
the
double bar then you can one hit kill
them yay they threw me a bone I wonder
is that pun on
purpose maybe not because the game is
made in
Japan and in Japan in Japanese language
ah that doesn't quite work that way
throwing a bone it's not the same pun
[Music]
should I go to this room
first yeah why
[Music]
not
momy ghost pop Love Bone yes ghost pop
that's why he's not with
me Ah that's what the grill is for uh
uh ghost pop is busy Reviving me or like
being on standby to revive me that's why
he's not in the
garden or maybe because it's raining
uh-oh maybe I should take
[Music]
distance or na a
ball
oh don't touch me don't touch me don't
touch me don't touch me now you can
touch me now you can touch me now you
can touch me try me
[Music]
ah they were waiting for me in my
weakest
moments I did not revoke the touching
perms
so my fault
oh gem or bone
or can't believe that even these balls
going to hurt
[Music]
you oh just money
okay think that's
finito the touch
PRS paty
perms patchy banana
[Music]
no go away no go
away no go
away these curtains are there on purpose
just for
this trigger
me
right I know how it is
[Music]
ceiling yes I do
it you got ah did they say it oh go it's
that
time yeah the ID stream um they just
announced
finally and next week on the weekend
is going to be uh ID Minecraft thingy
they already announced that that's
what's going to happen and if they've
been working on it for a while but they
didn't announce yet who the guests going
to be from the other branches I honestly
didn't think that they would invite me
again cuz I was part of it last
year but I'm very happy to be invited
did they also say uh who I'm in a team
with because even that is um funny yeah
P NY way I don't know if who put us
together but I'm with
[Applause]
waya I'd be happy with anybody but waya
is just uh you know too fitting isn't it
what a
coincidence yeah oh yes yeah yeah yeah
this was already in the plans for a
while I knew about this for a while so
next week on Saturday Sunday I'm going
to be playing Minecraft they have a
practice day uh on the eth but me and
way are busy on the eth so we're going
to do practice day on the
10th anybody but any no actually it
would have been so funny if they put me
with Anya and we would be forced to play
together in a team no missed the
opportunity who decided
this should have been with Anya but I'm
happy with waya too
Anya and Ena are team damn
it n it's okay if Ena would have been
with waya maybe I would have been a bit
jealous St thank you
a birds of a feather stick together it
is what it is they wanted to avoid the
drama of people hating each other yeah
yeah yeah understandable that's actually
very considerate of them they must have
played a lot of cookie y me in their
days in the
past
yay last year you did great in soccer
and Tennis oh we're calling it soccer
now
eh yeah yeah I wonder what they have in
store this
time why you you are cleaning out all
these webs I made an important Discovery
there's an incredibly strong paranormal
signal coming from the oh is there a
boss now is the next thinging of
[Music]
boss is that the uh is that the last
thing okay we got to do it we got to
finish it with a boss
oh have a terrible rep but I believe in
you Luigi once we find out who what is
behind this mess will put a stop to it I
will put a stop to it you
mean go the cell you'll need to take the
elevator oh yeah I saw that before
you'll Mark the cell I know where it is
I've been passing
[Music]
through yeah I really loved all the
games they had previously
H originally it was going to be this
weekend but they moved it because they
weren't done building it cuz they were
all really busy I'm surprised they're
building it
themselves like you can commission
people to do this kind of stuff and I
thought for something that's like this
ambitious I thought they would
commission someone to build
it but it seems like they're doing it
themselves yeah I've been seeing some of
the building process like little sneaky
tiny bits of
it now I will appreciate it even more
when I see it
properly
yeah Minecraft I'm Glad more Minecraft
stuff
so let's have fun with Minecraft next
week
[Music]
oh we're already
there oh we're going to get we're going
to be able to get right to
it I don't
know have to do all kinds of stupid
things before going
there elevator
music just twiddling is f oh uhoh
that was not as nice as it's as it
seemed at
first
uhoh oh we're going very deep
oh well that seemed like a fast track
pass to the Sellar because it was so
fast maybe this is a good thing
Luigi no more sucking of the spinal webs
necessary
right what the the
coin
bro no okay what the hell can I do it
from
here I think so
[Music]
it's
all it's all ending up in
wa's
purse hi Speeders you're going to hit me
aren't
you oh hey you almost hit the speeder
careful we don't want to hit the spider
do we wait so you have fire is
interesting wait wait when you go down
can I can I get
the can I not get it because like
there's like a little little
piece sticking out don't you see it
makes me think that they want me ah
whatever I'll just uh I'll take that
ball
probably and I'll bring it over to the
[Music]
soldier I guess this is the thing you do
in the middle of the battle
bringing the
ball
back uh hello scary can I have your what
is this your man bun the spider web man
bun
uh-oh okay ah oh my it's going back okay
well I how can you not take damage when
this takes so much time but okay woohoo
that was fast cuz I already knew what to
do yippee okay what now uh why is what
is
doing endless HP or what
suck same thing again
probably oh
no what the
[Music]
hell okay oh oh the path is longer now
is
it ah
I can't I can't pull it I can't pull
it
what
what ah wait it's a it's a
[Music]
f what the was that
shadow uh wait so wait what what I'm
turning I'm turning turning I'm turning
it I'm turning it
ah wait wait wait wait wait multitasking
Dodge and hit
it what I don't understand wait I guess
no wait never mind sorry ah I get it I
get it I get it now I bring it is it is
this close to enough
to
uh at least the spider's going to
waiting for me okay uh that's close
enough that's close enough that's that's
close enough you went too far probably
did you did you go too
far uh yeah I
think I got to get it really close
right but that's
so why is it got to be so
perfect no I'm just trying to suck
it what I don't understand
[Music]
I'm doing it f wrong
probably I'm I've been trying to trigger
it while it's spinning but it seems very
far away so I'm trying to get it into
this position that's
close and stop it and then suck it but
then the other time it like turned away
again cuz my aim was too high I guess
wait I'll try it
again stop Maybe
don't hurt
me see it barely I'm I'm as close as I
can get I think so this must be
wrong I don't know there's no other fire
Source just spein all the oh
[Music]
okay but and then what oh oh it reaches
it gets the height that it can touch it
even okay wait what now wait wait wait
wait wait wait so some ah ah now he's do
we do the same thing again and get the
thing stuck on his spare while it's
burning could that be
it uh no
[Music]
no the ball under the
spider
what yeah I see the ball there but it
looks like too
far also the the fire goes out so
fast
H if I spin
this it doesn't like stay firey forever
ah but ah do I make this thing stick to
his
spare may I please have this no no
they're going to kill me what are you
what are you thinking a health to where
can I get
[Music]
health there must be a way to get health
oh flash yeah yeah can I get help too
here
he looks
good oh look at that is that a bone over
there in that chest throw me a
bone no that's not what I
need okay I'm Healed a little
bit what was that
[Music]
X okay
nothing ah
[Music]
[Applause]
don't follow
me okay hit it hit it
bro
[Music]
okay okay so it was when I was thinking
of like going from one to the next but
he first needed
this ball
[Applause]
okay big brain boss
fight o thanks for the heal how are you
going to how you going to extend this
now
buddy
wait I should have hidden like here on
the side probably like here but I I was
too slow
oh oh oh what are you
doing all we going to do this now do you
still want me to get the fire from all
the way over
here no
right but I think there's there's a
detached egg there
though oh come on
[Music]
that's a detached
egg can I run while holding this no not
really they're going they're not even
going towards me they're just going
towards the end of the
hall do I really
got okay okay what why not
burning okay now burning
[Music]
I said Fire
Fire to the
Rain yeah B this is chaotic
now oh that's like a in case I lose my
fire I could fall there now woohoo and
recharge the fire if I wanted to okay
okay ghost time it's not over yet wait
no
no no come back what you can't do this
come back get out of
there wait wait wait you're so
[Music]
far I hate you he's going to go there
again let's go there ahead of
time okay oh oh I got him Luigi why
don't you run
F
really those long legs are not doing you
any favors I know you can use those legs
better though if you only try it
harder this is why you don't get any
platforming games you got those long
legs but for what you're not using
them running like a
slug
yippe thank you
thank
you thank you chat that was difficult
when I when you don't know how to do
[Music]
it small spider now eh oh you're just
normal now you're just mommy spider and
you're acting
sweet and like Mommy sorry
Mommy
okay H hm
seems like there is peace
now with the speeda
spa yellow
spaghetti remarkable a GH thing that can
possess other beans oh I think that's a
thing that they do quite often unless my
eyes are going dark going the processor
had a piece of the Dark Moon inside
himself oh by the way are you okay that
was a pretty intense
scuffle oh what you want poter ghost 5 I
was really show that boss ghost who's
boss I'm sure you're tired after that
fight I'll bring you back now
CH oh yeah wa did we get the piece of
moon oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh
yeah he'll dance with us don't worry I'm
sure he's in the mood for dancing now
that his mommy is back to
normal oh under 10 minutes oh but I lost
so much
[Music]
health and
what
bro whatever I don't care about those
medals I don't care about you stupid
medals just because Olympics are making
me hungry for medals no not at all yeah
I mean bronze for Austria is better than
no bronze or no medal at all H true
Luigi my boy what a
fight you really use your Noggin to
teach that GH
lesson let's take a look at the body
stal
[Music]
ghost what his eyes look like like upper
teeth H it's like one of those things
where you can see it in different ways
depending on what you focus your eyes
on
wow I think it's
both I think it's supposed to look like
teeth but it's
eyes
funny now that we've recovered another
dark moon piece we just need to find the
rest of them huh oh who the f wow that's
a solution yeah that's that's a
conclusion was that you thought we were
done no oh you didn't think the ghost
would keep all the pieces in the same
place did you no those ghosts are far
too crafty for that they've likely
spread the pieces across the entire
Valley anyhoo I suspect a piece of Dark
Moon so I got the tip of the
[Music]
bottom oh just like the other one this
is covered with the same corrupting
energy but it's nothing a good scrubbing
can
fix yes scrub it
down
yeah
put tell me your
[Music]
favorite
oh wow this one looks
nicer are they just going to get more
and more expensive looking now if my
suspicions are correct yes more of that
creepy fog has lied maybe the Periscope
will be able to locate more Dark Moon
pieces now let's take a gander at the
map and see what shakes
loose new mansion
unlocked Ah that's what all those empty
Hills are for 1 2 3 4 5
there's like
a th one and I wonder if nothing's going
to be placed
there new mans
hoodies that's it that's where we've got
to go
next are we going to get there you ask
well IED my Thum to this so I made a
couple of tweaks for the
pixelator should now be able to move you
to the next location check it out in the
monitor
t yipp
we did the first manner we could have
done it in way last time
but it is what it is they say not going
to do this now but good to know we're
set to go for the next
stream this is saved
right I would fix
so right
is my new Japanese
[Music]
account is this 3 minutes and or 3 hours
and
59 probably wait it says two yeah yeah
it's fine fine fine fine okay okay
[Music]
okay Big Stretch
wow Big
Stretch good Big Stretch Big Stretch oh
all the dog owners in the chat hear me
stretching like that they're probably
automatically like good
stretch good stretch
oh good stretch good
boy who's a good boy oh who's a good
boy
me okay guys I'm not going to read super
chat some TI um and it's late um uh
sorry but I don't know if I'm even going
to eat proper dinner I feel like I'm not
full at all from this one tiny hot dog
but it's already late and I'm not
exactly hungry like like deadly hungry
but I might be
fine but I do want to show you the merch
like one piece of merch
um where was it again uh
here previews of merchandise
[Music]
which one would you like to see
the uh the Water
chicken or the
happy or the card colder
thing the
doy the dock
oh yeah okay okay I have several
pictures of the
duck and then I will proceed to post it
on Twitter tomorrow when I wake up uh
you know this is actually smart
separating them I
figured I figured that out when I only
post one item at a time and the next day
the other item or
so then there's several tweets promoting
my
merchandise on different days with
different pictures I think that's more
eye
catching more occasions to catch
people's eyes yeah
smart okay so here
comes Tak kfp wubble
doy water chicken for your
bathtub she chicken she chicken chicken
she
chicken which picture
maybe look at this good boy
wow he's so cute he's so cute he looks
perfect now here is see in
water yes
waterproof of course he's a water
chicken he's swimming he's doing a
swim he's doing a swim in the in the
wobbly Waters don't put them into two
wobbly water I can't take two wobbling
Waters wow look at him go look at him go
swim swim swim swim that's
you he's just floating there menacing no
a
menacing I just bought this as a squeeze
toy or do you have a dog or if this is
going to be chewed up by your guys' dogs
I'm going to be so mad you got to buy
several then to make up when if one dies
if this becomes your dogs chew toys
man I can imagine it would be so be
careful of your dogs keep this stuck
away from them a
chicken and then I have one more
picture that's a little preview I guess
for the happy as
well when here is it being held
lovingly
cherishing gently hold gently hold holds
gently do and I keep on saying do
[Music]
chicken junky big boy he looks pretty
big in this H Photo doesn't
he that's is that standard bath top duck
size
[Music]
hm but I like it he's so round he's got
a hat he's got everything I want to see
his hole I
requested a video cuz they there there
there's still one item um the fan that
they don't have a picture of yet because
it's still like in production the
samples are still in production
uh and um what was I going to
say ah so I asked next time when you
guys are like you know doing these merch
pictures when you set it up for Merch
pictures can you like take the chicken
again and make a
video of you guys squeezing it for me
and for the fans so I can you know prove
that it has a hole and that it makes a
sound uh we need video
proof so hopefully they'll make the
video when they get to the
fan I don't even have a bathtub that's
okay you don't need the bathtub to enjoy
this you can take it to the local uh
lake or
Pond let it swim there or make a puddle
Out of Rain or just use a bowl or get it
like one of those small decorational
water fountains for your living room and
yeah let it swim in its own little
Lake I'm just putting him in a bowl
that's fine but honestly you could get
one of these like decorational drinking
FS not not one to drink out of for like
cats like I think there's probably more
like decorational
ones yeah put it to the sink or I don't
know put it put it anywhere just it's a
cute decoration it's basically like a
like a figurine of a chicken it's made
out of plastic but I mean figurines are
all out of plastic so same thing
actually it's better than a figurine
because this one makes
sounds you can fill it with water maybe
through the whole
make it heavier than throw it at
evil Intruders it will be a deadly
[Music]
weapon yeah it looks like good
quality no don't let you dog chew it no
no no I said no
[Music]
I'm happy with this this is
definitely a really good merch
item ah so cute I'm so glad I thought of
this I thought I really thought though
that and I mean when I thought about it
there was no other example of
merchandise rubber duckies but uh when I
released it and I I looked through um
the whole life merch
website uh to think of to see if I can
get any other ideas for uh future merch
anything I haven't done before and
then uh I see that very
recently there has been another Roba
ducky release in birthday merch I think
uh on the H of stars side I'm
like but this was before I set my uh you
know my Raba ducky plans in uh no not no
after I said it in motion is what I'm
trying to say
yeah how how are you
how how are there suddenly two rabad
duckies so close to each other in
timing bro I thought I was so genius for
thinking of
this but like you know we planned this
kind of stuff like five five six months
ahead of time and I don't know what the
others are creating so I really thought
I was going to be the first with a
rubber ducky and then I then I wasn't
the first of a rubber
ducky well I'm the first with a rubber
chicken oh no I I hope that hotori will
eventually get rot DUIs I
have suest justed the
idea
and it was well received so we'll see
we'll see just have to think of a
different outfit for mine if I get
another one
then I don't know what I would dress
another
kfb rubber duck in or we could make a CI
version but I'm really not that
connected to kri I don't use Ki much M
so I don't know different kind of what
other cloves do we see the kfp chicken
in I don't
know it's like pretty much always this
uniform armor that would be I think that
would stand out
weirdly to the others
but yeah I
[Music]
know out
bodyguard but we've never had the
chicken in that before fite head robbing
something
ah M just a hat with no
clothes
yeah but like too similar
I'll think of something when the time
comes but uh yeah putting it in a fre
night
outfit could
work maybe I'll ask uh I'll ask Duma for
some ideas
[Music]
to we've had you guys in a lot of
different outfits for the polar WS which
by the way I'm very aware that there's
still some missing I realized after I
arrived in Japan um that I forgot to
finish them I didn't really have time
but I forgot to finish them I wanted to
finish them in the week before I left
and then I ran out of time and then in
Japan I realized oh how am I going
to sign him now cuz I didn't bring a
drawing
[Music]
tablet so I was thinking maybe one of
those
days uh I could visit Ra's place and use
her t for several hours actually
shouldn't take that much longer when I'm
like in in when I do it in one go and
I'm fast I can do it probably in 1 hour
or
two 1 and 1 half hours
maybe that's what I was thinking but I
don't
know I think I did put the PSD file on
my drive at least in preparation
so or did I I think I did
[Music]
yeah off collab that no I need to like
focus on it but then I would combine it
with a collab either
[Music]
way yeah en know Ena is a possibility
too cuz she always brings something
probably just her probably just her iPad
though I have an iPad
too but I didn't bring the pen maybe I
could just borrow her pen for a day or
so or half a day
M I don't know either Ina or actually
yeah either way I'll try to finish it
while I'm in Japan by using one of these
options
[Music]
yeah I don't even know where my pen is I
do actually have an iPad pen turns out
but I don't know where I put it again
[Music]
okay so there you go he I'll upload this
probably tomorrow on Twitter and
tomorrow I will also upload the schedule
there'll also be a
stream um but I would say in the late
evening like 2 hours before
now or 3 hours before now 9 9 p.m. jst
or so I want to play the the 3D s whole
life
game the new one the treasure one with
Min Senpai in
it that's what I'm thinking short game
so late in the evening should be okay
and before that I can like make the
schedule and
everything sounds good sounds
good yeah it looks fun looks like a
little good oneoff game and it just
released so I think it's uh good to play
it now when it's still fresh out of the
oven
[Music]
Kyla Kyla reaching the high score
doesn't surprise me she's also one of
the first people to play it I think at
least in whole
life and she's uh she's grinding as
always
yeah might just stop to say hi and then
watch V okay thank you sorry that the
times are bad but I am um
planning uh there are like
some
streams uh let me see like this this
coming week
[Music]
um wa it's already already M okay
so m
the ID Minecraft stuff will
be partially
shitty no the the thing is it's the real
deal starts at 2:30 p.m. jst on Sunday
so that's probably shitty time like
really weirdly late but not too late for
Na and then early early early in the
morning for Europe kind of a weird time
um the day before that me and
waya are going to
practice uh also during the day but a
little bit earlier than the
real
happening yeah Friday I'm going to do a
longer stream but around the same time
as Luigi I
think Thursday
[Music]
probably gonna take the day off uh Cu uh
both on Wednesday and Thursday I have
like dance lessons and uh
recordings I would be free in the
evening but I am streaming on all the
other days so I figured I might just
take it
off the day I
mean yeah I'm going kind of backwards
here uh Tuesday I'm thinking which
spring r or Luigi so Friday will also be
either which spring r or Luigi or
Olympics
yeah yeah so probably Wednesday Thursday
off and the other day is stream stream
stream stream and
then the week after oh it's not New York
yet the week after that uh but the week
after that I'm going to be
honest uh might actually be for the
first time since I'm in uh since I came
to Japan it might be more on the busy
side with more days off
because
um we are going to have some I'm going
to have some
beak recordings long uh long day
recordings and dance
[Music]
lessons that week is pretty
busy pretty
beasy so going to stream at least three
or four times
[Music]
though and then the week after that is
the New York week
so that week is also a little
bit um scar sparse scars sparse scar
scars
Sparks
because well obviously New
York concert I have threee concerts that
weekend
free fight us at the Sunday one per day
bro bruh and then rehearsal and and
oh my God it's going to take full full
days many
[Music]
days y that week is very busy and after
that should
be the week after that should be pretty
normal again
and and with normal streaming times uh
like normal as in normal amount of
[Music]
streams but I'm H still I'm going to be
doing dance lessons in that week because
let me just tell you that is the week
the last week before my own birthday
live
recording so uh last couple of dance
lessons to squeeze in there between
streams
cuz I'm I have my motion capture
recording in the first September
week
yeah first September
week just so you know what I'm working
towards HH I've been raided by waa
thank you I'm about to end though look
at my merch look at this guys you can
still buy it Link in the description you
can get a a kfp rubber ducky don't you
want one you can swim it can
squeak it could be your dog's shoe toy
but I would ask you not
to he's a round boy hey did I really get
raided I only see members in the chat
HH are the chais all all members or
what I almost only see
[Music]
members that was a r
really there now I see it were you guys
prematurely telling me that there's
going to be a
raid oh oh ch
ch B with
[Music]
hello hello now they're here that was
premature I've been warned about your
arrival I knew about your arrival way
before you knew of
it I was actually just discussing my
schedule and about to end
myself wait that was weird phrasing
about to end my stream me
[Laughter]
too uh but uh here uh just while you're
here do you need a rubber ducky guys
Link in the description kfp rubber ducky
super cute super chunky nice quality can
squeak can be thrown can be drowned will
come back up to get air don't worry will
not die can be used as decoration very
cute
cute little chunky boy isn't he he's a
chunky boy RA are you
listening are you doing well man I I saw
her in the studio the other day but and
and I was like in a moment where I
wasn't feeling so well um I don't know
if she know this I think she lowkey
noticed but I said I'm okay okay but I
gave her a hug and
h i rested my head on her on
her
nice bonad donks and it was so soothing
and healing let me tell
you seeing
NAA really teared me up in that moment
you don't even know Thea I was really
not feeling well I didn't want to tell
you in that moment but I really wanted
to cry and then I saw you and it really
made me happy and then you gave me a hug
and your hugs are really nice and I'm I
was leaning my head on your chest and I
felt like really I was being like
nurtured by
mother you're really you're really doing
a good job as
Mama you're really like living up to
that
name I love you
H I don't
know you're you're my coai by free
generations and
yet you're giving me mommy Vibes and
[Music]
I'm I'm I'm feeling like a bobble when I
hug
L could fall asleep on that
chest thank you L she's got that or
that's soothing gentle Aura really it's
like the best person to hug when you
want to
cry yes I'll put on
pacifier Rich Mommy I
[Music]
guess yeah yeah so with that being said
thank you for the raid I'm actually
ending too but at least I could
advertise my my chicken here a little
bit to the
chais yeah she smells
[Music]
nice B byy the chicken by the chicken is
so
cute
yeah you look you can hold it
gently or you can squeeze it with all
you've got all your powers squeeze it
make it make it make sounds make it
squeak it will
squeak yeah you can eat it but I said
because it has a hole at the bottom you
should fill it with water and then if
you have an intruder in your home you
Chuck it at them throw it at them it
might become a deadly
weapon very very versatile rubber
chicken for your bathtub or your local
lake or your local pond or your sink or
just doesn't even have to be on a body
of
water no no the squeaking voice um
happens naturally because this thing is
filled with air think of normal rubber
duckies that they have they're out of
plastic they're filled with air they
have a hole on on their
bottoms so it makes a natural squeaky
sound
M actually I think they sent me a video
before of like a normal rubber ducky cuz
I asked okay if you're making this is it
going to have the natural um rubber
ducky squeaky sound and they were like
yeah like this you mean right and I'm
like yeah exactly
[Music]
okay so it's going to make the typical
squeaky sound yes proper proper squeak
[Music]
as it should so this will be uploaded
tomorrow with the schedule and then one
by one in the following days I'll show
you the rest of the and
merchandise pictures as they come in I
mean the ones I already have I'll upload
and then we'll wait for the fan yay okay
thank you for watching in German v z
good
night good night night why are you gay
why are you
gay who is
[Music]
gay please please watch the 1 hour
version of that interview please do it
if you haven't
yet I'll
[Music]
in bye-bye
H thanks for watching even if it was
just for the past 5 minutes and thanks
for watching for the past 5 hours as
well I'm going to go now and dream of
Waba DUIs
[Music]
who is
streaming oh no one is streaming no one
is
streaming no wait no there are people
streaming at this
time Sora Senpai you should be asleep
shouldn't you
[Music]
okay Target acquired I don't know if I
can uh rate her though let's
[Music]
see no I
can't no perms
no auki perms
[Music]
either I have mikoi
perms the migi
perms that hair is so cute okay bye