[music]
It's Yoridayosei's Kakoyoshi, Yes hash
The girl who was experimenting with tag Koyo is Zubo.
Is it okay or is it sketchy?
Yes, yes, yes, yes, it seems like a researcher.
Test feeling yes yes yes yes green test tube yes
Yes yes yes Oyori's female inn one name yes
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, I can see it.
Yes, yes, that's fine.
Okay
It's just the mayonnaise that I made in time for the drink.
By the way, I'm just a face. Yes, big brother.
Do you have frozen udon noodles available?
Lighting complete key Yes Yes Yes Yes Cook.
The cook was so nice. Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Only the chisels can make cobies, yes, yes, yes.
Are you okay? Hehe, yes, yes, yes, please.
Hmm, yes, yes, yes, I have it.
I'm going to give you a program to help you get better.
Yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes to
Yes
Yasshi Maata mayonnaise is a drink
By the way, the child is air, yes, meat replacement frozen udon
Is that what the reserve point is?
It's here, it's here, it's here, it's here.
Okoyoha during the hashtag Koyori experiment
Is this a sketchbook?
Yes, this is what it is, yes, yes, this is research.
Tiki tube yes yes yes yes tiki ka yes
Yes yes yes yes no inn one name yes yes
Yes, yes, help, yes, yes, yes, help.
Yes, yes, yes, it's not okay.
yes
Game
Yes okay
[music]
Wow
T
[music]
Here 24 starts
in
Haha, everyone has been waiting for a long time, New Year.
Thank you for waiting 424 times.
Thank you
From January 2nd to 3rd
Everyone is busiest during the year-end and New Year holidays.
But for everyone watching, it's the best
I guess it's time to take it easy.
It's already the year-end and New Year holidays for Hololive members.
I'll do my best, I say this during busy times.
I'm really glad we were able to hold the event.
Everyone who supports us and all our guests
Thanks to you and together
Mane-chan and Mr.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Thank you very much for your support.
I did it
So this is the New Year here 24
I was a bit worried.
However, the event was held successfully.
Maybe something will happen along the way.
I think there is a thing, so
To interrupt when something happens
Regarding the judgment, let me write it in the summary column as well.
It's all managed by Moe.
I'll leave it to you to decide what that is.
This is how it is written.
Yes, I wonder what it is about that.
The decision is up to the management, everyone.
Thank you for your understanding.
So I'll be there from 7:30pm.
The corner is about to start, so keep going!
Con24 I'll let you know first.
Sometimes that happens, actually.
I would like to give you some news.
So first of all, check the schedule.
Let's move on, it's like this Dededon
Yes, the first half was like this.
Everyone's waiting time is a bit long.
I hope that the guest will have as much fun as possible.
Toneguest is the corner where guests are
It would be great if the corners where guests are located are connected.
Everyone was waiting for about 30 minutes.
That's what I learned from last time's Concoyo 24.
So, in the meantime,
I thought I'd show you what I did.
It's a pretty tight schedule.
There's something like a gorilla werewolf here.
And the gorilla werewolf, and it's my first location shoot.
I went there in about October.
But inside Kagae and here,
This is the recorded version. Now for the second half.
Let's watch the battle here.
Well, the one that's being recorded is memorizing the dance.
Kaego says it's something that's done in 3D.
Thank you for the meal. This is quite a dish from that store.
It would be difficult without that kind of cooperation.
So I can't do it without that recording.
This is the delicacy I was expecting.
That kind of price guessing type, right?
There was also a corner where you could guess the prices of shops.
This is being recorded and
Home rating survey last 24 hours
The first thing I did was ask someone to come to my house.
Taraja, I'll do my best for the next 24 hours.
It's like, I'm asking you to go home.
It was something like that, but
It was, but that's not much.
It was too hard for me, so let's eat that meal.
It can only be done in that offline mode because there are things like
Since there is no such thing, I have recorded this one.
Also, the gorilla werewolf is all 3D, so I recorded it.
I will deliver it as if it were
Makonne's schedule is posted on x
Please check that as well.
Please, and this time it's 24 for here.
Koyorino's favorite topic is often talked about.
Kuru that otaku female manager is from a cat
It's that main manager, but...
I really want to go with that 24 from last time.
This is a mane-chan made by two people and three legs.
But, this is the second time we met.
Emane when we were talking about Masukane.
I want to do what you suggested.
I think this is it. Yes, it's Biko.
So this is that Bingo
That's right, there's a girl named Pointing-kun.
Let me use the one you made before.
I received it, but this time it's the bingo corner.
Yes, we have decided to set up a
This is it. If you achieve this, you get 1 rai.
If you complete the bingo game, you will receive that reward.
Produced by Mamane-chan that you can get
That's why it's Bigot.
I want to achieve this one thing at a time.
I think so, but that post is in the middle of nowhere.
1000rp and post 2000rp
I think there are some, but those apply.
I'll start posting now, but it's been 24 hours since last week.
Please post now that 24 is being streamed here.
I'll do it now
3219 I just said yes.
This post corresponds to this post
There are 1000 corresponding posts.
If you go to RP2000RP, you can fill it up.
I can check this Migo because I can.
Occasional break time
There is something like that, but that
Is it time to change the frame? Yes, 5 o'clock or 10 o'clock.
Check it at the timing of buying the quota from time to time.
If you achieve the goal, you will receive it on the spot.
So I'm thinking of doing it.
Yes, that's what happened while I was doing another corner.
I don't do bingo filling, so please understand that.
I would appreciate 1000RP
Isn't it too early to say that we've already surpassed that?
Thank you very much, seriously
Thank you, just a moment now
I wasn't quite ready so I'll come back later.
Please let me fill it up slowly.
It's finished thank you very much
So, this is mochi.
It seems like everyone is interested in the revolution.
However, the revolution eats that rice cake.
There is a corner where we will have a battle to decide who is the strongest.
I'm going to do something like that, but it's true.
That's what you all do, everyone.
I'm making ends meet with the recipes I got from
Well, this is all in the hands of that self-restraint.
Even if you say you're there, it's a revolution.
If you say so, it will be filled.
Yes, I think so, just over 2000
Wait, I should have made more of this.
That white coat from the cat that made me feel a little warmer
Hiyori is the one who decided on this item.
Thank you for reaching 2000.
There are 2 seats filled.
That's why I did it.The rest is X-wise.
Hashtag Konkoyo 24 is trending #1
There are also things like that, so that's good.
If you could give me a little more
I'm happy. Thank you. 10,000 yen.
I got yelled at and said I should have turned it into a crab.
It's almost daylight now, I guess it's the new year.
So here we are, just Nema Bingo.
But there's one more announcement.
Yes, that's why I'm here.
I would like to inform you that over 3000
Thank you very much.
Please aim for 54,000 yen.
Why is this happening?
Aiming for 540,000, even the gold melted by Koyori
That's what I'm aiming for.
This is the next announcement.
Anyway, it's E9.
Concoyo 24 Noe goods will be available!
Or rather, from 7:30 pm after this.
It will be released
Okay, so here it is, why?
If I were to release one, it would be the assistant doll.
But it appeared in the first year.
I want that girl-kun stuffed toy to be resold.
Even if there are so many voices to say, I'll say it already
If you don't have the time, just look at the stuffed animal.
Hey, I'm getting expensive, so why not do something else?
If you combine it with the one, it will be quite expensive.
I thought about it a lot and decided to release it.
I've missed it quite a bit.
I decided to release it here.
But it was a bit difficult to resell.
New girls' stuffed toys to cuddle
I decided to release it after changing the version.
That's why the elementary school dressed the girls in that new costume.
He says he is now able to hold him.
Yes, there are some places.
Back then, you didn't know Koyori, girl.
I wanted a stuffed animal but I couldn't buy it.
By all means, please take this opportunity to
You can even become intimate with your mistress.Removable fishing catch
This is a stuffed toy that can be used as a heart.
I hope you will buy it.
Well, it would be lonely to have only one.
As a result, 24 T-shirts will also be released in the future.
Yes, it's a mess, isn't it?
This is a convenient T-shirt.
This one is the best because it's black and sweat doesn't show up.
It is a free size and is quite large.
And the girl was cut like that dress
I think most boys will fit in.
It's about the right size, so don't worry about it.
See you again, Coco. When 24 comes, wear this.
I don't know if there's anything you'd like me to take a look at.
It's not like that, but I got it.
I would be happy if you could
Full set: 2 pieces and a voice.
However, if you purchase the full set
This comes with 24 stickers.
It's also super cute as a sticker.
It was designed by Mr. Asagiri in Canada.
It's a sticker that I received.
Click here too, please paste it on your computer.
Please, thank you very much. Yes, like this.
The voice that comes with the set is
Matched with that huggable stuffed animal
The voice of that girl holding you in her arms
It's a pretty interesting voice.
If you'd like, you can get the full set.
I would be happy if you could buy it. Thank you.
As a request, we also have some goodies.
It's now on sale. Thank you.
wish
That's how I'm going to spend New Year 20.
I'd like to, please come out here.
I think I'll leave it there.Yes, that's all.
I absolutely had to say it.
I did it in a hurry, but it took about 18 minutes.
I can talk to you about the link now.
I have added this to the column.
It's after 7:30pm so I can't buy it yet.
Yes, but there is no such thing as a limited number.
So when I want something like that slowly
buy it for
Please buy it Oh, that's nice
It feels so good, that tension is rising
Are you all looking forward to this?
Which corner are you looking forward to, especially Masaki?
Well, I'm looking forward to watching Holo's Uga right away.
I'm so happy to hear your voice, what's next?
Holo's sea turtle corner is actually for this time.
Thank you for creating the original problem.
So the rest is that original Uga Sue.
Do you want to change your name without permission?
I can't, but that's what I expected.
This is because there is a right to the problem, but this time
Hey, I got your permission. What's that guy?
It's like when you did something like that.
Let me change the name to that Holomen.
There may be some, so please look forward to it.
Please give me an academic ability test Phlox Gorilla Mind
Naruaa location rating is so good
I'm so happy. Almost everyone plays mahjong cooking.
I'm looking forward to seeing the horned ones too.
I'm happy to receive it. It's definitely smaller than this.
It's like a hobby corner, something typical of New Year's.
Is there anything I can do alone than Eco?
I feel like Amahjong is good.
Well, I really want to start the new year with something.
I guess it's going to happen, so let's try our luck this year.
That MJ makes me feel like I'm trying it out.
I'll do it with you, so I'll talk to you about it.
If you would like to play together, please contact MJ.
I hope you can prepare for
If I don't get first place in mahjong, I'll be the most worried.
Nanoko's Mahjong is number one, so it's Bingo.
What is this? I'm really worried. Wait a moment.
I just want to win a little bit.
I was a little panicked, but it looks like I can do it.
Do you want to fill in the bingo? There are so many of you.
Thank you for the RP, but here it is.
24Thank you to so many people for their cooperation.
Therefore, that is how it is.
I would be happy if a lot of people could see it.
That's what I think, so please spread the word and
I'm tweeting a lot so that it can reach a lot of people.
I would be happy if you could give it to me, thank you very much
That means
Good job
I got it okay
Nice nice, so let's move on to the next one.
I would like to go to prepare the corner Continued
Ehoro no Umi starts at 7:30pm.
So everyone please wait
Please wait a moment.
please
It's a face, but it's a hashtag practice.
How about a meal in the middle?
Yes, it's a sketch.
Yes, yes, yes, the experience of being a researcher, yes.
Yes, yes ...
Yes, the name of the inn is yes, yes.
Yes, tell me, yes, yes, yes, yes, pi, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, that's a lie.It looks like yes, yes, yes.
Yes, it's good, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Okay
Maria, mayonnaise is a drink
By the way, Nifu is air.
I hear you always have frozen udon noodles on hand?
Yes, the lighting is complete QED Yes, yes, yes
It's a cook. It was a cook. Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, only Haito can create conflicts. Yes, yes.
Yes, are you okay? No way, no way, no way, no way, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, I'm not going. Yes, yes, yes, yes.
It looks like it's going to last a long time
Yes, yes, yes, yes
Yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes to
Yay Maria, mayonnaise is a drink
By the way, the handle is air, so it can be converted to frozen.
I heard you always have udon on hand.
Yes, it's Seinokoyohari, Yorenokoyo
I'm experimenting with the tag.
Where is Desu Guno? Sketch
Researcher
It feels like a green exam.
Feeling good, yes, yes, I'm a fan of Oyori no Yado
Name yes yes yes yes help yes yes
Yes, yes, yes, please.
Why does it look so cute?
Yes okay
Hello Maria, mayonnaise is a drink.
By the way, the air is refrigerated at the entrance.
Is Udo prepared?
Lighting complete 9 Easy cook Cook
Yes, only good people can make a coby.
Yes, yes, are you okay? It's impossible, it's impossible, it's impossible
Yes, yes, yes, no, I'm not coming, yes, yes.
Yes, I have
Mashaifuhai fluffy program hare
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
The mayonnaise is a must see.
By the way, it's air, so it's frozen at the entrance.
I'm preparing the burdock. Is that so?
It's Se-no-koyo. It's Se-no-ko. Yes.
Okekoyo was experimenting with hashtag Koyori.
Is it crawling or is it crawling?
Sketchle Haikose's Haihai Research
The experience of being a real person.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, girls' inn fan name
Yes yes yes yes help yes yes yes
Yes, Tenney, yes, yes, yes, it's Pa
I can't see it, I can't see it, I can't see it.
Yes yes yes okay
Yes, Maria-san, mayonnaise is a drink.
By the way, I'm using air and freezing it.
I hear you always have udon on hand?
Lighting done 9 Iji yes yes yes yes [ __ ]
Yes, yes, yes, yes, it was a [ __ ].
Yes, yes, yes, I can make friends with you.
Are you okay? No, no, yes, yes, yes, no
Hmmm yes yes yes yes
Yes, yes, yes, from the pool, yes, yes.
Yes yes yes
It was
Mayonnaise is a drink, by the way, Fushiha
It's air, so the frozen udon at the entrance is advanced.
Is that right? It's from here in Yatase.
Yosei's here is a hug
That's okay. What about the clouds? Yes.
Yatari Sketch Len Yes Yes Yes No Yes
Yes, yes, the experience of being a researcher, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, the green experience, yes, yes, the color of the cage.
one name
Yes, yes, yes, yes, let's go, yes, yes, let's go.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, okay
Maria had mayonnaise in the drink
By the way, Nifu is air. Hi Oni-chan.
I hear you always have convertible frozen udon on hand?
Okay, lighting completed 9 days
Yes, it's a [ __ ]. I don't want a [ __ ]. Yes.
Yes, yes, I can make a coby.
Yes, is it okay? No, no, no, no, yes, yes
Yes, yes, I'm not going. Yes, yes, yes.
have
Yes yes yes yes fluffy
The program seems to be bald.
Yes yes yes
The mayonnaise I made just in time is a drink
By the way, Nifu is air.
Uwasu
Is that so? It's here in Yatase.
This is Seno Koyo, and I'm experimenting with Hattag Koyo.
How is it?
Yattari Sketchin is okay
Yes yes, the experience of being a researcher yes yes yes
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, a woman.
Name yes yes yes yes Iwa bu yes yes yes
Yes, let's try saying yes, yes, yes, it's the law.
Look, it's okay.
Yes, yes, yes, okay.
Mayonnaise is a drink.
By the way, the frozen udon that has been converted into rice is Fuha.
I see that you always have the lighting on hand.
Done 9 Ideas yes yes yes yes [ __ ].
The cook was hot, yes, yes, even in the sea.
I can make a habi yes yes yes yes is it okay?
Nothing, nothing, yes, yes, yes, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes yes yes yes
Yes, yes, yes, Khufu's blog
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Ugh
Hey Maria, mayonnaise is a thing.
By the way, it's air, so it's frozen at the entrance.
I hear you always have udon on hand?
It's Tasei no Koyo. It's Sei no Koyo. Yes.
Hashtag koyori experiment chi desu koyo
Sketch
Ren is a researcher
A green experience, yes, yes, yes, a green experience.
Yes yes yes yes yes no inn Wanemu yes yes
Yes, yes, tell me, yes, yes, yes.
Conte: Yes, yes, yes, that's right, so look
Yes yes yes yes
Geyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy okay
Maria-san, mayonnaise is a drink.
By the way, I'm an air converter to cold.
I heard that the udon is cooked well?
Lighting complete Heide, yes, yes, yes, it's the cook.
The [ __ ] was hot.
Yes, yes, yes, it's okay.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, no, I'm not bored, yes.
Yes, I have it
Yes, yes, yes, let Khufu's heart change, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
[music]
Alright, the mayonnaise that arrived just in time is a drink.
By the way, it's air, big brother.
Do you have convertible frozen udon on hand?
Yat Senoko
Yo, I'm Koyori, I'm Sei's Kuyo.
Hashtag Koyori Practical Chile
The sea of Ro is Hololive
Please wait a moment
Wait a minute, something's stuck in there.
Eo-san Yago-Ake-O-Ake-do-mo-san
Hello Ako-san Akoyori-san Hello Akeo
Congratulations!
I'm going to cosplay my body today.
It looks like you are doing a lot of work.
It's amazing how long I'll be cosplaying today.
It really suits you so much
I like that it looks good on you
Thank you very much.
Chan
Dabuki-chan, go away, go away.
That's good, I made a mistake. I called you by mistake.
I thought that was it. I'm obsessed now.
The way you say it sounds like a terrible curse
It's a bit like the mask of the boss
It was cursed, wasn't it? The mask of Yago. The mask of Yago.
hey
I'm glad it was scary.
I think it will continue like this.
I hope you're safe. Come to the three people I invited as guests.
Well, that's okay.
Mel-chan, please introduce yourself.
Now it's time for the Demon Genius Ban Hololive match, it's Mel.
I have made Gano soup once with Koyo-chan.
So this is the second time.Yes, yes, this time.
Please show me your genius.
Please, please, please, last time.
Seriously, you're so genius, it's a bit scary.
It felt like I was going to hit it.
Please be gentle with your hands. Thank you very much.
Habuki-senpai, everyone, it's Kimekitsune Shiro today.
I wonder if Mel-chan did that pon.
I thought about it, but I never expected it to be the strongest.
I think I'll leave it to you, thank you
I hope you leave it to me. You're a genius.
By the way, the sea god soup is
Do you have any experience with sea god soup?
I think I can give you a good answer even if it's somewhere else.
As expected, it's a little bit like that.
I don't have much confidence, but...
It's fun to think through trial and error until you get it right.
That's why it ended so quickly.
I'm in more trouble than I am, so please do that.
Please worry a lot, think ok
I'll try my best not to let it stop.
Thank you very much
Now then, it's time to ask that strange question.
Introducing that introduction that will give you a lot of information.
This is an introduction. Please ask me all those strange questions.
I'm looking forward to seeing you, Roboko Senpai.
I thought you'd forgotten me, but I'm not.
My senior introduced me.
I guess it was my introduction.
Hello Moe Takasei's virtual robot
This is Roboco. Yes, I was totally sweating.
But I feel like I'm in a hurry right now, so please explain.
More
What do you think? Have you ever tried sea soup?
I don't really care, right?
I looked it up and found out there was a game like that.
I see, but if you're strong then maybe
I thought I won, but what do you mean?
I might end up winding up the cat.
No, even if it lasts for an hour.
It might turn out to be a good episode
Even if there is nothing, there is something about genius and high performance.
We're fighting, but I'll do something.
Hey, I want you to ask me all those weird questions.
Thank you very much for your understanding.
Please, please, please take a look
Some of the people who are talking about Hollow or Uga.
Some people don't know about soup.
I think so, please explain what kind of game it is.
I'll give it to you. Dodon yes.
Yes or no for sea turtle soup
guess the truth of the story by asking questions
The beginning of the game
You can only teach the introduction and the ending.
Take a look and think about it in the comments section too
I would be happy if you could watch it while doing so.
Thank you, please, please
Please, please, and this time.
It's because it comes with the Hololive version.
Problem where the names of Hololive members appear
It's amazing how it turned out.
Create an original problem for this episode
We also receive
So it's really the first time we've published any questions.
There is, so let's all think about it.
Let's go ahead, let's get started.
I'd like to go to the first question, the first
I made the problem a bit easy.
This is Teren.
The youngest Koyori Ko-san is below everyone else.
I'm so glad it happened
Why is it that I am lower than anyone else?
I'm happy I'm happy I'm happy Um this is
Koyori loves being stepped on
You have a wall like that, right?
Maybe it's possible that it's in the same range.
I don't know, but it doesn't really matter.
No, it doesn't matter, yeah, down this.
That's what I mean
Is it under the physical ah yes good question
Yes, it's physics, yes, that's right.
That's physics. Is that a loli?
No, it's different. A different Lolico wall appears.
Isn't that a loli?
I thought about it, but it turned out to be physical.
I'm more happy than anyone else.
Yes, I thought you were happy.
Is your body shaking? No, it's hard.
That's different. Yeah, it's difficult.
Wouldn't it be nice if we were also lower?
Yes, that's right. I'm happy too.
I think everyone is happy, everyone is happy.
I'm happy
It's okay to be stepped on or something like that.
That's right. Is that what the wall is about?
It doesn't really matter, it has something to do with the body.
Speaking of which, it looks like you're fit.
Yes, it has something to do with body size.
It's not about size, it's about size.
no body
Down, down, down, down, this is something like that ranking
Is the format or numerical value relevant?
No, no, no, it's a coupling
Does it have anything to do with that?
I was happy
I've seen a lot of news, and I've heard a lot of stories.
Even if I feel like it's a possibility, I'm a little happy about it.
Maybe it's numerical.
Do you understand? It's not a number.
Yes, yes, it's obvious.
Is that something you can understand? Yes, that's right.
I can see that it hasn't been stepped on after all.
I'm being stepped on, yeah, I'm not being stepped on, I'm going down.
Why is it getting lower? Why is it getting so much lower?
I was happy, so everyone must be happy.
I thought it was based on height and weight, but it turns out it's not.
That's right, a suit, right?
Yeah, I'll give you a little hint.
There's something about the body.
This may be confusing, so please take a look at your body.
I said yes to my body in some way.
Ah, I see
Yes, somewhere in my body, somewhere in my body, yes
somewhere
Are you talking about lower body breasts? No, they are big.
Saga
Ah, but that wouldn't work on the lower side.
It's not big, it doesn't seem to make me happy.
Amo, I like loli, loli is loli.
Yes, I like lolis, but that's a bit...
Relationships that may have been information that is currently irrelevant
It doesn't matter, the size of the face or the difference
Well, it's different, isn't it the size?
I think they like it when it's small.
Maybe it's because it got smaller.
There isn't one
So the bottom is not the bottom of the Great Atonement.
It's not a compensation, it's not a physical
It's physically below Koyo-chan's.
Bring it down, bring it down, bring it down.
I brought it down and got it down.
Yeah, if you're lower than anyone else, give me one more hint.
There's a part of my body that seems like it's going to come out lol
It's not, but loli is better than that.
It might be easy to get into a situation lol
Underground, all that stuff
It's okay if you say it, Ta-senpai, I understand.
Uro angler means this.
What is a low angler in Angler?
Or look at it from below as a low angler.
So that's not the case.
I don't think so. I'm a loli, so I'm tall.
It's not because it's small, it's like that
Lying down like that, there's something about me that's better than anyone else.
Yeah, that's right, my body is lower than anyone else's.
Part of my body is on the bottom.
I guess it feels like a part of me is logically returning to Doshin.
I don't know if I'll go back to my consulate, but I'll go back to my sister.
Did it happen? That's what happened.
Hoi hoi yes, but the difference is that you can receive New Year's gift.
Masune
I guess it doesn't mean he's younger now.
Because he's the youngest, yes, even that adult could be one.
However, the images are a bit concentric.
I don't know how it feels, but what does it look like, child?
When I think back to my memories of when I was a child,
I wonder what I did when I was a child.
I'm happy to be on the bottom of the bunk bed.
Is that true? But there are quite a lot of them.
There is a possibility that there is
Oh, it might end up being about 5 bunk beds.
I can't believe it. 5 bunk beds. Comment section.
Well, I guess there are quite a few correct answers.
I don't know anymore
Are you happy to be everyone's little sister?
No, it has nothing to do with age.
No, no, no, it's physics.
I thought it was the number of pons or something.
It's different because it's not a number.
Na
Well then, let's say it's a game.It's a game.
Let's play, let's play, let's play, let's play when we get down
I'm happy when I get to the bottom
It's a fun game, but it's probably a fun game.
Tag is different, Karuta is New Year's day
It doesn't matter.
If you think this is something great, please give it a try
It felt like it was going round and round.
What is that?
Oh, let's play and play. Well then, it's New Year's Day.
Does it have anything to do with it? It might look good on New Year's Day.
I think I'll do something other than New Year's, which suits me well.
New Year's play Yeah yeah yeah right now.
The answer is, I passed by just now.
But lie once, Calcult Cult, where are you, Senpai?
Is Karta Karta Karta Karuta understood?
I understand
Or are you saying that you understand that?
The first thing you want to do when taking Karuta is
Are you happy that you got it?
That's great. Yes, yes.
Even though I haven't tried it and don't understand it, I say karuta.
So, let's play karuta.
The hands of the three of them all took out their cards at once.
While they were fighting, Eko's hand was on the bottom.
He was happy when he got the tag.
That
The title is, I see, I see, ChoRoboco senpai, this
is high performance
No, if it weren't for Roboko Senpai's cult.
It seems like you didn't know, right?
Thank you thank you very much
Something is passing by and I don't know what to do.
Well, it's just a simple problem.
It was, but I guess it's a matter of compatibility.
I thought it would be difficult after Neneko because there is
Sometimes you can get the right answer right away.
I think so, let's go next time.Yes, next time.
This is Robot Girl A Roboko.
I couldn't move my fingers, so I looked for the remote control.
Why on earth is it Poco? That's ridiculous.
Don't mess with me, it's too hard. I'm normally useless.
Is it because it's already common knowledge?
There may be a difference, but I don't feel it.
Hey hey hey my fingers can't move
What happened is it stopped working.
Yes, it wouldn't work even if it wasn't Ko-san.
Even in that case, it will all work out.
Do you look for the remote control when you can't move your fingers?
It's very possible. Maybe.
Does it have to do with the temperature of the room?
That's wrong. It means it's frozen.
It's a problem that even humans can deal with.
It's a good question. It's good.
is the remote control
Even humans can go there.I can go remote control.
Does it have anything to do with Darue Robo or home appliances?
Ah, there it is. Yes, home appliances.
Does it work? Yes, it's the remote control for the air conditioner.
Kaa, the remote control can be anything. Anything.
Anything is fine, anything is fine.
Good too
It doesn't matter what I do or what I do, it's who I am
I wonder what Ro-senpai is like, who is so caught up in himself.
My fingers couldn't move on the remote control.
I wonder what I should say.
The reason it's gone is because something is bothering me.
I wonder if it's like a house when I'm in the way
Yeah, I feel like someone other than me is nearby.
Is it related to that? No, it is related.
No, it doesn't matter, it's okay even if it doesn't matter
Is it possible for one person to make it happen?
I wonder if we're all alone.
I thought something was bothering me.
That's right, it's cute, it's cute, but it's different
Well, isn't that what it is?
Yeah, because my fingers can't move anymore.
I was looking for a remote control. I was looking for a remote control.
I'm looking for a remote control. There are quite a few remote controls.
This might be important.Why are you looking for a remote control?
remote control
Reason: Remote control or whatever is fine.
It doesn't matter whether you have a remote control or not.
Even if you don't like it
Yeah, yeah, but I can't move my fingers.
I've done this before. Can you move?
Everything is moving except for my fingers. Yes. Everything is moving except for my fingers.
Terue, what kind of situation is it?
Do you have anything in your hand other than the remote control?
I had some stuff.
This might get complicated
But the situation
This is my own finger yeah good question
Yes, no, yes, it's someone else's finger after all.
There's something wrong with this, Mel-chan.
The scent of an incident is the scent of an incident.
I wonder if you've just noticed the scent of
But it seems different. It's okay if it's different.
Try it and you'll see how your fingers look
I guess it doesn't mean it stopped moving.
Even if you say it's not yours, it's murder.
It was fine
I wonder if this is different from murder?
But why are you looking for the remote control?
i am a robot
A girl who can stop murderous impulses
Title: Adeko's title, I use it a lot.
So, the title of sea turtle soup is wrong.
Don't worry, don't worry about it, don't worry about it
It might be better to charge it.
I'm going to do it, but it's a bit good.
This is a very critical question.
Is it related to running out of battery? Yes.
Ahh, it has nothing to do with breaking 10 in a row.
I'm not a robot after all, okay to me
Leave it to me. It seems like the battery is dead.
I want you to think about this.The bench is broken.
Yes, Mel-chan uh screen
The cursor stopped working.
great answer
Yes, it was early. The electricity went out. That's what happened.
There's something with fingers on it, no, there's nothing here.
It's a little difficult because there are times when
But, Rico said anything is fine.
But even so, batteries were needed.
I see, I understand.
That's great, Roboco-san is on the computer.
I was working on a finger-shaped mouse
The cursor suddenly stopped moving
I noticed that my mouse battery was dead.
I ran out of new batteries.
I think it was a bit of a bummer.
Okay, so I decided to use the remote control for now.
I thought I would replace the battery and make it in time.
That's the problem. Wow, that's amazing.
This is a bit of a genius Mel-chan
That's amazing, but this seems like a cooperative type.
If we all lead this way and become humans,
I might be able to make it, that's awesome
You should keep saying this more and more.
However, I am getting closer and closer to the layer of the heart.
It was great, it was great, it was great, it was great.
Now I would like to move on to the third question.The third question is
This is the scary aquarium.
When Mel went there, he saw a dead fish.
But she looked very happy
Why on earth are you a psychopath?
There is a possibility from this, this, that, etc.
Speaking of dead fish, it's some kind of living thing.
I saw you feeding
Karaaaa what?
picture
That's what it means, isn't it?
early
The second time was really fast.
So this is Mel at the aquarium.
I decided to try feeding the seals.
The staff gave her some fish to feed.
It seems like it was handed to me.
I see, I see, that's why
Tabel-chan
Wow, even a dead fish is happy, Ka-chan
I can eat this
Dako-senpai's question was right, that's psycho.
It's a pass and I'm already Uebuki-senpai.
I figured it out right away or something.
I died just thinking about the scenery at the aquarium.
When you say dead fish, all you have is food, right?
It didn't come out, so it's amazing.
It's true that your imagination is quite good. Sea turtle soup.
It's important, so I imagine it's a mess.
I know what it means to look cute.
It was chan
What Mel-chan had a deep understanding of was Roboco.
It might have been a senior
With that said, let's move on to the next step.
I have 3 questions left to ask if it's okay.
I wonder if I have time for this?
It's starting to get better, but it's spinning around
I've become so fast that I can answer right away.
I feel like I'm going to give up, but I'll go. Come here.
It was so cold.
What on earth did my face turn into a liver because of?
That's what I'm saying, Lamy-senpai.
This is a related issue.
Yes, yes, that's the gag that Yukihana Lamy released.
It was cold, but that's possible.
No, it's not right, but it's not right, but it's not right, but it's right,
I told him that if he didn't, his liver would be damaged.
No, no, it's cold, it's cold, it's freezing
Isn't it a gag that makes you do it?
No, it wasn't a gig.
Is the face related to the liver and the face to the emotions?
Ah, this time it's a nice house Ah, what's it like now, Lamy?
It's dangerous if you don't stay away from Rami-chan.
Yukihana Lamy asks if it's really okay to leave.
Is it related?I don't think it's related.
But it has to be Lamy-senpai.
I guess it's not impossible, anyone is fine
Anyone can turn their face into a liver.
Hey, it's cold. It's cold so I drink alcohol.
I tried to get rid of the fever, but no, that's not it.
Does the season matter? Good question.
Is it related to winter?
Yes, that seems like it
[music]
It's winter and winter
It has something to do with hot pot, and I don't like drinking alcohol and eating hot pot.
I want to but no
But yes, I guess the face is physical.
became liver
Ah, I don't know if "physical" is the right word.
Wait, when I said physical, I got scared.
I'm sorry, but I don't think it's physical.
That's not scary. Yes, that's an expression.
Are you right? It's not ahi. It's not fire.
Then it became a liver. It became a liver.
I have a liver. What does that mean?
What's your liver?
It's not liver fire.The face that looks like liver means liver.
I wonder if that means it's strong?
My liver may not be particularly strong.
Hey, does it have anything to do with alcohol? No.
But I'm a little hesitant to say this.
But I feel like it could also be alcohol.
However, regarding this issue, it is a good house.
Well, it's winter because it's so cold.
Is the mask made of liver?
What is a mask?
Or wear a mask or a muffler if it's cold.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, it was your liver.
Na
I'm imagining it too much, and everyone has come up with it until now.
It seems like a new topic has just come up about masks.
It might be a bit unrelated, no.
Or the liver from a person with a frozen finger before Japan.
don't take it
Well, that's where the incident happened.
That's wrong.Yes, this has a face other than the liver.
Is it possible that this could happen? Yes.
Sometimes it becomes the heart.
If that kind of thing changes your heart too, then why not?
If not, then yes, that part is good for alcohol.
Is it related? It's a shade, yes, it's related too.
Do you want to do that?
Yeah, yeah, why does it become the liver?
Well, this is quite critical.
When I say it's cold, I mean it's cold because you're shivering with laughter.
That's not true. It's a parent gag after all.
No
It looks like it's a different season.
It's so cold, winter is nice.
Yes, yes, yes, it's time to make your hands cold.
Is that the doctor who failed the surgery? Well, Mel.
That's wrong
Hey, the transplant surgery failed, isn't it?
I'd be scared if I turned into your face, you're such a psychopath.
That's not a problem, I see.
He was a genius up until then, but he was only halfway through.
It was winter and I felt like my genius turned into a disaster midway through.
Is this a game? Oh, it's a game. It's a real story.
It may not feel like playing.
It's not just a game, it's hard to imagine.
Does it have anything to do with eating and drinking? No.
So it's not like I'm going to eat it.
Well, I see. It has nothing to do with the new year's face.
It's not even New Year's Day.
I thought I asked for it, but it felt like I asked for liver.
I don't think it's like it's just a meal.
what
Is a face a human face?
Um, no, anything is fine, anything is fine.
Anything is fine, anything is fine, anything is fine
What kind of face is that? Is that the face of a living thing?
Anything is fine, anything.
good
Yes, I guess the comment section is correct.
Everyone in the comments please be confident
How did you know it was Mr. Soroboko?
My senior went to space, but he came back.
Come back, come back, come back, come back
Come back. If you answer correctly, I think you'll come back.
But my face and liver are flying into space
A cold face is a liver
I wonder whose face it is, whatever.
It's probably just because it was cold, but it doesn't matter who you are, it's cold.
Edoshi's cold, cold face has turned into a liver.
You're making me work so hard, it's such a mess
Why is this space robot limited to humans?
It doesn't matter, it doesn't matter
Okay, it's difficult, but here are some hints.
It might happen, but yeah.
This situation only happens to people.
I see, I don't have to be Aiya Roboko Senpai either.
That fox that becomes a kote too
The face of the old hag is also called liver.
It feels like my face turns red or something.
Is that wrong? It's not like that.
But this face, any face
It's okay, no matter how complicated your face is.
This situation only occurs in human livers.
is
I guess anything is fine with a face that looks like it's got a lot of liver.
And Mel-chan went a little earlier.
Ta-ya was really right up until the middle.
What did you say, Merle? What did you say?
Only corpses come out now
I didn't say I wanted to move, but I'm a psychopath.
Only psychopaths appear.
1 piece ago
He kept saying things like he was a psychopath after that.
I can't help it, but my hands are Samsa.
Kajikan
Isn't it from there? It's related to the transplant surgery.
I had surgery, so I'm weak from the cold now.
My hands are shaking, my hands are shaking, my hands are shaking
The expression on that person's face when they're training because something's wrong.
It's not a facial expression It's not a facial expression
I made a mistake. I placed the wrong one.
Okay, let's be a little more specific.
I'm going to incite you to specifically say that you have a bad face.
I wanted to, but it turned out to be a liver, which is correct.
That kind of thing is so true, isn't it?
I see, yes, this is the answer.
On that day, it was so cold that it was snowing, and I touched my smartphone.
My hands are too stiff and I can't move them properly.
I tried to select the face that appeared in the predictive conversion.
Tap on the liver that appeared below it by mistake.
That's what happened.
Wow, that looks like it. It looks like it's called liver.
There are a lot of things that happen, so it's definitely possible.
No, I got it because it was Mel-chan, I got it.
This is amazing, Mel-chan is also real.
I was halfway through getting all the answers right, so I couldn't believe I had to port it.
When surgery comes later
I didn't think it was delicious.
It could have happened, it could have happened outside
The doctor who is performing the surgery is too scary.
Because he's a dark being, he's so scary.
It's scary, but we were talking about alcohol on the way.
I made a mistake when I said that when I was drunk.
I see, that's so funny.
There's something wrong with that this time though.
I mean, it's a bit difficult to make that decision.
Thank you for your understanding.
Look at that right face. It's scary.
This is a scary scary horror movie.
That's a really good title, I like it a lot.
This is it, it's original for this time.
I had it made for me, but no.
It was a really great question
Thank you, it was difficult
That was difficult, right? Now on to the next 5th question.
I would like to go here for question 5
is
Deden Hands Free Efuku always uses his fingers
What I'm pushing and getting today is something other than my fingers.
What on earth did you get by pushing it at the place?
What do you mean, except for your fingers?
It's not a gacha religion, I see.
It's like it comes out when I press it, yeah yeah yeah
It's different, but we might meet each other.
But it might be possible. Is it possible?
It has nothing to do with the problem that might arise.
Gama's religion has a nice feel to it.
Maybe, but this time it was different.
Is it different? It's a part of the body except for the fingers.
Maybe that's a good question, but no.
No, it's a different elbow.
It's not a body unless it's a body.
No, I usually press it with my finger, but I use my nose.
If I push it, it comes out, or if I push it with my jaw, it comes out.
Everyone from the gacha cult named Ruu is in the comments section.
It's full of things, after all.
There are many things to know about hair, right?
hey
Always use your finger to press Siri
It's not like voice recognition.No, it's not.
press with super finger
Is it something you press with your finger to do something?
Well, usually you can press it with your finger to get it.
The more it happens, the more it happens inside the house
Is there one? Oh, that's a good question.
Is it an electronic device?
Yes, electronic devices. They run on electrons.
Move anything with your electronic fingers
Finger, finger, finger, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click.
Ah, a vending machine?
Oh yeah, if it's automatic, then that's that.
It's not IC, but I use my finger at the vending machine.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure I bought it with a card or something.
That would also be the correct answer, but hey
But, that's also correct, it's correct, but already
I have one so it will take a while to get another one.
Please consider touch payment
No, it's not touch payment.
Yeah, yeah, that's not that.
When those numbers that happen every once in a while come together
The one you get is like that book is wrong. It's wrong.
Yeah.
What the heck?
Yes, it's a vending machine, right? It's an IC car.
This won't be the correct answer, even if I say that.
After all, you press the button, so that's correct.
No, how can I buy it from a vending machine?
Yeah, it's not a finger, it's somewhere other than the finger
You can press it with a place other than your finger on your mobile phone.
Do you physically push it? No, no.
Yeah, I wonder what it is.
I wonder what it is. It's different from the one I bought on the app.
Vending machines with different legs and feet have appeared.
But it's not just vending machines.
Yes, it's not just vending machines.
Places other than fingers Fingerprint authentication Eye ID
No, that's amazing. Is there such a thing now?
I wonder if he's going home like that. Is it kept at the company?
That's not the case with smartphone payments.
Yes, that's not true. It doesn't have to be a smartphone.
It's a finger I got somehow
No, no
Uh, is it a point card? No, it's not.
I bought it out loud, no.
I don't think so, just press it somewhere else.
I'm pretty sure he's pushing his elbow or not.
No, I just cackled.
Or the vending machine was broken, so I tried to come out of it because it was broken.
If you see something wrong, please report it to someone separately.
I don't think there's any crime that's going to happen.
Yes, I'm glad I committed that crime.
Don't mess with me, please don't mess with me.
No, the title is hands-free.
Nai means I don't use it.
I bought it from a vending machine, but today I bought it at a convenience store.
It looks like I bought it, but that's not the case.
That's because there is no male male.
Do I have to?
Osuuosu
It's free, use your fingers
It's somewhere other than your fingers, right? It's somewhere other than your fingers.
The palm of my hand is pushing, and the palm of my hand is not pushing.
Dosukoi is Dosukoi
This is just a place
It may be a little difficult, so use something other than your fingers.
It might be easier to understand if you think about it
I got it by pressing it with something other than my finger.
Yes, other than my fingers, other than my fingers, this is the vending machine I just used.
I said that, but other than juice and drinks.
Does this also apply?
It's limited to drinks, yes, but it's quite interesting.
It's a pretty good point to focus on.
Is it drink related?Drink
Is it a drink in a can? Ah, both.
Yes, both are possible.
Neko book
I'm sure that drink is some kind of paper.
I wonder if there's a cup or something like that.
Drink bar style drink in a cup
I feel like I'm going to push it.It's like I'm going to push it with a cup today.
Yeah, it looks like you're holding a cup.
oh yeah
Yes, that's what it feels like. That's what it feels like.
I feel like this is the correct answer, so press it with your finger
I tried it, but I pushed it in with a cup.
Yes, let's make this the correct answer.Correct answer
I now realize that this is indeed the correct answer.
The answer is that Ebuki is always
However, I bought hot tea from a vending machine.
Today I came to eat conveyor belt sushi, so I bought green tea powder.
Press the button with a teacup filled with water to make it hot.
I got some green tea from Elements.
But the drink bar is also the same gimmick.
I'm sure the answer is correct.I'll give you the correct answer.
It's definitely wonderful, isn't it?
That's how smart it is.
It was wonderful and I'm grateful.
When it comes to tea, I think of Fuki-senpai, so here we are.
I had the pleasure of making this with a problem blowing senpai.
It was difficult, this was also difficult, but there was a vending machine.
It arrived pretty quickly and I thought it was amazing.
I kept thinking about it while I was sitting in the vending machine.
That's true, but how can I convey this?
It was difficult, I see.
It's okay if you say yes, but you have plenty of time.
Next is the final question.
Come on, come on! The final question is the Hololive version.
Or rather, it's a little closer to the image.
This is an original problem.
I'm not even happy here
Aspa man pays 10,000 yen and appears in front of woman
A red band appeared, and the woman who saw it was a little nervous.
I was so depressed, I thought why on earth is this a horror movie?
It happened
The trap has a red tinge. Was it originally red?
Ah yes, that's right. Red from the beginning. Red from the beginning.
It's not like it's stained with blood or anything.
I'm still waiting for a murder to happen this time.
There's no blood flowing, that's right, that woman.
Are other people angry? Oh yes, that's fine.
That's a question, yes.
Yes, yes, I am very happy with the content.
There was no such thing as a sentence
no
No, yeah, a red band appears, this, that, that.
Does it have something to do with breach of contract?
home
Ah, I don't know. Maybe it's my senior.
Spa Super Chat
is
Is this supercha?
It's not a supercha. It's not a supercha.
Oh, it's tight, isn't it? That's for shopping.
Is this related? Yes, this is shopping.
I might have figured it out. I got this.
Well then, it looks like Fuki-senpai got it right.
I'll wait and see what happens, but I'll wait and see.
I guess I know, I've seen this before.
I've probably seen it before. Gray hair.
I think this isn't a problem, it's a thing.
That's the answer, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Roca-senpai understands that and that.
Everyone understands, it's probably a convenience store or something.
Is there a possibility?
I guess I got it, everyone got it.
Oh, I guess the last question is easy.
So, I don't know if I'll see you again.
I don't have one, but since it's everyone's fault, let's go.
Is that okay? Okay okay okay okay yes
I'm going
Ro's haircut is the same as haircut and haircut is correct.
[music]
It's already early
That's why the woman is at the convenience store.
The clerk receives 10,000 yen at the register and gives the change.
I returned the receipt, but on the left and right sides of the receipt
A red band appeared, marking the end of the appearance.
I have to change the paper for the receipt.
When the woman noticed this, she felt a little troubled.
I have experienced this.
I know, I know, I've seen it before
If you have experience working part-time or something like this.
That's right, the person from before was a cat.
Wait a minute I thought it was that red receipt
Please wait patiently for the receipt
I've seen the clerk writing about it.
I have to wait, yeah yeah yeah
It's so annoying.
I wonder if it will turn off when I work the cash register.
Yes, I understand, it seems difficult.
The answer was yes, and everyone was right.
That's amazing
or
So, today I'll play 6 questions.
I received it at the time, but it was already the beginning.
And then it got really crazy towards the end.
Wow, that brain wasn't spinning.
Wow, everyone is already doing a giant spin.
It was really amazing with the rotation.
Thank you, there are a lot of difficult problems.
I'm glad that happened, but here are my impressions of that time.
I have quite a bit left over, so what is the problem?
It seems like you liked it or liked it.
Hey there, Mel-chan.
Can I ask you something? Yes, no.
Is it Mel's favorite problem?
I'll take a look at that murderer.
I'm a sapa psychopath, but today...
It was peaceful, but there were quite a few people whose faces looked like livers.
It was difficult, you know, that transplant surgery.
I've already gone
Ah yeah yeah, that's a good title
This is such a great problem, it's already a horror story
I'd like to see a world championship, too.
Neuga soup is something that originally existed.
The origin of the word for the cat sea god soup
The problem is quite horror so yeah yeah yeah
That's right, Roboko-senpai next time.
I want to take it out. It seems like I want you to take it out.
So it was my second time and it was a mess.
It was interesting. This time was also good. Ungoza
Thank you very much, you are a genius
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Senpai, how was it?
I don't really understand Leatherface, even his gray hair.
It was Tana, but also that Roboko Senpai guy.
I really liked it Ah, the one with the fingers is Riko.
I really didn't understand the remote control either.
The finger is not really a mouse cursor.
I don't go there, I don't think so.
There's always someone falling down in the book.
I'm wondering if it's there or not?
I wonder what's wrong with my fingers?
Don't think it's someone else's finger.
Yes, yes, I know it's not my finger.
At that time, everyone was holding that person's fingers.
This is how I can imagine it becoming.
It was really interesting. Let me show you this.
I thought it was just a great horror movie.
Yes, it's a pretty common occurrence.
But yeah, that reasoning is crazy.
It's so fast that I'm really excited
Everyone will give it to us, so we'll just
I think so
I'm just saying it out loud, but I'm really saying it out of imagination.
It's okay, yes, yes, I can work.
It was really good Ask this question
It would have been a little difficult if the number of times was fixed.
That's what I thought, but that's how it is
I guess it would be boring if I couldn't get there
There was a feeling that the restrictions were pretty good.
It was just right, but I'm sorry, it's time
It's a little bit soggy. We're a little bit wet.
He was too smart, too genius, too.
Well, even if I decide how many times to answer,
It's okay
I might be able to win a little bit.
I won't tell you anything, so you can avoid it.
Don't move
There were eggplants, but even seniors and seniors
It was called Karuta, but I understand why.
I didn't, but I certainly don't understand that at all.
But I had no idea
But I didn't understand it at all, but I guess so.
If that fails, I'll give up soon
It's still there
I'm looking for someone who looks like Tasho.
Yes, I've been taking notes.
Yo Trip Trip, this problem is difficult.
But I'm really happy that you enjoyed it
Which one was really fun?
I've already noticed it and my brain is so amazing
I felt like I had a flash of inspiration and became smarter again.
I'm so happy about this sea soup.
That's what makes it so interesting, I think.
It's fun to become that moment.
feeling
It feels so good, I hit it in seconds with gray hair.
I really want to feel good, it's amazing
It felt so good, Mel-chan, that's it.
There's no way I'd be happy with a fish like that.I'm already happy.
All I could think about was that
I'm glad I didn't pass, I'm really glad
Basically, I can eat just by thinking about eating.
You said that after that.
Even if you think you can't eat like that
I'm sure there was something like this in that comment section.
There was someone who answered that.
Restaurant I went to the aquarium restaurant.
Some people say it like it's empty.
I see, yeah, yeah, he's definitely dead.
The cooked fish looks delicious and I'm sure you'll enjoy it.
Well, that's pretty cool too.
It's okay to eat sushi, that's for sure.
Even if you eat sushi, you'll be able to eat it.
I'm happy. I'm happy. At the restaurant. Sushi.
I wonder what would happen if I did it
I feel like this, but it's true.
I'm a little curious about the fish that look like the ones you see in aquariums.
This is the tuna that was swimming just now.
I want to
Why is that such a terrible thing?
The building and the sushi restaurant are a little
I'm a little worried about how harsh this is.
This is Naruko
Everyone is really sharp and a little bit
A little hint on the first question
I feel like it would be better to let it out.
I regret that I gave too many hints.
Everyone was a genius.
That was a hint.Oh that was a hint.
Thank you very much.
Enjoy the holo live version of the sea of holo
I hope you enjoyed it. It was fun.
It was fun
Tae, I would definitely like to try Nega's soup again.
That's what I'm thinking, so I'll play again then.
I would be happy if you could give it to me, thank you very much
Please, please, please.
Thank you everyone.
Please also subscribe to the channel
Thank you, please, please.
Please, thank you very much.
I'll move on to waiting. Thank you.
Yes, I was experimenting with Hattag Oyori.
Okekoyo is Zuno. What is Zuno like? Yes, no
Tari Sketchle Haihaisei no Haihai
Yes, yes, the chicken feeling of a researcher Yes, yes
Yes, yes, there's a green dot.
One name yes yes yes yes power yes
Yes yes yes continue yes yes
Yes, yes, it's news. I saw it. Yes, yes, yes.
Yes it's cute yes yes yes yes
Okay
Mayonnaise is a drink.
By the way, Fu is air. Yes, big brother conversion.
I have some frozen udon ready, how about it?
Lighting complete key Yes Yes Yes Cook.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, but I was a cook.
Can you make Kobe? Yes, yes, yes, it's okay.
Kana no no no yes yes yes yes I can't go
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, I have
The program for Masu Yes Yes Yes Yes
Yes yes yes yes
Ah yes yes yes yes
Ugh
Yay Maria had mayonnaise is a drink
By the way, the air is frozen.
I'm ready.
It's from here, it's from you, it's from you.
I'm experimenting with tag koyori and it's okay.
Is it okay or sketchy? Yes, this is it.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, I'm a researcher and I like it
Yes, yes ...
Haihaiiri's female hostel fan name Haihai
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, please.
Yes, yes, yes, I can see it. Yes, yes.
Yes yes cute game work yes yes yes yes
Yes okay
It's just the mayonnaise that I made in time for the drink.
By the way, I'm Air, Onii-san.
I have frozen udon noodles at the entrance.
Funny lighting completed 9th grade
Yes, it's a cook. Yes, it was a cook.
Yes, yes, I can make a coby.
Yes, are you okay? No way, no way, no way, no way, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, I'm not angry. Yes, yes, yes, yes.
have
Masu
Yes, the fluffy prora looks like it's going to fall off.
Yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes to
Yay Maa-san, mayonnaise is a drink.
By the way, I'm Air, so here's the conversion video.
I hear you always have udon on hand?
Tasei's child is here.
Yes, I'm experimenting with the hashtag Koyori.
Yokoyohazu is Zuno is ho? Yes no!
Or Sketch Len, this is the best.
Yes, yes, a researcher-like skip, yes, yes, yes
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Accommodation One Name Yes Yes Yes Yes Help
Yes, yes, yes, yes, I feel fine, yes, yes, yes
Why does it look so good?
Okay, yes, okay.
Mayonnaise is a drink.
By the way, the air is frozen.
What about lighting?
Done key
Yes, it's the [ __ ]. Yes, the [ __ ] was hot. Yes.
Yes, yes, only I can make kofu.
Yes, yes, yes, it's okay. Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, I can't help it. Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, Khufu is about to fall.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Ugh
Mayonnaise is a drink
By the way, it's air, so it's frozen at the entrance.
Is the udon ready?
Nokuyo
Koyoridayosei's Koyoyorihash
This is Okekoyoha, which I was practicing with Tagkoyori.
Sketchle
Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Researcher
It looks like a test tube Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Green Test
Tube Haihai Haiiri no Yado One Name Haihai
Yes, yes, I say terrorism, yes, yes, yes, yes, I say
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, I can't see it.
Yes, yes, making cute tapes, yes, yes
Yes, the orchestra is big
The mayonnaise I made in time is a drink.
By the way, it's air, so it's meat conversion.
I hear they always have frozen udon on hand.
Done lighting done key yes yes yes yes
It's the cook, right? The cook was very nice. Yes, yes.
Yes, yes, you can make coveys in the sea, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, are you okay? Nothing, nothing, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, I'm not angry.Yes, yes, yes, I have it.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, fluffy
The program is
Oh yes yes
The mayonnaise I made just in time is a drink.
By the way, it's air, so it's frozen at the entrance.
Did you prepare the udon?
Saw
Yoridayosei no Yadeshai Hattag Koyori
I did it during the actual battle. Where is Zu now?
Yes, it's sketchy.
[music]
Yes, a gorilla werewolf blends in among gorillas.
Of course it's a werewolf game where you guess the secret person.
Gorillas who can only speak because they are gorillas are secret people.
If the gorilla can be expelled, the winner will expel and attack the gorilla.
If it's 1 on 1, it's a victory gesture.
Prove you're a gorilla with your hand gestures
let's gorillas
All the gorillas
Mr. Miss.
Hey everyone, I hope you're doing well. I'm C-Quinn.
My name is A, a friend of mine, and today I'm talking about a gorilla.
There are three more hidden among you.
Apparently so.
Ho
That's a good reaction, turn into a gorilla
Well then, the way he looks and talks is like this too.
Become a gorilla and save your life
It looks like he's targeting me, so talk to me, gorilla.
Banish the Hunter
Just a moment before I say please, that human.
Be able to speak the language a little self
I'm thinking that I need to be introduced to you.
Well, Mel Gorilla, please.
Introduction and enthusiasm, the genius of the demon world
Gorilla gorilla yo, Melda, what are you doing today?
Apparently there's a traitor, so I'm beaten up.
Gorilla Punch
Thank you for your help. I'm half a gorilla.
Now then, Autumn Gorilla-san, please.
First of all,
I'm fine
Na
Today I came to become the strongest gorilla.
Hololai's healing gorilla healing
I'm Lila Aki Roseta. Thank you.
Please, I can see it, it's dangerous
Next up is Gorilla-san, who has a muscular build.
I'm so happy
nae live 3rd grade
Well, today I want to win everything a little bit.
For those who think, if there is a boss gorilla among these
It's going to be easier to cut down on that.
Thank you very much. See you there, Gorilla.
Sandose dodo sundo sundo sunbos gorilla
Is it Godzilla or the boss?
Noa, it's the boss.
Taoro Live Battle Suzuneuuu
Thank you very much. I'm just Nene.
Isn't that a gorilla? What was it that moved so fast?
Well then, Mr. Small Gorilla
Woo Hololive Snow
Gorilla than bad boy
I heard there's a gorilla that's having fun.
Well, you may have paid.
I'll try my best to be smarter than my boss.
Thank you brain gorilla
Thank you very much everyone, I wish you all the best
So, let's deal out the first game cards.
Let's start
Uhololive's brain
Gorilla, I've finished dealing the cards.
I have no idea how you feel
Some people write things that are a little bad.
Look
I can't show it. Well then, everyone.
Don't let anyone find out, just play all your cards at once
Please take a look
Please check each other's reactions.
It's okay, how are you both?
I don't know at all, I say yes.
So close your eyes once
Please, yes, then there's someone in here.
People who are in secret cannot open their eyes and be found out.
Please appeal to us so that we will not be found out.
Like, be a little quiet.
Hey, it's this person. Now, close your eyes.
Please, everyone open your eyes
Please, there are ordinary gorillas 4th grade and secret.
There is one person
Cheeks are the first day's discussion
Start Uhoho
cormorant
Nonono
nohouhoho
Woohoohohohohohohohoho
[music]
Uuhohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohoho
Hohohohohohohohohohohohoho
Uhohohohohohohohohoho
Uhohoho
Hohohohohohohoho
Uuuuuuuu
Uhoho
Woohoohoho
Cheeks
Ohohoho
Uhoho
cormorant
Uuhoho
Hohohohohohohohohohohohoho
Uhohohohohohohohohoho
Uhoho
Uhohouuhohohoho
Hohohohohohoho
Uhohohohohohohouuuuuu
Ho
Uuuuu
Hohohohohohoho
cormorant
Uuuuuuuhoho
Hohohohoho
Hohoho
It's like it's written like this
[applause]
to
Nononohoro Live Battle Momosuzuneneuhoho
Uhoho
Yes there
The hellish discussion is over, right?
I wonder if that person was a secret person?
Please take a seat
To all the gorillas out there, there are people who you think are secretly both.
Please point to me, please!
Uhohohoho
Uhoho
Uhoho-san Neneho-san is Noel-san Aki
It has been designated as Mr. Mel-san.
And from here, Mr. Gorilla is Mr. Meru.
I am referring to Mr.
Gama voting results: Nene will be executed today
I'm a gorilla
[applause]
Is Mr. Masane Gorilla a gorilla? Both of them.
is
[music]
mosquito
So Nene Gorilla is a trio.
Tamin Wow, real gorillas are different after all.
It leaked out that it was about a short time.
As it says on the cheek
Look, Naru Shirokane of Live 3 regulations.
Yes, everyone understood right away.
But how did I know it was a gorilla?
How did you know I was talking?
Human words spoken
There was a limit to how much I could talk.
The brain was fast, and the brain was very fast.
That means I thought I didn't know.
It was leaking out
Neya-chan, only leak poop
Please accept this stinky throw.
tea
cormorant
Today I'm here to become the strongest gorilla.
Hololive's soothing gorilla stone
Autumn Zeta
But yes, I've already looked at the cards and wondered who I am.
Here are the gorillas who know
This time, we will reveal the position to the viewers.
Since they don't, who is the gorilla and who is the secret agent?
Take a look and think about it
Please, there are ordinary Ora 4 and people in this.
1 person
And what today is
Two mutant gorillas are two mutant gorillas.
has appeared
First of all,
Just say I love you
I keep staring at one person again
To take the Qi code you have to
Hey gorilla
is
and popo
oh
Genius is Mel Gorilla
That's provocative.
Let's go drink some drinks and call it a day
eye discussion
Start hohohoho
centre
Uhoho, I love you, I love you, I love you
I love your cheeks
I love you I love you
Cow
I can love you
Ruuhoho
I love you, I love you, I love you
Teru
Ruru
Ru
Hororo is right there
[applause]
Until then, everyone please return to your seats.
All the gorillas are scary
I don't understand
Do you know who the secret agent is now?
If you don't understand, you don't understand.
Then I think all the gorillas are secret agents.
Please point at someone.
Funene gorilla Nene gorilla, please help me
Nene Gorilla has 2 votes.
It's Mel Gorilla.
Help me think it's Noel Gorilla
Nasuri
The acquisition of Keho Negorilla and Autumn Gorilla is
Will it be a decisive vote? Will it be a decisive battle?
Oooh no suritsuke
I couldn't get enough of it
Hohoho then Nene Gorilla and Noel Gorilla
It will be a decisive vote on which one is more suspicious.
Please let me know
[music]
[applause]
Teru's amazing acting skills
The one with the most votes right now is Noel Gorilla
A Noel
Those who voted for Gorilla Noel Gorilla should hand it over again.
Please give it to me Noel I think it's a gorilla
I thought
people
He has 3 votes, so he will be executed today.
This is Noel Gorilla.
[music]
Is Noel a gorilla or secret agent?
is
Kau gorilla
gorilla aka gorilla
cormorant
Noel-san is not a secret person.
So the game is still on
Masu Noel Gorilla has a new will.
Please leave two words of 5 letters or less.
Please 2 2
From Tsurenekuro
Love amazing game Nene black game
Ninene black
Love, love ...
I am saying that I am making a big deal of it.
Noel gorilla execution
Wow, we're friends
genius of the demon world
gorilla
Melda Well then, it's night.
Secretly open your eyes and see which gorilla to attack.
tell me
Please, I said yes and looked at you again.
close
Please, gorillas, it's morning. It's morning.
I just woke up
[applause]
Please, when I wake up in the morning, someone sends me a message.
The gorilla was lost
cormorant
good bye
Oh well then let's talk about the second day.
start
Please love me
Love from Teruneko
black
Stroke
Love cheeks Nene black Oh black One black I love you
Nene Kuroko I love you
Oh I love you, I love you
Teruhohohohohoho I love you uhoho
Love
Teruhoho I love you uuuhohohoho
Ohhohohoho
Uhohohohohohohohohohohohoneku
Koyori love uhohohohohohohohoho
Love oh I love you
Uhohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohoho
Cheeks
love love love
lala love hotel
Over there
Well, everyone, come back to the world.
[applause]
Please, that's it
Well, let's go to the gorilla who thinks it's secretly both today as well.
Please vote for me!
Gorilla from Unanko then, two votes
Nene Gorilla is collecting one vote.
So the gorilla who received 2 votes will be executed.
Next door
Masu
[applause]
Koyori Gorilla-san Koyori-san Flying Gorilla
Or is it a secret person? I love you
In other words, he's a gorilla who thought he wouldn't get voted out.
yo means
Are you happy? It's a victory for all three.
Congratulations
Masuuuuuuu
The secret person is the autumn gorilla.
Ta
Cheers Junior Ho Junior
Houu
[music]
Congratulations on the victory of the three Urukas.
Thank you
Autumn gorillas are secret people.
My sister who didn't get up was happy in the end.
I thought the secret agent wouldn't kill me.
Because you say so, Akoyori was the culprit.
I was so happy thinking that
Nene is that secret agent, and Autumn Gorilla is a gorilla.
I thought so, so I'm actually going to Noelgoria now.
I wanted to stick to this love, but this is love
People will believe me if I say that
It's so obvious that it's not.
After all, if you loved me from the beginning, leave it behind.
I gave it to you
It's a monster
Oh my god, why did Mel Gorilla do it?
Did you get attacked? I'm sure you're right next door, Kuro.
That's because the language of Torilove remained.
I'll leave the two of you behind, so I can't get enough of them.
A little bit of Necro and Zan-san.
It was suspicious, it was suspicious
I was talking to Nadeyaki Gorilla, how I feel now
is super feeling
good
cormorant
I'm here, right? Yes, I'm here.
Okoyoha who was practicing the hashtag Koyori
Is Kusuku blue? Is it blue? Sketch
Research on Ren's research
Exposed shine, yes, yes, yes, change of sheets
Yes, yes, yes, one name
Yes yes yes yes help yes yes yes
Yes, yes, yes, yes, it's a lie.
Yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
Yes yes okay
Mayonnaise is a drink
By the way, fu is air.
Yes, it seems that the frozen udon noodles are on the rise.
Yes, the lighting is complete 9 Yes, yes.
It was a cook, right? It was a cook.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, I can play beer.
Is it okay? Unreasonable impossible impossible yes yes yes
Yes, I'm not angry. Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Mashihaihaihaihaiku's program is
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes yes yes yes
The mayonnaise I made just in time is a drink.
By the way, it's air, big brother.
Do you have frozen udon?
Here in Haisei
It's Yodayosei's Koyo, and it's Hatag Koyori.
Are you experimenting? This is a horn. What is a horn?
Yes, I'm sketching.
Yes, yes, it feels like a researcher's test, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, the feeling of green, yes, yes, this is the accommodation.
Waname yes yes yes yes te yes yes
Yes, yes, here's the news.
Yes, I'm going to make some good games every day.
Yes, yes, okay
Maria had mayonnaise in the drink
By the way, Nifu is air, converted to Haioi.
I hear you always have frozen udon on hand? Yes.
Lighting completed 9 days
Yes, yes, it was a [ __ ].
I can make a bi, yes, yes, I guess it's okay.
Yes, yes, no, I'm not coming. Yes, yes.
Yes, yes, I have it.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, fluffy
Program Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes
Yes yes yes yes
Maria's mayonnaise is a must see
By the way, the song is air.
I always have udon noodles.
This is Tase's Kokoyo.
Yes, tag Koyori is in the middle of an experiment, and this is a cloud.
Is the cloud blue? Is it bright?
Sketch Ren is here, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, a sense of place as a researcher.Yes, yes, yes.
A sense of place in a women's lodging
Nemu yes yes yes yes help yes yes
Yes, I say yes, yes, yes, yes, no.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, it's here, yes
Yes, yes, okay
Mayonnaise is a drink.
By the way, I'm Air. Yes, Battle or Frozen.
I hear you always have udon noodles available? Yes.
Done lighting done 9 yes yes yes yes
It's a cook. It was a cook. Yes, yes, yes.
It's better to make products than yes yes yes yes
Is it okay? Unreasonable impossible impossible yes yes yes
Okay, I'm not coming.
One
Better
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh yes yes
Mayonnaise is a drink
By the way, Fu is air. Yes, big brother conversion.
I have some frozen udon ready, how about it?
Tasenokoko
Yodayosei's Kokoyo desu Hatag Koyori
I'm in the middle of an experiment.
That's okay, so let's start a little early.
This is the first slot for New Year's greetings.
Just saying yes, that's it.
Maybe it's because I saw Gorilla Werewolf in the comments section.
There are many gorillas, and everyone is wondering when.
Did he somehow become a gorilla?
The comment section made me a little uneasy
However, thank you for waiting
What about the gorilla werewolf?
It was hell, more chaotic than I could have imagined.
I'm sure you're wondering if there is, but...
Thank you for being trending #15
Well, there's a lot going on in this world.
Is it possible to be number 1 in the trend on bingo?
It's a bit difficult, though.
I don't know but if you don't mind
Tweet with hashtags at Kokoyo24
I would be happy if you could watch it while doing something else. Thank you.
Please, no, everyone
It was fun, everyone, the gorilla path was amazing.
After that amazing king-like moment 2
There are two rounds, but each time there is one match.
We are in the shape of doing that 2nd and 3rd time.
In the third gorilla werewolf frame, that's right.
Increased positions and more power
We will deliver it to you, so please wait for a while.
I hope you will enjoy it.
I think so, just like this, with four gorillas.
If it's just one poacher, it's quite a lot.
I'm running out of ideas
Yeah, yeah, it's a bit of a werewolf game.
I think it will evolve next time, so I'm looking forward to it.
The gorilla will power up
Everyone is coming back.
Everyone is getting used to the gorilla werewolf atmosphere.
That's right, so the 3rd frame and the 2nd frame are more
It kind of looks like that gorilla.
I don't think so, everyone.
The movements were really interesting and it was great.
Moko's video is actually edited and checked
I've watched it 78 times, but I've pretty much made up my mind.
by the way
I'm laughing. Something about this makes me laugh.
Something like this, I've heard this over and over again.
I watch the video and remember what happens next.
I saw about
But it was hell every time I checked.
I keep looking at things I can only hear
The answer is yes. Please come next time.
Please look forward to what comes next.
In this corner, since it's New Year's Day,
Even though it's New Year's Day, I can't keep up with the past.
I was able to contact you and tell you that you haven't been talking much.
I'm a little upset with people who don't think so.
I was like, "Can you answer the phone?"
I would like to say hello to everyone since it's the new year.
I want to do something like this.
I think so, here it is.
That bingo thing, wait a second, the bingo thing.
I am also involved in image bingo.
Let's play bingo here 24 bigo this.
Yes, this is it. There are 3 people and 10 people.
I have a goal, so I'll do my best.
The courage to be able to write quickly is
I don't have one, so can I just hang up a little?
The person who contacted me and got a reply
I am planning to contact you.
But what should I do at first?
Let's get in touch with someone outside.
I don't think so, but I don't think so.
I met someone last year who I can't talk to.
There are a lot of people, so that's why everyone I met last year
I would like to extend my New Year's greetings to Mako.
I wonder what that is, and I hope to see you again this year.
I feel like I'm going to play something a little this year.
I wish I could talk to you in a way that sounds like "Let's do it."
I think it's great, but so do you all.
I think you're busy, so please come out.
Please stop doing that.
Please, I'm a little nervous at first
Thank you for the praise
Let's do it at first
Well, let me know what that is.
I want to play a lot of things
I'm doing it, but
[music]
that
I don't have many opportunities to play with it, so it's a bit
Do you have any streams that you'd like to talk about?
There are quite a few broadcasts that are not available at this time.
Wake up
I have contacted you
Ta Shiraihi-san
Hey, hurry up, I came here. Echochochoo
Just a little bit more
Actually, I've talked to Tama before.
Kana is in this stream
Is there anything like that other than that convexity?
over it
Masua
Hello, what is your name?
illustrator noe
Shigure is laughing lol
I thought I was talking about Mr. Sensei.
I'm your teacher, please stop.
Right?
[Laughter]
What are you saying?
Congratulations on opening the cage.
Congratulations on your opening
I'm so happy, thank you for coming out
Please wait a moment.
While I'm talking, I'm preparing to stand up like that.
Please wait a moment, please don't wait.
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
I want to do more with Iyako and Me-senpai.
I want to play, so yes, I want to play.
But I've never had the chance to play in Taiwan.
Maybe not, right?
I'm playing Splatoon, yes, yes, yes.
There was one, but then there was another one the other day.
In the game of life called by
I thought we could do it together, but that might not be the case.
I thought there might not be one, but there might not be one.
I think I want to play.
I can play in 2024. I'm happy to be able to play.
I'm so happy. I wonder what I should do.
That's right, no, that's always the case
Yeah, I guess it's a surprising collaboration between the two.
I was wondering what I should do that doesn't seem difficult.
I just want to play it safe like before
I know it's easy to do, but if you don't think about it, you can't play.
My hands are stretched out in front of me, that's what I mean.
Nade-san, why are you inviting me like this?
Apparently, I wanted to invite her.
Then I thought to myself, ``What should I do?''
I can't just invite her out like that.
I see, it happens quite often, and recently it has happened.
Beyblade and all that collaboration
I'll show you in the video whether it's possible or not.
But it's a video.Video.
I've never done anything like that before.
No, I've never played a Beyblade.
Yes, let me know if you want to try it or not.
Please 31 Let's go, let's shoot
knowledge
I don't think I've ever done a dialogue shoot.
I've never shot anything before.
It doesn't seem to fit in, so I took it off once.
It happened though
It seems surprisingly easy, so please tell me a little bit about it.
Oh, let me tell you that. That's amazing.
only
But
Please tell me, if you do it even once, you're a senior.
Unseya na naruyoe after that pokekapokeka
I want to do it. Yes, yes, I want to do it.
I don't have my own deck with Tayoneki-senpai.
Yes, yes, yes, I want to team up with you.
Hey, I want you to team up with me.Actually, it's mine.
I didn't build a deck the other day, so what deck?
The deck is Charizard deck. It looks strong.
Yes, strong, strong, yes, quite strong.
But I was playing with someone.
It's becoming a big deal, so let's do it now.
So I'm going to make a Talyzard deck.
No measures taken
He made a deck and told me honestly.
I wonder if it's okay, then a new deck.
I have to make another one.
Terrible, terrible weakness
It's twice as tiring, so it's a weak point. That's pretty bad.
That's right, twice the price is quite dangerous, so let's get it out already.
If I had any weaknesses, it would be over.
It's the ones who realize it, it ends so quickly
But I'm happy. By the way, what are you doing now?
I was thinking about Takaekoyo-chan, don't lie
It's a lie, it's true. Is it true? No, it's a lie.
It's true, I saw a gorilla. It's a lie. It's a lie.
I'm happy to say that I'm a gorilla.
That's what I was thinking Takako-chan is a gorilla
The five people who showed up were all gorillas.
I'm so happy to have seen you.
I'm so happy! Wataru-senpai will also play Gorilla Werewolf.
Let's do it. It's time to really become a gorilla.
Seriously, after seeing that hell, that ride
I never thought you would give it to me, it's okay now
I'll do whatever you want, it's too much of a lie
It was a bit of hell so no one came
Even though I thought he wouldn't ride, the second time
I had given up, but I can't be alone with you.
Are you okay
It's just the two of us who gather together. It's hard when five people gather together.
I'll do it again sometime if I add 3 more people.
The two of us can be hell, even the two of us can become werewolves.
That's right, that's actually a scary gorilla.
I've never done it before, but Hoano Card 3
There are 1 human beings and 1 werewolf.
It seems like it can be made like autumn.
Talk to each other and trust the other person.
You can play as if you thought you were a werewolf.
It's okay, it's going to be a little rough.
I really enjoyed the voice, but what do you think?
If you're someone who doesn't play werewolves that much, you'll be nervous.
Are you going to
Do you feel sad?
You don't believe me. You don't believe me.
On the other hand, the two of us are like werewolves.
What happens when you point it out together with that autumn card?
It makes me want to hug you, for sure.
[music]
Maybe you can deepen your sleepiness a little
I don't know if it's possible to do it via streaming.
No, but I'm sure
I definitely want to do that too.
Sea turtle soup makes me so happy I want to do that
Please do it again in 2024
I wanted to come, so I said hello.
Please let me do it I'm so happy I did it today
I've never done it before, but I've never done it before.
It's a quick game so it's easy.
I really hope so, so I definitely did it.
Yay, call me. I was really happy.
I'll call you anytime, seriously.
I'll be happy if I call you in 2024.
Please play various things. Play lots.
Let's play first.
This is where I learned the beyblade.
I'll definitely call you too.Okay, let's play.
I'm happy to have an appointment
Let's play, let's play, let's be real
Thank you for your time during that busy New Year holidays.
Thank you very much.
Good luck, thank you very much
Thank you, senpai too, have a good night.
Well, the song will change, I know.
Terunoe, I just saw the schedule, so I'm streaming it.
Whether or not
Thank you for your thoughts. I'll do my best later.
I'm looking forward to hearing it. Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work. See you again.
Because I did it, my senior came out.
I'm glad it was a little bigger.
I prepared it in a hurry just now, so it's a bit...
Sorry for the big face
Not only is it delicious, but it's also really fun to play with.
I'm really happy that I was able to make an appointment, but yeah
I really want to play forever.
I was thinking, why should I invite you?
I don't know what this person is like.
This game looks like this and it feels good.
That's what I thought about Buwan, no, no, no.
No, no, your face isn't big. No, no, no.
The size is different from that slightly different one.
But I guess I got the size wrong.
That's from this place.
It was too big for me
That's right, that's what I thought.
I'm sorry, but I have to adjust it.
That's what I mean by not being able to do it.It's that extension method.
Exhaust method Wow senpai's face is so small and cute
It will appear tomorrow, and it will appear from the new year.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Even though it's a place where you can get along well,
Somehow, the bridge fell apart and is now in ruins.
I hit the bridge with a stone.
It's dangerous now
Please try to get along well this year as well.
Thank you very much. I'll give you something different.
I just thought I put out the wrong size.
Na
Well then, let's move on to the next one.
Wait, now Sawatari-senpai.
Now that I have the courage, what should I do?
I thought I'd try it, but it was amazing the other day.
That thing went like hell
I'm sorry, I followed my senior.
I'm very sorry for making you go through this.
What's more, it's already flowing and I'm going somewhere else
I'm sorry, it's totally fine.
I'm glad, I'm glad we can get along well.
I'm glad I finished it.
I guess it's good that it was good.
We've been in touch since last year.
Last year we were in touch in the morning.
For the first time, we went on a date and had yakiniku.
I went on a date and the taste was amazing
It's amazing and you embrace me somehow.
Should I go and see that person whose voice I was imitating?
Try it
Maybe something in case I can't make it out
Let's not say that, he's a good boy
Let's not say it even if it takes a little while
May I
After this, I don't know who anyone is.
Please contact us as follows
Wow, wait, it's really fast, it's really fast
No, no, no, no, that cat is really
Um, seriously, that's the reply.
Speaking of fast responses, Hololive
Majin Senpai and
I want to call this person right away.
I think so.
Let's go out
Good evening, dododo, that's it, another time to my senpai.
Sorry I ran it
I love you, I've called you one more time.
Sugia, just now with my senior, that face
Because I said something about
I wanted to apologize, but whose face did I call?
There's a difference between saying that and not saying that.
do
They look quite similar.
What is your real name?
Illustrator Shigure Uidewayui
mom
Thank you teacher, happy new year
Congratulations and best wishes this year
Please, please, please
I'm sorry, I'm sorry about that substance.
I'm really sorry, but...
Yes to not having more standing
I'm glad you sent me that life.
I'm sorry for sending this to you.
Thank you very much.
After a busy New Year's holiday,
Thank you very much for your help
This might be the first time we've collaborated on meat.
Is it true?
Nice to meet you, nice to meet you, that broadcast
But it's nice to meet you and we went for yakiniku.
But yeah, actually, in the broadcast, I
I invited you to a hellish collaboration before.
But what kind of collaboration was it?
I would appreciate it if you could explain that yourself.
What should I do while I'm standing there?
I'm going to laugh at Koyori-chan a little bit.
The sound material called Shigure Ui Button
Hello, this is a one-chan conversation with people.
I wonder if I can do it, Makoyori-chan
I'm kind, but even if I make a mistake, I wonder if it'll work out somehow
If I did that, it would become hell.
say
That was amazing the first time.
The first victim seems to be Watari-senpai from earlier.
But no, it was quite fun.
That stream was hellish but he's a really nice guy
Seriously, he's such a nice guy to talk to.
They tell me that I'm a good girl.
Please be kind and forgive me if I make a few mistakes.
There is legal power that can help you, right? But that's more important than a child.
I guess there's a little bit of work to be done.
I see.
Well, I guess I like hell a lot.
After all, people with one foot in hell are different.
Oh, yeah, that's right, we're already like each other.
I feel like it's mutual.
Because of that Uma-sensei thing, I am so Uma-sensei.
I feel like the teacher doesn't know what to do.
Oh no, I did it once.
Is it okay to say that there is no longer LINE?
It's like being exposed as a positive person.
I only asked E-san if she was going to help me.
But what is a gorilla? Is that a gorilla?
There's something called a gorilla werewolf.
Is that because you can only speak now?
I'm a werewolf who uses hand gestures.
Maybe it's too dangerous, but if it's Umama Sensei
I can't go, but that's off.
Are you going to do it? Even if it's off, this is a big deal.
You're welcome, but on the other hand, what can you tell by turning it on?
Is it okay? Yes, it's an off-collaboration.
That broadcast made me think it was off.
Where there is no
Don't do it in a place like that, let's do it
It doesn't make sense, I did it here.
Before that debut, I looked like a gorilla werewolf with my friends.
He said he wanted to play a gorilla werewolf for everyone.
I'm going to tell you, that's amazing, my friend.
is
If I were to do it, it would be in 3D.
That's the sound that surprised me.
I can't do it, so I'll go to Conco 24 and apologize.
Seriously, I rented the 3D part.
That's amazing, that's amazing, Florive.
I guess I'll give it a try anyway
no word came
I don't think so. There is such a thing.
But on the day I do it, I was alone just now, so I took Cotton with me.
Isn't that good? Yes, there are 3 more to go.
Good luck to the 3 people who are supporting me. I was cheered on.
There are about 3 more people now, it's just the opposite.
The gorilla werewolf won't appear for everyone who does it.
If you say that, people will hate you.
People are talking about there's no such thing.
Uma-sensei, who gave it to me, is pulling it now.
No, no, I didn't hear that. That's unique.
I thought there was a place like that in Gba.
It's just a vtuber
I am a more sophisticated illustrator, so now I am an illustrator.
The teacher is absolutely right.
If you ask me why I'm an illustrator...
That's right, I'm sorry
Illustrators can become gorillas
No, I'm really interested. I'll get used to it.
Let's do it once offline. Let's try it.
Is it okay to have one off?
Even two people can do it. It's really true.
I'm different from the guy who explained Nowata's story.
No no, that card, that gorilla
If you use 3 cars, you can try it once.
Tame is also involved, and the three of us are definitely doing it with three people.
I tried it with it turned off.I tried it with it turned off.
Let's go eat, let's go, let's go eat, let's go again
Let's go, let's go, Shikoyo-chan
The bolo you gave me was really delicious.
Thank you for giving me that.
Everyone, let's eat adult eggs. Let's eat adult eggs.
I guess Chan kindly gave it to me
After all, I'll give you that thing as a present.
When I think I want to meet you for the first time
Good
People will tell me again, what do you like about Ekoyo-chan?
Let's bring some raw meat next time.
Isn't it a good idea to bring
Maybe I should do it a little more hygienically.
Let's eat at Pon's and Shiko Pon's restaurants.
Yeah, I definitely want to eat it so I'll take it with me.
Maybe not, but I have that souvenir.
It's a difficult one that I thought it would be possible to do.
The answer is suddenly, suddenly, there's something wrong with that.
Why, don't forget that
I'm so happy to receive it, but I also have something to do with the teacher.
I want to play, I want to do normal things.
No, I've always been wearing phlox.
I'm aiming for the brain position, so yeah
I'm sorry, but I'm aiming.
Or wait, how nice are these people?
I picked it up and tried to crush the small thing.
Maybe it's an evil organization.
Jit-icchan is so cool.
You look like that too.The materials you just gave me are also pictures.
Moe I want to be there I want to be there
So let's take that seat and hang the baton.
I guess I should just buy it with my brain in mind.
Then we'll have a brain battle.Let's go back.What should we do?
Is it multiplication or something? I feel like I'm going to lose.
I'm not sure, but is it okay? I also do multiplication.
If that's the case, I might still be able to make it.
to
Let's stop playing puzzle games and play puzzles.
It's also good as a game. Oh wait.
I feel like Neko-chan was strong at Tetris.
Don't play Tet, no, this is already Tetris
How many months has it been since I worked hard? It's been 7 months.
I think I've already forgotten since it was about that time.
No, I can win. Sorry everyone, I'm strong.
Strong image 3 years ago when it was considered strong
It's longer than that one and it's standing pretty well 3
Years ago 3 years ago But I still remember how to put it together
Teru Dannai Sukaecho DT4 etc.
I forgot, right? Yeah, I forgot.
I've already forgotten it. I've already forgotten it.
It's possible, it's possible, it's possible to meet Catrice
I was playing Pikmin 2, right?
It turned out to be a terrible thing, though.
Mama-sensei was also a mess, right? Everyone was a mess.
I don't know what's going on with Naruno.
There are some cool moms in the comment section.
I feel like it's kind of the same thing
I'm holding it like a wave
It's not me and Koyo-chan's fault.
the game
It's been a week since Bad Pikmin 2. Yeah yeah yeah
Oh yeah, it's an easy game to play.
Hey, yeah, yeah, I'm not sure about that, but maybe
Maybe it was just off-season, but there was a match.
I feel like it's a lie, I don't like Pikmin
It happened with the GameCube, but it's a lie.
I wonder if there was that switch thing?
It makes me feel good to do that. It's a lie, it's true.
Well, I don't know anything about it either.
The rumor I heard somewhere about that is true.
There will be a battle in 2, but it seems there will be a 4 as well.
That's right 4 Yeah, that's what I read.
It can be done on the job, but it's also fine off the job.
But yeah, I'm totally fine with it being off too.
I'm totally happy and happy even if I'm a Pikmin
That's cool, I'm going to play Pikmin.
I don't know if I'll play it, but I feel like it's a game that will pass us on.
certain
I just did each of them, but each one is fine.
Koyo-chan wa wa Yadatta 4 and that trial version
I just did it, I haven't done it yet.
I haven't done it, I wonder if I'll do it in 4
It's possible to do it, and it's possible to do it in 2.
Yes, yes, yes, I'll contact you again in a bit.
I'll do it anytime, anytime Chinayocho
Yeah, let's make plans.
Let's make some rice. Let's make some rice.
The gorilla that did this won't stand up.
Yeah, I'm a little shy about the gorilla.
But I would like to try playing a werewolf.
Mashoa Japanese Werewolf is the first to do it
I think it's easier to understand from the gorilla.
No, definitely not that
If not, I'll definitely go with those two.
I went with my senior and there were like 3 of us.
Maybe I should try werewolf first.
Let's try it, thank you 202
Thank you very much, please play.
I'm happy. Good luck 24 hours a day. See you tomorrow.
Thank you very much and wishing you a happy new year
Thank you for spending the past year
Thank you for your hard work, Masuamata.
Wow, you're so easy to talk to, Mom.
Since I'm a teacher, I hit Wibeam.
Good ui
Thank you for the beam Ubishi
Tokouchi Soneta Generic
Beam Necha is so happy
Just a moment
Even though I got angry, this is really just a game.
We went on that date and talked about having fun.
Sometimes we talked about a lot of things and we hung out again.
I said something like, ``I want to do that.''
It was really easy to talk to you though.
I had no idea you could battle with Pikmin.
Takara
I'm so happy to know that Pikmin battle
I want to do it, I typed it. This is the type I typed.
I'm going to send you some emojis that I'm thinking about.
I think so, so this was my teacher.
Thank you, thank you!
Beam Werewolf What Soreko will make new rules
Who is the real Ui mama?
Is it something like that?
I'll try to get in touch with you.
I feel like if it comes
Okay, please wait a moment.
[music]
Hey, just a little bit
Good job
If you don't come within 5 minutes of contacting me, please contact me next time.
I think I'll try contacting someone.
Look, I'm looking for an illegal Ubeam, but it's all in my voice.
I understand
You'll understand now, right?
It's like a game to identify the mama teacher.
The story of the button
I thought I wanted to say that at the time, and now I'm home.
But that Umama teacher's Umama
At that time, I was talking to a button.
Looks like I want a button too
Talk about how amazing Ubuton is.
Yeah, I was doing it on stream, and then I saw that.
Buttons are also available from cats these days.
This was not mentioned in the distribution or anything like that.
Yes, but that's why I did something like that.
When I tried it out, when I pressed the button, a girl appeared.
Looks like it's jumping
Something like that
There are many other homepages, such as the ``Nesu'' button.
Some people seem to have some people and some people don't.
There is
It looks like it's probably the first distribution.
Looks like I can type something like "yes yes" on my own.
I feel like I'm starting to feel like that.
Mayo Beam Warm Koyokoyo Beam
Warm
mayo
Beam: Well, that's how the button came out.
But this button was created already.
Absolutely, Mr. Umama called me to that hell project.
I just gave it to you
But someday, Mama Sensei Button V
This button is absolutely impossible.
I don't know if it will last 3 minutes.I don't know if it will last 3 minutes.
I'll just do it like a challenge.
It's like I'm the loser if that voice leaks out
A battle?
Na
It's a negative thing if a voice leaks out saying, ``I can't do it anymore.''
All we have to do is fight
A corner with a hellish feeling of coming and going
It became
Is it still difficult?
Na
Please contact the next person in a moment.
[music]
Let's look at the next person.
but
If you can contact me
If 3 people clear this bingo game
That's right.
The person I just contacted will be back in 10 minutes.
I can go about
Yay, thank you very much
Masukashi Komarimashi
Ta
Wow, 1 person called after 10 minutes.
It has been decided
I wonder if it'll end up feeling like there's something behind me next time.
death
Tara whispers so cute and sneaks so much
I'm really excited when it's the other way around.
I get flustered and my voice gets low. I feel nervous.
That's amazing. Wait a minute, then wait.
Let's think about the deck
Um deck deck deck
Deki conversation
I can't do it today
Hey, the first time I put it on, I was like, I'm gonna have to listen to this.
I had something in mind, but I forgot twice.
I forgot twice now, but I was able to ask Watari-senpai.
I talked a little too much to Mr. Uma.
I forgot to listen
No, it's not the color of the pants.
Oh no, it's a New Year's greeting, and I don't usually do it that much.
I'm going to ask someone I don't know the color of their pants for.
It's too dangerous, I don't want you to hate me
twist
Conversation
The deck is a gorilla gorilla deck.
I don't think something like that would work.
Two people talking about gorillas in a row
Well, I want to ask what you were doing right now.
It's a new year after all, so what have you been doing?
I wonder how you're spending the new year?
That's why I want to hear it.
Gorilla Deck Yes, but let's stop it, Gorilla Werewolf.
Are you interested? Let's stop for a second.
That's your trump card. I'm interested in the gorilla werewolf.
What do you like about Kakakotsuke and Kouea?
Hey, what did you eat today? It's New Year's Day.
hey
Adesaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhh what's your favorite thing to set up?
is
[music]
This year's resolutions This year's resolutions are quite extensive.
It's important, so I'm in such a rush.
When asked, I thought it was something like that.
But anyway, this is what I'm doing this year.
Talk like you want to do your best.
Could you please give it to me?
What was my first dream? What was my first dream? It was a dream I had when I went to bed today.
It hasn't happened yet, so it hasn't happened yet.
I won't sleep today, so I won't have my first dream.
This year's goal
teeth
picture
Yesterday 12th night, I was already asleep.
A dream I look back on on the morning of 22
Or so?
I don't remember.
Oh yeah, it's not the morning of the 1st of the 1st.
The morning of the 2nd
Kaede: I don't remember anything, but I slept a lot.
I slept a lot thinking that I would have some sleep.
Yes, from yesterday to today, that 12 o'clock
I woke up around 11am to do Asako.
Even though it was just before 11 o'clock, it was still too long.
I went to bed around 24 o'clock yesterday at 24 o'clock.
I went to bed around 10pm and woke up around 10am.
I was able to sleep for 10 hours, but I woke up once.
I ended up not being able to sleep anymore.
Much later, there were preparations, final preparations, etc.
Please check it out
So it ended up just like that.
I woke up at 10am and haven't gone back to sleep.
So, today at 10pm
I have to be up until 7pm tomorrow
Did you have your first dream?
I don't remember, I don't remember, it's mostly a dream
I'm pretty sure it's almost 12 hours.
It's true that some time has passed since I woke up.
Did you buy a lucky bag?
I bought it
Next time, there's probably about 5 minutes left.
One person and one person who said it's okay to take a bath.
It's like I just tried to contact you.
Much less
I even called someone else in the last 5 minutes.
If you are in a situation where you can
I feel like it's going to have that weird feeling.
I want to spend the next five minutes like this.
thought
There are too many decks. No, I'm not going to put them all out.
That's not it, the car is already out of the deck.
It's called Dodo.
There is a possibility of one or two. What are you doing now?
I don't want to know if you did it.
Wait a minute, who can write next? What are you doing now?
I know what you did
[music]
I know what's going on
Na
Currently being distributed
[music]
The color of the pants that aren't there is not a compliment.
You can do it if you praise it
If you do it, you can do it.
But
It's a little scary, but this is really cool.
hey
Don't be rude in any way other than to your face.
I can't have a goblet that doesn't exist anymore.
If it was a deck that was waiting for something more convex.
It's like the color of the pants is written on it.
This culture is here. What do you think?
Other
Office and other vtubers
What?
Is this there?
There's no culture, it's normal.
Hey, I think there's a 2-jisaji-san.
That's right. Something like this is everywhere.
When girls gather like this, I'm waiting for the convex.
When things like that happen, you have to wait for the convexity to begin with.
After all, it can't be done without more people.
Even if you wait, even if you wait alone, no one will come.
Some people do it because it doesn't exist or it seems like it.
Maybe, but even as an individual
It's easier to do well in the Ne group.
of
So, where that is, there is the color of the pants.
Is there a place like that?
Well, it depends on the person as well.
yes
Stop it, there are 0 people in the group.
Stop acting like this, cat bingo 3
I stopped once just before the word people
There's this real Sayoko episode called Ruu.
No, but this can be hung.
There are 3 tiers and you have to wait at the top.
It's okay, it's okay
Okay, wait, this is the pinned comment.
Let's change this by tweeting at 24
If about 3 people can go at once, it will be cleared.
pace sure 10
I'm sure people must be a little braver this time.
Have you tried going outside and getting a response?
Thank you so much
Thank you
Can I go?
Na
This really has a big chance of not opening at all.
Well, there's no way to win against the guests.
I'm entering it thinking I can win.
But if I seriously erase everything
end end end
You know, that home street is that place now.
I guess he's after Teruto and Kanewatari-senpai.
That's right, after this
It's been an hour since I didn't even know which mahjong place was 1st.
Is it possible to get first place in mahjong based on time?
I don't know
below the logo
Let's do a lot of trends here and there, New Year's.
So
Well, it's quite difficult.
yes
Karayabaimage-chan is thinking hard.
Gave it to me
What should I do with this guest?
Even if you win against the guest or vice versa, the three of you will still be here after this.
[music]
You know, the ones who came and said they could go.
If I can, I'll break through.
Well, all you have to do is follow the trend.
Ta
hey
Hey, it's exquisitely difficult
It's all about everyone, even if it's bigo.
It all depends on the recipe you gave me.
There were lots of interesting recipes
A revolution that I think is possible
[music]
is an exquisite anti
Right, the first place in mahjong is 2 if you beat the guest.
Mahjong isn't just a piece of paper.
A viewer-participation type battle with girls
Why is a guest a guest?
This is it, that kid, Bigo, thought about it at the end of the year.
That's right
[music]
It was ranked in
I'm going to play Mahjong MJ. I think I can do this and that.
mosquito
It's been about 1010 minutes, but can I go?
Na
When you can
[music]
please
My mahjong history is pretty good against female opponents.
Saying that I feel like I'm on top
I feel like there is solidarity with Mijokan.
But
Na
Nesone 2nd place 1st or 2nd place or 2nd place Yes, this is it
I was really worried about whether to combine them or not.1
I don't care if I put it in rank or higher than 2.
I thought it might not have enough power1
If you get first place once, right?
Okay, so it's super fast.
Let's turn it
If you can hit it several times, several times, thousands of times, at least once
I think I can get 1st place
[music]
I'm ready to stand up, I'm sure I'm ready to stand up
Toko
Good job
Thank you, one hour is not twice.
If it was a match against Topu, it would be around 4 times if you turn it quickly.
When did you not hit it?
[music]
I always felt like I was able to receive and hit that much.
I feel like something will happen if I do that.
[music]
Hey, it's not like I'm meeting someone for the first time.
Or should I say the courage to lie down to someone you meet for the first time?
I don't have a way to contact you in the first place. Wait.
I can go.
Tayoshi choneja bingo eraser
Okay, that's a bit, I asked someone.
I want to call
Well, the third person
I wonder if it will come out? I wonder if it will come out?
Happy New Year!
Congratulations on last year.
Thank you very much and let's get along well
Thank you very much for this.
What is your name? I was 2 years ago.
Yomirena is Yorumin
It's been a while, it's been a really long time.
What did you do? What were you doing?
I'm doing Coco24 here.
What time did it start?
Amada was held from 19:00
It's just the start.
It takes about 50 minutes and I can still go on.
Hey, I'm totally fine, Yurumin-san.
What were you doing with your sister and sister?
Hey, it looks like you want to open a Yu-Gi-Oh! lucky bag.
I got it right, are you serious?
Are you not interested in Ena cards?
It's better than that small school because it's a poke section.
It's true that I'm also holding a boke party.
Well, I bought a lucky bag card this year.
I bought a lucky bag, right? I still took it out.
I don't have it, but I'm buying it. Yes, this is sweet.
say
I've bought absolutely everything.
It's fun, but this is actually my first time buying a lucky bag.
Isn't it already difficult to buy lucky bags?
Well, it's definitely a battle, right?
It seems like it's sold out, right?
Yes, this is my first time opening it, so it's amazing.
It was so big I was shocked.
Surprisingly, more so than I thought.
I wonder what that is, it looks like Puck Oripa
Isn't there something like that? Try your luck
There are only a few pieces of something like that.
It was an image, so yes, yes, yes.
Yes, that's right, so a lucky bag is such a big box.
I got a little scared when I got on top of it.
I'm looking forward to it, I'm looking forward to it.
Did you win? Well, I'm still confused, Yu-Gi-Oh!
The only thing I opened was Sugu-chan's lucky bag.
It was my first time getting a card lucky bag this year.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah so sweet
If I were to say I was looking for something, that would be it.
I hope I win the girl's card.
I won the game, part 1.
It's shown in the picture, but I see some of it.
You two look like girls, yeah, yeah, but you two.
I'm glad that the girl won the prize.
That's nice. There aren't many girls in Yu-Gi-Oh.
I don't have an image of it, but I'm sure it's a dragon or something.
Yeah, yeah, it's a cool type though.
There seem to be a lot of cute types as well.
Yeah, I didn't have an image of it.This is how it turned out.
The cards that come are like this
That's right, it's a strong card.
I have an image of it being valued somehow.
Yeah, Yu-Gi-Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, but
Good job, Yu-Gi-Oh! cards too.
Isn't it dangerous? Yes, it's true.
I don't have much money, I'm doing so much
Really? I feel like we're already here.
Maybe you're a collector too.
Also Yu-Gi-Oh, Pokeka, and Yu-Gi-Oh!
I can't do that, it already has too many effects.
That's right, that's that, that's so difficult
Yes, it's a game or an app.
Yeah, the app is still keeping it just fine.
I don't know how it feels, but it seems like there's a lot to remember.
That's what I think when I watch Yu-Gi-Oh!
But Pokeka Pokeka is definitely simpler.
It's true, it's true, it's true.
Stars fall off so quickly.
I haven't played against anyone since I made Neuchi Mosa.
I want to be proud of what I created.
I left it like that and before I knew it, I couldn't use it anymore.
No, it doesn't seem like it.
It looks like it's going to be really early, even before the debut.
I had put together quite a bit and looked back at it the other day.
It's been dropped so much that it's unusable
It turned out that it wasn't there.
Well, that's fine, that's not the case.
I'm building a deck right now and it's already going down.
There is a terminal
Okay, let's play together once we're all together.
Nemu, why do you make it? Let me ask you something.
Let me ask you what type you want to make it with.
Hey, if that's the way you ask, I won't tell you.
I can't tell you, you just have to listen better.
I should have asked you what type of person you like.
I like type, I don't care about type, that much.
I'm not particular about it, but it seems like it.
Also a ghost type and similar esper.
What about the type? Psychic type?
That's good, since he's a pushover esper type.
Eyurumi-san, who seems like she's done with it, is my favorite.
Who do you want to play?
I haven't told you this, but it was my first dream.
Yeah, seriously that Pikachu with 8 eyes
Pikachu came out
What kind of dream are you having? Is that something you don't like?
That Pikachu, that Pikachu
I've been alive forever and I'm more alive than that human.
That Pikachu seems like it can't die anymore
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
Because I can't do it, I've been watching the flow of time forever
I spend all that time looking at you
Yeah yeah, it's Pikachu and I'm the same
I'm not that immortal, but yeah yeah hehehe
Come and say I'll be with you
It ended with such emotion, yeah, it's really cool.
It's a good story, but why did Pokemon come out?
It's here, 1 fu 2 taka 3, it looks like Pikachu
It feels like that, but it's still Pikachu
I wonder if it's a deck. Isn't it also electric?
Maybe it's different
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah pikachu
I don't know why it came out, but yeah
I was playing Pokemon Sleep with a pillow book.
Pokemon Sleep isn't playing right now, huh?
That's right, I was doing it last fall.
I guess I forgot to press that button.
If you forget to press the button
I can't get Pokemon, only biscuits.
Because I can't get it, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
I just feel sad.
It's going to be so yeah yeah yeah yeah
I just stopped playing that one more than the cat.
I fell asleep thinking about setting it up.
Yes, that's right.
I'm fine with getting a biset though.
I can't wait to play it again this year.
I'd be happy if you did.What do you want to do with me?
What do you want to play in 2024?
Yeah yeah yeah I'm starting now
Start making plans like this from now on.
By the end of this year, we'll have become very good friends.
Isn't it? Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I'm so scared of what you want to do with me.
It's scary to hear that, but it's not like that, just like me.
I want to get along well, so what do I want to do?
Are you interested in the gorilla werewolf? What is that?
This is the first time I heard about it, but I thought it was a dark pot werewolf.
I've been hearing about it a lot lately, but I don't know about Yami Nabe Werewolf.
Nie
I don't know about gorilla werewolves, just say something.
I'm a werewolf, but I'm not sure.
You may have heard a little bit about it.
It does exist in the game, but I think so.
Is Ade Gorilla humane? Is it okay?
Is that okay? I'm not interested. Yeah, yeah.
I like horror games, but I don't like them.
Please operate it, I'll watch from behind.
Yeah, but I want you to see it. It's not true.
I'll take a look at it.
I don't really have anything to say.
Don't do that, Jako-chan
I've been operating it all the time, I've been sitting next to you.
I'm glad you're right behind me, protecting me.
Hey, don't be scared. Why is that?
That's the kind of thing that protects.
Why can't the ghosts save me?
No, no, no, no, it's like this
I hope you have some fun stories to tell
I'm so excited that you're confusing me like this.
That's right, that's right, that's right
I guess so, but I don't want to ruin the atmosphere.
I want you to break it, I'll prepare a scary story for you.
So let's play a fun game
I definitely want to do it
Why isn't it scary?While I'm doing it, I even tell scary stories.
Do I have to ask? I guess so.
Why are there so many stories about my experiences?
I have to listen to the real thing
But it's a fun game
Let's play a fun game
Let's see again
Did you play around with Granblue Versus today?
Well, first I turned it, turning it 10 times in a row 10
I missed in a row ah 10 in a row Amone 10 in a row
That's what happened today. Ah, it was good.
Now that I think about it, the old battlefield will be in 3 days.
Please open it because it's there.
Yes, yes, that's right, you can open it.
It's okay, Neri-chan, global.
I said yes, so I'm looking forward to it.
Well then, thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your support. I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
Thank you
Yorumi-san is such a scary person.
Tat
When I talked to Moe about that and that.
The image seems a little different
I felt like
But I said, Wait a minute, so I went to Yomi.
Rena
I was under a lot of pressure.
It's amazing, there's more to it
I think he was like, ``You're cute, aren't you?''
I did it, but it's been like this for several months.
talk to me
If I hadn't talked to you, I'd have a really hot fever.
I've become stronger, I guess it means I've become deeper inside.
Is that what it's like? Is it like this?
Good, good, good, something better than this
Did I do something?
That's what I thought because it was the last bus.
Before you know it, the trial period has ended.
It's over. It's really something like that.
Now while I was playing Granblue Versus
He replied saying that he could go.
But I'm not sure, if that's impossible, I'll apologize.
Thank you very much
Do you want to
The next corner is about 50 minutes long.
I have some free time, so it's 10pm.
Please wait for about 5 minutes
This is the original meaning of two spoons.
I should have asked the color of the pants because of the figure.
Honahhonah, it's already a little scary, scary, scary
Excuse me when I said that, the color of my pants
What color is it? Maybe I should have just said it out of the blue.
Shire
do not have
I don't know if Kapha really exists.
Hmm, only Pecola-senpai knows this.
I'm currently in a situation like this so I don't understand.
A little bit of water for the old line
Deck water fire fire or fire fire deck deck
I'm thinking about preparing a little water.
There was a bonfire.
I thought I'd prepare some weapons or something.
I started doing that, but it's just for this place.
I was too busy preparing for it and couldn't finish it.
weapon
But next is Hiri.
hey
It's January 5th. I won't make it in time.
Well, I guess I won't make it in time, but that anger has come out.
Come on
Yes, the Asa stone will also be withdrawn, will that become the Sa stone?
Become
Or if you take Percival, it's OK.
I still take the one I can choose from Gachapin.
Since there is, will Nico and I be able to choose based on that?
Nademo Hyla looks like water, just a little bit of that.
is
It's like water because it's resistant to fire and fire.
I feel like my head is a mess lol
Wilnas Ney Wilnas A Wilnas Sub
It's a happy fire, isn't it?
Nene Aso Mikael also appeared, so it was surprisingly complete.
Maybe I can run?
I'm wondering if I should go for a little run
By the way, I can call you right now.
I thought it was during that call.
I was contacted by you, but it's difficult.
Because it is so
If you can come again at another time, please let me know.
I'm sorry but thank you
Thank you
That's why there are 3 people in this corner.
Watari-senpai, Eui Mama-sensei, and Eyorumin-san
Gayorumin-senpai and Yorumin-san are mixed together.
Yumi has become like Yoruminse
Thank you for coming.
Thank you very much. Next greeting is reverse.
Is it possible to make an e-mail in 2?
I'm looking forward to it.After this, I'll start with eco-yori.
I went to a location and streamed the footage.
I'm so happy at the end of this video.
There may be some news.
Check out the initial footage
Please take a look at Kokoyo 24.
Thank you. What's going on today?
Let me collaborate with my science brother number Koyo.
I received it from Mr. Ariga in Fukushima Prefecture.
I'm here on location
Let me see how sake is made
I'm going to have it.
Nice to meet you
Nice to meet you, my name is Koyori Shirai.Today, I'm Koyori Shirai.
Thank you for your help.
Yes, thank you very much.
My name is Yujiro Ariga. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Yes, I would like to take a tour as soon as possible.
Yes, but it's quite long.
It's long, about 100m from here.
That's the pull all the way to the back, that's amazing.
It's a bit long vertically. Yes, it's long if you do it vertically.
First of all, this is the experience group.
If you're in a club like that, please come inside first.
Ah, sorry for bothering you, thank you.
There are other people who come to experience what I am saying.
Does that mean you come often?
That's right, when I originally created this experience pattern.
The president of Hamauchi actually made it.
I'm a farmer and I'm interested in sake.
I would like someone to actually experience making sake.
So I made it.
It will be a facility, and there will be other Sakakura.
The biggest difference is that it is very compact.
Yes, I was able to make a really miniature version of that.
A very big feature is that
Maybe this machine can already make sake?
Does that mean it's an opportunity to do it? Yes, it seems like it.
Wow, this is so small.
That's what you see. Let's eat some rice.
Let's call each other our own
It's a Masu-style Yes-style. Normally it's big.
It costs about 1 ton of rice, but yes.
This is 60kg when I use it normally.
Yes, I am currently using it to make 60 kg of rice.
Yes, it's about the same amount as you would normally buy.
However, if it is 1T, there is no way.
That means you can use just a small amount.
That's right, that's why I'm so excited
It's small and looks like you can make alcoholic drinks.
What's going on? Yes, this is it.
You might also want to take a look inside.
Please come
Please see here too
Yes, I have laundry. Oh, this is laundry.
Sorry to disturb you, here's some rice.
It looks like it's in there now.
It's called Damima and it's placed directly under the well.
A cover that prevents steam from hitting the
I'm doing it, but if I put it in, I'll do it quickly like this
It flows and sake enters here.
Is it going to take shape?The rice is right there.
Ema the rice that has been puffed up like this 2
There are two types of sake:
Eo rice Nema Kojima for making rice construction
That's good, and the other one goes directly to the tank.
This kakemato refers to the rice that is put into the rice.
I'm calling for some steamed rice.
Eh, we're this Sarashita, right?
Put some cloth on it, then put some cloth on it.
Use it to cool down the enemy.
I'll put it on that side.
Right quality and character quality are read as righteous quality.
Nesouun
So it's a place where construction work is done.
Put it in here for about 2 days.
I'm going to make some construction work inside this place.
I'm in it right now, so I'll just put it on today.
I'm sorry, it's being made right now.
Yes, it's the shape. Well, now the rice is here.
I'm waiting for it to be completed.
That seems to be the situation. Construction is currently underway.
Places where construction funds can be issued and construction work can be carried out.
It's already here, so don't disturb me there.
I wonder if it's closed for now.
Well, it takes shape, right? We actually do too.
Before entering, please drink alcohol or something.
It seems that there is a place where you can enter.
It doesn't seem like a big deal if the money comes in.
Yes, thank you very much
Thank you very much. See you in the back.
I'd like to move on to
This has nothing to do with sake, but pine isn't great.
I guess I've been in this place for a long time.
There's something special about the pine trees and the garden.
It's okay to mess things up like that.
Yes, thank you very much.
It's been like this for a long time, and I'm here too.
Since I was born, it's a view I've seen since I was a child.
I have one, but it takes a lot of care.
Thank you for being attentive.
My younger brother was climbing and playing on this stone.
A stone of memories That's right, a stone of memories
Wow, it's pretty spacious here.
Well, my parents are on this side right now.
Yes, yes, yes, there are parents, right in the back.
Well, there is a bit of gravel.
And here is a newer looking building.
I'm standing here, actually in front of me.
Kuragae 2 was standing, so that's it.
At the time of the Great East Japan Earthquake, the earthquake was still in the top 5
After all, there was a tremor here.
There, Emaku Moe's two swords were crushed a bit.
Did you put it away?
Sometimes this refrigerator is new.
I was allowed to put up the refrigerator.
This is palm
Do you mean that or God?
Yes, there is a God, and we are here to celebrate New Year's Day.
Yeah, at times like that, let's all do this together.
I'm doing something special called visiting shrines.
It's normal for Sakakura-san to be like that.
Or rather, normal imitation and Kouma respectively.
Alcohol is originally a gift to God.
Yes, it is made, so it is true.
That part is very important.
Yeah, yeah, there's a relationship there.
I think there are all kinds of Sakakura after all.
But I think Sakakura has something different for each of them.
I believe there is a strong God, right?
I didn't know there was something inside.
If you're here, I'd like to take a look at the refrigerator.
Let's try it in the refrigerator.
It's cold, it's cold, my 5 degrees
It's a minor 5. It's not a freezer.
It's close to the freezer, but it's a minus.
If it's 5 degrees, it's still refrigerated. It's barely cool.
Inside, the alcohol is in such a state that it doesn't freeze.
Some people are always working in
I'm here, sorry for bothering you.
[music]
There's a lot of cool air blowing out.
I came in
Wow, isn't it a treasure trove of alcoholic beverages?
Well, most of our alcohol is in this.
It already has the scent of Japanese sake.
I feel like it does. Yes, it does a little. Yes, it's amazing.
What is the current state of this?
Nemoet The sake I made last winter is in the house.
I bottled it all up and put it in this
Store everything in the refrigerator at -5C.
The one you see on the right side of the back is a science major.
It's my brother's normal bade, and the label is still
I don't know because it's not on though
Number Koyo will collaborate with you.
Tagata Brothers has a variety of other alcoholic beverages as well.
There are so many of them.
This is the construction work I made.The construction work was like this.
This is where it's put away and it's called construction work.
That's right, this is how it turned out.
It's construction work. Oh, it's a small rice.
That's what it feels like, right?
Can I open it for a second? Yes, open it.
Is it okay? Is it okay? Is it okay?
This is okay, it's already done and air
It's okay if I touch you, this is just a dream
The raw breasts next to the scent will be 6%.
Yes, this is amazing. This is going to be sake from now on.
I was able to see a little bit of it now.
It looks good, thank you very much
Yes, this is my first time seeing it live.
What a wonderful garden!
From here
Look for it
good
I guess I'm standing on a stone of memories
Next, what is this place?
The rice I harvested this year was eaten during my lifetime.
That's where it's saved.
Yeah, this means it's all rice.
Well, everything in this bag is rice.
Please feel free to visit us.
It's warm here, isn't it?
This is different from the previous refrigerator.
It has the fragrance of Fukushima Noemi in it.
This time, I will be collaborating with two science brothers.
Sake Moe: Made with this dream scent from Fukushima Prefecture.
Even if it is the same variety because it has become a thing
Noe became a slightly different animal when she was alive.
This rice will eventually become science brothers.
Well, let's all drink deliciously.
I heard that you will receive it.
Is it open? Yes, it is open.
It's okay
This is Eno's rice, still white.
That's right, regular rice in a kota shape.
It feels a bit translucent, but yeah.
Yeah, yeah, there's a bit of a white part like this in the middle.
I can see it, I call it a heartbeat
What's more, Sano's characteristic is that he has that kind of heart.
It's definitely better than regular rice.
It's also a bit small and has a lot of white meat.
There is an image of him rolling around.
That's right, this is more than half of that reality.
It's something that's been removed from the original, so I guess it's fine.
It's in a state where it's been deleted, yes, yes.
Originally it was bigger and I ate it normally.
It comes in a much larger form than rice.
Yes, yes, if you cut it in half,
Your heartbeat is as small as this.
What does that mean?
Well, heartbeat is written as heartbeat is white.
That's what they say, but there's a telegram room inside the rice.
That lumpy part of Unun is
Yes, it becomes the heartbeat.
A place where the wind is so tight
That's really cool, isn't it? It's mostly rice like this.
There is a lot of sake in the center, so it is very convenient for sake making.
The most important part is umami, or rather, umami.
In other words, it's sweet and sweet.
It's okay to have an image like a collective body.
I think that's the key point.
The umami, flavor, and sweetness of sake
Changed to dattarsadattar or eh.
The white part is turned, yes.
Right.
Yes, next, which room is this?
It might be an amusement park called Ema Science Brothers.
No, but here is analysis in the analysis room.
It's a room that doesn't quite fit the image of Japan.
That's right, let's analyze that makanakae here.
There may be no such thing as
Please let me see it at Neo.
yes
Please cover it already
It feels like a science laboratory, but it's disturbing.
I'll give it to you. It's amazing, like a dropper.
Oh yeah, the familiar graduated cylinder.
Yes, it seems like it's an analytical device.
Okay, okay, what are we doing here?
Right now, here's the alcohol.
The rest is called a stick, but it's also called a Japanese hand.
I'll tell you, yes, the sweetness and spiciness of that alcohol.
Do something like measure something like this
First, yes, that's the machine.
This is it. Yes, this is the machine.
Sandwich and Anosa Yeah yeah that kind of thing
It's really an opportunity to analyze
It says it's a synergistic amino acid system.
The fermentation stage is called Komoromi every day.
Analyze the alcohol and replace it with alcohol.
Masou Sake Sandoa Sandwich
What kind of publications can be measured?
I wonder if it's progressing. Well, it seems like it's happening every day.
Is it like keeping a diary every day?
I guess so, so let's do a little something like this.
There's so much alcohol out there.
It's so sweet, but there's alcohol in it.
When you say that, fermentation has progressed a little too much.
I'm not sure if it has that kind of thickness.
Let's hold it down or give it some water.
Or maybe lower the temperature a little.
I thought I should give it to you.
Analyze it every day to make fine adjustments.
Where should we aim for the final flavor?
I'm going to calm you down like this.
That's pretty much what I'm doing.
It seems like it was adjusted from a scientific point of view.
Do you mean sleeping alcohol?
This is a brand that has more than its science brothers.
I think they put out a lot of them.
But everyone is being watched in the same way.
Yes, they all have the same shape.
I'm doing it. Yeah, this is when the screen appears.
It feels like a bad trade secret.
Probably.
There are some mistakes, but it's a bit too much.
I think I'll try to stay away from it
Yes, I felt like that, but it was painful.
This is it, it's cute, it's cute
What is this? What is this now?
Liquor that is in the fermentation stage
Put it in and it will hang down under the
Here's the transparent part of this, this is how it's analyzed
Well, that's fine. This slime is great every day.
I hear that you are working on it.
But then a slime says a lie Dragon Quest
Do you like it? I love Dragon Quest, right?
I was able to get Shinachi all of a sudden.
Well then, we've been playing Dragon Quest together as brothers.
I did it, my favorite numbering fly 3
That time is 3. 3 Yes, is that already? That one?
Released at the time of the release of Twos, Watwos, and Aene.
I used to do that sometimes, too. It's hot, isn't it?
It's hard to get that taste in real time anymore.
It seems that there is no real tie.
If you do 3 in real time, definitely don't do it.
It will be, right?
Yes, it's a fun and fun feeling, that's it.
No thank you yes
Thank you.Okay, let's continue.
Drum type laundry for slightly larger occasions
This drum type looks like a machine.
Is it likely that the washing machine will run out? Yes, it seems so.
Yes, I thought it would definitely be different, but this
What kind of drum style is this?
I use a lot of fabric.
Yes, I went to do some laundry earlier.
I'm going to do some construction work to replace those things.
When it comes to things that are used indoors, this is the way to sterilize them.
This has to be disinfected, right?
Well, you wash those things with detergent.
After that, you can inject the final solution.
Use that water to do all the work, even the slaughter.
It becomes something like that.
Like a drum-type washing machine made by Masuja.
Well, that portrait machine statue and specialty store.
It's a washing machine. It really was.
That's what it feels like. Thank you here.
Yes, this is now
I think I'll start working on Tenuri from now on.
That being said, it's already taking shape.
That's that machine you see over there. Yes, this is it.
Yes, yes
Yes, I will wash the rice with that machine.
Ah, it seems like it's done by hand.
The water is spinning around in there.
All loading and unloading is done by hand.
Yes, I'm doing it, so please wash it.
The real question is how long to soak it in water.
This has become a very important task.
Yes, yes, please tell us the amount of water in it.
I work with units and things like that.
However, the records around here are like this.
So if you are 1 second late, it will fail.
It looks like it's delicate, but it's roughly like this.
Well, 15 seconds, for example, this will change from 15 seconds to 10 seconds.
That amount of water can be absorbed by just that poop.
Yes, the 10kg one is 13.1
Since the weight of 10 kg falls by 12.94, this
Is it really bad that the deviation is about 10?
It's only a second, but to be honest, it's already 1 second
It seems that you can enter the world in 10 seconds.
Yes, it's amazing, 1000 pieces every day.
Does it happen every day?
Ah, today's record will keep up with me again.
That's right, thank you very much
Thank you very much, I also do this
I'm in charge of this, so I do it every day.
I have one job to do.
By the way, there was a loud noise.
What is that machine doing that produces the
Right now, that's that steam boiler.
A steam boiler is that boiler.
That is what people often say about Atsuhara.
Yeah, use that to make hot steam like this.
After puffing the rice, etc.
They also make products for heat sterilization.
I'm sure you're doing something right now somewhere.
Now that the rice is blown up, the rice is blown up.
It's not, but it's a little behind me right now.
On the other hand, wash the bottle with warm steam water.
I also use it for tasks such as tattari.
I see, it is in operation.
Well, every time, I have to get this to work.
This might be the most important opportunity to start.
Is that so? It's already a heat source.
All the heat here, all the heat, so I'm keeping it
Yes, good luck upper air boiler
There's some steam coming out though.
Well, that's actually steam.
warm
Give me the hot water bag.
Let's boil it and then go to the hot water over there.
By attaching a device or attaching a device,
This is how I see if I can do something like that.
Toko
It's kind of classic, or rather Kogoemon.
I'm being attacked by a power that makes me feel like a bloke.
Well, even if you look at the first one, it's a bit
You can feel the history, or rather the professional feel.
That's good. This is the one from before.
Hako Zonsui has a slightly new feel to it, I'm sure.
Something like Showa, Edo, Edo, and Japanese.
There's something like that next to it. There's something else.
It seems like it's a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit
I have the washed emoji here, so here it is.
Yes, that's right, this is actually
This is washed rice. Yes, this was washed yesterday.
I just washed this one just now.
Yes, I washed it in the morning, too.
Ariga-san says yes, it's already morning.
Wash it, wash it in the morning, wash it, wash it from now on.
Yes, it seems to be together with rice.
The rice you saw earlier was really nice.
There's a translucent part and a white part.
But this is pure white in this form.
Ah, it's true that the rice will absorb water.
The child's poop becomes a certain color.
What process will you take after this?
Is this rice going to eat today?
Let me sleep. Tomorrow morning, that power will hatch.
I think I'll be able to get away with it in just one day.
Well, I'll take it to Efushi tomorrow morning.
It's in a state where it's wet.
As a furnace that can be put directly into the tank.
Is there a range for the tank used?
Well, if you go there, it's still at the publishing stage.
I'm in a state where I can't find the issue.
Yes, yes, it's quite fast.
Well, I went there the next day and
See you next time, Mamoromi ni Mafukasu.
Wash the rice and puff it on the day of
Tomorrow I have to work during the day, so let's have some sake.
I prepare it in three stages, but this is my first time.
It will be divided into three parts, one for each dish.
Divide the rice into 3 portions.
I'm going to put it in, but yes, I'm going to put it in now.
Well, there's a second round of work tomorrow.
Yes, I finished preparing it.
After that, it will enter the fermentation stage.
It will be issued for about 4 weeks.
Just as the alcohol content has increased
It seems like it's going to be a good drink.
It feels like that alcohol is rising
Kana was in the analysis room earlier.
Yeah, I get angry when I see it.
Japanese sake comes from so many different families.
to see that it is becoming
Thank you very much
[music]
The next tunnel is a bit scary.
Like
There is, but yes, this is
Yes, we call it Kogura.
This was built over 100 years ago
Well, that old clay-walled storehouse, isn't it?
When you look at the clay top, you can feel a bit of history.
Well, I guess this is an earthquake disaster.
Stay strong, stay strong.
We fell apart, but we were close to each other.
Sometimes I get a little nervous.
Also, um, actually, Reiwa 3 and Reiwa 4.
There have been two earthquakes with an intensity of 5 or above in Fukushima prefecture.
By those three earthquakes
Now, the building itself is quite distorted.
Even if it happened, I ended up in that situation.
Alright then
Next year, this hog will be in a good shape.
I'm glad I saw that.
Well, I really need to get rid of this pog now.
It's the same in the same place.
Although the location is a little different
It is planned to be built on the site of Ekoko.
It seems like it's a place with a lot of history.
Yes, that's what's happening here.
Well, it's actually a brewing tank where sake is brewed.
There are a lot of things to say, so please take a look.
I apologize for the inconvenience.
Yes, this is already a big first experience.
It's a completely different size and completely different from the place.
It's the size
Yes, 7600 or 7700.
It becomes a tank that can hold about the same amount of litter.
If you compare it to a lifetime flight, it's 1000L.
It's about 5,000 pieces, one Ojakore.
There are about 5,000 lifetime flights.
Approximately 5,000,000 to 5,000 pieces
It has become something that I can crawl around on.
There are so many of them.
It's amazing, but when you come inside like this...
It felt a little chilly, didn't it?
Yes, this is what was built with that clay wall after all.
It just has a heat retention effect or something like that.
Things have become so solid
Fermentation is less affected by outside air.
This is a very good building for
I think it's true that people from the past
It's a technique created by
I think power and things like that are amazing.
I really feel that wisdom all the time.
Or rather, it's like historical wisdom.
However, there are temperatures that are comfortable for cats.
Actually, it's already winter here and the preparation is already underway.
When it starts, Eko's tank is filled with Eko.
That's how I feel every day.
I'm always tasting things like analyzing them.
Since I'm the person in charge of making sake, I'll start drinking sake in the morning.
I feel a little jealous when I see the sake
But it's work, right? It's work.
That's the science behind analysis.
I feel like I've tasted this from a different point of view.
It is said that he is being watched over by two people.
That's right, after all, that's it.
No matter how many analytical values there are, it's still the taste.
So, the sense of taste is to confirm the taste.
I wonder if there's a gap between what I'm saying and what I'm analyzing?
I decided to drink this every day.
So I wonder how much alcohol I have now?
After drinking it and actually analyzing it,
Things like adjusting the discrepancies in this way.
By the way, I am a strong drinker.
Yes.
No, it's not really. Yes, it is.
Well, I'm not drunk.
Well, I'll be here in the morning and I'll have 8 Ema tanks.
I'm going to taste all 8 of them.
It started to feel a little better towards the end.
But then I have to work again in the afternoon.
I have to have to have a little bit.
It's so difficult even though it's so fluffy.
It's a bit of fun. I can work happily.
I wonder if it's okay, but I feel kind of sick.
I guess it's okay if it's not my type
That's right, I'm already sick because I was born to that person.
If you're the type of person, it's okay.
It was difficult, but that was due to the education of those parents.
Good
Is it a gene? Yes, it's genetic.
Thank you yes thank you
This is next to the portrait gallery.
This is the sales office. In the back, there are colorful and elegant sales
This is the place.
Look for it
Uii
Ta
Here, we will drink sake made through this family.
Can I help you?
Yes, thank you very much for today's introduction.
That's right, let's eat here first.
Science Brothers Normal Version
The regular version is delicious.
So this was prepared last year.
Yes, I prepared it last winter.
It will be bottled sake.
Yeah, it's something that's on the market right now.
May I have it? Thank you.
This is the difference between this and Nabar Koyo.
First of all, the sake is polished.
Yes, and it looks like it will be used later.
I wish I had a different number, especially when it comes to hiring people with numbers.
Well, that sake has a very strong aroma.
I use a factory that is expensive and expensive.
Yes, it has a very gorgeous scent.
Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you for taking this.
Masu
Ah, the scent is so good. I drink Japanese sake in the daytime. Excuse me.
It's so delicious and beautiful.
Yes, the taste is different every year.
Yes, that's right, after all, that same rice every year.
The quality of the food has definitely changed.
Depending on the weather, etc., that year's
I can't help but taste it.
After that, it's all about that house.
While I make all kinds of things every year, this year...
I reflect on all sorts of things like ``This is how it was.''
I think it would be more interesting if Kako turned out like this.
So, let's talk about that and then this year we'll do construction.
Let's write a little bit about that.
Write about the recipe and other things like that.
Every year, we decide to try something different.
Because I am given this challenge.
There are so many changes every year.
I think that has led to an evolution in flavor.
By the way, I'm doing something like this this year
It seems like there was something like that.
As for this alcohol, it's better than ever.
Types of construction and amount of additional construction
That's a little different.
By doing so, you can
Sweetness too
While adding a little flavor,
Yeah, it's a little light in terms of alcohol.
It's true that the aftertaste is so beautiful and messed up
Easy to drink, aromatic and delicious
Thank you and next time
Yes, that seems like it
Well then, let's skip to the middle and this one.
God night, autumn is coming, this is the person's house.
It's a local brand from Monogama Uchinoe.
Well, this is what I'm talking about.
Speaking of people, this is the Echigo Takada group.
The official who keeps the Etobi of Iuehan lives here.
There's a thing called Hitoya right behind our storehouse.
Oh, is that so? Let's go from there.
It is said that sake making in Ariga Kamimichi began.
It is called Kamiya after that name.
By name, Arigazi-san's first rice is
It seems that it is a person's shop, so it is said that it is already the origin.
Yes, that's the name. Yeah, that's right.
Yes, it's very tasty too.
But this is a light type.
Now that I'm drinking alcohol, I can't wait for autumn or summer.
It's a very mature group.
This alcoholic beverage is characterized by its mellow taste.
Thank you very much for the night
It smells even better, thank you very much
Masuun
Oh, it's completely different, it's different again, isn't it?
It's very fluffy and fruity.
Yes, it's delicious. Thank you.
It's also very easy for women to drink.
It looks like you can drink it, but actually these 2
We both used the same workshop, yes.
Is that so? What's the difference?
Is that so? It's completely different. It's completely different.
This is Masu Neri's Ema club and this time
70% The rice is not so polished.
I'm making it, but yeah yeah yeah yeah that.
It's very fragrant and soft.
The taste is also very soft.
I think that's really the difference.
Yes, but it's not something completely different.
And in the middle is this thing
Well, thank you very much for that sake place.
There are many people who think that way.
I thought so more than the small one, but yeah
Yes, that is what it is, yes, it is now.
But speaking of information image, it is actually Japanese.
Is that what it looks like?
I'm making it and I'm just saying it's crazy.
But according to the classification, it's a pure ma species.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
That's right, in the book.
Learn how to make Japanese sake that captures the essence of Eso.
The method of making Kaema sake that has been recreated
This is the type of alcohol that has evolved.
So when I opened it like this, there were bubbles.
It's going up a little bit like this.
You can see that I'm still alive in this way.
Yes, that's right. I'm still inside.
It's an alcoholic beverage that you don't often see issued.
I think so, I need some time to free up some time.
It may take a while though
By the way, there are a lot of bubbles.
It looks like this was actually just installed yesterday.
Yes, I just bottled all the alcohol yesterday.
It will become a food item.It will be freshly made.
Yes, it's just freshly made.
Please take care of this.
It was amazing Tapotapo Itadaki
Masu
I'm so angry that I'm screaming.
There is a sweet image of stiffness.
But is this sake?
If you drink it, you will feel like drinking Japanese sake.
Yes, yes, but there is a country.
Yes, it's dark here.
That's right, it's the number of alcohols after all.
Ordinary sake is 15 degrees or so.
But my Makori is 9%.
Easy to drink, low air
Yes, yes, yes, those who like drinking
I can enjoy the throat very much.
I'm drinking about as much alcohol as I can.
This is not the case.
It's dangerous, but it's also very scary.
That sweet guy is like this
There's an image that I don't like.
However, this is also true for men
Looks like it's going to go crazy.
I can drink it.
After all, it's like Yakiniku, with that oil.
A little sweet sauce or something like that
It goes really well with food, so you can really enjoy it outside.
A little barbeque or something?
Now it's time to actually have Yakiniku at home.
Let's have fun together like this at times like this.
It's a product that I want, yes, no, no, it's a new flavor.
It was my first time drinking it.
Thank you for the sake of Tako Thank you
That's why I finished it.
I ended up including the alcoholic drinks too.
Thank you very much.
Thank you. Yes.
Thank you for visiting us today.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Here's a little interview
I would appreciate it if you could let me do that.
If you look at the image from here, it's fine.
The image of that Sakakura-san who is a new believer
There is, however, Japanese sake was made.
Was it first started by your brothers?
Well, that's right, it's called Japan.
Because it was a popular Ekura that was completely reborn in the early morning.
Yes, I prefer sake instead.
Especially things like Junjun City and things like that.
There wasn't much alcohol available.
It was dark, so wait a little longer.
When my brother and I returned to Emma Sakakura,
After all, local sake is not like that.
Let's talk about what's going on
Oh, I can hear people say it's delicious.
Let's make local sake like this!
That's why I started writing.
Hey, let's make that sake.
It's like the trigger that started it all.
I wonder if there is. Well, it's like this after all.
Local restaurants and liquor stores
We don't really care about our own brand.
There's no such thing, even though I'm the only one
Don't leave it at the liquor store too much.
There are a lot of things that I haven't received.
Well, that's a bit frustrating.
In fact, even Koma ourselves
That's how you make delicious alcohol.
I really want to aim for a place where
That's what I thought, so I started Fukushima Prefecture.
I also felt like I should try my best.
Is that so? Yes, that's right.
Ema, my brother and I also remember the earthquake.
I'm coming back to Sakakura because of something.
Yes, yes, yes, that's right.
That's why I say that.
Based on that, I think that Fukushima Prefecture's
After all, there is a lot of reputational damage.
Yes, there were farmers like that.
There are so many delicious things, but I can't sell them.
I think there was probably a lot of pain like that.
But yeah, I'm with those people.
Thanks to all this hard work, Fukushima is delicious.
This is how I want everyone to know about things.
It sounded like I wanted it
There were so many of those feelings.
Thank you very much.
I was particular about it, or I had that feeling.
I feel like this is because of Kamako's worth.
Please let me know if you have any questions.
What does it mean to make sake?
After all, what's with such a long history?
I'm coming with Tee.
Yeah, how can it last this long?
After all, it comes from everyday life.
When I think about it, it's like this every year.
I wonder if this is what people do.
I feel like I grow rice fields every year.
If you don't, you'll end up spending a lot of money.
It's because of the human activity that we're in now.
I think it's a slope that continues, so I said that.
Local culture, food habits, and so on.
The person who is closely involved in this part is Masakakura.
I guess that's what I'm talking about.
I will continue to protect myself from now on.
We're the ones who have to go.
I think that's the mission of
This is how the fields are managed.
I would like to talk to the people who make Manori.
Are you sure about that contract?
Farmers create the scent of their dreams.
I received it because I had already returned from the earthquake disaster.
We've been together for over 10 years since I came here.
It's going to be that series for a long time.
In other words, it's like we're working hard together through these bonds.
Well, yes, the topic is a little different.
However, I really like books, so I majored in science.
I would like to collaborate with my brother.
I was so happy when I heard the story.
Thank you very much.
What led you to collaborate?
What does this character look like as Morizo?
It was Tansu
That's right, Koyo Shirai is also great.
Kou is now called a science-oriented character.
By the way, there are parts that I really sympathize with.
Yes, among them,
Japan and Kouma are a little different now.
It may have come, but after all
Whether it's history, sex, or even alcohol,
As for the person, I have to say this.
The number of drinkers is decreasing. Yes, yes.
That's right, that's right, that's right
I felt more like boob.
But I like it, so yeah, a little bit.
That's right, that's right.
I really hope they drink it in Japan.
The people who are suffering are suffering from pain.
I want to increase this even more.
Well, yes, yes, yes, partly because of the place.
Well, we are also science brothers, and we also have a brand.
Make it, it's a collaboration
I am allowed to do it in the form of
I'd like to say it more casually, or really like this.
It's not a matter of preference or anything like that.
Yeah yeah, it's more light like this Japan
Even if I drink it, it's usually that place.
Yes, I think about it every time.
Let's collaborate like this wherever we go
It's more like I'm going to get it.
Our own sake is even better.
Connect with a wide variety of people
I thought it might be a chance, so I decided to do it.
I would like to collaborate with you
I think so, thank you for the opportunity
I'd like to hear from Mr. Cland.
Was that the case? Yes, at that time
Did you know about vtubers?
I'm sorry, but to be honest, it's like that every day.
I'm busy, but I'm still working on rice.
I also looked at YouTube itself.
No, I've already watched YouTube
I mean, I just show it to my kids.
It's only a feeling, yes, yes, no.
Well, at first I was like, "What is this?"
Takane, yeah, what is a vtuber?
Maybe he's not a YouTuber?
It seems like it all started from that point.
Isn't it V virtual?
Well, I guess you had the courage.
I don't think so, but it is.
I think I'll change it to that anime.
I also like games and Dragon Quest.
That's right, that's a bit
That's great. Yes, anime games are
I already like it, so I'll put it in that kind of place.
Unchanged prejudice or something like that
Kuununununun new content and
And then it continues to develop like this.
That's right, Vtuber and Noe.
Let me collaborate with Tokoro.
On the contrary, I felt grateful.
I'm happy, thank you, just one thing
Finally, take a look at that white broadcast.
Have you ever become a science major?
At the time of the brother's collaboration
Yes, I was secretly watching that.
Thank you very much.
Did you find anything strange? No, no.
It's just amazing, it's really that popular.
No, no, no, yes, if you realize that already
It's like it's not there anymore.
I thought it was really amazing.
Thank you very much
The number employment is really delicious.
Since you gave me this, I will do it every year from now on.
I want to drink it.Thank you for your continued support.
Please yes thank you
Thank you very much
Thank you very much for today, Masuhaga-san.
Thank you very much.
By the way, Arikawa portrait will be released next year.
It seems like it's a memorable land.
The Aliga statue commemorates the 100th anniversary of the company's establishment.
We are celebrating 250 years since we started making sake.
Our ancestors have always lived around here.
It's a drink enjoyed by the people who drink it.
After 250 years of continued service,
We have been making sake here for over 100 years.
What can we do to help them?
I will continue to make sake from now on.
I think so, and next year will be a memorable year.
Memorial statues and various
It is true that we are planning to hold an event.
Yes, please come visit us later in Shirakawa.
and
I'm so happy that you all come to visit Shirakawa!
After that, I wish I could drink and go.
I'm really looking forward to the Millennium.
I've already put together a plan.
I'm really looking forward to it today.
Thank you very much for your busy work.
Thank you very much. From now on too.
We look forward to making delicious sake.
Thank you very much. Yes, I will analyze it thoroughly.
I'll try my best. Thank you.
Thank you very much
Thank you very much for letting me sign your autograph.
Please visit if you like.
Hey, here's an important announcement.
What a science brother number Koyo is this January
We will stop eco from 17:00 on Friday the 5th.1
Cland is available only until Wednesday 31st of the month.
We have decided to resell it at
Yes, that's fine. I've had a lot of requests for resale.
It will be resold. This is it.
It's only for a limited time, but the quantity is limited.
It will end as soon as the limit runs out.
When I think about it, last time it was like 5 minutes.
Since the alcohol is sold out, here it is 1
Friday the 5th of the month at 5pm I want to drink that.
If you are interested, please check it out.
I'm so happy, I'm adding links to the summary section now.
Please check it out.
hand
Please, it was really delicious.
I also got to see that hand this time.
I learned a lot.
I was really nervous but it was hilarious
Find that slime other than that one.
I couldn't find any other places
That's why I wanted to do it.
Thank you very much, Mr. Zizo.
Have a drink and say hello to the Chikara Brothers Nabakoyo.
Please
So after this, life starts from 11pm.
Let's play a game, wait a minute
[music]
I was experimenting with Neyo and Hatag.
Okoyo is Zuno, no is it?
Sketchle yes yes yes yes yes yes
Yes, I feel like a researcher, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, green, yes, yes, one name for the inn.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, I'll say it.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, it looks like it.
Yes, yes, yes, make good games, yes, yes.
Yes okay
It was a long time ago
Mayonnaise is a drink, by the way.
It's air. Today, frozen udon at the entrance is always available.
What do you think? Lighting completed 9
Ide, yes, yes, yes, yes, [ __ ], [ __ ].
Yes, yes, yes, I'm here.
I can make it, yes, yes, yes, is it okay?
Yes, yes, yes I'm not going, yes, yes, yes
Yes, yes, hold
The ship's program is
Yes yes yes yes
The mayonnaise I made just in time is a drink
By the way, this is the air. Hello.
I hear you are preparing frozen udon noodles?
Yay, I'm here. I'm here.
Yes, yes, this is what I did during the experiment.
Is this a good day? Yes, I did
Koyori Sketchren is here.
Yes, yes, research-like chiki, yes, yes.
Yes no Tiki or Yes Yes Yes Yes Oyori no Yado
Hun name yes yes yes yes terrorism yes
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, no.
Look, it's so cute!
Yes, yes, yes, okay.
The mayonnaise that Maria made is a thing.
By the way, it's air. Yes, hello.
Frozen udon noodles are so hot.
Completed 9 Ide Yes Yes Yes Yes Cook
I did the [ __ ], yes, yes, I did it.
I can make a coby. Yes, yes, yes, okay.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hmm, yes, yes, yes, I have it.
Yes, yes, yes, fluffy
The program seems to be running.Yes yes yes yes
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yay Maria, mayonnaise is a drink.
By the way, I'm Air. Yes, Onisa Battle or Frozen.
Is it true that the udon noodles are delicious?
here
Yes, it's from the side.
I was experimenting with the hashtag Koyori.
It's Zuno. Zuno is doing something.
Sketch Ren Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes
Yes, I feel like a researcher, yes, yes, yes.
Feeling of green, yes, yes, yes, Oyori no Yado One
Name yes yes yes yes help yes yes
Yes yes yes compini yes yes yes method
Why can't I see it? Yes, yes, yes, guess what?
Yes, yes, yes, okay.
Mayonnaise made in time is a drink
By the way, the edges are air, yes, brother.
Do you have convertible frozen udon on hand?
Done lighting done Q yes yes yes [ __ ]
Yes, I was a cook.
Yes, I can make kofu. Yes, yes, yes.
Is it okay?
I don't burn it
hey
Chiku's program baldness
[music]
yes
late at night
vinegar
It's Puff Puff, so I'm on 24th for the first time for 4 hours.
Time has passed, thank you everyone
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you to everyone who gathered at this late hour.
Thank you very much
Please enter from here.
What do you think?
Everyone is always awake at this time.
Because it's late at night
Don't pick up all the polka bullets, just a polka
It's a dropped bullet. Are you going to pick it up?
It's a ball, I'll pick it all up.
Please listen to me.I said yes.
Right now, I hear the sound of the switch.
It is, but that is
I'm going to go straight.
I went there, I'm here now.
It's good, it's good, it's gone for a moment
I'm sorry, but I said yes.
I'll fix this audio.
Chama, please introduce yourself.Yes.
Hachimachima Worldwide's best idol is
This is Chimoko Red Grouper. Thank you.
Happy new year this year too
Thank you very much.
Well then, senior, I'm munching on my porridge.
I heard something like, ``My stomach is covered.''
It's the first time we've all had call and
For the first time, it was not a response but a overlap.
But it's a place for responses, idols.
That's where the response is, so yeah.
Everyone Momo
Delicious
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
Kororo Haiji Polpol Haiyo Live Show
It's a potty polka.
I wanted to give it back, but I couldn't.
Tana
That's how it starts, so it's cool.
I wonder if you guys should go too.
It's Orukaoro. Do it, you guys.
Let me hear your cheerful voice
Thank you for giving it to me. I'll do it again today.
Happy new year
Happy New Year! This is a great corner.
Neko to Tomorrow Late Night Sugo 6 Nesunoko
Sunanote
Thank you for your understanding.
Thank you very much.
I feel like it's New Year's day here and here.
I don't want to play like this for a while.
No, I'm definitely feeling better, not just a little bit more.
I want everyone to understand.
Hey, I'd like to hang out with you guys for a bit.
I was allowed to call you.
Well then, I'm in Issei mode.
I want to relax and have some fun
Masukari Ichi
Thank you for matching the color of Nayoshiko's frame.
Yes, the red looks a bit sleepy, so I guess so.
Let me turn it into a bit of pol por orange
I can't take it, it's impossible.
That's what I want to do here.
I think it feels good, it feels good.
Is that the A button?
Okay, I just looked at it and didn't choose it.
There are so many different types.
Chanesoukochanma again for today
I haven't made anything like Neo on my collaboration trip.
I didn't even do it for a while, so why did I cover it?
Why do you wear that? Why do you wear that?
thing
Yes, why do you wear it?
be
lol Prempolepole hasn't changed either.
So is that it? No, it's just this.
I see that you are trying to become a distributor.
I don't think he's a streamer by the looks of it, right?
It makes me want to do something I haven't done before.
It's a game of life, it's true, it's true
I want to be a chef.
The beginning of learning to cook
It's the beginning, I hate making promises.
I'm motivated to switch something up
My senior is pushing me
My teacher said that the person with the most wins.
There are only strange people, but somehow
amazing
It's dark. It's a bit dark without children.
Pol Pol
It's not just books, it's hair.
No Lupe
This is the first book with more meshes.
This is the era
Chan-chan starts with some kind of Noh
dashi
I have decided on things like Chan-chan cards in the future.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It seems like everyone is really into this.
It's the third time, seriously, Haa-chan hasn't done it yet.
It's also my third time, how long have you been doing?
I've done it twice on Masuka streaming, but it's not streaming.
It's amazing how much I messed up by myself.
It looks amazing. It's amazing. I'm streaming alone.
Let's do it.
Let's run side by side. You've done a good job Pol. There's already 4 or 5.
You're doing a lot, you're doing a lot.
Don't do it, you're making a scary face ...
He's looking at Teruari with those eyes.
That's right, I'm staring at you.
That's what it's like
Isn't that nice? You're getting smarter!
I certainly don't need these 20 cards.
That's right, Pom Pom Pom, that's right.
I've already decided what to do, so yeah
I'm good, good, good, this is bad.
Jansen whole card is amazing
Is it a sense? No, I'm jealous.
I had a great sense of humor.
It's amazing, it's full of rares. It's full of rares.
Leo leo jan le, it looks like my stamina is increasing
No, no, it's still a baby
That kind of thing
It's already decided
Totally super lucky
Experience a politician
Even though I was a baby from a young age, I had political experience.
However, academic ability does not improve dramatically.
After all, it has to stop at rare luck.
That card too
a
Lost it in the New Year's Game of Life
Wow, this is what happened when I was a baby.
Raki doesn't hurt that much
Oh no, yes, yes
The race is going up, it's going up, it's going up
It's okay to go, we'll be left behind.
Kanene also said level 2.
It's so good, stop it, doctor.
Sanda, the doctor is good, and the doctor isn't bad either.
I don't have a doctor who is universally popular.
I feel like Iosamo was having a hard time.
It's not hard, so everyone, open up.
Do your best, go there, ah, but just barely
Safe barely safe
Yeah, yeah, it's great, but it's average.
They're all going up by the same amount, wait, that's me.
I got something like a whole 20 ma.
[music]
I don't have that card. It keeps growing until I become an adult.
It's okay because it's like that. Without that, it would be the other way around.
Other than Erekana, which I think is dangerous.
Did you get it from school?
Maybe it's over, porporaaaaaaaaaaaa
It's amazing, it's amazing, everything, everything.
Good luck today, my luck this year is amazing
It seems like something is going to happen, so maybe I'll try my luck today.
Is it a game?
Alice's New Year's Nene 2024 is possible
Possible
Yako, it's become an important battle.
Yo
Okay
keep it up
Too much haste
It's okay, elementary school students are red, elementary school students are already that.
I put it on my mouth
Let me hang it, let it go, let it go, let it go
Looks like she's wearing makeup using Tesouno's cosmetics or something.
Wait, that's it. I'll get 5 million yen.
That guy, 5 million yen is good. Pi's voice is also correct.
It looks like it can be mixed with makeup.
I was trying to figure out which one would be better than that one.
I don't have to decide, that's pretty much it
It's a little easy to understand
I wonder if I'll get a card. It's cold right now.
Everyone has a sense of taste and a sense of what they want.
Wow, this is turning into a crazy battle of tastes.
There is a battle to see who can hone their sense the best.
Seriously, Kakoya-chan and I are the same.
Add this too
What is this battle in the same place?
I wonder if it will start, I wonder if it will start with each other
This is how we raise each other up
Thank you very much
Masu Bar is only for adults.
Tarane is amazing. I'm also VRA.
VR is aimed at becoming an actor who is starting to wake up.
I can only live with Virgil now
It's big, nice
Kiria and 2 turns worth 5,000,000.
Five million yen in pocket money is really crazy
That's crazy. I got a pattern for that.
Mon a shika moa
No, it's here, it's here
I can't eat anymore, I can't eat anymore
I told everyone that it wasn't there.
I was wondering what you were saying, cute.
I guess I remembered it. I heard it. I can eat it now.
do not have
What's this quiz rally? Let's solve it.
What a treasure
Strongest, Strongest
This is better than the first one, I love it so much
enviable
[music]
I really want it. It's Seth after all.
But
It's a department store, right?
That's the way I know
This is Seth, legal, yes, totally unrelated.
No, but it's Mio-chan's fortune telling.
Apparently my luck is bad this year, so it's not luck.
I see that you are trying to go with a strategy.
Hey, I'm from strategy.
I'm being praised, but I'm being praised.
hey
Now
I'm thankful that I'm thinking about what I'm doing.
Lots of things, pretty good sense
So how should I respond with my sense?
I'm screaming in a voice I don't understand. I'm saying everything.
Ah, I see. But I talked about being a doctor.
Karaun stamina is amazing Aa de Nano Maru strategy
I was told it was a worse year than Kako.
[music]
That's right, it's from a cat.
I understand it now too.
That's how it's always been.
That's it, head was there.
Two people are possessed by this suspicious thing.
A beautiful woman came here because she was feeling a little scared.
If you do that, you'll have big words and Mio too.
You're so bad you're lucky
I can't even say that if I did that.
Ah, it feels like cutting it open, right?
I see. Thank you for pushing me.
Isn't it amazing that it's true?
It's kind of difficult, I'm sure it's just love.
I just loved you, but it's true
I feel like you're talking about the effect of the card.
That's true too. If you get that card,
Card Saasoka also does this.
Yes, this one is for Ako too, and it's already long.
It's amazing, I'm lucky, it's amazing
It looks like it's going to be funny. Tarot every week over there.
I've been looking up the meanings of the cards, so second senpai.
Look at the cards I put out, they look so good
I don't think so
I was sad to see that.
It doesn't matter if it's academic, just grasp it.
After all, it's definitely a word that has various meanings.
Nesoumio-senpai, even if it's a bad card,
But if I do it this way, it seems okay.
You can give me some advice, right?
Why don't you just say items?
This week is chorizo chorizo.
Chorizo Chorizo is great, what should I do?
I wonder if culture is a cancer when it comes to taste.
Yeah
Everyone in the literary arts club joins the cultural club.
Today is going to be a battle of sense, I'm sure it's going well.
That's right, what can you become if you have good sense?
No, it's not true.
There may also be idols with physical strength included.
But I'm sure my physical strength is pretty good, so what?
What is it going to be like?
The one with the most money
It's an easy strategy to laugh at. It's a good strategy.
sense sense sense
I'll feed you, I'll feed you, my sense is just my sense
No, the chefs are always at the same level.
I don't spin the roulette when it's up.
It's like spinning the roulette only at the very end.
Yes, but I'm a big fan of life games.
I thought you looked like Mercury.
You can make a lot of money being a chef
I'm sure it's true, but it's true, Saki-san.
I wonder if it was a fee, yes, yes, that's good, on the contrary.
Contrary to what I think everyone knows so far,
It's funny, he's not really black.
On the contrary, it turns out to be a dish.
It's real to marry a nice person and have children.
I'm watching real life
This is Haya-chan Haya
Dakoneha-chan, red heart-san
Na
Today, it's totally fine, I saw it as a strategy at all.
It's so red that it looks like it's going to a lost school.
I went to a cram school and had bad luck.
Let's go
from
This person who is really doing it has great luck and academic ability.
Because it's a scene right now, it's dangerous, it's dangerous.
When I went to cram school, I was letting go too.When I went here, it was too extreme.
Become the kind of person who would like to receive this card.
It's really bad, it's really bad today.
I didn't know that you were late at night.
I'm really worried.Oh, I'm reading this.
Tokooka nao amazing se is also thinking about distribution.
I'm sure you'll be streaming a bit soon.
I think we need to think about distribution.
Thank you for your consideration. Thank you.
There is
Thank you so much, Neko-senpai.
No matter what game you play, it's like that.
It's better to improve a few points than to break through one point.
Yes, because the range of occupations is expanding, so it is wide-ranging.
I guess they're trying to expand the possibilities.
It's possible that it's possible, and Kukoyo-chan is also
He's rich and the god of clothes is at work these days.
However, this 5 million is good.
5 million yen is just barely in danger.
It's just a small amount in the end, isn't it?
Don't say it, you can win with 55 million, can't you win?
It's decided, it's big. The one who had money from the beginning.
I'm sure it's good money, right?
It's a nice D to have, it's amazing
I might have caught up with my senior
I don't really know what you have.
Catch the beetle that won't move forward and bring it to my neighbor.
If you don't give it to me, I'll give it to Nene.
I want it
No, wait, it's a card.
Is that that card?
That's right, the treasure was great, Tom.
no la
and 5th name
Kayoshasama is also big, big, big, but
passing by
It was cold. What's this elementary school recruitment? This is a challenge.
Let's try it.Challenge.Challenge is important in everything.
Okay, I've been saying nice things since the new year.
If I didn't wait and adjust, the price would have gone up.
Have you ever gone up?
Hami of club activities Hami of club activities
I think it's a club activity.
Let's get together and have a baby
I'm so excited. You're really lucky.
The ambassador is in trouble.
Runda
[applause]
Etei
It's too bad and I'm going to use up all of this year's money.
So I better stop it, it's dangerous, I'll stop
It's better to stop, it's better to stop
Stop, stop, Shi is also riding, stop!
Stop, stop, stop, you're a dangerous adult.
There's a possibility that it'll slip away, right? I'll wait.
What's the treasure? Treasure hunting. Is this a treasure friend? That's different.
It wasn't there, I gave it to you.
I wanted the treasure, but I got the card.
Luffy
It's already an asset, so the asset money chapter is amazing.
Somewhat
I'll get the money, wait!
He has so many cards, he should be the god of clothes.
Oh no
Is that why you're saying you might have thrown it away?
God ha, this is 12 even if it's something like that.
No trespassing. Leave. Stop that.
Maybe I should try my luck
Okay, let's just leave it like this.
Kagin said it was amazing.
Please
I thought I would never be able to get a target
amazing
Text translation of an email from Suonada's family
What kind of automatic translation dictionary do you have?
It's automatic translation
There's no point in automatically translating this.
I'm watching it as it goes up.
It's funny how you feel, but after all, it's wise.
What the hell is that?
I wonder if the silver dais with the silver polka and the silver elephant
Is that so? Or is it because there was no shi?
There's some kind of special prize, isn't it?
Oh, it's the last one, I don't know.
It's random, I guess.
Seriously, there are a lot of pros in the game of life.
Bringing in too much information
I can't help but worry about the content.
is
I did my best to get to the top 4 and my physical strength was D.
Please be popular, I wish you good health.
I need to pray for good health
Oh, I have to get married. Oh, that's true.
But even if you don't have it, as long as one person comes
Yes, you can get married if you have a guaranteed star.
It will be 100% soon
It's really this guy
A wonderful way to meet your future partner
This is your chance, everyone.
The partner I meet here is still a star
Oh, my life is so new!
There are no new and unusual Kirari.
There's no glitter or that pink hair.
There's no pink hair or blonde hair either.
Don't know the details, wait, isn't this life?
I thought they were always together.
The guy is wearing glasses and a cap.
I don't see anyone who seems serious.I'm a liberal arts student.
There wasn't anything like that.I remember the name.
Everyone is amazing, I can't remember what's going on with everyone.
Well, I feel like this girl was 4 stars.
I don't know this girl, so I give her 4 stars.
It's random, just like the stars. Sometimes they're a little different.
I want you to catch a glimpse of me, Chokoko.
It was the first time I met her, so she looked like Princess Chokaguya.
I'm going there. I wonder if she was a fragrant girl.
It was Karuko, thats amazing
Is it a star?
Yo
No, the ones here are probably 1 or 2.
Probably something like that Eri or Hoshi-san.
I feel like there's a girl on the bottom left.
I think the stars are probably strong, I guess so.
I can't have a heart, what's going on in high school?
Even if you reach the heart max, it's a date card.
I can't get it, right?
The life I want to quit
There is a possibility that the distribution is dangerous and the strategy distribution is bad.
teacher
Game Real Game Strategy Good Graphics
Let's develop our senses right away
You're doing it right, it's great, it's great!
Wow, I'm going to be S soon.
So, it's fast, it's fast, my physical strength has increased, sense
Hello Culture Department
Hello Saaaashi 5 stars 4 stars or 5 stars
It's not even like the one that smells like that.
At this point, this child has become a chef.
Yes, this child knows that
That
Research destinations outlook on life
You're all out of place on the stars.
Girls, girls, stars, everyone.
You'll see it no matter what.
star
I'm going to do it in Sumerunaka, which focuses on powerful stars.
There are so many 1's today, it's amazing part time job life
Saver, I don't have any stamina, I don't have any stamina, but I have life
Can you protect people? Please protect me a little.
You can go, you're going now.
I'm still going, I'm an unbeliever, even if I get help
Chai
Is that okay?
I got some help, but who is the truth? What is this?
I want this person like who is this?
Dede but probably to someone after these four people
not get married
People who were empty don't get married that often.
yonaun yun erisan nee star
[applause]
Egacha
Delivery, this is gacha delivery, right?
Thanks to the fighting, Eri Hoshitake is 4 stars, so stop it.
Don't eat it, right? Just take it away.
Well, I found it first too.
It's okay, I won't take it away
I dream of taking this away from you 2 and 3
Something happened because I became the next
Something happened in front of the candy store. Something happened.
Tanero: Something strange happened.
I fell into a terrible depression
Mominaa and others are gone.
Now, everyone is cooking and cooking quickly.
I'm sorry about that.
I have more things that I can exchange.
Because I have it, because I have this and that.
I won't forgive you for 224 years, so it's dangerous.
36 Acha Uso
Well, if you study a little, you won't be happy.
That's great, I'm sure you have a CD.
I started using cards like this and this one.
It's scary, I forgot when I used it.
That's right, after all, I use it when I use it.
I feel like it's a waste, but how to use it
That's good, don't forget to get the card right away.
It's going to be full, so I have to throw it away.
Are you saying you can't do that?
It's like a disease where you save up recovery medicine.
feela elixir food
group
I guess FF has a proper name.
I feel like that's where it came from. Oh yeah, that's right.
You're so nice, the conversation isn't that great.
Heart, you can meet someone
inside
Cute
It's a good thing that you gave me some sense.
Let's become a 1-star Yabako-chan account.
Isn't it cool? Just have a little fun
I'm a little tired of it happening, but
This is the game of life, and here's the surefire way to win.
That's right, get married early and have children soon.
What is that? That little star child is that.
The worst thing is that you may not have enough money to give me.
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, I feel like saying something dangerous
Even my practice was short-lived, so I got 3 stars the other day.
So everyone else is 4 stars, yeah everyone is like
About 40 million, Ha-chan too.
It was about 20 million yen. Oh, it looks like a child.
The one with a bigger star will become a genius or have a good job.
It is easy for children to have a lot of money to send back.
Awakening Genetic Awakening Awakening Genetic Grandpa
There may be awakenings, but there are times when that happens.
Maybe you'll suddenly become a genius.
You might even become a genius at an event.
Yeah yeah yeah I like 5 I like it 5 I don't like it
Is it?
I started playing seriously
Something came near me
Isn't it 1 star in Nede?
Ah, maybe I can marry Kira.
Ah, it's an idol, an idol, an idol.
I wonder if it's the broadcaster or what?
I guess Kirari is
What the hell are we already talking about Kirari?
I've decided, but what's the point?
It's so bad, it's so scary
Too bad Aha-chan isn't going up either.
Do you have any knowledge?
There are so many, so why?
I should have come up with a good strategy, Aone Adult.
Well, that girl who came to my heart again
That's it, that's what it's like to be a day.
I'm sure he's a baseball player.
Yo
It's too late to do NTR
Mandao, the taste of NTR is delicious.
That's why NTR is fun.
There's a new way to enjoy the game of life in the new year.
From the first shot, the god of clothes has disappeared.
Oh, you saved 56 million, that's great.
I can wait
Even if it's big, I won't take it easy, I'll do it normally.
Wow wow that's a great lucky sebo heart
Taa Heartmas stars 4 stars 4 I'm jealous of this girl
It was a star 4 stars
Oblique
A few stars are getting married soon.
I thought it was good from the beginning
You're sweating. There were so many people.
Did you come here? Is it the culprit's teacher?
I think I've had a teacher until now.
It seems like it will only come when you realize it and make a choice.
I want to get to work right away, so I go to work.
Spear
I wonder if I can become a professional who doesn't use force.
If that's the case, I think everyone will be able to get a job normally this time.
It's quite expensive, Minaka-chan too.
Noisy
I'll give it my all at first
Ura yoshaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
I'm sure you're small and have no sense.
I could really use your advice once.
It's all over. I can still use it, but it's over.
It was written all the way back to when I was in high school, but now
Eh, 7% get a job. Oh wow, what are you all doing?
Shall we do it?
I wonder what I should do with this life I have no choice but to live for the fifth time
About
Life is definitely going to be a live game this time.
That's because it's the first time in 2024.
Sofufuchi can also go, sure, chidore
It's a little suspicious because the enemy says which one.
morning
Thank you for being such a kind person.
I might do some NTR, so just a little bit.
Sell it?
If I don't, I'll say it out loud, trying to raise it and lower it.
Tenna
Yoewo Shopping Center
protect the shopping center
Oh wow, it's here, it's here, it's here, suddenly that gold
Revitalize shopping centers that are no longer open.
It's fun to get paid for that, for sure.
It's amazing, it's been revived more than I imagined, and it won't wither.
Well, everyone got a job, right?
I guess I should go to work. You're the one who likes work.
I wonder if there is
What happens when you take an entrance exam and become a university student?
It seems like alloys can be made, yes, yes.
Certainly certainly only high school universities
I'm going to get a job.
Ah, what do you think about buying it here?
Suruma Panpan is a product.
Incense pon pon pon is amazing. I can afford it.
Ah, I want to give this a little boost.
Yo
I'm jealous, I didn't wash it and choose it.
But you can't see it
Please help me by taking the exam.
Please hold a group date.I want you to hold a joint party here.
I'm sorry for praising you and asking you to open your mouth.
In addition
It's true that my childhood is over and I'll move on from here.
The age of adults and adults, Okochakoyo
I don't want to wait for Chana
Aka who hasn't been able to do it and hasn't done it on his own
It's just 100%, so come on
I'm waiting for you to say that, wait.
No, I can't wait. I don't even remember my name anymore.
I'm waiting for you here
I'm waiting, what will I become?
Yeah, you have a great sense of wondering what's going to happen.
The chef needs sense D, yeah yeah oyocha
the cook cannot
He's looking for food, so I'll take him as a chef.
I wonder why it's all about sleeping, cooking, and sleeping.
No matter what, no matter what, it's crazy sense D
It was warm, it was warm, it was the last time.
Well, I guess I should become a manga artist.
Yeah, I think it would have been better if it had been made into an anime.
Yeah, I think I'll draw a one piece.
Wow, that's a plagiarism
I want to have peace, I want to have peace.
Masukoyo Peace from Neto Connector
You're a great woman who's already finished reading.
do not have
I'm not going, so I'm more than a cat.
Let's make peace a big hit, ladies and gentlemen, ladies and gentlemen.
I was swaying. 1 Ah, the start.
It's okay if you want to cut the dash.
sketch
This is where Zoko Peace began.
Romance from this park that started from
Now it's Seth C or something.
It seems like the choices are the same.
I feel like it's because I have a power advantage.
I can't use that power, I can't use my intellect.
Maybe it will get tougher in the future.
Isn't that amazing?
I want to do what I want to do.
I'm going to become an actor from now on.
I like Rugoze Gekidan
Sesaicho danger
[music]
I almost played the role of a Yankee.
I have to change it.
Hey, even if you roll a 5, it's still a small 2.
Even if I show my eyes, it looks normal.
I'll keep it around the number 7.
Awesome
[music]
Even if you roll a 7, you'll get a lot of progress.
What should I do? Practice loud noises.
first
This is power, power, power, power that is not in order.
Sweet
find work
It's just that this isn't there yet, I'm sure
You can do it, it's happening, Sarah.
So 123 I see, what's going on now?
Well,
3 I don't have a dog 4 I'm going 4
Kaa, I'm using a card. I have a good card.
Masune Wow, it was so good!
It won't be as bad even if it's not hazy.
How many are this and how many are that?
Lou, what's this smell? Eat that food.
I'm fine, that's the victim.
Looks like it's different
Akaru is just not that cool.
Hey, how many date cards should I change?
I was so quick to grab Riku that I was bitten by a bug.
yeah
You can't even grab it with a bag.
I really did it, what should I do? Internship study
Let's study. You just changed the way you said it. Intelligence.
That's what I thought
Studying while doing something else
I just noticed something after all.
But no, no, no, no, I want to give up my strength.
I don't like loud voices
Don't kill me, I don't want you to hate me for my beliefs.
Please polo polo
Okay, I'm going to take a picture now, so let's take a look.
Please give it to me, Pol Pol, this is all.
Somehow the two of us were getting a pass check together.
But who is Killet?
Who is that? I gave it to you earlier, so why is it like that?
Chicken Chick Chicken Red, I know this
I get it, let's keep it exciting
If you burst 12, you die.
Masu
Scary, shallow, shallow eyes, shallow, shallow, No. 1
It's a resaw device, but it's amazing. Even if you put out 6.
There's no problem, wait.
Amazing 8 Nemama If you can get 4 or more Mako
90 is a little scary but I'm with you
This is so cool, I'm going to spin it, burst.
It won't burst so it's 2V
Ah, I lost in 2v1.
Tatao Yata Ooruoko
Stop it, it's too fast, it's taking away my sense
It was sucked away, it was done.
The day you want to play 3, the day you want to play 3, the day you want to play 3.
I want to show 3's small eyes.
It's a card
Bibibi33
Do
Let it out
Fans of the amazing hot springs are calling out to us.
I've seen it
I don't need a fan card.
But I guess it's useless when I retire.
Then you can use it as a politician or an idol.
I'm going to slide something to the slide streamer.
Then I might be able to go there or that.
There's no point in it, I'm in a love where I can receive something.
tea
Are you going to decide soon, Eri?
[applause]
Or do you put 1% on it before you get cuckolded?
No, it's still too early to propose, right?
I'm going on one date with that cute girl
1 time
Even on a date, what would happen if you were taken away during that time?
I don't think so. I'm already at 28%.
But damn, I'm going to spend 3 million yen on a date.
No, let's go this way. I might get cuckolded.
It's cheap even though it's not there
Save money
I'm losing, even if I say this 2
It's just a discount, it's definitely only a 20% discount.
It's just that 1 is divided into 2.
It's cool here
Isn't that bad? Isn't that bad?
It doesn't seem that bad though.
Seth is on the rise, amazing. I see.
Ah, it seems like it's a bit like an exchange...
I don't have enough physical strength, so I don't have to worry about it.
It's the same bus again. Lucky.
Please don't come, newbies, 50 million yen.
Eh, that kind of thing
this
Battle Even though I don't want to battle anymore, I battle
This is why you're always like this
The battle is about to start and Karari is on her own.
This might be my first time shuffling
Anyone who can memorize the cards will respond.
That's right, shuff, okay then.
Okay, I'll tell you something.
Yo, that's different, that's different.
Is it good if the roulette wheel comes out big?
It's like that color
It's 10. This is okay.
Tomio, see you in the comments.
Are you looking at the comments to see if Polka is going to die?
They came at me from over there and did their thing.
What happened, what happened, what happened, what happened
I'm going to win badly because I can win.
Well then thank you Pol Pol is the worst
You got it right, I'll never see you again
I'll never watch Ako again, so I'll definitely watch Pol Pol.
So I definitely want to take a course on how to prepare for the role.
Let's take the classroom lecture.
I guess it's necessary.
You have to be smart
I'm just saying that based on your appearance.
It's funny, it's pretty serious Odayo everyone
I guess I still can't get enough of my payday.
Everyone writes that things are not progressing smoothly.
I won't upload it because it didn't happen.
I see, I guess I'll use Nekocchi.
Ah, that death zone is definitely a dangerous place.
It's amazing because I can see it, it's a card
please
Oh, I need to study. That's great. I need to study a little.
I have to do something, it's amazing, it's the best
I can't do it with too much D, what should I become?
get lost
I want to sleep, but I'm not sure
Rank up your lost rank
There's one slot open for the challenge, go ahead.
Good luck!
Don't be stubborn
Yeah, but it's really going well, Peace.
This is the number of times the series has been published.
I wonder if Romance Dawn was good.
Oh, I'm aiming for the Koyodo line, Koyodo.
line and
It sounds a little nice, but take care of your family.
A life lived with someone
Is that an actor? What about an actor?
If you don't be smart, that's why you'll be smart
death
It's no good if you keep saying this to other people's words.
I was scolded for doing that.
Now, there is a terrible control
I'm going to turn it into a cat, please help me
Yahoo hachaman's sense and sense
what
I thought that was it. It said studying.
That's amazing, isn't it?
1234 Now, A-chan is amazing!
I feel like it doesn't matter
That's amazing!
Is the strength needed right now? I need to increase my physical strength.
Even if it's not your cat, let's talk properly.
It's amazing how much you have to do that. Yes, that's right.
Because it was interesting that I wanted to give it to you.
Is it too crowded? Please open it.
First of all, let's go on a date, and this is the future of permanent dishwashing.
I can't see it, I'm waiting for you in front of me
I might even propose to you before I go to sleep 2
You can still succeed in this turn.
I went there thinking that I would never propose to you.
In that case, you can go on the road of destruction.
I can see it, so I have to do it yet.
Chamaya hiyo chama always theory
Promise
Somehow, it's a success
Maybe if it's a success, I'll get more.
Well, if you spend 3 million, you'll probably get more.
Serve me your home-cooked food there.
That's fine, but I can see it.
It's okay, it's 3rd place and 3rd place and hell is running away
It was dangerous, I had a group date that I could afford.
That's good, what should I do? D
It's okay to stay like this, isn't it?
Don't hesitate, I'll give you a B if you have great sense.
Let's stretch it that far
It was really, really, really growing.
is
If you say so
If you say it will grow, it will grow. Polka voice recognition
I guess this game doesn't exist.
Oda-do who used the Yonai Yojutsu
Let's do this. Wait a minute and let me know.
There are stars and reds
Koyomi says what did you do when she was crying?
I had an unpleasant encounter after just hanging out on the wrong side of town for a day.
I'm aiming for 5 stars because I still have a few options.
Is there a 5 star rating? There is no 5 star rating.
I wonder if
It's like a star. Is it up to 4 stars? I'm looking for an encounter.
Let's all meet because we don't go on blind dates
I want you to have a cat, Nanaoka.
Senpai, it's not opening, wait, this person
Besides, I have to do some research, mama.
A woman who is married and only true love
I'll do it anyway, but there's quite a strategy.
It's nice to see 4 people with 5 stars on the right side of the screen.
This is a comment. I'm wondering what's wrong with you?
I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy!
If the happy star cat is gone, choose a star.
It's okay too
Hey, that's not a cute reply.
I'm seriously going to play the game right now, so I'm serious.
Arekata-kun, a supporting character in the anime series
I'll play the role of running away from
I miss it so much. It would be terrible if I broke it.
You look plain like a supporting character.
It's dangerous to destroy it, it's too conspicuous, isn't it?
I was trying too hard to stand out. I'm glad I did.
Just for the supporting role that came to my mind when I first saw it.
Card properly
1223 I don't know what the role of running away from Kamata-kun is.
I don't think so, but it's amazing how people run away from places.
Apparently he asked me to do it.
Yeah, that's right, that's right, it's so close
It's just barely okay, I'm still in love
I wonder if it's not worth seeing, but I'm waiting
That's right. Isn't that enough? It's a proposal.
I have another proposal. I can't wait any longer.
Hey, it's okay, your senpai went on a date too.
Karasa-senpai, let me hear your reply.
Hey, let me hear the angel's reply. What's going on?
It's really good
ultr
The one I was trying to sleep with was Oka-senpai, but damn.
net counter
amazing
Awesome, at least it's 1, at least it's 1
Don't joke around, don't jump.
Can't you give me more?
worst
You're a student, you're in debt.
I'm a student. I've graduated. I've graduated. I've graduated.
Graduation fun was born and almost anything leaks
Awesome, amazing, it looks like a doctor and a scientist.
I wonder what it's all about, I'm also a little confused
I want to become an actor, but there is a competition between actors who have intelligence and talent.
There is also the power of having dangerous physical strength in the battle for actors that is about to begin.
There's a new guy who's moving, a new guy is here.
Amazingly large
We're newbies. We're probably from the same office. Same office work.
After all, work is important, because you are a senior.
This one is faster, so in the same moment
born
Toyabai Yabai Ehi is also not great as the main character.
It's amazing, isn't it? It's a large size, even though it's a child.
You're a newcomer. Your role in the movie is really great.
Dako's
Newbies started attacking your movie roles.
A shopping mall with small eyes
I don't think it's okay if it's passed on to children, on the contrary.
I'm sure there are people who saw this movie and said it was scary.
You're having so much fun, stop it.
I didn't think it had Go in it, thank you for your hard work.
Dekoyori na
Go Koyori's Go
5454 ah
Yeah, it's a run card or a slump card.
We have to destroy it in some way.
That's terrible, I didn't like it, it was just a joke
In high spirits
Here it is
You can also go to peace ma polka, this is probably
I wonder if I can go? It's okay. I'm done.
Masu's God of Love It's fun here, so let's go.
Even if you go and go, you are still going to New Year's visit.
I'm not going here, I'm playing conger here.
Game New Year's visit to a shrine with a game
Do you take something from the last person who drew the fortune?
There is something like that
New 111 Akonai big dechato
It's different
Let's see Yacha here Peace copy.
I came out because there were suspicions.
Is this what it was? Or did it become known? Koyodo Line
Was it bad?
It's a bit noisy, but it's still that way
Were you able to go?
Looks like there's going to be some pi
What's wrong with the octopus? It's okay.
What's up, junior, it's a little different than I imagined?
What?
The junior left a bad impression on our office.
Stop sniffing.
You were chosen to be the main character from the beginning.
It looks like it, but it's a little bit
I play VR when it's private.
It turned out to be a good thing, so I was happy.
But it's okay
I don't like it when I put a sleeping V-goal on it.
surely
It sounds like it. I guess I'll go over here a little.
I don't know who it is, but it's called a woman's woman's woman.
I said I had to go to work.
Mon, no, no, this is different, so again
I was told to stop it.
It's true, but what's up with Kiki?
I want to be with you as much as possible, so I went to the hospital.
I'm a nuisance, a nuisance, too much trouble.
Too bad
At worst, you'll be found out right away.
The scandal is real.
Tetta
Not even a lover
You're so strong!
Hey, lovey-dovey cards are good.
Wait a minute, I guess I'll fill in the SR kids for this.
Is it possible that he will come out of the wood?
It's dangerous if you can't grow.This is the best thing to do.
I want to do this, this, this,
I like it, I like this kind of thing, and it feels like it's made of wood.
This is the flow I wanted to follow.
Why don't you follow me like a stalker?
That's right, that's what it is.
Stay hehe hehe safe safe safe safe well
Well, I was just born, so it's already over.
Congratulations, I'm in debt.
I'm pretty excited. I have a little bit of debt.
This is the person I can definitely return.
I'm so sleepy, I'm not going to fall in love
do not have
Eh, why not just go ahead and do it?
If I could do it, it would be about 2 levels of mess.
I think you can do it, you must have good musical instrument skills.
It seems like it's a minute
I hope this is a success
That's a terrible age hierarchy. I'll go to the office first. Oh, nothing.
I can't hear
No, no, no, no, no, no, you're a newbie.
The stability is gone
The one who is going on a trip even though he is
Oyaba
I feel like I can't say anything lately.
The new guys that have come in are really growing.
It's actually a tobacco spa.
In real life, I still want to get married though
Marriage is tough at 18, no, no, no.
It was 30%, so I have to change it.
One little date, one date in between
Yes, yes, it's high class, but it's expensive.
Yohae Yakori is rich because he has money.
I want to do that, it's so amazing, so fast, so fast
45 is no longer good, it's enough.
Yes, even if I reach the goal
Is it good? Yes, I think it's good.
How is everyone's heart going?
The heart that everyone is rooting for can't stop
I can't stop
It's been a long time since I've been forced to have sex with Kayu
Let's talk about life together.
The second half of life is a series of choices.
Making huge mistakes is part of life.
Why are you doing a play here?
Oh, I gave it away Yeah, I gave it to you and nothing
I can't fall in love
I just went to the doctor for now.
It was even possible to prevent this kind of love from happening
It's a scandal. It's a senior agency.
I'm protecting you. I'm protecting your office.
Hey, wait a minute, what should I do?
I can't do it. I made a mistake.
No matter what, I'll change it.
Even if it's dangerous, I'll change my house. This is how it will change.
Yapa
I'm strong enough to change, but I'm also too strong.
You seriously came to work, didn't you?
It's really dangerous to live your life through work.
Okoyo-chan Po-chan is a rough character
Hey this guy
Peace treasure is a treasure, right?
It's not dangerous
The original drawings are so awesome Peace's
The original picture Okoyo-chan is also amazing, and the money is pretty dead.
Well, I'm making money, so I guess it's surprising.
No, I don't know what's going to happen from now on.
Nannachimaun
What's going to happen? What's going to happen?
Marry Me
Kure Lucky Seven Cebu Yes, that's quite true.
Hey, what's going to happen? 40% of the time here.
Ka-chan has a pretty high percentage.
I went there for 30% and couldn't go by Stommel.
It makes me laugh. Don't laugh. Don't laugh. Don't laugh.
I'll laugh at other people's rudeness. Get married.
Please, please, please, I can go.
I can go, I can go
I'm sure it's okay even if I get rejected
I wonder if there is a relief for those who were dumped.
I was rejected a lot at the end.
I'll get 300 million for it. Is that it?
And it's random so I've never seen it before.
It's okay because I hit it twice.
Well, Randa-chan can't take that anymore.
That's definitely true, that's right, that's right
It's possible, it's dangerous, senior scandal
It's okay, no, no, no, no
Taore-san is
It's okay, it's a star play scandal.
I danced with the section chief, Mr. Seven.
I'm just an ordinary woman, whether I want to cause a scandal or not.
I'm an ordinary woman. What's wrong with this?
If I let it out, it will be the end of the world.
Nene, there's nothing wrong with marriage, right?
You should get married as soon as possible, then buy a house.
It's okay to borrow money, I understand.
Yes, I can do it.Oh yes, I can do it.
Yeah, that's a strategy. I'll buy the big one later.
Yaro-chan and I will really come to fruition this year.
I see, there is a way to do that, but it's a trade-in nether.
I'm sure there are some, but even just one is fine.
I think it's true that he won't be coming back.
What should Hachi do during this time?
There are about 3 more people who are thinking about having children.
What should I do if I summon it?
I bought some crazy cards, Jim.
Maybe I didn't need a car
There are no people who buy insane guards.