[Music]
hi everybody
hi
i've been this nervous in a really long
time
hi
thank you welcome to
um it's just a normal stream welcome to
the a normal stream it's it's not
anything special um
it's just my it's not my birthday but
it's it's nearly my birthday it's kind
of it's it's kind of my birthday
[Music]
hi
um i've been losing my mind for the past
like three hours
um
[Music]
wait
double voice
what
is my mic okay
everything good okay good good okay i
was like confused for a second bruh i
underestimated how much i how much setup
was required for a birthday stream i
mean it's not my birthday but i'm just
saying like i i i i i i
um
so we've got
um a very
packed
schedule for today's stream thank you so
much for the super chat
i will read them
uh next i will thank you i appreciate i
why are you so upset i'm so upset
because i'm i just i am overwhelmed with
absolute love and
i'm so nervous
uh it's been a while it's been a while
since
there's been i don't know i feel like
[Music]
a lot of the times i just kind of
i just i just exist and i don't really
you know there's not much special um
not that there's not anything special
about me but more like
it's not that all the eyes everybody's
looking and i'm like ah i know don't
perceive me please
okay so we've got a pack schedule today
so i will briefly explain what is
happening in today's stream and then
we're going to talk about a few things
we've got 15 no we've got 18 minutes
before the first call-in start this is a
totsumachi as well um thotsumachi is a
coleman stream so i've got a lot of
friends um calling in today thank you so
much literally thank you so much
i feel so loud i feel so loud
it's not even my birthday
it's not even my birthday bruh
okay
first things first
[Music]
did you guys did you guys like um this
song
did you guys like the song
did you guys like it
they club it was a clutch the miracle
happened
it wasn't delayed i'm sorry thank you
everyone thank you management thank you
my nintend thank you everyone
thank you
it was great it was a banger
hashtag
[Music]
i'm so excited
it was amazing thank you thank you
um so i might announce it now so the
envy is out link in the description
below yo
go check it out if you haven't checked
it out um um so this is going to be
streamable
soon
it will be streaming uh available for i
don't
i do do i know what this means not
really but um basically my song will be
able to uh be streamed from uh midnight
first of march uh jst those are the
other times yes yes yes you can find it
on streaming uh platforms
can you tell i'm nervous i'm extremely
nervous i am so very nervous i'm just
gonna leave this over here
um i have so many people to thank thank
you so much i don't know what to put
i'll put it here
thank you so much um so
drew this absolutely beautiful uh
background with these assets for my
birthday so thank you very much um we've
got i saw he did the logo and i just
want i'm so i'm not ready i'm excited
i'm really excited i'm really excited
yes i need to calm down okay
um so
basically what is happening today is um
we've got to this stream which is going
to be a totsumachi with announcements
very fun announcements um and just you
know um a
standing celebration stream for um
a day that is the closest to my birthday
um and then tonight we've got a karaoke
chill
uh like after party stream um where we
count down to the really to the release
of you know the streaming uh
of play dice being a being uploaded to
streaming platforms so we've got that
tonight as well if you want to join me
that would be absolutely
amazing
yes
[Music]
smash that like button yeah
can we hit 1 billion likes i'm sorry
okay
um okay so we've got this song okay i
hope you guys like it i hope you guys
liked it i worked really well everybody
worked really really hard on it um the
song has been in
the works for
about oh
i think
like four months
was it four months
i think it was four months yeah four or
five months i don't really i don't
really remember i forgot when we started
um but yeah
[Music]
um
yes that's that's yes so yes um so we're
gonna have uh
i'm not very good at this okay
physics don't play the dust baby
um i feel like the song encapsulated me
pretty well um i'm not gonna talk too
much about the song because i will have
a um like after party for the song
itself probably after my break um
eventually so stay in tune for that
where we can break down the song and
stuff like that but i just want to thank
everyone involved
rock you are amazing um
thank you for the beautiful
it's amazing
it's amazing actually it's amazing i
couldn't be happier with the song
[Music]
um now
so yes
before
we start the call-ins i want
to take a moment
and say
thank you to mikka
mama
did you guys like
the learnings oh wait wrong no no i'm
not angry i'm sad
did you guys like did you guys like the
loading screen
[Music]
to this ad because she also sent me a
letter that i wanted to read the first
present from um that i received was from
nika mama i'm so incredibly honored i
can't believe she made an animation
it's too beautiful
um actually i've been um like every time
i go on my timeline i see that mika mama
has you know like her animation like
videos and i'm like that's amazing
and that's just like i made one for you
for your birthday and i was like oh my
god i cannot believe it
um can we say it again uh sure
[Music]
come on look at this
look at this
look at that
we've got everyone in ian
drawn and animated i cannot believe this
it's absolutely god here
[Music]
she also sent me a letter that i want to
read
i'm gonna attempt to read this uh
because i
i don't know if my brain is functioning
today but i would try and read this
first in japanese and i'll try to
translate it
[Music]
thank you so much
um okay so what she said was happy
birthday um it's been about six months
since i first met bae and um um
every time i watch your streams and see
you having fun on twitter i get a lot of
energy um and i
and i feel better genki yes i i feel
better as well
um from now on there will be a lot of
fun times sometimes there'll be sad
times but i'm sure you'll be fine
um
there are a lot of people who watch your
streams uh that gain happiness
um
from all around the world so you'll be
fine i love you big tongue
thank you for everything mika mama
you
thank you so much
thank you
so much
[Music]
so sweet thank you so much thank you
thank you
um
iris's love is back bruh no
no
also um if you hear me just typing it's
because i am currently still
in
[Music]
i'm still talking to mani-chan who's
frantically trying to put things
together for me
um
[Music]
but yes
head back to monitor yes headphones to
monitor
um but yes uh first we have um
some collins from holly and friends yes
uh we still got seven minutes be good we
could be good um but thank you guys so
much i woke up to so much love um i
couldn't sleep much last night because i
was so excited
seven minutes we gotta stick to a
schedule we gotta stick to a schedule
uh what else haven't i said i feel like
i just i'm very scatterbrained at the
moment because
i don't know i is
it's been a very very very very very
very long time since i've celebrated you
know my birthday you know
so i'm not used to this not used to this
but
yes squeaky squeak squeak yes squeak
squeak squeaky squeak
ah but i guess we can talk more about
this song my gorge my my gosh um but i
just i feel like the song is just it's a
very danceable song dare i say twerkable
song
um yeah
happy not birthday thank you thank you
thank you very much
[Laughter]
hi hi hi
[Music]
have a very
merry on birthday thank you very much i
don't know how long am i turning i am
turning 12 and a half that is how old
i'm turning yes
12 and a half billion centuries
yes i've got myself some cake
i also have a custom mug
[Music]
which you can't see because this is
covering it i'll put it over here
i got a custom coffee mug
uh yes yes yes yes very cool yes and
this is the it's a souvenir mug
[Music]
it's a super souvenir yes
i'm so excited can you guys guess who
who would be calling in today
is it or is it not your birthday
yes
[Music]
everyone
yo if
hold on i need to find something um for
money
sorry
oh interesting guesses interesting
guesses
interesting guesses happy not birthday
honestly i was a bit conflicted on you
know
when i should do birthday stream
um but
uh
i wasn't really sure
um
yeah
[Music]
wait wait
give again
between the 28th and the first yeah i
don't know like but you know with time
zones and everything i was just kind of
like so do i
do i like
when does it you know switch over
is it like that weird time where like
you know all the clocks are you know
going past 12 a.m onto into the 1st of
march
[Music]
i wonder
keeping it in feb is bad yeah i feel
like yeah um
[Music]
embrace the chaos you right you right
birthday collab with a child when yeah
it's also a chance birthday
music
it's actually her birthday it's it's i'm
i i'm an imposter it's not my birthday
i'm an imposter
in my pastor
imposter sorry
it is a pasta birthday
will you give us live singing of play
dice
maybe if you join my karaoke tonight
mayhem
honestly i haven't sung that song live
in a have i ever saw that song live well
definitely practiced it but you know
that song was actually i remember the
first time i showed iris the song and
she's like i bet this is extremely
difficult to sing live and i'm like
can you imagine other hollow memes
singing her play dice i feel like
that'll be the most
like interesting like imagine crony
singing play dice
or like imagine like inna singing play
dice bra that'll be so cool
[Music]
challenge accepted
yeah but i just want to thank everyone
for
you know i just really i really
appreciate all the love and support um
[Music]
um a lot of holo mems especially like
from holland english gay so my support
for the original song build up so much
hype and i'm just so glad i just hope it
did just everyone's expectations justice
um when's it coming out on youtube music
it should be available
uh when it's
when it's available in other streaming
platforms so i think it should be after
the
midnight jst tonight
um that should i think that's how that
works i don't know how that works but
yes
it went way beyond my expectations
thank you
okay well i guess we should um
you know we've got a minute
we've got our first round of call-ins
let me just move over to the
[Music]
corner
hello so
uh we got our first batch of coins
and we wait
[Music]
um can you guys guess who's first
how do i
uh
hello
hi ris
it's iris
oh my god i have a hat on
i am infecting bae with my
iris my hope
opium
no
happy birthday thank you it's not my
birthday good thank you oh yeah happy
not birthday happy
you know what since it's not my birthday
i'm gonna give you a gift i'm gonna call
your iris senpai for the next four
minutes
all right oh yay
yay
for the next four minutes next four
minutes cherish the next four minutes
okay
yes yes
for all of the cause also i should
mention um i got i'm gonna ask you a
question the question oh yes would you
answer it send pipe oh this was so wrong
no nothing's wrong it is exactly correct
the way it should be
all right
please uh answer the following question
uh what was your first impression of me
my first impression of you
my first impression was
that you have a lot of energy
and just like
basically i still remember like um
when we first like chat basically i
think
when you just came approaching to be
like hi iris senpai
senpai
i'm so excited for your debut i'm just
like oh my gosh she's so friendly i mean
i feel like first impression now they're
still they're still like it's still kind
of the same like not not exactly the
same but i still feel that energy from
you even now like i'm not the type that
can like really approach people that um
easily so i'm just really bad at it so i
was really i even now i still admire
that part of you
and in general it's just you you're such
a hard worker like when i first saw your
daily stream i was like oh my god like
how like you know you're you made that
uh that quiz that quiz and you're so
creative
respect from your senpai you should be
proud of yourself
[Laughter]
[Music]
you're doing great you're doing great
thank you thank you very much ah
please wish me luck i'm so nervous i was
telling her i was i'm just so nervous
i've been nervous for like the past week
bruh
no your your song was amazing i love it
i heard it before i heard it before
because you know yes privileges but like
um
but you know yeah you guys you guys are
very lucky right okay you guys better
stream it you guys
yeah go play dice maybe you can play
some days with them on monopoly or does
monopoly have dice i don't know
yeah it does do that yeah
oh yeah
you can call it monopoly now oh my god
oh my god first song play dice second
song
oh my god we should do it but we should
we could do it that'll come monopoly
he's a
here's a coupon
oh
my god everybody
oh my god
wait let me get it up oh my god
free disneyland ticket it comes with a
churro you better come dammit give
people only redeemable if nephilim comes
with you to the magical land
yeah you can't go on
oh my god yeah what a deal this is going
you can come to disneyland with oh no
gears kneel out with me from youtube
oh my god thank you
so much i'm going to put this right here
i look forward to it we're going to have
it yeah
yeah i can't wait for the day that you
can come here yeah to virtual japan yeah
happy birthday thank you
have a great rest of the day thank you
i will i will yes
all righty then i will now yes go
for the next person yes
yeah oh can you call me senpai one more
time
[Music]
that was iris okay we gotta keep zooming
we gotta keep zooming next person hello
hello
[Music]
thank you
how are you are you good you're doing
good
i'm
doing good i'm wondering uh you see this
hat where's my limiter
it's under the hat
okay
it's resting perfectly on your limiter
don't worry about it
so i i can't move yeah don't worry about
it
okay okay i'll be very very very careful
yes be very very still i want to thank
you for the beautiful cake guys oh yes i
sent i sent that a cake
it was so nice you know oh my god can i
tell you the most most face palm moment
of my entire life so um sana sent me a
beautiful it's like uh it was like a
cheesecakes uh cheesecake slash pudding
thing right
and there were
there were clear instructions in the box
that tells you how to eat it you know
you're meant to like flip it over and
you get this all over oh no
there were clear instructions and then
because i i put i got it i received it
and i put it in the fridge and then mama
rat was like oh my god what is that and
i'm like my friend sent it to me and she
was like oh my god next morning i open
it and there's literally just a spoonful
missing and i'm like
yeah what are you doing and
how am i supposed to eat i'm like mom
there's clear instructions on how to eat
it mom
yeah
so unfortunately we we're we haven't
been eating it like a pudding we've been
eating it just like out of the box
but it looks amazing though yeah i
wanted myself
i wanted to get you a cheesecake and
then i saw that i was like this is
perfect it's just as soft as you oh
thank you
thank you so much i really appreciate it
congrats on your original
thank you
thank you thank you so much
all right um
question okay um all right question
um
i'll say anything
if you could describe me in three words
what would it be
taco seasoning
[Music]
um protect protect this rat
protect this rat right
i don't know you're like um
you've always been
someone who's very very sweet to me
oh stop you
and i just want you to um continue to
have fun forever and ever and
you make me so happy and like make a
mama said you make um a whole heap of
people around the world super super
happy with your streams so i just want
to protect that i'll protect the ass
thank you you're so sweet
you're so sweet
you said that um you were very very
nervous for the past
private chat yeah i'm so nervous
i think that means that you put so much
heart and effort into
um everything your original song your
birthday your um streaming for an entire
month ah
and because you put heart into it but
that means you really care for it that's
why you're embarrassed um and it pays
off
oh thank you i don't know what to do
with that i feel weird i feel strange
i love you
thank you so much for stopping by
and thank you so much have a beautiful
rest of the day and enjoy the rest of
the pudding cake yes i will if mama rat
doesn't eat all of it i swear to god i
swear to god
man
mama rat like sweets more than i do so
thank you
i really appreciate it
okay i'll guess all
carefully okay
don't make sure the hat doesn't fall off
[Music]
and that was sana
oh
yes um i won't be able to talk to you
guys too much because we got bam bam bam
bam bam you know we've got clothes
coming in okay next person is already
here oh would you look at that who has
joined the party
hello
[Music]
yeah hello hi
hi hi happy not birthday thank you
thank you oh my god how you feeling i'm
feeling great now that you're here i
feel like with every single uh different
member who calls like i feel like my my
vibe is going to change thank you for
calming me down are you going
i'll talk to say i was like from
normal
normal day heart rate to inna's sitting
resting heart rate how are you doing ah
i'm right now i mean i was like uh
a bay heart rate like probably like five
seconds ago but then now that you join
i'm in like
i'm in like mid ground middle middle
range
oh are you sure cause my resting heart
rate is pretty
pretty up there apparently but really
anyways
[Music]
i remember my heart just leaving my body
preparing for i can only imagine how it
feels right now i don't understand oh my
god the prep the insane amount of prep
that you have oh my god i can't i
don't have big enough brain for this man
it was all worth it
yeah
i just want to say your song is like
perfect match for you
um
i know i know chameleons on it he writes
a lot of like very energetic chaotic
songs yeah perfect
yeah i will have it on move for the next
week
thank you so much
screenplay guys
what was your first impression of me
i've never asked anyone this before so
i'm very curious really yeah
my first impression
was
is that a hamster
oh no
i don't get a young kid oh
i was like actually
my first impression of you was that um
you were
a lot calmer than i expected
you know you know when i when i first
learned of chaos i thought you were
going to be
bouncing off the walls but i don't know
if you were like nervous like first time
talking to like uh
probably
you're a lot calmer than like bouncing
off walls of what i was expecting but
you know you're
you know you're not like like like what
should i say like bouncing a fall
chaotic but like
you know you're like a happy energetic
chaotic and i really like that
thanks
thank you i remember you're a good
student here you know
oh no let's not go there all right
i mean
really has that nice little ring to it
you know that's true
that that's true you right
you're right
[Music]
man
you really do calm me down thank you so
much oh you're welcome i'll be up you'll
beat
don't worry about it yes yes uh
for thank you for sending me your chi
chakra of zen thank you and it's 5 49.99
[Music]
[Laughter]
but anyways i hope you have a blast i
will everything else in the stream
keep watching while i roll on the ground
happy not birthday thank you
bye
[Music]
she's so cute
that was email everybody
yes
joined the party
who is this beauty walking in oh my god
also if you didn't know we're in the
middle of a club at the moment so we got
another
invitation
another guest
oh
hello
sorry hello
hello hello
i'm strange i got teleported
sorry that was me i was trying to i was
trying it's like i was opening the door
for you but then you were also pulling
on the door you know to the disco so
sorry sorry about that it's like when
when you try to hold the door open for
someone but then they're trying to hold
the door open for you and
we're both just standing there awkwardly
yeah yeah yeah yeah that's what happened
i'm sorry hello
hello happy not birthday thank you
hey
congratulations
play dice is so good
it's amazing thank you so much thank you
congratulations you've been working so
hard this whole month and like forever
so i'm really really happy that
everything is paying off for you and i'm
proud of you for all the hard work
you've put in you've earned all this
yes you
i swear i'm gonna cry every single time
i'm just gonna cry thank you i hope
you're doing well i hope you had fun
thank you
i'm so sleepy
split the price
yes actually i have something for you
um i made this in my sleep deprivation
you shouldn't have
thank you
ah that's so cute oh my god this is so
cute happy birthday
thank you
[Music]
oh that is so cute
oh
my god
oh my god that's a little bit or
something for a little rat thank you
i'll go right here
right here very nice right here
oh my god
thank you so much oh yes i've got a
question for you actually
yes
a question has there been anything that
you wanted to ask me
that you haven't been able to if you
could ask me anything what would you
want to know
i feel like i should have thought about
this more because this is like a once in
a lifetime chance right s and color is
in your hands corner
the power is in your hands
but the only thing i can think of is
how
they how
well you see
time space
[Music]
nature
people yes
that is
yes
i hope that answered your question thank
you so much thank you so much for the
questions
thank you thank you next year i'll think
of something better than just how maybe
we'll get to the why next year
[Music]
we're just gonna work our way through
the different questions who where why
when eventually eventually i will truly
narrow hodo i see we'll see
i said to enlightenment
light event
oh
my god
man but thank you so much for stopping
by
thank you have a great rest of your
birthday have fun talking to everyone
and have fun
and karaoke
i'm so nervous i'm literally so nervous
i can't but i wouldn't tell you not to
be nervous but i would be nervous too so
um all i can say is to have fun with it
okay i will
have fun it's your birthday or you're
not birthday um you're the princess
today that means you can do no wrong so
that's true just have fun that's true
that's the name the world is your oyster
and if you don't like oysters then maybe
it can be
your face okay is today my lobster
is your everybody my love do you know
that reference
um
i wouldn't think i've heard of it isn't
that something you say to someone when
you like them you're my lobster yeah
oh yeah yeah
all righty thank you so much tommy enjoy
the party yes the party that is so
pumping as you can see in this
background
[Music]
and that was fun everybody
we're waiting on the next guest
but
uh
man
i'm really getting uh i'm already being
overwhelmed
absolutely
with emotion i can't i can't imagine oh
hello
i didn't see you there hi
happy birthday hold on one second i've
got a special rendition of happy
birthday i'll do it for you i hope this
taxi driver doesn't want to beat me up
honestly
happy birthday
to you
[Music]
if i say your name i don't know maybe
then maybe the taxi driver knows you i
gotta be careful birthday
yeah
i gotta i gotta rap but it's gonna be
later okay i won't rap in this
they won't rap in here oh good thank you
happy happy freaking birthday to you i'm
so
so proud of you because your new song is
great
it's a certified banger certified
yeah
yeah of course i freaking love his
certified rat classic thank you
you're welcome you did amazing you
killed you killed it with that that
japanese wrap too i was like damn
i was getting flashbacks to like when i
used to listen to lots of japanese rap
and i was like
oh this is sick this is tight
thank you happy big day
you're welcome can we expect more from
you
more
i hope so
i hope so i would love to hear i would
love to hear more songs from you i would
love to
uh i would love to make more if i can um
yeah you can do it
maybe
um
um fingers yeah yes you can yeah maybe
we can we can we can
yes we can
yeah i make song with everyone
especially especially you yeah yeah we
gotta do the chad cast official like
wrong you know me and iris let's go
yeah let's go
let's go this year oh sometime this year
hopefully let's go
[Music]
yeah i have a question for you
yes i prepared for this what was your
first impression of me
oh i knew it was gonna be that one
i've never asked you this before
when i first
saw
like your
your in the image of you
what i thought and based on like how you
typed to me
and like how we talked before i ever
heard your voice
i imagined you'd be like some kind of
like
bouncing off the freaking walls like
rafflecopter la mao
i like crazy chick honestly i thought
you were gonna be
[\h__\h] like
beyond wild like chaos beyond like
hashtag what is acceptable to nature
hashtag
the hashtag wild for real no actually i
seriously i thought you were gonna be
absolutely nutty but then like i got in
a call with you and i was like oh she's
cute and then i discovered like
the the chill side of you which is like
most of the time that like i'm talking
with you you sound like so laid back and
like
like just like chill it's hard to
describe but like i feel like when when
we're talking especially off stream
um you're very like laid back and like
kind of just chilling and you know what
i'm glad that it turned out that way
because i feel like if you were just
chaotic off the wall bouncing off the
wall energetic all the time i'd probably
like bang my head against the wall i'd
still love you but like
there'd be some blood on my wall you
know more blood for me to clean off the
wall so you know i love you the way you
are i'm glad you you turned out you
swear thank you i love you too
yeah dude you're the bestest you're the
best
you're the best
well yeah how's the house hako doing
um
don't know don't care
yeah i feel i feel that same way about
calvin but he's been asking me he's been
like he's been like hey yo hit up
hit up
hit up bay real quick ask how heco is
doing we need to hang out again because
i guess they're like they're like
becoming friends and like it's scary
it's kind of scary but anyway yeah
thanks for coming
you're welcome my dog i love you happy
birthday thank you
okay take care of yourself bye bye bye
bye
bye bye happy bay day peace
[Music]
and that was cali everybody
oh would you look at that you know we've
got one beautiful
lady entering the party and it's time
for another beautiful lady to enter the
party hello
hey uh
hey happy
not birthday
thank you baby thank you
thank you do you like your hat
yeah i don't just like it i love
it hi
congratulations on your original it is
such a banger thank you
thank you
oh man
i'm gonna be listening to that for a
while that's like one of my
favorite types
[Music]
jazzy but fast-paced uh-huh you know
what i'm talking about yeah yeah
yeah
how are you feeling
[Applause]
[Music]
are you doing good
yeah i'm doing
actually i'm a bit tired but i'm doing
pretty good
are you
nervous or anything or yes i mean i was
gonna i was about to puke before the the
the the original song came up but now
i'm doing a bit better because i'm just
talking to you guys i love talking to
you guys i feel like when i get to the
other course i'm just going to be dying
just
internal combustion
um
gotta ease into it you know so
ah that's right
oh i love i love it i love how my mood
like my vibe changes with every single
person who comes in normally when
currently and i talk we're literally
just like yeah bro what's up bro
how you doing how are you doing bro
are you dying bro yeah
yep yep
but uh okay what shall i ask you
oh i feel like okay we talk quite a lot
and i feel like you know i'm not quoting
pretty well but
has there been something that you've
wanted to ask me that you haven't been
able to yet the power's in your hands
you can ask me anything and i'll answer
truthfully
i feel like i've asked
a lot of things to you and
i feel like
what is there to say um let's see
[Music]
hmm
how
do you
what do you think about me ah
[Music]
i feel like i asked that before
no actually i don't think you have uh i
think oh no i don't think you have um
how do i feel towards you i
have the utmost okay truthfully you know
i have probably the highest respect and
admiration for crony i'm being
completely honest
[Laughter]
um i look up to you in a lot of aspects
and i just i am
very honored to be able to call you my
friend so
yeah
shouldn't you be oh is there is there
any question that you want to ask me
then
ask you
yeah it could be the same question or
something else ah i feel like it would
be the same question
like one of those i serious i just need
to know how do you how do you really
feel about me
[Music]
that's a solid sip
thank you
i'm
hmm how should i say
it's uh
i i didn't think that
cause since uh since i'm a bit
introverted i
didn't think that i would be
like
getting like getting along as in like i
wouldn't be talking to you as much but
um i saw
so like a side of you that's kind of
chill and we related to a lot of things
and
i
i'm really glad that
i got to know you
okay that sounds like a red flag i'm
really glad that i know you
ah thanks man not a death flag or
anything um so i'm really glad that i
know you and i hope thanks doesn't
change
we gotta we go we'll go collab soon
again it's been ages since we lost
collab i feel like
i know yeah power wash let's go
let's go
let's go okay
well
thank you for stopping by get some rest
yeah
you two oh wait you can't but
afterwards and have a merry on birthday
[Music]
that was crony and would you look at
that we have another guest whoa she is
glowing she got that yellow drip on her
who could it be
hi
hello
i'm dripping
the hat really suits you you know when i
was like putting hats on everyone i'm
like the hat really suits your head
ah that's the drip you were talking
about huh yeah
i met you
i made you something i'm sorry i wanted
to give it to you i'm so excited i guess
you could say i
baked you
i'm sorry
sorry it's a weird resolution
oh
mom
gosh look at that oh my gosh
holy moly
i love it i'm putting it right cupcake
thank you i love it that's perfect oh my
god the guys with the candle oh my god
it's
it's beautiful
thank you
excited i listened to your your song
earlier it's so great your music video
was sweet it looks really cool
very bright very like whoa
yeah i love the effects and like the art
was so good
thank you
um
before i leave
your quest yes if okay you could
describe me in three words what would it
be
um
does i count as a word in the sentence
no
oh [\h__\h] alright
[Music]
wait i want to give a serious answer uh
wait that wasn't a serious answer okay
energetic creative and sweet
oh
thank you
yeah i see it you're doing a lot of
stuff and it takes a lot of energy while
streaming every day of the month this
month it's insane you're really hard
worker i'm really proud of you oh thank
you i look up to you so much bro
[Music]
yeah i'm is like the pioneer of just
creating
content and i was i'm just like i gotta
keep up i just
man
i'm like even just the the recent like
the collab and stuff i'm like man man
i wanna be at here level one day i gotta
learn more
yeah you're already there you're there
yeah
you're doing a great job
thank you
thank you thanks for stopping by
no problem good luck
i'm sure you're all very tired
yeah yeah
you guys sleep
uh
just a little bit only a little bit
it was really cool though i love i love
to visit youtube or visit us or just
watch you guys together too that'd be
awesome i'm gonna come i'm gonna go when
i can't yes i will yes yes yes we're
gonna have plans i'm gonna go you gotta
go
soon
please well thank you
for the amazing cupcake i will it's
going on
the table yes my my personal cupcake
thank you very much i hope it tastes as
good as the one santa sent you oh i'm
sure it will
thanks for stopping by
yeah good luck on the rest of your
collins and happy birthday i'm looking
forward you haven't announced uh any
other things yet right
i'm looking forward to it yeah
thank you
yeah
all right all right
see you later
[Music]
also i don't know what happened with the
lag there bruh pc [\h__\h] are you okay do a
quick refresh okay
[Music]
man
i missed them so she's so
she's so ahmed she's so cute so sweet i
can't
well what is that noise
[Applause]
hello
[Music]
hi
hello
[Music]
i got home and my internet's not working
i'm on my phone hello oh you sound great
don't worry about it you sound beautiful
welcome thank you happy
birthday
question mark thank you
what year is it
um
it's currently 2022
okay that's good to know yeah
i have something for
i tried to make something but my
internet's not working so i had to do
something else do you want it of course
he didn't have to
message me messaged me like last night
she's like bye
i have i
got gift but internet i would not work i
would gonna be like i'm so sorry and i'm
not let me it's okay don't worry about
it don't worry about it
okay listen it wasn't supposed to not be
working right now
ah
i don't know what's going on but here
you go
let's send it
thank you
there you go
that's so cute
oh my god that's so cute that is so cute
so cute
[Music]
oh that's huge
hold on hold on we got a infiltration oh
my god that's so cute thank you
you're welcome
you sound sleepy are you okay
no i'm just sad my internet's not
working like giving me cute something
better it's so cute
no it's amazing i love it i love
it oh maybe i shouldn't ask questions
there's not much time that's okay you
know we got time to worry about it
oh i'm just gonna say how's it going and
i and i tried i heard your song i held
it to my ear i could hear it and i
watched it thank you i did it all thank
you mimei was like frantically dming me
while um the the song was premiering and
she was losing her mind and i was like
but i was losing my mind we were just
both losing our minds
what minds yeah
yeah
congrats i'm so happy
hey you
it's awesome babe thank you it's so good
this whole month has been amazing thank
you
all right quick question before we
move on
yeah yeah yeah what was your first
impression of me
oh i thought about this why okay well i
i thought about it and it was easy to
think about
i remember
i was so
so happy when you used xd
because
i hadn't seen it in so long and i was
like oh my gosh i get i have someone who
uses
i just i was so happy because i i
i don't know how to explain that but i
was so happy that you think he's 16.
wow that's that's the best that's
i'm so glad that's the best answer i
could ever expect oh my god
what did
oh my god that's amazing i remember we
talked a lot i remember before debut
yeah yeah i think we i think i talked to
you the most i feel like
maybe we were i think everyone was eager
to talk and like get to know each other
but maybe we were the most like could
not contain it and could not like oh do
it the slow way we were just like hey
how's it going
yeah you right you're right good times
good times
yeah and now you're older oh my gosh i
know i'm 12 and a half now
amazing
but thank you so much get a good
rest get a good rest
and i watch the rest of
what you did today yeah oh thank you
oh are you sure you haven't eaten you
know what's been really concerning me
recently is that i will work during the
night and for some reason mummy answers
my messages that's quite concerning um
no
don't worry about an owl i was dude it's
still changing
that's okay okay okay
all right i promise it's
alrighty thank you for stopping by
we have them have a great must be your
birthday i love you goodbye
[Music]
cute
man i love them i love my family i love
my holiday and family
um so
uh that's it for the collins for holiday
and um but
uh gura and kiara could make it which is
absolutely fine but they send me video i
want to watch it with everyone uh it's
all about the family
ohio family
is that how you do it right
or how many family family means
i don't know how stitch sounds anyway
um i've also run out of coffee which is
an interesting situation um
should i make more
do i have time to make more
we'll see anyway
um so i want to watch the videos that um
gura and
uh kiara sent me i haven't watched them
yet so i'm very excited okay let me just
turn the music off
okay are we ready
so the first one is from
kiara
that's i'm hoping this works okay what's
up why am i lagging hello
hello okay we're good
just too many things going on it's too
powerful it's a bit too powerful okay
let's go
[Music]
oh no
this is upsetting why can't i hear it
[Applause]
hold on everybody hold on sorry
technical difficulties
oh no
there a way that i can hear this
hold on
happy birthday
i can't hear her happy birthday
they're bails
i will sing
i hear it i hear it okay play again
happy birthday
they're bails
i will sing
for you now
happy birthday to you
[Music]
your day yeah i hope it goes your way
yeah
eat some good cake
thank you
[Music]
listen this is important okay take care
of your body okay okay
you work too
hard when you need me
happy birthday bills
that was amazing
oh my god i love this so
much we had a little bit of technical
difficulties but it's okay we got it
working it's okay
thank you kiara
thank you
thank you so much thank you thank you
okay the next one was from gura
i hope this works
[Music]
okay
i'm not hearing anything again
i don't know there's something weird
about the whole um
there we go
hey
hi happy birthday
[Music]
if
if you were a cheese
you would be gold cheese
because you are
the greatest of
all time
the gold
i hope you have a fantastic birthday
baby thank you good happy birthday
thank you
okay but i was gonna by the way
[Music]
we gotta watch that again that was too
brilliant hold on
[Music]
hey
if you were a cheese
you would be
gold cheese
because you are
the greatest of all time
the gold
[Music]
i hope you have a fantastic birthday
baby
happy birthday
okay but always good by the way
[Music]
oh my god that's my favorite part
ah
thank you gooda she's so cute and
oh my god it's amazing that's freaking
amazing okay
[Music]
i'm dying i laughed too hard bruh you
and me you and me both you and me both
um uggy
oh okay
what is this
sorry i gotta send something hold on oh
yes um so we are taking a small little
break from
uh tutsu
monkeys at the moment
uh because
it's announcement time
yes announcement time
it's an announcement time
um depending on if i have time i might
also go make another cup of coffee
because
oh i can and this is my birthday stream
and there are a lot of you guys here so
just bear with me if i take a couple of
minutes just to go make myself another
cup of coffee okay um but
it's announcement timing
[Music]
is everybody
is everybody ready for the announcement
right
[Music]
we have merch everybody can i just say
designing merch it was probably the most
fun thing i've ever done in my entire
life that is so cool it's so much fun i
just yes so uh we have birthday march
everybody um and i hope you really like
it because i really like it are you guys
ready you're not ready are you ready
you're not ready are you ready you're
not ready first of all can you look at
this amazing art this is done by mika
mama as well isn't that amazing amazing
beautiful amazing okay full set
[Music]
we've got
the goods yeah
so we have a boom boom rubber mat uh
which is like the keyboard and mouse mat
with the art done by mika mama we'll go
through all the items individually as
well in a second we got a snapback we
got a mug we got a keychain and we've
got voice pegs oh my god voice pack
let's go voice pack let's go um and then
bonus uh oh yeah the keychain is the
complete set exclusive item which means
you can get it only if you buy the full
set um and then we've got a bonus uh
postcard and a bonus voice line um just
to say thank you brett if you buy the
complete set
okay so let's go through each of these
items one by one um
you know what
give me two seconds i don't know what's
going on
[Music]
i don't know why i'm lagging and
honestly it's quite rude
it's honestly extremely rude okay can
you
bait can you just
keep it together bae
can you just please keep it together bae
okay keep it together okay
okay what are we doing oh we're going
too much okay okay
um so the first item is the boom boom
rubber mat which look at this freaking
art it's freaking amazing
i need to get one i i want one i just i
the art is by mika pikazo
we've got the japanese um
visuals uh coming up soon so i'll just
read off that because i literally don't
know how to say this in japanese because
i'm small brain today um the art is done
by uh mama
um
and
it's literally beautiful um so the theme
of this year's birthday if you couldn't
tell was neon party chaos
it ties in with everything with the song
with um you know the birthday and i
wanted the merch to also um to kind of
emulate that as well
so um in this picture you can see i've
got kind of new drip i've got some new
drip we've got we've got a new jacket
we've got it says bad rat i've got some
piercings headphones
new drip
fishnet yes new drip
um so this is amazing so thank you so
much mika mama for drawing this
absolutely
beautiful artwork
um and then probably
the main thing that i asked for in merch
it's the official
bra slapper
i'm so excited i am so
freaking excited for this okay we've got
i can't i can't it's so cool we've got
you know the signature black cap you
know snap back uh we've got some studs
on either side because we're edgy just
you know because i got studs on my on my
collar you got put some studs on you
know the hat then we've got some rings
you know on the on the rim because i'm
edgy like that bruh yes um and
yes the the main kind of selling point
is the bra with the under
under the rim bruh with the red
because it's like a it's part of the
club you know anyone can have a hat with
you know a cheese kind of cheese emblem
but are you part of the bra club you're
part of the bro club can you imagine
walking around with this on and then you
see another person and then you just
flash the bra
bruh
[Music]
i'm so excited um it literally looks
exactly how you know i wanted it to and
i'm definitely adding this to my
collection as well and if you noticed
sorry i'm
i've been shouting a lot so i've been
clearing my throat a lot if you've
noticed
you can see
that the bra cap
is also
featured
in the art
wouldn't it be cool if you have a mat
and it has an illustration of the cap
it's in the art guys it's in the art
imagine you have a picture of the cap
but you also have the actual cap
[Music]
amazing
beautiful
it's amazing
[Music]
you're going break dancing with the cat
i don't break dance anymore but yes
i would
yes
what a deal what an actual deal this is
absolutely
amazing and i love it i love it so much
um and i hope you guys like it too
i remember when we were brainstorming
ideas for merch i was like snap back i i
want snap back please please snap back
please please snap back thank you very
much snap back
um so
when you get a 3d can you break dance
for us no it's been
many many many many many many many many
many many years and i didn't know how to
break down to begin with i was baby
breakdance okay don't worry about it
but i'll do the worm i'll do the worm
for you guys okay
[Music]
yeah
and i feel like the design is like you
know it's not too out there where you
know it will clash with um outfit
options i feel like it will match um
whatever you wear so
i hope you guys like it um and moving on
to something that i will probably use on
a day-to-day basis
now
i wanted to make a mug but i didn't want
to make just any
mug
i wanted to make
a mug that was big enough for the amount
of coffee that i drink on a day-to-day
basis
this mug
is a 1.25 liter mug
it's 1.25 liters
[Laughter]
that's huge
um and basically the art was done by
snow meow which um actually i found them
because of remember the fan art that um
was me on a tomato the chibi of me on a
tomato
yeah
this is the same artist i reached out
and i was like i really like your tibia
would you like to collab on america item
yes that's what i did
but
the selling point of this absolutely
it's 1.25 liters guys think about it if
you're at work and you need a drink do
you need to keep refilling your cup over
and over again no you've got 1.25 litres
you know that cuts your refilling time
in thirds because this is three times
larger than your traditional mug okay
you can put anything in it it could be
even a soup cup you can make soup in
this you could you know those instant
soups a soup mug it can be a tea mug it
can be a water mug if that's your life
you know stay hydrated
or it could be a coffee mug
whatever you do just hashtag stay
caffeinated
it's a party mug it's amazing one liter
it's too small excuse me it's 1.25
liters
it's 1.25 liters okay
[Music]
it's a comically large mug actually no i
have several monks that are this size
um but they're all too
like fat like wide this is a very good
um cup because it's tall
[Music]
but i hope you like it
because this is definitely something i
need to use
like i don't need to if i had this mug
right now i wouldn't need to be going to
make another cup of coffee now would i
no because i would have had 1.25 liters
of coffee i wouldn't need to leave my
seat
for an entire stream
it's good for your health it's
convenient and it looks cute
believe you know it speaks for itself it
really does it really does
take a dip in the mug bro
you can probably put an entire ramen in
that i don't think you can
can you
i don't know buy it try it out you tell
me
wow okay
and then next one uh so that does it for
the three main parts uh three main merch
items um the rubber mat the uh
snap bag and the cup
um and if you buy the full set you will
get this exclusive i repeat exclusive
exclusive brass keychain
um so you get it's got you know mr
squeaks has also got two dyes and pretty
cute
it's pretty cute you know what a deal
pretty cute
um
yeah it's really cute i really like it
uh so uh just a reminder again that this
is only available um for purchase if you
can buy the complete set guys so yeah if
you want little mr squeaks dangling if
you want this little mouse dangling off
wherever you decide to hang your
keychain yeah it's really cute it's
really cute
are the dice actual dice yeah it's
actual dice
[Music]
it's actual dice
uh-huh
what to do
what a deal
amazing
um and then
uh this is the uh bonus uh postcard art
um that is the same art
on the rubber mat so the same one that
mika mama drew
[Music]
my signature and just a little thank you
message and with the postcard um bonus
also comes a voiceline bonus um thank
you bratz because without you guys
i don't think any of this would ever
have happened for me so
i'm really really really really really
really really really thankful thank you
so much
um
so it comes in a bundled sale which is
the birthday merch complete set you can
buy the rubber mat the mug and the
snapback individually if you want and
you can also buy the voice pack
separately as well so there's a
situational voice pack which is kind of
like a role play
um a scenario uh type voice pack and
then also there's a system voice pack
which is just you know um a couple a
couple little short you know voice lines
voice packs that you can potentially use
for i don't know
system orientated sounds
let's just say
[Music]
so i hope you enjoy it yes yes
um i do think that's it for the entire
birthday set however
this is just the japanese version
[Music]
um i'm gonna be back okay give me like
three minutes i'm gonna put this on
i need to go make another cup of coffee
i really should have thought this out
but
um okay
[Music]
does this work
hello
i'm trying to put it on autumn auto mode
auto mode yes okay it's working i'll be
right back uh i gotta go facilitate the
guess that's exactly what i need to do
okay so just let's look at the merge
i'll be back in three minutes okay
[Music]
do
i'm back
okay what was i talking about merge okay
so i have my let me go back to
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
i don't know how to
please please you know
please please pick one up if you would
like
[Music]
my
foreign
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
holder then she loved that little little
play on words
amazing
so uh we've got this oh wait
hi kawaii
squeaks
uh
[Music]
yes
all right back to english that is the
goods
so just a quick announcement so these
goods will be available for sale at uh
the same time that play dice is
scheduled to be released on streaming
platform so it will be released at the
same time 12 am jst
[Music]
karaoke
so i'll be doing a karaoke countdown not
only counting down to play dice being
available on streaming platforms but
also a countdown um to when the merch
will be available for purchase um
my
is the link in the description below me
haps
me haps
mayhaps ready
mayhaps it's probably there
is it there yes it's there okay
um so that link it probably isn't
available yet but the link is there um
at 12 a.m jst sharp
the goods will be on sale um as well as
play dice available on streaming
platforms so
i hope to see you guys there and thank
you for the support
i'm really proud of how the merch came
out
i really love everything so thank you so
much
[Music]
and that is it for merch
yes thank you thank you so much
let me just sit my coffee real quick
[Music]
i just love the art i'm going to change
my profile picture to this
[Music]
youtube
actually all right well
what what is this i hear i hear
footsteps why am i hearing footsteps oh
oh oh are we oh yeah oh
footsteps oh
guys i think it's time for
some more
[Music]
and who was this
all right um so this is the second round
of collins and i am literally
forgive my absolute you know i'm
[\h__\h] balls help i'm so nervous
i think that's the first time i've ever
like fully cursed on stream not even i
am [\h__\h] balls help me i'm so nervous
okay
um but first
hi
first guest
hello
[Music]
i think i think
i think i think she hit the hit the door
on her way in hold on
hello hello my dears
can you hear me now yes i can
[Music]
my daughter my sweet sugar mom happy
birthday thank you thank you so much
how's your day so far i'm [\h__\h] balls
i'm so nervous help oh [\h__\h] you're
sitting
bye basketballs
that would hurt honestly
that could be a big [\h__\h]
i'm really nervous that's all um
i was mentioning to like the en members
when they were calling in that some
members who
you know very graciously took the time
of day to call in i some of them i've
never spoken to before so i am
very nervous how are you i'm really
looking forward i'm doing great i woke
up and i heard your original song i
literally put an alarm for it and
i do say it is the absolute magnificent
banger i dare say that the song is a
beast itself that's the beat that slaps
the ass of thee
why thank you thank you kind kind madden
um
i'm real
i'm
hold on let me get the accent i'm i'm
really really
thankful
that uh you liked it
oh it was just
beautiful
my fair lady
thank you thank you
oh
thank you for calling in holly
my my pleasure i'm sorry like everyone
gave you a gift but i didn't really give
you i didn't prepare
can you shut up right now oh my god this
one okay everybody she's saying that she
didn't get me a gift but literally a
week ago literally this one sends me a
gift
hemp up
oh my freaking god literally
i i feel bad because you know like like
like usually when i come to totsumaki's
i give like also a virtual gift but i
only give you like a physical gift and i
don't feel like it's enough i wanted to
write you a song because i don't have
them
shut up oh my god literally mama rat
accepted the gift um like open like
answered the door and i came in and she
was like it's really heavy i don't know
what it is but it's a dress to you and i
was like okay i opened it there was
literally first of all a bottle of
champagne
what yeah
then there was like a silk robe silk
french vanilla almonds a candle uh what
else was there fresh oh face mist bra
it was too much
soap and soap yes that was soap as well
i tried giving you the best
it was all thanks to sana sana made it
possible she was like oh yeah give her
hampez
[Music]
thank you ollie you are literally insane
that's too much thank you
it's in my name
oh wait i spoke your name wrong hold on
[Laughter]
these things can be pretty hectic
sometimes yep understandable yep but
before you get off really quickly um
what a three thing if you could describe
me in three words what would it be
um wait uh heartful passionate and pride
because you are my soul my pride my my
little angel i wish i could describe you
more if if i was la mama i'd be like
yeah my super cute exquisite amazing
wonderful magical uh
pretty cute kawaii super magnificent
ultra mega
daughter
[Music]
thank you
you are literally a gift you are a gift
to this world man i'm so appreciative of
you excuse me no you no you you know
reverse card no take a look in the
mirror reverse card that uno uno the
reverse reverse cod and then skip
because then you can't reverse
get the card
i'm beating this child
anyway thank you so much for stopping by
ali enjoy the party yeah
non-existent party but yes
i see i see hakka in the back djing and
it's pretty cool i hope you have fun i
will thank you
thank you have a great one bye bye
[Music]
all right um
the next guest will be switching
languages i'm [\h__\h] i'm so nervous okay
[Music]
foreign
um
[Laughter]
is really curious whether i would get
balloons from twitter does anybody know
did i get balloons
[Music]
foreign
ah
[Music]
know
okay
[Laughter]
so
[Music]
thank you
okay there's just been a there's been a
change
[Music]
[Applause]
wow
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
um so i asked her the three questions
very interesting um she said my singing
voice
the cute kawaii and coolness and oppai
which i don't think i need to translate
thank you
senpai
highway
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
yes
hey
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
what just happened
i don't know what just happened but i
got uh i was offered marriage proposal
then i became her kid and then we asmr
off collab done okay
hi
what's up
[Music]
thank you thank you
hi
ha ha ha ha he may not i'm not cool
oh
[\h__\h]
yeah
[Music]
no no
nice to meet you yes nice to meet you
i am
[Music]
big big big brain uh
[Laughter]
um
foreign
[Music]
um
thank you
[Music]
wow
oh
[Music]
yes
my gosh
that was
my first
talk with coyote
i feel like my heart is about to explode
i am so
i am
absolutely
positively losing my mind everybody is
so cute
everybody is so cute i can't she has
great energy she really does what
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
m
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
thank you
running a little bit behind schedule but
that's okay that was me
[Music]
mushy
hey
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
oh
m
um
[Music]
foreign
so
[Music]
i've scored big time guys i scored big
time
i've scored big time
i've got a kabedon and i got
uh for those who don't know what a goku
is it's a chin lift it's like when they
you know the protagonist lifts the chin
of the shorter of the shorter of the
shorter um
person
i'm winning i'm freaking winning i'm
actually winning oh my god
yes
um
i seem a bit on edge because one
that was sort of senpai
i didn't realize
i can't
believe
that i would be talking to sora senpai
and asking her for a cabin
in what universe
did i allow did anybody allow this to
happen
i can't talk i was so
nervous oh my god
but
yes i'm gonna invite i asked her if she
won if she liked alcohol because i was
thinking of inviting her to rat reviews
but
um she was drink orange juice and i'll
get absolutely smashed in front of dai
senpai of course
wow
i'm so nervous bro i'm so nervous
[Music]
who's next
while we wait
sorry guys i been i'm just i i am
absolutely overwhelmed
i've never done a totsamachi before but
i am i i i just i yes i bruh
she's the only idol of her life honestly
no i was gonna say honestly you kind of
right but like no i can't say that i'm
idle
i'm idle
i'm idle just breathe for a minute i'm
gonna breathe
i'm gonna breathe
i'm gonna breathe we're gonna be fine
i don't know how people do thoughts
i'm just extremely
nervous i just
breathe
we're just gonna breathe
okay
i should have worn a heart rate monitor
for this no that's a terrible idea bae
what are you talking about that's an
absolutely terrible idea
[Music]
no i don't know why i said that
literally terrible
terrible
terrible idea
heart rate monitor totsumachi when never
that will give too much away hello
hello
hi
i'm muttering to myself i'm sorry hello
no no it's okay
hello
hello happy birthday
thank you
it's happy birthday since i've talked to
you
yeah it's been it's been a while i think
the one that and only collab that we
ever had was on the mccorone collab
and it's not you know it's not even a
collab yeah
yeah yeah i mean we were we did collab
um like a little bit during um the
minecraft sports festival thingy i
remember oh yeah the minecraft sports
festival yeah i guess that can be called
a collab yeah how is it going
i'm
overwhelmed
um
i'm just i can't see that very like i
don't know how to function anymore um
yeah
yeah but i'm glad you're here
[Music]
there's so many people on youtube
just so cute just nervous nervous
laughter um how are you
how are you
i'm good thank you
i have been i've been watching your
stream
no
and seeing you saying you're getting
nervous
and like wow look at that so cute
says you excuse me
excuse me excuse me
excuse me
excuse me excuse me no i i pop into your
streams from time to time honestly
literally i aspire to be like anya oh my
god you're so like can i can we just
talk about how
absolutely smooth and silky your
japanese is bruh
literally i don't understand please
teach me i don't understand no but your
your japanese is also good no
no did you well you were watching the
stream you could hear me stuttering i
can't even say more than two sentences
without stuttering
no no no no it's okay we can we can both
be nihongo jozu
yeah both of us
we can be nihongo
[Music]
yeah but yeah we should definitely
collapse yeah if you want yeah let's
let's play games maybe i love games do
you love games i love games but i'm
terrible at them so
i mean me too
me too
it's okay let's game together or
something yeah we should
yeah
yeah i also listened to your original
song i love it thank you so much i love
it thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you
if you could describe me in three words
what would it be
um hard working cute bread
yeah
hard working cause i saw i saw you
streaming for the whole month oh this
month
and i thought to myself wow that girl
that girl is crazy she's chaotic chaotic
really yes because you're chaos oh my
god thank you the first time anyone has
called me chaotic
thank you thank you for waiting i mean
you're cute thank you thank you for
thank you for validating my lore okay
i feel like i need to do that i feel
like someone needs to do that at least
one person one person needs to do that
you know one person needs to validate
hear that chat i'm validated okay
everybody stop saying oh yeah she's not
chaotic oh my god
oh my god thank you so much
thank you for calling me of course
bye-bye
thank you
[Music]
man she's so cute i can't handle
i can't handle she's okay
base valid i'm validating
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's
me
[Music]
um
bye
[Music]
i love her
yeah we got bae what yo we getting we're
getting freaking you know we're getting
ideas left and right let's go
we're gonna have nine star in baywatch
let's go let's freaking go hello
hello hello
hello who am i speaking who is this is
this the bishop day girl is this new
girl uh no wrong number
four
thanks for coming are you okay
welcome nice okay i'm just i just it
just you know had you know what's he was
he called again in in english
[Laughter]
want to try to explain it in the group
right i have a
what what the heck is tayden in
goosebumps like what the hell is that
right right right right right it's okay
okay
thank you guys
welcome
we kind of like talk a lot right yeah it
doesn't really feel like it's been a
while no we talked like literally
three days ago two days ago
what's up
what's up what's
[Music]
oh
thank you
anything for the birthday girl
[Music]
oh my god that's so cute
oh thank you
welcome
i love it
oh thank you
oh oh big
i kind of want to draw your mouth on the
top of your head but i kind of like
where should i put it hold on
do you have the name for the mouse a
little better mr
i don't know i feel i feel you know i
feel like because we talk normally it's
just kind of i'm just um yeah what's up
how are you doing you're doing good yeah
you're doing good yeah good yeah
what should i ask you um oh
what was your first impression of me
don't don't don't get mad at me but
actually i don't remember
honestly i don't remember either what
was when
when was the first time we spoke to each
other hold on oh it was it was it was um
the fashion phobia like a sudden collab
is yes i remember i remember
yes yeah yeah so i was gonna be like
playing it alone and you're kind of like
throw up in the chat
go go jump in with me just kind of being
my assistant
yeah i remember that i remember i
remember i remember also i'm just yes i
remember yes that was the first time yes
yeah i remember yeah
i actually kind of like talk and
actually like a game yeah
oh that seemed like a long time ago
but i felt like a long time ago and then
you kind of like go with ollie and then
and then the group happened
[Music]
because i distinctly remember i was
messaging you about the say i literally
was messaging you to the same thing and
i'm like why am i literally just
repeating myself i'm just going to make
a group yeah
yeah
yeah we have the coolest name group and
they never guys we do
we actually do we actually that's really
cool yeah but thanks for coming
oh thank you so much thank you for your
gift i'll see you soon i'll probably
talk to you very probably very soon
[Music]
[Laughter]
all right
[Music]
[Applause]
we love your
[Music]
we're gonna wait for a little bit
i feel like a lot happened um again in
like oh
[Music]
m
high
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
me
oh
[Music]
um
oh
[Music]
yes
[Laughter]
bye
thank you
[Music]
i have released some
some confidential information
yes it actually was stated on my
contract that if i don't become a good
idol
will be given approval by yago
to consume me
you heard it here folks
you heard it here
oh
my god um so that's the second round of
totsu machi callings we're gonna take a
little break um
let me go back to
we're gonna take a little break now um
because
you know celebrating my birthday is not
only about um
you know senpai's all also about all of
you guys so there's also like um some
oh wait a second
oh wait no wait hold on there's more
wait i gotta wait talk too much he
hasn't finished yet i forgot i forgot we
got some gifts um so basically there
were some senpai's before uh i asked you
know if they were uh free to join the
tatsumati i forgot guys i forgot look
it's been a long day you know i got
offered you know many collabs i was
nearly eaten and you know sora senpai is
giving me a cup of a lot of things are
happening so my brain is a little messed
up if you can't tell okay i'm sorry okay
um so
um we got some gifts that i wanted to
show everybody because um some senpai's
said that you know they're really sorry
they couldn't make it but they wanted to
send me a um i'm like a message instead
like a like a video and
i'm very excited
are we ready
the first one
do the ones who sent videos get goodie
bags um yes i will send them the goodie
bag as well after thank you for
reminding me actually um okay the first
one i might need to play with the volume
a little bit because i think i know um
how to get the volume now so
then
yes the first one is somebody said bye
i'm also gonna hide all of these
i'm so when she oh no when she said no
this one when she sent me this i was
like
somebody said bye
i'm gonna
cry this is the best thing in the world
okay let's hope it works happy fast
i'm sorry i couldn't
make it to your birthday party even
though you invited me
sorry
but
i sending you a video letter
i have talked to hakosha in micro and
collaborated with you in mario kart
tournament
but
we have not been able to collaborate
with 101 yet
if you want let's collaborate it
sometimes
ah i love you hakko
you are always so cheap
cute
[Music]
bye happy birthday
i'm gonna die i i can't i'm gonna die
i'm actually gonna die i'm gonna die
help i'm gonna die
she did it in english as well i'm gonna
die oh my god yes um so um she uh
i'm fine
let me just take a moment um
okay
um
somebody simba and i have
collabed
literally with the fates are on my side
we were on the same team for minecraft
we were in the same team for the maya
tournament
so it gave me a sneaky reason to be able
to talk to her
um and
i the reason why i haven't reached out
for a one-on-one collab is because one i
will literally puke but also i need to
think of like a bang-ass idea in order
to give me a good reason to like you
know be like hey
collab mayhaps you know like that kind
of vibe so
thank you oh my god it's okay she
offered it first that means a collab is
on the go right right right that means i
i'm in right does that mean i'm in
okay
i love her i love it so much i love it
so much
i love you i love it so much
i'm in collab confirmed great okay
wonderful
thank you so much
you know what my dream is actually my
one of my dream collabs is to be able to
go to virtual japan and play sauce
sauce sausage
what's the game i don't know what i know
the game is sausage but i don't know
what the actual name of the game is what
is it
sausage legend yes that is my dream
collab with subaru senpai to play
sausage legends as an off collab that's
what i want to do
that's what i want to do
you may not
know
[Laughter]
ah i want to play that game it looks so
funny and i know it's a game that it's
like you know it's it's a it's a horror
game you know actually if you if you
want to play sausage legends you got to
play with play it with subaru senpai you
know
that's why
okay um
so
uh the next gift is from
my precious
wow
let me just
[Music]
happy
happy birthday to
bear's name
[Music]
thank you you are my wonderful senpai
and a wonderful sister
my english is not so good but i want to
be you a good friend
now i
hope we will keep our relationship for a
long time yeah i wish you a wonderful
day
happy birthday
[Music]
oh she's so cute
she's so cute
um actually we've i have a collab plan
with iroha
but i haven't been able to prepare for
it because i don't have time um so
hopefully after the break you know we
will
be
absolutely collabing
absolutely 100
we're absolutely gonna collab
um
yeah base family's getting bigger and
bigger yeah bruh
let's go
yeah
her english is quite good yeah english
is really good yeah um so look out for
that yo i'm just getting
collabs left and right i'm so happy
that's the best gift i could ever get um
but it's kind of ironic because if you
know what's in the goodie bag um kind of
ironic yeah
okay and we've got one more video gift
i'm kind of scared to watch this one
okay um so
i got a video message from aradan senpai
from holostars he also sent me a picture
uh i may have died laughing at the
picture i will show the picture first
look hey he said bye okay you know what
i'm a
yeah look up yes it's it's great
look i
i love it it's great it's amazing i'm
gonna put it right here
right here
so
i will send this image along with a
video
and i'm kind of scared now to of what
the video is but it's beautiful it's an
absolute art form okay so uh let's watch
the video that other senpai sent me as
well
what happened
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my god
[Music]
present for you
i'm losing it i am absolutely
losing my
mind
[Music]
yo
that's the best that's oh did you say
those edits
did you see those freaking edits
a bruh
that's a bra moment right there bruh
i can't breathe i literally can't
breathe oh my god okay um i can't
breathe i literally cannot breathe okay
[Music]
present for you thank you that was great
i
i'm gonna watch that again
just when i have time just to really
break down the video
i didn't really hear most of it because
i was just too busy laughing but anyway
we gotta move along we're running late
oh my god okay um
[Music]
um so basically we have a little bit of
time before uh the next the final round
of tots mates um and you know
celebrating my birthday wouldn't be uh
you know complete if i didn't celebrate
it with you guys so
there was a lot of you know gifts in the
um under the hashtag and i am just so
absolutely
absolutely my mind is boggled just at
how you know so many so much love i just
can't um so i do have some videos and
some pictures from you guys i won't be
able to go through all of them um so i'm
really sorry but
i
thank you guys so much i appreciate it
more than you would ever know
um
but
the first one i really want to watch is
this video that money chan sent me um
and i was made aware that it was
um okay so uh
shout out big shout out to
you ding zee
is our same name and the event team over
on the silhouette discord for putting
together this birthday card project as
well as everyone in the various fan
discords for taking part you brats are
so amazing and wholesome and i love you
all so much thank you boom boom
here's a message from manitou
thank you guys you guys are amazing
thank you um so i'll watch the video
first and then
um i might go through some of the fan
gifs and then if we have time maybe at
the end we'll finish them off um because
i don't want to be late for the tots and
my teeth um okay
hold
on this is the first video
um
[Music]
so i see this screen
um
hold on i'm gonna make sure the volume
is okay
[Music]
all right
music off
so
i don't know who this is from i what was
the i don't know what the oh uh so it
was from
delta happy not birthday bae to
celebrate your not birthday a bunch of
breath and i came together to sing the
hakota opening we hope to enjoy our
totally not scuffed
oh my god are you serious
[Music]
are you serious
oh my god
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
oh my god we have another one as well
whoa
okay that kind of scared me why why is
it me what's this okay we got another
video um let me just make sure i can
hear it
what is this
[Music]
okay
me
what was that
what in the frick
what what what in the frick what what
was that i don't know i'm
i'm
lost for words
that was beautiful that was absolutely
beautiful okay
um
i
you know
that i i literally have
no words i have no words whatsoever what
i
thank you
it's the only thing i can say really
because
what the actual
okay well that's big
um so many town also made a collection
of like just um art and oh there's a
sexy shot right there um
and like we got a lot of letters as well
which oh it's going really quickly
okay
so we got a little bit of time before
the next totsumachi star so i want to
have a look at these the iso stuff is
amazing
you guys never cease to amaze me you
guys are literally amazing oh whoa okay
[Music]
wait wait never mind put it here okay
look at that oh my god that's amazing yo
i want to use that that's like that's
like a magazine cover right there
[Music]
keep being wholesome the queen of chaos
happy birthday thank you
oh my gosh solo oh my god i want to be
able to read all these messages uh i'll
read them after i swear
happy birthday thank you literally bae
you're insignificant here okay you can
just be small there you go
oh my god it's so cute
[Music]
i went down i went
oh my god
thank you so much for the uh thank you
for everything
[Music]
thank you
we got the cake
[Music]
i'll read that later happy birthday
question mark thank you i love the
question more thank you
oh me sleeping
that was actually me yesterday night i
was sleeping at the table oh thank you
[Music]
happy birthday so many signatures thank
you
oh my god it's so cute
yo oh my god what is that homemade
bruh i see the mask as well
it's so good
i love this one the bows let's freaking
go
taco juice
bruh
oh that's so cute
oh my god thank you guys so much
thank you
[Music]
wait is that it
that could be the right file hold on
oh here we go there's like messages hold
on happy birthday thank you so much for
being the amazing rat i wish you
happiness because you deserve
thank you there are a lot of i know
there are a lot of um what do you call
it
a lot of birthday letters um i would
definitely definitely definitely read
them all
i'll definitely re read them all
ah that's not what i want
no that's not what i want sorry i'm cut
help i'm cut
where am i where did i go
everybody help me everybody i'm not okay
there we go i'm not okay i'll go cut i
just there's too much for me to handle
[Music]
chaos i'm breaking the dimensions i
really am i'm gonna keep that at the
back because this is amazing
can i have a real talk with you okay can
we stop the music for a second honestly
i don't think i have ever received so
much
love at one time
in my entire life
and i just i
i
am absolutely
flabbergasted at just how much
you know
how many people really support me
because you know a lot of times i'm just
doing
my streams and you know there's always a
number there but
you know in order to be able to
do this sign of you can't really look at
numbers that much right so like the
number just it doesn't mean anything
um and
a lot of unless you see that number like
in person you know because like
that's a lot of people
but that's that's a lot of people
um and i just want to say thank you so
much for supporting me um
it really means the world
oh i just i'm not used to like so much
so much support um because i'm literally
just
doing whatever but
thank you guys
i
appreciate every single one of you um
and if the day ever comes i want to be
able to say that you know
to you guys directly
you know
um
i love you all
now this is a very sentimental moment
but unfortunately
i need to go use
uh i need to go to an idol meeting
look guys
it's a birthday stream nothing has
changed okay look i i gotta go to and
i'll be right back
[Music]
do
i am back
[Music]
i'm back
um
so um
it is now come the time for the second
round of totsamatias
and if you're hearing my voice shake
it's it's your imagination okay
okay it's just your imagination
do we understand each other
okay
all right
do we understand each other i hope we
understand each other
all right
[Music]
i'm not nervous you're nervous
where do all my presents go there's one
there
um birthday card
okay
i'll put this one up here
all right
let me see anything no i'm not okay
[Music]
and then
who's at the door
whoa we got a pretty cool looking person
let's get it
[Music]
happy birthday
to
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
today
what food are you
favorite food favorite food favorite
food
favorite food
oh cheese
[Music]
oh
is that you are energetic and
be vicious
[Music]
and powerful
powerful powerful
whoa mom pretty
oh
sorry
[Music]
[Laughter]
red hair big eyes upbeat voice
okay okay
okay very good
thank you yeah
thank you
[Music]
wow
that was um hika senpai
i'm so nervous i haven't i've never
spoken to him before and i was really
really glad that he reached out and said
yes uh okay
what we've got you know the cool people
after cool people coming in hi
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
video
uh
[Music]
oh my god it's so cute
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh cooled out no i gave him a tick
that's so rude don't bully the birthday
girl
um and speaking of um
hi hey
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
i'm
fine shut up okay we're good all right
hi
we're gonna keep going hi hi
hito uh
yeah so meeting you or talking to you me
too
[Music]
yeah i am imposter
no no
[Music]
happy birthday to you
happy birthday to a child
[Music]
is
friendship achieved yes yeah different
friendship long friendship big
friendship
yeah
[Music]
you were very great in japanese
experiences
tell me the art of ice oh learning
english
oh
[Music]
so if you want to improve english
speaking
[Music]
of
is
foreign
she's so cute i'm gonna die
chan is best girl actually she does so
much she's so cute and i just scored a
coffee date i'm just winning
[Laughter]
i'm just winning
actually just winning let's freaking go
happy birthday chun
i'm an imposter it's actually her
birthday today so
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
thank you
um
[Music]
hey
wow
[Music]
foreign
um
oh
[Music]
boom boom one after the yellow we got so
many guests
here
[Music]
wow
yo
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
what is your favorite game
favorite game
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
yes
destroyer
[Music]
foreign
i feel like time is going by so quickly
i want to talk to them more
bro
move the hunter
[Music]
[Applause]
a
foreign
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
is
who's next
[Music]
thank you so much i have a gift for you
please accept it thank you sorry just
burped
thank you thank you
[Music]
oh i thought that was the gift
[Laughter]
wait do i just screenshot the ah okay
thank you
[Laughter]
thank you it's based on our beautiful
memories oh beautiful
beautiful memories oh yes oh yes yes
happy birth yes oh beautiful yeah
absolutely happy stunning happy birth
yes thank you i hope you like it
i love it
thank you
how's the party been so far
amazing everybody is too sweet too nice
to me i don't deserve it
no it's your day it's your day you
deserve all the love
you just do it
no no no no but anyways yeah i really
really really really like your
i don't know
when i when i first when i first saw you
i was like
wow
this rat
is interesting interesting as in like
you know
you're cute you know i think everybody's
saying you're cute
but then you know no no no cause like
you're one of the ones who are like in a
good way like super chatty and nice and
i'm like wow this rat is so wholesome
i love
you
yeah i had a lot of fun talking with you
and also about that picnic one again
thanks bro thanks bro yo you really
helped me out there thank you
yeah
man
we need to play together so i feel like
i feel the same about you it's like it
was so just instant click it was just so
easy to talk to you so you were amazing
too um
i mean you kind of already answered the
question but um
yeah do you have another question okay
um
how would you describe me in three words
hmm
you're
you're like i said you're a wholesome
nutritious no i mean because there's
like the cheese on your nutritious
and
also
uh what's a good last what's a good last
keyword
your
fireworks when i see you it reminds me
of fireworks just cuz how
explosive
you are explosive explosive oh by the
way your original song is a banger logo
thank you so much
thank you yeah
yeah i love it
but yeah you really look like a you know
a ball of energy but that there's also
that little dash of wholesomeness so
it's really complicated to describe with
words but yeah i hope you have a
wonderful wonderful wonderful wonderful
day let's do something yeah we should we
we should we definitely should
i know sometimes soon
sometimes dude of course i'm always you
know i'm always you know a dm away okay
yeah
yay
[Music]
slide into the dms actually
thank you rey nay i love you
[Music]
oh we got next person as well hello
hello
[Music]
can you hear my voice clearly because
right now i'm not in front of my pc i
got black out oh
that's okay that's okay
thank you so much for coming
happy birthday
thank you
well it's so weird how like our
positions changed it was like how was
that yo tsumati while like not that long
ago and now you're at mine
yes
anyway anyway um
i have i have a gift for you a plan
yeah i have a present
it's a really really uh
you have to use it i have to use it okay
yes you have to use it i have to use it
i i
i make it by myself
it's reminding me uh of you i i usually
have uh my version is called muntato
because it's a potato but for you it's a
cheese soap
cheese
oh my god
this is the most beautiful thing i've
ever seen in my life
oh my god
yes
hello
thank you so much
that's that's really sweet
thank you thank you i will use this this
bed thank you i will use this for the
rest of the stream and also for the
karaoke tonight this is wonderful thank
you so much i love it
thank you so much it actually fits
perfectly oh my god
yeah it works perfectly right yeah i
know
it's beautiful and beautiful thank you
thank you so much um i got a question
for you
okay question for you um so
what was your first impression of me
um
i talk you're gonna be
so loud
loud louder but
um after time by time i
i don't think so
like um
i thought you're gonna be just like
as loud as only oh uh-huh uh-huh
it's like oh this is gonna be gonna be
as crazy as holy uh
probably louder but apparently
rather than loud it's just cute i feel
like you're cute thank you i mean i feel
like i am pretty loud sometimes um but
yeah thank you
thank you i can't get over it oh my god
it fits me so much
like it just sprayed me as loud as as a
as a rat
look at the face
oh that's amazing amazing
thank you so much for stopping by
thank you happy birthday i hope i hope
the lights get come back on soon thank
you so much yeah thank you anyway your
your new
music original music it's better i love
it thank you
uh you're you're on this banger too bruh
you're you're your new ops banger
together yeah
we should
okay my time probably gonna round out in
a few minutes so thank you so much thank
you for coming
bye bye bye
i'm just winning i can't stop winning
today holy moly bruh actually
this is the most beautiful thing look my
face fits perfectly competition
[Music]
hello
hello are you
are you the agent of chaos i have been
searching for that is i
hello yes
now it is time for us
to meet it's time for the first time
hello the legion of holly rodents
continues
yay
hi
nice to meet you i mean i've talked to
you before but nice to meet you yes nice
to meet you my fellow rat i am so
jealous i can't roll my eyes
let no
i'll i'll i'll roll the r for you oh my
god it sounds so good thank you so much
please continue rolling i can't how do i
do it
no
i'll do it like this like
[Music]
i'm so jealous
thank you so much for stopping by
finally happy birthday although i can't
really prepare anything but no don't
worry though here's the thing about bae
she's so sweet even though she's the one
um
who has birthday today she gave
us um a present beforehand so
ah
no it's just something stupid something
silly something stupid something silly
don't worry about it
don't worry about it thank you and happy
birthday thank you thank you so much
um i have question for you
all right question um
if you could ask me anything what would
you ask me you know since like this is
technically the first time we're talking
to you what would you want to know about
me you have the power in your hands
okay if i have the power in my hand
i would actually
ask you for a date
yes
because
i love cute girls
i'm going to ask her for a date
sometimes so
would you like to go on a date
sure
that sounds amazing pog answer okay
plug answer yeah of course where are we
going to know uh because to know
someone's better we should go on a date
first so where should we go where are we
going
i'll leave that as a surprise yeah okay
okay well i'll be waiting
you know
rodents that stick together you know
stay together
yes right we wrote in scottish together
yes
we may be small but together we are
forced that no one can ever come come
come come
no one can defeat yes that's the word i
was looking for
but thank you so much thank you so much
for coming
thank you for inviting me
happy birthday
thank you
thank you sorry i'm literally trying oh
my god wait she left already oh it might
i'm trying not to move my face because
literally it looks so freaking funny
like this i can't
this looks so freaking funny
bro
thanks ladies to send bye
i haven't really talked into this
descent by too much um but that's gonna
change because she just asked me on a
date bruh can you be as smooth as this
am i also just winning
i feel like i haven't stopped winning
ever since this second um second collar
second block started i mean i was
winning beforehand but now i'm really
winning holy moly okay
um
next person
moshi moshe
[Music]
huh
okay oh my god okay i'm ready
uh
[Music]
oh
hi
oh my god i just died and went to heaven
go to heaven i am in heaven
stay
[Laughter]
[Music]
yes
so
cute
and
very kind
[Music]
message and your
like
talk to me
thank you
i
love
your personality oh
thank you thank you
thank you
[Music]
i
wanna try my best
for
speak english
because you
yeah you're doing great
thank you she's so sweet amazing
beautiful you already know japanese is
so good no
no not no no no no no no no no
thank you thank you welcome
we should do um
i know callie had the english speaking
collab and stuff we should do english so
we can collab soon as well
[Music]
[Laughter]
i can't wait hey pretty good yeah thank
you it's pretty good can't wait okay
[Laughter]
hi i'm looking forward to talk with you
and travel with you yeah
you're welcome
your original song is very good thank
you
thank you i
repeat
more wow thank you
hi
mom
[Music]
thank you
and guys
that leaves us with
[Music]
a final guest
i can't believe it oh my god we've
called everyone
and honestly i'm very excited for this
last guest
because i have not spoken to her before
and
i really really wanted to okay
so just prepare yourselves
[Music]
nice to meet you nice to meet you
ah happy not birthday
thank you thank you thank you
oh yes my
[Music]
um
is
[Music]
m
i wanna
um
she's so
cute i can't handle she is so cute
um
oh my that i
i have no words
[Music]
oops
uh i was just instantly absolutely i
don't know what happened um hold on i
need to add this again
i was look guys i am absolutely
i can't i just
i am overwhelmed with all the love
what was that i don't know it was gifts
um but thank you guys so much
i
this has been probably one of the most
memorable days ever since i started
streaming um and it's not even my
birthday
so that was amazing thank you to
everyone who called in
[Music]
so
uh thank you to everyone who
participated um
thank you so much for calling in and
please do grab a goodie bag on your way
out which is available in the server
i hope you guys enjoy oh my god i can't
believe it's over also don't forget the
collab promises guys i will hold them
until you know to the grave okay
happy not birthday thank you guys
guys thank you so much i am absolutely
i.e
it's been amazing also
i've just been informed that the mb has
already
passed
k are 100k
serious
are you serious
oh my god
that's amazing
oh my god that's amazing
thank you so much thank you i'm gonna
actually cry um but it's not the end so
we still got a lot more coming um
so just to
um
refresh everybody's mind about the
announcements we go merch yo we got
merch um
we've got merch and we've also got
[Music]
we've got stream the song stream
available also i don't know what's
happening in the screen anymore there's
a lot going on okay i'll put this over
here um so we've got a karaoke uh stream
tonight which is just me getting drunk
and singing karaoke for you guys
counting down until uh play dice is
available on streaming services and also
counting down until the merch is
available as well
please
please post the link to the next stream
oh i haven't made it yet
i haven't made it yet guys i'm sorry
okay um i'm gonna spend probably the
next like six hours um staring at the
ceiling in absolute shock and the
bewilderment uh thank you thanking each
and every
uh
every every person that came to my
stream today uh
and also just
just
i'm i'm lagging i'm actually my brain is
lagging i can't
this is why i am i
time and time again i'm just amazed at
you know the support in this community
and i am
thank you thank you so much will the
karaoke karaoke stream be archived yes
it will be
yes it will be um and then i'll also be
spending a lot of time reading through
the letters that you guys sent me and
and and the amazing art and and i just i
love you guys i really do
i really really love you guys so much
[Music]
so
i can finally say this now stream play
dice guys i can't believe i can say it
already
[Music]
i am too blessed i don't deserve this
this is amazing thank you guys so much
thank you
i will get going now and
eat some food stare at the ceiling
ponder about life
cry a bit
thank you
this has been the best birthday ever
i'll see you in a couple hours
also
a stream play dice
all right
bye bye
bye
[Music]
you