[Music]
do
good morning afternoon evening
it's taco time
and it's also lunch time i was eating my
lunch
hi
how are you guys
how am i doing um not 100 but i'm still
alive
not 100 but i'm still alive i don't know
what it is with my room but the
temperatures are all over the place like
even when i had my computer on for a
while um
yesterday my room was completely
freezing
um
i don't know why so
my nose is a bit runny
and now that i have the heater on i have
a heat pack on me and
everything else it's kind of
it's kind of okay i guess
yeah
i might be casting a coat i don't know
where is it running too
it it's running too
devoid
but yeah
it's so weird because if if the
temperature changes a lot like this i
usually do catch a cold
because my body's just like oh it's hot
okay i'll be ready no it's cold okay
i'll be ready oh it's hot i'll be ready
and it gets really tired and then and
then the cold is just like hey
may i come in
yeah
so
am i sick no my nose is just ready
i'm not coughing or anything it's just
my nose is running along
[Laughter]
i'm joking
all my food
okay that was my lunch
i had really
i had really um spicy
chicken
what is this like chicken
stew thing
it had a lot of peppers in it
you know when when your food is really
really spicy
and you inhale it you're just like
and then it just goes
in your in your breathing
breathing tube and i just like oop okay
you know actually i finally became
myself taco at january 1st i can still
remember the moment i joined the
membership if you allow my queen might
still be one of the taco community
members of course and you don't even
have to pay
you're always welcome here and with same
with everyone everyone is always welcome
as long as i'm streaming you guys can be
always free to join us whenever you want
no voice chat today oh i will be joining
voice chat in a little bit
um just be sitting there if people want
to join they can they can hop in but
if not they don't have to
i literally just told everyone like
right before the stream started so
usually a lot of people are asleep at
this hour
will i be playing with people not too
much today
because i played with you guys
for the last couple of um practice
streams
i want to practice some
shortcuts
and actually find some shortcuts that i
can practice
uh while racing against some ghosts
there are a few tracks that i really
need to improve on like ribbon road um
so i'll be working on those
and uh yeah just some refining time
because i have a
i have another collab tomorrow with some
uh members
across the branches
oh yeah so i guess i'll kind of see
where i stand roughly
um with everyone uh
i haven't played with before actually a
lot of them so
yeah
you do hold on minecraft minecraft
minecraft
mario kart
can i play against other whole members
schools if i have a friends list i do
see some of them
um but not all of them
like for example i wonder if there's
anyone who has
ribbon road where's ribbon road
it's on the one
track that i'm really bad there we
go i should be good with ribbon rope
because i was on the game boy
i mean i can't even win against
see like
okay i i didn't know what against that
question
uh the
the time difference between
[Music]
me and aqua senpai is a little
it's a little
um
i don't i don't think i'm getting that
so let's uh maybe start with another
maybe there's some that i have not
beaten yet
okay there's this one
oh i guess not many people uploaded it
to this one
i beaten cheeky i did
oh yeah i beat sana's record too i think
ah
two seconds are up
is a little busy you know preparing for
a concert but you never know you never
know
i need some practice with this too
actually look at my score look at my
score
i think it's a little rough
yeah okay i think this one i can work on
definitely
i have oli
and sana to be
huh
hey you never know with aqua senpai she
might practice a little bit off stream
and she'll be de-rusted like no problem
yeah
okay maybe i'll start with this
it's always
i want to view the ghost first actually
the nintendo ghost oh
i didn't do very well
um
i was bumping into stuff
yeah
okay i'm just watching right now this is
the ghost my hands are off i'm not
driving
the nintendo ghost isn't even drifting
is that the
are they using tele controls
[Music]
i'm being beaten but
health controls
[Music]
not drifting just following the road
oh
the ghosts are terrible apparently i'm
worse because i haven't beaten them yet
[Music]
okay there's always that branch that you
gotta jump using the mushrooms
oh and this one okay
on the second lap they use it on this
one
oh
[Music]
i'm really bad at picking up coins here
so i guess technically this part is
actually
pretty hey it's not using the
thing on this one is saving for the last
because of the twisty turns i think it's
really
really nice to be able to jump that
coins are important so i got i got to
figure out how to get as many coins as
possible though i feel like in the
actual race like i lose so many coins
even if i get oh
what
it's just showing me all the different
different ways to uh use the mushroom
actually not too bad okay don't come on
stop stop
okay
face against ghost okay
i see i see
[Music]
i feel like that's the middle part is
definitely
worth
um
hey i want to get going
oh
okay right here
now drift here
zoom
hi my name is
i miss all the coins
i
hi
oh i'm so bad at this part
oh maybe on the second lap i can take
that
[Music]
okay i got two
oh yeah
okay i gotta make sure i land properly
there
okay
then go go
okay i missed that
i can get that boost
um
okay i don't touch that
it's much
ah the right side okay there's a little
bit of boost at the end
i still only have six coins why am i so
bad
[Music]
maybe that's not the spot
uh-huh
[Music]
i'm already
i'm already done
i'm already slower than my last record
and there's a little bit of bump here i
can get a small bit of boost
oh come on
oh it is a new record how slow was i
i lost okay second lap i was faster
i lost a lot of time in the first lap um
i can improve my third lap definitely
the second laptop
[Music]
practice going left at the sand pit
okay
don't over shift
try again
you know
knowing what to do is one thing actually
being able to execute it is another okay
so no matter how much you yell at me
[Music]
i might not know
i missed all the coins yay
ow okay
[Music]
it's going a lot better
the last shortcut is better
so like this part oh so where you come
out of here and you just zoom over oh
no
oh i'm just i'm just driving on the sand
now this is one of my weak maps i
thought
[Music]
huh
hey i got two
how's they turn so well
[Music]
just like slow down not accelerate
it was right here
and i needed to make time okay
yeah i'll take this coin
okay
okay so the thing about breaking while
drifting right
um
is it a little tap because if i press
break too long then it like
stops the
okay i almost clapped i almost cut up
okay
yeah i'll look at chad after i need to
focus focus opina
okay i can't beat the ghost
okay
i beat the ghost but
um
but
the
the um what's it the
oh man i was i made it for a lot of time
at the very end huh i was late on both
oh the second one i was a little faster
but
but um
the break like if you hold it too long
you lose your drift right or can you
hold it like how do you
how do you
how do you do it
[Music]
no break on drift it's bad in 150 okay
just tap it right
okay so it is just a tap i have been
practicing a little bit on some tight
corners
yeah okay um
[Music]
i wanna i wanna practice against some of
the ghosts
brake drift is only in 200 ah
i know about the um if you hit hard
right hard left you get more more um
drift boosting
i didn't know about it right
i told you it's one thing knowing about
it and another thing actually being able
to carry it out
i do want to see a different ghost for
this one though
let's see is there like a not not too
fast
i feel like all of these will take like
the same route
should i should i
should i look for a sub two minute
um
go with the first
always go to first
okay world record all right
i want to see it i just want to see what
the time difference is
learn from the best oh they're using a
different cart
maybe this is the car to go for this map
huh
[Music]
way
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
um
i don't think i can
oh
yeah
[Music]
how
just drift bro
okay
well i hope i'm not racing against this
ghost
i am
what happened
yes
[Music]
fine it's fine it's completely fine
wait they went like here
and they went like a boost here
and like oh
[Music]
i don't understand
i have a feeling they're gonna like lap
around
for me
like
like very soon
they went like this and they're like
here and they boosted and they put stuff
[Music]
yeah the ghost disney
you wish you wish
oh my god wait i'm not in the voice chat
yeah i forgot
ah
hold on
uh
you know let me race you just go home
welcome home
let's
i'm on my phone because i moved my
switch over to my to my bedroom to my
big tv and i've been playing there today
it's really cool i think i'm gonna play
the tournament from beds as well oh
that's five eight don't fall asleep
if you start running into the wall i'll
know i'm dead uh-huh
i stay in bed and i erase a little bit
and i just turned the tv off and i go
back to sleeping
so if you um start running into the wall
you're gonna end up with a zucker cup
uh that's okay too
that's okay okay i made a room if you
wanna join me is it just gonna be us or
is it gonna be other people too it's
gonna be me you and the cp youth
okay
let me get coffee under my blanket
oh i hope you don't hear wait i'll turn
it down a little bit
oh you're gonna be playing the music huh
that's fine i have the
i have it all on blast
you hear me well yes i can hear you
okay
uh
oh wait i need to get out of my own cups
oh oh golden golden
oh golden award from the last one i
played oh
you hear that very good very good
okay okay but you sent it to me and on
where
oh
yeah just to join the friends yeah okay
okay okay
comfy racing
uh
online play how's it going in yeah
pretty good
that was you in like
5 000 years of practice
oh don't underestimate me girl
all right all right all right i'll see
what you're made of love right now even
my final form i still don't have the
cards that i want to go with i just
laughed into my coffee and the sheer
force of the last splash
[Music]
oh no coffee on my keyboard what am i
gonna do
no no no no
because no 150 no teams hard to come
all vehicles
um
four races just four weeks is good
i guess okay
i i don't i don't think you can take
more than that enough
you're going to cry
i'm sure about that okay okay
i mean in that in that desperate map
where you just wear in i think i'm
better than you oh really let's go
i think
oh oh but i didn't i didn't warm up
yet so let's go let's go
[Laughter]
oh random i see you're there are you
chicken are you chicken
i need to warm up
are you chicken or you're we're warming
up in a nice desert okay no problem nice
and warm no problem
no probably you're gonna
[Music]
all right all right teach me your ways
oh i see you changed your car mm-hmm
no i this is still the same i don't have
i want
the one that you got oh i see i see it
when you beat me just now at the girls
you didn't have that uh
how's that
maybe it really was kiara
let's go
there's a rule of thumb in mario kart
it's never good to go first
i've been underestimated
right behind you
[Music]
yeah i see a cute butt
was mine
oh i felt it i definitely felt it
bullying me now oh no that's so good
[Music]
not cool
who was there
who was that
not me not me misha
[Music]
you see me
yeah
okay
easily
no
no no
i'm never number one in your heart am i
oh
[Music]
mama
what i did not throw that i did not
throw it
oh come on
that was me
i hope you like that one i do not
okay
oh yeah yeah yeah
you're catching up catching up
it's just a matter of items if i had a
better item at the end i could have
gotten ready
[Laughter]
i don't know about that i don't know
about that
what shall we do next
oh i'm just think random now
if there's one that you have to practice
make sure uh you can feel like
[Music]
oh do not
do
planes oh okay
don't not playing around
[Music]
oh
we got the same item
[Music]
did you say bye because i was going
ahead
i was ahead of you for one second
it's good enough for me uh-huh
[Music]
i've been
i've been when i was practicing today
and yesterday i've been paying more
attention to collecting money now oh
really it's really important so
yeah
wait how did lincoln afford me
not for long
oh
oh no oh no
i couldn't see
where are you
uh
okay there's a there's a shortcut here
[Music]
oh no
hey you're still there you're still
third
yeah
no
oh i think
i bet zelda call or something
to get to the finish line
well well well he's a quick guy
he's not the hero for no reason
[Music]
oh
we should
focus about this time
[Music]
oh
look at me again
[Music]
how's the viewing up
uh
nice yeah it's pretty good
[Music]
it's
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
i see
you oh no no no no no please no no no no
no no
[Music]
okay i'm still ahead i'm still ahead i
can i can do this
oh is that your shell
yeah
good
[Music]
i love how the music goes like really
weird too to be honest
wait is that link again oh no
that's you
i swallow
oh no oh
oh that's too unfortunate isn't it
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
oh it didn't hit me it didn't hit me at
all
i think it might have hit link
i although i was i was number one for
quite some time
oh yeah you're getting there you're
de-rusting being rusty
and i haven't even practiced that much
yet i haven't done i want to do the the
the ghost time races
and i also want to look up at least some
shortcuts
i think the only ones i remember like
the ones i grinded on stream otherwise i
like don't remember
one of the few ones that i know is the
one from yoshi's island but
yoshi's island really confuses me
because there's so many routes you can
take
so many i don't know
like one side cut
oh no like like there's like different
branches that you can take right
oh come on
[Music]
i'm really bad at this part of big flu i
need to practice this
[Music]
i didn't faze me at all
let's see
oh i'm still number one
what is going on you know what is going
on
oh oh come on was that you was that
my mom was that my boss and gotcha no
that was my bug
no
oh come on
oh
there was a blue shell but i blocked it
nice i had to ride him in just like
a moment before
where's the moment i fell down you're
getting a little bit ahead now i guess
oh
are you still first
cuz i'm like fourth person oh god
no hey no no
okay
[Music]
oh what what is this a golden trophy
mine beautiful rose gold okay rose gold
rose
i know the difference between rose gold
and bronze of course of course
[Laughter]
do i need to leave uh no you're not
coming in here no i don't i don't see
anyone
can we do four more yeah if you want to
i was just gonna train against ghosts
for the entire stream if no one came
around
okay
all right same foreign
[Laughter]
let's go
what will it be
what will it be oh also not oh are you
also not planning to stream the
tournament i feel like no one from myth
is streaming it
i feel like everyone she doesn't want us
to be and i think callie also said she
is not going to stream it's not sure
it's already free people
yeah exactly that's probably why
they don't want to stream
i understand
[Music]
i have so many bad memories on this
track oh really
it was when you're playing in your
viewers
yeah
[Music]
not today
cause you're in the anti-gravity mug
[Music]
at least now i can uh keep up with you
yeah exactly you are improving
you kicked my ass by the npc's oh no
you can kick them back
[Music]
oh
okay
[Music]
oh come on
that wasn't even you kiara that was the
animal crossing villager i can't get to
the front anymore
you can do it don't give up
[Music]
it's not fair back here the front is
more peaceful
[Music]
what the hell
that was just unlucky yeah that was that
was oh you're also pretty far back that
was unlucky i got like unlucky at the
end
let me try it
i tried it yeah i was like sixth and
seventh and i still only got shitty
items
i guess it's like sometimes like when
the first place is like really really
ahead and they get you get like really
good items even if you're like pretty
high up but
apparently some people said that but is
that not just a myth for a holo myth
[Music]
i don't know
second
okay i just gotta beat that
animal crossing villager
[Music]
that's what it is
just gotta get that back drift yeah
do that oh i didn't get the silence
oh yeah
fine
i got a shell that's good
rejected
the present you're used to it
[Music]
i hope you're not right behind me
okay
okay i'm so far ahead oh
did you get a blue shell
no
maybe it was
maybe it was just chance that i didn't
block that one shell because the blue
one was going oh
[Music]
why
all according to keikaku are you okay
what's going on
you take like the uh the shortcut but it
wasn't really the shortcut it was
actually a road to nowhere oh i was
trying to take the shortcut once so and
then
just test it and i realized okay i need
a i need a speed item for that and then
later you know the part where you
get
[Music]
the same one again
oh yeah okay yeah fly i was i was taking
off but then even though i didn't get
hit by an item it let me like drop to
the oh you have to like steer so make
sure you like don't fall all the way oh
was i staring too low maybe yeah
it might have been pointing down kind of
automatically when you fly
i never realized you had to steer all
like i mean maybe for some of them to if
there's like a choice like in some maps
there's choice between
two different places to land on uh-huh
but i didn't realize for that one
[Music]
you know when you fly a paper airplane
and like
like aim it like up and it goes a little
like higher
and then it goes a little further down
oh
i'm never good at taking this you could
put paper airplane in here
i've made some good ones before
[Music]
but um they haven't gone that far
i've seen some that go like super fast
and super far
but i've never tried to make them myself
because i don't really go outside to
test them out
that was me
don't worry i received the gift very
nicely um
it shattered on the way though blame the
delivery
it's chatter yeah
oh
i did not throw that shell i think my i
think my left bumper is broken
let's probably use the trigger button
sometimes i don't release the button
really
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
is right on my tail
i'm fine
do you like banana
no do you like no banana
no
no banana
i hate potassium
oh we might have a second guess she
might not be joining the voice chat but
she might be doing the race
oh
cool
uh highlives number one detective
yeah
okay i don't know if she's joining the
next one or can she join mid-race
together is she doing mid-range let's do
it i wonder
[Music]
oh oh
it's starting okay oh she can she can do
in the next one
yeah
she's she's apparently wrapped up nice
and tight in the burrito in bed
yay i'm tori burritos
burritos
it's comfy
the best way to play mario kart or any
game at all i'm actually kind of wrapped
up in blankets myself except it's just
my bottom half i'm not fully covered up
in blanket sadly i wish i was
yes you know let's do this let's party
[Music]
i missed
you know which side is better here is
there a better side i don't know which
color you're comfortable with i think
as i get them you know
[Music]
oh come on
did i hit you
it was shorter for me to let's play okay
[Music]
come on mario you can get her oh mario
got himself
oh
oh come on
that is unfair
[Music]
still number one
how does it feel
wonderful yes
it's it's like how the world is supposed
to be it feels right
i see number one fast cool chain in the
world ksp kfc
oh that was not me
i'm really bad at using the boomerang
though
yeah that one is i don't enjoy that item
either
it only hits when someone's like
insanely close to you yeah i think
i see you above me yeah
oh
above this yeah because your your track
is like oh you took that i took the
green one you took the other one
oh thanks for taking that away from me
[Music]
decent i'm i just want to be decent and
i'm decent right now so i'm happy
you did it well you're pissed
off now not even getting rose gold
really you got the participation prize
there she is
a man
i'm using tokens
that's lame
let's go okay you ready for four more
kiara
i wonder how good emma is but yeah i'm
ready maybe she's been grinding off
stream
yeah
on 50 60 race no teams
normal items
hard to calm
all vehicles
four races
okay random and three cuties
and three cuties
[Music]
[Laughter]
you know
you know it's okay
mummy
yo she is like
oops i got no boost yoshi's like
maybe like one of my top three favorite
characters
oh
he is cute
how did you how do you always have
something to block my you know
i don't know it's orangey
fun
[Music]
i missed all the coins okay
hi
[Music]
okay okay
oh god
[Applause]
[Music]
she also do something stupid yeah
justin
[Applause]
oh my god
i did it
oh
that was really unfortunate for you
though to bump into my green shell that
i had in my box oh yeah
if it weren't for that then you might
have been number one after
a
i i messed up a lot in the start
wait what place was almost almost sixth
apparently
okay okay
okay you know she said she just woke up
she said i can't even open both eyes so
she was playing with one eye what is
that
just awoken that tired okay
let's give her a break then
she's playing with one eye until
controls oh man
and that's my controls that's even worse
no i'm kidding what the tail controls
who knows
she's playing blindfolded with her feet
exactly
wow
[Music]
maybe she learned that from guru
speaking of good though we might have
our joining the next round maybe
next already did you say so
yeah like like the next round of four
races
oh my god
it's gonna be a party
a party
hey
why why
why nice uh nice boost there
oh
the npc just
i miss
what
okay
it's always this part with the weird
sound
[Music]
i should have gone for that double box
i missed my chance
[Music]
oh my god
okay nice
items yeah or lack of items i guess for
me
okay
[Music]
oh no
my lucky streak is ruined
[Music]
oh
i hear the blue show
it's coming from me
it is
oh my god okay
it's okay
[Music]
finally caught up a little bit
ah
i missed the job not a second
[Music]
okay nice over
oh oh that was lucky that was so
lucky oh my goodness
what happened so there was an npc in
front of me right there was a ramp
that was supposed to take
and um the nbc just got on the ramp when
they got
lightning so i didn't have to get
lightning
that was unlucky
i had a red shell and a and a speed
mushroom so first of all
and then i speeded
okay
i stole it
it's all good it's all good
all good in the neighborhood wait it's
not it's good at joining now uh no no
because there's a set of four tracks
so yeah yeah she can't she can join
after this one this is the fourth one
yeah
who is she going to join
huh
i think she's just gonna play from her
bed too no problem why is everyone
playing from their bed right now
i mean i i mean it's usually their like
wake up time where they're like
just getting to bed well i don't
honestly this is the first time i
brought my switch to my bed since like
i'm always too lazy to disconnect it
from my
uh
[Laughter]
yeah i was thinking about getting a
second one too just forget one of those
like oled switches you know
i guess but with that that one can't
stop right no it's a normal switch it
just has a oh let's scream
it's only the switch light that can't
stop i think
oh
okay
i remember i practiced this course a
little bit with the ghost
it was really hard what did the ghost do
something interesting
oh my god that
is that ominous
no that's an npc
you at least
somewhere behind you oh an npc just fell
into the
into
nowhere oh no
oh no
no
oh my god
i think i bumped into almond then i
couldn't slide
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah i gotta remember not to
[Music]
i can never take that shortcut it's
really hard
[Music]
no
blue shell oh come on
nice
oh come on maybe some time to catch up
so nbc
still a chance to win
i can't see anything that's right scared
to take that shortcut at the end the one
with the big jump right around yeah
do you need a speed item for that no i
mean you can i think you can like jump
over
like a little hop over like a little bit
of grass at the start but i've never
been able to do it
[Music]
oh my god
another blue shell come on enlightening
oh my god they're kidding me what around
oh my god i got two blue shells like two
lightning
i don't
[Music]
even know
it's okay you're right beside me
where was that
[Music]
what was that
that was rough
that was a cursed round
that was okay oh i guess we have oh
there's gura
oh yeah well if she's also not joining
worcester then i'm gonna stay to keep
you company oh thank you
it was gonna be like exactly like like
um racing with the ghosts
except it's live
[Laughter]
we are here for you yeah
yellow ghost
you have real friends you know you don't
have to imagine you're not a ghost
i'm not imagining oh good at once
not again that one
girl just wants practice on this yeah
yeah it's good
[Music]
i guess i could technically just like
have a lot of races and then
you can leave whenever
yeah this this track is like so
hard though
yeah we're warmed up but they need to
warm up
did you fail the boost again at the
start
yeah i did
[Music]
that's him
mom is warmed up now
yeah right behind you right behind you
nice nice banana
i feel like i can just hear on my screen
she slipped to my banana
[Music]
you keep confident
okay it's okay
like that the lightning got rid of all
the small like bats in the cave though
that's good i have to bump into them
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
banana peel
man this race is tough with all the
girls in here
my one defense item against blue shells
[Music]
apparently you can dodge a blue shell
every time like pixel perfect the boot
like the mushroom boost
what
no it's like a
it's like a
what's it
it's not a feature but like you can
technically like outspeed it
when it explodes or something
technically the
what's it the the shell is exploding
right
it's a feature
it's a mechanic that's what i meant to
say not a feature
it's the miracle that i ended up being
forced because i was behind everybody
for most of the time oh no it's a
miracle
oh man what happened
rng oh i got so much trophy oh
it's not the white gold
okay
well then our g r g was uh not kinda
okay i'm gonna keep doing the tracks um
i guess i'll tell them particularly
whenever i'll do 12 i guess
uh
doing 12 races you can leave whenever
you feel like
it
okay
this is some good practice you know
last minute practice i wonder how i'm
gonna do yeah it's definitely different
to practice against you know you girls
than practicing against cpus
yeah it's different than play against
viewers sometimes the viewers they
like they show no mercy at all
some of them are really really really
good so
yeah
myth racing team let's go you know what
what is that um tv supposed to be on
your screen oh it's the it shows the
placement because you know my my model
is kind of
blocking like the placement so it's like
a different tv that shows
my placement yeah
i see i see
oh baby rays bubble bubbles
how
this is just random orangey
um
[Applause]
[Music]
there's a chance that might have been my
own
banana
see this is like really orangy uh this
course
[Music]
hey
i just don't want to bump into anything
i don't think that's working
[Applause]
i want to pull it bill
[Music]
[Applause]
i just really hope i don't get this
track like during the during the match
oh my god
are you first
fallen behind due to unlucky
circumstances oh no
wow
[Music]
nice i didn't
this track goes by so fast i don't even
know if i'm like where i am
of course of course you get a second
wow
oh my god
kfb must be so proud of me right now so
proud
okay
maybe i just need to do better with the
tight corners
yoshi
[Music]
i never realized the yoshi track looked
like yoshi until recently
what
you know what
you need glasses inya
[Music]
i drifted too early i don't know where
to go for this one
exactly this one i don't know
[Music]
i think girl's right behind me i'm
scared
oh my god
oh yeah
i can't believe it i'm number one
oh you're
yep
thank god you're doing well kiara see
the practice is paying off
what
it wasn't even that much practice
[Music]
oh nice touch nice touch
also that banana was you
maybe
[Music]
oh no
oh no i only got one item okay that's
fine that's fine
as long as the boost okay it's good
hello
[Music]
no good enough
we're not going to be driving
i like how everyone just slowed down
oh it's good
okay
we're also close together
oh
i'm missing out i'm missing
get out of the way now
get out of the way
[Laughter]
yeah you're improving so fast kiara i am
proud hell yeah yeah when when we were
all together in one blob uh i got the
speed boost that you get when you come
oh yeah yeah when you're right behind
them
see but there's no like auto chat thing
for it was the ping
ping
oh i'm so bad at
for this one i didn't practice much but
i hope that the ping and that the
connection issues oh that is cute
that is true
i remember during the enid one there was
a little bit of troubles a little bit i
think arena
yeah
once
oh yeah
so i wonder if maybe i hope they thought
about that if they have some rules
because i didn't think about it for my
tournament and then i was like kind of
unprepared
maybe you should ask to watch someone if
she thought about that
it might happen quite often
yeah i guess they don't have that many
troubles like what the gp only but since
it's a a lot of international um
members are playing this
time ahead of me what should i do
um
do your best that's what you should do
nice okay
i think i got someone
[Music]
oh
i'm so far behind no
you can do it
[Music]
oh i missed a boost on both of them
okay i got these two coins i'm back
and full boost nice
oh no girl's right behind me i can feel
it i can smell her press
smell her fishing
oh
do this
no
oh she she just red shelled behind her
gura you
girl are you
oh
oh no kiara oh no
bad luck
it's okay it's okay that was that was a
nice play that's a nice play
oh
go easy on me
on you
you don't need that
i'm using tilt controls
go easy on me
i feel like i feel like twisted mansion
may be like one of gore's best maps
maybe
oh i remember i remember playing against
her
on her stream too
cara's on her phone
that is what she sounds like
oh yes she's wrapped up in blankets
i'm having a nice day off
i wonder what chords will be oh it's
this one
oh this one can get tricky
i feel like we're always getting like
the same ones yeah
i'll choose a different one next time
it's a nice comfy day off for everyone
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah
oh yeah that's good we don't have good
against us at least
i mean it'll be good practice for her
too
to play against us
[Music]
oh
she has something behind her
okay
i missed the coin
oh that was close
[Music]
oh lucia coming from
behind not minded
oh
he's boosting on a head
okay
oh tell me
i can't see for me
oh
she's so far ahead i can't catch up
[Music]
shell towards her way
place too late it's a little too late
i messed up
we have two at least these between me
stupid
oh she's zooming
yeah glitter is getting real good
real good ride
oh i should have chosen something that's
not random uh oh yeah i i i forgot
all right
oh
okay she needs to she needs to show no
mercy for to survive in group b
yes
honestly though group d is pretty scary
too
i think i think oh mario wrong
participants
neil belser city they're still slippery
this truck
[Music]
it's called quickly for me
oh my god
[Music]
yeah
another break
this dip truck is actually really hard
because the rain makes the track
slippery
[Music]
opener
so many bananas
[Music]
doesn't keep falling oaks oh no i
accidentally used my items
oh no
oh not the lightning
[Music]
oh
yeah this is probably one of the tracks
i did practice a little bit with the
ghosts because i kept slipping off them
i practiced it too but that was a
[Music]
that you guys have i still can't get it
um there are because
um there are different like because each
card in character is different stats
right so you can like combine
some of the cards that you probably have
already
to get the similar stat yeah i don't
know which one it is though i think it's
like like
wario
and some other cart too maybe
okay
we haven't done royal raceway before
oh whoops i'm still
i forgot to move my cursor before i
pressed okay
the bike has the same thing standard
bike
[Music]
we had this one before just a little bit
ago oh yeah yeah
[Music]
so many actually this one i need
practice with so it's okay
do your best though
standard bike has the same stats but
wiggler is cuter
apparently yeah
[Music]
i'm gonna
oh i see that banana drop girl
[Music]
was that you
yeah
maybe oh my god girl is so far ahead
what
look at her go
so proud of her
you must have practiced this
you can't decide huh
[Music]
oh this banana is evil
right before the double oh no my
mushroom
i'm gonna take the one that you dropped
okay because okay thank you yeah at
least it's not going to waste yeah don't
drop your trash on the ground guys
find the trash can or find the tiato
it's kind of the same thing
i'm
[Music]
in hi yummy
halloween
[Music]
so far
oh
i think she already went in
[Music]
or she is close to getting in
oh come on
[Music]
i hear someone
this is what happens when you don't look
in your back mirror
that was just lucky though i was just
lucky
nah skill luck is a skill
okay what should we go for someone we
didn't do yet
i'm gonna choose one that we didn't do
yet oh how about this one
oh my god
[Music]
these are too weak for me these
opponents
he's like i'm not going with these
losers okay i need some better rivals
[Laughter]
she's all warmed up now
[Music]
gg gg
good game gargoyle no match
oh no goose for me
i was getting comfy
[Music]
it these tight turns are really hard
i like them
[Music]
i should come to the top
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
oh come on
[Laughter]
you're welcome
[Music]
maybe yeah
oh it's unfortunate
[Applause]
[Music]
there's another one coming
oh come on
wait could have at least put me on the
other side oh come on
[Music]
it's fine
oh
i hear star
that's me
you are my style
oh
my god
[Applause]
[Music]
i'm sorry i'm going to be listening to
this
camera's doing pretty good too
yeah it's doing good much much better
than the uh
what could we do
i think i really wanted to told harbor
so i'll choose that
what
she chose it a couple of times i think
which one uh toad harbor
[Music]
water to something else
you know learning how to drift is hard
um
i tried teaching my family but they
couldn't
oh
[Music]
i'm gonna need a new controller is there
a controller still like the broken one
from like
when she around when she debuted
uh
wait i think she just said something
about that yesterday i listened to her
super chat reading
[Music]
ah why am i drifting so far of course
i'm so bad
oh link
that's my speech
[Music]
okay so the first first trap first trap
still good
i need to learn how to get coins in this
map
really bad that i think i oh
was that yours
oh that was not mine you sure it was oh
i was hit by it just like you
into the water i go
from first to six
oh and second
oh one first ah
i fell in the water
that's where a taco belongs to
excuse me i'm a human
how many times must i tell you
i should have probably gone for that
double item up there oh well
i probably didn't need to go
what drifted wrong
no
okay take this boost take this boost
okay
this is bad
oh i'm is in front of me
[Music]
are you going first are you first kiara
will you make us proud
i hope so but i think they're gonna get
me right at the end i don't think so i'm
pretty far behind
not you that's stupid link uh npc oh
i can never
never expect link
[Music]
oh can i get on it
keep doing link pass
[Music]
[Applause]
before this one
um the cloud top i think
how top cruise no i don't i don't want
that one no
no
no thank you
i can't believe i'm getting first places
here sometimes
[Music]
this track is so difficult
also i drank what's left over of my
lunch and it's so spicy spreading my
throat
what did you burn
it's like a little bit of soup left over
from my like lunch
oh
oh it's so spicy
if it's spicy for me it's really spicy
[Music]
you're not the spice girl ah
i missed that's okay
[Music]
see like this
map is so fast
[Music]
so like slip a lot i feel like maybe i
should treat this the same as like the
new bowser
[Music]
so many boosts
i think this one is easier to find out
which uh
it is less windy i guess
i feel that the the curves are not as
harsh as the ones uh-huh
from the
new bowser one
okay
i just gotta know which
part i need to like drift that in which
i don't
oh
that was me by the way oh please no
camera
oh
that's not me
i tried to get you
i tried to get you at the blue shell
while you slowed down too
no i didn't actually
no i didn't slow down enough
[Music]
no
[Laughter]
[Music]
is kind of
oh wait
hey at least i got the banana out you
know
[Music]
wait driver still got second
[Laughter]
get out of here
oh
i thought i got the uh the banana off on
the dry phone but i guess not maybe
all right oh let's go rainbow road
rainbow road is a staple in any mario
kart tournament
amel greece
i'm fine with both of them i've i
learned how to deal with rainbow road by
now
okay
and this one this one is uh
a little rough sometimes
oh rainbow road
take me home
[Music]
oh yes can't wait for the zako cup
can't wait for rng to take me to zappos
where you will then with first place so
i
drifted wrong and i fill my items
i did
[Music]
i don't know what you did there though i
need to follow you next time
[Music]
[Applause]
no i don't think so
[Music]
uh
oh wait i'm so far ahead
oh no please no not the push out now
it got me too
[Music]
and i'm number one
i kick it and kicked her butt
she retweeted that so i feel like she
wanted to kick carry kicks oh no i'm
dead no this isn't it
i got too greedy
[Music]
excuse me hold up barely miss stop it
what is going on
the new menu is gonna be hot
what's going on
[Music]
that's about this castle yet
[Laughter]
oh my god
oh my goodness
you are doing so well
thank you
you too and i'm a tutor yeah mommy's
improving she's warming up she's getting
there
which breakfast i mean ami is an a
because i ate for ami i remember saying
oh no
she can do it she can take home
top three today i believe
she must she must glory to her life
english
you must bring us honor
[Music]
oh i forgot the boost
exactly
[Music]
i know
oh come on
did you get hit by a retro no
damn it
oh come on
just unfair
i have all the colors here
all the colors and the randy are purple
[Music]
luigi where'd you come from
oh
[Music]
i barely have any points in this round
this is maybe the reason why i'm losing
only have three
now four
god i'm sweating
i'm sweating
oh no no no no no no no no no
oh we're okay
oh my god
uh it's the very end everyone's passing
me okay
okay
almond with a third
just climbing up
climbing up slowly for surely
he's getting there
[Music]
and you and you wanna do the electrode
right or mount mario no no i wonder
i like mount mario
it reminds me of my yeah
this is uh race
12.
this is 12. uh i think it's even 13 by
now no i i put 12 as the maximum
[Music]
oh yeah because like i gotta go after
around two hours today
oh oh i gotta
i gotta finish this
it's already been two hours
oh yeah i know you have to finish
something
you know what you know
i'm working on it
what is more important the art that you
have to draw or uh super mario winning
the cup uh in my repair
i never told you or told my viewers that
i mean they probably knew that it was
art but
oh sorry
we could be anything it could be that's
true oh no i'm okay
that's true that's true
i mean when are you not drawing art
enough yeah you're right you're right
you have a point in the point
[Music]
bye kiara
it's nice knowing you
don't worry you'll know me for a lot
longer i'm not i'm not leaving yet okay
[Music]
oh come on
my chance
why always me i mean i'm always first
that's probably why
i wonder why
wonder why
uh oh this is bad can you see the trees
yeah i'm seeing your
butt
are you able to see it
my beautiful my beautiful butt nice yeah
all the trees all the trees not the
trees
show who the real australian is here oh
yeah yeah
you better be better at skiing than i am
i am i am
okay
okay that was not worth
[Music]
always put out of myself
perfect score perfect score let's go
let's go kiara
nice
oh my gosh
[Music]
i'm so proud of myself holy
[Applause]
you lifted me up today i you you you
showed my real potential today yeah
you're doing so well like if you
continue doing this you're gonna be just
fun
we're gonna be middle of the pack
middle of the pack again
uh
right after waking up i think i think
that might be a problem the thing that
could mess everything up is the lack of
sleep
yeah well let's do our best enough on
the service
i guess
you're ending it right yeah yeah i gotta
go okay okay
thank you very much for joining and
thank you ahmed for joining too and
we'll garagey fine we'll have a lot of
fun in the tournament that's what it's
for yeah it will be fun and we'll at
least not
make a a
a full update
i mean even if we do we'll just end up
in the soccer club
yeah
okay okay okay
that's where the real winners are yeah
exactly winners from the bottom
bye bye
okay
have a good sleep goodnight
how do i leave this voice chat uh on the
phone
bye-bye okay
well thank you very much everyone for
joining me today i know today ended up
being a little shorter than uh usual but
it's gonna be a busy
week um you'll see why
soon pm so
i'll do my best um tomorrow is gonna be
a little later
than usual stream um where
i'm gonna be racing against some of the
other members i have i haven't collabed
with some of them before so i'm kind of
nervous so
um i hope i hope i can do okay tomorrow
and the actual tournament the day after
but yeah thank you very much everyone
yay
uh i'll see you guys tomorrow
thank you always for your support enjoy
the super chats welcome to all the new
members old members all the members all
the viewers always appreciate your
support yay
but thank you maybe if i get some time
like right before i see about train a
little more but yeah i got some good
training in today i had a lot of fun too
okay
thank you again
thank you until next time
bye bye
[Music]
wow
wow wow
you