​​​ ​A phoenix has countless lives.​ ​​
​​​ ​​​ ​​
​​​ ​Sometimes, a symbol of hope.​ ​​
​​​ ​Sometimes, a portent of prosperity.​ ​​
​​​ ​Sometimes, an avatar of rebirth.​ ​​
​​​ ​For eons, I've used​ ​​
​​ ​my power to help people.​ ​​
​​​ ​There's not a problem I can't solve!​ ​​
​​​ ​Or so I thought...​ ​​
​​​ ​It all started one day,​ ​​
​​​ ​when I decided to drop by​ ​​
​​ ​my favorite fast food place​ ​​
​​​ ​for one of their delicious burgers.​ ​​
​​​ ​I found out that​ ​​
​​ ​they were almost broke,​ ​​
​​​ ​and would have to close​ ​​
​​ ​if they couldn't pay back their debts.​ ​​
​​​ ​Pfft, with my powers? No problem!​ ​​
​​​ ​We just gotta make​ ​​
​​ ​this thing called... "profit," right?​ ​​
​​​ ​Should be a piece of cake...​ ​​
​​​ ​But it wasn't!​ ​​
​​​ ​Once I became a "part-timer,"​ ​​
​​ ​my fate was sealed!​ ​​
​​​ ​It was work, work, and more work!​ ​​
​​​ ​I used to lead armies!​ ​​
​​ ​Now I'm working for minimum wage?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Making money is hard...​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't just beat up bad guys.​ ​​
​​​ ​Instead, I gotta​ ​​
​​ ​keep the restaurant clean,​ ​​
​​​ ​serve good food, and make​ ​​
​​ ​customers want to come again.​ ​​
​​​ ​And keep doing it,​ ​​
​​ ​day after day after day...​ ​​
​​​ ​*pant* *pant* I'm gonna die!​ ​​
​​ ​And I'm supposed to be immortal!​ ​​
​​​ ​At the same time...​ ​​
​​​ ​it was also a lot of fun.​ ​​
​​​ ​I learned to do so many new things.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm happy,​ ​​
​​ ​and everyone else is happy, too.​ ​​
​​​ ​They all tell me how good the food is.​ ​​
​​​ ​Business is booming,​ ​​
​​​ ​and the debt's all repaid.​ ​​
​​​ ​In fact, even the debt collectors​ ​​
​​ ​are now regular customers.​ ​​
​​​ ​The owner was overjoyed.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'd call that a happy ending.​ ​​