foreign
[Music]
what's up
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
mascara
hello are we live
yeah yeah let's go Geico's John
everybody hi it's my birthday it's my
birthday we're live okay I'm seeing the
chat now we're live yeah yeah sorry for
the little delay everybody Geico's John
is here to celebrate unlucky that beat
guy called
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
because because my skeleton friend is
here I don't feel alone but I also don't
feel alone because you guys you guys are
here with me welcome welcome to my
karaoke room pick it up it's made from
me
it's all made from me bust it down Bust
It Down Bust It Down Bust It Down Bust
It Down bust it down sorry sorry I'm
really happy
I'm happy because guess what everyone
I'm officially no years old
yes that's right happy Birthday everyone
I'm reading the comments too cute cute
thank you so much you guys like the
balloons
[Music]
happy birthday Mori thank you so much do
you guys want to sing some songs we're
in a karaoke Booth right so let's sing
some songs I prepared a lot of songs
today there are quite a few new ones too
so get excited
[Music]
Mr Bones
nah it's okay you guys will see Geico's
China is a really good dancer
get ready
let's sing songs you guys ready we
should sing okay let's go first song
[Music]
the first song is
foreign
[Music]
you know
foreign
[Music]
hey hey
son knows
[Music]
wow
foreign
[Music]
yes
Ina
dance dance dance dance dance
Studio
you look really cool Callie thanks
duh
[Music]
I'm all coming up
here
[Music]
answers
you'll be
careful
[Music]
foreign
Wellness
[Music]
I do matter
he can't take
[Music]
dance
come on
[Music]
again
thank you
[Music]
let's sing something unexpected next
day
[Music]
foreign
yourself
[Music]
tonight
foreign
[Music]
song
you got any games
[Music]
foreign
bye -bye
[Music]
myself
science
[Music]
tonight
hey
yeah
yeah I did my own backing vocals you
guys did you like them
I shouldn't dance so much Wilson
unexpected
I freaking love that anime anyway
oh I think we have a guest do we have a
guest here
oh my God
whoa happy birthday to you happy
birthday
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh my God
happy birthday to you
me that's so nice
[Music]
wow many special details yeah
we'll sing together
[Music]
happy birthday today thank you so much
congratulations
yes that's right
ah
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
that's right yeah yeah I decided to ask
Louie to come sing with me because I
wanted to sing a really low song
and uh she has the lowest voice that I
think I know in whole life aside from
TOA Senpai we'll have to do maybe next
time but but I love uh doing this voice
[Laughter]
oh my God
oh my gosh
okay we got it we gotta switch my
experience
[Music]
thank you wonderful well let's sing yeah
yeah all right I'll have a good song
what do you think it is
what are we saying yeah oh well let's
see bloody
dream
okay
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
tonight
[Applause]
Jojo Jojo
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
oh
like a bloody soulmate I said like a
bloody star oh no
saki yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah
yeah come on
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
time second time is 3D collaboration so
the next time yes
yes
[Laughter]
please enjoy hi enjoy
[Music]
yes yes yes
have a nice day that looks so good thank
you I'll do my best and they'd be
bye
I knew that she was gonna sing that song
so good I knew it I knew it she like
wasn't super super familiar with it
before but like she knocked it out of
the park I knew she was gonna be amazing
ah psycho it's like a blessing for my
ears that's why I chose
because I knew she would bless my ears
with her low tone Oh stick it up
God she's so amazing now but she's she's
a busy lady so I'm gonna let her go
sh a bit lonely but that's okay that's
okay I'm gonna show you something I want
to show you a thing
you both slayed it thank you so much you
guys are very sweet really amazing
indeed a straight flyer her voice is
beautiful agreed just so amazing
um so we're gonna watch something so I
can sit down for a second right uh we're
gonna watch a video now you guys know
it's my birthday right
it's more day you can tweet out hashtag
happy Mori day uh with your screenshots
and to show your appreciation for for
your Maury if you'd like should you be
so inclined right
um if you'd like to so uh additionally
there's something I want to show you
guys
it's a video a video of things
you can buy
that's right do you guys want to buy
things
check it out everyone
tired of owning useless items you'll
never use because you got lured in by
that low low price of 19.99 well fear
not because on today's shopping program
shop till you drop dead featuring
Calliope Mori none of our items are
19.99
oh no
get ready to Feast your eyes on some
premium deer items you'll literally want
to gouge your eyes out if you don't own
them out of sheer fomo and additional
existential dread of The Emptiness of
your life without them you
items you need that
why not get a sick poster of your one
and only boy to display it work and
assert your dominance over your friends
that's right folks Maury calliope's
special birthday poster features Mori
Calliope rocking out at a concert she
definitely did with an outfit she
definitely wore you won't want to miss
this premium item because once it's gone
it's gone for good
get it now
ever wanted to bathe yourself in sweet
smelling delicious purple liquid well I
sure can't relate but if you do then you
better get your hands on this special
dual set of bath bombs from Maury
calliope's favorite premium underworld
Onsen they come in two cents Maury Rose
and death Sensei purple Mist get yours
today you smell like
thirsty surrounded by hot e girls who
the hell isn't but too bad for you
that's no e-girl on your mug it's your
dad you're Mori dad with an exclusive
design by Maury Calliope father to all
you'll be feeling like number one as you
sip your stress anxiety and existential
dread away don't miss your chance to
grab it dummy
[Music]
gotta get yours
plush comes with one outfit design
details differ from final version no
trees are guaranteed to be saved by the
making of This plush
are you waiting for deadbeat if you get
the whole set a limited number of
deadbeats will get a hand signed
postcard they're gonna sell out best
because I really like my hand but never
fear if you buy the full set you get a
duplicated autographed postcard remember
deadbeats shop until you're dead
[Music]
no one's laughing at that is true
don't worry about the ending part that
was just a little bit it wasn't real it
wasn't real anyway anyway what about it
you guys what do you think of the merge
it's pretty cool right pretty cool you
love some good violence no no violence
here no no no no well I hope I hope you
guys will be excited about this um and
enjoy the many wonderful things bath
bombs whoa crazy a plush of my own I
hope you guys will get it yeah it'll be
really cool I swear you'll use things
every day you'll use the things every
single day and and it's not it's not bad
expensive I don't know your financial
situation so be careful additionally
additionally additionally
um there's something else I wanted to
talk about yeah yeah I've already talked
about this before but I'm going to talk
about it again because I need more time
to rest and also uh just because it's
really important to me that you get it
because if you buy this my dreams will
come true so what else do we have here
I'm gonna show it to you again it's the
Blu-ray
laughs
[Music]
what's up
yeah Blu-ray Blu-ray and if you get it
you get lots of nice things too what I
mean look at look at it's behind me
right here look look at all the nice
things you get depending on the store
you buy it from there are like all kinds
of different little things that you can
get
um in addition the only way to get them
all is to buy the Blu-ray many many
times I don't know
um if you'd like to you certainly can
because like I said if you buy this blue
right oh my dreams come true yay Mori
store yay more restore yay
um yeah it would make me really really
happy because I'm super proud of uh of
this of this release
um so yeah check out the Blu-ray and
don't go anywhere because I still have
one big announcement a couple
announcements but one really big
announcement at the end of the stream so
don't go anywhere okay we still got more
to do but yeah by the Blu-ray it would
make it would make me really happy yeah
that'll be really great another really
big show might happen someday well I
guess the surprise is kind of ruined but
just kidding here it is
um
but I tell but you didn't see anything
you didn't see anything you didn't see
anything you saw nothing oh God God no
don't look there don't look there
no no no no it's fine you pretend like
you didn't pretend like you didn't see
anything there's still another there's
still another announcement okay just
just pretend like you didn't see I don't
know what you're talking about hey I
think someone's here oh my gosh what is
this perhaps the sound of a phone that's
about to ring uh
we have a phone over here isn't that
great uh it would be awesome if it was
to ring at some point
oh it's ringing
oh my gosh no way all right let me see
if I can grab it watch this
[Music]
Iris Cali I heard you're lonely at a
karaoke Booth by yourself on your
birthday is the phone okay yeah no I can
hear you perfectly well I don't worry
about it it's fine it's fine it's hold
on let me hold on let me just t-pose
real quick
hahaha
thank you okay let's see oh hello okay
sorry I can hear you perfectly now Iris
hey what's going on hey I heard you were
lonely and I was wondering if you wanted
a visit from a certain Nephilim or so
definitely but wait no no no you don't
you won't want me to come no please I
don't have to come you know I want to
sing with you Iris please come here yeah
that's karaoke party I'll run there
right now I'll teleport there yeah are
you sure you can run yeah legs to run
with
there'll be something I'm sure I I might
go too fast I might I might lose some
dimension on my body but okay well good
luck I'm just gonna go ahead and put the
phone away then all right all right
hanging up now bye
there it goes I put the phone away hi
okay it looks like iris is gonna come
and join us we're gonna maybe sing
together
see when she's gonna be here me and guy
called China waiting
whoa
whoa what happens
no I just I I came too fast I couldn't
process my whole body into into the room
oh my God what's wrong do I look
different do I look Ed at YouTube a
little beautiful as usual right well
yeah of course naturally I mean you're
all you're always very pretty
um but you are you are definitely flat I
think that's okay because it just means
more people can get excited for your
official 3D debut right yes it's flat
wrists
that's right that's right wow I mean hey
you know what as long as you can still
sing I'm happy to have you here I am
happy too and you know one thing that's
good about being flat what is that you
know since I'm basically just a piece of
cardboard I can touch Cali I can do hold
on imagine what I'm doing to her right
now no no no no no but you can't tell
because it's no full body track no no no
no stop that stop stop stop why are you
being weird stop you're like a you're
like a fly oh I'm gonna SWAT you stop
doing that no no no no
all right well it's fine it's fine you
know what I'll allow I'll allow your
little your little Shenanigans as long
as we can sing together yeah are we
gonna sing
I was thinking maybe we should sing a
song from an anime that we both have
seen and we both have talked about on
the chadcast yes that's anime that anime
with the with the bad ending oh the
anime itself is was a good anime but man
the ship
best girl lost and so I'll never forgive
that anime she was robbed she was robbed
uh we're gonna sing we're gonna sing the
opening of
true tears I think it's the opening
cheers yeah it is okay it's the opening
we're gonna sing foreign
let's do it yeah yeah
[Music]
foreign
tonight
[Music]
wow yeah
the your turn
[Music]
[Applause]
now I'm sad
because our ship's saying yeah
I'll always be bitter hey it's true
tears right yeah
[Music]
over me
that she
died
[Music]
think of a really messed up English
sentence
yeah that works
[Music]
yeah
[Laughter]
that was fun I'm jumping right now by
the way she is but believe believe she's
she's doing it I am jumping yeah she's
together together just kidding I'm not
trying to tire you out we still have
another song to sing
we still have another song but that
other song b something really hype we
should sing a really hype anime song
such as one that like everybody knows
and gets really excited about like um
like they want us they want to shout the
first part of the song ah that song yeah
the one that starts with a a g g g g
Onna show colors
let's go
yeah yeah bring it down hey hey here we
go
[Music]
together
foreign
[Music]
but she came
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
let's find out
[Music]
oh God oh God
wow she's clipping through oh Lord
ah she's gonna see something yeah bye oh
no
nobody we knew this would happen you
want to t-pose and fix it oh yeah sure
sure
oh stop
stop
hey alrighty please fix me
tipos little tipos for Iris as she gets
she gets fixed
anyway they're gonna they're gonna fix
Iris
they're gonna fix her she got a little
crazy it's fine we did this to ourselves
this was our bed but it's it was worth
it to watch to watch Iris clip into the
ground so and have her kick me it's fine
it's fine
it's all good in the neighborhood hold
on she's getting fixed now
you guys want to hear a joke
I want to hear it
I don't I don't have any jokes sorry I
just saw it I was just asking I wasn't
gonna tell a joke I was just asking if
you wanted to hear one
[Music]
oh wait
it's fine it's fine it's fine okay
anyway oh someone's calling oh hey hold
on a minute who's this
musi
Moshi Moshi
moshimoshi
Moshi
with this
open this
this
is
must be a prank call somebody oh oh oh
hold on a minute
I'm kidding oh my God I was gonna beat
you for that bales
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh no I Disappeared into into the ground
again he's uncovering you oh wait I
don't know she's swimming now
I'm making the the same pose that
coworkun made when he was uploading with
Shinjuku
[Music]
yeah of course of course there's any
time for you I was so excited
I have a question for you bae a little
birthday question yes what do you want
to see me do this year it could be
anything
what do I want to see you do this year
oh that's a good question yeah
I want to see you wait is this like a
promise that you'll do it uh kind of
we'll see that depends
it depends on some factors
I see
um
as as your sister I actually would want
to see you take an actual break oh
I was always nice
that's what I would like you to see hola
cool like like oh
shouldn't
I should learn to break dance or
something but you know what you're
saying no okay look you said Okay that
was my sisterly answer
um
if okay what's something that I would
want to see you do this is something
cool let's see um
you know what I would actually want to
see you try and do a oh we should learn
how to do a freeze together
um it's a break dancing move it's when
like you do like a break dancing move
and then you freeze
in like a in like a position
yeah oh okay yeah yeah definitely I mean
that sounds cool wait so like you mean
like a super cool like Matrix kind of
thing like maybe like we we swivel on
our heads and then like stop
I think um
okay the phone is fixed oh okay okay
yeah you said you wanted to you want to
yeah together what's a freaking phrase a
phrase is like when you like stop it's
like a pose but like you're suspending
yourself off the ground it's like a oh
like break dancing pose yeah something
like that that's kind of advanced but
like there's things like a baby Freeze I
think that's the first thing beginner
break dances try and learn yeah I'm down
all right then then let's do it I mean
if we ever do like a big chadcast like
live performance or something I want to
try a freeze with you yeah oh yeah I
don't know how to I I don't know how to
do it wait you don't know how to do it
it's been a very long time
[Music]
all right all right well I'll give you
some time to learn and then I'll learn
as well okay okay oh my God that'd be so
much fun my heart stopped when I heard
laku in earlier oh see I
I've been singing that song yeah because
you know we're all Inuyasha gang here so
yeah yeah that that makes me really
happy well speaking of songs that I'm
doing what would you all right I'm gonna
give you the ability to ask me for like
a dance move or pose request for the
next songs that I'm gonna sing you don't
know which songs they are but
I'm singing a sad slow one if you want
me to do the worm I'll do it don't
choose that by the way
all right
um do you perhaps okay there's okay I
would like to see a pepper grinder move
in there what is that I like it
okay so put your two hands in front of
you okay one and then pretend you're
grinding pepper
that's actually that's pretty cool okay
I'll do that all right I'll do I'll do
your pepper grinder yeah do the pepper
garden and I'd like to see you hold a
squad for a song
but okay
all right
under my eye they're from you but but I
love you very much
I love you too Happy Birthday Kelly
thank you for the birthday wishes you're
the best Bae you're the best I'll talk
to you later talk to you later bye-bye
I'm still here bye
[Music]
there we go that was that was Bae Bae
gave me a call on my birthday wasn't
that sweet wasn't it sweet Iris yeah
yeah okay she's become a ghost but she's
still Among Us don't let's chat never
mind all right well I wonder if somebody
else will call
oh my gosh someone's calling someone's
calling
calling all right let's go pick up the
phone again let's see what happens
I got it oh it worked much
[Music]
hello what's up oh you got like a super
special themed karoka room I do I wanted
to do something special this year you
know oh my God what but it's like
normally you get these super boring
karaoke rooms if you go to karaoke you
gotta pay extra for the special ones so
how much did you pay for the special one
you don't want to know Kiara you don't
want to know how much I paid but you
know what I'm having
but sometimes you gotta treat yourself
to something nice that's true that's
true you know what that's that's the
spot it's the spice of life honestly
that I get to do this kind of stuff I'm
really happy I'm lucky you know yeah
happy birthday can we thanks so much
kiwawa I appreciate you calling in to
wish me a happy birthday I gotta wish
you a happy birthday too I have it in my
calendar
oh yeah thank you well it was still a
long time to go but I was so surprised
when I realized it wait what Kelly's
birthday already no what is that like
just yesterday I know when you had your
last one I know time really flies well
I'm gonna eat lots and lots of kfp on
your birthday
a cake that looks like fried chicken but
it's actually a cake you know those fake
cakes that is a real thing people do
know how to do that yeah that's crazy
well I have a question for you uh what
do you want to see me do this year
this year in general yeah don't say take
a break because Bae said take a break
I want you to realize some plans that
you have on the you know what do you
call a back burner or like not back
burner I don't know oh yeah plans that
you have had since like maybe a year or
so
and yes make them a reality this year oh
you know what I mean I know what you I
think I know what you mean wink wink
wink wink I like that idea okay well
you've inspired me you've inspired me in
Al qola okay I'll do it I'll do it okay
just do it just can you give me a like
with the hand poses like you know
walking around and then with the finger
onto the hand just oh yeah wait hold on
finger onto the hand
that's okay
[Music]
thank you
something like that I'll do it too I'll
do whatever you should you should do it
too hey also you get a request for the
next song that I'm singing what kind of
like dance move or pose do you want to
see me do
you know like roughly what the Vogue
dance style is
um can you give me an example
I think oh hi Iris that's the first word
out here
[Music]
what is that what you don't know well
it's kind of I mean there's like several
parts to voguing but I think like what I
want to see you do is like over your
head like frantically move your arms
over your head like you know like swirl
and twirl and and then one hand to the
left one to the right and so dance
kind of copy what she's doing oh yeah
yeah yeah okay if you could vote
together with your dancer doing the
maybe during every chorus Vogue okay
every chorus every chorus all right oh
I'll try
as much as I can I will you know
oh gosh she's giving me a hard one all
right I'll do my best thanks kiwawa all
right
yeah oh hold on one second everybody
we're gonna fix Iris for a second and
I'm gonna put away the phone real quick
I love you bye
[Music]
there we go we're fixing Iris and she
doesn't need to be fixed in my opinion
but that's okay that's perfect the way I
am exactly hold on let me try the Vogue
thing
yeah you're doing it you're doing it
you're doing it I see it
I'm trying it's beautiful thank you
Arigato thank you thank you very much
chance thank you Chan is very cute she's
scared of me though I think oh no I
don't think so
I don't think so she's just a little shy
but she's very outgoing around me yeah
okay cool cool
well I wonder what we should do after
this here let me sit down for a second I
still have a couple songs I want to sing
you guys I want to sing some more songs
um I'll do my best we got some emotional
ones in there too
oh boy oh man and also we have some
announcements so don't go anywhere but I
really hope you guys have enjoyed the
show so far I know that this is a lot
more like casual and like cozy and
whatnot it's not like a really big Grand
showcase or anything like that but I
think that's okay you know you guys
always tell me that I should have more
fun
um you know just having a good time
singing and worry less about like how
high quality everything is all the time
and stress myself out over it you know
fixed fixed speaking of which looking
very high quality thank you
thank you the quality PNG floating
around oh well I can't wait for your 3D
thank you Kelly it was fun very funny I
want to sing with you in 3D again we'll
do it yeah we did it the Fest yeah yes
definitely alrighty then well since my
body is fixed now I think I should be
heading off to do my Nephilim duties
maybe perhaps an idol meeting I don't
mean maybe perhaps an idol meeting that
I've been that I've been getting an
emergency alert for oh my God
not in my karaoke room oh I need to go
I'm a flyer
out fine get out Iris your virus get out
she's leaving now yay I was uh I was
really quiet I was lonely I mean I know
that I have my dead beats here but it's
even better with friends right
yeah
anyway I guess we should sing some more
songs is that okay I think I've
sufficiently arrested enough
okay well let's sing let's continue
singing that's what we're here for right
I've got a couple more songs in me so
let's go
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
whatever
okay
thank you
[Music]
foreign
with us
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
oh
[Music]
God
what I die
[Music]
now
let's sing one more song
[Music]
foreign
oh
come down days
thank you everyone thank you so much for
coming to my karaoke party I have one
more announcement two more announcements
but one really big one one really big
announcement okay everybody
it's my one year anniversary with
Universal Music as a major artists yay
so everyone I would like to introduce to
you
Cinderella
LP lb
that's right everybody we've got a vinyl
release coming out
that's right and orders are going to
open up tonight if you don't want to
wait six months to get my merch you can
go ahead and get this or you can get
both both is good too but if you don't
want to wait yay more restore yay more
restore you can add Cinderella to your
vinyl collection yay More Much More Much
More Much of course I wasn't Gonna Leave
You Guys Without a vinyl no no no I'm a
big fan of Records myself so it's out
now oh looks like it's out okay it's out
you guys can get it check the link in
the description if you want to grab it
the vinyl's out you can go purchase it
yeah so you guys can check it out
I'm so happy I'm so happy I hope you
guys get it I can't wait to to play it
on my little my little phonograph my
little turntable I'm very excited so I
hope you guys will get it as well lplp
already bought oh my gosh you guys are
fast wow you guys are really fast yes
[Music]
foreign
yeah it's also super Limited in quantity
they are now they are now telling me
it's very limited
um because we can't we can't make a
million of these you guys know that
there's you know kind of there's some I
don't know you should get it now you
should get it now is what I'm trying to
say
it was what I'm trying to say I'm so
happy I'm so excited
um so yeah please grab it thank you so
much everyone and I have one last thing
to announce I have a cover coming out
um I don't know exactly when because
it's being checked it should be within
the next day or two days or so but
foreign
what song is it
what song is
so please
look forward to it I'm really really
proud of this one it turned out super
good and I think you guys are gonna love
it so yay please look forward
and with that being said you guys I'm
your Mori I hope that you'll remember me
this is a really fun stream
thank you so much you guys thanks for
spending time with me thanks for singing
with me and I guess I'll catch you guys
on the flip side okay everybody take
care be sure to grab the merch again
that would make me happy and yeah with
that being said everybody I'll see you
later thank you for coming
bye bye guys Janko here bye-bye see you
everyone
peace out bye
[Music]
thank you
tired of owning useless items you'll
never use because you got lured in by
that low low price of 19.99 well fear
not because on today's shopping program
shop till you drop dead featuring
Calliope Mori none of our items are
19.99
oh no
get ready to Feast your eyes on some
premium deer items you'll literally want
to gouge your eyes out if you don't own
them out of sheer fomo and additional
existential dread of The Emptiness of
your life without them you need
you need that
why not get a sick poster of your one
and only boy to display it work and
assert your dominance over your friends
that's right folks Maury calliope's
special birthday poster features Mori
Calliope rocking out at a concert she
definitely did with an outfit she
definitely wore you won't want to miss
this premium item because once it's gone
it's gone for good
[Music]
ever wanted to bathe yourself in sweet
smelling delicious purple liquid well I
sure can't relate but if you do then you
better get your hands on this special
dual set of bath bombs from Maury
calliope's favorite premium underworld
Onsen they come in two cents Maury Rose
and death Sensei purple Mist get yours
today you smell like
thirsty surrounded by hot e girls who
the hell isn't but too bad for you
that's no e-girl on your mug it's your
dad you're Mori dad with an exclusive
design by Maury Calliope father to all
you'll be feeling like number one as you
sip your stress anxiety and existential
dread away don't miss your chance to
grab it dummy
[Music]
gotta get yours
plush comes with one outfit design
details differ from final version no
trees are guaranteed to be saved by
making of This plush
so what are you waiting for deadbeat if
you get the whole set a limited number
of deadbeats will get a hand signed
postcard they're gonna sell out best
because I really like my hand but never
fear if you buy the full set you get a
duplicated autographed postcard remember
deadbeats shop until you're dead
get it
beats like the name of the Bands
don't shut the up no one's laughing
at that wait man
Nina song
what's up
[Music]
you know
foreign
[Music]
tired of owning useless items you'll
never use because you got lured in by
that low low price of 19.99 well fear
not because on today's shopping program
shop till you drop dead featuring
Calliope Mori none of our items are
19.99
oh no
get ready to Feast your eyes on some
premium deer items you'll literally want
to gouge your eyes out if you don't own
them out of sheer fomo and additional
existential dread of The Emptiness of
your life without them you
you need that
why not get a sick poster of your one
and only boy to display at work and
assert your dominance over your friends
that's right folks Maury calliope's
special birthday poster features Mori
Calliope rocking out at a concert she
definitely did with an outfit she
definitely wore you won't want to miss
this premium item because once it's gone
it's gone for good yourself
[Music]
ever wanted to bathe yourself in sweet
smelling delicious purple liquid well I
sure can't relate but if you do then you
better get your hands on this special
dual set of bath bombs from Maury
calliope's favorite premium underworld
Onsen they come in two cents Maury Rose
and death Sensei purple Mist get yours
today you smell like
thirsty surrounded by hot e girls who
the hell isn't but too bad for you
that's no e-girl on your mug it's your
dad you're Mori dad with an exclusive
design by Mori Calliope father to all
you'll be feeling like number one as you
sip your stress anxiety and existential
dread away don't miss your chance to
grab it dummy
gotta get yours
plush comes with one outfit design
details differ from final version no
trees are guaranteed to be saved by
making of This plush
so what are you waiting for deadbeat if
you get the whole set a limited number
of deadbeats will get a hand signed
postcard they're gonna sell out best
because I really like my hand but never
fear if you buy the full set you get a
duplicated autographed postcard remember
deadbeats shop until you're dead
like the name of the fans
yo shut the up no one's laughing at
that wait is crazy
Nina song
what's up
[Music]
foreign