next up how about rainy hi attention
please I'm popular Rainey from whole
life ID generation 2. my goal today is
to be number one in your heart and also
not that last night
huh yeah yeah I thought you were good
you and Iris have heard good good good
news about you
we had a good practice yesterday right
right yeah we did
nice thank you
bye
[Applause]
[Music]
hello my name is
Indonesia generation one nice to meet
you
what's the motivation for today oh well
I I want to be at least not on the last
okay
[Music]
the last in someone's heart is that such
a good thing does it sound like a good
thing yeah okay
how about
hi hello hello everyone I'm ayundaris
from Whole Life Indonesia and thank you
so much for inviting me to this collab
I'm so happy though I'm so excited they
go thank you
[Music]
my motivation for today is that I would
like to have fun though although yes I'm
not really confident but let's have fun
all right it will be fine it will be
fine
that's all that matters
and Ollie yay
crazy
second generation hi guys
um
motivation I plan on ranking pop so that
you guys become my bottoms that is
motivation
[Laughter]
I'll bring you guys into bottoms
okay seems jokes on here we're already
here
we won't be dominated that easily senpai
and I think wait did I get all the
introductions from ID I think I did
yeah
let's introduce the E inside let's start
with Iris
oh yeah hiris it's Iris whole alive
English project hope V singer here
um my goal today is to get first place
Victorious
[Music]
thank you anyways for participating and
looking forward to your driving skills
yeah thank you so much for having me
here so I heard that you waited for yeah
for me to come on you we're literally
the last person that I needed because
before you it was we were elf elf that's
one that was German we were 11 people
yeah thank you next up how about
um
today I'm gonna win probably okay okay
this is the I own I heard you only
played Mario Kart so far in a members
only stream but that's about it
yeah I won in that one too oh oh okay
I see oh then you might be the hidden
winning choice that the one
a wild card player welcome
thank you thank you next time
English
[Music]
um
um I'll do my best I think we have a we
have a future competition to be not last
and to be first so I'll do my best
yeah I was also taking this very
seriously in her practice round so I'm a
bit scared of Ina um I don't know I was
still falling off Maps it's fun oh yeah
it happens oh Kelly joined yes nice
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
nice then let's start and let's continue
with the introduction from
IOP Maury
hello everyone my name is callipi my
parents are still asleep and probably
can't watch the news this morning Maury
nice to meet you I'm gonna be talking
about because it's a bit early uh so
excuse me for that guys but I'm very
excited just to be here I really didn't
think this was gonna work but it's
working I love this it's of course
thank you Kelly for joining even though
it's such an early time and to kind of
uh Troublesome with some setups and all
that I'm glad you're still here and you
know what you being so whispery and calm
might be a good uh thing for driving
because that way you might be able to
focus more true facts
and I'm kind of sick today and if you're
watching on my side I just need to say
this now I've had some technical
difficulties very suddenly so I am made
of cardboard I'm sorry please well I it
was not my fault it's out of my control
right now so anyways I'm PhD tuber Doma
somebody does a PNG tuber Let's Race
today baby I'm the wild card today
[Music]
in my dust well you know on the screen
there's there's gonna be a lot of things
happening so your viewers should be
looking at the game and not you anyway
so I think it's fun I'm curious of
course they want to look at me right
[Music]
yeah
of course
all right that leaves uh me I think yeah
yeah
welcome everyone I wanted to do this
tournament for a long long time uh I I
think my viewers have heard me talk
about it since months ago and finally
it's happening uh and I'm very glad to
have all these lovely girls here
together it's the first time we're doing
a tournament like this so I I don't
think anyone has to feel bad about you
know not being so good it's all fine
maybe we'll do it some more often in the
future so please don't stress yourself
out let's just have fun today yes
no problem and with that I think we will
go to the roots but before that let me
say thank you is the hats and the cards
are sponsored by ninoma inanis yeah hey
guys
um just want to say my steering wheel is
made by JT maches thank you very much
also
um
I can't hear the bgm this is going to be
tough for your boy but you know what
hard mode extra challenge yeah
okay tournament rules easy there's not
many rules basically uh all characters
all courses are allowed however if you
choose uh please do not choose random
courses please choose a certain course
that you want to actually erase but if
that course has been used before like if
it has actually been chosen before
please do not choose the same course
again
number two items are allowed number
three uh we are racing in 150 cc with no
assist everyone please check if you have
turned off your assistance
no
okay yeah if uh wait a second it's if
you press Y and select your character at
the point where you select the card you
can press on a plus the plus button
um when you see the the three options on
the right side if you press l
uh if if there is a if there's a sign
that says no
then it's uh Auto steering off that's
how it's supposed to be okay
yeah it's supposed to be crossed out
exactly the other ones you can ignore I
did it oh oh
[Laughter]
I just want to quickly let you guys know
um yeah I'm on I'm gonna be on like Auto
mute this whole time so unless I have
something to say I'm gonna be muted
don't worry if I'm a little quiet I'm
still here with you guys in spirit yeah
okay okay
and next row uh oh yeah there's no more
rules there's Facebook is just a system
we're doing the first cup all versus all
big mixer for races then we get we will
mute each other by the way during the
race and just to focus everyone on what
we're driving and then we get back
together and Discord talk a little bit
then we're going to the second cup which
is en versus ID six versus six yes yes
we will separate each other in uh The
Voice channels by team this one in this
one we will actually talk with one
another if you wanna and then we uh give
some comments together again when we get
all back together in the same channel
and then we do the third cup with random
randomly thrown together teams no Ian
versus ID but like all mixed together
naturally beautiful
random random random we will just like
I'll count down and and then everyone
joins Eva voice chat room zero or voice
chat room one no who's this
well done we're gonna have to do it
again and again and again
and by the way just just so you know the
the those like team cups would basically
be
um like the same room as all versus all
the difference is just basically like if
you throw items like red shells or
whatever and there is a teammate in
front of you it will not go to the
teammate obviously it will go directly
to the closest opponent driver uh that's
around you so yeah that's how that team
system works I think oh my gosh
is everyone ready to get started who is
that
I'm ready
[Music]
okay okay
then everyone who's ready mute yourself
on Discord if someone's not ready then I
will ask you why you're not ready okay
wait guys uh how do you go forward in
the game
you push the a button is it the a button
okay okay
gotcha all right thank you thanks guys
love you okay see you soon
okay love you too
oh [\h__\h] what have I done
[Music]
you guys can hear the bgm right
foreign
as long as you guys can hear it then I'm
happy
[Music]
I take the nice easy one
okay guys let's not get last
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
that was the best thing I've ever seen
in my life
that was so good
guys I should not have gotten third
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
really
[Music]
good
now last okay
okay and please everyone do not use
cheap cheap beach or a Mario Kart
Stadium anymore for your race collection
thank you I'm gonna try and remember
that but I don't know
[Music]
yeah nothing that looks like a beach and
nothing that looks like a fancy night
life place right but isn't there
multiple Beach
uh yes but the cheap cheap beach the one
that we just did from the DS version not
any yeah okay okay okay are we doing
team wait when are we doing teams
uh we still have two races to go before
oh this result okay
nice hat you know she's muted okay
are we oh sorry okay
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
's not bad
lucky number seven looks a whole lot
like not 12. to me Deadbeats
[Music]
I like baby park because I'm a baby at
this cave
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
guys I got disconnected
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
okay about the disconnection I'm
I'm not sure like normally it seems like
in in the whole of Japan tournaments
they automatically give the one like
well the like this qualification like
last spot if you uh oh if you are oh wow
uh congratulations or everyone cannot
mute themselves now
okay oh yeah
[Music]
sixth place.com
but she still was a fourth or what so
yeah
I think that's just how we're gonna take
it it is what it is yeah
so uh let me let me just uh enough was
number one right number one
congratulations
[Music]
I I thought you kept on selecting
Rainbow Road
you know
what yeah she practiced on that one a
lot I think that's why she was going for
that
okay
um
we'll get it oh okay someone has to uh
yeah wait uh wait who was number two
okay
no problem who was number two though
Irish
how did you how did you manage to get
number two today I I did bad on the
first race so that really pulled me back
but yeah Ina Senpai was very quick uh
but I did my best I did my best
you were amazing
oh wait me and Elena were third are we
tired
good job good job wait wait are we
complete in the lobby right now one two
three
okay
okay well then shall we uh continue uh
but Muna senpa is currently unavailable
I don't know which one is low battery oh
um
do you think you were fine to go or you
need some time I I think
everyone who needs coffee go get
yourself a cup of coffee
I have the caffeine shakes already so
I'm banned from coffee I was actually
really surprised about Thomas driving
too like I thought you know because she
didn't like we didn't see her practicing
we didn't see her play the game and to
begin with a lot
clear place to most of the races until
the end when I got [\h__\h] over yeah
screw it over
tonight I saw you go off the edge though
once and it was pretty good good gaming
tactic as planned right it's all part of
the plan yeah
whatever yeah no it wasn't the waste if
you would have shellcasted how you uh
suggested uhmed because you were such a
good driver we need you we need you
all right then let's uh okay only okay
okay Ollie is going to another game are
we picking teams like dodgeball no no no
that gives me really bad flashbacks I
don't like that someone
picked last and I don't want that I'm
gonna go at my full power now because
now I'm fighting for the en ladies
yeah
this is where we put our all in it yep
of our teams
[Music]
two of the strongest ones are in Ian
wait me too
[Laughter]
I'm okay at not getting last place so
that's good news
yes Morrison is a good asset to have I
want her on our team hell yeah thanks
guys
sorry uh Indonesia's uh back yeah it's
okay I will I will support Rainey
[Music]
everyone uh please split into teams by I
think let's just um Ian go to Voice
channel oh one thank you okay
um
and I guess so we're going to
stay there
yeah
unless unless Kelly
hello ladies I'm back hello what is our
strategy for winning against Eddie don't
lose it
don't let go of the a button
but like um you know for items do they
automatically um not hit our teammates
yeah it only hits like oh okay
nice yeah but I've never parted teams
yet I'll see how we can select that I
think we will um like every every
participant will have a choice to which
which team they can join I think that's
how it works let's see no more items no
CPU all vehicles race four races let's
go let's go so long as Watson doesn't
drive off the edge we should be all
right
okay oh
I I I'm the one doing this okay uh
player was Ollie right yeah
no no no no no no
no no no how do I how do I cancel this
no
if I have to you might have to ah oh no
problem okay it looks fine
communication
all right
[Music]
sorry girls I did a little mistake
because like I thought uh oh yeah you
know uh again
okay
yeah you can you can join in again it's
open again I think it closed once you
can join again now yeah thank you sorry
[Music]
like it's ready to drift
drift as much as you can that's that's
how this works
yes but not overdrift you know you know
there they are oh God the bald one is
back
[Music]
full power with the baldness
um
wait I'm a complete one two three four
five six seven eight nine ten eleven
twelve okay I think we're complete
teacher's doing a head count everybody
stands still
I think we are okay
no CPU all vehicles for races
look at the other ball
yeah he's a little Baldy
just so you guys know my mom is watching
she's not gonna say anything but she's
watching everyone says hello hi
are you sure you don't want to say
anything
good morning this is how you do it
one two three four five
ah this is so who is that Anya okay okay
now it's even let's
we can I can just do the random button
we don't have to do the voice chat
thingy wait we have teams now yes
please choose again a new map a new map
which one do we want to use which one do
we all have confidence
I want to do Wario stadium and Yoshi
Music Park
they're using a tactic you guys are
overloading the probability
when do we push the go button on the two
yep
that was my shell I'm so sorry in uh
does it work with like the same people
oops it shouldn't really I don't know
Chad told me that it doesn't hit uh your
own people unless I don't know it wasn't
a green shell oh yeah I don't think you
can control it it was red it was red it
was red it's red it's red it's red
okay I don't know well then you just
gotta be careful
[Music]
what the hell
oh I see someone right in front of me
I think we're laughing
oh no no no no no no
there's someone in front of you on this
road
[Applause]
I don't know
oh
my God
okay we got it we got it
lucky number seven that was my red shell
I believe
okay no we did okay we did
that was nice
[Music]
out on the red team no
the a is oh
um
Bowser Castle Bowser Castle which Bowser
the New Belgium no no that's new the
crown called whatever it's called I like
Mount Wario or like the animal crossing
map is easy like easy as in it's like oh
no I like Wario Stadium personally
cheese
thank you
um we have clowns
oh the sand [\h__\h] [\h__\h] okay okay
what no I don't like cheese one no
these not the lactose
[Music]
I have practice in that one
isn't it yeah
it just has a lot of traps and a lot of
obstacles
hey everybody don't suck I miss evil
laughs oh no
yeah I was dirty
let's go
[Music]
I was number one for one second I love
that one that was a good second
I like this music it's hype
stop it
oh shoot
okay
I'm not used to this oh my God
oh God oh God oh God
[Music]
okay who's in front of us
yeah okay so everyone's eating then okay
things
I won't use the Shelf
thank you
that wasn't me
it seems attacked
um
these Corners are tricky
[Music]
um okay no
oh no oh I know you're gonna play by ID
oh no oh no yeah it's actually pretty
good yeah
we're good we're good yes it was a
little yeah bye
no we got bikes
monkey mode Let's go okay yes
foreign
[Music]
should I throw the Red Shell right now
with enum so that I can be number one
[Applause]
oh I hate it when the lightning hits
when you're about to film and he was
like I'm dead alrighty let's freaking go
places
oh no oh no
what oh no
I feel like they're definitely getting
technical at us here you guys we gotta
I'm gonna ramp up our strategy
oh my God but we shouldn't jinx it right
guys
no okay ladies
rainbow wrote on the crown yeah rainbow
road on the crown on the ground okay
what does that mean let's hit him with
us
oh we all have shiny crowns on our heads
look at us
cheese versus rainbow
yeah
Kiara you have one job
this one it's a good one the chances
that it's gonna be that one don't worry
it's gonna be Rainbow Road and I hate it
um I feel like it's gonna be cheese
yeah it's too much cheese here
oh
okay please land why do they like that
one so much
[Music]
is probably really good at that one
that's why I chose it oh probably trying
to get the points back we can't let them
oh yeah look at him look at him we have
a good Head Start yeah hell yeah oh I'm
gonna burnout just kidding
he took us there
I didn't even know that was a shortcut
they know the shortcuts were in trouble
they do they do
it's okay I'm still I'm still doing okay
we're still good we're still good oh
that was dangerous
oh God
someone else in front of you which will
be number 12 I guess
it's gonna be a long road for that when
Red Shell yeah
I shouldn't have listened
oh
okay so she knows the shortcut I see how
it is I thought I I just saw it I was
like oh yeah there was a shortcut here
at the very end
oh
it's okay
nice nice nice nice
oh wait I like that oh my gosh
no
oh
oh no I'm going off track what the [\h__\h]
okay only only iris is ahead of me
that's good yep
oh Raina came through the shortcut no no
oh no I didn't have a boyfriend to use
that shortcut okay she's first now okay
give me something good oh no not a
banana
I'm gonna kick your butt
now look I hate this road so much
come on guys come on in don't lose it
now
oh yeah
oh my God okay
guys together
[Music]
hold on oh god oh
oh
[Music]
my God
uh that's the last doll
for the way in the end rainbow
S I think it will bite Us in the ass but
we have Ina so okay
yeah I don't know I'll do my best yeah I
don't know the shortcuts for this so I
don't know any shortcuts here but the
shortcuts just go down in space to Sana
areas through yeah
for that
no oh we're getting right oh
yeah
let's go pick one
will be fine
we'll be good yeah
yeah let's go we're pretty ahead though
no we can do it
just don't fall off the edges
yep
[Music]
universe
oh thank God
[Music]
oh
my god oh please please don't don't this
is so slivering scares me yeah
okay we are at one two three right now
yeah it's all of us okay okay
okay that's fine
that was not me that was not me either
but it's fine
that's close to me don't get too close
to me I have a retail on my back okay
that's fine
and I'm just gonna follow you
soon
why'd they always get me when I'm in the
tunnel
no
foreign
[Music]
let's have it
okay
[Music]
oh yeah I see it
come on chocolate
oh that was a shortcut
[Music]
nice
easy easy okay
it's so scary there
I think
I had that I was like third fourth place
the entire time at the until the end
of the race let's go
still not last still not last
whoa accomplished
[Music]
thank you
congratulations
I'm going back okay we're going back
was somewhat in control there because
like It's gotta be a road where Elena
knows the shortcuts and stuff yeah I am
yeah
choosing it
uh do we have uh some uh comments from
the winner Ina it was number one I think
ah yes uh I would like to thank my chair
mates
um
[Laughter]
yeah go let's go okay okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay so uh we're doing random teams next
there's four more races so please
everyone be careful to not choose any
roads that have been chosen previously
that I would appreciate that right um
[Music]
well even if you accidentally choose one
that has been uh chosen before don't
worry it will probably not be you so I
liked it so let's just let's just try to
not choose the ones that we have uh
raced before then I will do the random
teams now actually there is uh we don't
have to do the voice chat thing because
there is actually a way to do it here
and then once the teams are selected oh
there it is okay so uh invoice chat zero
zero zero one we want uh gura
and your feet all right
all right here we go
crazy wait what
huh
in one team
yeah I'm gonna lose where is it we
haven't played it once yeah
is it on hmm
oh
well this one
[Music]
is packed with like the really strong
ones I'm just like
right
yeah
let's go
let's go also I'd like to apologize to
you personally because I kept bullying
you in the previous rounds I got Karma I
did not know
[Laughter]
let's do this team so we got this go we
got this
We Believe
together
where is this
wait I hate this map
particularly hard for me I never
witnessed this map
it's okay
right in front of me right now uh okay
oh
let's go
yes
at least I don't know
wait we can do it guys don't worry we
got it we can do it
did I just beat you what
[Music]
no no
okay we're doing good
what oh
my God
oh no oh no this is bad this is bad
like even the zombies
[Music]
this one feels like a Toy Story
three more
[Music]
oh no wait who's in front of me right
now Arena
[Music]
um
items
oh my God oh my God
[Music]
oh
that was close that was very close Okay
uh second uh Ina I think I was seven I'm
seven
sorry it's fine
it's good it's good uh this is fine like
it's still fine it's not that bad it's
not that bad right now yeah yeah
okay it could be worse yeah
I don't like that we can hit our friends
that annoys me
please
[Music]
okay guys
okay
I just gotta beat Nina it's gonna be
Inna
I could do it let's practice today yeah
yeah you are our help
how are you guys so strong
Amelia Senpai can't you rewind time so
that we can like redo that and win isn't
that crony's job
for everyone just me Amelia is the one
with the watch right so yeah yeah and
she can go back in time and practice a
lot
um
what is this
oh what is this big blue I don't know if
I've ever played this one before I think
I haven't tried what is this this one is
like futuristic water parkish
oh
ah
okay I think what I don't like is that
the NPCs keep harassing me oh the ones
in the map yeah in the way
yeah
because
[Music]
oh I love this music though oh yes
oh oh Iris you're
okay yep I'm in the front right now but
this is very early game
yes
oh my God
[Music]
come on
oh there's somebody's actually flying
with bananas
well that's me
I'm gonna be careful okay
[Music]
really destroys my Pace okay
come on come on I want to see Ina I
don't know
[Music]
I didn't mean to I see her okay
he's using a shortcut oh okay
let's try to skip this shortcut really
helped though
legit like I don't know any shortcuts I
did not make it
uh I should have studied more
it's all right
sorry
oh
it's online
I don't know if you've ever played this
map
lucky number seven maybe uh I'm I'm
getting really right now I'm being very
salty right now guys
airport will do Us justice we'll ascend
and be embarrassing though you got
airport and I still do bad at it
thank you
I believe
let's believe believe
oh everyone's to the airport
wait is this the third race or the last
race is this third right I think this is
uh we got it yes okay we got this we got
this we got this okay
Sunshine Airport
[Music]
let's just hope that Ina doesn't really
know this map but I probably she
probably does
I think she does yep
do you guys know how it's nice with the
items that we got
uh like what do you mean by lose as in
uh from like thunder and stuff there's
no way to really prevent that
no no no I mean like if we got something
but we don't want to use it how how can
we
[Music]
trash
there is some of the items that I don't
really like to use
[Music]
it
come on
please
come on come on
I don't really get how this music like I
have this like speaker looking thing I
don't really know how I'm supposed to
use it
oh it's like uh if there are like a lot
of people around you you can just like
honk it
okay and everyone's just like I'm just
gonna honk it uh
let's just use it I have a bad habit of
holding on to items yes Ollie go Ollie
okay
the metal
come on
we got first and second place right now
I don't see Nina
no my item is good okay
you win
Tina she's in third place
okay oh
ouch
oh my god did I hurt you we're doing
good we're doing good so far okay
whoops I'm sorry oh that was close
okay we got oh God
[Music]
oh
please whoops
[Music]
let's look it we're in the same team
okay
just gotta make sure it's not enough
[Music]
[Applause]
listen oh my God
oh my God what's that
what is that what I don't know I'm eight
pretty you got nerd
okay okay I wonder how this looks right
now
[Music]
is just fine for me
what is it yeah it's such a close paddle
okay what are we gonna do next does
anyone have anything that they're
confident in music like I'm very
confident I like music Stadium
I got disconnected
before we picked the next one oh wait
wait wait wait I'm gonna join all right
[Music]
Music Park okay yeah
oh no can I can I join before it is ah
oh I'll tell I'll tell first all right
run for it it's not ready yet
right yeah people having children
there we go
wait I just realized you got a crown did
you get it yeah yeah we're like ahead by
six points
explains we gotta keep this up it's a
very close race
it up we got this we got hope
uh every Point counts ladies let's do it
please not not the clock not the clock I
don't like the clock
I hope so okay
this one has a lot of drifting so
whenever you guys uh
do you know the shortcuts for this okay
there there are a few shortcuts but
they're actually pretty tricky so I
wouldn't recommend them okay yeah all
right let's let's do this I don't really
recognize this place but let's go you're
gonna win this
oh no I just passed
screwed up on the beginning okay over
here
[Music]
then let's go when you're in the Brian
house smell you later
so you gotta drift in defense
and then another one drift
people
oops
oh yeah this is a lot of Dripping okay
here but it's really really tricky
[Applause]
shoot
okay okay wait uh who's first right now
I see Inna Nissan first
who's the first
because I saw them
oh God I don't like this map
oh now Guru is in front of me
[Music]
oh you're our last hope right now I'm
I'm doing really bad I'm a Zombie how am
I
it's okay
I got enough
I've eaten a lot of your kind so we're
good
Hope Has consumed zombie meat a lot so
we're good
I don't know
okay that's not good okay okay
oops
did I accidentally hit someone
okay be careful
oh no we got disconnected
oh God it's connected I got disconnected
control
Destiny is in your hands
sorry I'm gonna go watch one
of your
perspectives to see what's going on
[Music]
so when I eat okay I'm lost
well it was a valiant effort ladies and
one four four hey that's two fours in
there it four is a good number I like it
I can't say I'm unhappy
uh
yeah
and we have two disconnections so it
kind of doesn't count
um yeah
and when I rejoined like my points are
are reset yeah
um
I got disconnected like right before the
last lap oh no that was we sent my Shark
friends after the Wi-Fi cables
that probably means that you know the
last round if if Lisa you know got
disconnected and the points got deleted
that means that the last round final
result is not really accurate
um but that's okay but let's just say
the last round was an extra Encore for
fun and
yeah and I would like to give out some
golden yagos
right so okay they're not showing up on
your stream
but I'd like I would like to give one a
golden juggle to Ina for winning almost
everything
good job congratulations
[Music]
and I would like to give another a
golden Yago
um as a to Iris for also being
absolutely amazing
[Music]
another golden juggle goes to Dana for
being I guess the strongest in the ID
team holy moly okay
another golden jungle goes to gura for
being absolutely the speediest shark
I've ever seen now
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah for being super a big surprising uh
what do you call that
um
damn Wild Card yo honey
[Applause]
another golden juggle goes to Muna for
being amazing
I didn't see you that much on the race
but I think it was still shining
brightly as as the moon always does
the darkest time
for being also surprisingly damn good
number one
yeah
I know
[Music]
speed squirrel
s
[Music]
you'll participated
and another golden Jago goes to Cali for
actually really you know I don't you
surprise me you surprised me Cali I was
I was looking at you driving there and I
was like damn well what the hell man she
didn't even do practice arcs is she so
good yeah
yeah my mom was playing instead of me
that's why I was so good
[Laughter]
I didn't I didn't get last place even
once guys that was my goal and you know
what yeah I'm happy thank you for
cheering for me everyone thank you
we love you moving don't mind me uh chat
I'm not gonna be able to fix that now I
think one two three four five six seven
eight nine ten eleven
wait who did I not give her yeah
you were you were surprised
surprise sometimes I have I had an eye
on you thank you
[Music]
the last one goes to me
very much everyone
um I hope you all had fun
um can we get like a last last comment
from everyone let's start with uh Anya
oh me okay
um that was so much fun but I have to
practice more
I don't know maybe maybe
it will definitely be a next time yeah
there's always room for improvement
thank you
for the fun time
tell me what's your closing comment
uh let's see my closing comment is Kiara
thank you for everything you made an
amazing tournament you worked so hard on
this you had a logo commissioned you
made all of this stuff in as well for
helping with the assets but like oh my
goodness you organized the whole thing
and it was a blast and I just wanted to
have fun with my friends and I was able
to do that because you organized this
amazing thing just thank you so much for
for working so hard on it because it was
a blast
thank you I'm so glad you enjoyed it
thank you
Mom and Dad yeah thanks for everything
it was fun to look at nice good uh
closing comment please
oh thank you I want to say thank you
also to Ina and Kiara for all the hard
work you guys put into this tournament
thank you and I'm very I'm proud of
myself for not doing nearly as bad as I
thought I would and I would like to uh
say that it was probably because I fixed
my switch legs so I didn't have any lag
let's go Gamers let's go
no excuse I watched and I won though I
can use that excuse
in a long time I think yeah no practice
baby
let's go Raw Talent let's go rob
challenge
[Music]
ah yes so I'm just uh thank you for
organizing this and now we have uh
mishaps and some troubles uh Beyond but
yes thank you for this golden young I
will cherish it and talk to you thank
you so much
thank you too
thank you thank you okay I've completely
disappeared I'm sorry guys
okay Iris closing comments please thank
you so much for inviting me to this
wonderful tournament Kiara and thank you
so much Ina for the very very cute
assets and yes I will practice more so
that we can I can go against Ina
yeah yeah my goal is Nina yeah I'm
excited to do this again hopefully one
day yeah
[Music]
thank you I hope yeah one day I want to
win against Ina too that's a big pickle
that would be a big accomplishment it's
not that big of a goal
[Laughter]
I'm so glad I'm so glad you joined Holo
Ian because that's what made this
tournament possible yeah I'm really glad
to be able to join this wonderful
Tournament being part of the cool kids
yeah
all right Ollie closing
okay I'd like to say a very very big
thank you to Kiara Senpai for organizing
this I've organized it once and it was
really hectic so I can't really imagine
the links that you go through
logos and stuff and even the thumbnails
those must have been hard and also for
ears and wife we're making all of those
acids so quickly like you guys really um
how do I say it I really appreciate it a
lot and I'm sure all of us do so thank
you so much for your hard work it was
really fun playing with everyone and um
I may have not popped everyone but one
way or another you guys will all be on
the bottoms
I forgot about that goal yeah
you'll get them someday only you'll get
him
thank you thank you all right
um first of all um thank you for you
Kiara for organized this thing and no
you guys can stop thanking me
I I don't think without without you
organizing we wouldn't be like this I
mean it's it's rare to gather all the
whole life Indonesia yeah that's true
yeah so I'm so thankful for that and
also
um big thanks to inatsu for making the
assets it's really good thank you so
much and I hope in the future we can be
like this again yeah yeah
yes yes yes I hope so too definitely I
was thinking like maybe on on uh like
around Christmas or New Year's Eve we
should do something like this
yes
okay Nina closing comments please yeah
I'd like to say a big thank you to uh
Cara for organizing it of course I know
like organizing collabs and everyone in
different time zones and like schedules
it's really really difficult but you
really put a lot of effort into
organizing it commissioning like the
logo and everything really thankful
um and everyone feel free to use your
how to send cards like in your Mario
Kart streams in the future too
thank you everyone for joining us today
like it was so much fun like playing
with everyone and I hope you can do it
again it's been a pleasure
oh yeah thank you enough
cooperation this was a great
collaboration between uh kfb and Taco
Taco Bell taco eats definitely yeah
so well together you know
our fast food franchises are meant to be
together yeah we're speeding
okay all right
those comments
yeah I know you said stop but thank you
and also innocent pie uh thank you so
much and I had a lot of fun oh there was
a little miss out there there was a
little disconnection issue but overall I
had a lot of fun and I would love to
have this kind of tournament again in
the future let's do it you are so good
yeah
thank you
training so I'll get better
next time
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you
holding comments please
okay so it doesn't end there I would
like to say thank you
to everyone here also especially uh
Kiara and Ina like who's our amazing and
also okay uh I'm really happy because I
could actually uh gather and play with
all of you guys here yeah yes like well
uh I'd appreciate more more more
collabs like this so if you guys are
planning to do so
I I'd love to I'd be I would be happy to
participate so yes
thank you so much I love
it
[Music]
okay
please closing comments ah well first uh
I'd like to apologize
if I was salty if I cursed at you guys
oh no yeah
[Music]
uh and uh yeah thank you Kiara and and
Inna you guys worked really hard thank
you guys and thank you everybody for
participating it was really fun I know
it's hard to organize these types of
collabs everybody's so busy and
different schedules thank you and I had
a lot of fun thank you thank you
you know now that we have um now that we
have Polo Council we can like we don't
have to relay on these exact 12 members
anymore so next time if you want you can
do shout casting
thank you thank you everyone for
participating today
um I hope I hope everyone had a great
time even if you know maybe you were not
number one number two number three
that's fine I think today was really
just about getting together putting um
two communities two fan communities of
hello Ian and hello ID together ever and
just feeling United definitely and I am
always glad to do stuff like this again
so I would gladly invite you guys again
whenever you have time for it and want
to join and I'm sorry that you know
because since it's such an international
collaboration
um it's not gonna be an ideal time for
everyone so I'm so sorry for the girls
who had to wake up at like six seven a.m
or something like that I'm so sorry I
know it's tough it's no problem it was
fun it's okay I just wish my parents
could watch the news but I'll be I'll be
handing it back over to them soon it's
okay
I hope your mom enjoyed the tournament I
think she did I think that she enjoyed
it she played well hey hey
well well then with it I would like to
officially close to Holo Ian Holo ID
Mario Kart tournament everyone be take
care of your golden yagos to polish him
every day he wants to be shiny and
sparkly and yeah I'll see you guys soon
peace
[Applause]
[Music]