[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
[Applause]
do
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
for today
hello hello everyone harry hello hello
everybody hello everybody
hello did you guys miss us we didn't
stream for one day or two days
it's just one don't ask me i can't count
guys right now vacation and we still
stream this is the first time
the first stream and you got videos too
like honestly
[Music]
i just our fans are just so spoiled what
a luxury
yo
so many crying kiwawa
oh
cute
it's been eight years or eight don't you
mean 84 years 84 is that a meme yeah
i think it's from titanic okay
when it starts you know the the lady
that survived from the titanic she's
like she's starting to tell the story
and she said it's been 84 years i think
that's it i see yeah have you seen that
yes but like my bird brain was you know
a glitter yeah honestly when i picked up
the meme i didn't realize it was from
titanic until later on
yeah i think well welcome everybody uh
welcome to elena move your head
by the way yellow the other way
you're too tall q a and color okay with
pablo nessie oh cause i'm in the way
we're still on vacation we're still in
the maldives for the 100th time yeah
yeah not in bali not in valley but we're
on a beautiful tropical island where
there is like a resort on it and we have
a beautiful
hotel
hotel palace
and villa
been enjoying our vacation but uh we are
here to make memories so streams are a
must as well uh if you guys missed the
last stream was on dana's channel we
played super smash
30 fps let's go yeah no it's not bad you
guys you guys are already spoiled
nobody can complain about 720p like
that's actually a blessing that we're
even able to do this yeah exactly
yeah yeah yeah
i'm not tan at all i'm just red
it doesn't stay i have a really bad
sunburn so sad elena seems fine so far
i'm fine peoples are immune to sunburn
but we both have like bruises especially
nina because she keeps on hurting
herself or furniture i don't know why i
have so many bruises from this vacation
yeah
yeah she keeps on hurting herself like i
just chill and suddenly elena walks
around the room and suddenly
and i'm like what what the [\h__\h] did you
do now
nothing
yeah it's so long
that's how the conversation goes wow to
be fair is like you know unfamiliar
terrain so you have to like get used to
it you know right right right yes hello
uh i hope you guys decided for the q a
yes
is that a pun
no
spicy terrain spicy
spicy she says but it's so funny when
she says spicy it's so funny because you
are saying spicy no but then like if i
say it's like not very like you know i
say it all the time but then you start
saying it yeah
because it's kind of spicy when you say
spice but i like it because you don't
only say spicy about like hot things you
also say spicy about everything else so
yeah like the two curls
oh yeah
yeah we were watching
oh she was watching a crow doing during
the breakfast and she was like spicy
about spicy
maybe she's thinking about eating it
yeah just like you and the the the
hermit crabs and the transparent cream i
don't really care that much about them i
care more about the shells that they're
wearing right the hermit crabs
but you're like you're also like you're
even worse than me when it comes to
marine crabs you see the hermit crab and
you go you're crazy about it than me i'm
just like
no it was guys this is a lie guys this
is a lie you see
let's just say we're both crazy about
the hermit crab i'm not sure enough
but i'm actually like i've been
collecting like spicy shells
yes
yeah some pretty shells maybe i'll make
like a necklace or something out of it
when i get excited
yeah they look pretty and sometimes they
pick up a shell and they'll turn it
around and there's still a crab in there
hiding it looks really cute it's like
the picture that i showed you guys on
twitter it's cute because they they act
like no one's there and i see you dude
i'll see you you know
you see them and they're like
yeah it's so cute
well guys today we'll be doing
marshmallows and karaoke but we will do
it like scattered like we sing a song
and then we do these questions and then
we sing and then we do questions and
then we sing but we only have three
songs you know because we want to go out
and watch the stars before we go to
sleep yeah yeah guys for real like
they're like reverse mech flurry like
mcflurry like has the chocolate thingies
but it's like the the white part that
are like sprinkled and they they twinkle
like crazy it's it's you know i know
people are feeling sorry for me when she
tweeted that no no for real guys yo no
it's nice to like hear that you saw
it's unrealistic you think like it's one
of those things that are too good to be
through true and then you're like huh
fake or real and we came out of that
like we had a massage okay and we when
we walked out it was getting like pretty
dark already and i looked at the sky and
i'm like oh then look at the stars
they're pretty and she's like it those
that's not an airplane i'm like no it's
not moving it's not an airplane the only
twinkles in the night is airplanes
yeah but
after after reassuring several times
she was really fascinated by this
twinkle twinkle little stars
when we walked back it was like
so yeah but now it's even better because
like now it's really pitch black dark
yeah yeah and you see so many there's so
many wow even for me like in austria we
see stars but like maybe not as many and
not that clear um but here i guess
because it's an island somewhere in the
nowhere there's like absolutely no
pollution
yeah no cars no i mean yeah there's only
golf carts here
so that's why it's so clear here it was
really nice really really beautiful yeah
even though i'm fascinated yeah to be
honest
yeah well anyway
um should we start with the first song
and then rate some questions sure sure
we picked some
songs yeah we picked like three songs
that have nothing to do with vacation
but at least they can be archived so you
guys can watch the archive if youtube
doesn't uh private the stream let's go
if it does then it will be fixed surely
soon after so don't worry about it so
also tell us about like the delay we
tested it oh yeah but like just in case
you can tell us if it's like
we did test it and the other thing is
that um we we only have like
like
one headphone thingy
and we'll i'll just be holding it up in
the air and we'll be listening to the
sound blasting out of the headphones so
you got to keep that in mind too we'll
do our best though we tested it and it
works in theory
[Music]
i said we'll sing this one first right
we can just sing like from five meters
away then there will be the natural
okay i'm gonna mute this one
what are we gonna see what uh did people
recognize that already i wonder
it's an old vocaloid song
and we took the time for the stream to
part the lyrics so that it's not so
boring i'm actually like uh singing uh
solo sometimes and then together again
yeah
okay let me see let me quickly actually
i didn't check the i don't think i
checked the volume
[Music]
what do you think is this good
all right
like around here is that bad or not
different nah nah are you enjoying it
i think it's probably good
okay let's sing then
all right
i cannot oh it will be louder i think
oh wait no wait
i'll raise it here and i lower it even
more here cool
probably probably
yeah yeah it's probably probably fine
from
my
legs wait wait let's start again
again
there was some scuff there
what do you mean i'll show you the
comments if you want here comments
comment down
okay
again
a
[Music]
communication
it's really hard to hear the headphones
oh my god
where's my mouse
[Music]
is
oh
did we stay in the rhythm cause like in
the chorus we're singing so loud that we
get lose track of the instrument
good job i think
it's okay we did fine
they said okay this is fine you're fine
do you think it was nothing too weird
okay
there was like that one part but that
was like because you weren't really
listening yeah we know but now we know
we're like like in between us there's
just like
[Music]
oh well okay so now we'll have a little
singing break we'll answer some
questions and then we'll sing again guys
yeah like yeah sorry guys i feel like
it's you know the levels are kind of hmm
what's that what's probably fine i'll do
some tropical music oh
as a background music so let's open the
mushroom we didn't save the pictures
we're just going to look on our phone
guys sorry we got bad stuff to do yeah
okay okay you're gonna read first
question i can't read which one this
first one
if you go on a vacation together again
someday where would you want to go he
says
um i think
um i would want to go like kind of visit
lena in indonesia but and then kind of
like like together go to bali after
checking out lena's place
and maybe like seeing
you know this the the city and maybe
it's maybe some other id girls maybe
and then go to bali from there on
because now we're not in volley
we're not in valley
and we still see some people like being
like
bali they see in this yeah
but i've heard a lot about um bali as a
good vacation spot before
um but i didn't quite realize in my
brain that that place is in indonesia so
once when you told me i was like oh
yeah it happens all the time yeah guys
bali is in indonesia
sounds like like it um
isn't it pretty cheap to go there yeah
the hotels it was definitely more
affordable
oh oh so lasagna doesn't cost um 35
dollars in bali no it doesn't i don't
know how much i paid today for lasagna
for lunch 35 [\h__\h] dollars can you
[\h__\h] believe it six dollars still
water which you didn't even win yeah
let's bring that six dollar water bottle
even though in the room we have more
than enough free water yeah it says the
exact same thing the same bottle but
they always bring us a six dollar bottle
for me yeah whatever they're like
sneaking up for me once you want still
water yeah i like it as a tip that's a
tip for the stuff yeah
why would you wanna go on a vacation
together
eh i would wanna like go somewhere in
europe
like um
i don't know just like visit visit good
places because like you know like i
don't have i don't have that much
knowledge regarding europe like i would
know like tourist destination but then
from the from the point of view of like
uh you know uh
what's it called euro europe liver a
european european
yes you're a european yes yes yes i
would love to visit different stuff i
don't know
yeah my eyes open to the world i think
in austria i could show you
places that are not so touristy but
every other european country i think i
would probably also kind of go to europe
uh to to the popular
um
tourist spots i guess because i mean
there's a reason why the tourist spots
because they're beautiful and they're
worth looking at yeah but i think i
could at least like help with like
organizing where to stay and where to
eat and you know plan all that kind of
stuff i think i could do that um
yeah and there's so much so many
different countries to stay in europe so
i would love you to come over and
honestly look i'll show everyone around
who comes to europe please come please
come yeah
so basically yeah the answer is checking
out each other's
places yeah yeah yeah yeah
i talked to i talked to her before about
this and it's like oh what months are
good
and stuff like that so yeah i'm excited
i'm waiting for you okay next question
i'll read that one how is waking up
early in the morning to the sound of the
sea waves early verb life
easy or do you struggle to wake up
honestly when we arrived we were like
for example the staff told us that at 8
00 a.m there's morning yoga and we were
like no [\h__\h] way that we're going to
wake up at 8 00 a.m
yeah but then um ever since like the
first night
like already on the first morning we
started waking up early and every
morning we started waking up kind of
earlier i mean we didn't go to yoga
yeah i was you guys know i have really
like problems like i need i need hours
and hours to fall asleep and i have a
really [\h__\h] sleep schedule but i don't
know i was able to fall asleep
immediately every every night and also
easily even without an alarm woke up at
like 7 30 woke up later
and then yeah we went snorkeling
together stuff like that so
really healthy right now yeah
i guess we know that you know we can
only do snorkeling in the morning so
yeah that motivated us yeah that's more
important like you can wake up late any
time like anywhere yeah but like well
you're here might as well like you know
just spend time to the fullest i mean i
mean on a sunny day you could probably
snorkel later too but we were like
trying to deal with the rainy weather in
the first few days yeah and then like on
the rainy days we only had like non-rain
in the morning time so we're like we
have to we have to wake up and go
snuggling before it starts raining like
the problem is yeah the weather is like
super super super unpredictable yeah
yeah throughout the day yeah like for
example i would check the weather report
for tomorrow or even for the current day
like in the morning i would check the
weather report for the current day on
like for example tuesday and it said uh
okay two hours sunshine and then what
happens
rain rain rain rain and then
after the two hours maybe one hour
sunshine or whatever but like it's so
unpredictable it's never accurate here
and i guess it's because monster season
so rains are unpredictable happening
whenever
we were walking outside and then we were
heading somewhere walking on foot and
then yeah i was like oh look there's the
thunder we've been looking for and then
we just started walking and then like
not 30 seconds after that we got rained
on so yeah
yeah
but when it thunders
it's usually a sign that it will
pretty immediately start raining really
not the hard way but no we left our room
and we're like okay well it's not
raining so let's for once walk by foot
because up until then we let our butler
pick us up all the time because we have
a butler it's included in the in the
rain so
we we open the door we walk like 10
meters and then we hear fun and i'm like
oh this is the thunder from the
thunderstorms that i've heard about
because so i thought we only had storms
but no thunder yeah they said
thunderstorm versus thunder no now we
hear a thunder or like a i didn't see it
but just
thunderstorm and and then yeah as randy
said 10 seconds later really strong rain
rain starts like screaming and freezing
okay see she's so weird see if i'm weird
if you get rained on you would be so
cold there and that's nice but it was
still warm outside that's the thing with
like the time the rain is so the water
is so cold i actually are aren't you
calling she's like no and i was like
we had to like be in
to the to one of our yeah
like we were trying to take cover under
the roof of the entrance from another
like open water villa
and uh
yeah they opened the door they were like
what was with you and they're like sorry
sorry look at the rain they're just like
taking cover from the ring yeah and then
you know she's like that but then like i
don't want to get into the jacuzzi the
water is so cool or like the the
temperature in the room is so cold it's
21.
but then i'm also like it's too hot
sometimes
for the night time because the covers
are so so so thick and warm
we are weird like for the things that
are super cold you're not cool before
this you're also wearing a bad dance
you're also like suddenly i ain't too
cold
because it's real cold like imagine
getting rained on
well but yeah i mean honestly i felt
like okay it was a little bit chill but
not like like freezingly cold
after that we went back into we finally
made it back into our villa after like
we were picked up by a butler who was
just coincidentally driving by the golf
cart yeah she asked for her she probably
yeah so we ran in there and we were like
can you drive us like five meters
she drives us five meters we run back
into a room because then is like i need
to immediately take a hot shower so she
takes off the gloves runs into the hot
shower for five seconds i'm like
sorry sorry about your son
just saying like one minute because we
were gonna have her drive it somewhere
else now
yeah i i need to run that hot shower for
myself
yeah that was
really dramatic the rain makes
everything so dramatic but thankfully
recently that
what is the most surprising thing you
discovered about each other by staying
in the same hotel room or is everything
as expected
uh i don't know
ah i don't know
one thing i uh was unexpected i thought
was unexpected about you is that you um
you never drink
liquids except for when we have like
dinner or something i'm drinking liquid
yeah because i told you to drink
something
yeah but normally like you know i i try
to hydrate myself like throughout the
whole day
because i feel dehydrated so often and
then and elena only drinks at breakfast
at lunch if there's a lunch and a dinner
and like in between i said no i'm even
surprised that like you don't feel like
thirsty after waking up for example
oh i don't know but when you drink you
drink a lot
yeah maybe you know maybe pea falls have
a special water storage system thing
that's different from the uh
that's why you guys
i think i see why you're storing all
this
what was the question ah surprising
thing i said anything embarrassing
something embarrassing damn suddenly i
can't hear is it the uh
anyways oh yeah i didn't really know you
know like i talked to her but i don't
really know much about kiara you know i
think um it was it was so funny when she
gets like so excited about like hermit
crabs or
one time she was like you know we're in
a restaurant and she was like staring at
a gecko in the ceiling so excitedly oh i
wouldn't take it home
it was cute
i know it's cute but it's no it was more
like i saw it like up there really high
up in the ceiling and i was like it's
like you know like those cats up in the
tree needs to be rescued by firefighters
oh it's like you know how cats often get
you know stuck and they have to be
rescued by the firefighters
i was trying to get your attention
because you were on the phone
but but i mean okay i agree it's cute i
agree it's cute cute yeah and then you
told me that they're like really really
common yeah yeah yeah
uh i told her that you know um house
geckos there's just gonna come
and then uh oh no no i asked you like
don't you have don't you have a uh
geckos where you live and then we have
some but not like in the room london
houses just like in
in a forest maybe yeah she said no we
have this so i started like telling a
story about like how in the house my cat
would like play with the geckos and
she's like wait you have them in the
house and i'm like yeah
it's so common that we even have a
children's song that yeah but when you
said that i thought that maybe it's like
treated like uh like like uh
cookie buddies
oh yeah yeah cockroaches or so it's not
really treated like that but apparently
not really
it depends on there are there are people
who are scared of cockroaches and there
are people who are scared of these
lizards but
yeah no no no next question next next
what food from your own country that you
would definitely make the other one try
out okay weird sentence but um
what food would we make the other one
try out okay for austrian foods um i
mean in austria we eat because it's in
the middle of europe we eat a lot of
like dishes from like around the count
the countries that are around us but
well the most famous austrian food is
the schnitzel
have you heard of it yeah yeah yeah yeah
there's like um there's all kinds of
schnitzels but the like the austrian one
is called the viennese schnitzel
and you eat it uh with a special type of
lingonberry jam it's like a sweet gem
but don't worry it fits really well and
it's also served with um uh parsley
potatoes parsley butter potatoes really
good yeah so you know what it is right
like how it looks like look like the
the breaded uh breading yes it's really
good and you should eat it when you're
here what about you okay me ah but you
ate you ate this yakitori looking satay
oh yeah i really liked it yeah yeah yeah
yeah that was common in indonesia yeah
yeah yeah it's like street food
basically
the street food that's yummy you don't
like spicy food yeah
yeah even though i'm so spicy and spicy
spicy chicken
let's see i mean there's a lot of um
okay i wanna it's the stuff i wanted to
bring you i wanted you to try the kopi
luwak chocolate so is this it's a kind
of coffee maybe you can send it to me
when you send me the keyboard
yeah like i like i'll like chuck it like
one or two yeah i requested it to make
me a keyboard and she got really excited
to keep on geeking out of that i was
looking like hey do you want you know
and then the more stuff came out of my
mouth the more i realized like okay
let's just have this conversation later
not from this point
all right
you may read the next question
on the scale of 1 to 10 how hot was it
there and it really depends on the day
yeah it depends on the day yeah but like
even in the super sunny days wasn't even
like
super well it was 30 degrees
on a sunny day
which is for me like
yeah pretty much the maximum of where i
can say i can handle this after 30
degrees especially depending on how
humid it is it's really bad for me but
that's like in austria it gets hot but
maybe like i don't know how hot does it
get
sometimes it really does get to 30
degrees but
not human so anyway but on the first two
days uh i think it was like 20 degrees
most of the time which felt really cold
a lot yeah so we didn't even feel like
going into the ocean when it was so cold
but now it's much better yeah yeah did
it feel hot to you
me
honestly like i feel like it's normal
like this is how it's supposed to be
kind of yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah it it's
hot yes
it's sunny but like that's just how it's
supposed to be and then the water is
like pretty cold too so it's like nice
like when i compared to the oceans in
europe i feel like the water here is
like a really really
kimochi
um
thing between cold and warm like like
not exactly lukewarm but it's like a
refreshing
coldness that i wouldn't call cold hey
but what about over there
well i feel like in um many the most the
oceans in europe
feel really cold maybe it's because of
uh
the like which depending on which ocean
it is
like atlantic ocean i don't know i don't
really i don't really know anything
about that one anyway
yeah and but um yeah today was today was
especially called uh uh hot and even
though it's a bit tough that's how it's
supposed to be on vacation so i'm happy
with it um
yeah wait the next question after having
such a fun time during a trip do you
think you would ever want to visit the
maldives the second time and who else
would you want to invite
me
for me yes of course i would want to
visit the maldives the second time who
else would you want to invite you know i
would invite her again if she wants to
yes yes yes yes yes but next time not
during the monsoons oh yes please like
let's let's let's have a yeah like
in the proper season yeah yeah because
the rain [\h__\h] up um like half of the
vacation we still made the best out of
it and tried to say stay positive but
still but honestly like realistically
you know it would be even better if the
weather was perfect exactly yeah it was
really beautiful like
compared to
like a um
a vacation destination that's not an
island
i feel like this place you know an
island like this it's just so is it the
word secluded
it feels so so private like there's not
like no real tourists it's just like the
few people who are in the resort at the
time yeah yeah and the staff are because
of that also very very intimate and nice
and caring so it feels very different
from like a proper
uh no problem like a little
vacation on on a bigger
part of land where you know other people
are yeah yeah even if it's like the same
like tropical place you still see like a
lot of people everything is so public
you went to yeah you go to public places
this is like so yeah nice it feels so
private yeah private and i like it
it feels like you're in a different
world true true true true true truth
okay should we sing one song because we
already did half past uh sure sing one
song second song is uh um
we're gonna sing a whole live song
in bossa nova version because i thought
nobody kind of fits the tropical theme
at least oh
[Music]
it's a fun song but in this version it's
a
very peaceful
sorry i hope i hope we can hear this as
well
it's okay i'll try my best
[Music]
general
yes
[Music]
long instrumental break
uh
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
all the time
is your hat poking me
[Music]
foreign
yes
[Music]
one person saying susan no yeah why
aren't you done
i think it's fine
back to questions we don't have much
time left damn it uh rule okay okay come
on okay here uh you read uh no i think
we kind of had that
[Music]
unforgettable moments together with dana
also santa claus yes she's a big big big
klutz man
really surprising it's like dojiko she's
very dojika
she will like in like even though you
know as i told you she will hurt herself
so often but then also
she will like suddenly scream about
things
listen if you're surprised you can't
help but yelp right like
yeah but for example like it you you
scream like because you're surprised
about things where there's like nothing
really happens like something just like
for example let's say a tissue falls
down and you're like
no
something false and i'd be like ah you
know because like i'm startled from the
sound see that makes sense it often
doesn't even make a sound
do i need to record you for proof no no
i know when to film you because it just
happens whenever please know like on
solicitor recordings like come on like
no no no no no no no and very dojika
very spicy very spicy i love her
i love that she says that so much
anything weird about the moldings that
neither of you expected i have one thing
do you have something
ah
i think i remembered something i was
really
surprised at at least on the island
they're not i was gonna you know i told
you guys i was gonna change euro to
maldivian dollars but they use us
dollars everywhere they are they're
doing the billing usa all the all the
money on uh on the menus and the
restaurants they all talk with us
dollars
yeah they they just use us even though
they have more even dollars no it's
really weird i think they used their
money in like the main island maybe
probably because this is like a resort
area right so maybe usd is like easier i
don't understand why though
i was but then i'm actually really glad
that i didn't change any money
beforehand because it would have been a
huge [\h__\h] waste yeah
yeah i thought about it but i didn't
because then indiana was like you know
what i'll use my card
hopefully it works yeah no i didn't
change it yeah elena came prepared with
us dollars though yeah i did was also
really confused about why did you bring
someone's us dollars in cash
she was gonna give it to me because i
pre-paid the vacation but then i'm also
like
if you bring a
a currency that's not indonesian then
why is it usos why is it not euro
you told me
yeah i don't even catch but i'm from
europe we don't use u.s dollars oh well
it's okay it's okay that's funny it's
just funny is there nothing you else you
know i couldn't think of anything for
now maybe like let's move on
uh
oh yeah
um
so the thing is there's someone asked
are there unique local cuisines in the
maldives if so were there anything you
two particularly liked or found
interesting i'm gonna be honest we're
gonna be honest
once we arrived in maldives we
immediately were transported to the
resort so we didn't like have the
opportunity to really try anything
because even the restaurants here yeah
there is like
basically the only well deviant food
here is the moldivian breakfast yeah
then i had i had today and breakfast it
was like some curry with like tuna and
stuff that's i think that's the most
deviant thing we ate like throughout the
whole vacation yeah the rest is just
like you know oh yeah we had like
southeast asian food and stuff like that
that it was great but also yeah they
have different oblivion restaurants and
they're all themed after like a cuisine
but it's really not
deviant i don't even know what the
leaving food would be besides the
breakfast that you have which was
curry yeah we had a curry yes yes yes
with some was that a crap or no it's
tuna it was tuna no i mean the yeah it's
like also tuna
it's electrino no you had some tuna in a
bowl yeah and then you had the the flat
crap looking thing that's not chili
chili something no no not that
i forgot okay
no the crab you know what a crap
[Music]
yeah something something like crap some
bread yeah some bread it's not like
bread it's a crab wasn't it
not a bread it was some crab it was it's
not too hot so it was like some bread
maybe maybe well so and i'll get to eat
more even food somewhere but up until
now no
you want to read the next question
oh
this is
this is what is this
what are you guys thinking
[Music]
she hums all the time
suddenly
so many different songs i'm like how do
you think of these songs like suddenly
she will hum sparks and then she will
hide
she keeps on humming and then suddenly
she comes wicked wicked weekend
humming all the time at home all the
time every single time we walk we walk
back to the villa and just like
one time we
um came back to our uh house when there
was still a housekeeping person in there
and i'm just like you know trying to
take like out of his way and all that
and then we're gonna start humming even
though the housekeeping person is there
he must have been very happy to hear
like what did i have an idol
i don't know you were humming something
or like not even humming you were
singing at that point
yeah you wanted a walking playlist yeah
that's what you want i was i am kind of
actually okay on the first day i kept
singing
yeah there's something a small cute
happening
[Music]
do a lot what do i do
i don't know i was more focused on like
your
your hermitcraft interests and like how
um
i don't know
maybe i don't really have maybe
yeah it's like it's like so you know
like she sleeps so normally i sleep
normally is that she sleeps what kind of
criticism is that no i was like you know
she's like oh i can't sleep before i
don't watch netflix but then like she
watches netflix not even one episode
and then i sleep normally unlike you who
pokes me in my sleep
okay listen i was only the first night
though yeah yeah i was like after that
every night every night i was like did i
do it did i do something did i do
something and you're like no i'm like
okay good
i mean
yeah well
last night you were really like you were
pacing around the room though oh oh yeah
that's because i couldn't sleep
i didn't do anything in my sleep open my
eyes and so they know running out to the
balcony and then back inside doing
something inside and running and running
this way right now i'm like what is she
doing
but i realized after you told me that
that was still like really shortly after
i fell asleep i thought it was like 3am
or something no no no it was like very
shortly after you fell asleep it was
like 30 minutes after i think and aina
has quite the pace soon ah yes i am oh
yeah she is yeah that's a lot of habits
very pacing
yeah
see she knows so many things and yeah
i've noticed so many things about you
you have a lot of um
character traits
to traits yeah like also you you get
like bored really easily
i noticed so many things you get really
active
and talkative after drinking one drink
many many mannerisms that i've observed
about you some some i'm not even gonna
mention quirks you know huh
[Laughter]
but
it's just like i'm bad at putting them
into words maybe i'm just very observing
and i'm
but honestly when when if i had to think
about a habit that i have that you would
have noticed
she's always like super excited about
everything
[Music]
you do but like if we would say i
haven't i can't think of one myself i
haven't i'm just looking at it sitting
on my legs maybe but is that i guess
like okay well yeah when you stream you
always like do this the the saints are
like things yeah always they say that
i'm like why do you why do you sit like
that
it's more comfortable more comfortable
anyway
how many times has kiana talked about or
showing you pictures of a cat so far
okay this is very funny because up until
like very like today
i was always the one showing my pictures
to her and i enjoyed seeing them cause
like uh wait one second
[Music]
her cat is really really really really
cute
yeah i finally saw her uh her cast it's
very cute very cute i i saw the baby
picture and it
yeah after we saw that question on on
master model uh lena was like okay
you're gonna show me your question yeah
why are you done is this common like why
are you not doing this why are you not
showing your account no no no no
i enjoy showing my cats to people yeah
maybe if they ask her but i guess i
don't do it so unprompted but um i
welcome it i welcome showing people my
cats and i welcome people showing me
their cats mm-hmm
[Music]
hyped
about it that was because dinner was fun
yeah we had like
live music and yeah there was live music
i thought i didn't like live music but
then it turns out you know they just
didn't yeah the one i've been to they
just didn't have like the right levels i
think today the atmosphere just faded
well yeah
yeah the atmosphere and like all the
levels like you know we could still talk
to each other and listen to each other
wow
the music because usually like it
overpowers like
we can't chat when there's like live
music right so true so true music was
spicy
[Music]
and people were dancing too
yeah
somebody was like oh do you want do you
know what you don't want to join i'm
like yeah we have something to do we
have a stream oh anything shocking
what's your impression about tropical
climate so anyone said she kind of lives
in tropical climate yeah yeah so like
she was or anything like i basically
expected everything the unexpected one
was the star
yeah
i live in a non-tropical climate um but
i have experienced tropical climate in
japan which was that was really
surprising to me that japan has tropical
climate i was like so surprised the
first time like what i didn't expect
japan to be like that but
honestly japan summer so far was more
unbearable to me than here maybe maybe
if i wouldn't come in the monsoon season
if i would come into high season here
maybe it would be more unbearable but
the air
doesn't feel so humid as japan just
looking at your wrists
they're so [\h__\h] red it hurts all
right nice question let's try to answer
many
[Music]
well you know what
we're planning something we're planning
something so you know as mentioned
several times yeah just wait for it it's
coming it's coming and
during
june june um illustration is finished
uh we're still working on circulation
illustrations so cute yeah it's fresh
and super cute i want to show soon
yeah and look forward to it please guys
um
last time you went for a vacation with
cali and had a near-death experience of
skiing so for this vocational brand i
hope there's no more near-death stories
but if there is can you tell us yes so
uh
my floaty died the one already i told
you guys the one on the plane ride where
i was when turbulences were so strong
and i thought this was the end
and i didn't write my will
uh
and the other one
wait that was another one
i thought i was gonna die when like you
know i had like water in my
snorkeling i was like you're so dramatic
you say that so often
like oh my god i was gonna die
i'm dying the only way to save me is
that if you watch me if you watch five
episodes of animal documentary can
someone save me please
gosh i like getting a cramp in my life
oh kiara do you know how to how to heal
your crap maybe you should watch a
little bit of an animal
help me guys can someone take care of
reyna for me
okay next question
uh here uh you read
um writing for the vacation camp was
very worried about looking for the full
senpai to you the qrs succeeded
[Laughter]
i think like she's a rather than cool i
think she's a really like sweet person
she would accompany
watch
netflix
and bear with
my commentary what a sweet person
you would do that again today right
a little bit maybe but didn't you think
i was cool when i told you about the
stars yeah
what did you tell me about the stuff
that they exist
and
uh did you think that was cool when i
let you listen to my two upcoming songs
yeah yeah yeah yeah that's so cool
no no like um she she showed me like a
bunch of like idol stuff oh yeah yeah
yeah i thought that was really cool she
she really really really likes this
she's so like dedicated
hello
i didn't say i didn't even mention the
second one yeah i got my i got the first
demo of like yesterday and let uh
listen to it together yeah let's
continue okay where was i
uh hello project yeah yeah a bunch of
bunch of stuff like she also like you
know uh sent me the names in case of get
which i already forgot but like i
remember in my head they're all good so
maybe like
i was so happy that someone would like
like i i started showing her one song
and i was like she seems receptive i
guess i can show her one more song she
kept on showing her and she didn't seem
like she was sick of it she was very
interested and she appreciated the idol
songs that i showed her
all of you know my my favorite idol
groups from hello project i was i was so
happy like
sharing my interest she was she actually
said she wanted to sing them in her kind
of orchestra because this is kind of her
taste of music i'm like yo a yo yeah
i watch um i'm i'm not really uh you
know exposed to like the whole idol
music thing but like i i mean i really
like anime i had a little ani song
and yeah so uh i still like you know the
genre itself and it's like
they're so nice okay you know what we're
gonna sing one more song and the rest of
the questions we can answer in the recap
okay okay oh my god already one hour
oh my gosh where did the time go
okay next song guys i'm gonna [\h__\h] up
because i don't know about but i thought
you guys would like to hear this song
so
dana can sing it better she's going to
carry me
we're still last song guys and then
we're going to
go
exactly yes
okay
um yeah okay
jeff tell us when the bgm is too loud or
something you're a school
uh who sings the first part
are together yeah together okay oh my
god it's great happens it starts so fast
it's like one of those like fanfic
prompts you know like oh it's so scuffed
but then it turned
higher
[Music]
[Applause]
guys it louder wait you don't hear it oh
wait you guys
oh my god come on
i'm sorry sorry super lovely because you
couldn't hear it at all never mind sorry
i doubted you guys
[Music]
me
let's go
[Music]
m
it
[Music]
you
is
[Music]
foreign
me
[Music]
mama
that ended up being pretty nice yeah i
sang a spicy song spicy
yeah
wait which one's the spicy song this one
this one oh this is the lyrics it's
spicy okay spicy
i will be saying that a lot probably
even when you leave
spicy wow
well that was one wonderful hour and
then it was fun but we guys uh we guys
we we will have to leave you guys
because
because we have to watch animal
documentaries please
save me
like i don't mind watching animal
documentaries but she's like okay so
every five seconds you see for example
like a bear and she's like oh my god
spicy oh so cute i'm like hello hello oh
oh my god what's gonna happen oh [\h__\h] oh
my god no bye oh oh my god look look oh
oh oh she's so cute oh look at this
go get the fish
see what is the name of the area that
they're in what is the name of the baby
yeah so make sure you're still you're
paying attention no that was no it's one
but you were so excited about i don't
know i can be so freaking excited about
a freaking animal document i'm trying to
enjoy it and like just chill but she's
like dramatically subtitling this the
whole show it was you know netflix
there's like one uh the animal show that
we're talking about is about like babies
uh animal babies yeah
maybe you guys can find it and if you
watch it you'll probably notice that
this is
not necessarily something where you
would throw in a comment every five
seconds
it was funny if only i wasn't trying to
sleep but other than that it was funny
yeah that's why i don't sleep yet
but i know
then it
was go let's go and she literally like
waves at the baby pubs puff pups in the
in on the screen she's like
like she waves her hand
really
several times because it's so cute
you're you're kind of cute but
also also very active
yes very active
it's weird when we're in mountains we
have to be at it
no i kind of regret uh offering you
today to maybe uh
drink some alcohol again at dinner
because
i i said that because you know gotta be
active late at night to for a stream but
now now i get regret
because now we gotta watch animal animal
crossing the netflix show listen
whether i drink the six dollar still
water i'm still gonna make you watch
the animal documentary
a [\h__\h] a sit yeah oh oh just let me just
close this up before people get really
annoying apparently like i was surprised
about this too but apparently in the
maldives generally alcohol is not being
uh drunken because of what is the local
i don't know what it's called i don't
know oh um but uh uh this is a resort
and a resort in the maldives uh it
doesn't apply yeah yeah people the
resorts sell alcohol and it's all good
all good yeah some don't worry about it
okay but i i mean i don't think you guys
know me
yeah
so
everybody shut up about it okay
so we are going to
sleep
watch animal videos sleep no first we
look at the stars
and you can be like oh look at that
stuff oh my god it's waving at me
they're not animals
okay look at stars for a little bit and
then watch animal videos and then sleep
okay
you better keep your word
what's gonna happen if i don't get my
word
go find out you can you might fall
asleep you can just continue watching if
i if i'm if i if i if you fall asleep i
will tickle you i'll watch one episode
you said see she says like i don't wanna
be tickled so i respected her wishes but
look at one episode okay what guess
isn't it
no
sir no three four no [\h__\h] no no
oh
we're still after the vacation we're
still going to do like a recap and [\h__\h]
and we also want to do a vr karaoke
stop dying come on
do you need my phoenix feather to revive
i need animal videos to reply okay let's
go
bye-bye thank you bye
bye i hope you had fun guys the vlog may
disappear but don't worry we'll come
back yeah
bye-bye subscribe to the channel in the
subscription
[Music]
you