do
hello how
is everyone doing how's the audio
all good all good we are glad yes how is
it
check one two checking
i'm y'all
yeah yeah i think are you good are you
good we're good thumbs up
hello everyone it's been a liar
[Music]
it's been over a month since the last uh
collab yeah
oh yeah it's been a minute huh it's
christmas
yeah christmas seems so
far away i know
how long has it been 58 years
it's been almost two months wow
approximately
yeah no it hasn't i thought we were a
lot further into february never mind
it's been a month every month it's over
month
okay yeah how is uh how's everyone doing
today
answer them yes
[Music]
it's a tiny bit tiny bit yeah your boy
did you just wake up
hungry my tummy hurts oh no you get some
food
my reaction was late hi hungry oh he's
scared
i stopped myself from saying that i was
like oh maybe i did that too many times
don't care i just went for it
but i've never done that before oh my
god is low
am i low oh
yeah i think amelia is also frozen and
uh both kiara and guru left the room
so should we leave it oh no no
i'm using i'm using the jumpy jump jump
yeah
yeah f wording with y'all okay
okay okay i just did the uh
stuff so oh
what's happening what's happening on
stream
[Music]
don't worry about it oh pretend we saw
nothing
okay so um today is the uh
we're gonna be drawing as you can see
but we didn't really decide what to draw
yeah what should we do i was thinking
about that i wonder what we ought to
draw
i remember carol was like let's do a
dragon clap but
each other like for example cali like
everyone draws the person next to them
yeah that works okay please don't make
me draw tentacles please
[Laughter]
you got it boss i'll drop this it's
already no problem let me pull up a
cousin
reference you don't know
my heart what do i look like i mean i i
still you have so many little details
you know
everyone has so many details so true
yeah hey who owns the layer
underneath uh cali1 um
the one titled cali 2 who is the owner
if you could relinquish that layer that
would be fantastic
not
is there like a eyeball if there's an
eyeball highlighted
oh yes right right
click and leave okay
my hero thank you oh okay now everyone
is ready okay
now we're good everyone two layers you
can use
um
hesitation in your voice do you not want
to join me would you like to
know he's fine it's fine i'm satisfied
with this
is fairly easy to draw so yeah
a good good position to be in
yeah i'm a shark hat with legs that's
pretty much all you need to do
are you going to draw the butt thing
again the butt mud
huh that's not what i was drawing what
do you mean
my mcnuggees oh my god
okay what fun fun
you don't get my writing
no no i want it now now i want it
give it back please
okay i mean that's fairly is everything
okay
what's going on oh don't worry about it
okay oh don't worry
you know we should do we should try and
draw something from memory and then we
should like
not look at each other and then we
should zoom out and then see how we all
did
does that make sense no reference
drawing
yeah and then we yeah what the hell is
going on here
don't worry about it okay okay okay
how dare you mess up my masterpiece how
dare you mess up me
what are you talking about this is uh
this is what you look like it's
ha oh sorry excuse me hold on can't
forget the legs
wow wow those are wow those thighs
i know it's just great
unbelievable yeah
look i'm just i'm aiming for accuracy
here okay
this is what i do okay
okay okay let's go for real now
let's go for real this is for real
[Music]
what are you talking about
what do sharks tummies look like
ah they're round and
yeah hi
no i'm calling you very soft
it's very high
how do i deselect something i selected
something but how do i deselect it
dammit
try at first it didn't work now it works
okay
okay well well well
i can't that's such a beautiful
beautiful satori
i'm sorry i'm not sorry
i haven't seen yet i don't want to look
i don't want to be a surprise
[Music]
okay
maybe i should just look away from that
left side
yeah i won't look until it's finished
although
my obs is open so i can kind of see
to the in the corner of my eye
i mean it's kind of cute but that's not
me
oh i mean i
probably knows if that's true
you know what okay kiara i i hear you
loud and clear i'll draw i'll draw
i'll draw the the fake version of you
the your other form
maybe i should be sending you to the
local room huh
uh good luck i'd like to see you try i'd
like to see you try to do that because
i'll draw you know what i'll draw i'll
i'll draw the way that you think that
you look how about that
okay but i'm saving this
i'm saving this this needs to go in a
museum
in a museum i tell you the way that i
think i look are you denying hookah
papa's majestic art
of course not i'm just saying that i'm
saying that the spirit of
who papa's uh masterpiece
uh is the was what i have drawn here
today this is what uh
this is what who k papa intended this is
this the soul of
his this is his drawing mom and dad
wearing a shark head but what if she was
a shark wearing a human head
that's a horror
i can see that oh my gosh it looks
something like uh
wait isn't that like a mermaid a shark
instead of you having a shark hoodie has
shark teeth that had human teeth
now
images
wait what would that look it would look
like what does a shark look like
even
it's a great question
yeah i just watched yeah
they had lots of sharks in that no i
actually didn't
wait this looks like i've ever seen a
hammerhead shark um
yeah they look funny
yeah they're like a vacuum cleaner and
they have a little mouth that's a great
observation
i forgot the bottom bottom little bit of
the canvas gets covered up but
maybe i can decrease the size of it a
little bit
is that a hammerhead shark or a dice and
vacuum
i see what you mean i see the two
different pictures
they're the same thing that's like that
picture do you know a picture of that
teddy bear with the human teeth
oh yeah what yes yeah i'm curious
you've to my curiosity let me see
there it is hey misos what makes things
creepy where do i have this
hey vsauce good out here hey visa is
good here why does this teddy bear have
human teeth
oh my god i think it would be less
scary if it had like sharp teeth
honestly
that's a special kind of curse that's so
cute though
huh huh okay you have a really
interesting idea of cute
kisses between what you've said today
about my drawing of you and this
um anything that ina draws is cute
that's what you're talking about never
mind everyone oh that one is cute that
one is cute
i question yourself so cute a little bit
it's a cute cute cute it looks like
looks like a fish a cute fish it looks
like that that one orange
that talks yeah yeah
no
[Music]
a little more flat than that
oh damn it i don't even
you know cute oh my god i am adorable
i finished
more detail more detail maybe you can
give it more color and stuff
okay yeah
we got like a half like half an hour
what you want to do is try to make it uh
hyper realistic but don't change the
drawing like the way that it is
like you should just try it yeah yeah
they call it do they call it rendering
i'm so cool
hyper realistic rendering shading
either one is fine okay is the screen
frozen by any chance
um nope oh okay
chad was saying stuff like that it's
just it's just no one's drawing so it
looks frozen
don't worry about it
you know you look like a bunny rabbit
sometimes with your
ah that's cute you look like shrek
i love shrek love shrek you know what
you know what somebody once told me that
some bunny ones some bunny once told me
somebody was told who is that bunny
that me and callie matt we met a sweet
bunny
cuddled a lot with that bunny and now
callie wants to get a bunny
yeah i'm getting a bunny now oh are you
ready seriously
uh-huh i'm going to pick it out uh maybe
next week but i want to research a
little bit more about taking care of
rabbits first
oh cute yeah because i'm just
i'm kind of i don't know i get a little
lonely these days
i understand yeah i almost got a
tarantula because i also feel lonely
oh that's so sweet they're sweet
yeah they're sweet creatures maybe you
should get a pet kura that can
interact more with you i didn't crawl
all over you
and then you would get it that's what
they do
but thank
dragon would still be cool just uh not
very practical i don't think i mean we
have komodo dragons in the underworld
but uh i don't think humans can really
raise them
yeah so bearded dragon it would have to
be
yeah yes even better
go big or go home
yes sir what are you gonna name your
bunny
yeah good question i haven't decided not
pecora
not naming i'm not naming my bunny
though after my senpai that's strange
not peccary for dinner
that would feel so weird stop pooping in
the cage
that's my senpai that's my i want to
respect my senpai i don't want to treat
my senpai like a pet
so yeah i don't know yet i'll have i'll
let you guys know though when i figure
something out
yeah gotta think long and hard give it
like a really terrifying name
of like something something powerful
from the underworld and then it's just
fuzzy fuzzy bunny gilgamesh or like or
like
killer or satan or like destroyer or
something like that
yeah yeah yeah that's a perfect name
it's not
[Laughter]
sorry excuse me i had a little episode
there sorry
excuse me now you know if you know you
know
that's great
wow the details on gura beautiful
i gotta say that belongs in a museum
thank you
where are my toes oh okay
kiara has no arms yet i'm wondering
where i should put them maybe behind her
back uh like somebody who's copping out
and giving
up um
why are you sorry i'm sorry
that's what i do when
i draw hands people always describe it
it's like a box right
yeah and then it's french fries coming
out of it yes
yeah this one and then hand
plus a pinky perfectly beautiful
thank you 10 out of 10.
dad that looks like a robot
mom is it true that
in your hand some people do you know
what i mean
what
i think you're right actually okay they
do
they did try to make uh many of the
kanji look like what they're actually
supposed to be representing
oh so that would mean that when you hold
hands
i'm not sure if that came from that but
it makes sense
makes sense it sure does
that's very smart
[Music]
okay all right well yeah
that went bottom lap yeah i sure did i'm
not surprised
it's getting intense
everyone's drawings are so good i'm done
[Music]
okay you gotta you gotta spend
more time
[Laughter]
time for the second frame
that would actually be so cool if you
can find me on here
i feel like that yeah a whole new
a whole new world don't you dare close
your eyes
can of worms yeah they probably would
have to
format it a little differently huh yeah
but
my train of thought derailed when
someone said
yeah a whole new world whole new world i
was like your dress
my principle is just lacking today
it's okay it happens to the best of us
you're all good
i actually don't even think um that i've
completely woken up
to be honest i could still be dreaming i
could um i could still be in a dream
sneakier yeah i don't know um i really
i don't know i feel like i could fall
asleep right now that's why i'm drinking
oh wow oh why here to ice cubes i'm
i'm drinking uh it's not alcohol
[Music]
it's not it's not it's a chai tea latte
it tastes like christmas yeah yeah yeah
i mean they aren't really serving i know
i know they aren't serving hot drinks
for some reason
um which made me sad but what can you do
so
yeah it's iced ice is good though
it's like how ice cream is good in the
winter sometimes you know
even when it's gone yeah exactly you
can't really explain why but it just
tastes good
what's everyone's favorite drink
water
okay we got two waters waiting did you
also say water
i was i was just repeating someone oh
droopsy right
doctor whoopsie yeah it's not isn't that
even his favorite
i don't know these things i don't drink
it that much but i'm saying this
i'm drinking it right now oh my god
i got one next to me too oh
we're dr oopsie buddies right now i feel
connected
it's just sweet give me a sip
my favorite is uh iced tea dough like
lemon iced tea
or pink iced tea oh it's not orange soda
no yeah i thought you loved orange soda
what why
because every time that we hang out you
buy an orange soda that's not true
that it is true that's not true it is
true i'm the one that had to throw away
the trash when you left
i put it in the in the bottle in the in
the bag of bottles it was
it was a fonta an orange fonta and i
remember it
i literally found it only one time and
the other time we hang out i remember i
saw you holding it
you were holding an orange soda
yup i remember your orange thought
escapades you like orange soda
the verdict who's telling the truth
hey you know what you exposed me plenty
of times yesterday
plenty of times yesterday now i'm
exposing you you know that kelly
talks in her sleep did you guys know
that uh-oh
thanks for telling the world this is a
conversation
with like full out conversation with
them no but i realized i should have
tried because apparently when you
actually try to talk to the people who
talk in your sleep they often reply
and they do yeah what they what they
said before usually doesn't make sense
but when you reply
their answer usually makes sense because
they're like talking to you then
i should have done that missed
opportunity
yeah yeah what a shame
[Music]
does anyone help else have like uh
sleeping have ab habits that they know
about
um what
what i like to kick a lot oh oh
stormy sleeper i see
i apparently giggle in my sleep a lot
like i laughed
[Laughter]
that's true if kuranami have a sleepover
it's gonna be like i'm a kicking girl
girl be like
oh my god
he does like so long
because i look wrong his feet are huge
[Laughter]
i gotta stay grounded you know
definitely but does it mean that when
ina
when you draw inna with huge feet does
it mean ina has
huge tentacles how does that correlate
i've heard that correlates how i think
that's
it sounds uh that sounds fake um yeah
that sounds good
let's not cross that line chiara i don't
think they got it
like somebody's playing the job
[Laughter]
definitely has huge tentacles
i mean have you seen your tentacles
i mean it's mommy
[Music]
i'm your mommy yeah
yeah i'll say no more i'll say no more
then you girls gonna do the talking if
i'm gonna shut up you guys you guys no
you can keep talking it's just uh uh not
everyone might reply
okay we might just be uh
facebooking a little hard
yeah i'm just really focused on this
drawing yes
yeah yeah focusing on that looking good
yeah it's looking it's looking pretty
nice over there
yeah i'm quite happy with that
uh-huh glad to hear it
[Laughter]
hey when's the last time you guys
replaced your toothbrush
wow a few weeks wow maybe one week ago
actually not too long ago because it
worn out
that's good how about eight times
i actually have several that i kind of
like rotate through
you said we had to carry the
conversation so i'm carrying the
conversation
[Laughter]
i think it's a reasonable question can
we hear the
thought process how you got the
toothbrush
do you remember no
i have no idea it just came in my brain
did you change your toothbrush recently
no
i haven't for a very long time very
honest
and very honest honestly you can sell it
for a lot of money
well i'm using i'm having an electric
one
get my girl toothbrush for sale oh
you should smell it you can make a you
can make a bug off that you know
oh god black and tartar included
yeah hi
i i wouldn't i wouldn't sell that i
don't trust the people who gonna buy
that i don't trust them
i mean when do you you trust their money
though
no all right well i guess that's fair
money is not everything
that's true that's not what i said
that's not what i said i'm just yeah i'm
just saying money is not everything [\h__\h]
yeah
did you buy kelly's toothbrush
no
shocked everyone's so shocked what she
wouldn't buy her toothbrush
i thought she's a pure hentai what i
mean that's the correct response
um it's the correct one but
i too was a bit surprised okay
i guess i'll keep drawing this one
i don't know how to draw me
just draw circles and call it done
hey dad where are my
arms oh my god hang on
you could since you've got time you can
also draw her tentacles
her huge tentacles
[Laughter]
but don't forget the louis vuitton
pattern
yeah yeah um you got to tell me where
you where you bought those tentacles
because i like louis vuitton
yeah oh really are you sure
you know literally their designer brand
louis vuitton louis vuitton don't look
too closely at the pattern yeah i
totally got it
[Music]
[Laughter]
wait are you telling me that that it's a
knock off oh my god
no it's a girl it's a limited edition
exposed limited edition
you know i think you gotta go to jail
bunk jail
girl no it's limited edition
one one in the only one in the world
very expensive you can't get it
i really want to see um ina get like a
collaboration going off with like a
designer bag company
yes please oh yes i'd buy that
and i'd strut around the city with it
just saying i would probably uh
ask if i can get a sample
i mean sure you need to get the product
of course yes at the end of the review
you know
yes if you cut a tentacle off does it
grow back
that's a great good question oh my god
like in uh super mario sunshine
uh you know that that weird tentacle
master it's not exactly
something that ina is it's not exactly
the same
thing but when you pull out those
tentacles
i think they don't grow back what about
enoch
well they they kind of get summoned from
the void
so ah there's a lot of them
replaceable yeah
whoa so we can make a delicacy
out of it i mean i mean can you make
it yeah people
eat anything we have me and kelly
on our trip once again we have realized
people eat
anything but would you eat switch
cartridges
what i tried it i licked it how was it
oh my god
it's very bitter
she didn't like it because she was
testing it she just thought that it
looked tasty
looks like that is accurate
accurate look like potato chips
yes gamer chip give me a change
oh dear
i think i think yeah maybe
we need to think about our um
food intake
we gotta have you know we gotta eat
healthy so that we can do this for a
long time
i had a salad the other day it was fine
okay
a burger yummy
you know hamburgers are pretty balanced
it has like
bread and like lettuce and meat yeah
as long as it's not every day then it's
uh yeah sure as a fast food
worldwide fast food franchise owner i
would like to say
that burgers are healthy
yes but it wasn't kfp i'm sorry that's
okay that's okay so burgers are helping
but next time you better buy from kfb
they didn't have delivery
oh you got to fix that attention
yeah i wonder if we have a delivery
department uh
got to check up on that yes you can team
up with uh uh taco eats
yeah yeah yeah hell yeah
taco eats i didn't know that existed yep
that's delivery
are they well paid or are they you know
there's only one dying from starvation
one worker is it you
i just you got a side job delivering
food
yeah are you okay financially
i love your food yeah do you do you need
help
should i borrow you some money or no no
no no i just do it because i like doing
it
it's like it's like you know when you
get to travel around the world
and deliver food and taste a little bit
you have a little bit of delivery
just a little bit yeah how much
time does it take for uh uh to deliver
to
my place uh
do you have a fridge that can
uh fit a uh a person inside
no no no wait what
more importantly is it running
[Laughter]
no
i mean i think you know what i'm
thinking but don't worry
about teleport proofreaches you can
teleport through fridges did you know
that
neither that's why sometimes you put
like
you put like food in the fridge and then
like sometimes it goes missing
i know that works also with microwaves
yeah
when you put uh when you put a banana
into the microwave
you know what you get out of that jelly
banana
exactly you know i love you what
wow that's sick
[Laughter]
[Music]
sorry sorry
anyone doing anything special for
valentine's day
yes uh dying sleeping oh
same i mean i was thinking of
doing like a little stream for the uh
the deadbeats
um so i think i'll do that probably yeah
i'm doing uh i'm doing something that
has something to do
with uh my announcement that i'm doing
after this collab stream
oh yeah that's what i'm doing on
valentine's day
wait oh okay that makes sense i thought
we were i thought it was valentine's day
i was starting to panic i'm like wait a
minute
i was like wait wait we already made it
[Laughter]
but yeah i am uh making chocolate
already today on my stream
valentine's day a bit early but i i just
thought i
it would be fitting to do it today will
you
give us some i will give callie somebody
i don't know about you
oh wait hold on what yes
i thought for me why yeah i'm making
chocolate for you
that's nice can i share with the others
i can't eat it all myself okay i'll give
some to gemma
to manage your son
he
i'm making it with your beloved uh
german chocolate that you like so much
because i introduced you to german
chocolate
oh all right thanks yeah
it's interesting how um valentine's day
is so different
in japan compared to other countries
well yeah cause other countries don't
really do white day today
yeah they got to valentine's day uh in
japan
but i don't even mean that i just mean
like on valentine's day in japan the
girls
kind of uh all make chocolate on their
own and then
and they give it to their crushes or
there's also tomochoko which is like
um yeah chocolate for their friends yeah
and there's girichako too which is like
you give it to like your co-workers and
stuff which is why i
i wish i could give i could give you
guys uh something
you know yeah well basically everyone
every girl in japan is making chocolate
for valentine's day
oh really yeah i i never did
that before so today is the first and i
hope i won't fail
chocolate okay so this is the thing my
viewers are also confused as to how i'm
making chocolate it's not like i'm
making chocolate from
scratch like out of cacao beans or
whatever
and you basically you buy like cooking
chocolate
and then you make something with like
pralines or cookies or
muffins or anything most girls make like
pralines
and they decorate it and they add some
stuff like nuts and stuff into it
and they package it nicely it's it's not
that difficult but it's just the thought
you know that that you make something
handmade instead of buying store-bought
chocolate and giving it to your crush
it's more personal oh okay
very cute that is cute yeah that's what
i'm making
see i see i like chocolate covered
strawberries
yeah i made fun do recently and then i
dunked the strawberries in there and it
was really good
oh yeah i love fondini mm-hmm
i got a fondue machine have you seen
those videos where they put cheese in
the fondue machine
and then it gets
hardened when it starts flinging around
what i've never seen that that sounds
dope
it's very very very wow i'm gonna show
you that
what it hardens up it shouldn't be doing
that yeah they were trying
trying to make fun like cheese fondue
but i think they got like the uh
recipe wrong maybe and then it was like
you know how it has like goes like
through the two and like flow out
and while i was doing that it like
started like spinning and then like
everything started falling apart and
like flying off
and the cheese was just like woof
yeah i don't know if i can find the
video
this dank i want to see well i
definitely prefer uh chocolate on you
i used to do that a lot for christmas
chocolate fondue
oh maybe i'll link it after because i
don't know if you haven't
audio muted but yeah oh yeah cool
yeah but i think i think kelly would get
a good laugh out of that one
yeah i love cheese fondue as well so
yeah that sounds perfect
i never had fondue doesn't i put like
alcohol and cheese fondue or am i
thinking of something else
you can but yeah it's not required
are you gonna add color um
maybe i'm not sure i want to add color
but amma has this uh check checkered
pattern on her skirt so cute
yeah i'm probably drawn and i'm for some
reason i decided to draw her
like with her backside and now the thing
is i don't really know how she looks
from the back and but
but your mama at least recently uh
uploaded a reference but i i'm not
look right now so that's that oh
that's australia are you not allowed to
look at references
yes we established that in the beginning
whoopsies
yep it's okay your your drawing looks
very accurate so
um at least at least um you mean this
one hold on yeah this one
this one this one right
don't get me wrong the other one's like
a fun doodle but this is the real one
yep
i really like the crazy thing that gouda
drew that
on the left side
looks like really crazy some nightmare
stuff
it's perfect we actually have things
like that in the underworld so
i feel really excited
do i know i know i'm sorry
i love um how much of a thug i look like
up up there
ina in your drawing um the gap moe is
very real and i enjoy that
so yeah wow super dope yeah just you
know big ups
thank you don't don't mind me you're not
you're in a paid outfit don't don't mind
oh no it's okay i think i think that's
cute um
that's even like more gap i think now i
kind of want to be a maid
just just for a day just you're watching
moe moe kun how's that
excellent yes
wow so good i got experience you know
one of my past lives
been there done that oh the maid
hell yeah
do
[Laughter]
kind of sounds like death if you say it
a certain way
yeah death yeah that's it
i like that can you only uh sell shades
in this uh program oh i think there's a
soft one too oh yeah if you go hardness
and then you lower it i think it might
oh softer
now ah
i see oopsie
what did i do okay let's go and
gotta do this with two layers huh yes
you can always out of there i guess
was that a sneeze i was a cough bless
you
thank you though thank you for the
blessings yes
can i lock a layer hell yeah i can lock
a layer fantastic this program is
amazing
oh amelia that's really good i like that
yeah
you're welcome wait no i can't
muscles there's guns
it's a lot to take in i'll make a muscle
i'm good i don't know you play fps games
he's got guns
she doesn't have eyes once
[Laughter]
[Music]
new outfit review and she did such a
good job that i wanted to learn how to
sing the song
dude it's so fun don't let your dreams
be dreams
i won't i'll make all my dreams come
true no matter what it takes
yep you got this girls be ambitious
like like this old man what what
sorry that sorry that was a never mind
it was a rookie i'm sorry excuse me
never been called for
let's go and call for
the song
[\h__\h] rocking
[Music]
that how do you say that for rooney
literally
in my streams uh we
we have tried out a lot i have almost
saw some
sung the whole let it go song oh
and you know how disney is yeah wow oh
my gosh
it seems like it should be okay can't
touch this name
sorry dun
you dun actually people seem to really
like the acapella
i had to sing acapella during my um my
endurance stream because the we just
couldn't fix the lag
so i was saying everything acapella
people really liked it
acapella streams are fun
wait how do i add a new layer
i got it i got it i think is that a copy
oh yeah it's a copy okay
now i do hold out this is fun i like
that we're drawing like this together
oh yes nice i miss uh
drawing with friends actually back in
the day i used to do this kind of stuff
a lot
yeah with my reaper friends we'd all
just jump into like one of those what
are they called google hangouts or
whatever
um they just draw together yeah that
sounds funny
yeah you know what to do today back in
the day i used
these uh oy cocky boards
it means yeah drawing
dale i really enjoyed doing that oaky
wait i can't oh i was gonna say i can't
draw my
new layer well i was on my eraser makes
sense
nice mystery soft
there you go oh [\h__\h] what's your what's
uh
it's good skin color oops that's
too dark okay kelly what color shade
would you like
wow um gosh for maximum let's see
um from uh maximum tool bag
neon green nice good chili yeah
thank you i think that would be perfect
beautiful oh boy are those lighter
shades
edn that's green for shrek
yeah you really like shrek don't you
i mean yeah it distracts eye
you know i just like um i don't know i
really like shrek's confidence
you know how he's all like get out of my
swamp and you know that that kind of
thing
yeah like shrek is like you know
confident um did you say that
shrek is what's life
i'd say love first but maybe life
afterward
hey question does anyone know shrek's
kind of niagara height
by chance what i can google it yeah
well i'm sure they know yeah i'm sure
i'm sure chad will let us know shreks
can like can anyone check
the shrek wiki the shredder
oh man i guess it's not meant to be huh
all right well no problem
hey listen we can still be friends
shrek is a great role model that's all
i'm trying to say
i'm trying to say it's
listen it's a good role model
i mean it's a touching story if you
watch if you watch the movie
and you really pay attention to like the
plot um and just like the themes and
like the motifs you know it's it's a
it's a good movie you know i like the
gingerbread man
i was about to say my favorite
i'm getting all these shrek memories i
can't wait to watch it with kiara
yeah we're gonna do marathon shrek
marathon
trek along yeah
that's gonna be fun it's gonna be great
i can't wait
we're gonna watch uh both the movies
right kiara of course but yeah they're
one reason you think both but isn't
there free
there's there's a third and it's fine
but it's just i feel like the first two
are just you know
the classics you know those are the best
ones
yeah if there is
then i have no idea
oh no
oh god no
all right so yeah three shrek movies got
it no problem well the first one
first one is definitely the best forever
in my heart
yeah did you guys play the shrek video
game on
you had like press the buttons and like
not really a rhythm game but there was
like a button like mini game you press
the buttons
in the fights and stuff yeah i don't
remember wait
it's the shrek 2 video game you could
choose to play as like shrek and then
like put some boots and like other
characters
yes yeah yeah it was my favorite game oh
man guys my favorite game back in the
trip collected like eyeballs and stuff
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah oh my gosh you
remember do you remember the level where
you had to fly the dragon
i could not do that i had a hard time
with that
oh my god that was a good game
it was a fun game i also remember a
shrek game that i got i think in a
mcdonald's happy meal
um it was for the playstation one um
and yeah you just you went around shrek
swamp and you could play little mini
games
um i forget what it was called though
but i i never beat it because the the
disc was scratched and i couldn't beat
the final boss
that's heartbreaking yeah
mm-hmm
oh man someone new in the chat that's
right yeah shrek treasure hunt
yeah all the good memories are coming
back
sorry this is turning into a shrek
stream excuse me i'm going to calm down
on the shrek you know i don't want to
push my interest on other people too
hard
excuse me that's very ky of me sorry
about that
do you own any shrek like goodies
goods oh memorabilia
you know what guys merchandise yeah i
remember
i remember um for my what was it it
might have been my
uh 500 millionth seventh birthday
um i remember a friend got for me um
a shrek plush and then also a puss and
boots plush and you like pulled
you like pulled uh you pulled his tail
and then he like said like
little um antonio banderas lines wow
yeah it was good it was good
i don't have them anymore they're lost
with time but i treasured them
they were my treasures didn't they have
like
a lot of food shrek food items like
twinkies and ketchup and stuff like that
was it green i remember shrek fruit
snacks yeah
yeah they like green ketchup green
twinkies
i don't recall it tasting very good
maybe it slides not around anymore yeah
probably
it would be fine if it tasted like
regular ketchup but it just kind of
tasted um
just you know just kind of bad which is
unfortunate tasted like green
yeah it tasted like the color green
yummy sure
i wonder if it was just like really
really like
pulverized relish
you know that's a possibility yeah
that's i know i mean it depends on what
you like
you know if you like relish on your hot
dog i suppose maybe it tastes good i
don't know
maybe maybe kind of curious what it does
taste like you know
yeah maybe we should
ketchup and then we all try it together
fantastic they can eat the twinkies
though drink you never go bad
oh yeah yeah i'm sure that there are
still some that exist from like 10 years
ago that still tastes great
i thought people like debunked that like
how twinkies never go
bad oh you do
i was like oh my god oh
yeah it was a marketing ploy
oh no we've been lied to oh we've been
had huh but i've never had twinkies
before
uh-oh i'm not sure what that looks like
yeah i was gonna say maybe that's all
right maybe that's a good thing
yeah i feel like a lot of the things
that you girls have eaten
is things that i have never eaten cause
i'm from australia
wink oh yeah
[Music]
have you had kangaroo
no but i think i think i've had
crocodile before
yeah tastes like chicken right
i don't remember to be honest it's been
a long time
i don't i don't necessarily want to
repeat it but i i don't think it was
very uh super bad
it's kind of like how how frog legs
tastes like chicken
maybe since they're sort of similar
maybe it also tastes like chicken
and here's what i thought yeah
[Music]
i generally am like like uh
someone who prefers to not eat things
that i don't know
a [\h__\h] but adventure
yeah i did try some new things uh
recently
with kelly and uh i have to say it
wasn't as bad as i imagined you didn't
hate the sashimi
what yeah yeah you thought it was fine
yeah it was a
um it was a good
i wouldn't say it as good as chicken
all right i mean that's fair hmm fair
chicken i mean you love chicken though
i love chicken sorry no no no um i don't
want to scare my employees i don't eat
chicken
i i eat phoenix yes yes yes yes yes yes
i don't eat chicken my
on the thing is my employees are all
chicken so when i say i eat chicken they
kind of panic
hey chiara you eat your own kind no no
no no
no i don't eat chicken and i don't eat
my own kind and that this is okay
um we don't we don't want to question
all of that too much because people get
into the usual room for questioning too
much please
please um just uh change topic
i like uh beef beef is good too
yeah me too yeah they're pretty
yeah you gotta decide which one
chief chief
i'm just going for chief chief could
also be a combination of beef and cheese
i was gonna say that sounds good
that sounds like a lot of
yes it's like a lot i
also just thought it derailed somewhere
it's lost
but it's just just like when you uh yeah
have a beef patty and cheese on top of
it
not a big difference okay like a
cheeseburger yeah
just you got it all in one already have
you guys ever
seen that uh like that video of like
how they bring like a like a block of
cheese and they like
torch it and they just like slide their
neck on the cheeks
it's like yeah have you ever had it i've
never had it but
no i've never had that before
but um i watched something like that
before i went to bed and i went right to
sleep
that felt nice do you not feel hungry if
you watch food videos
before sleep nah not really yeah
i mean i try not to eat in the evening
anyway sometimes i can't help it
like for example for on a vacation oh
but i try not to
yeah so i don't really feel too hungry
in the night times but sometimes food
videos do occasionally help me relax
because i have a hard time sleeping
every time i watch like
gordon ramsay's video i'm just like man
i'm i'm a master chef now i can totally
make this
i like try some i'm just like oh i'm not
at all
i mean they make it look really easy i
think that that's the the point
yeah at least at least i learned how to
cut onions
oh nice yeah good job
it's uh it's that's that's already an
accomplishment gotta start somewhere
i wanna make beef wellington
again what is that again
it's like a chunk of meat right it took
a chunk of meat
[Laughter]
pastry thing yeah
and then inside the beef is like wrapped
around some other stuff i think it's
like cheese or mushroom i don't remember
oh it sounds like it could be yummy
my home country ah
england
[Laughter]
i had to think for a second
you know what else comes from england uh
jellied eels have you ever seen jelly
water
jelly eels um
is it just eels made out of jelly it's
eels that are cooked in
clear gelatin oh whoa i've had eel
before
unagi in japan it was really yummy my
god
it's super yummy what the hell no the
picture
and then they put liquor sauce or parley
sauce on it
so well that's disgusting so then
it looks like this
oh ew
oh yeah is this the soup
i don't know oh my god
no thank you thugs tentacles
yeah oh yeah
if you guys if you want to have a good
eel then go get unagi don in japan
ah i thought that you didn't like
fish like things it i like uh most
like i like most fish if it's grilled
and unagi is like also
when it's like it's like cooked it's not
it's not raw as long as it's not raw i
can eat some things
i see i see unagi don is so yummy
yes i love it
good good good good stuff one day i want
to go to one of those like really like
fancy
you know places where they like show you
how to like
how to like clean up the clean up the
eel and then like
screw it i don't want to see that you
want to see that
yeah it's like being made fresh right in
front of your eyes
yeah it's like it's like when you choose
um the crab that you want to eat or the
lobster that you want to eat and you
take it out of the tank and i say all
right this is your dinner and they wave
it around and then
they like here it is again they bring it
out to you just so you remember this is
your dinner
and then then they cook it and then they
they say it's dead now here you go eat
it yeah i
prefer to not see that oh okay well
that's understandable
well well well it's uh yeah i don't like
that either
i wish i could get eel in australia wink
dell because uh they don't really sell
eel
like there yeah we don't have eel
sometimes sometimes you can like uh
contact the uh sushi restaurants and
stuff
but i don't want it as sushi i want it
as a unakidon
yeah you can make your own son no
yeah you only can't because you say that
you can't but if you try you might find
you can do it
a certain bird just told me like a
couple minutes ago
oh no
i love how you use like uh these orange
lights and stuff when you're drawing a
lot
yeah that looks really dope what the
heck it's green
yeah heck yeah it's green
yeah that's so dope
it's like i walked right out of the
swamp my arms crossed it's me saying
this is my swamp now
you know like that's just the feeling
that i get i'm not trying to bring the
conversation back to shrek excuse
me that was really uh i really didn't
read the atmosphere there i'm sorry
excuse me
i'm just saying though just look man
kelly really likes shrek i mean
he's all right you know
now we're circling back again
let's just repeat the whole conversation
again yeah let's go all over again loop
endless loop
sorry i'm sorry
no no problem with that it reminds me of
uh
re-zero though very devastating endless
loops
i've been meaning to watch that yeah i
heard it's really good
it is it is i have i still haven't
watched the new season though because i
just
i don't know something about anime
that i don't know i just can't watch any
more recently yeah these days
yeah i don't really watch a lot of new
stuff either yeah
i i don't watch as much anymore since
i just watched youtubers
i think it's the accident where i fell
down the rabbit hole oh yeah
hop on the rabbit hole and then i
started digging it
you became the rabbit hole i am
same yes we all just you know just like
tap people's shoulders and they just
fall down the rabbit hole
the hell is that good what
what is that what it's a beautiful
takaraki
there's a lot going on here
[Laughter]
beautiful it's like modern art
yes everyone deciphers it
a different way
picasso who
a big fan of that i like the eyes
oh thank you yeah they kind of look like
um
like fried eggs okay maybe you want
breakfast
yeah i want breakfast okay
i seriously did just wake up
i'm wondering when things will start uh
feeling real to me
does it happen that's a really good
point actually
it's a really good point actually
my that's how i feel sometimes recently
but i'm not going to go too deep into
that because
have you ever had a dream within the
dream
a dream within you know actually yeah
i think so i think i do remember that
but i don't have a lot of dreams
recently mostly uh just nightmares
yeah oh see is that is that why you
we're whining maybe maybe that you mean
you remember when i asked you what you
were doing you didn't remember but
usually i don't remember it's either i
don't remember or the dream is like
a long saga that spans like 10 episodes
in my mind and it feels like i've lived
100 years in the dream
um and then i wake up and i'm like oh
that was one night yeah
you know recently it's okay but i used
to have up until recently i used to have
like over the span
of many years i used to have these
dreams where i
would desperately try to run away from
people chasing me and while i'm running
away
i would be i was able to kind of low-key
fly but it would be so difficult
i was really struggling but they uh kept
on catching up to me and the moment they
would catch up on me
i would wake up but yeah that that kind
of dream was following me for many years
that's cute jerry and
it would be like over like over huge
cities and over
huge deserts and stuff i would be chased
through
for the whole world it's kind of crazy
are you sure that um are you sure that
that's just a dream
or maybe like there's some kind of dream
agency that's like out to get you
because you know something in your
subconscious or something like that and
that's why they're treating you in your
dreams
interesting yeah just a little theory
you know
i i don't know i feel like that might be
what it is you want to scare me or
something
no no no this you know we're looking at
all the possibilities here
but yeah actually now that i think about
it i actually i'm glad i have less
nightmares than
i have before maybe i'm just more happy
now oh
that's so good yeah
yeah nice
oh yeah oh someone in the chat just
wrote it's your past lives quiet maybe
my past lives are chasing me
it's your ultimate alternate dimension
kiara
brain explosion could be
like
i think when my brain explodes because i
got a one million iq
it makes a bit of louder sounding now it
makes like
oh wow just being
more accurate please next time oh okay
thank you thank you
i didn't have a reference because mine
just goes
[Laughter]
yeah i
oh my god
those look like maddie's breasts oh my
god
[Laughter]
i mean i don't i mean i don't know well
think about it i mean okay
so here i mean think about it this way
um
gooda's hoodie is uh it's kind of baggy
you know i like to wear really loose
fitting clothes also
when i walk around and it's kind of hard
to see um you can't really see the shape
of um you know that that area so who
could say no one knows the truth
we can't perform anything we can't
confirm anything though let's just keep
them guessing
you know
thank you for trying i appreciate you
you're welcome
i don't know what you're talking about i
just have a i just have the
ancient ones whisper the truth yeah yeah
it's okay though if it's gonna be
anybody it's gonna be you guys and
that's
that's good that's fun
don't worry i wouldn't mind if you girls
saw me naked either
let's show you around let's go to the
onsen yeah
yeah episode
yeah anytime
anytime i'll go to the onsen forever and
ever and ever and never leave
ah i watch you guys back
i saw your uh also totally of you guys
going to the onsen i was like oh i want
to go so badly
did you see the photos yes yes it looks
so
good in the winter yeah winter time is
the best time
yeah yeah by all means come on over
yeah last time i went it was one of the
times though and it was the winter but
there was no snow so it wasn't it wasn't
the same
oh yeah i guess not huh
prime onsen time and also if if you go
to a place that has cherry blossoms
springtime is good too for the onsen
yeah spring could be good too because i
just like generally japan
japan's summer heat is absolutely
excruciating for me
so i wouldn't want to in that summer
heat i wouldn't want to go into a super
hot bath but in the winter or in the
spring
or in the autumn that would be nice well
that's why kyoto you got to go to the
onsen
that have like the hot baths like
outside also outside baths and the cold
baths because what i like to do
is i like to go out into the hot sun and
sit in the hot bath and then you go in
the hot steam room and then
you dunk yourself in the cold icy water
and it feels really good
you really i really i love onsen i love
onsen
i know you do i think i would pass out
if i did that i would overheat
that's why you just sit on the edge and
you just put your feet in but like
we go back again i want to go to the
onset again
[Music]
ah onsen strip eventually guys let's do
it
yeah yeah and and if not
um i don't know maybe go to the pool or
the beach or something
okay i feel like i'm just gonna i'm just
gonna
become like like steamed taco if i go to
okinawa sounds like really really really
hot there
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
word on the street yeah maybe for sale
in the winter so it's not as bad oh
actually yeah
um my my friends told me that in okinawa
like summer is super hot yeah but like
if you go in november or something
it is still summer temperatures but much
much more like
you can take it so november
or october would be probably a good time
to go to okinawa
really the food is really good too i've
heard they have a bunch of strange food
too
yeah i forget i forget all of it though
gotta go look it up later weird okinawa
food
yeah probably a lot of seafood
seafood delicious
eat fish food yes
diet diet
talented look at these artists
[Music]
raw talent i still think i like um
amelia's the best though
i'm like oh this is tough i like
everyone's but i just those are
those are really uh speaking to me like
on a spiritual same
spiritual level
oh yeah i mean i just as i said i'm
drawing qr the way that i know that she
wants me to draw her so
here we are basketball that's all i'm
saying
that's all i'm saying man yes
whoever's drawing that arrow i agree
i noticed that was the first thing that
i know i mean well not the first thing i
noticed about keanu's design but just
i don't know your body listen
it's just something that i like
personally that i when i see drawings
that look like with the thighs with the
and then you have the the tight they go
up to the
middle of the thumb and then it's a
little and it pops out just a little you
know just
a little bit too small yeah i understand
i understand
completely i relate to it yeah
that's coffee generates
i'm just saying okay
i guess amongst friends and also
36 000 takadashi's chambers teammates
kfp and debbie sauce but you know
no pressure no pressure no pressure
all right i think i'm like pretty much
done with mine
i missed a spot cute
we just gotta we're just gonna get
uh done sometime before my stream
yeah i think everyone is
almost done right yeah i don't really
have any plans to color this
i don't think um yeah because it's pink
outline i kind of went crazy with the
sketch and just like refined that so
oh well uh but i will go ahead and
refine the other one really quick
i mean just because i owe it to myself
here i'll look yeah i'll do the same
thing that i did before uh here hold on
on the on the legs how do i make a new
layer there we go
i i just copied it uh oh oh gosh
away with you a new one okay here we go
it did there we go
perfect i think
all of these should be in a museum
really
look at that yeah
yeah i missed collabing this was fun
that's shrimp delicious
tasty that's a tasty looking shrimp it
is
yummy
i'm hungry me too no i haven't had
breakfast
yeah oh no you gotta eat breakfast yeah
i gotta eat i'm
i mean you're gonna be tasting stuff
while we're cooking right
yeah taste the chocolate
just have like crackers on the side so
whenever you make
like a little bit of chocolate you can
just like like melt the chocolate so you
can like dip
it and then go
[Music]
it's a good idea
oh man those juicy legs oh they do look
juicy huh
yes you can take a bite out of them you
know this is chicken
yeah chicken exactly
yep because that's not me i like uh
sorry like your addition
really like nice yes i give you the
heels
beautiful yeah
yeah thank you
good looks good and this is fun i like
it yeah
yeah definitely i want to draw all of
you um not necessarily as chickens but
as you know how i see you
i guess you know
i just i just imagine all our like
mascots with like human legs
yeah see now there is a good idea for um
an art piece
yeah and super buff and like really
muscly arms
yeah it was a lot of veins yeah yeah
yeah it's perfect
i like that
i'm sure somebody will make it now and
it'll look really disgusting
mm-hmm i mean oh no it's just like
oh that doesn't remind me of you know
the birds with like human arms and stuff
they're like yeah
that's what i was thinking of that is
one of my
favorite things of all times
i remember good uh good at linking some
of those pictures i think
body with human arms and legs
that's basically me sorry it's like
the pictures oh
sorry i'm sorry
what we see i think you can probably
paste
images but again we can totally just
like
draw it out right yeah let's just draw
exactly
i'll i'll draw the rooster hold on i
just need to copy it
i got this this is the roost
new layer i'll just temporarily make a
new layer
draw it out yeah so this is the rooster
that i see
what did what did i say as her debut uh
trailer line
in it
what does that even mean it's elementary
is it elementary school
like it's easy mode ah it's easy
i didn't know the meaning of that oh
that's why it's elementary school
because it's easy oh my god what
oh my brain the knowledge i have
received in imaginable who's gonna draw
that one
i vote for ali yeah i think amelia will
do a good job with that one
oh okay
you can add new layers yeah yeah yeah
people are like kiana please but guys
um excuse me english is not my first
language so stop being an ass
i'm gonna be like uh viewers please when
you guys don't know any german okay
means well sorry about that
for victor scheister
oh i know what that means
oh yeah good that maybe knows a little
bit yeah
[Music]
oh me and good are we really going to do
a german class
uh sometime soon yeah
yeah yeah are slanders
yeah i know that one archlanders
you remembered that one wow yeah from
papers please
yeah the archlanders the arslanders
foreigners
no arslanders allowed
i think that's what it was
the knife it's a big old knife i'm
having a hard time including it in here
it's not enough room
i think it's kind of rude um someone in
the chat said uh
is is kelly continuing to draw kiara
[Laughter]
you caught me pictured on screen sarah's
sending her workers to the usual room
[Music]
you caught me you caught me
that's [\h__\h] that's looking pretty
cute amen what the hell
thank you uh that looks cute
nice it's laying both eggs at once
nice i want to know i want to know how
they do that
teach me maybe you can talk to them
question
is it a chicken out of chloe go what
what so what the turtle's awesome
what i'm serious oh what
the turtle's also okay never mind i'm
sorry i didn't notice that i didn't
think i was just it was a genuine
question all right i wasn't trying to be
oh it's okay yeah no i get you
i'm curious what you what you were what
you meant though
ah it's how birds lay their eggs
like this little thing right here does
anyone know what this is called
this this the gobbler
gizzard yeah some people eat those
[Music]
yeah some people think they're tasty
yeah gizzards
yeah they put them
anyone in chat can confirm if gizzards
are tasty with ranch
ranch specifically important with ranch
they're good
it's tasty okay tastes like liver
what does this lover taste like
that's a great question i've had liver
before
uh i forget what liver it was it wasn't
very good oh liver i found leather oh my
god
yeah i eat leather regularly mm-hmm wait
but if you eat chicken like
like like skin is it like eating leather
we don't eat chicken
turkey yeah turkey turkey is more like
it yes
turkey is okay yes yes
yeah if you think uh turkey like skin is
it like eating turkey
leather what
now now
i know but oh my god the
the turkey skin
roasted so yummy it's not like most
sometimes that's the best part yes
because that's where all the seasoning
is
and like like when you like make the
turkey and like all the oil like
like is it like god and it's like
yeah crispy crunchy
oh
oh my god wait i just noticed the one
the bird that ena drew wow
so yeah that's really it's actually
quite quite accurate
coming for you yeah
oh good i would test her with that bird
i'd tussle with that bird have a little
fisticuff
yeah i'd fight that bird i think we
all have quite some artistic talent
don't we yeah
emma's bird is just like like
overflowing with smug
[Laughter]
wait does he wait the bird that is
drawing it
i see the i see the beak but i also see
a mouth smiling at us
exactly
[Laughter]
[Music]
what do you call that uh when when
something like transforms into something
uh better
upgrade evolution
yeah mutate i wanted to say that it's a
mutation of a bird
messed up
ah also to say
where birds like
comment share subscribe i came from a
dinosaur
i had this theory carrot dinosaur we're
like
what what what don't worry about it
phoenix
and they die i think
like you're a dinosaur because you
keep dying and coming back to life yeah
the dinosaurs didn't come back to life
[Music]
i like how your whole chat is spamming
enough
alexa play unravel
i was practicing that song yesterday
it's a hard
song to sing yeah it's very uh
dramatic and high yeah tell me about it
[Laughter]
mm-hmm
what is that it's my uh leftover doctor
oopsie it's all gone now
i want one too mine is from yesterday it
it lost all its uh bubbles
it's just sugar in the water mummy
they're a root beer and then leave it
out for like hours and hours so it was
flat
me too i did that
people said i was weird because i like
flat pepsi and i would like
kind of crack it open a little bit and
leave it in the fridge and then wait for
it to go flat and then drink it
yeah me too yes
does the bubbles hurt your nose when
yeah
i just heard myself wait you guys
haven't mastered the art of not burping
like through your nose when you drink
pop
what i didn't know what a thing it's a
thing you can do
you can train yourself gross
you can't train yourself to do that
where does it come out then your mouth
how does it not come out of your nose
though wait what you just i have to plug
my nose around when i
yeah why are you doing this
because we wrote our exit yeah okay
not your nose
wrong turn
well well yeah
am i really just like butts is that what
it is
you told me you guys told me to draw
this
yeah i know i i think that it fits uh
perfectly
yeah looking back um looking back on the
cursed
uh drawing of ina that you did
that was also a very important part of
the drawing so
yeah that's why i requested it
it's just art you know the emphasis um
on the contrast
yeah beautiful
it's just art you know that has the same
feeling
it just works okay sure does yeah
exactly
next thing i like big but i cannot let
oh
sing it do it you've started it
finish the mission
i'm just gonna i'm just gonna uh uh
uh uh
she doesn't want to challenge dmca exit
stays right she's too scared
exit stage right yeah i'm gone
yeah yeah
nothing happened
what's without drawing now it's a bird
pulling up his pants
than my hair
something in my hair finish it off
callie finish the song says the chat i
can't i don't remember the lyrics i
can't tell
all the bird i see as i went seriously
yeah the bird the bird actually the face
in that one takodachi looks so beautiful
i know it's like is that like a
supermodel taco that see
fishnet edition sexy
you see an idea where's the upgrade
button
oh yes there it is
[Laughter]
actually i think that'll be the go back
button oh my god
the whole the whole like gooda column
is just so beautiful
exactly oh i can imagine now like you
know how for school
you sometimes have to do like collages
of [\h__\h]
looking like that my least favorite
words to hear were
cut and paste i'm like i'm gonna
because i had it you had to get the
little the little tiny baby scissors and
cut out all this stuff and you have to
use glue sticks that all
dried out
i hated the glue sticks everyone always
had glue sticks but they barely stick so
i wanted to use the
the liquid ones but no one ever has
those just use tape
it's so much easier and it actually
sticks
beautiful you know oh thank you oh my
god fishnet tell you
more
[Laughter]
lifting its legs and dancing for a [\h__\h]
somebody animate this quick do it yeah
three
one day favorite one
okay okay okay
this that doesn't have uh uh what's
gonna call it the uh
animation function so we gotta do the uh
analog
oh there we go there's the leg oh yeah
lift that left baby
this is just two frames that's all you
need
to do but what about the other side
you're gonna lift the other leg too
otherwise you're not doing it properly
one over the other come on
all right all right i got it oh someone
in the super chat world i'll animate it
he's on it now
all right somebody put it to the can can
dance too
i need to hear that ah
horizontally flipping it oh well no no
no no no we gotta just gotta put the
effort into
it you know oh an effort okay i'll give
you an effort
oh what oh wow
sorry i i is that what you said i guess
it's that time
but this time at least i beat myself i
put an effort into the f-word
oh are we communicating
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
oh my god and
let's see look at the whole stream just
communicating like this
oh morse code
okay okay
now that literally every one of us has
this uh go xlr
so
my plan worked
i kind of influenced many of us
yes really happy with my go xli
ah oh god it works oh
it works really nicely finally no more
microphone stuff
is skating now yeah i thought it looks
like uh
looks different it has more body now
more gave it an upper body
ice skating oh it's doing the grapevine
nobody knows what the grapevine is
no what's that what's never mind we're
not going there okay nevermind
you're being called a boomer
ah tell me something new come on chuck
come on with something new
[Music]
fight fight fight fight
no one grab the popcorn
now it's just yeah
this is moist morse coding uh super
chats
oh my god
well good that you don't have to figure
that out because you
don't do a super chat readings i guess
that's one good thing about that
actually i didn't
do baby super cherry i do it sometimes
don't you want to do eight hours of
stupid charity come on
i try i try and keep up with them as
they come in
no i didn't put yoga i thought you were
calling me out
no no no
[Laughter]
sorry but good that you felt called out
yeah
wait those cats are so cute oh my god
ah isn't that the
keanu yes
i think i understand oh cali is finally
back
where what do you go oh i've been here
the whole time
i've just been chilling i'm feeling a
nap coming on all right
i'm still hanging out i'm still hanging
my masterpieces i think so me too
okay who has the most accurate drawing
me i do i vote for
uh kelly yep this one maybe
maybe amaze is pretty good i gotta say
yeah this is pretty pretty good very
realistic
that's great okay i'll uh get rid of
this
wait
i like your buff bird yeah
i skipped let's skip like they though
very intimidating
[Music]
thanks oh there you go
wow so cute yeah that was it
beautiful that was chill that's a lot of
fun
yeah do it again
yes
[Music]
uh anything you guys like to announce et
cetera et cetera before we
i would like to have another
i would like to announce that kiara has
an important announcement
thank you i would like that i have an
announcement
coming up in my coming stream in one
hour
thank you for announcing my announcement
of my announcement thank you you're
welcome
yeah okay um
i have a bunch of announcements this
week um
so yeah look forward to it won't happen
until maybe
the 12th or something uh late later in
the week
uh look forward to it also i'm really
only playing games this week so look
forward to the schedule
it's coming up soon
one of those hammers like a judge
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah it sounds way better okay
going twice okay
[Music]
now thanks for coming to lastly and
thanks uh everyone for
uh taking your time to collab today
uh we will see everyone
next time okay maybe in one month maybe
in one year who knows
maybe in one second not in one
second maybe yeah yeah
okay
[Music]
i don't know
you