foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
Michelle
key
chat
local
chatoku
h
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no
candy key
wow
wow wow deep deep stuff Chihuahua
so true so true
oh my God she just speaks the truth
hey
uh wow
wow sugoi Bang
did you see did you watch it
Bang
did you watch it
like you want it
yes
yes well if you didn't watch this one
then you must have at least watched
wait wait for it
then you must have at least watched this
one
because that one was free of charge on
YouTube
it was both thank you
um
[Music]
yay it was supposed to be yesterday but
you know trouble happened and it to make
up for it I guess
they uh ended up showing off day one for
free on YouTube fully
and refunded all tickets
for day one so in case you bought a
ticket already please go ahead and take
your time to
get your refund I don't know how it
works but go and get that refund yes and
then day two followed after that
and so both of these well you know day
one day two huh but it happened on the
same day now at least for me it's
automatic oh okay well then that's
comfortable
yeah a day one honestly like I knew I
knew I was gonna be at least in the free
section the what 30 minutes or so
because
I was in the opening song
um which was the summer theme song
so I was excited about that because I
don't think I ever was in
a free section before except for the Ian
concert I guess the opening the group
song The the everybody's singing song
yeah but like in terms of units and so
on never
so uh yeah you know I was just you know
thinking obviously not everybody watches
or wants to spend the money to watch
these concerts but
uh in this case now the whole concert is
out there so I but I think that is also
time limited so yeah they will I think
make it private or so
after the usual month yeah
um but yeah now my Horror Story section
is also free to view and you guys can
see the full real choreography we kept
the chorus still very simple you know
the the chorus dude
that part um
uh but yeah look at everything look at
it look at it
uh until 27 September wow wow that's a
long time I I saw it like meow meow oh
oh meow bring bring the
bring the juice the noise and the juice
so the part is not Dull remember
smoothie
throw up today makes me worried
um what was I gonna say uh
is she okay
sometimes they just meow weirdly okay
yeah
um and sometimes they just throw up well
but I do want to bring her to the bed uh
I've been waiting for some time to do
that
uh what was I saying oh my god
[Music]
um
uh I forgot ah we we had the mc2 I was
lucky I got an emcee with both horotoni
and usaken but yeah maybe maybe we
talked about some of these things maybe
um if we can
during
the actually let me I want to write
I want to write a note here note
so I don't forgot those pagato
[Music]
um
no
wasn't there one that I had with like
the right color
no
uh
no but it's okay I'll take that one
and
MC
uh no
no generally
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
you did the whole hotel we danced with
us thank you uh
uh ah
yeah
uh
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
I can't think of things
head empty
thank you thank you Crusader King
station archive I don't know what to say
about that that was fun but uh yeah uh
did something special happen I'm not
sure
uh
I already said you know I'm lucky being
in the theme song Let's go did you see
it at the end of oh God the tangents I
can't hold them back did you see at the
end of the uh they showed some like I
think they were shown for the first time
some new art with the group of the
summer theme song uh like two different
artworks
that were really pretty and in one I was
like running in the middle everybody was
running but I was like pretty big in the
middle and the other one I'm like
peeking from the side yeah yeah yeah
behind I think I was behind Susan senpai
yeah but then there's the one there's
the one I think and then I saw a picture
of uh
uh I think
what was I don't know they cut they cut
it differently so that akua Kanata me
and so on we weren't in it anymore
maybe if it's like is that the Blu-ray
cover maybe then we are on the back and
then in the front are the others I'm I'm
not sure anymore but yeah I might be in
the back with the others but I'm pretty
big on that one though yeah it looks
nice
oh yeah I
um is there some
image to show
I think I think I also saw in the kfb
hashtag
a screenshot should be in the whole live
shop
um well I see one
let me explain this to you actually
this one
oh
put it up
uh so what this is
there they announced
the other thing but this one this one's
something else this one is uh animation
like drafts uh collection for this
animated MV
uh so you will see like all the drafts
which looks really interesting um it's
um I think it's not digital right it's
like an actual book I think
and that's the cover for that I suppose
and then there was another one yeah but
me and seriously we're chilling we're
we're chilling together
look at me and Swisher simply this is
this is you know their management is
pushing us to become closer don't you
think
yeah and then the Blu-ray
the Blu-ray
is this
it's on sale starting from today but
this is the front side I didn't know
that this was the front side where is
the pit the full picture
I want to see the full picture
wait maybe wait was there a link
cats running around cats are zooming
right now
here
I feel pictures on it okay okay oh there
it is can I save this image
oh yeah
oh
ah nah you hold on I see what they did
there I only ever saw this full picture
I didn't know that we would be cut off
like this but okay
yeah look it look at that
I love this illustration
I wanna I should put this as my
wallpaper because I have the actual like
big big original size like management
scented for us to check it uh every time
but yeah
this is nice
it was pretty
wow wow
I'm so orange guys don't I stand out
with my orange
there's a lot of like whites like EO
figures
but they're all like so white with their
hair and all that
and there's some purple blue colors
which are also very very close in the
color spectrum and then there's wow bam
Orange in your face
[Laughter]
maybe because I stand out too much they
put me on the back of the cover
uh
stand out too much
color free erase my passion hell yeah
yeah but ah this this was a fun fun fun
fun fun fun fun fun oh yeah wait I wanna
think
um
okay
we'll talk about things wait was there
something was there something else I
should write down uh
oh cool uh am I forgetting something
I mean I want to talk about the MCS
maybe uh and behind the scenes a little
bit
um
yeah yeah
which is the first line basically remind
me of everything hopefully okay ah honey
works I don't know what I can say about
that there's a there's a trailer there I
love honey Works apparently there will
be uh honey works and whole life
collaboration or something like that
whoo
interesting
I I also did uh honey works
song covered at night
didn't I do something
do they cover honeywells before I think
I did
[Laughter]
right
did I I mean I mean I definitely did
doing a karaoke
first decal now honey work still alive
winning yeah it's so cool I was
wondering
um you know if they're gonna keep up
making like collaborations like that so
that's really cool
hmm
also the theme song is made by
honeyworks after all
[Music]
whoa you didn't know oh my God
what do you mean no
hey
boys and girls
what about Davis well I don't know some
girl running around in Shibuya with her
phone I don't know man she's on a
mission
she's on a mission you tell me you tell
me
why game not show on screen I it will
come right it will come surely
wow come on come on come on come on come
on come on come on come on come on come
on come on baby
I'm just waiting for you to show
yourself an obs
I know you like to take your time but
now is the time
to show yourself
did you update the game yeah I think it
updated
I saw it updating
bomb you don't want to you little
you little how dare you how dare
you you little
you're gonna ah there is the little
there is it there is it
need to make it smaller
can you guys read it
somebody might be watching it on their
TV and be able to read it
and their big ass TV okay
I'm bad
Pokemon go with whole life girls oh
wait fun
um
[Music]
sounds good I'm on your 4K TV let's go
reminder for ants yes remind those ends
remind them of their failures that they
will never become as big as we are
their failures in evolution
we're back we're back in battle skate
yeah so I wasn't sure until last minute
what I should stream today but in my
head this whole time
there were these two words floating
around
[Applause]
Papa's game
play me
so
I was like yeah well you know what
people are gonna enjoy it if I enjoy it
right you guys should play things that I
enjoy so
all right all right fine
um the Mind players the Mind players
but I brush my brush before right before
the Stream
I did
oh man
I'm affected by mine flare yes it's in
my brain
your bear
um
um I don't wanna go go too far no there
was no crack I was just it was just a
lean it was just a stretch
it's just a stretch here
yes stretch
oh okay
uh
please click the chain on the left
chain
this
how's my ankle
press G
what does it do what does it do
what does it do
so that they come with me
ah wow yeah we were all like all over
the place
um
ah
ah I did push that before the end of
last stream right to do some free thing
all right let's talk to people and
explore
um I want to be very very very
um
deep
you know I want to take it slow I want
to talk to everybody because we
shouldn't go too far anyway in terms of
story because I don't wanna but this
seems like a lovely little spot the
sense of impending tube aside
suddenly I clicked on him so now we're
talking okay uh
tell me about yourself so tell I'm a
magistrate back in the city it's all
rather tedious
shallow heart talk to me
this place
we found true yes we have to do that uh
hmm
when you think of all that's happened
what do you think of all that's happened
to us so far I don't really care what
you think about that to be honest I I my
my I am too great to be caring about
your thoughts
oh
yeah
seeking solace in root and soil
grounding what am I say what
Shadow Hearts actor is dating the actor
for the scribbly what do you mean
she's acting as squirrel as she's dating
a squirrel
obviously a squirrel must be acted by a
squirrel what the are you talking
about
um how do you mean the voice actor
I thought that was like a motion actor
too
uh wow magic was heavier here seeking
sauce and written so a little grounding
one might say
uh-huh let's see I hail from Water Deep
city of splenders I am a wizard of
considerable acclaims
exceptional accomplishment
reflex cat a weakness for a good glass
of wine the mood takes me I'm known to
try my hand at poetry
there
don't stop there you must have many
stars to celebrate
um
uh-huh
I am interested but my character is not
interested I'm sorry what's going on
here let's let's let's see what's going
on
go on
give me a Best Shot
bad that that sucked again
yeah try harder
ah
smack his booty with the sword no more
no more what was it I'm not like you
what's up
it's a sandal
you just have to buy enough time to run
come on
I believe exactly yes you can do this
so oh wait I was I was kind of waiting
for something to happen uh uh I was
actually like legit immersed in her eyes
um
this wealth is hopeless you're wasting
your time oh yes ignore her
go on now practice what you've learned
don't you dare ignore me
well met the blade of Frontiers at yours
the man smell bends downward what's
happening why did it cut off
you are the blade of Frontiers racing
through the waists of avernus
ahead a diabolical figure red skin
single curled horn blazes with flame
bloodied great exhale it's skipping
I'm not clicking anything fires
ship
huh
uh yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah who the hell was that woman
the one in your thoughts
I didn't know I didn't click anything
leave a keyboard no my hand was off of
the mouse so you saw her then
avocado the advocate of the evil
Devil's Advocate I am a genius between
diabolical forces and demons
archdevil soldier I've heard of that
name
I tracked her through the hells to the
Mind flayer ship but the Damned lithids
infected me before I could end her she's
out there now
preying on the innocent I don't kill her
she'll leave behind nothing but a trail
of corpses
wait
this guy we can add him to a party here
I'm more concerned about the parasite
AKA I'm more concerned about my own
problems I just suggest research for
Hilo together you know I want to play
her as evil but sometimes the options
are just not really evil you know that's
my problem an excellent suggestion but
your party's full up still when the time
comes call for the blade I won't belong
to answer
okay cool
everybody you know but that
play with I guess I guess so become my
minion go to the camp a splendid plan
we'll talk more about it because my team
is full Gala proves okay okay Gail
approves of him being in the camp and
not with us okay okay I saw you at the
gates
you fight well
me oh oh you shouldn't ask me uh
bad news children you're all going to
die
[Laughter]
well you asked the wrong person man
The Illustrated Adventures of balder and
can I read this
this book is
the woman's eyes were Dusky filled with
mystery and promise Baldwin was
intrigued anything he asked anything she
said just name it and it can't be yours
and what do you want in return
just a small thing she smiled balderan
left nothing about him was
I want your soul I want your soul
balduran
she sighed give me your spirit and
whatever you desire shall be yours
Baldwin considered this for a moment
very well I want a turnip
she hesitated you're so in exchange for
a turnip
nice turnip no that follows around
very well dark smoke swirled around the
woman whose skin was turning red then
you shall the next couple of pages have
been worn out when the storms the woman
not fully revealed as a devil is
kneeling at balran's fate curse you
bowed around I am Bound to You yours to
call upon when you need me and your soul
is your own once more
let that be a lesson to you laugh about
the Run never estimate the power of
attorneys
what
ha
huh what dude what isn't a turnip of
freaking vegetable
not a sanctuary
clear off while you can you are so
British tell me more tell me more
inside failed
oh seems like she has succeeded though
Donnie what's wrong what are you doing
past you as if you're invisible or
boring what
show you I'm not boring
or hmm turn you around and see what he's
talking nothing out of the ordinary as
you turn back the chance slips between
the rocks
I didn't see that what search the Rocks
when opening is he gone what is he gone
now they didn't show him slipping
where did he slip
oh I didn't need the bonus guys you find
the edges of a concealed entrance he's
really gone
oh yo let's go I found something cool
did the girls find this in the collab
ing Hideout oh there he is hey hey
you just keep on granting at me huh okay
wait where am I
secretarial
no they all we all ran past it cool
and now he's looking at
what oh can I jump over there
hmm well you just keep on grunting
I wonder if I can jump
push him oh
no
oh
it doesn't here they come what do you
mean what do you mean here they come
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry
what's coming
who's coming I don't see any money
coming
we're good I think we're good I need
oh you're a pickpocket
pocket picker
should I be sneaky well oh look who's
come to visit oh my kids say you've
been busy since you got here not sure
why you're poking your nose in our
business though
oh
I don't even know where your business is
yours this is our hideout
hey maybe you didn't know I didn't know
because of that I'll give you a 10 count
today
you're joking right
are they really counting
you want to fight oh yeah let's
fight sorry what are you gonna do what
are you gonna do what are you gonna do
what are you gonna do
commence battle
no need honey is it gonna like make a
rock drop from up there
where'd he go oh he ran into like a hole
over there
what so what happens after 10 you just
flee
it's scaring me
there's still people there oh and the
thief stash
haha I'm gonna rant I want to rain 10
seconds
here we go
let's read this book maybe it'll help me
I'll find out later she's gonna tell on
me but they're the thieves
another time in another place
would be celebrated as a revolutionary
and Father's gate in her own lifetime
she is known as a crime Lord a Kingpin
of the guild rolling over the city
within the city that is at this District
of little collection
did I do it wrong where's the story
began when she was orphaned at a young
age her father was hanged by The Flaming
fist for Sheltering his fugitive brother
soon after the her mother was denounced
by the jealous wife of a patriarch and
imprisoned in the sea Tower where she
perished alone in the world she had
learned two valuable lessons
I should have left oh
well thank God that's the first thing we
did today and we can uh redo it when the
law is corrupt it is a necessity for
those who without the support of its
enforcers to act outside it and when the
Lord is an ethical oh my God there's so
much
no it's fine
others
that's not important okay okay ooh a
mirror why why may I not interact with
the mirror
so what about these other kids like they
have their stash there
let's talk to them
you don't look so tough mofo of a
hobgoblin all by herself
what
what if I steal their stash I want to
steal their stash
these cigarettes raise the guards these
cards these children guards or what
okay okay we had practice at this
uh last time
our resident staffer is a Starion so
well how do I distract them
I'll take this way we're pretty girl
how do I how do I distract them
they're not even looking at me can I do
something to distract
I can't can I make him blind
someone can't
wait who was uh who was able to summon
things
me right ahead
I can't summon it here
you can start talking with one card use
the other how when I'm always in the
cutscene
minor illusion
minor illusion create an illusion that
compounds nearby ah yes okay okay okay
I'm scared wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait uh
let's
okay
where do I where can I put it
I wonder if the gods are watching me
Maybe
I don't know how this works
not enough space
what
cute
oh I can
control it
meow meow meow meow
meow meow
too far goddammit
mmm
meow
would you can I
the child is back
uh he cares about the cat though
but these two don't
oh disappeared now I got another chance
at
spawning it
okay okay
will they look at it
I guess I end my turn
uh one with the weave is this shirt and
for him he already must
hide no uh sneak how do you sneak again
what button was that cute no see it's
very quiet
but
difficult
maybe meowing would work
if I go into the red now now I'm not
even trying to attempt anything yet but
is this a problem can I like
um
I'll just enter here let's see if they
do something
go look at the cat
hey don't look at the cat
no they don't look at them
quite ready for you
what's next I wonder
it doesn't even how do I make a meow it
doesn't even want to meow
um
I'm ready
still breathing despite everything
you're the first grown-up who's ever
gotten in here not bad
mole attende and she'll own Boulder's
Gate
see
uh well have I when I talked to them how
do I
huh seems like a good
one I'm not ignoring you what do you
mean a Super Chat I'll be reading super
chats in a Super Chat reading I don't
read in the middle of my streams
um they're looking at me now so you
think that's gonna work
okay
I'm scared
yeah
we lost the condition hiding
I like to race
and now there's not it's not gonna work
so useless okay
are you ready
[Music]
wait let me exit this okay let's go guys
let's go let's go there's nothing here
except for another book
um
I feel like there should be more let me
try them go over here can I also
go for the whole
all right and where where there's
there's no way that
uh okay I can't can I not fit through
hmm
what if I blow it up can I blow it up
too big need to be huffling
can my little pet go through no what's
up
you could be small only small creatures
damn it
all my companions are big too
ah okay this guy itself is smaller
character
do I have that disguise
oh my God
smallest thing is a gnome right
I can't do that
oh my God okay let's go oh
what's that whoa
whoa
I found something
hello I am scared
hello you little shits didn't think I
would fit through the hole huh I'm
superior
I want to talk to him why can I not talk
to him
the people down there
well I could probably also find this
from the other side right
hold out your hand lady
The Gnome
Take This Ring
it's lucky
[Music]
that was a fancy trick you haven't seen
anything yet Lady it's cute take the
ring and watch your fortune change
um mimic his trick and make the ring
disappear oh
why don't we just take it though
what is this ring there's there did that
ring cannot be good
but maybe maybe it's good to entertain
him then he'll start liking us
Maybe
let's add this bonus come on 15 that's
pretty high
oh can do can do can do yeah yeah no no
you bullshitting me
ah let's roll again let's try it again
come on
ah there we go that's what I'm talking
about
thank God for inspiration
there it goes
he likes it maybe you don't need extra
luck but since you're already holding
the thing yeah call it heads or tails uh
hmm Tales
Tails it is yeah I feel like I'm being
that's the kind of look you get from one
of my lucky Rings cool I've got more
where that came from real cheap too
interested
they actually give me a luck Stat or
hello Raiders
um
hold on one coin toss doesn't prove
anything okay fair
let's go again heads or tails call it
[Music]
heads there happy no I'm not
happy
flip it again really I mean fine
tails
of course we got Tails wow what a
surprise
oh flip it again come on
okay
heads or tails
he's getting pissed off it's
heads
no let me throw it
um I want to see where's take the Rings
[Music]
that's what I got I perceived he did
something weird I think oh but hey he's
actually got some stuff can I take the
gold oh
don't hear me out
hi
hi it's got some food
Supply ping pong Red Dot dies
picture of beer
and can I buy the money oh no I guess
Adam that money is like what you know he
could use to buy stuff for me
[Music]
but I don't think I need anything
although wait
he's got those rings
it says it says you know that it does
things but it's not like it has any
stats so
meow indeed yes drunk thank you thank
you for giving me advice about this
yeah
I feel much more confident your eye huh
nah
um it's nothing but junk not sure what
you expected I'm a kid living in the
back of a cave why don't you live in
front of the cave again sometime take
care he's nice so he's nice
you spot the boy giving a Sly wink as he
turns away oh they stole something from
me
[Music]
okay uh my team shall come back to me
wasn't this where we entered let me see
um
these kids are confusing me I feel like
if they make this whole area there there
must be something more to it
but maybe there wasn't
why do they
what was the counting about too
I need everybody to come with me
one moment oh wait now they're here
okay
look up the chest again
the kid next to him so go for me did he
really
kill the Thriller and I have lower no
what about
these local shits your little
you're a little
time to rest
why don't you guys walk together are we
now we're together okay
let's see what else can we find
boots
oh what is this
oh are you a chef
can you make me some proof
are you guys coming yeah
they're orphans oh
oh hello make me food please
saw you fighting those slimy bastards
fancy a bowl best to fill your belly now
yeah nice lady you're not poisoning me
are you
a bowl of gray cool reminds me of home
um what is it food you want it or not
but it might make all the difference oh
the only way we'll make it to Baldur's
Gates is to run and run hard
egg white scramble that no
item received cruel
is that a camp supply or what where is
it
grow
I don't see it
how do I say everything again
supplies oh okay cool cool cool
thanks mommy
the talk of the camp thank goodness you
can't belong when you oh oh there isn't
a piece of color in those cheeks
harsh excuse me this is how I look by
default
Galore she's nice too
let her fuss over you
uh what are you an alchemist thing as
fancy is that
I come from a long line of women with a
dab hand at such things uh-huh
you take a super that and you'll feel
right as rain sweetie that's such a cool
bottle I like it
um
Midas concoction also help with
something more serious I already know
where to go for the Healer but maybe you
know maybe she's the Healer actually
that depends what's wrong lovey lovey uh
I have a condition and unusual condition
I've seen it all I once had a fella
who'd been caught dabbling with a dryad
the wife was none too pleased and
introduced him to a part of boiling oil
worry not I fixed him up and depending
on the lighting he looks good as new
well thank God he had you whatever else
yeah I promise I've seen worse oh that
makes me feel relieved what's wrong
pedal
hmm I've got a mind flare parasite in my
head count your adventure
months along her eyes wide
does Shadow heart disapprove
my heart goes out to you truly thank you
can you be my grandma no sign of a
tentacle yet ah but that could change in
an instant you need help serious help I
agree I agree an air proportional lotion
here that could do it but
you may have something doesn't want to
share information huh yeah she's
secretive as
um I may have something at home oh
there's why would I why what's strange
about this lady she's she's giving me
this option but I don't see anything
strange about this old grandma she's
just really nice
hmm
but I do Wonder
I do wonder I guess I sense it oh
whatever do you mean petal huh I don't
know you have little Grandma Vibes I
guess almost like a fake like well
wasn't they like evil fairies right
Evolution ah might you hail from they
perhaps
ah
this is just super nice and I'm calling
her out on seeming like evil
but evil to another evil is just you
know a friend so
maybe I'm maybe I'm being confused you
know
someone's just like being Grandma type
of nice to me and the evil inside of me
must have confused it with that meaning
oh oh she must be evil because she's
nice if to me that feels you know you
know you know it's
nice people can't be good
in in my in I don't know I don't know
Grandma confusing me
I don't know what's evil anymore
hey I don't wanna accuse her I don't
even know what this means though
what what's say
ing like one of those red wizard lit
Slickers please
she's not even offended they're as
exciting as it gets for these old bows I
love her I don't know if nurturing I'll
be heading home shortly here
chunky
monkey you're so busy careful on the
road I'd hate if something happened to
you
take care of it thanks
a calling
wow
that was nice having this conversation
salt I'll find you salt someday and I'll
come back I don't think I have salt now
we'll talk to you here I'm talking to
everybody I looked in
what
did you get poisoned oh no
wait go go go go go here no
why is he looking
into the boys
Goblin Slayer I'll show anyone to be
seen with me I ain't exactly popular
with this one
how's it going chunky monkey
thank you
here come play bothers game with me
oh where's that cute
and
yeah oh really uh hmm I respect you now
I'm gonna take the blame for leading the
Goblins here and losing track of the
bloody druid
I forgot about that like what through it
who's the Druid you lost track of
yeah
was we've got a contract
the track down some Relic and he wanted
in on the job
slits up when he heard about it
when we were turning Sail
these are the digging the trains are
boiling in a cook pot by now
I don't know what to ask
contract
what contract
wasn't gonna make fun of him there's an
entire Hive of him
construct failed to mention that part
foreign
I don't know what I expected that much
gold for some long lost Relic and from a
wizard too
I should have known
you leave Boulders Gates stupid thing to
die for
um it's called the nuts tell me what a
relic is supposed to be hidden on the
December where the Goblins jumped us
the goblin Temple Brian kept hold of it
like his own charger goblins made sure
to the fat old
across the contract it'll show you where
we turn back if you feel like that you
know she's really annoyed but she loves
me she can't help it sometimes we need
to force love onto these cutie patooties
remind them of how irresistible they are
it'll show you where we turned back if
you feel like dying thanks
both like me
be well on my way to Boulder's Gate when
you
I will never die stamped hand bill
oh
adventurers wanted for perilous and
profitable quests Master Laura and The
Arcanist of at Cutler the reclusive Rama
Zips Tower six Brave and enterprising
individuals to delft treacherous Temple
and recover storied artifact the Night
song for preservation in Baldur's Gate
only start of heart and king of might
need apply Fame glory and incredible
Fortune assured
that sounds great find the Night song
wait so with our group we're currently
at the goblin Temple
we're gonna find it anyway right but
this did this just like kind of opened
me a sign a side quest that we probably
don't have
as a group
would it be better to have the quest
because then apparently maybe I'll get
fam and and money and all that
[Music]
very long Quest you can pick it up and
light up
okay okay
she's a thief hell spawn and you will
wait for corgis judgment now get back oh
let me through miraculous Admiral Ricket
and throw it out
oh oh
I remember this a little bit maybe
do I
wait what don't fight guys calm down
no fighting
who was the lady who was just angry was
it you
know lives are at stake and the cowards
only care about their bloody rituals the
bear
we could help each other bite the
Goblins together instead these fools are
trying to chase us away
Joyner come on
calm down
[Music]
you don't you don't scare me
I just want to give you a hug the other
tieflings
um foreign
[Laughter]
if it weren't for me you'd be overrun by
goblins now I'll go where I'll please
back
it's my hand and I'll show you its claws
Gianna
what
oh I understand
you
should always works to you go ahead
ha ha
we may go ahead wonderful what's going
on here anyway like can this be
explained to me like I only remember
from
our grip collab that they tried to steal
this thing but like what is this even
about I want to understand
hello what's up talk to me Volo
Gates just now no crossing a spell to
cut this area off from the rest of the
world
to protect themselves
there's no overstating my internships
[Music]
a few questions okay
Glory
nothing
in the collab already
size nature distinguishing qualities you
search your mind successfully recalling
various details of goblin Behavior yes I
remember totally uh
give an exact description here there you
Goblin's word of rare gem-colored Hue
and wielded magic blow guns
is that really what I said in the rear
was it of the brass or silver variety
three
uh there's been a misunderstanding what
do you actually want my friend not a jot
more or less
did the attackers rally to the absolute
when they fell upon the gates
rally to the absolute
I
don't think so
well this does complicate things
but then again
never mind no speak your thoughts
a captive In This Very Camp She reports
they've abandoned their God mclubbiet in
favor of someone called the absolute at
the Scandal
how can you already decide that it's a
scandal Goblin Superstition not worth
the ink and parchment hold your tongue
why would I say that why am I insulted
now you mind
I'm on my way to their Camp as we speak
I always knew my studies would come to
some use
oh
what project uh
what about what's the what's with the
dragon though every story benefits from
a dragon ah until we meet again
okay I see so you're just adding it for
for the sake of entertainment hmm can I
talk to them while they're in the ritual
[Music]
um
what is this can I take it can I touch
it
oh it wasn't red so I was allowed to
pick I got a recipe
foreign
[Music]
it doesn't look like you're helping with
the ritual
whatever you saying to the bird I didn't
notice her saying anything to the bird
but let's ask her the bird knows
she needs to know you do not
rude
because I have defend this group I'm not
your enemy
I did indeed do that
but I am your enemy but let's you know
let's tell her
let's try to calm her down so she will
be on my side hi
forgive me
it is not you I fear oh really welcome
back why are you so much every day
they were afraid and she offers a simple
solution
ejects the refugees and we will be safe
you still haven't told me what you were
doing with the bird yeah
sounds like she has to be stopped
or
she's wrong
question mark
I know perhaps not
but that does not make it right only
Master halsin can stop this
pray my bird returns with news of him no
that's what you asked of your birth
everyone here
bringing you some Intel now
um
I hear a ritual can protect the Girl by
you helping prepare it you're not
helping others prepare it the ritual is
caucus decision
but she is not our leader Master housing
welcomed the refugees in
I wait for him to resolve this
well good luck
good luck I guess can I can I take this
back at all
I take this
gray dust the road dust gray clothes
actually they don't even look so bad but
I'll leave it in there
look at that cute bear sleeping oh but
aren't his eyes open
tuffet
always on alert
I don't know okay let's try uh
the stone door
Aya out
cute pigs
the emerald Groove I'm so
oh no what's happening
please
I'm sorry this is madness korga this is
just a what wrath a thief a poison
a threat
I will imprison the devil as is the
child that they were talking about
outside
yeah
um
well I don't really care about what
happens to a child haha one of your
guards outside said you wanted to see me
here I am see I I say I care but my
character doesn't care just so we don't
have a misunderstanding here okay we'll
speak soon enough
first
judgment must be passed
he was almost holy Idol she is the same
like wrath lock her up
sheepling right as me to the right is
complete
still
maybe I should feel it's Restless
supportive of other teachings surely
do it
um
[Music]
right kaga's mind prepare to attack
and
then
yeah you do your thing I'm here for a
Healer not for this
Tila to me
that was not supposed to happen
no
by the gods Koga what have you done yeah
what have you done
that's what happens
they're just outside this Outsider will
take word once I've spoken to her
we must focus on the right
she's there tired for that Koga we are
Guardians
she knew the danger
still tried to run the longer we stay
here well we come to reaching the same
fate
hello
it is what it is if they they wanted to
get rid of the child right so and there
you go that's what you get maybe not the
most ideal way loot the body
I should not only would never let the
teeth like poor child it should never
have happened oh that's a child
yeah
the dead child uh how do I do this again
ah the necklace the necklace it was Gail
right into wolves
uh how does it work uh
that was a girl
no it was asterian was it wait I don't
see the necklace I'm blind
direct me it's already activated
okay
don't touch me don't touch me oh my God
a long way from Water Deep hello another
rain we are not to be trifled with I
just hope they leave and we could close
this grovid piece and if it comes to a
fight you'll not shy away from Bloodshed
I hope since when did we become Killers
I am
I gave it to Gail
learning all right we get five questions
right
I hope it's not like the cause mad that
I didn't try to help him
um
how did you end up in Druids girl
[Music]
new parents what should I tell them
silent
because there are no parents oh sad
valuable
more more more
some person with the name of Mall
something something has valuables
I'm nine and a half
and that's why your story ends
good night Arabella
[Music]
Swift as my feet can carry me oh I can
open this wicker chest
for grass attack thank you
hello You Are the Healer I think that
I've been looking for I see you
just give me a moment huge burp Hooters
good job a fair feather excuse me I'm
more important than some bird girls are
field mouse no one's more important than
the patient in front of him
hurry up
there hurry up hurry up turn up
life for death
now
what was it you need it the one that
counted to ten oh
um
healing looks like I came to the right
person um yeah I need help now I'm
speaking of my bedside manner is better
than yours come here let's have a look
at you
let's look at me
a bit tired from the eyes I've got a
mind player lady
um
more than tired something crawling to my
eye
some sort of bug
oh
wait did it look like a tadpole yes but
from your worst nightmare yes all slime
teeth and tentacles yes not the kind of
cute one
that becomes froggy Wawa
help me
I'll do what I can come follow me
continuing to disturb me this way
[Music]
what's going on
head on in okay
I'm coming
oh who's this in that vessel
take a closer look this one had the same
problem as you attacked us in the woods
together with some goblins
tadpole crawled out of his head soon
after
hey
[Music]
so I killed him and laid them out until
they were because
seems to be a common experience huh
I'm good don't don't no at least that's
what Master Hudson suspected you got me
instead of him
he understands these things studied them
still
we have options don't poke me with that
don't you dare told me that to be here
for this I'm interested in the procedure
actually please
go ahead all right
let's see what we can do
uh
what's that plan will it help she shifts
uneasily hesitating
something's off uh-huh
but first things first
tell me about your symptoms don't you
dare kill me with that anything strange
happening
okay
I fell from a ship in the sky but
something probably to save my life oh
yeah I'm curious about that too
[Music]
um
well
yeah I guess I I can merge my mind can
identify each other
not that the others know they're victims
of course how'd you pick up the parasite
Halston was desperate to find where all
this was happening
it's not like I picked it up it was
forced on to me
look are you going to cure me or not I'm
trying to help you
need to be sure
so tell me where'd you get that thing
kill me first and I'll answer all the
questions you want
[Laughter]
oh yeah I'm in trouble I'm in danger
yummy I'm in danger
blow but as you regain your footing you
can see the pain in her eyes I'm sorry I
truly am but I can't let you you tried
to kill me just now if you transform out
there you'll kill everyone in the Grove
everyone for leagues around
um
I ordered
it can hit me let alone kill me don't
make me put you down
oh let's go
easy win
[Laughter]
yeah I'm trying to be not too nice yeah
you
you're right
I'm no use to the other's day oh that's
very reasonable thing to realize that
maybe yours is too
exactly I'm glad you're coming to
yourself no one else can stop this
comments you need me I just want to find
cure
[Music]
um
you need me all right but in one
condition
this is a vial of wyvern poison
swear to me you've swallowed if you feel
any symptoms
[Music]
I'll take it but I don't know if I'll
drink it
is that something to kill me immediately
when I drink it just so that I can stop
like
some kind of transformation
no I'm not taking poison from a woman I
can't stress don't you understand yeah
but I won't swear
it to me without swearing
okay I'm not good okay never swear I'm
not gonna swear for her no and I have no
choice
I'm sorry
okay
oh
well
yeah why why must we fine why must we
battle
okay I take it back I take it back
no
no that was your last mistake lazy
ah I don't think this will end well if I
kill her like surely I can kill her but
you can do non-lethal
how can non-lethal blows
where is that
passives
isn't that like here
can't find it bottom tabs ah
okay knock someone unconscious instead
of killing them oh
so okay can we really do this
okay this one failed I suppose
and try again
no okay
wow so much for peace
was this repelling
no no no try it or not
we're not trying to kill it what was
that was that non-lethal be careful be
careful do I have to knock her down
still like get her HP down
uh I turn it off oh no oh no oh no
it's on right non-lethal damage okay
and so any attack now that I do is
non-lipple
ah okay okay
[Music]
like this
there's a lot of blood there for not
being lethal
yikes oh she wants to oh see I
forgot about that
uh Shadow Hearts still in mini mode
chibi chibi mode
Heart Stopper
this is
this is still not lethal right
only the last one has been only okay
okay
miss me
[Music]
okay
that comes easy these days
uh
here it is so I was looking for this
menu
[Music]
she healed herself
mmm
we have The High Ground oh oh oh she's
not dead right
[Music]
let's get out of here but uh how long is
she gonna she's dead
what it might do to keep our condition
on a need to know basis
the whole city gonna attack me now
[Music]
where was this thing that we were
looking at by the way
um
can we find some kind of Secret in here
or was it a different room
and that was ranged and what
what that's like I don't know I thought
that's the same thing
where's the exit anyway
the stone slap right
but it's it's locked
talk to her corpse ah
yes shall we
seems willing to speak
but not to its killer
I'm no one who did the final blow
I think a Starion okay what was it it
wasn't me
wits and blades or wish up
they've had this spell heard disguise
she would look different from before
can she talk
this guy's well can she do that too
disguising herself sometimes
can I even do that
it's okay we don't need to but let's
also talk to this one yeah
the dissected draw
the corpse regards you lifelessly
who killed you
oh
the bear
what happened
[Music]
and then they attacked you randomly or
what
[Music]
um
of the absolute
absolute there it is again
the corpse remain silent it doesn't
understand the question oh yeah we're
out of questions
you can ask no more questions
[Music]
okay I am ready to take the consequences
of my actions I suppose
um one day I'll catch a break and wasn't
this why is it red
why locked why why why why we need to
wait
um
uh like a thiefing kid yeah
can you use it on this and how do you
use this
I can't even see a lot to pick
ah there was yeah I mean I also don't
see it she has keys on it yeah I don't
her body is red though I don't want to
touch it
whoa there's no way I'm getting away
with this right
animal friendship
key of the Ancients wow
the branches of the circle are half
fossils passed down for generations of
Druids
I'm not getting away at this
no witness so it didn't happen yeah we
just gotta close the door behind
ourselves right still alive wait so am I
supposed to wear this thing
uh how do I
there we go who has this thing you
I guess I'll put it on my head everybody
will see it that is probably not smart
foreign
[Music]
am I getting out of this really
hi
this stuff happens yeah I I
I just I just didn't want to be too nice
I didn't think we would have to kill her
but why is she so aggressive it's not
even my fault she was aggressive as
man
all right Daddy
um
she wasn't gonna heal us anyway so
whatever
I did nothing wrong yeah I was just
being me which is mean
you could have lied to her I don't know
I'm I'm uh I didn't see a need for that
I'm I am
I have too much pride
man
okay where does this continue do we exit
by the same path or
wait am I still supposed to do something
here
so I have to talk with kaga
I can leave if I want you didn't talk
with Kaka yeah
which one is kaga
wait ah yeah
shouldn't kaga be standing like here
um oh wait was it inside
oh it's just not maybe not loading the
people
I'm coming back
snake lady
[Music]
my thing
why is it like chilling here
okay let's go
let's go outside la la la
this is a pretty game it is I like it
you you didn't uh
you didn't find the dead body of netting
yet did you um
go on
say it
you think I'm a monster oh okay Dad I
thought you were gonna say say it you
killed Nelly
oh
not at all that was quite a show
monsters both then
Viper to Viper yeah what I just did was
pretty monstrous yeah I took back the
idol of Sylvanas and the writers resumed
we will seal the Grove free from harm
free of intruders
okay I'm eating a banana by the way
um
free from the threat of little children
nope
not enough time
do what you want now my concern so you
say
yet you share their infernal blood
great metal
the metal of a skilled sword for hire
I want you to provide your services to
sevlor
offer to guide The Outlanders out of the
Grove
I'm sure they'll reward you well they're
to be gone before final prayer
if they are not the Viper must strike
oh
[Music]
um
I really aren't my concerns then they
soon know the sting of my event okay get
out
we have no more business oh yeah
fine
[Laughter]
that's one edgy lady you think so
why we even come
you miss out on the quest
[Music]
um
investigative Temple return to devlar
get Auntie edville's help
let's we can talk to that guy
[Music]
Marissa hi
you don't like do not like his hat
if it isn't the consequences of my own
actions yeah I know I know
um
uh what
save our Bella find arabelle's parents
ah cancel eh arabella's parents Arabella
was that child
the quest markers today always like show
the destination of what I where I need
to go
yeah let's break the bad news I guess
um
um oh God
banana
oh no no no puppy hi chunky
Mouse
do you hear this
oh hello are you the parents
unless you have news of Arabella I don't
want to hear it I do I do
um
she's bitten by a snake it happened
quickly she felt low pain
kind of kill your daughter she called
her a parasite and a threat cooker
yeah she did that yeah
indeed it was a snake
complete safe Arabella even though I
didn't save her
[Applause]
yeah that's that's sad uh
get the forks the Pitchfork
the Torches yes yes
where's the Sada Quest guy this is fine
so rude
ah this is the one
uh
uh I think
wait wait wait wait wait where's that
where is that
here
the type of thing
let's keep the Goblins out forever that
is around the corner
over here
ikaron
for you guys
all right then I remember you
have you checked out the beach here
have I I don't think I did yet
maybe not
diamond
through the door oh okay
knock knock
knock knock knocking on battles
secluded gender oh
sorry
no need to worry about the BART lady if
you keep going instead of going to her
you'll find a beach beach let's go to
the beach beach
which which BART lady I gotta find the
BART Lady it's not you right you're not
in this game right now are you what are
these movements are you shaking
something off
Shake It Off you're the one who helped
to the gate she just took out her swords
the moment needed I came up to her
don't fight me
hi Sephora I've already heard and old
yeah
but at least she got to see the whole of
Summer
every natural law demands I take up my
sword storm their Laird but no
that's what kogo wants to prove we are
exactly what she says
threat I won't give her the
satisfaction me neither I'll get my
people clear of this but on our terms
good good do it on your terms at least
yeah at least the child saw the whole of
Summer
if it would have died a year ago it
wouldn't have you know seen the beauty
of it
so honestly she saw all that there is
just see
oh look I need the light already up
towards this because
I really want to push this but uh
yeah
there's a whole Army of goblins out
there at least I'm helping my teeth
please
doubt your abilities
you're no Army if a one-man Army can be
a army then I can be an army with my
five people
a little different
unlike them to organize
organize somebody
must bringing discipline to their ranks
oh you are that leadership don't be
no small thing to ask but I've seen you
fight you're equal to the task
I am the superior evil what do I give a
about some random child dying in in
some process like it's not my job to
save her
I if I was playing a normal good
character then yes yes my my conscious
my hero conscious would tell me to to
save her but this doesn't give a
you know that
uh I am the superior evil yes
fetching and happening
you're so right for that let's go and
see improves
I am cartoon evil no that's that's no
that's not Superior I am more Superior
than that
I'm sorry I want to be sure this isn't
the dark urge play for I've heard about
that maybe I should have done that
uh
yeah can you pay me I suppose
we don't have much but we'll scrape
together whatever we can for money I'll
do it because I need money to
um buy I don't know ships and stuff to
take over the world
um
make sure it's enough everything we have
anything we can give you we will we'll
be ready to leave as soon as you give
word
a red I'm ready to leave now
clear path past those goblins
they'll find it yeah yeah who's talking
you of course
wait I'll take a rest though right I
should rest
the long rest
ah party members in the conversation I
don't think so
I mean the party members in the
conversation ah just wait this is good
as her oh wait wait this is what you
guys thought you've been threatening
what's up
oh
wait is this mall now talking to my
quaso or to me
this is quite delayed isn't it
I am not going to prison you little
ah
Daddy
who is rolling anyway
you can send the question to prison I
don't care but what
what what happened lies only inflame the
matter further things could turn ugly
very rapidly
[Laughter]
surrender my croissant
wait the only one of us that he got was
my croissant
shouldn't they be trying to imprison the
others
I just disappear I'm out of here
I'm
well that made it really easy
changed things
yes
the floor
ah perfect
I'm so confused but that's perfect
she can't keep getting away with it this
is the second time I ended up in prison
oh welcome to the campsite
why are The gales doubling something to
ask
are you fascinated by your beauty me too
hmm
leave him here in a moment
huh
well what are you doing indulging enough
spot of vanity
handsome
what does it make you think of
uh
uh the tap tadpole until they're quite
recently nothing at all nothing just
well yeah I guess let's talk about the
tadpole oh spot on fever and memory
chances is back hallucinations and
graying skin chances day three hair loss
and blood leaking
I need to go on
yes
day four excruciating pain is the
skeleton and organs reform and
reposition day five the host personality
has disappeared fingers and toes and
limbs elongate elongate you Elon Musk
elongate
what a interesting pronunciation
you might as well finish the picture yes
the flesh around the mouth splits to
make way for tentacles
day seven a mind flayer is born
annotated version of course
[Music]
um
should be having a fever by now greens
can even
approvated oh oh
spot on again
I'm so smart remain blissfully unblooded
our heads remain clear and our blood
temperature normal
any expert will agree this is
abnormal
long live the abdominal can you explain
why the symptoms aren't showing and What
Makes You the expert huh yeah I wanna
know study
but what is happening what is that study
I don't know what that is
Uncharted Territory The Silence of the
storm yeah purple something to sleep
we should get some rest
you should teach me how to make a copy
of myself as well
oh hello sir damn your clothes are tight
have you ever heard of Banshee scream
um
yes of course I have yes yes in in
Charmed there was an episode where I
think Phoebe turned into a bansheeable
wasn't it loud enough to Wake the Dead
and Shrink not me the Golden Goblet
I felt it the most terrible noise in all
16 planes but there's one even more
fearsome than that
this are you talking about this sound
that chunky wonky makes
I bet it's historians flirtatious drawl
Laser's tenacious battle cries oh hell
yeah her
the Clutter of the rising Undead streaks
of the goblin Zone laser not even close
I find them comforting even what I'm
thinking of is far more malicious
the doubt in our minds crying out for
attention
is Will approving of himself stop
resisting give up and give in
doubt is the greatest villain we Face
greater than all the hell's Devils
greater than a murderous yum yum doubt
can stop you from doing everything from
saving the world even it's a good thing
for us that we aren't most people
I am the superior evil
dragon
glad to see you're not one to give up
I'm stronger than that worm in
my head yes yes
so true
tell me more tell me more let's talk to
asterian tell me more tell me more
tell me what's going on
so you're getting a lecture from our
Magical Friend
I have to say I thought you'd look worse
but no
not a tentacle to be seen
that's what everyone's saying this is so
strange I'm hoping it'll stay that way
not yet I could say the same to you
indeed you could
we're all doing surprisingly well given
the circumstance yes isn't that Sassy
I'm not taking anything for granted of
course why are we all doing so well I
don't have to stop that pretty little
heart of yours oh
I am open to suggestions knives poison
strangulation no you will not
you will not do any of that
um
try it and spill your guts don't be so
pig-headed it disapproved how much
damage will you cause if you transform
how much blood can you bear to have on
your hands every every single ounce of
blood in this whole world will be on my
hands and I
I'll make the right choice
sweet dreams darling
oh actually I think I think we're good I
think we are
we had a good conversation there where's
Shadow heart
oh oh hello there what bus is here
welcome to the camp my friend
we meet again
it's predicted how did you know
because I like him I told him to come to
my camera
mm-hmm
uh what kind of services can the
skeleton offer ending of the threads
between
life should thou or any of that
if I I will cleave soul to body once
more so revive us
um
and look very ugly doing wow wow
because it is my calling there is little
else to explain
okay
um
oh and then he can change my class but I
don't really want to do that right now
so that's fine
thanks
for talking to me death oh what is
Shadow heart doing there
staring at her fine all right I could
have helped but didn't
anyway I feel the same other than the
occasional mental exchange it's almost
as if we're not infected she really was
listening the voice on the ship told me
I've become a beautiful weapon
what do you think it meant weapon of
Destruction
um
well maybe Houston knows
we can't take the lack of symptoms for
granted all right I've kept you from
your blanket long enough
rest well
short conversation all right not like I
can take you any longer than that layers
are layers or how's it been in the camp
all alone all this time well while all
of us are out there having fun huh
our bones should ache our mouths should
bleed yet we thrive
it is madness keep your rest short time
is not our Ally
oh she doesn't even want to have a
proper conversation with me all right
fine me neither me neither
oh the sausages
I had I made German Curry Roost Curry
sausage two days ago for dinner
uh
yeah I made the sauce myself really good
stuff
it's like a mix of curry powder and uh
onions and tomato
um
what's it called some tomato paste and
oh jam actually apricot jam surprisingly
and there are some some spices and herbs
and stuff ah this and that this and that
just a little bit of jam yeah I didn't
know that was in there
yeah and then I had to
um puree it with my pure purifier ha ha
yeah but turned out really good the
sauce turned out pretty good pretty good
pretty uh authentic just like in Germany
the rest was easy though
really easy just the sauce was really
like the most effort the rest was like
Bam Bam Bam easily created
um
cheese potatoes yeah I never made those
cheesy potatoes before where am I right
now ah here and
our time grows short if cougar won't
abandon her Madness then we'll have to
try the road goblins or no
can't let the turrets Force you out so
long as Koga leads them
never be safe here
if you're suggesting we remove her
that's exactly what I'm Suited
whatever decide I'm not involved I live
on your own terms before it comes to
that I'll help yeah yeah
whole Army
Army like the bodies hit the floor
abilities
away though goblins
are a little disciplined it's unlike
them to organize so cleverly somebody
must be leading them bringing discipline
to their ranks
take out that leadership and they'll
scatter there's no small thing to ask
but I've seen you fight you're equal to
the task didn't you tell me that already
we already had this conversation
so I suppose so we don't have much but
we'll scrape together whatever we can
okay
okay of course we'll be ready to okay uh
where Where Are You Gonna Be Ready how
do we go
how do we go that I was trying to start
that actually show The Flaming fist
pardon
okay we go to the goblin Camp just on
our own or what like a clean
okay where is this beach
and Lisa was talking about
visit call someone in prison he's only
no no no no no he vanished
it was all an illusion
their blades
beach beach beach beach beach
next to the Grove center near the bear
okay
I'll check it out wait which way is it I
think that way
what
did I click what did I click what did I
click
what did I do
why
they go could I accidentally click on on
the trunk or what
is it because
what did I do what did I do Camp science
campsite
a glitch related to the prison no
oh
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no it's Mom
Kitty over
I think I have to leave the city
is gone crossover
shouldn't be starting any more troubles
and let's just fast travel out of here
I'm terrified
yeah
uh oh yeah we're still on the Grove now
okay did we rest we're ready to leave
right yeah yeah
yeah
but the quest
we don't have to talk to him again right
travel to the goblin Camp okay
um can I get out of this map
oh what
let's see
oh well we're we're out of there
okay fine
now this is where oh Hunton karlak is
I am we should we should go here right
I'm kind of far away
now
find Carla on my step okay shall we go
for that one
oh this way
wait no this way
go exploring all right all right all
right
this way we haven't seen this place yet
I like we'll fix Kiana's waist
no one can fix my ways because there's
nothing to be fixed you mean just
waiting like a lovesick puppy
Showtime amusements are much less hassle
does this lead anywhere where I need to
go oh the goblin camp and the temple and
oh so that's where the goblin Temple is
right
well Carlock is actually closer
yes Carla can Carla can
who the is
something not like that
who are they
shall we help
I feel like Shadow heart might want to
help you're a true soul
you can't die
stay with us
what happens
can you hear us Ed
you not a step closer
My Flesh
within new stairs in response
I will go where I wish
yes
elephant
oh yeah okay I will go where I wish
difficulty class two oh
shouldn't be an issue
yeah I
know that's our brother true Soul Edwin
he's so cute
I wasn't thinking so cute something's
still red head just cute
it's taking something you'll know on
their back
the injured man locks eyes with you the
parasite rides in your head
hold his stare your minds intertwine
staring contestants andrick and Brenna
new recruits
yours to Shepherd
mine protect them
mind the true soul
she will
see
Edwin head Ed please Eddie's with the
absolutely absolute a truthful
the absolute Edwin
our brother
he was chosen like you like like me do
you have orders for us
orders
they think I'm I'm their leader because
of my tadpole
oh my God
how did I know this is perfect this is
exactly how they should react to seeing
me yes I am your new Overlord yes let me
tell you what to do hmm explain this
absolute to me what I know it's me I of
course the absolute as me yes absolute
is our goddess me yes she's going to rip
down the old world I knew it I'm just
testing you we'll be the ones with the
power well you will firstly drizzle you
don't need me to explain that
the true Souls You Will Rule I will
indeed thank you
please finally someone of reason would
have an uphill battle
what what are you doing donkey monkey
I I bought a makeup sponge a while ago
to test it out even though I always do
my makeup with my hand but I thought
okay I'll try it again why not and I
didn't really like it and now I just had
the makeup sponge lying around and
chunky wonky decided it's her favorite
new toy to play with
it's like she plays with it like a
soccer ball and kicks it around the
apartment
sponges are so easy and I prefer just
using my fingers
[Music]
um
sponge is annoying because you have to
clean it too
anyway and it's supposed to you God
would have an uphill battle
you're mistaken I'm not Russo yes I am
why are you out here the Wilderness will
happen to your brother exactly what
happened we were looking for future
survivors from that ship that crashed
farther west of here instead of them
like me Edwin found an oil bear ah an
owl bear hungry one we managed to drag
him away the beast's claws had already
done their work is it the one that being
true brought us to see with oil Bear
Tracks
aha
forget the hour you're still alive so go
you need to find the Beast Avenger
brother I'm a Survivor the crash looks
like you found me
yes
oh wait oh that oh they're good but
oh
well then okay
let's have some violence sometimes
fine with me
let's fight
let's fight speech
I'll take the high ground
if that can be considered The High
Ground
you shall die as what you get cultists
oh turn off non-lethal uh
wait
passives there you go okay
we are
back to lethal baby
what what
I'm not like I've killed less people
than people and Galley and then the
others you know I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm
not even that much worse than they are
what is this pretty strange
foreign
six meters would be a movement speed for
the rest of your turn roll range damage
twice
and use the highest result
why have I not seen this skill before
how does it how did it come here
foreign
[Music]
hiding successful
oh yeah
oh she's here
oh 94 let's kill her
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
cloud of daggers I Feel the Pain Feel
the suffering
yes yes yes yes yes yes you shall suffer
you and everybody else who will be in my
path
shall suffer
what's what's the best choice
all right then
eat this
oh I missed
ah
all right that uses up a spatula I kind
of forget about that stuff
that's lame oh he died
oh oh get out of here get out of here
why are you so stupid Oh my God
why is she so stupid heal yourself
okay
um Can This Cloud of dagger go away so
that I can pick up
something from their bodies
strange power resonates within the
corpse
to you
Moshi moti
hello
[Music]
Moon Accord
ing
to Crave oh why let its hosts memories
go to waste
a tadpole has absorbed it all its
experience could
strengthen you
ah there's a cancer when I go on Gale
bottom left okay
should I let the tadpole do its thing
what happens if you go for that
um
do it it's fine let it
oh
yeah
we healed him we saved him just a little
bit too late
while we extracted the turtle and now we
put it up her ass okay okay cool
that's a waste of no time in abandoning
its host oh it's not sentimental
creatures clearly
item is it my favorite my player
parasite specimen could be useful to
have for experimentation
remember Mario Kart
uh I'm gonna take this and put it up
your ass or something like that
is this the path to the bear I think so
actually
yes
could have jumped over the stones
F5 all right
sure why not
here
should we go for a different option than
what we had before
what did we do last time we killed the
mom right and we kept the Child Alive
let's let's just see how it goes let's
let's go with the flow but can can she
heal herself one more time
oh
is there like a
a maximum of how often she can use that
much better take a peek
oh that's tent a little bit short rounds
but everybody else is fine
to get going
even if she uses the same thing over and
over again
thank you Munda
Daniel oh hello there's the cute fluffy
chunky monkey
what do I do
what I do never dull moment
how do we do
you feel the Quake of its heavy
footsteps before you see it
face kill the darkness
it's not role-playing correctly it's
just shouldn't be scared I don't know
why she's such a way
I really don't know
doing it wrong
I will huff and puff
round round
she's pretending to be afraid to to make
the owl bear feel more confident
feathers quivering
[Music]
oh it did go back yeah actually indeed
hmm
um
[Music]
may I pass egg
okay battle
it sensed that I want to hatch its egg
this is the kiwawa
Chihuahua desires
oh
I can't attack
am I like
done
what's going on
New Egg welcome to the membership
oh it goes after a Starion hmm
just like old times
wow
I think like naturally I would go for
the more threatening thing
so I might just do the same
I'm not sure
yeah not the baby wait we we we also
we also killed the mom and the collab
right
baby would be easy to kill though
yeah yeah we did um
[Music]
the others might want to walk away from
that that's my breath
[Applause]
what's the difference
this one's better
a nice
okay ah wait this one that's the right
one
I feel so bad for this one I really like
fluffy big animals like that I don't
want to hurt them
but I wasn't the one who initiated the
battle
field no no the person behind tanakisha
feels sympathy
he's still playing with the makeup
sponge cute
I went for the egg no not really not on
purpose I was just trying to walk around
[Music]
yeah I'll throw it for you I'll throw it
see it he didn't see it I threw it
she brought it to me she's a dog
so cute
[Music]
all right
of course I miss my 55 was pretty bad so
normally should I do non-leafone yeah
no oh
my mommy
oh I can't even go that far
what if I if I jump though it's like it
takes up
the bonus action
hmm
normal attack
foreign
stay I guess but
push this cup away you don't want to
fight with us believe me
oh
freak
oh oh my God she died
is mad uh
um
Let's help her
come on Shadow heart get your
together
the Battle Is Not Over
how how to throw
this potion
uh
I'm going to do that again
oh it's an action I can't okay
[Music]
I guess this is worth the cost
the sun was in my eyes
what can she throw it though
because I only did like a main
action didn't I yeah
could could I throw it at her
oh oh it's a Oh I thought it was a one
of those uh bonus actions
uh okay
got to keep fighting you should maybe
heal yourself then unless does she not
have a
a healing
potion
I guess not
yeah
I should I give it to myself then
or to her doesn't somebody have a bigger
one
um this one 8 to 20 healing
four to ten
but I I think I'll I'll just um
I'll use the normal one we don't want to
waste the big healing potion yet
oh but can she not use it okay
drink
there we go
okay now we're surviving
hopefully
oh we're all dying let's go go let's go
Mia
ah I just wanted to move into the Unseen
from this one
but the the red area now isn't it the
range that the Albert Cub can see
because I wanna I just want to hide from
the Big Owl bear
you could I could
um
but it's shared oh okay
yeah it's got a hit
it has to
mm-hmm
I would have been mad if I had to revive
you a second time and
magic magic
Missile always hits
a blocks
dead mother
hmm
oh man oh man
single strike will end his suffering
well
thanks
that the small
Albert Cub is no danger to her
what are they improved but it hurts okay
what hurts
watch speechless
Cub begins to eat his mother
at least the cob has a fighting chance
now that we've just prolonged its misery
we'll see about that
I know that look you're wondering why I
was in pain before
yeah let's just clear the air about that
fine flare
it's just an old wound that hurts me
from time to time nothing to be
concerned about
it's nothing to do with the tadpoles at
least are you sure your imagination is
in danger of getting away from you
foreign
it's just something I have to live with
are you sure it's not connected to the
tadpoles positive
you can trust me on that
turn to other matters
oh there's so many matters
your fear of wolves what do you think of
all that's happening we should get to
know each other
something about them seem to catch your
eye the murals in the grub something
seemed to catch your eye can I say they
were eye-catching
oh wow how sophisticated
why you scared of wolves predators with
fangs like daggers
it's hardly an irrational fear to Harbor
must be it's been decent to me so far
maybe if you can
don't make me face any more of them
at least
not alone
seems to be connected to her
maybe maybe to the the wound maybe maybe
I don't know but
maybe it is
I'm still really they're just dogs with
no table manners
uh
uh yeah that's what I'll say to the next
one we cross paths with then provided it
doesn't tear your throat out first
I'll be fine
calm down Shadow Heart You You drama
queen
why is this gloating heavy Stone it's
it's so heavy and that it's like able to
float in the air so go away
so I can open this kill the chest right
I'm gonna stop you it is stinking cave
hardly a place of honor a saloon statue
it's pretty
I must there's magic keeping this chest
sealed all of this we feel it's aura
here's a trick to it good luck yep go
open it that is attracted if you
remember I don't remember
I don't I know that we I think we jumped
over
I think
foreign
maybe there was something behind
there's a book
there's a candle
let's say let's see the book let's see
the book
an agent telling the town detailing
house
thank you for seeing the prayer sheet
that's probably more interesting
a prior dedicated to Salon employing all
to accept the moon maiden's blessings
and share in her bounty
prayer sheet
with the same symbol as the one on the
chest yeah
so why do they sound like they
understand and I don't
[Music]
know
how do I take it we're traveling with a
famed blade of Frontiers
I feel safer already
I wanted to right click it
not you
[Music]
uh
all right then
uh wrong thing uh this is the one
I read it
my prayers are answered
oh
I can take it now right yay you should
leave it or even destroy it if possible
why this rubbish isn't offering to
soluna at best it's worthless at worst
who knows could be cursed yeah do not
trifle with that Moon witch or her
trinkets
only trouble she seems to have very very
strong feelings huh
I'll do so please if you want to try
stopping me for my kids
I don't care so much
[Music]
I am an intimidating person
her God Star hates Saloon
ah all her homies hate Saloon her God
doesn't like Saloon damn
well if religion is the thing that
tears us apart so it shall be
oh
[Music]
fuzz
take them if you must but I'll remember
you didn't listen to sense
I think you're just being very
superstitious
oh yeah this is fine to take
the pendant driving Raven dance when the
weather has 50 hit points or less they
don't provoke opportunity attacks oh
huh
why am I needing to roll why do I need
to
um
no
so that she doesn't see I don't care if
she sees
um
oh well again
make Shadow heart for the pendant oh
she's gonna be pissed wow what
what was wrong
man
oh oh this was just for her to not
disapprove
oh I take this
portion of healing
speaking
whoa Scroll of detect farts
oh
what was this
last jealous okay oh the war between oh
she's standing right at the book to tell
me to educate myself all right and
that's the volume that speaks of the
conflict between the sibling goddess is
Salud and Char after Saloon ignited the
Sun and brought life-sustaining light
and warm to the universe that sounds
like Saloon did something wonderful what
is your problem huh what is your problem
Shadow heart
maybe I should send her to my camp
[Music]
incense cost a lot of money it really
uh it's way to the nearest library well
now everybody's coming not not everybody
almost everybody just uh bring the
instance
we're selling that
what about this one too
much chunky wonky what's going on
her name is shadowheart not true
maybe she should open her mind and
become light-hearted
and then she won't be even so angry all
the time anymore
thanks for updating me for enough to
worry my stomach fits in no rush to go
away but I can't relate
time to see what's new or is waiting for
us yeah where do we go now we could go
up here
um
we do want to go in this direction
does this help me
going up there
yes I think so
in the face
if I pick this up can I fish
from here
to style a sweetheart perhaps oh
Neil hats
the city is a veritable Feast oh my God
this hat looks like my hat it's a bit
big
it's a little bit too big
like we got two necklaces right
do you want to wear this hmm
no I kind of want to give it to myself
so what does this one look again speak
with that Aya
Aaron you can have this one I'm gonna
have this one
and you can have this one
oh so devilish
this doesn't this hat is like a potato
sack for your head it won't look good on
anyone
yeah
the idol of saloon
you think he pulls it off
it was a little bit smaller than yes
maybe ah
I hate mushrooms in real life but
if it's in a game
berry bush
is this camp supplies
yes it is
we need those camp supplies
fastest boy yes
no one can resist the door cool well
he's so upset don't go scratch watch
you know I should have my companions
interact more with everything because
then I can go for some nicer answers
um
don't be angry
well I'll try animal handling and I'll
probably fail but oh I forgot the
bonus
ah man
if only I had the bonus
hello
what's happening instead the dog's
hackles rays
hackles
can I try again
Pierre and his collar probably says his
name does it
this time I'll add Garden
says
do you guys mind if I snack on a Kinder
Bueno
I bought a couple of Kinder buenos and
holy they're so addicting I knew
that already of course but you know you
see a name
etched into the leather
scratch
scratch oh it's his name
well it's literally telling me to
scratch him
it's all right scratch I'm not going to
hurt you
oh
[Music]
wait we can have him follow us that
remains rooted by the corpses I thought
so
oh
[Music]
what was that a yes
will we see him in my camp
um
maybe
is this a dead end
where will they go if I'm
push him
you seemed quite fluid with your
compliments earlier oh we'd only just
met seize the day I say
more now than ever
oh this is
this
this is where we fought before
oh but they already moved on over here
is it safe here
is kind of making scary noises holy
what's this there's loud stomping noises
coming from inside
ah
[Music]
should I
I don't think I should open those let's
try to go over here oh
there's a big chunk of roasted meat open
it
do it but say first real clear
you guys what do you want you want to
see me fail you want to see me being
eaten by a huge troll
Feast fit for an ogre
and it is A peculiar dagger
[Music]
that's a nice dagger
yeah I should have switched to me again
but we'll do this one investigate
15 should be doable come on you never
found this it's Excalibur stuck in a
piece of meat
you notice the blade is at an angle to
the meat me grain if you align the
dagger with the grain
should slip out easily uh okay
do it
um
I'll try this option
we're pulling it out in style delicious
method pays off
um Glides smoothly see it pays up wow
can we get to use this
ah
[Music]
not for me right maybe for me
yeah
this is all the same
but this one says one two four even when
I switch it out
oh
I don't use it okay
um
okay I thought it would be something
like that with the offhand
why does the meat get its own cutscene
dad I want use use
does that mean they'll eat it right
right away then maybe maybe a Starion
should eat it
why don't we just cut it up
why are you guys being so weird about
this meat
some tools
empty empty
mushroom rotten though not taking that
okay
I will open
this door even though there cannot
possibly
be anything good behind it come on
things have stayed interesting I saved
approach
someone
something I was having a bit of fun oh
hey I mean let's quiet uh arithmatic
are you having
some private time right now leave it
whoever's inside doesn't want an
audience
I open it anyway
very curious I am
no
what the hell are you doing
oh my
God that's the big lady
attack the couple hmm
um
see we missed out on all the good stuff
in our collaboration
no no
don't disturb why is there a dead guy
here
no
[Laughter]
and would they have been happy if I
would have chosen number two
oh man
and with no oh my God he he chose to
smash oh no man
uh
59.
I I
don't think this will go well
what did you just join in
um I I have the exact same feeling and
reaction as you do don't worry
who do we take on first the smaller one
I need to get some more
distance though sustain everything
and ideally The High Ground can I get
them to come outside
so I can jump on the Rocks up here and
attack from above
can move the barrels why would I move
the barrels
I should spread grease inside wait wait
wait wait who's the grease spreader
no their pants weren't down probably
because I have the nudity off
but I didn't catch them with their pants
down not at all I didn't do that at all
no no no no no no
the dance Macabre oh
um he's attacking next to see it oh
um
uh wait which one okay
he is
currently able to hide
can I do this
this is possible
yeah it's
it should be
oh
it is
yeah okay hiding was lost but it's okay
we have an advantage at least and he's
pretty much dead I wish I could kill him
[Music]
I think my turn is done for him
that was good damage yeah get out oh
he couldn't attack her hat because he
used up his action
okay and we're we are luring them out so
maybe there's a chance for us maybe
there is
uh we probably want the higher ground
for her too
sixty percent
five no okay I'll go for the hamstring
shot
Grace of kale
maybe after the big lady comes out
no
man
I want to protect someone
[Music]
where to put the grease is she even like
capable of
walking out for the store because she's
pretty big but somehow she must have
gotten in
should I put it like here
or here
got in somehow you know
okay
oh she's coming no
completely the grease
oh man
I gr I forgot I would grease myself up
as well
um well
he's
he's all lubed up too good for him good
for him
[Music]
um
that's what I'm talking about
what'd you say
[Music]
sad
sad my way
s but to keep going he's hidden now all
right
Eldritch blast
oh oh
it worked all right I think I can win
this I was not very confident in the
beginning but I think I can win this
good job good job walking out of that
grease I'm so proud of you
I I wouldn't mind her coming out again
though because it's all greased up and I
want to fire a fireball here
ideally
or is she greasy now too by just
standing in it maybe not
we'll try it once
said damaged okay
um
hey careful don't fall down
uh
jump out of the grease and then it's too
late now
get out
she's not gonna
she's not gonna burn it up
let's finish this
come here come on I can't attack you
from here what do I do
sacred flame
can I do this
no
heal up
uh who needs healing
a Starion
yeah and then I need her to come outside
so I'll just be waiting here
I'll just wait I guess
just aim up and ready what does that
mean can I do that where's that
just uh
phrase she could jump to move further
I want her to stay up there for The High
Ground though
one guide yes he's
oh
oh okay
um
do I shoot at the floor or at her does
it matter
20 damage
it's rooting through
yeah I shouldn't have
you'll hit Gail
um
well he's slow
okay okay wait how about at first help
him up and then they walk away
um
I can't can he ah he can't
just just uh shall be done
is this far enough how big is this gonna
be
we'll see I guess
we have to test it out
wait does he have a oh yeah he could
check this
although I don't know if that's gonna
help
if he gets enough for 20 damage then you
know
only the grease area okay then that
shouldn't it be safe now I think
I think everybody's out of that area
I won't give in
then
[Music]
guys
I thought I can just shoot at the floor
let's have some cups wait I have fire
too don't I no
or he has fire nah but he can use it
I hit the blood ah come on
ah no no no no we need some fire we need
it now
no no no no no no no
no we gotta do something here
The Alchemist fire item uh
uh
uh which one
we could also throw
always
this thing no that's oil
I don't speak it draw poison
shadowheart has it
but she has to give it away huh
[Music]
acid
fire
that is such an embarrassing fail
let's go I don't want to do this wrong
how do I
like this
I don't know what I'm doing
I shot the blood
Pro
fire
hey okay so here for example is fine
right
tab
you have fire on your character yeah
well now I do what do you mean
take it from someone else I have it
though
[Music]
um
you want me to use this instead
foreign
okay all that trouble and it was only 11
damage
kind of made not gonna lie oh
I should teleport myself into safety
and The High Ground let's go
damage is damaged she'll take fire
damage every time oh
okay
what do we do about you I would like you
to survive my dearestarian but there's
not much you can do is there
um I could I could push
but hide here we could hide there maybe
no no can't reach
good heart here
this is really hiding can you really
consider just hiding
oh yeah he's done she's
I'm done
let's see what boofier will do
um but okay it's the one who was already
low HP so
fine
uh
okay
still 27 man we need some big big big
damage you know
I'll just believe in the elders blast
yeah
what was that seven and five
so 12.
that's good
that was good that was good that was
pretty decent
let's do Shadow heart first
um
75 one to ten
I think I'll go for the fire
more fire Miss
girl you had one job
there and it's okay even if you die
it'll be for the greater good and I'll
help you
um don't worry don't worry
we must not let them procreate after all
this is this is for the greater good I
can't walk away can I oh wait I can walk
to here
I can't hide again
I thought
I thought she don't see me but yeah why
can I not hide can't be threatened
what does that mean
you can disengage hard and then Sneak
Attack Just engage
engage
ah
frightened within five feet oh five feet
how many meters is that
wrong one
I already had the snake really still
oh well that's then the only real thing
I can do
where is it
doesn't change anything
just that I'm I guess not threatened
anymore
uh I don't know if I want to waste no no
he's still fine he got 20 hp
but I got six damage okay okay
again
yeah okay that did a little bit of
damage
[Music]
it no babies for you I'll put this
behind us no ugly ass babies for you
help Gail
when we don't get from it well that
must be more to this
some gold or Javelin do you have a
Morning Star and Viridian crystals
combine three of this to grind them into
salts
and there must be some treasure in here
for this big fight oh okay okay okay
Alex here of Hill Giants
well that would have been useful maybe
if I had it before
increase to 21. and Chris drink to
increase your size
you can't Advance on the strength checks
and say it replaces effects because I've
used all of this
oh
oh okay I've taken it beforehand
the realm according to Bumper who's
bumpo
I don't want to read that
well let me read this
he follows a dog-eared page in which
Bumble describes the more unusual races
he's met in his travels but they weren't
half so strange as the bird folk the K
of B
first our crime Mets had the head of a
parrot the body of a human and wings
also of a parrot I tried not to stare
but it was real hard and stop staring at
us
it's embarrassing and it makes me feel
uncomfortable turns out she was one of
the mostly party cars around her table
where a tabax see catfold a janasi
element for look at the tortoise
Turtle food of fun trying to act
casual I asked why the hell what the
hell they all were they ignored me but I
can't blame him to them I must have
looked awfully dull on average for they
were the first of the kind I'd seen but
I was just one of a billion boring
humans to them
there's Turtle falcon cat funk where how
can I find them
[Music]
how can I find this A is for Azul and
other gods a is
and other gods B is for
bunk the troll
as if the god of wizards all who spent
their whole lives learning he grants
their spells both big and small for
mistra always yearning Bane the Tyrant
the black hand make sure the strong do
rule he spreads his Darkness through the
land praised by the harsham crew beshaba
will bring forth your doom unless you
chant her prayer split from Tamora in
the womb she brings bad luck to space
sparra I guess even if you wanted to
rhyme
nahone
stack Swift tonic susilian sweet and
well yum yum they got some yummy looking
stuff
okay what'd you say guys was this worth
it I think it was worth it for at least
watching that cutscene
right right
too bad we missed this
before
how do I get up there
maybe like walk around to the left or
did I have to go from here
I wanna go here
um
you you could have gotten more if you
just what
what do you mean like a baby
no thank you I don't want a troll baby
the river has a spot you can cross or go
over the bridge to your East aha the
river
so I shall go back here
surprised I haven't been finding any
like marks for teleportation
then I shall
return to the river
am I right
I'll just help myself
something over there
anywhere
you mean the honey wait what what's this
we found another hole
wait we should camp
first
we shall camp
uh oh I didn't do the the long rest
thing but I can still do a long rest
while I'm in here right
and just uh
and today
yes
let's go to bed man
well don't automatically eat the all
Bear right
did I even take it maybe you wake up
because you know something is wrong or
maybe you just get lucky
no no it's not what it looks like I
swear
are you in love I I wasn't going to hurt
you I just wanted me well
blood
ah the vampire Scott
he really is it can't be held right
now
uh how long since you killed someone
dates I always pick up steak and
launched the monster monster
he's not a monster I've never killed
anyone well
not the food oh really
I feed on animals balls deer
cobals whatever I can get
it's not enough not if I have to fight
it feels so
weak
if I just have a little blood I could
think clearer fight better
please
a strange sensation courses through you
and your companions mind unfolds
Secrets half revealed
[Music]
and why don't we let him drink our blood
huh
bro thinks this is Twilight I never
watched Twilight so I can't relate but
oh why didn't you tell me gotta be
honest to your leader I'm sure you'd say
no more likely you'd Rama steak through
my ribs
no
I needed you to trust me
and you can trust me
holy I can tell him to leave like
forever not even just to camp but not
not even just staying in a camper like
forever
him
and I'm not I'm not that like upset
about what happened
if I was then this would be in character
but I'm I'm not that late
concerned about it it's okay I guess
thank you
do you think you could trust me just
a little further
I only need
this one oh
oh he still wants it the try Shadow
heart man don't don't go for me
yeah
well oh
well are you saying that if I don't do
this you will die and oh that would be
too unfortunate sure like just a little
bit it's like a blood donation right it
won't really affect me but yeah I gotta
keep my party alive like yeah but don't
drink anymore than you really need
it don't look at me like that
challenge
the ball we gotta be comfortable for
this okay okay
that was terrifying that look at the end
of ice into your neck can you not be
more gentle in that fades
good breath cat
pulse quickly we're never doing this
again hysterion
yeah yeah seven seven
what if they see us they'll think wrong
and they'll be misunderstanding
driving into his heart was an option oh
my God
Mamma Mia Bella moment really
oh holy I really want this to stop
look at me with my 22.
oh God
of course oh God
amazing shut up it's just food for you
I feel strong
I feel
happy happy
show me that happiness in the upcoming
battles
[Laughter]
[Music]
wrong yeah
and again his guards down grab the steak
and drive it into his heart no it felt
wrong
oh
don't be so dramatic
this is just a little transaction
between friends
what do I get together we can take on
the world yeah but I'll kick you out at
the very end of it
um
these options man are so against
vampires
um yeah if you ever try it again it'll
cut you in half it won't happen again
of my word
so if you'll excuse me you're
invigorating but I need something more
filling
this is a gift you know
I won't forget it
he watches he stalks towards the forest
stronger more confident ready to hunt
this is very interesting
there's a lot of uh Vibes going on
wait he's got a
got a little Mark there
how do you feel how do I feel
oh my neck hurts how do you think I feel
I have I've
be grateful I have a lot of pain in my
neck at all times abide from them and
you might wake up as a vampire spawn I
got a debuff right yeah I think I saw it
all of a vampires hunger with few of
their powers
um
uh
is that how you can stand in the sun
because you're not a true vampire
I should be Cinders in this light is it
because of the hat right the hat is
saving you I'm such a genius someone or
something it's shielding him
they've changed the rules they've
changed the vampire rules The Meta
wandering into homes without an
invitation they're all like we just did
with those trolls for my other quirks
well
we can figure those out in time
figured them out quickly I don't want
any more surprises no more surprises you
have my word
he is I'm just so so polite to me
Revelations
I was worried people might turn up with
torches and pitchforks
although there's still time
a vampire
I noticed until
we're each monsters in the making after
all through
oh and a quick word of warning historian
I taste absolutely awful keep your
distance how do you know
hmm
yeah I trust him are quite the opposite
I'm here a lot of this approval there
well together where even are you to
disapprove words but I'm not so sure you
mean the right things
still
decision not just demeanor there now
guys all taste wonderful I know it I
know you do ahead of us especially with
the right herbs Anya how do I get rid of
this bloodless woozy minus one to attack
world saving pros and muscle Builders
but until I sleep again or what
man
until long rest okay that's okay that's
just minus one and I have a fancy glow
thanks to that looks nice
I'd like to check this body out before
is this from the fight
I know it's a dog oh the double owner
I didn't wanna take his things because I
thought it was disrespectful but I guess
maybe I shouldn't care so much
these letters
gum Wick be that uh be doubly careful on
the way back to battles gate I've
received more reports of attacks on
travels throughout the region I can't
have my best messenger winding up face
down in a ditch somewhere
oh that leather didn't really help much
ah
David it's a boy it's healthy and
perfect I've named her mother's father
come back and see us as soon as you can
leave Dave David
his name is gomwig
Nani
tough letter
nine fingers I won't come back to the
city not while you have your folks
looking for me if you want the depth
page you'll have to trust me thanks for
the man
is that isn't that what I do all the
time huh
you'll have to trust me and collect it
yourself go to the graveyard and look
for where an M curve in is buried get
digging and you'll find enough valuers
to settle matters between us
well where is this will I find this like
by accident
oh no uh
oh okay it's over there so
I could walk over here no
I will get there
here and um
should be able to jump further no
jump
eh
is this not the right
maybe maybe here
just walk now
oh okay
um here
all right
[Music]
okay now we're really close what's over
here
that looks familiar actually
needs help
come on guys just do what I did
do I need to tell everybody how how it
works
when did I come back
stay there stay there
what's next
just follow my example God damn it if
it's so hard
aren't they grouped
no
body told you okay but now they're able
to do it I guess
I've
important to discuss with you oh we've
been traveling together for a while now
and it's just about time that I've
shared something snacks
prefer to keep quiet but needs must when
the devil drives
I have no choice but to speak you see I
have this
condition very different from the
parasite we share but
just as deadly tell me more
but first Neil
so you've been lying to me this whole
time wonderful that's so
what kind this could be the rather
personal but suffice it to say that it
is a malady I've learned to live with
not without some effort what it comes
down to is this every so often I need to
get my hands on a powerful magical item
and absorb the weave inside the weave
what's the wave
you're addicted to Magic
consume raw magic I'm going to need
oh it's it the weave is the magic
ha
hmm
now what happens if you don't tell you
the finer detail
begins with a simple biological
deterioration muscle spasms
disorientation a slight ringing in the
ears only slightly here too long it's
bearable catastrophe
since before we were abducted oh no
well where is it by that I mean
imperative
strands of weave at the earliest
possible Junction
sounds very important he's so serious
about it
um
true I failed to see why you need me to
help you with this you've done fine
without me so far that is very true
a fair point yeah however until recently
I was able to rely on a supply of
artifacts stored in my tower in
waterdeep
ply that has now run dry
the reality of the matter is that a lone
wizard with a chronic impairment such as
my own is not in the most ideal in
situations with regards to self-defense
maybe just maybe Anita not often found
waiting patiently on a shopkeeps Shelf
one usually has to lift them delicately
from trap-filled tombs or prizing from
the hands sounds Troublesome there'll be
danger involved maybe it's just time to
get over the addiction maybe we can
start that journey together and we can
be your supportive
friends to help you with that and then
we don't have to waste
our money and time
and our health huh
are you ready to start that journey I
guess not
hmm
why would I risk either of those things
for boys that I barely know I'm not
happy to help I could help but I'm not
happy to help
right
ah
yeah then I suggest you look closer huh
is it like me around is quite the Boon
when facing the perils that stole these
lands
are far harder for me to assist you if I
could barely stand up right
please
trust me
your help could be the difference
between life and death
no
use your telephone seek the danger at
the heart of Gail's request does that
mean seek the danger
is that a yes or no
because this is a yes and this is a no
what is this
I'm willing to tell me the truth on that
Hillary
learn more
you're gonna say okay well I I don't
know I don't have much wisdom at all and
I'm minus one
and I need ten
come on we've been very unlucky so far
we gotta get lucky now
please oh okay
without the guidance I wouldn't have
made it but
now we're good
start oppressing you it's inside of here
a mighty Darkness radiating from your
chest from my chest yeah that's my dark
black heart but you'll hold over Gail I
know about this it won't be easy delving
deeper without him noticing
didn't help me so far
I will delve deeper
I must 15 now come on come on yes
hey
let's go oh oh it was in here okay she
talked about it like it's my heart you
[Music]
spawned
suddenly open oh inside there are no
Pages
swirling Mass a blackest weave that
pouts it's not a book then it's claws
it's Unstoppable as it digs through and
becomes part of you him you mean God
says it ever hungry giving me a suspense
are you where come on tell me
do we have an agreement or not
uh I don't know what did that tell me
that he's got some struggles but
what you saw makes you hesitate
question isn't it
what could you pull yeah I'm on my voice
thing a lot of time with this I agree
with that off again yes I keep it to
myself and I offer my help to give me
exactly what I need what
I have it
oh any magic
I only want to learn I'm more used to
wait what artifact do I have what would
I have been giving him any grain no
no I need my green items
I can't help you right now I need my I I
don't I think I need
them
I need all of them
don't eat all of them
I don't think I have many green ones
maybe two or so
[Laughter]
can I even undo still no we're in this
now we're in this
and say bye bye together no he will
understand
all right all right take it
I see no let me remind you that it's not
something that can be ignored forever
okay we're fine the facts are of little
use if you don't live to enjoy them
foreign
addict man
man
your problem not mine
we are here to hunt down
the man
and I want to look around
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh wait isn't
this where we yeah
no
oh
you're gonna get destroyed in this area
[Music]
oh wait I'm here at the quest marker
come here
but I don't
is this Carla
oh
ah
why hello there I was just here
collecting some herbs happily that are
drenched in blood apparently
and then I
I just lay my eyes upon you what is
going on who are you you look
you look very very
cool
[Music]
oh she's mobbing
oh she's on fire oh
one horn
like new like what
okay
huh oh my oh my God why the leg
holy encoding overloaded consider
turning down videos or using a faster
OBS why are you overloading
what's wrong
my whole it's not the game even a game
game is not lagging for me it's OBS why
is it the fight but why how is it how's
it how's it let's douse the flames
that does dowsing mean putting them out
study on Soldier oh my God
it was just that one scene weirdly oh no
wait there's two there's two ah ah there
we go
how is this
affecting my OBS it's you and the notes
annoyed please tell me I found you
before they soaked chicken says well
me
I know it's a like a phrase but I'm
surprised she talks like that I like it
uh
I don't remember you from the ship yeah
now that's a story and I'll tell it to
you but truth be told we shouldn't stay
here too
paladins of
a great heat
oh yes the hills then you're lost
versions of demonic armies doesn't tear
through a landscape of Fire and Blood
you soared from above as the north Lloyd
passed through avernus
was on the front line huh
ah what was that
leave me alone
it's the tadpole in their hands
man it connects us
yeah
sake what the sake yeah
mountains as far as girl I don't know if
I can have you in my party you make my
OBS lag just by your sheer existence
you've made some inroads trying to get
the thing sorted why is she glowing no
joy
I'm karlak and you are
she's a tiefling too right
leave me alone
um
[Music]
should I really say that now
um
[Music]
spicy
she's too spiced too hot
well met Soldier now that we're all Pals
how would you feel about helping me kill
some evil bastards
needs something to point at
you already know I fought in the blood
War I was good at killing demons really
good hmm so good zariel the arch devil
herself made me her personal attack that
sounds like you're fit for the superior
evil that is mean until I could get the
out of there
took me 10 years to probably Escape but
now I'm free now you want to attach
yourself to me Rosario sent goon after
goon to hunt me down but believe me when
I tell you I'm not going
a group of dopes posing as paladins of
tear
wanna help me take him down
sure
evil John needs new attack dog yeah
yeah a strong Melee character she lens
look like a strong Melee character and
she's got a glowy glowy heart cute she's
on fire she's like she's basically a
phoenix
not quite but basically
she's a golden retriever keeper
cute golden retrievers are cute
um
[Music]
mmm now yes yeah
oh my God she kills my OBS every time
there's a close-up of her why don't we
mop them up we can work on evicting this
parasite and take pharoon by the short
hairs hell yeah sounds good
perhaps a little rough around the edges
huh but I suppose I can be smooth enough
for two
all the Flames but no I don't understand
but this is weird OBS is just capturing
yeah I don't get it
um
yeah let's do it join my team whether we
replace though
hang on though this is shuttle hard
I'll catch up with you when it's time to
Camp yeah yeah but don't get to any of
the fun stuff without me got it
I don't know
Gail okay
at least we got Carla Carla Carla
on our side now wonderful wonderful we
haven't found Carl but I guess it
doesn't matter now collab because we we
are our own party
we don't need
all these NPCs in our party yes
girls should be bench girl is the most
Expendable new wow you guys just like
Gales oh they're like cute I like
them all I want a bigger party
also why did somebody say that this area
is too dangerous for me is it really
oh pumpkins
I don't know where to go next where
should I go next
oh hey
strong enemies for real for real
the camp
what to bring Cola can
it's doable go away
[Music]
item Affliction seems very high
maintenance true
[Music]
hmm okay
we have to do a long rest for that
all right let me pick up some stuff here
first
Apple
um
something to write through these people
does the rotten food count
yes
oh my God these pork back they're eating
the each other ah
damn what's going
[Music]
I want to pick up all the food lady
we can't let this food go to waste
uh even the half eaten apples yes yes
all of this is camp supplies good job
good job yeah I think I got it I think I
got it
ah
looks empty you sure
why don't you just look inside and
confirm that
safe
wait I don't know should I go that way
to the hyenas it's a little bit
unnecessary
we shall switch out someone in our team
though Gail is that and for real for
real
one horn oh the stink of a furnace
avocados diaboli oh I'll be God's damn I
like her will so you better shut up
thought I'd shaken you for good
that'll teach me to underestimate you
karlak the archdevils Aerials Gladiator
come to burn the sword Coast to Ash
why don't you
if I do this will he kill her like right
now sheesh oh
the two of you have met before I see I
met you mean who think it's through the
hell with this on my tail
shut it devil I know you're kind a heart
darker than a Shadow's nightmares you'd
cut a child's throat just to Taste the
Blood a devil hmm
I didn't take the blade for a fool I
think she got what it takes
through you on the fire of the first
tearing through demons across a blood
red landscape of fire and Volcanic
symbols the front lines of the blood
wall
s mistress Ariel's purpose
clear a Summer Sky it's over Carla it's
time you feel the sting of the blade I
cried constipated I don't know what you
think I am it's the tadpole
Ray's slicing through Devils zarya's
servants oh eyes Dart around
shutters with colax desperation she is a
victim of the blood War not an agent
topic
no I will not be tricked I'm back I'm
back the truth
I may be an effective Soldier but I
never wanted to serve Zario legged it
away from her the first chance I got
and yet you served
you do what you gotta do you know
um
I should have never trusted you Carla
you're as good as dead you want to fight
will I'll give you one well yeah
everybody calm down calm down
um
yeah you saw what I saw breath in his
lips come on
she had dread twists his face
no Devils cannot be trusted he's scared
hmm
hold on
it's you I don't trust will
hmm come on why do you guys have to
fight like that
like that
you know monsters better than anyone
can't you look in my eyes and see I'm
not a devil you look very devil like
though I gotta say like your visuals you
literally on fire I'm asking you got
horns you're red don't want to hurt you
and to be frank I'd rather not find out
how the blade got his name
I swear to you on all I am I'm not look
at those nails are the ears
oh oh he got emotional you really
are no devil are you oh I've
I've been deceived oh ah thank the gods
oh I was gonna have to take your head
yeah me too you would have died in the
attempt but there have been enough
threats shall I load my safes and we'll
try it
I truth
I promise not to lose sight of it
even when the hells burn hottest
huh well that ended nicely
Gladwell Source sense even more glad he
decided to stick around takes a pretty
slick mover to track down is she not a
tiefling because I thought she is but
she looks very different than me because
I'm not on fire and she is
why why can't she be on fire
she is okay then why is she on fire
a curse
just modified she's been she's been
modifying I'll find out I want to find
out now
um
[Music]
still the man's got a reputation for
being lethal with that blade
I'm glad it's on our side yeah true true
can I romance her just ask him for a
friend
I wanna I wanna feel that hot fire on me
ah
foreign
satisfying
thanks for that
you've been witness to a pantomime I'm
sorry to say and I've played you part
all too poorly oh wow he's very
self-deprecating right now what does
that mean laid out plainly well
if you weren't so useful I'd drive a
dagger for your skull if it brings you
any comfort
my reckoning's coming one night soon
when we make camp
the veil will be lifted and I'll pay my
pennants what the that scares me
what are you saying should I be worried
um it turns out to see the blades
a little bit concerned about that
statement but uh Tana Keisha says it's
intriguing you
I don't know what it means
I don't know what he's trying to say how
do I switch uh
I thought I am switch members of my team
down by the river the girl
I'll tell him to stay oh man I feel bad
he's a cool dude
I wouldn't mind like
even if I don't take him on on the
journey I wouldn't mind like marrying
Romancing him
the odds are stacked high enough can I
romance all of them no need
at the same time
oh wait oh
um
it oh he's ah
he's not feeling so good
ah
yeah that's what I thought
[Music]
not at the same time but like after one
another
can I do it after
what's on your mind
apart from finding me an artifact to
consume which I assume you're consuming
no emergency them what the hell why not
um
I question the wisdom of that decision
oh man I really like him
oh
yeah we'll travel again maybe
the hours oh man oh no you know
if he sees must feel in this situation
you know you know you have to imagine
that there's like Souls like people are
stuck in this body and they're stuck in
this game world and I I'm the only one
who can activate them give them
something to do whenever I don't even
have the game open they don't even get
to idle and then and then now you know
they must be suffering when I make them
wait in my Camp because what you know
what I'm saying you know what I'm saying
is the theory that these people are
actually like you know
somewhat
real and they have their own minds they
they are more than just data you know
but but but without me without me
or and or other players who are playing
a game
they're like forever stuck in the void
oh oh man I feel so bad
it's got nothing to do he's just gonna
be in the void
Soldier
that's it
those dance moves no
I'm not taking you no no that freaked me
out what what
what's on your mind
I don't know girl that was a surprise
like I didn't expect
nothing respect that what the man
what
I've read about those paladins you want
us to comfort Comfort them by yeah
killing them and letting them feel the
comfort of death the sweet sweet release
hmm
what's the best one this is
actually end up fighting in the blood
War trust me I'll tell you all about it
after we take care of the goons on my
tail okay well you know everybody is God
you know like they want to do with
me though like it might take a while
but you're joining me yeah yeah
stop lagging my OBS okay
mm-hmm
thanks for being
with opinions oh
are you talking about like Monica
wow
yo yo yo look at those juicy
fries
I I like that she's not just like a
stick nice
wow what a what a woman
huh
Wild Heart
what uh what is this
Legacy of everness savings might fire
damage
fire damage dot damage this one Wild
Heart Berserker wild magic you guys tell
me you guys tell me
Berserker Berserker Berserkers
[Music]
okay
seems like the winner we have a winner
we've got a winner
team her portrait looks so nice
everybody everybody's portraits look
really nice actually
[Music]
do I aren't we we don't have to eat the
camp supplies now right
because uh already
hit points
[Music]
I can just do partial rest right
yeah okay I'll leave cam
well this is fine too seems fun
good
[Music]
you guys want to hear some
usaken behind the scenes
yes
yes let's go
I'll tell you I'll tell you about
towards Empire
[Music]
oh she's excited
you haven't got some laughing curse have
you maybe she does
incredible just keep it down I can speak
to us enough without your hyenas
speaking of hyenas there's loaded hyenas
over there yeah uh you know when we like
prepare we have to do some kind of like
movement and stuff and they like play a
video for us to copy the movements it's
always the same thing and if you do it
for the first time
um it's like it in all of the difficult
it takes takes like a few times to
really grasp it you know I want the milk
please
[Music]
and then
it was so funny because she asked them
to speed it up like a lot and then she
was like making all these super speed
movements while everybody else was did
it normally but she was like
I just wanted to get it over with really
fast and I was like damn what a flex
girl
I'm doing that exercise yeah honestly
she's not the first Senpai though that I
saw doing that some some sambas they're
like so confident in that
someone eviscerated those null
they just want to like get it over with
really quickly
what is this hyena here yeah
disgusting
[Music]
and then I don't know if you saw this
guys because I ended up not seeing it
anywhere but
um besides
uh you know there was a Whole30 dance
short right
um but besides that oh
oh we filmed uh with both Lisa again and
horotoni we filmed
um
all kinds of like small videos that were
supposed to be apparently used as like
advertisements
that are shown I don't know where uh
but apparently not uploaded as like its
own video
what is this place
and I never ended up saying that did
anybody see them you saw one of us again
do we got to see I don't know man how
you would say it but for the second one
it was basically Us in the background
while uh pecora Senpai was like you know
um advertising the concert
um I guess we'll confront the paladins
here huh how do I confront them are they
inside
scary
uh we were kind of like free videos I
think oh this is scary
yeah free videos
with us again
and then
um also free with horotoni
and
430 I did all the talking and the girls
were doing some stuff in the background
so if you guys find that video you
should like screen record it or
something because it seems like most
people
just didn't ever see those videos yeah
YouTube I was told that they were being
used for yeah ads on YouTube and
possibly on Tick Tock or so I don't know
where but maybe also on Twitter
hmm I have premium oh you can't save a
pre a
damn I would have liked you guys to see
some of them hmm
somebody said I should make potions how
can I make the potion oh I don't have
the right stuff for it what makes you
think that I could make it
speaking of
um
you don't have any more
but you can heal but still
all we give yes to you and we'll see you
[Music]
after the Gathering some herbs you in
there
I'm seeing the more though just more rib
cages
uh yeah and then yeah for hello Tony we
took the whole three dance video which I
orchestrated basically like for us again
and I think all the other video videos
that were uploaded as YouTube shorts
oh it was like management kind of
like would that worry you
deciding what to do I suppose foreign
[Music]
way too big another hole man okay
I wonder what's underneath should I
check it out I was so fun right dancer
was so so fun
uh but yeah basically I don't know if
you guys ever have seen them before but
like especially with K-pop
um there's like this thing where when
the new song comes out they will do like
dance relay
dance release where they stand in one
line and then one after another they
just you know dance a little bit of
their choreo and it gets pretty
interesting Waypoint that's pretty
intricate
and sometimes they even make their own
like formation choreography for that
stuff
y dance was awesome it's so cute thank
you so I've been watching those capable
of dance relay videos and I thought I
would be so cool if I could ever like
get the opportunity to to do something
like this but for my own songs it makes
no sense because I'm just one person
um but I kind of wanted to do it with
myth but
yeah done we didn't get to do it
um maybe another time should I is there
someone in science hello
there are the paladins aren't they ah
yeah
um yeah so I asked if we could do this
and so that was our short and then for
us again for us again let me just
quickly tell you we
um maybe you saw it we took this video
where we were like exercising and me and
Muna were like supposed to have a good
time exercising while you look over to
Bhutan and pecora and they were having a
really rough time exercising and Tula
Senpai was the one kind of like
reporting on that and the funny thing is
when we recorded this
um they set up this like selfie stick
camera angle she was actually holding a
selfie stick and she was supposed to
film it in like um you know selfie stick
angle
and she tried again and again but she
was like really struggling with it
because it was kind of heavy and the
angle was kind of weird to like position
correctly so yeah we had to retake it a
few times and then
in the end
she requested to give up on it and we
just had a camera person do it instead
yeah so
possibly not only noodle arms Wawa but
noodle arm still I said bye
yeah we ended up just taking it normally
no no selfie stick not really
[Music]
um
yeah
exposed
it took some trial and error do I just
walk in here hello
please no more leave us in peace and we
shall leave you in kind are you scared
already I just walked in ah
ah I know what you are
don't let her hurt us please we just
want to go home
but
I guess they look nice though why are we
why why do we
um want to kill them
probe his mind
yeah these people seem harmless
detect fonts
let's see uh oh is he deceiving me is he
just really good at looking nice and
being nice
foreign
[Music]
they're pretending to be paladins
head on a pike
oh did you just fix Ed out loud
because I heard that
hmm
you know if they're calling you want to
kill her on zarya's behalf
I never was good at playing the no you
were kind of good at it I believed you
the hell's I fear not with her ladyships
protection I believed in this dog
this animal
she destroys all she touches useful in
the blood War
ningly dangerous anywhere else
Rage or you want carlak burn with the
might of the hells zariel will find you
she will bring you home in pieces
and your little friends will have to
watch
unless we feed you their eyeballs first
melty no
but can I shoot them
oh my God oh my God what's happening oh
Hunter's Mark on you she's already down
to 24. can I shoot us
cool maybe
yes
okay first is just these two huh there's
probably more over here no oh wait no
I mean I aren't
we
I think it would be anything oh but
wherever first we're first uh attacking
with um oopsie vegetarian huh oh gold
um wait I want to I can't it wasn't a
shift to see the
to see the the
red stuff
foreign
it's a bit buggy oh really
I want to see it I want to hide
I'm probably but if I if I if I go here
they obviously don't see me so I hide
now they don't
this
yay
yay oh wait how much damage was that
oh good twelve
let's go let's go what is this by the
way vampire bat oh that's new suck the
blood from a living creature to regain
hit points
[Music]
um
all right
they won't know what did them
bite is super good really
it's also pretty decent in Pokemon
though
let's go
so what do you do you're you're mainly
right we we can bring her up to the
front here
you don't have quite enough movement
though
what do I do how do I fight with this
lady what's this film attorney getting
advantage on intimidation should I
always use this first or so
jump um
still
now
we can't jump anymore
rage start raging
raging
you mean uh
Frenzy
your rage turns into a frenzy you gain
frenzied strike and then arranged and
raged fro you can also make an
improvised
weapon
[Music]
click to confirm
Ary
speaking of Cali I want to say uh
her performance of gouda was one of my
favorite things of Splash partying uh
night version
that was like
so
wow so different right
very different
very interesting I love Toho so I know
all the Melodies I love Toho songs to
her music
did that yeah okay
I love
they're all like very familiar to me and
but the overlapping was just so cool I
really liked that
mmm
holding me
oh
what
what how many people are there
this one's kind of dead
we have to save the baguette it's a
friend of course
well it's just completely I thought
maybe I just can't move out of here but
hey let me let me do let me do let me do
the thing what the
what should I return to Swift
maybe maybe
um
maybe I can blind one of them
guiding both the girl in the back this
one or you mean her would be nice if I
could finish her but somehow shadowheart
always misses man
I must try to ah ah we just have to
damage her to end the holding person
okay okay
come on eighty percent
oh but
wait what we gotta we'll just end
yeah we have to walk over here first I
suppose on my way
nice okay
eh I'm still in prison
Arrow no
no hmm
she rolled a set
thank you
[Music]
come on what was that oh
unbelievable you little piece of
out in there
it's a hard fight if you don't choose it
how to cheese it
came out of hiding for you miss
um
I don't need healing but it seems like a
good thing to do right now
let me try this
oh
he gets a buff from there too
all right all right all right
um
okay
it'll be pretty good if I kill one of
them should be possible with her
friends you strike 55
80. okay
what's this Reckless attack
throw her
does it also do good damage on the
hurdle
Florida
how does this work I select her first so
the target is too close
already targeted aha eh so I'm already
throwing her
yeah looks like it
oh
pretty good if I throw it at huh
no I want to see it why did the camera
change man
okay they're not dead but um
wait I can still attack
I can still attack I'm not gonna like
this mate you're not gonna like this
mate
let's go I like her so far look at above
the cleave cleave
[Music]
too late now but oh is this an AOE ah
damn attack up to three enemies at once
damn
see yeah this is my first battle with
her I gotta get used to it please don't
hit me with 16 damage you
[Music]
I'm already dead
what acid
oh my God doshio
get up
oh could I have done it with only I was
gonna do help up and then he'll
there's a difference
can I use this one
uh
healing Ward would have brought it oh
okay
um per level
I'll do it
hi
[Music]
okay is she standing in acid now too is
that a problem
she doesn't seem affectable but for me
it's
two to eight damage per turn
do I have like an item that can heal
that
[Music]
increase your size strength
um
the important is ever easy
I originally wanted to get up here but
they never let me I could go now
I could get up
here
Hotel
[Music]
that's all I can do right now
but at least I'll stay alive
oh nice
what was that was it what did he do at
the end some protection
oh but thank God he missed on on the
Starion holy
well that prioritize attack should I
attack Mamma Mia Mamma Mia I think I
have to what's what's the what's my best
thing to do
oh
it's got 15.
[Music]
I can't kill him
get Carlock first
should I try her because I could kill
her
or do I go with colic for him and then
try to finish her with a Starion because
he should be able to finish the Starion
just engage hard sneak attack
with with her
you mean with a Starion right kill the
bigger fret yeah okay
um foreign
6 to 17 6-17
not enough movement
[Music]
ah
okay
yes I killed him
yo you deserve this let's go
got a pair
let's go that was the close one
she gonna be okay she should die forever
can't see
Justice is a very good sword
you sold for college oh run
this one for color
Sword of Justice
hire is protection level one app
generation spell
ing
two-handed sword okay
not in combat not a model
foreign
that's not what I wanted shift okay
on the way
the subtle approach the subtle approach
sauce now
die
[Applause]
[Music]
paladins
him yeah cereal yeah I won't
go back I'm never coming back
and if any of mummy's little friends
want to pick up where the others left
off they'll find nothing but a pile of
Ash
easy color you're burning up my OBS
um
not big enough now get out before you
get hurt now
what's wrong with it what's you
doing
what's he doing
why can't she stop like girl I need to
loot
and then to help this discussion well
she's
oh the up
she's raging
flute girl girl
what what's that
oh my God wait what is this Shadow heart
[Music]
oh my God this is so chaotic
we all do ah yeah
attacking me right
[Music]
can you can you stop Carla please
that's a little for little steam after
facing Fire trail just like me a hollow
cure granted the fire is lasting a
little longer then
how do I look
I don't know we should leave we should
uh
slightly mad to be honest are you all
right hot careful Soldier
if I burn any hotter
don't explode please please let me out
here
infernal engine for a heart or how has
me burn as hot as the hills how did how
do you do that running in overdrive
since I left of earnest she do that
won't be seeing my mechanic anytime soon
so I'll just make the most of the extra
heat just don't get too close until I
found a way to calm it down
okay now now we're talking
how the hell's huh did you get an
infernal engine for that probably in the
hell High pain tolerance and the dynamic
duo of truly shitty bosses but it's a
bit early in the game to be getting into
tragic backstories oh that was the scar
show for later after we've worked wall
breaking meanwhile I'll need to find
someone who can tune up my engines
sooner rather than later believe me when
I say this thing is hot
time I faced down those paladins I
believe you're not slip there was an
infernal mechanic in the area
tiefling he might be able to stabilize
things
if I can find him hmm
ah this is the reason for us to go back
there I'm scared of going back to the
Grove I don't know if they'll imprison
me again
um
sounds like a good lead oh she wants to
go there and be among them tune up would
do this old tub a world of good
I I hope oh see yeah everything has
cooled down thank God now we can look
chilling
and you look very yummy toasty
I want to add some garlic on to you then
then you're the dream baguette that I've
always dreamed of
oh
well if we go back we can also sell
everything
that'll be nice
am I missing out on something dry
clothes
stitches
sausage sausage
I wouldn't have seen that otherwise oh
yeah let's go
scruffy Vagabond cloves
sausage is great for supplies sausages
are great for everything
hell yeah what was that one bedroom oh
wait
bucket
shabby wardrobe
I'll take the Apple
why is why is there such a weird sound
is it her heart
huh
having the sound is coming from her
heart
household prayer more books burlap sack
I want some gold
there's a special item on the Roof oh
yeah oh yeah
do I get there from inside
oh
11 bucks huh
there's also this hatch
now body's so ripe I need to drink the
blood with a fork oh that tall collector
tall for what
whole house Ledger
let me read I want to read this
before I pick it up
[Music]
oh
that's why you got that gold oh that's
only a little bit though is the rest of
the gold in here
oh
yeah
oh yeah always gotta open everything up
next
people right out
keep on forgetting that
I'm just checking everything
and uh
you know what I mean
veggies
um
veggies so many crates here
an ax oh paradigmo
um
I mean so far all these like random
clothes and
um weapons refining are not better than
we already have
positive and it's been like that for a
while
that's kind of disappointing
but yeah I guess we can sell them yeah
so uh who's got the necklace currently I
think him no
he does have it
uh but uh it just fell still on me wait
how do I
how does it work oh there it is
about all the money you've been making
uselessly
um
how did you die
goblins again
it's always the goblins
hiding oh
so you're not always here
abandoned you fans
I know about that
okay
well then have a happy afterlife I
suppose
locked we shall ha
shall we attack it then I haven't found
a key anywhere
huh
thanks
do it
yeah yeah
it's kind of tough
it's corn on top fellas
whoa
is it burning now
no that's it I think it is
kind of
do you think fire damage works
no it's not several as well that ends
as well as he could have
oh
press t for details
resistances
fire damage against his entity is
doubled well I can't really notice much
about that and force damage also
slashing damage
really doesn't have
slashing fire and force
um yeah I know it's medium tough but how
do I make it less stuff
is this a slash attack
just
damn it hit it harder toughest enemy
today
kick the door
well let's put those trying to fire
again come on
the key is pretty near to where you
found Carla
that's like somewhere outside
gnome
yeah kind of pretty strong to break it
it didn't seem like it
um
what's your shadows okay okay wait we
found her here
you said it's pretty close there
if colic has the sword she could be
strong enough really yeah
okay I'll give it one more attempt
um
[Music]
one more try
okay Carla don't disappoint me now
what's the like best
best way
Laster it makes me think of lactating
let's try
hmm
wait ah wait I got this one back
oh we're getting weaker
leave that mofo
come on no no no no
why why
just attack
there's no more attacks
there we go
yeah bye
are there more traps can I see another
one
foreign
[Music]
just want to check out everything oh
rotten carrot no anything of yours
reception failed
step on them was she stepping on it
broken patent armor
oh another hair
cute that one has feathers on it even
[Music]
rags
rotten
cheese would have been good but it's
rotten cheese
[Music]
hour of acid nice
good stuff good stuff
241 gold
rotten chicken
eggs who forgot about the newcomers guys
somebody was in charge of them and
forgot about them that person is going
to the usual room yeah what the
I know you like dancing Carla but you
don't need to show it off right now
she's done now
Grant's Ingot yes oh there's another
door what do we do about this one
this one just opens all right then
I'm so scary when they when they're like
trapped
trap makes me think it's really
dangerous but it's actually fine
something the matter I accidentally
clicked on you guys all the time please
please don't
engage
oh a fancy wizard hat oh yeah
[Music]
how much 30 ish
foreign
guys I have to check out literally
everything
I are incoming no no no no no no no no
no no no
no no no no no no
[Music]
so what what was your guys's I mean my
some of you might be biased but what is
your guys's favorite
um performance ew uh from the concerts
tell me tell me one of my favorites was
the
the good uh Kelly one
Tony hey
you guys are biased
on Anya was so funny what was that like
that was so comedic they had like this
this
thing going
oh draw poison
poisonous potion
mind reading this is these are good ones
yeah blue Clapper they had like a new
version of Blue Clapper
um
look blue Clapper not blue Challenger
don't make me doubt myself there
empty potion bottle
wine
better that will fit in my pack
large bottle oh let me check out these
and then we'll think we're done
oh cute
huh
yeah yeah was there anything else really
special in here that I'm missing what is
this
there must be a hidden door no
how do I get into here
secret room
um how
if I sit on the chair does that activate
something
no that's a pressure plate in the chair
I'm missing something
there's a press it clicked what do you
mean what do you mean I'm missing
stuffing it click oh wait ah
watch your back
on this one
we have to stay seated
um I will I will walk in oh my God I got
it immediately holy
what she saved herself from the toxin
but
simple toxin am I good to walk around
what is what is there now
quick
uh I think esteron is the only one who's
being affected
don't die gorgeous staff
gold let's avoid that trap
great sword okay okay well we'll heal
afterwards me ow
is this better
is it
a healing potions
in the wooden chest oh
gloves baby gloves of heroism
warding hands when you use your when you
use your channel of spells you gain
heroism
noise
helmet
candle
Shields Vegas I think I've got lots of
the good stuff
ah is he okay
oh
let me read this book while I'm dying
may I please read this book in peace
can I fast or loud I think I can yeah I
found a waypoint out there this is an
excerpt from the play a pleasurable deal
banned and no feared and force it is for
its loot content
it's scandalous Nate this is a blue fan
fiction scandal's nature led to a number
of widely distributed and illicit
printings I found the biggest treasure
down here let's go
come here Fair folk a tale now lost to
time in grief this man will sunk to
death Sublime a gift he saw to win his
lady's heart our cambian smiled for now
the game did start enter Robert male
tiefling crying call Isle whatever his
name stage right flesh of smoke oh this
is a stage play
we
weep not young man though free your wife
has fled and comfort found in comrades
arms and bed she licks her lips and
cries his name oh my and now seek you to
be the apple of her eye
how does a stranger know such things I
ask
I watched you from the shadows and I see
your shame and grief for Nature's Melody
you seek to win young lady and her bed
to have your name upon her lips instead
you know my curse my pain my grief my
bow
of you I know you seek a larger hope to
plow their maid and sow a seed to grow
but like a mighty horn and Mast with
which to guide a mate to bed and fast oh
no maidens
I hope I found everything important
because I'm I'm gonna leave now
oh I couldn't disarm this plate huh
I'm leaving now
uh which one was that
I think this one
there's one more thing
I was scared
oh wait it's only him only he went okay
um
great because I ungrouped oh yeah uh
something about swords you guys say
Shadow heart I'll die where are these
swords I mean these ah
um
I was about to heal myself uh
elf outfit
real crazy oh my God thank you for the
Super Chat
[Laughter]
I'm lacking a person how can I heal her
laughs
um
stop it guys stop it
the 34 one maybe the 41.
I need to hold on I'll try this one
I used to read the book yeah you can
cover the vents of the boxes eh
foreign
[Music]
I just want my stuff and then
leaving
the fancy things there was indeed some
fancy sword on on the table
okay this is where it opens I rent one
so super rich isn't it how can I make it
so that there's no toxin
um
well hello
you know what we'll have someone else
sit
disarm the plate
how does this work
all right that I mean
10. with all these bonuses let's go
oh broad so now no toxin
looks like it
oh so that's just
this is the way to do it I see or see or
see now I can carefully check every
single vase to make sure they didn't
hide something super special in any of
these
great sword let me check that out
way
this one
yeah I mean not something I would use
but certainly something to sell
a great X plus one this one's green
what's in here hmm
[Music]
I'll take this one too to sell
maybe the gloves could be decent
these gloves of course and all these
things again
the necklace I didn't see the necklace
before I figured
this sword
Gail
what I'm not giving anything to Gail
he'll be fine right he must
this book was funny
all right
unless you have another funny book like
that
I'm quite satisfied
he'll leave oh just one other but he's
dying okay okay I'll look at what I have
but I can possibly give up
um
I'll consider it
okay uh can we go back to the camp from
here
is that what I want to do what did I say
I was going to do anyway
okay everybody's outside okay okay
um
I'll go I can't use them okay you think
those gloves are for him they're for
Paladin only oh okay
well well oh I like how sometimes you
camp looks different I guess depending
on where you were until that moment
interesting
wow this one I haven't seen before
uh oh I don't need to rest anyway huh
maybe not no need for a long rest though
okay Gail
how do I give this to which one actually
these ones
but they look so nice
we're giving this one away
with the heroism
okay
finding it quite difficult to
concentrate my condition gnawing at my
insides like a teething displacer kitten
how often
with green things
[Music]
um
that is most gratifying to hear
well I guess we gave vegetarian blood
which three times a total okay we will
give him
magic artifacts
just to be fair okay what do the others
need from me then
[Music]
no okay I'll give him okay okay
here oh wait he's got who's got some
stuff too oh yeah right I gave him this
thing these things didn't I
if I take this from him
hi donate
thank you
yeah that's the bow that we stole hey
that's the spot I'd hit the spot I can
feel it work
the magic it's like a lullaby that sings
to sleep the demon inside metaphorical
demon at least the point out but no less
dangerous now we're inner demons yeah
yeah continuous ravages
[Music]
and perhaps now you'll tell me what all
this is an aid of
grateful as I am the course of our
camaraderie is much better sir by not
taking that particular detour
not just yet sincerely though
I understand I ask a lot from you with
few answers in return
but in time nah it's it's all we'll be
told not a big deal but I don't know why
you're being such a
annoying little piece of
do not tell me what this is for really
hmm
[Music]
the condition of yours is a very
expensive one getting more too deep
I think there comes
well well I'm happy for you I guess but
please do something about these
cockroaches because this is disgusting
very disgusting
okay that's all we really need to
do here I would say
um
I don't want too long I don't think why
do I want to Long rest
and lightning really messes with you
obvious the lightning I don't know uh
something is messing with me indeed but
this time it's not just OBS this time
it's the actual game you know when OBS
was freaking out about Carlock that was
just OBS but not the game
hmm
what's going on
house fire
he's coming huh
what
no need the
well
you've been benty and you know what
happens when you're naughty is that his
dominatrix or what anyone but her
who in the ninth house are you that's
exactly what I'm thinking that's just me
God damn well get out of my Camp that's
a nice set of wings let me guess what's
pattern yeah yeah that's what I was
thinking is this one of the patterns I
have still not seen my own pattern but
that's uh I was I was thinking that
could be his Patron
like the the other thing I created in my
character creator right
handlers the word if it's all the same
Handler my puff here's been on freaky
and his leash
his Patronus quite the dominatrix
indeed will I hope Mama Tony won't be
like this to me I've taken more pleasant
shits than you mizora
okay just like we for real for real
by the way Carlock Zario sends her
regard you
you told me
Devils only
she's a tingling not a monster how
precious
the little popsters found his bark
claws G section nine Target shall be
limited to The Infernal the Demonic the
heartless and the soulless what's she
talking about Carlock meets the criteria
by virtue of having no heart
uh
uh she wants Carla to be dead
um
oh can we attack her catch the poor
devil what do you want the point
oh yes thanks for the reminder
what oil burns in the fires of avernus
the lightning storms of Death Strike his
flesh his soul passes through each layer
of the hell oh this fire is fine obvious
is it and they're torment
oh he's oily
oh
he's got horns now
that's better why did you do that what
have you done
it's broken a price paid he looks more
like Carlos now get used to the new form
Pat
There's No Going Back
some magic even I can't undo some magic
even I can't understand how the
Frontiers fare without their precious
blade
keep an eye on him would you I'll be
keeping mine yes
oh and well it's like one of us don't
forget
our pack still stands
I am more confused than I was before
he's a devil now what the man
everybody wants to talk to me what is
going on explain God's damn her straight
back to the house just look at me I did
what was right and Missouri made me pay
for it I'd be hunting devils and demons
why can't she do them traitors and
hypocrites heartless evils of All Sorts
but not
the Real's victims
innocent teeth like
I don't understand
he broke a contract Oh by leaving Carla
alive
why did they make how do they how why
why did they did what does everybody
have a contract man
um
hmm
lucky she didn't take her soul when she
came
I'd count my lucky stars only warlocks
but I reckon luck is on holiday oh I'm
only alive because my Patron still has
use for me
it's mizora who grants me the power to
conjure armor and cast Eldritch blasts
Elvis Presley
some investor in clouds but and I
promise you every thrust of my blade and
every flame I sparked was for the good
of the coast
well
so what's my
what's in my contract
I don't recall the terms I need to call
my lawyer
maybe my password is nicer hopefully be
cute
and mistress could do the same with that
no hell nah
she better not
hmm
what are the terms of your pack I can't
utter the terms or circumstances oh NDA
tell you most all else but the pact and
forbidden unless mazora permits it but
I'll say this
the moment I packeded myself to Missouri
I have not regretted for a heartbeat it
proudest deed are you sure about that
I'm not done with you why did you end
our conversations I hope he got what he
needed from it
yeah
questions
[Music]
how does it feel to be a devil it said
that anyone who bathes in the river of
blood emerges as one born anew
it's a lot like that I imagine
I feel the weight of these horns on my
head turning upwards like a mammoth's
tusks I feel these ridges snaking down
my neck not to mention a few bumps and
prongs in unmentionable places oh but I
haven't seen my reflection just yet
be my mirror what do you see
uh
freak of nature Gods put your hands
I don't know what to make of it
yeah I'll fight ever harder
the ever stronger till my Deeds Eclipse
my appearance can he turn back we'll see
a curiosity maybe even a beast hungry
for their souls but I will slay their
monsters keep them safe and one day they
will see the blade of Frontiers again
tell me about those Play-Doh Frontiers
my father once said one does not pursue
a Champion's life
one merely answers its call
so it was for me
I was hunting near the cloak wood when I
heard it at a child crying out from a
lone Farmstead I found him in the fields
flanked by a goblins
his mother's corpse bled into the soil
next to him I don't remember much of the
battle
but I remember drying the boy's tears
after
[Music]
he named you blade of Frontiers no
but he named me friend
and that meant the world but what if the
others
the children never saved
the cries never heard in the boy's tears
I finally saw the suffering wrought by
the villains of the Wild
the Frontiers demanded a blade
and so I heated
[Music]
ah so many questions
and before that roller skate bowling and
raised the only son of a single father
he wanted one life for me I chose
another oh we haven't spoken since I
left the city the classic drama a
staunch father and his rebellious son
better heard from The Bard's lips than
mine
you should get out of this pack can you
suppose it's not
but I don't have a clue where to start
other than play her games and play by
the rules that's the only language
Devils listen to
wild bear at all of course you do that's
worse than she already had true I guess
she could probably kill him could we
just attack her the next time she pops
up um
can we
yeah can we can have all for it but it
won't so much just
chip a nailed claws she'll escape to the
hells and if we succeeded my life would
be taken in exchange my contract is very
clear I can bring mazora no bar
she'll have to let me out of my pact
willingly oh the only way out is if I
can out bargain her we're standing here
with nothing but the clothes on our
backs and the worms in our heads well
maybe we can offer the worms
um
we can be there if we put our words
together yeah our one brain cell worms
[Music]
um
I'm sure here broke
if you see me as more than my patrons
pet
of course I do because I have one too
but I guess my character doesn't know
about its existence yet I really want to
meet the my own pattern is it like so
far in the story that I would meet the
my mommy
does that take a while
as she knows okay
she knows
Guardian is not oh Guardian is not a
patron
she knows it's a willing concert okay
okay
it's a guardian Albion Soldier unreeling
will hardly knows me but he chose my
life
it's over here what about me put their
neck out for me like that
yeah but it would be kind of cute if
they end up being lovey-dovey hmm
the finest bathroom light that was
extremely dangerous it was courageous a
very stupid move yeah wouldn't be
courage without the risk would it
I'll figure out a way to make it up to
him
what a Heroes like
swords like what do guys like
um
pocket watch belt uh
but belts
the ties uh
depending on the person I suppose video
games aftershave gel wrist watches I'm
not gonna give someone a motorcycle
like it's so easy for me as a girl to
give something to a girl but if I had to
give something to a guy I I would be
pretty lost
um
[Music]
Chihuahuas membership oh that sounds
good
that sounds very good
socks oh no I'm sure people receive
enough socks already we don't need any
more
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah when did you
still have the exclamation mark I mean
we already talked about that
no less bound to wake up again to
continue its ravages
such as the nature
why does he still have that I thought
we're yeah is it a bug because we
already talked about this
well I'll just end this conversations
sincerely though
I understand I ask a lot from you with
few answers in return my lady
okay and now it's gone okay
anybody else of a exclamation mark no
okay
uh
isn't it insane how fast the time passes
oh my God but weren't we supposed to I
just wanna I think I think
I want to go back to the city see if I
can go into the city
um
should I just do partial rest
partial rest
I'm gonna go to the city because I was
supposed to go to the city I think uh
for something I've already forgot I just
know I was supposed to go to the city
um because because uh I think Carla
Carla Carla
there's such an English pronunciation to
pronounce her name is carlak
um let me get out of here
I hope you're enjoying the game I am
there's actually I'm really grateful it
feels like we barely made any progress
um
which one is the closest I don't know
these waypoints feels like we barely
made any progress which is a good thing
because I didn't want to go past the
collab uh point
I took my time with everything Emma Road
Grove okay
thank you
yeah I'm glad we got a chance to meet
Carla I don't think we will
unless I forced them to I feel like
we're not not gonna
go that way will we because we're
already past the point where she was
closed was where we already had I think
a fight and we're already past that
point so yeah let's say because who
knows
if
they will be angry at me how do I get in
here again I just walked close to the
door right
no reason but he's interesting
and she's she's interesting
just uh interesting characters
short red oh yeah oh
that helped hello I'm back is there
anybody who wants to attack me please
calm down
where where uh this one no which one
what's what's the quest
am I going to the
what's the thing that we gotta do
Shadow heart this one
it's an infernal mechanism ah we're
looking for Druid right a Druids
I think in here quickly what do you say
is that what you say I would say
I'll also sell some stuff a blacksmith
not a druid I uh
a tiefling blacksmith
but please remember
you're not the only one in need not
one
what's this is Alex why does he have an
attitude
okay let's sell something
uh how do I
how do I sell several things at once
hmm
rather attitude better prices oh
[Music]
no I don't know
let's take all his money do I need a
torch I'll keep the torch right because
I still don't know what the soul coins
do
spy hats
you can double click
foreign
I guess I can sell these things now too
don't need them anymore selling letters
why would he buy this
I guess who's archiving it maybe
float
when nobody here is proficient right so
let's sell it too
recycling
can't believe I'm getting paid for this
stuff
what do I do with this
I thought it could be camp supplies but
it seems like it's not
ah
[Music]
you can always buy a bag if you need
later yo yo yo have you tried performing
on the instrument you're not perfect no
I didn't know I didn't know that's
possible
I can still try to perform
Bloodstone ingot
ingot
what do you got what do you got oh
ah is that the gold all right so well
nice to be with you thanks for taking up
my stuff okay let's find
a
blacksmith tiefling there are a bunch of
tieflings
I wonder if he would be very hidden
can't really see anyone here
why why
is it just a tea flakes maybe that are
mad at me but why
why
what did I do
but quaso was so
how do I fix this I need to be here
story-wise
I didn't steal anything it was a wow
like some stupid children but they're
all friends like what do they care uh
disguise yourself well now it's too late
don't you think
just run away for a moment
is there like an action to run away too
how far do I run away
disengage
I can't
ah this one
moving won't provoke opportunity uh
ah
[Music]
important but then
but then can I never come back here
what
I was only him
enemy too close
[Music]
ah this guy's spell I can disguise
myself I think wait wasn't me or
no it was I was a shadow heart hook in
Disguise myself
as long as it says they're temporarily
hostile then you can come back okay last
time this happened I reloaded huh so I
never gave it a chance to like snap out
of it
27 meters
ah there's another one
ah
an unoccupied space so that you can see
it's probably more there
can I go here
uh wait all right
and
run the wrong way yeah
all right I'll teleport over here
ah
why you gotta be so complicated
wait
oh oh I switched I was trying to see
what he's doing I thought he was still
there
um
what happened here
dazed no I missed it
oh
okay let's Dash let's get out of here
heading there
[Music]
please don't follow me
oh wait you're ah you're not one of the
enemies
let's go
oh oh wait I'm stupid
Count On Me
no I won't reload we have to get through
this once if I understand correctly we
have to get through it once
apparently somebody said that
so
I hope that's true
wait what's happening let me go I want
to see uh
just sending the people who aren't
wanted I'm not sure who was wanted to be
honest
no no no not everybody has to join this
fight
[Music]
ah
true Carla should be fine at least
[Music]
let me go
very well
foreign
yes we're out we're out we're out baby
you think she would be welcome
can she stay
will they try to fight me
if I stay in Iran okay
okay
well
that
unfortunate I will it's only called like
Anyway red who needs to find that person
so if we could go with just Carla now
they're separate right
let's go
I want to move
only Carla here does this work
yeah
okay we're on our own but that's okay
oh wow what
down by the river
why do they hate you there was an
incident earlier today where I found
something interesting to explore
and then turns out that there were some
kusogaki tieflings
uh little children
and they wanted to pick a fight I
suppose
they want me to get out in 10 seconds
and I didn't because I thought well
what could I want to see
that I wasn't sure what was the right
thing to do
um
[Music]
he warned me but nothing happened
afterwards so I thought okay this is
fine probably then
um
yeah and then
I don't know is this a blacksmith it
might be
oh this looks like the right person yeah
I no no it's fine
it's surely fine and then and then
suddenly I've realized that my my minion
that I was supposed to be dragging
around was stuck somewhere I noticed
that like way later and when I checked
it uh I I saw croissant the million was
in a dialogue and I clicked on him and
the dialogue turned out to be me AKA my
minion being put into prison
and then I thought well also because
Chad told me I can just
I can just uh get rid of the minion and
then the mini oh she's dancing then the
minion will be out of prison and I did
that
um so I didn't really serve my prison
sentence either
well
[Music]
so much I sent
something Inferno what's your story
hey I Remember You The weaponsmith Right
your city was swallowed up by a furnace
and you were enlisted against your will
like Mike itself
Oh I thought they had you for Keeps glad
you got out
I got lucky
looks like you did too
and
brought some infernal Machinery he's
smelling it
a little gift from zarya
keeps me burning yeah she gave that to
you huh very hot by the smell of it
burning out a piston ring
oil
that reminds me of she honest
shots smash a sword through her Burning
Heart thingy
I don't understand
I might be able to help
but I'd need infernal iron
and a prayer
infernal iron the temperature a little
worried I'm gonna go in for a handshake
turn down the temperature first
much
I'll see what I can do to give you my
machine that complicated is going to
need serious work
more than a purpose Forge can handle
oh I'll take very mysterious
I've sensed some during our travels it
pulled to it it sounds like it's gonna
be very rare once you know
I can show you where I'd look so rare
that is possibly only in one place see
me again soon
oh why where am I supposed
oh what's a Fair Quest say now
there might be one nearby nearby
it's quite a lot of it oh really there's
a bunch of necklines oh really I already
have some
don't
wait wait wait
yeah
no way
there's supposed to be one down here
what's this
uh-huh
it's kind of close it's kind of close I
kind of want to get it but I don't have
a waypoint close by
how
am I you think I might have one are you
sure are you sure are you sure what does
it look like I don't think I have one
you guys say I might have one but I
don't think I have one Inferno iron I
don't remember getting an infernal iron
there's no infernal iron
in my inventory
should have got one from the tombs I
didn't I don't think no
maybe I got it in the collabro
there was one in the tombs
I would
no iron
that was a soul coin oh
we could go there but it's already so
late why does the time go by so
fast
but see by taking care of all these like
character Side Stories it's like
something we wouldn't do in the collab
so it's easily different content
man
um
but I also wanted to read some super
chats
part free
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
well I'll save this for now here
part 25
this is game we're probably at this
pacing take me 50 parts or something
that is not smart at least that's the
impression I'm getting from it so far
oh
foreign
[Music]
two years from now baller's gate free
finale I can see it yeah
I can sense it
I mean I could probably
run through it quicker you know like a
Speed Run the game of course and ignore
a lot of things but that's with a game
like this you should enjoy everything
every little corner Ever every NPC
interaction
[Music]
um
oh man I am in a kerfuffle
such a kerfuffle
such a Gruffalo
ah
how much now
you could play to relax offstream and
maybe I will maybe I will
maybe I'm well
I was sent something that I didn't
expect to be done so immediately what
the
okay I'll quit game but I'll save it
again though
um
uh oh my God thank you guys for Super
Chat though
yeah because you know I'll uh you know
I'll be doing some stuff some special
stuff next week right I'll be showing
you guys some special stuff probably
um
and for that like just today I thought
of something like oh this would be nice
to have you know like
a quick little something and then I I
organized it and I can't believe it's
kind of apparently already finished I
want to see it can I see it I'll mute my
it's just a really short thing
removed my desktop audio
you will not hear this you didn't hear
that right
there's no way you heard that you don't
have to mute it yes I do
yes I do
[Music]
oh my God
oh
[Music]
pineapple
huh
you didn't hear that no you didn't
pineapple
never
huh
I'm excited
um tomorrow is Monday right
you can maybe expect something tomorrow
already
basically
the first half of the week will be
pretty much dedicated
all to whatever I'm hinting at whatever
that possibly could be I don't know what
it could be I don't know I don't know I
don't know
so there will be a stream tomorrow
um kind of late in the day I'll make a
schedule after the stream is finished
um
why am I teasing us again
excited
I did I'm excited uh Mamma Mia
um
[Music]
actually I didn't I didn't really
um tell you much at all I I think like I
didn't I don't have that much more
tangents that I didn't tell you yet I
told you about
I already told you about like
warming up to pequoda Senpai before a
while ago right
um that was part of that
uh I told you right
like how I was like uh I I gave her that
little toy
um because okay you stand by and told me
oh she usually likes this character and
then she didn't like it after all it
wasn't her favorite but she didn't even
tell me that
tell it again I can try to quickly
retell it
um yeah so I was out with gura and ukai
right and we went to gacha
um machine store and I was like I don't
know what to get and I find some like
character gotcha that I knew that
generally like there's several smaller
characters but generally this is what uh
currently Piccola likes is what I knew
and
um
was like next to me so I just confirmed
with her this is what peculus ever likes
right and she's like yeah her favorite
is this character so I was trying
several times to get this character the
specific one out of the gacha and I
failed several times eventually I got it
so I was satisfied and then I I um on on
the day that I met um pekora Sam by for
the first time like properly I uh very
proudly gave it to her in combination I
think with some Austrian chocolates
yeah and I I I I heard before from like
pecula in her stream uh about the
character that she really likes but I I
don't know hearing it from okay you so
so
confidently like oh it's this character
you know I thought well she must know
like yeah sounds about right
yeah and then
if I didn't tell me but I was like here
this is for you you like this character
the most right and she's like
[Music]
and I'm like ah yeah I did it and like I
awkwardly quietly move away again and
sit on my side of the table
and then later on later on uh I hear
pequoda Senpai talk about it on stream
and then I realized oh
that wasn't her favorite
[Laughter]
but she didn't even tell me right away
she was just so thankful very nice she
didn't she wasn't like no this is not
the character that I like but you know
thank you she didn't even mention that
yeah anyway that was you know uh I got
closer as in like in the beginning was
really awkward but then later you know
when we were recording all those like
advertisement videos and stuff as well
um yeah in between the waning time there
was a lot of waiting time in between for
setting up everything and so everybody
was like really freaking tired so we
were just like lazing around on the
floor and
um it was like kind of quiet and I
thought oh I need to make some
conversation to fill up the silence
um so I I started asking people stand by
some questions about like what she does
in her free time and stuff and that then
then I was actually able to have some
non-awker normal conversation so I was
quite quite happy I'm proud of myself
that worked out well yeah
[Music]
um you know with all these like
International
groups like
and also the the theme song group I've
noticed you know the Ian girls I told
you before but this again was uh again
showing me that it's not just me the
other en members also mostly seem to
prefer to change in the changing room on
their own the ID members don't care so
much and the Japanese members also don't
give a they'll just go in together
but when when
members and usagan members noticed that
we didn't want to go in right away I
think Luna was actually also kind of shy
and preferred to change alone that was
the impression I got
um yeah when I know the stage is also
like they went in one by one and then
they were like okay you can go
you girls aren't used to each other yet
that's not it's not even it like I'm
used to myth members but I still kind of
well well I don't know when I changed
with Gouda we were in the same room but
like I was okay with that because I know
she's
like kind of shy about it too so I knew
that she wouldn't look at me and I
wouldn't look at her like we have this
understanding like we have to look
opposite directions
so I was somewhat okay
with changing with Gouda
prude Ian I don't know
and oh is it prude it's just shine
you know
yeah and a lot of them uh often you know
this is the first time you're like kind
of like getting naked together like not
completely naked but um
you know
oh yeah but I'm I'm actually glad uh
that there were no no incidents like
oopsie I entered your changing room when
you were naked oh no no no I
I usually also went in like last anyway
yeah yeah yeah yeah need also an
experience I had Onsen experience with
Kelly
but yeah
I don't know
hmm
[Music]
yeah and and me and Muna I told you guys
we're like we felt like well I felt like
we were giving each other a strength
because Muna was like
awkward because she didn't understand
what was going on and I was awkward
because I was nervous about pickled as
an advice so I was so happy to have
um
yeah
because like
I felt so awkward we were we were
holding on to each other
and like in the off time we were leaning
on each other and jumping around
together
that was nice yeah
um
yeah did I write down anything about
Horror Story
[Music]
oh yeah
I I told you already about that
partially like doing
new jeans and then me now with the short
out I can tell you I taught them little
Dance and yeah now you know I I told you
about it before it came out right the me
teaching mume like some movement she
wanted she was like
what should I do I don't know what to do
and I'm like I don't know do something
like this like um you know I was just
like singing out the lyrics and moving
along to it uh stand up search yourself
all right you go down and then you stand
up when it says stand up and then you
start your stuff maybe do a pose like
this
um stand upset yourself what was it I
don't know anymore
yeah
but I gave her a little choreography
and I basically orchestrated the flow of
the dance relay and yeah I wish we could
have done a full version that was so
much fun so everybody got like you know
some time in the front and then they
moved to the bag until at the very end
it was me and at the very end everybody
was just like you know falling messing
around
um
hey
Chihuahua Senpai roll yeah yeah yeah
movie was very very lost
I helped this last owl
um
you know they're doing the maintenance
yeah yeah right before we started
recording I was like let's do the
meeting dance when it starts okay
and then so what do you say if I try to
join in when we were like already done
doing our thing cute
Subaru struggles because she's
I have this feeling sometimes
it's not a real bird but I'm not sure
about it but maybe that's the reason why
she kind of struggles to adjust uh to
adjust to us but I don't want to make
any assumptions you know
um you know we don't wanna we don't want
to come up with any rumors now you know
no no no no let's let's not she she's
probably a bird probably probably
I'm about
93 sure
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
no I'm sorry for making you guys feel
uncertain too like she's like obviously
a bird I mean of course she is of course
of course sorry sorry sorry sorry please
forget what I said okay I whispered it
you shouldn't even have heard it
just just forget about it just forget
about it
I forgot about it was a swan
super fun
[Laughter]
[Music]
forget about what um
uh
yeah yeah
um
okay
oh did you see in
oops it was yeah the the the usakan
performance man bang was so difficult to
sing yeah like
when when choosing the song There were
some suggestions
um somehow
bang was like a really popular choice
and I was like
there's this song even fit a goofy group
like ours
but we went with it I'm like okay I mean
it's a it's definitely a cool song to
show off some
vocal skills but I was like yeah kind of
uh effed when like the lyric split is
basically done by management ninja sent
a lyric split and I look at it and I'm
like uh
these parts
you gave me guys they sound kind of low
and I tried to sing it and honestly it's
really really difficult
that's like as like the absolute maximum
it wasn't comfortable to sing it
it was like
that's so low I can't I can't go that
low not comfortably
[Music]
okay okay
that wasn't even the only part man
yeah
and then I got a really high part and
normally high parts aren't so difficult
for me but this one was difficult
because there was like this
what was it like
um
[Music]
uh where everybody say I want to live
freedom
something like that that was also
difficult
and everything everything was difficult
about the song
it was very difficult and then that part
that went like
um
[Music]
like the pronunciation of the word is
also quite unusual
um like it's like it's Japanese so maybe
some of you most of you guys don't
really realize it but it's like a really
cool way of pronouncing these words
partially
um
ah it was so difficult
but yeah Luna honestly Luna fit the song
so well I love hearing her
um
sing it like she wow wow the like Flavor
of her voice you know she has this like
naturally sultry sound in her voice
um so the song was perfect for her
there was actually one part that uh kind
of confused me I think
um I think for there's this one part in
the beginning relatively in the
beginning first half of the song where
um you hear me saying
everybody say I want to be free where
I'm on the left side moon is on the
right side and we're like doing this
like drop drop the hips move right
um and it repeats like twice everything
[Music]
those parts that was supposed to be me
and Muna singing together but I think
Luna's microphone was off
somehow because I I could only hear
myself
did you notice when the close-up on the
second line close-up was on Muna
but did you hear Moana sing
I listened back on it several times and
I don't I don't think I heard Muna sing
[Music]
um
so I brought it up and maybe they can
fix it for the Blu-ray
you only heard me right yeah we were
supposed to sing together
um
Marissa liked that part oh
I think I only heard you I think so too
I was like am I am I deaf huh what's
going on I'm like pretty sure I don't
hear Moana
together
ah yeah I don't know
do we I think it was funny like how they
were first of all with pebbot
uh
they were like performing this like fun
song and then we join in and suddenly it
gets like really cool and there's some
English and song and suddenly we're like
really cool you know and Sultry and all
that sexy let's go
apparently it changes the whole
atmosphere
and then that in that performance I
kicked
the speaker and I broke my ankle and I
now totally have
a cast around my ankle
yeah I was I must be so professional for
continuing to keep up a cute face and
singing and dancing right after kicking
the speaker like that
man I'm so professional
[Music]
Yeah I broke my ankle
oh yeah that wasn't cool
[Applause]
for the pain yum yum
why am I the Tom Cruise of whole life
I'll be fine by tomorrow going to London
wish me luck Ricky
where are you going to London from
you're donating in pounds
are you I'm gonna please
go to the for Manchester
how come you haven't reported to me yet
about going oh yeah finally I see you in
my chat
why why didn't you go to the musical
yeah
[Music]
sure okay
let's go you're a mod now you stand out
now I can see your properly let's go
so
you blew
do I get an answer
from Ricky did I miss it where's my
Ricky
where is my Ricky tell me about your
excuse for not going even though you're
in the country
I should go yes you should perhaps no
excuse me
wait what's closer Manchester or London
that's that's probably
London is probably closer
oh yeah Manchester is like very far okay
well how
long then you should take this
opportunity
to check out the plane
bye bye
oh I'm so excited we reached 1 million
already
I'm really excited I I didn't think it
would like do so well I'm quite proud
very proud
1.1 already holy I wanted to make a
tweet about it wait wait wait wait wait
can I
um what's this like site where I can
screenshot this nice one million counter
um
YouTube video views counter
Real Time YouTube live okay
um
auditory dance
oh no Tony dance hey
[Music]
that's the one
snippety Snipping Tool oh my God why is
it growing so fast huh
what the
oh my God I'm so happy and proud of
monotony our first ever original song
reached 1 million so fast
yeah
let's go
let's go it's fine
[Music]
let me post a link so that we get even
more views I wasn't even because I was
busy and all you know I wasn't even
promoting it that well
it's just like so smoothly
okay so smoothly it's doing its own
thing on its own it doesn't even need my
help
oh I got blessed by the algorithm let's
go
and I I said I wanted to sing it right
shouldn't I try to sing now I know I
should read some protects but maybe I
should try to sing it instead maybe
that's a better thing to do
[Music]
I don't think I ever tried singing the
whole thing on my own though
load the
thing already
[Music]
but I I have it I got it because I asked
for it
there it is
[Music]
I will this this is better than super
chats right
foreign
[Music]
oh my God
uh lyrics I should have just typed in
lyrics
my fault
[Music]
why didn't I do that
okay I'll type it in
[Music]
there it is
sorry the value of request it has been
deleted all right
Dance lyrics Google let's go
[Music]
I believe
that there is you know like all these
websites having our lyrics up this like
again it's like one of those moments
where you realize oh wow
are we kind of well known
damn
[Music]
for a good time but we like things
dance
[Music]
announcement
announcements
stand up got your stuff migrate onto the
floor give us your best clocking moves
we wanna see you so get ready
show you what we got yeah
dance
[Music]
yeah
I'm satisfied
sure
oh my god I've barely hydrated myself I
just noticed throughout the whole stream
I just drank one glass of water so far
it's been six hours homo
short perfect for looping
I guess so
mmm man
hydration Check Yes I checked myself
I have succeeded the hydrogen Jack like
a perception check
okay
so now that I tweeted out the thing
and I drank some water and I sang a song
Maybe now I should read the super chats
freaking can't here
um which ones
a little bit a little bit all right a
little bit um
um which ones though where do I start
um
Ohio
the ad games Okay thank you
okay here we go uh ad games thumbnail
I need the thumbnail oh thumbnails I
still gotta make the schedule too yeah
bye
if it isn't the consequences of my own
actions to be honest I wasn't planning
on playing so long but like
it's just like the game
it made me feel like I barely made
progress so I felt like I needed to play
longer also because it was fun and I
wanted to make more progress you know
wow
yeah
I was planning on finishing after like
four hours
well I only I I was able to hold myself
back to only play like five hours at
least
instead
hmm
I contemplated skipping dinner to keep
playing just the good thing is there's
so much dialogue you can kind of like
eat while playing the game a lot of the
time
now it's also played a lot after really
narissa are you listening are you never
listening
listening is she listening
she said she play for seven hours no
don't dot me
oh is this a cat that enters my room who
who dares to enter my room it's moving
my
phone
[Music]
oh I the last two nights I didn't use
the automated feeder
uh because I told you right that like
for two nights she wasn't eating it even
though I put it in there
uh like two portions now 190 only ate
one
but not even completely I think and then
the other night she ignored both
and I'm like hmm that's weird
I'm like why because she ate it for the
first couple times I don't I don't know
what it is maybe it is just the the
freshness or the lack thereof
[Music]
um
but yeah that one night she didn't even
like bother me about it like
you would think if she doesn't eat that
then she demands it from me separately
but
she didn't really
I don't know I just uh yeah
didn't use it one night and tonight yeah
the last two nights and
she didn't wake me up that early either
she just woke me up at like nine a
little bit and I ignored her then she
woke me up again at like 11.
yeah so
I'm currently back to the usual but it's
not so bad it's not so bad it's from The
Robots movie that would be ideal but I
get it I clean I clean it out I clean it
like every day after you know or before
I put in the new stuff
so that also the older ones that because
I don't use like all of them right I own
there's like a like six Chambers I think
and I only use two I only fill up two so
I could leave the other ones inside the
leftovers but I don't because it stinks
pretty badly
you know another microphone but I don't
know she was fine first maybe maybe it's
really like especially on the hot days
it doesn't keep the the food as fresh
and it was quite hot so
it might be that
[Music]
um
I really don't know
it's a mystery but it's not so bad right
now she's she's being
acceptable yeah
even for the night I thought yeah quite
hot
[Music]
now I bought it so I don't want to
I don't want to just give up on it but
um
I put cable on the field I don't need it
to be in the feeder though because I
have separate like
little
bowls for that and they just they eat
the cables whenever they want
[Music]
um
the little robot has been amazing the
only problem I have with the little
robot is the the plastic the wobbly
plastic guard thingy that chonkers likes
to destroy it's it's been destroyed
pretty much it's like ripped and but I
need to replace it
and I I you know I couldn't find where
to buy it and then somebody pointed out
to me a a place to buy it
for austrians too possibly and I can't
find it anymore so if you're listening
now please send it to me again
I need to buy the wobbly plastic yes
because chunkers destroyed it
and you guys are so good at finding
things hmm
thank you for the pinky wow my second
birthday in kfp is Saturday 19.
of August oh that was one day after you
sent it this is my first Super Chat I'm
now 34. I started working again and
wanted to treat you to a belated
birthday gift thank you a fancy meal or
a massage oh since I have definitely
gotten both of that I think into two
humble requests employee number and
while I picked job title
how the did you not get it until
now
I'll pick Jordan oh you don't like the
one you currently have Friar of Chaos
yeah I don't like that one that much
either
oh how about
Wawas
tissue
dispenser
for when I sneeze
isn't that an honor
okay
where are you you can't say no
are you here
I don't see you
but yeah uh wow dispenser and your
number
I haven't given out a number in a while
oh oh let me think let me see
there it is there it is it's um
yeah
oh my God it's midnight
it's midnight at this very moment
there's nothing
here right now at least except for this
this little small paper
I guess it sounds the same way okay
I checked because you guys are doubting
me here it says
it says 288 for a golden Umi yeah
I confirmed that are you happy now
I I'm I'm 100 certain no so
anyway Happy Belated Birthday
Freddy four oh my God my throat hurt oh
congratulations
and thanks for treating me but you must
also treat yourself yeah treat yourself
as I like to say and Parks and Rec
yourself every time I say like that I'm
referencing Parks and Rec do you guys
realize
yourself treat yourself
anybody who recognizes that yeah yeah
treat yourself
yeah
I love that I love that
I wasn't being hip with the kids no you
can treat yourself now to what to food
tweet yourself now
thank you for stopping here
ah thank you for two pinkies I used to
be SCA gang a weak one who couldn't stay
up so I'd go to sleep listening to your
voice instead now I'm in Germany yeah I
see you're donating in Euros for my new
job and I can finally watch your streams
properly with other kfp moving away from
everything I know didn't I read this
before
halfway close to the world is scary but
I'm grateful that I have you to look uh
forward to when I come back from work
thank you for continuing to be a Shining
Light in our lives and here's some of my
first paycheck as a tribute
did I just like roughly read it on
stream
right because I remember this
well well thank you once again for the
support I'm glad that now you should be
able to very much so watch my streams
more you guys should all do that if you
have struggles watching my streams live
you should just all move to Europe
it's that easy guys it's that easy come
on
where is your dedication
ah thank you sir I hope you're having a
good time in Germany I can imagine it
must be really scary also because you
probably don't really speak the language
yet but at least everybody speaks
English I would say mostly you will
survive but make sure to you know tackle
that German don't be scared of it and
make connections meet some people
and have fun during your time in Germany
maybe travel around Europe you can sit
down because you're at least perfect I
wonder where you picked that one up you
can also say avidazen
you should be able to say yeah and nine
and maybe
choose even
um
a couple of words yeah can greet people
with Kiki yeah totally no don't do it
don't do it that greeting only applies
here
that's not a real greeting in German
language it's just the noise of a
rooster let me tell you that
what did you just say
wise guy what are you saying did you
just join the stream and heard the
rumors
because if you saw the stream then you
knew that I didn't smash the ogre
I passed
yeah okay
I passed but it was
shocking
oh my God
I don't want to think about that anymore
that was funny though man
[Music]
Patsy that question Studio Rob once
again thanks with Pinky pinkies
you always said the same Super Chat
something new
take out words thanks for the rest of
the Chad hi attention today's my
birthday can I get a happy birthday from
you also did you know matches together
and release the Lord of the Rings said
recently I remember this too somehow it
has a new art for a lot of the
characters in case you are interested in
collecting some looking forward to the
hotel song
oh Magic the Gathering I
laughs
I requested prompts for that
I don't think I ever heard
yes I'm still waiting for a reply
[Music]
that was a long time ago though well
maybe I'll request it again I don't know
weird but yeah thank you for letting me
know once I get into it if it's like
still available then I wanna get the
Lord of the Rings set hell yeah let's go
[Music]
that would be so nice and happy
it's already a while ago sorry about
being late but I hope you celebrate with
yourself and had a great day and a great
year ahead and behind you and everywhere
around you next to you on the left on
the right take care of yourself
birthday kiss
it's okay I had fun with my family that
sounds good
that sounds decent
also hope you enjoyed the horror story
song Because here you say you looked
forward to it I hope it was
living up to your expectations
uh what are you guys talking about like
the the like real life cards are they
also available online like in the online
PC Magic the Gathering it was better
than expected let's go
let's go I'm happy to hear that yes
ah okay
okay
[Music]
yes I do want to play that I think when
it comes out the Super Mario RPG remake
I think so I think I was interested in
that right
um
so I can catch Pokemons I've been
working like 14 hours a day no yeah you
need to take more breaks
yes
uh right now thank you soon jailbird
Road Star ah donkey I saw you in narissa
chat
Taylor thank you and Hildegard thank you
I can't teach her something I don't know
foreign
[Music]
but I think I'll leave now because I'm
getting a little bit of a headache and
I'm really hungry I need to cook
like my forehead
the inside of my forehead what what
ah yeah it was six hours it was a nice
six hours comfy
um
I still need to make the schedule
I'll make it after I cook probably
hmm
uh yes
let her cook
I wonder you know I'm still kind of
behind on the recipes I have
um I don't want to cook I think I'm
cooking a like a risotto next Maybe
like usually
usually when I see risotto recipes
either on hello beep or outside of hello
beep it's always either a seafood
risotto or something with like shrimps
or whatever or it's a risotto with
mushrooms
but this one didn't seem to have
that or or I'm getting rid of the
mushrooms
may may be in there but the rest sounds
nice
why is why do why does everybody make
risotto the same way
why
can't they try something else
why is it gonna be mushrooms or shrimps
all the time huh
I don't get it yeah asparagus risotto
that's the good of hell yeah
I think I made that before
why don't you try something different
then well because I need hello beep
to show me recipes that I like I can't
put together my own recipes in a hello
beep that would be cool but they only
have always a certain selection and I
that's like the free recipes the minimum
of that those you know the minimum of my
order already pretty much covers me for
a whole week most of the time
um so I don't uh usually I don't cook
anything extra besides those things
um
yeah normally I don't I wanna uh I mean
I buy ingredients for like breakfast and
lunch you know
I don't care if we give you a QuickBook
but that's for the future
yeah right now I'm still focusing on
hello beep when I am done to graduate
from Hello beep
then I can mix all these recipes yeah
I'm not ready yet because it's very
convenient to just have the ingredients
be sent to me
the G word
okay
calm down
it was about hello
okay I'll go now okay chill calm down
calm down I'll stay with you for quite
some time
um
guys next week
calm down calm down calm down don't
shh
I have to go how's it going I have to go
I can't I need to oh my God I need to be
productive okay okay okay okay okay okay
all kfp make sure to visit all all
everything everything
next week you have to be there okay it's
an important time
I'm waiting for you to be there
okay
let's hype let's hype it up let's hype
it up
tell the others
to be there or I'll make you square
I'm in Conference next week well you
better be
watching the boards
okay okay don't mind if I do thank you
I'll be working but I'll watch the world
thank you I'll be there no matter what
thank you if it's not 5am again maybe I
don't know what wait what time zone are
you in I don't know
I can only be there involved that's okay
thank you
I'll be there thank you I'll be there
any time of course you will thank you
always there thank you what what you
then okay thank you oh me and we're
gonna start this week but I'll be there
anymore thank you
thank you thank you I'm so excited me
too
the thing that shall not be mentioned
until it's mentioned officially we are
all excited for it and we all have no
idea what it is no idea no idea don't
know what it is
tomorrow
[Music]
thank you
hello smoothie
[Music]
hi
he's talking to me you can't hear it
[Music]
she's doing a sniff stuff
foreign
[Music]