[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
assistant
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
no no no no
no no no no no no
no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
okay
hmm
[Music]
I took
oh I tried to take a nap so I got some
tired
[Music]
um
TV eyes on oh [\h__\h] hell
um no
okay is it really oh yeah it is wait I
can turn it off even now oh
okay it's off now
[Music]
uh
ah
do you hear this
[\h__\h] I want it to be louder
[Music]
I want it to be louder without being
louder in my ear I don't understand
I don't understand
okay I will fix it I know how to do this
qawwa you know how to do this
you know how to do it ah
[Music]
there we go
oh genius Chihuahua
oh oh
I'm tired
[Music]
look
can can this just tell its own story and
I just let it speak for itself
too tired
can you just imagine
he wants some context oh man
oh man
[Laughter]
oh
it's got a Time
yeah I took this photo today
yeah
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay
um starting from today
there's not only this but like other
whole life organized and this one is fan
organized
advertisements
going on in Tokyo
this one is on a famous
big spot that everybody knows
my least favorite place in Tokyo
[Music]
Shinjuku
oh I see your least favorite because
Shinjuku is like
it's it has this place this District
that's called kabukicho
you know is a lot of
like it's like nightlife District I
guess but
uh
it's just it can get a little bit like
spooky sometimes maybe for like girls
mostly
um
uh but like kabukita doesn't like for
sometimes you still have to go to
kabukicho even if you're not looking for
that kind of stuff because some things
just happen to be in kabukicho for some
reasons
um yeah like uh
Life concert houses or I think there's a
cinema as well and
I don't know I don't know some some good
restaurants are there too
and yeah it's
it's fine I guess
um but even outside of kabukicho
Shinjuku
which is always intimidates me
basically Shinjuku station is a dungeon
and not the good kind of dungeon
with what if what do you think I'm
trying to say
not the good kind of dungeon like the
Tales of Symphonia dungeons no no no no
with riddles and stuff no
no it's the worst because there's like
so many
uh train lines that pass through
Shinjuku
so
yeah changing can be
I got lost many times before
Daddy
foreign
and it's um
very close at the station depending like
from where you're coming from which
train line you're coming
so I know that some people eh this is
new art gonna be the new formula no
no I'll go back to the old one I just
didn't have it on the laptop
um but what was I saying
you got me out of my bubba
oh yeah lots of
lots of people who even are not going to
expose
right now
uh
who didn't get a ticket still when are
you going to Japan right now to check it
out I've heard that some of you came
feed
uh even trying to do the same things
that I did like going to enoshima for
the trip
yeah I guess part of my part of train
train line does not pass for Shinjuku
it's not supposed to pass through
Shinjuku
hostel
um
laughs
on
foreign
like two kfp went to enoshima today
taking the same pictures of enoshima
that I did and and they look the same
because it even rained uh in my trip and
their trip so
that's nice but apparently it rained way
more
um
on their uh day so I'm sorry about that
yeah but but I that is like really the
shittiest weather you could experience
when going to enoshima but
maybe you feel less bad about it because
you have pretty much the same experience
as me maybe that makes you feel better
about it
but they said it was like really really
tough strong wind
for us it wasn't that bad but the
pictures looked the same the pictures
looked the same
you got the same pictures please feel
good about it
yeah
uh
[Music]
so so well well so oh and then I I did
not I don't think the members knew about
this unless maybe the ones who are on
the special banners maybe they knew
about it but I think mostly the the
other ones didn't know
they announced today on Twitter I did
not know about this
that they would be having a huge
advertisement in Shibuya station
uh go on Twitter check it out but like
okay the zionica thing is already at a
famous spot okay and by the way thank
you for organizing it Paul and and uh
making this it's gonna be on there for a
while every hour at 54 minutes
um it's quite easy to find
and the other thing
let me see let me pull up like a
picture
there you go
I cannot believe I wonder how much it
costs to get this
look
this
is
like literally if I'm not wrong and I'm
pretty sure yeah because I've been here
like a while ago
this is
and
one of the most famous tourist spots
ever this is the entrance to Shibuya eki
that is right in front of Hachiko and
the huge Shibuya Crossing
you know that famous Crossing
soon
[Music]
cost this is not the only one so they
have like
similar ones
uh inside the station too apparently
[Music]
the inside just looks like every other
station so I'm not sure where exactly it
is but see this is really long so when
you walk
inside the station there will be
hundreds and thousands of people passing
by
I see myself on this one I'm at the top
[Music]
come on
how did you even get a picture of that
without people
and then there's more of these like
uh I think they literally chose the most
oh like
two popular Ians the most one popular
idea and the most couple of popular
Japanese members so
yeah yeah it's
Senpai and then there's one with swisse
and uh Senpai and kawaiiope and there's
one with Kobo
uh
and
ah what's this one with caught on the
Sound by and fubuki senpai
oh sure
there you go
it's so cool
they look so high quality like
damn
[Music]
so many people are gonna see this
I wonder for how long
probably not much
uh
longer
after
um the festival
today
wow this is this has like professional
ad vibes
what does it say uh on the left
um
foreign
okay so it says like
when you don't know what's gonna happen
in a new environment where you started
Living like when you just moved
somewhere
when you know nothing about this place
and oh yeah it's completely like
starting from zero
don't worry you'll be fine
because this voice that you hear
will be with you and all your negative
feelings
we'll just
fade away
yeah yeah so it has like
motivational or whatever and like
nice nice phrases
oh yeah oh yeah the big thumbs in the
middle says
you're new
you're this is is this a cult your new
everyday life is right here
next to you
oh
[Laughter]
it's a parasocial parasocial cult
no but these look really cool these oh
[\h__\h] I [\h__\h] my battery
yes
ah
now man thank you
[Music]
okay so these are cool if you happen to
be in Tokyo right now go and find these
check them out
they're so big this this one should be
the easiest to find because there is no
way that you're going to Tokyo and you
will not go to shibuya's main station
but I was thinking when whenever I
release oopsie
a new song
um I want one second I want
to
if you guys were able to afford it I
feel like maybe I could like
pay for my own
advertisement for when I have a new song
or or an EP or so out
[Music]
I want to buy an advertisement on on
Unica
because even before this was happening
the other day I walked around it I
walked by this thing
um and uh there was like a that was just
at that moment they were running like
some charts and it was like literally
all kpop
and you hear it even from pretty far
away
[Music]
so I really want
I really want
um
how much was it
Paul
how much did it cost
eh I don't think it's so efficient for
personal product
I want no I think it could work quite
well I I would I can see how if I would
have played like do you here
wasn't
oh
I expected why did I expect it to be a
bit less
seven thousand oh
should we raise funds for you
oh
[Music]
damn seven thousand for like a week no
even a bit more than a week right
because it's like from today until 19th
no that's a week I guess that's a week
yo
yo oh
maybe maybe we can make a fundraiser
because otherwise I would have to pay
all of that out of my pocket and I would
make probably
minus from my EP
[Laughter]
[Music]
maybe we can combine powers
yeah
thank you
I want
um to advertise my my my next
musical Thing properly
I feel like it would have been so cool
and and I feel like it would have been
quite fitting and effective if like this
would have been a thing for do you for
example with that super cool
MB no no not proof Super Chat no no no
but that's super cool MV
free DMV which means okay I will have to
make another super cool MV
[Music]
can we fundraise for more songs also
please
no mental jelly no not here
more songs
um I don't even
have like a plan of which songs
from which producers Etc I want
um but um we're still like in the face
of I don't know my budget yet
I don't know
I have not been told my budget but
um I have like I have
I have a demo I have a demo for a song
and I don't know how much it costs yet
but I really want it because I'm I think
that song has huge potential to be
I mean it's already amazing I love it
[Music]
I think that might be my like main
promotional song for
um
yeah
huge potential
[Music]
yeah
um eventually if I like for now I have
to focus on the original songs
but there's two this year there's two
two people I wanna have a cover with
maybe one of them is to watch Empire
because I agree I agree that it sounded
really good the contrast of the voices
just have to find the fitting song
[Music]
um but I would say that would be for the
second half of the year
um
thank you guys
um yeah I'm sorry that was kind of
scuffed but you know like
I had
uh
uh kind of a stressful very stressful
schedule last week
um you know even on those days where I
wasn't streaming
there was a lot going on
trying to squeeze in as many things as
possible in that week
yeah
and then before the Tula Senpai collab I
had two streams on the day before
and I cleaned my room and I would say it
wasn't a decent state but
towards if I made a comment
that she wants to clean my room
I think she's just a particularly
cleanly type I think she seems like it
uh
apparently my room wasn't clean enough
for her it's because there's like not
that much like space to put things away
so like the one other table besides the
uh
the PC table
um has a lot of my my [\h__\h] on it like my
my two makeup bags and
some a lot of like stuff so that table
is cluttered the floor is however like
clean and there's not like it's not like
the table has
a lot of empty bottles and cans and and
and
um some Bentyl leftovers here and there
no no no no
it's not that bad this is this this was
in a good State decent state
uh but yeah
do you live like this
[Music]
yeah well
so
I felt a bit embarrassed because told us
Empire was like yeah
[Music]
I'm money
Ma
huh
what a devilish action
what did gonna say about your room oh
nothing
I mean
there was really nothing to say
because it was recently cleaned up hmm
[Music]
and uh yeah
I wonder what kuba's room looks like
I've only entered her room on that uh
one day where
uh like she basically arrived
uh and I think I left on the same day so
at that point of course no it was like
in one of her first days not the day she
arrived but yeah in her first like two
three days and I entered and at that
point it was of course clean it was just
super freaking cold
hahaha
super super cold
I think she hasn't uh had figured out
the air conditioning yet at that point
when you helped her with the router
no that was I think that happened
through online
[Music]
I remember
um there was like something like that
but I think I was in Austria for the two
weeks
and we recorded uh that was the thing we
recorded uh an expo program and a thing
that you will see I think you can watch
it through YouTube too
I think it will be streamed for YouTube
yeah yeah we were trying to help good
out with her internet
[Music]
um
because like it wasn't working well
spy thing yes
yes
[Music]
did you not forgive you for the room
criticism I don't think so
no
ah okay so I will not tell you all my
attentions today but I can tell you the
one like my point of view
I can tell you that one if I still
remember damn I think I wrote it out let
me see
I feel like I've been losing my notes
how is that possible
okay I look through here and then look
for Nene
[Music]
maybe it's
I don't know
maybe here
why is there a note
ah
why is there a note that says in a
punching wall
ah
I know
I found some notes
she snap she's snapped that's it that
was that was the maximum she could
tolerate she Rich couldn't yeah she best
of all no no no no no no
um is that it's a note from a dance
lesson
she we had a dancers in a in a room that
has really
uh low ceilings
and Ina was you know
in in heels
and gracious
but no even I could reach Loki Reach the
the ceiling
and then yeah she during dancing she
would punch the the ceiling
[Music]
I would also yeah
touch it good I couldn't reach it
um
yeah we jumped really small jump and
then punch
she's Super Mario punched yeah
[Music]
where is the other one that I wanted to
tell though
um I guess I mean while I'm here
otherwise I'll forget this one probably
did I tell you
Italian girl maybe good all
I think gouda told this one
no yeah so I think I also told this one
the one where am I mixed everything in
her cocoa on her hot cocoa
wasn't happy with her cocoa yet she made
the Watson concoction and this is
my face was like
[Music]
you're ruining
you
she liked it though
but one more thing about gouda during
dance lessons that I forgot to say
during the dance lessons
she she told me
this but I I think I've also kind of
noticed
like generally I was just like always
staring
in a void in the mirror I didn't want to
make people feel awkward and look at
them but I also felt awkward to just
look myself in the eye the whole time
uh so I was just like I don't know look
at look at my feet or look at some
thing
like like
without focusing on it you know just
void stare
yeah I just I felt awkward like uh
looking at myself the whole time because
that would feel like I was like
like seducing myself
I didn't want to see myself the whole
time
so yeah I just I just she had dead
inside stare the whole time
but I've I've been noticing some looks
from other members to me because
uh sometimes the teacher would not dance
with us and just sit or like stand on
the side and watch us to see how
how well we remember without her guiding
us and of course then everybody looks to
me and gura especially she would like
follow me and when I would I was like so
under pressure
and then
when I would make a mistake
everybody makes a mistake gouda said
this too like good I would copy me and
then make mistakes because she was
copying me because I I I I didn't know
everything perfectly ever sometimes
uh
yeah
but Ina you know is a quick learner
I feel like
and me and you know there was a there's
a part
um
in non-fiction
which was always so fun
there's this part uh you may have seen
it in the Freddy group collab
um but because of the angle you don't
see it that way it looked it looked uh
it feels better
in real life but there's this part where
I think Cali is in the middle singing
and then me and Ina are on on the left
side and I'm in good on the right side
and then we
start
walking
outwards both teams on the outer sides
we start walking outwards and then we
reach our hands outwards and then we
start walking back to the middle and we
reach our hands again
and
uh we were just it just always felt like
me and Ina were so in sync like I could
really only see Ina because we were
um even when standing before walking we
were always like facing diagonally to
the outside
and so in the side of my eye I could
only really see Ina and then we would
start walking we were both always so in
sync it was just always the most fun
part
like take free steps reach take free
steps back and reach we would always
like walk this exact same distance and
in this exact same Rhythm and Temple it
just felt so good
we synced up so nicely
yeah
hmm
and I think on the other side I'm in
good or syncing up
uh but
like when comparing the two teams
[Music]
we eventually realized but I think it
was too late it was too deep in our
blood we eventually realized that we the
two sides have been doing things
slightly differently
just because like
uh I think Ami was saying
was saying it but they like just did
whatever the other person did
and then yeah so takutori was adjusting
to each other and then I'm in summer
were adjusting to each other and there
was like some slight differences in the
choreo
between the two teams hmm
yeah
eventually we noticed what I think it
was too late
um
I thought it was intentional
no no no no no no no no
[Music]
I'll talk about that and never time
thank you but wait ah the prank okay
before we start reading super chats but
once I start doing that I'll be going
through them
seriously
hopefully maybe even finish them today
um so let's just have another tangent
before that a prank I did not find the
notes but let me try my best to say my
point of view because apparently I
didn't yet
oh anyone
go because of panic disorder
you're going now good time
I am proud of you
good job title fighting
I think you know it's surely difficult
to like go back after you haven't gone
for a while but if you just keep it up
like this
then it will be normal and then you have
your Ribbon bag
you know then you can like bond with
friends again make friends again
yeah
you'll find your space
your place
again
so keep it up keep it up
education is important
and keeping you know a rhythm
in life every day
is important
hmm
okay fighter
so so so so so so uh
so
the energy part
was pre-recorded
I'm not gonna lie to you
due to scheduling it was pre-recorded
scheduling but also like I just uh you
know was way too nervous about making a
mistake
when dancing with someone together so
yeah pre-recorded and on the day of the
recording this was this was on the day
of the recording
um you know it was in my schedule so I
think Ina saw it in my schedule
um and she was like can I can I come to
um do my prank and I was like sure okay
she wanted to do it successfully one
time
[Music]
um
so
uh me and me and Nancy we were like you
know doing our recording and I think
this was after we were done we we had
our good take
foreign
which you know has like a table and all
that to chill there
and in it was janma and Inya and
we walk in it and I'm like you know just
out of like reflex I'm on the verge of
saying hyena and I go to High e
and then I stop myself because that's
the moment where I realize ah
ah so I said uh um
because I just wanted
like uh some Japanese selling name and
I guess for some reason it became money
that's their last name yeah yeah or like
something similar
yeah let's move yeah but she she didn't
catch it and then she didn't catch it
but and then I guess I just kind of
decided you know is playing uh with the
name of Modi now that's her name now
so we walk in we sit down but I ask you
know I'm I'm also fully into the bit you
know I
I try to be realistic here so I asked
nity is it okay for her if in this room
the managers join us
and I say this this is the new like
um assistant manager to my actual
manager Jen Ma and she was like yeah
that's okay she's very nice
and she was very nice so we sit down
and
you know uh we kind of like
start explaining
uh who who she is I guess
and uh yeah that she's new and then we
like
all of the Yen staff you know they live
in Japan and they all speak Japanese or
English and English fluently this and
then
um
yeah yeah
Assistant two then you measure wait wait
wait wait wait wait are you doing like a
little bit of the office
wait that was
oh oh oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah that
was a little bit an office joke right
I feel like they did it in Scrubs too
[Music]
I feel like there was something similar
in Scrubs where
um
JD and and
was her name
they had the same job
and then they had to like I know change
position
something like that and they weren't
happy with how it sounded like one of
them was higher than the other
I thought you were too no not me
Paula it's not Paula
anyway so yeah and then and then
Eva
oh yeah because I was like you know yeah
we we we're continuously hiring new
people so this is our new edition and
then Ina says that she is a fan of
energy
and I am being realistic here
that I worry
if if like someone new joins the company
and
has no chill and immediately like
confesses to someone
one of the talents that they're their
fan and especially because like Ina was
doing it in a very
like kind of unprofessional way
purposefully
Medina
yeah so I was like you know I don't know
I didn't say you know I was like
with this car
so
I was like kind of like getting upset
about it yeah cause like
I would be concerned about that too I
mean of course I was kind of like be
flattered but when it's like that I
would be concerned too like did this
person join with weird motives you know
okay but that was fine but then she then
she goes like
um
can I have a sign
was that the was that really the first
thing she did I guess no no handshaking
I think maybe first she did
she ask for handshake she may have asked
for a handshake
I don't remember anymore it's too long
ago
and I was like what
okay and I I'm like jenma jenma
can we really have this happening
we don't want to freak out ninety she
asks then for a sign on her
iPad with a permanent marker on on the
like cover of her iPad
and she not only a small one she asked
for like a huge one
so Nancy's like yeah yeah of course of
course you know really sweet and happy
the whole time I was like damn does she
really not mind because she was really
believing the whole thing
to hold back my love
but also trying to stay in character
like how it would really act if some
staff would like
become turn into a full-on fan Girling
person
hmm
so I'm like
are you for real now body son are you
for real
like this it can we can we really
forgive this janma janma
gemma's just like
quietly enjoying the whole experience
not really
saying much so I'm I'm left here to
try to control the situation
yes all of this in Japanese yeah
[Music]
sipping coffee eating popcorn
is
so then she moves on to sign the iPad
and then I look at I look at Ina I give
her this like
this look this expecting look like this
is a let's just say this is really
a new new joint new hired staff Ian
staff member yeah
now
she fan girls
be all over energy
while I'm also in this room asks her for
a signature and a handshake and
everything
and and she completely ignores me
right so I'm like I give her this look
[Music]
and she looks back at me and she's like
oh
[\h__\h] and she pushes over the iPad to
meet you and gives me the the pen too
so I then sign on her iPad too she now
has
and then she's saying their signature
and my signature her gen mate on it
laughs
I was like yo yo yo where odenzu okay
and I feel like it would be only
respectful if you don't completely
ignore the person you're actually
working for supposedly as an En staffer
ah
yeah so even though I'm a gen mate and
she surely did not need my signature on
her iPad
I signed my thing on there too even
though kind of reluctantly because
I'm really worried about making energy
feel creeped out
so and then after my signature I gave it
back
and then
ah she asks to have her name
added I guess
uh you know asked to have her name added
yeah and I'm like can you stop now like
can you stop
annoying the like the challenge right
now
like oh my God
this is enough but I didn't know that
she had to continue because this was the
way she needed to reveal it I didn't
know about that
but I'm like that
like this is this goes so far like
give her a break enough
yeah I was like getting really mad at
this newcomer you know
and then she signs it and she said and
then she's like oh oh like should I sign
like morisan and then Ina's like uh
[Music]
yeah just it was like one or two seconds
of silence and then she starts giggling
and then then she's like what
you know damn yeah
then it just genuinely didn't care but I
feel like it's just like realistic like
I think other members maybe would be
like more concerned
I don't think that it's a it's a very
like
um like normally this shouldn't happen
I don't think so it makes a talent or
some talents feel uncomfortable
if some new staff member especially a
new staff member goes full on Fanboy
fangirl mode
that is uh
concerning because you know you see
signs of the talent that
you know you don't see from the outside
like you see them in their free time and
you know
yeah
gotta keep it professional
yeah yeah but then it seems It's just
sweet
[Laughter]
and now
has another G sign which she probably
really appreciated and the sign for me
which she does not need at all
just because
you know
I forced it onto it
[Music]
you can sell that I put iPad cover for a
big price someday if she wants to
[Music]
um
it's a relic
is
[Music]
no way she needs her generate signature
and so big they're both so so big
[Music]
hey Auntie P what are you saying you say
you Spain energy that's gonna be worth a
lot hey you're completely leaving out
the fact that it was also signed by me
oh
[Music]
okay
oh
[Music]
just uh saw
some updates gotta read afterwards
[Laughter]
[Music]
my first and only orange merch so far
signed by Kiana
yeah I just you know
I just wanted to play it realistically
it was hard to hold back my Laughing Man
and I didn't think like Ina would go so
far and like play it for so long
damn that commitment
I thought you know there were some times
where
at that everything just seemed so
surreal
and I was like low-key not giggling but
definitely definitely a suspicious smile
was going on by me and jenma we were
both giving off suspicious smiles and it
was just too surreal I thought energy
kind of knew what was going on but
apparently she didn't
it just seemed
so surreal I think energy is just a
little bit naive
uh
yeah
too trusting man
anyway so what I did today is I went
to Shinjuku to check out the
the Unica Vision thing I wanted to do
something afterwards actually get
something done but
my I didn't charge my phone battery So
eventually I just hurried back and you
know I did have
some yummy
uh
they had a galette and a crepe
in like a
crap and garlic specialized French
restaurant
in Shinjuku
honey yummy
so I had like a Savory one and a sweet
one but I underestimated how big they
would be and how filling they would be
on the picture they didn't look that
filling
but they were quite filling
meme thingy like for a YouTube short
s
I love it
[Music]
I wanna I wanna
where's the transcript
push
or is it where is it
why does no one write down the
transcript huh
but how the [\h__\h] did that start anyway
gosh let me just mute this
I want I just want to say it once okay
this is not gonna be my YouTube short
but I just wanna
I just want to say it I need to I need
to get it out of my system
okay
today I wanted to eat a croissant
so I went to a place that sells
croissant croissant and I bought a song
and I returned home with the croissant
and then I ate
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
awesome
[Music]
oh
my boo I'm I'm
this is my current favorite thing
oh yeah I saw I saw the version that
Elena did
[Music]
[\h__\h]
what's up
awesome
[Music]
I wanna do a 12 hour croissant stream I
want to
do
[Music]
quantum
croissant
close
[Music]
up
croissant awesome
[Music]
thanks for the pinky
Jeff
I'm not sure
about that
but thank you
can I yeah can I say croissants
[Laughter]
I don't know what it is about that it's
so addicting
waffle
Castle
ah
being cheered up from my homesickness by
[Music]
e
faction
should I do it with someone else because
I really want to say
[Music]
I feel like with crony she has she has
the perfect voice for reading out um
the the other part
although it's unrealistic that she would
eat a croissant she would eat a sandwich
but
[Laughter]
you know every time
when I mentioned because I did meet her
when I mentioned sandwich to her which
wasn't many times I did like one time I
did a joke and I noticed how sick and
tired she is of it
so I I was like hmm But I wasn't the
only member like Cali would make a joke
like that to her too afterwards and then
crony would just again be like oh
[\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
it's like she had to hear it from
everybody at least once and then
and everybody then understood oh oh oh
she's really fed up with it
she brought it upon herself she signed
it well well well if it isn't the
consequences of her own actions cronini
croissant huh
muscle
today I ate a Subway sub
tle today
I wanted to eat a Subway Subway
so I went out to buy a Subway
[Music]
Subway and then I ate the subway
so cute
okay I need to stop please stop it
stop me
okay I can't
that's all
it's been an hour
Can't Stop
the spaghetti I'll tell you about
spaghetti another time
[Music]
thank you
sorry I'm worried about about General
which is okay she just has to do
something that is not in her job
description
so I said she should let someone else do
it
[Music]
yeah she takes on a lot of roles I know
you guys are probably so fed up by my
stupid question right now I'm so sorry I
just can't stop
[Music]
awesome
it's cute right what it's addicting
isn't it
[Music]
sorry that's too loud why is the robot
voice always so loud
the things I actually really love
croissants like so much
I love croissants
oh yeah that's yeah that's right I
remember now I wanted to recreate the
meme oh
like by filming like you know me getting
a croissant at San Marco Cafe
because I love
croissants from San Marco when it comes
to croissants in Japan
oh can you guys remind me to do that
tomorrow tomorrow
um remind me please
please write write tomorrow tweets to me
maybe around
11 A.M
thank you tell me to do croissant at
some Saint Mark Cafe
I mean I just want to like film some
scenes and then do a voiceover
can help me put myself into it like you
know like the Maldives video
short
[Music]
demon Fang yeah demon Fang and the other
thing I wanted to do I couldn't do
because
it was not
allowed
was not tolerated
during that time it's too late
but remind me whenever I get another
chance to
basically if I go to Japan in June
remind me to do it then
foreign
[Music]
I did
um
basically like she said it herself so I
guess I can say it but
one of the things I said when I met her
I noticed when she took off her mask
that she has this typical like Idol I I
called him I don't like teeth yayaba
because
uh I noticed like when I was like
supporting hello project
a lot of the girls for example also
Suzuki ID has this you know the one who
did the
um
[Music]
yeah cute fangs sometimes only on one
side some people have it on both sides
um Suzuki has those too and I think it
makes her look really cute
so
so a lot of Idols have this and don't
fix it because it's just kind of cute
it's actually like here I feel like
overseas maybe people would definitely
fix it because they don't see it as cute
but in Japan it's actually kind of seen
as cute
a snaggletooth kind of yeah I guess so
so I told her you know
she has she has so cute
and like generally like she was so cute
and small so I said yo you could 100 you
know
be an idol
she is
I was like yo you look like an idol
the combination of cuteness and
smallness and yayaba
so cute
oh this sweater is so hot what the [\h__\h]
yourself
foreign
thank you there is croissant
yeah yeah I feel like I feel it's a
trend in Japan however has changed
I might be wrong but I feel like in the
past 20 years more and more
um Japanese girls
who have that
have like nowadays the the girls who are
now in their
um teens
[Music]
I feel like more would just like thick
go and have them fixed
and I think it has to do with the media
with like Kpop becoming more popular too
and then K-pop yaiba is not a thing and
they all have perfect teeth
I think that just like you know the
beauty standards are kind of changing
hmm
he knows
[Music]
I just thought it was really sweet how
you know
such imperfections were really
appreciated back in the day
it's really nice
so I can now I mean
[Music]
you know
um
okay okay let's read super chats see
I've tangented it for an hour or so now
after I change my shirt once again
and then we will comment
comment Chapel
[Music]
imagine records no way
don't they sound like the original I
feel like I sound like there was not
absolutely nailed it
[Music]
does someone remember the number where I
stopped last time
oh
[Music]
817.
okay
thank you most proficient Crystal
croissant reading
yeah I haven't done an M video in a long
time right
maybe I should make one
I know I haven't just I just haven't
thought of it uh even though I could
have probably easily made one to fill a
day with it
maybe I'll make one this week
I will not be streaming tomorrow by the
way I'm meeting a friend
um
meeting alfredendo
[Music]
unfortunately she's not a question man
I wish she was a colossal
what which number was it again
[Music]
800 thank you 17.
foreign okay
817 did I read 817 I think I stopped
right before the red super chat huh
[Music]
okay come
on do I have to say goodbye to the
console now
in the croissant on my head can I at
least go to audio stock and find a new
bgm because this one's nice but I I I I
can't I can't
um
[Music]
how about I look up
maybe there's a bakery bgm
no
there's like Cafe in bgm I guess
foreign
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] loud
[Music]
oh that's so [\h__\h] loud
oh
[Music]
this says
happy Cafe music Latin jazz
oh there's something weird about it the
main sound I like
but those sounds
they sound kind of weird
waffle
oh wow
song
this is nice
this could be a little something it
could be a game be gym
of a village
yeah
oh my God I want to play jrpgs
I want to play a Zelda game
[Music]
I guess I liked this one
let's take it easy for now let's let's
listen to this one this one's good
foreign
French enough
it didn't say anything about being
French but I guess yeah I can see it I
can hear it
it's nice
relaxing
I wish I I want to say questions
but then it's not a proper super chair
reading
okay okay here comes the last
croissant
for a while if I can resist I I'll try
to just get it out there
okay
[Music]
okay okay
big nothing monster man
Chester
for the red super chat your timkins are
so proud of you thank you thank you for
an amazing career so far it's been a
blessing
I know what I want to do
just about that
I feel like this would it's just
genuinely something I should be doing
um when I do like really long Super Chat
readings
I'm gonna do a window capture one second
of the number
[Music]
oopsie what the [\h__\h] is that what did I
just move that on
um
just roughly though because
there you go
doesn't this help like insanely
huh
in case you really like you you have to
watch the archive to catch your reply to
your Super Chat
just go to hololizer
find the area that I'm on in that moment
okay
yes
I mean yeah you could just look up your
where your Super Chat was and the whole
wiser the number hmm
your Champions are so proud of you thank
you thank you for and um an amazing
career so far I've been blessed it's
been a blessing to be following you
since debut may your dreams come true
and new ones be born every day
thank you thank you soon I'm proud of
you chickens too you guys aren't proud
of me well I'm also proud of you guys
thank you thank you thank you thank you
for the support and for being there on
that important day big nothing monster
man I like your profile picture
nice chicken
you are
obviously proud to be a kfp because I
can see it in your profile picture thank
you
[Music]
thank you
for example chat
look at Rubble goal absolutely killing
it up there tension oh what was I doing
there
that was fever nine that must have been
family night
thank you thank you thank you thank you
I Wanna Dance favorite night in that
other environment that I told you about
the bigger one
because fever night has a lot of like
you know
wavy upper body movements and some hip
thrusts and stuff I mean I feel awkward
about the hip thrust anyway so I don't
mind if it doesn't show that well
yeah but I think oh come on
I think um
you know when uh you know Holo life
announced that they're gonna be having
the biggest
that's what they said right the biggest
3d motion capture
Studio
in Japan that's what they said right
saying we knew about this
being planned for a while
um
and I know that it's gonna be even
better than the one that I have been
like testing that out in the other day
so I know that we're gonna definitely
have some quality improvements there
I don't understand the whole stock thing
because I don't understand how that
works and how that makes a difference I
if it's like happening already anyway I
thought that you know with a big company
like this
and it was already happening
I was confused by that announcement but
yeah
no
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
um
yes yes so I'm looking forward to that
yeah
that was already the top of the top but
apparently or not
um
I do agree I guess I don't know I I
whatever question
[\h__\h]
[Music]
it was a while
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you
Red's full football
infinite heck
you know the word heck written like that
it kind of gives me you know those dog
video vibes
where people transcribe what the dogs
are saying totally 100 that's what
they're saying
yeah
can Susan
you're doing me a bamboozled
I love those kind of videos
but there's a dog
uh that I found the other day
that I really recommend because she's so
funny and her owner is so excited and
together they're like the Dream Team the
cutest like dog owner interactions I've
ever seen
the dog is called Nala and if you go on
YouTube they make a lot of shorts if you
go and look up Stomp
or stomping or Stomps Nala
you will find it
they do this cute thing where maybe
somebody knows where you know the guy he
has like a Golden Retriever and they're
really funny happy dogs right
but this dog is
exceptionally happy so the dog like they
got the guy would like spread his legs
so the dog would go underneath
and with his butt facing
uh
the other way than the owners but
and then they do the stomp then some
they do the nail Stomp The Stomp The
Stomp they do the normal stomp like he
he says it like this and while he does
that he like pets his dog goes um but
and then Nala do this Stomp The Storm
she do the numbers and there's so many
different storms that do it everywhere
this is like the ritual and sometimes
she has like really excited films she
stop she stopped
sometimes she does she does smaller
stamps but usually she does big thumbs
because she's always so happy
yeah it's so cute please watch it it's
so [\h__\h] cute I like I couldn't stop
watching it
yeah
it's so cute
she like literally she's twerking
I don't watch dog cats what the
[Music]
I feel like I'm impersonating the guy
perfectly he's so happy like he I don't
know he has so much love for his dog
it's so sweet to watch that
if you go through his videos he does
some non-stomping videos too
but like oh
he gets so much happiness from his dog
and his dog gets so much happiness from
him that's like damn
the happiest owner dog couple that I've
ever seen
it's so sweet
he like lets out this really happy
giggle that you rarely hear from a guy
but maybe you should hear it more often
because it was so pure
no
[Music]
love to see happy pet owners
y'all I wish I wish I was that right now
on YouTube yeah yeah check it out just
look up Nala storms
foreign
you guys should giggle more you guys
oh my dog doesn't sit there and think of
a way to get something out of me
[Music]
taking notes to giggle I don't giggle
like one song that's nice too
sensible giggle for me
I'm not cute enough to giggle it doesn't
have anything to do with that
if you feel like giggling giggle
cackle like a witch
I rarely giggle unfortunately why what's
holding you back
I'm extra dorky
what what makes you think that huh
muscle
I do more of a belly laugh or have it on
the giggle yeah but you know that's what
times for different Giggles or it laughs
there should be a time where you just
giggle
think when do you giggle I think it
would be like when you're
just
surprised with joy
sold like I don't know
I don't know watch that the owner and
you will understand how to giggle from
your heart
anyway thank you infinitech cute cute
profile picture
and ice bomb Dunkin sir 956 Captain
Thunderball dangashon Alex Hedges
donation for the pinky
it's amazing to see you finally have
your 3D debut your dancing was great for
your birthday quasel but this is just
another level I hope this is just the
first of many Freddie appearances
okay
I hope so too
um
I'm still not sure what's gonna happen
to my birthday
um
that was one thing that you know I was
kind of unhappy about the other day but
there's like
first it seemed like there's no hope but
maybe there still is so
uh I'm still hoping
um
that I can record it in Japan but
I
uh
well if it is recorded in Japan it will
most likely be an external
Studio the question is just
a question of cost and you know
it's just external studios are
unrealistically expensive that it would
never make sense
um
yeah are they cheaper than in Europe
oh yes but still unreasonable so that I
would lose money
so that's just stupid
yeah I know some other members have been
doing that recently
and yeah
I don't know how much I can talk about
it so I'm just not gonna but yeah we're
still figuring it out so
please hold on for a little croissant
thank you though Alex Hedges I'll do my
best to make more happen so please
be patient
thank you thank you for your sweet words
thank you soon
thank you for the rest of the chat
um
[Music]
Tana
katana
thank you
Elven first
thank you for the red super chat
oh wait I think I forgot the kiss for
hikoto
salamat at us
oh it's not the whole Super Chat in
Indonesian right
showcase yeah
yeah
and last we can see Kiana upgraded the
dumps I mean 3D model I always support
you and watch your stream and bond I
hope you can achieve your goalsis here
and always healthy long live kfp thank
you I appreciate the
the butt fan art some of it you know
thank you
people have been drawing me in that post
that's exactly what I wanted please more
and more and more and more and more
more
I should eat more croissant
so that the butt becomes bigger
no I I didn't mean it like that that I
only enjoy some of it I'm saying uh some
of the fan art has been
um but fan art
that should be more all of it should be
but fan art
icles
be careful what you wish for
yo I'm
I'm I
celebrate the butt so
bring it on baby
[Music]
say it with me
thank you thank you thank you
yeah Evan thank you
thank you soon Long Live Carefree indeed
I hope they live long
same goes for you
and thank you for watching the 3D
showcase I appreciate it thank you thank
you
you here too aren't you I saw you in the
tattoo
show yourself
[Music]
I saw you
why are you tired of my croissant [\h__\h]
oh there you are
those moves I can't Tanto is literally a
force of nature how is a humble chipkin
such as I supposed to be prepared
enough to be prepared
that was more than enough
man
please pull over no
I will continue to quattle
and thank you well maybe you know
we needed some time to
uh what's the word digested so no yes
are you over it now is it have you have
you fully
prepare Al bite it is
digest the closet
and sometimes now I feel like we're all
you know chill about it
everything is good now everything's
chill
what I have not digested yet is the
queen song I'm still blown away oh stop
thank you
now I'm flattered thank you so much
[Music]
have you changed your clock already or
maybe it did it automatically it
probably did it automatically
welcome to Summertime even though I'm
here it's still freaking cold over there
it's getting so warm here like I've been
going out without uh
without a jacket it's really warm here
summertime is next week in Europe though
when I Googled that said
hey you last uh that was us oh not
Europe yet they have different times
where they change it
oh
croissant
okay so next week is crossover time
ha ha ha
I see you
okay
no no I just uh checked I Googled
time change thingy
and yeah then it said that date so I was
like oh okay already
yes yes I can use it for any noun and
any verb
come on
I'm so sorry
thank you for the red super chat
laughs
I can function for the pinky just
stopping by while on my break to say
kiwam was so [\h__\h] cute anyways back
away so I can afford more Super chats
keep giving them more heart attacks from
cuteness and killer performances thank
you oh even in the middle of working
when are you working are you a console
Baker
um
or are you a croissant deliverer hmm
or a kumason designer or a croissant
eater or a croissant
shaper
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you today is
all about Quantum
[Laughter]
I I
must have eaten some funny beans
[Music]
I'm broken
okay okay okay okay okay okay
I can do it I can do this
DM details what a name
DM me the details yes that will be my
YouTube username
why thanks for the pinky with the
stunning performance uh performance yeah
potential big congrats on your Freddy W
thank you for your passion always warm
our hearts for two and a half years by
the way may I order attention handmade
burger please no
you can have a quaffle
um I think people need to appreciate
croissants
need more love
like for real I feel like you guys would
choose anything over croissant like what
has a cool song ever done to you you
maybe it's the problem that you guys
don't live in an area where there's a
really good damn good
you know French typical french butter
croissant
hmm
you need to surround yourself with
better questions
I don't know man I'm spiraling
[\h__\h] I need I need I really need like
this is getting weird it's getting
[\h__\h] weird
[Music]
wait
thank you
[Music]
awesome
right
[Laughter]
waffle
and croissant
[Music]
what what am I so fine what what
are you seeing watermelon bun he wasn't
in the chat right
I didn't see her in the chat why are you
thinking do I look like what am I stand
by to you
they look like horns
awesome
happy now I feel I feel
fulfilled
synonyms
open aside
okay
[Music]
happy
Princess Leia
she gets it
it's my new look now
of course
what if I go to my favorite
Cafe
and I go up to the counter and sit and I
say can I please have a
H I need to film their reaction
can I get a uh
[Music]
[Laughter]
they wouldn't I don't think they would
even understand
what a what excuse me what
what because you have to say Kuro Watson
otherwise I don't think they will
understand
okay [\h__\h] stop now
we're all getting sick of it except for
me but yeah I have to do it for the
greater good I have it in my hair now so
that should be enough
to cope
foreign
I want to finish your super chat today
so come on come on come on
[Music]
okay
thank you
for the pinky
congratulations
thank you for watching and for waiting
so long I appreciate it thank you for
supporting me please continue supporting
me
yes
thank you soon for your love
not too little thank you for the recipe
bread dog
foreign
perfectly balanced boob ah that was when
I was doing the balancing
um
yes yes
that was easy that was no challenge
balance challenge no challenge for me
I don't think you're here right now but
no worries you will find it in the
archive easily if you use the new
technique
yeah yeah yeah you own that
easy peas and lemon squeezing
for giving me a pass
thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
I wish you were here right now you would
enjoy the croissant I'm sure of it
um
John Nissan
foreign
[Music]
form is so good I can't watch this
enough cute cute you're dancing at some
point you sound lovely so proud of you
and so happy we finally have this moment
thank you I wish we could get more of
this like
I feel like you know times have changed
in whole life too just because there's
more members
back in the day
doing 3D streams wasn't only
for reserved for like anniversaries and
birthdays you could even do it like
every once in a while for a random [\h__\h]
and now and now it's even hard to do it
for your birthday or anniversary
like I can already tell you there is a
zero percent chance of me doing a solo
3D anniversary stream
that's not happening
I'm pushing for a group one but I don't
know
yeah
it's uh unfortunate because now now is
the time when we finally are able to
make use of it but then we're not
able to make use of it
yeah back when we joined it was still
like usable for a lot of things
and then we couldn't use it
now we could use it in theory
but we can't
well
that's how it is
praying for the group at least yeah I'm
really I'm trying to push really
generally
[Music]
it looks bad but I'm pushing
you know that's how the croissant
crumbles yes
get the others to push with you
what kind of
um I don't know we at least um set it
together out loud
um
to the staff in person but
now I continue to push
through Discord
um
no no I I wouldn't even say it's the
lack of uh
the studio space
it's just more of a lack of people who
can work on it I would say
[Music]
um
not so much the studio
[Music]
because that other there's been some
days where I just saw it empty and I'm
like oh man this is like such a waste I
wish I could just
do everything myself operated myself
turning it on and then you know make use
of this empty Studio
yeah anyway thank you you need to chat
you're the best
so cute thank you ah my European kfp
ah
I'm really glad you guys you know woke
up it's such a shitty time for me thank
you thank you
I appreciate it thank you sure and
regano
thank you for watching I hope it wasn't
too rough too
watch it
um thank you I didn't slap didn't sleep
ah I hope you slept afterwards and it
wasn't too rough afterwards
maybe eat a croissant
makes you feel better
I had so many alarms
then in Japan this morning oh nice oh
wow I think the first thing you should
do is eat a croissant
I already know what everybody's gonna
write in the after tweet
oh well I'm gonna ride in my after
tweets
crawling at my Facebook
no aren't you enjoying it
you should be enjoying the croissant
for me I'm wasting so much time I
thought if I could be done early I could
go get a
awesome no actually I just really want
um I wanted to eat katsule for dinner
let me check one thing
[Music]
don't you hate it when something shows
up on on Google Maps when you scroll
like when you scrolled out pretty far
but when you scroll a little bit in but
like not even like that much but you're
scrolling towards it it disappears
so stupid like what the [\h__\h]
yeah right
you're trying to look closer to like
where exactly it is but why does it only
show up when you zoomed out
and then you like completely lose it
even when you like directly on top of it
oh well okay
can we finish them in one hour do you
reckon
I think then I could still get a
croissant AKA akatsu
cute
does this place have croissant
uh
obviously
secret word for katsu right now
if you limit your tension no now now
it's just you know the music is making
me feel so chill which is a good thing
in general
wait wait wait wait
does this one have
this one doesn't maybe it doesn't have
Kung Fu
yeah it makes me want to play RPG game
too
if there's high quality croissant fruit
delivery at this time let me see
I just wanna like
eat it calmly afterwards and I don't
want to warm it up because if you warm
up a console AKA Katsu
um it's it just loses all the
crunchiness unless you warm it up in
like a proper oven
and I don't know how to turn on that
function in my microwave it supposedly
has that but I don't know
how about and look for Katsu
Katsuya my beloved
there's a katsu chain
in Japan that I really recommend just
because it's easy to find and they have
really good Cuts in it
poof okay
they closed early
for all your progress to reset at the
full face nah I don't think it will be
that bad
I don't think so like last year it was
just because it was the first
time ever for 3D
and and yeah
I don't think you guys
will go that crazy
maybe some you know nice words here or
there
well I will never reach this volume
[Music]
you're gonna have to help me with my
Korean homework if I get homework I
wonder if there will be homework
involved I mean probably not
because it is like a private thing
if I want homework maybe she didn't give
me homework but I think in general she
won't give me homework but
I will try my best to like study a
little bit at least in between the
lessons to like repeat
yeah yeah and I don't want to do maybe
once monthly Korean study stream
review what I've learned in that month
so let you guys know my my progress
yeah
hey
I really hope that I can pick it up well
three years since you moved to Europe
celebrating
you moved to Europe but you donate in
Korean one
why
sounds like a plan yay thank you for
being here right now too thank you I'm
Korean yeah but love wouldn't you like I
don't know
oh
I mean you do you hope you're enjoying
Europe and the croissants because you
know if you're in Europe croissants are
pretty good in general they don't need
to be from in France
I think we are pretty good in our
croissant game
that they are depends on the shop well
yeah but it's not hard to get a really
good question
thank you for the rest of the chat
and sing a dance and sing with your
Senpai is finally so today many congrats
thank you and those is so cute thank you
and you know
um it was a 3D showcase so I didn't want
to get like too many guests but I think
in the future for like birthday
um I will try to get more
guests
have like maybe two solo songs and the
rest uh like no no games in between just
focus on performing squeeze in as much
as I can
do some link not like uh two people like
Duets but like some bigger groups too if
possible
would be fun
hello yeah I've talked with her about it
too like
you know
maybe in the future we can dance
together
the games are fun I think so too
yeah but the trend with full life pretty
uh birthday anniversaries Etc has been
just like
100 percent
songs nowadays
every now and then there's like some
that do like some kind of entertainment
stuff too
but yeah everybody is like focusing on
doing like music in there
3D streams mostly
um
which I want to do too you know I I want
to use that opportunity that comes very
rarely
well besides that we play games all the
time on our streams so you know
eventually I mean it would be cool to do
something like you know
I don't know filming something outside
and then
making it into like a TV program kind of
style program
boom
[Music]
I don't think they have what I want
sorry still I looked I checked the
manual again no they don't have it [\h__\h]
the job
chickens you know
um
don't worry dakuma has been paid for you
know giving us
the rights to use the dacoma chicken
design actually
quite a long time ago
a long long time ago
they're so good
yeah fluffy fat chickens they're Canon
and they're official
oopsie
thank you
get that bread get that quaffle
oh that was a perfect course
you for the rest of the Chad saying cute
thank you thank you you're cute too I
love frogs Frog's cute
maybe not frog on croissant but frog in
quetzel how about that
question
[Music]
oh you see it
I forgot that you could see it so I
should switch tabs
thank you soon for the rest of it
love you Kiana
gonna get extra points with the teacher
when I flex those couple of words that I
know
there's like really some random words
that I just know like eggy baby
um
wait what else oppa
foreign
stuff like that
should be helpful
thank you Tony thank you
oh that oh 176 thank you for the words
congrats on the 3D showcase to my Aussie
your pretty looks awesome and gives you
the possibility to show your great
dancing skills fantastic show I'm really
excited for four Fest too thank you I'm
really motivated for you know improving
the way it's showcased and my own
dancing too for the future
yeah
thank you for watching and supporting
and yes for fast is happening so soon
I wonder if anyone's doing a watch along
of day one because uh uh no wait of day
two I mean because I know Bales is doing
uh day one uh watch long
I wonder if anyone plans a day two one
should I do one
I don't want to do one if like
one or two other members are already
doing a solo watch along it just feels
weird to have two free separate watch
alongs
I might ask in our chat
is only oh what day is Ollie
isn't she day two probably
was she on the same day as me
ah she does have the tickle thing yeah
only it's day one
oh
kind of both yeah well me too yeah
[Music]
I'll think about it I'm not sure if I
can do one but I'll think about it
otherwise you know we'll just do one
afterwards for day one only
together
and then maybe just uh the parts where I
perform on on deco
that one part we'll skip all the uh no
yeah but it's just in a wands
members are regular
I don't know
last time it was members right
at least the one I think I did a public
one for where I didn't perform and I did
the members only for where I did perform
ah I'll think about that one too I don't
know yet but yeah we're getting excited
oh my God it's this weekend is this week
and what the [\h__\h]
it's happening it's happening
thank you who's that
thank you guys 9 000.
thank you for the red super chat we
friend
Orange let's go oh this was when Iran's
was happening yeah
the second duet with a Japanese member
you know it was so fun to do with ninity
you know I was really looking forward to
practicing together
and to perform together sing together
I think I chose a great song like I wish
like if we would have had more time I
feel like I would have liked to also do
the full choreo but the full choreo is
like so hakushy
foreign
I kind of like wanted to do that one too
oh well
oh wow seems like you've done a bunch of
bonding this trip
yeah but overall like in this trip I
focused on bonding with the en members I
would say
I feel like I bonded the most with
good iron Cali hmm
yeah
I will miss gouda so much
you know I feel like something
opened a door has been opened
and
it's just really
just just things that
I don't know only are possible through
meeting IRL
but
last time when we met like last year
uh in America
I don't know I feel like
I don't know what what what it was
that it didn't happen back then that
happened this time like
I don't know
there was just a I don't know it's not
like we didn't get along at all but it
was just kind of different like this
time it felt so natural
maybe it's it was we had more time this
time and we had more like activities
where you can bond this time you know
like learning choreo together
yeah
and living no I guess we did that too in
America living in the same place but
still
we had way more time this time
and I was just like committed
to improving the bond with everybody
like that was kind of my
commitment this time I wanted to
really
do the best I could to also like I tried
I know I have like
um
a very open and direct personality and
maybe that doesn't fit everybody so I
try to also adjust
depending on who I was dealing with
I tried to adjust myself to what would
fit them best possibly
which took a lot of energy from me but
um
I just
I just really didn't want to feel
disliked or
you know I I really wanted to
get things to a point where
I wanted it to be
hard to say
it's hard to say I don't know what I'm
trying to say
but
yeah
but it made me feel you know kind of
regretful
in this one month
I've bonded so much
of like especially Google
where I felt like damn
we like
oh no we're getting along so well now
like besties
I wish I wish it like could have been
like this from the start
but it's just so difficult when you live
so far apart
this kind of stuff doesn't just happen
online
it's just not the same you can't like
connect with someone
so
truthfully
hmm
you have no idea Savage I was trying so
hard for the past two and a half years
I was trying so hard with everybody
it's not a problem of me not trying hard
enough
it's really just the distance it makes a
huge difference to
be there together in person
no there have also been times where I
didn't try you know I've been trying to
like mix it up
see what works best but the result
always when I didn't try was that
nothing would happen at all
when I wouldn't try and then nothing no
progress and I when I would try it and
it was like a weird progress
where you know I'm not sure like is is
this really like working I don't know
maybe
well
I'm not like
I'm really just putting the fault onto
the distance
again because I talked about this before
it just you know I I envy ID and Japan
members
for being able to do this from the start
born from the start meet whenever they
want
do Optical Labs hang out
help each other out
um
in person
so much more personal
it's all the snow
yeah yeah whole life English could be
literally anywhere
breakage on his doors yeah I would love
to break each other's doors
but honestly I'm just so happy
about you know
progress I mean I'm [\h__\h] homesick
but we were homesick together
and you know
I feel like our feelings were
closer to
be synced when we're in sync
we were feeling the same things
experiencing the same things
doing the same things
I think
um
I also like really felt more comfortable
around them in person too like I didn't
do
my makeup like
I only did it like twice
in a month but not for them hmm
and like also you know you know uh
how in America you know when we did like
the Pop-Tart stream for example when I
was sitting next to gouda during her
stream
um you know back then I feel like it was
still kind of awkward to stream together
as an off collab
but like
you know it would be awkward because
like
looking at each other and stuff like
that this could just come out awkward I
don't know but this time for example
when I did that stream of Buddha
or also the the cube stream with uh Cali
for example or the the watch along of
the Nintendo Direct with Inya and so on
all these things
like you know we would look at each
other a lot while doing it
I'm especially surprised to know how
comfortable gouda was with that
we were actually a lot of the silent
moments of the one to switch collab
um I guess they didn't really translate
well on stream because you guys don't
know what kind of looks we were giving
each other we were giving each other
like threatening looks
stuff like that
a lot of communicating through the eyes
through Expressions that you guys
couldn't even see
we would give each other a look and then
and then giggle
hmm
I think um the direction of where I was
looking was captured quite well
because when I would like look over
there I was looking at gouda hers wasn't
captured so well but yeah we were
staring at each other a lot I was
surprised because the game tells you to
look at each other for doing these games
I was surprised God I was feeling so
comfortable to do that you know
hmm
but this is so different like being able
to communicate with looks and
expressions and body language that you
can't give each other during collapse
online
when you're like you know miles apart
that's
like a completely different way of
communicating that we can't normally do
damn
[Music]
so that was really special it was
something different
times
foreign
[Music]
maybe because you guys have met several
times now so she's slowly getting
comfortable with your company
yes yes yes
I'm just I'm just so so happy
also gouda gives the best hugs
I didn't think so but Guru gives the
best hugs like we've been giving each
other really tight long hugs
makes me so happy
uh I love hugging her
[Music]
the end is near you now so
of this time together so
I've been
I guess kind of getting needy and very
clingy
I've been getting so clingy and good uh
totally
accepted damn
man I feel like I I
made a sister
I got a sister in her
[Music]
thank you
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no
I got tears in my eyes
[Music]
hmm
I'm just so happy that
we we are at this point now you know
the distance doesn't feel so
big anymore
[Music]
um
so I guess you know all the
time here definitely was worth it not
only for you know doing Freddie stuff
but also for
bonding like we have
never bonded before yeah
and I mean with everybody I bonded with
everybody but I just feel like I bought
it the most with Guna because there was
just always the biggest
emotional distance you know
to begin with
and we like
jumped over a million steps
and stairs
in this time
yum I'm happy
yum God can I stop
it's been a wild ride yeah
I'm looking forward to the future I'm
gonna invite Kura to girls talk next
I'm already thinking of ways of
doing more stuff with her so she's she
actually she told me she would love to
participate in girls talk a while ago
like you know already a while ago when
girl talk happened
hmm
yeah she wants to do girls talk
she will have girls talk we're doing
yeah
sorry I had a little titty
um emotional moment
it's coming to an end when you first all
met in Japan it didn't feel like it was
going to end at all
um
to end when you
understand that
but
hmm
let her cook
no I wanna bake a croissant
ah that sounded so good
[Music]
cattle I need katsu okay okay okay for
the sake of the katsu
and clumsy Heroes
what a pinky I hope you never get tired
of hearing that kfp is proud of you
because I'd like to remind you again of
that I've been following you for more
than two years now and you want to know
something you've never ever stopped
being amazing love you Keanu
no I love hearing that thank you I'm
happy if you guys are proud of me it
makes it worth to work so hard like
I really try my best to improve myself
even though it's difficult you know
certain things are just difficult
because
it's just you know you can't just
suddenly become a different person but
you guys are also just accepting me
as the kind of person I am
makes me so happy
you guys are in the sweetest I don't
deserve you guys it's so surreal it's so
surreal to have
so many
people
loving me
pointing me
thank you
thank you thank you
even when I'm
insane and saying so every second
you guys still love me
and keep up with my stupid stupid things
you know
oh man why are we so sappy right now
so savvy
I feel like you know nowadays it's not
so bad
but especially in the first year
you know I feel like it was just a trend
to dislike piwawa
so the people who chose to not dislike
me especially then
have a special place in my heart
you really do
[Music]
um
thank you
thank you for believing in me thank you
I hate myself right now
[Music]
thank you
for not you know jumping onto the trend
for going against it
I love you guys
man
glad I wasn't there in the beginning
people are mean to people who want to
work hard yeah I guess you can see it
like that too
hmm
you weren't my favorite from the day I
discovered whole life thank you I love
you
thank you
thank you chose to follow this door key
tell the bird thank you
here since the beginning of May thank
you
when did you get those ears killed ears
those are not ears
that's my new hair my twin tails
I guess now I really need to add anime
hairstyle you know that's shaped like a
quaffle
but I don't think it would even suit me
unless I have the whole outfit fit
something like that like Gothic Lolita
or or I know
but that's not really something that's
on my bucket list in terms of outfits
hmm
I wonder if you could make it work with
something else
just don't think Jet Plane again
I don't know when I'll eat it again
oh babe I love croissant
laughs
croissant version
oh song
I'm not singing Jet Plane not even near
a single jet plane in that one
it dampened the emotional impact that's
good because we need to get out of this
happiness
thank you Julia love you nude
[Music]
no motion cute
hope you're enjoying Japan don't go on
Crazy Taxi rides anymore all right
thank you for the pinky hope you're
happy I read one of your questions there
were so many questions sorry guys like
it was so difficult to you know do a
short
collab when I feel like I could have
talked forever and sung forever with to
listen bye
um really had to shorten it Tantra looks
so amazing and pretty had been looking
forward to your 3D for ages congrats
well thank you I I thought you know you
were only wanting to watch it bye
but you also watch Chihuahua thank you
that actually surprisingly more than
just one
person who loves koala and Tawas Empire
yeah yeah I'm surprised it's like an
interesting Oshi choice
look we're very different people because
we stream very different things
oh
it's interesting to see people's
combinations like Oshi combinations
like okay there's some people who just
support literally everybody so whatever
can't really see like an ongoing theme
there but when there's someone who has
like two or three or she's
and then one of them is me with somebody
else it's like oh sometimes I'm like oh
I get it this person has like you know
a taste that I can understand like I see
I see why you like these people because
I feel like there's common interests and
so on and then sometimes this is just
like completely different opposite
types of girls
foreign
Nanda
no no no no no no
sometimes you just like someone without
needing any reason yeah yeah yeah yeah I
know I know
Vesper trying to figure that out now
that's already so many that's like DDD
you're a DDD
um well
but
I see partially I see a theme in your
interests but
one or two stand out
free no that was five
that was five names
I feel like Ina and Zeta are like your
your calm soothing or she's and Kiana
are you oh she's dead like
are that you watch when you want to
watch something like
exciting and uh
just like brain brain yeah I don't know
that's just the impression I get from
her voice so it is not calm oh I don't
know her well
I don't know her well her voice is
calmed out though like really sweet
sweet kind of voice
I love her voice
calmly Furious all right hold on
okay I have to read someone
thumbs up fire down thank you for the
pinky even though it's gonna destroy my
wallet I had this in the super for the
performance of denji oh thank you thank
you we worked hard on that one even
though I feel like choreography wise you
know
I guess it wasn't like the most
difficult one the few parts that we did
dance were like difficult
but most of the time it was just vibing
but the focus was on the singing anyway
thank you for appreciating it
gotta go to work fight
don't bring me a croissant
when you come back
my French kfp
I didn't watch uh other more than you
but other girl is like one of my friends
and I will always be there for them
homo homo
and so you only watch me and a friend
he managed to run that move into the
ground in less than two hours
well
maybe in your point of view
I wanna run that Meme into my tummy
though
in my tummy
already that was my intention
don't worry this is the only stream
where that will be happening next stream
I probably I'm back to normal
TM Lena to get the word okay I will just
like literally
is she streaming right now
we're saying it
I just dm'd her
with
him what's up uh Temple Run thank you
for the pinky from Canada
for watching
please continue supporting kiwawa I
would be really happy about it thank you
hope you enjoyed it
logical Paradox target shoot for the
pinky oh there are a lot of big words in
here
absolutely marvelous simply Divine
utterly Exquisite superb a fantastic
amazing adorable wonderfully fun
Splendid excellent excellent awesome
these words describe everything I just
saw the choreography that the set design
the skits well worth the wait thank you
thank you
I'm glad you like it I I'm really as I
said before are you happy with the
outcome of my showcase
yeah thank you so much
I'm glad you like it I've been like
planning this since
like two years ago
yeah
still remember when I first
made like the the outline of what I want
to do
um
a classic Freddy showcase
thank you logical paradox
this crap creative thank you for the
rest
thank you
no Abby don't answer what the [\h__\h]
uh Korean says I was here and even if
it's 4am the excitement is keeping me
Wide Awake congratulations on your
official 3D showcase and the and the
debut of your fixed mom will thank you
along awaited Milestone was reached
today thank you for an amazing show love
you milosi thank you action
yeah it was definitely necessary to fix
the the shape of the butt
so glad that we got that ready in time
thank you for watching it at such an
ungodly terrible time
thank you thank you thank you it means a
lot to me that you were there thank you
I'll be back to European prime time
again soon please wait for me
every bit of the show I expected
hmm oh amazing music guests and all
around a great show it was worth the
wait and the years of unpaid labor to be
here for this
hey hey
the possibilities are well honestly kind
of terrifying if you keep unleashing
your 3D power on us don't worry I can't
I literally can't
[Laughter]
it will be kept for special occasions
if I'm lucky
so I think you'll be fine but I will try
my best to also continue unleashing my
2D power on you
thank you Typhon for supporting me for
such a long time
waiting for me
and working hard
to continue on the unpaid labor
let's not talk about it though
that's NDA stuff
thank you
count counting to construction for the
pinky we're sure we've sure waited a
long time for this one it's such a great
3D showcase loving the work you put into
the performances thank you thank you
I practice really hard for those man
man
that was it was difficult it was really
difficult
had to remember
like bring back into my memory all those
choreos
that I had
done before but long time ago
hmm
try to uh
improve myself but
yeah there's still room for improvement
that's for sure
but I hope
you enjoyed it
pretty close all memories
it's impressive how you managed to
remember so many careers oh it's not
that many
um
yeah it's not that many I guess
that's a lot all right all right
wasn't so bad thank you counting tickets
I'm glad you enjoyed it
yeah
hopefully more at some point please
continue supporting kiwawa to see more
yeah
Julio Hernandez
[Music]
for the pink Super Chat congrats on 3D
showcase to enjoy it was really a great
time thank you
I'm glad you enjoyed it thank you for
coming to see it
thank you my sweet Korean Bros for still
supporting me
thank you
[Music]
no words but you're still here that
means a lot to me thank you Tai Chi for
enduring
so many of my teases about you not
talking to me
it's okay you don't have to talk I guess
as long as you're here I'm happy
thank you thank you thank you thank you
sad ill show buggy oh in Japanese even
thank you for the pinky
data
same place
I've been really looking forward to this
and glad it's finally here congrats and
thanks good job on you Japanese y'all
if we need you in Japan right now
Kansai been cool yeah yeah I do also
have some
I say words I just can't get rid of
the good Japanese
good job you did your
your practice quite well
I wish I was in Japan hmm
I'm sure some kfb could use you
for translation help
maybe another time but yeah
yo that sounded really good thank you so
much for the sweet words
and appreciating my creativeness as well
no
thank you
as well
AK stf2 thank you sure
Jason Jason
thank you love you too
thank you soon
poor saying it
without feeling embarrassed about it
just say it how it is
share the love [\h__\h] Wawa let it out
let it out loud
let it be heard
and be proud
thank you Jason mwah cup episode oh my
God that is a huge red Super Chat thank
you
crowd doesn't begin to describe how I
feel congratulations again
oh my God thank you triple red Super
Chat you crazy
thank you my God
that is some huge support
Abu I deserve that thank you thank you
thank you thank you
you didn't have to way too much
wait wait wait wait wait too much thank
you
thank you
oh baby a triple wow what a chat wow wow
wow the Huawei mode is perfect I wish I
could raise my arms like that you
totally deserved it no
yeah thank you I'm glad I could make
something that you really enjoyed
thank you
no please
continue supporting kiwawa
your great kfp employee I'm proud to
have you too
thank you
mama
is it an L or an i or a one
one B Mayan Duncan or lb Mayan yes
[Music]
thank you
thank you moose
I appreciate your support thank you for
being here on that super super super
special day supporting me on my British
showcase mwah
be it fun thank you for the pinky get a
free birthday party sorry it's amazing
the song dance you nailed it absolutely
perfect even I
heart you mean love
it cut off there though Who Do You Love
is it me
must be me
thank you I'm glad you like the song
Choices and the dances I think it was
just
full 100 kiwawa
every kfp must have seen this
that is a stream that you just cannot
miss as a kfb
it's YouTube default they cut off my
Super Chat what
how dare they
well well I assumed you were trying to
say you love kiwawa I love you too thank
you
unenthusiastic
Maybelline thank you for the recipe chat
the Majesty the grace The Willpower the
heart tensioner true Phoenix true Idol
congratulations Kiara you deserve and
earned this moment kfp is proud of you
thanks for being you you're truly one of
a kind thank you Maybelline
oh
thank you for being one of the kfp
to be there for this moment
and believe in me thank you so much
[Music]
foreign
I'll continue doing my best
apparently I am graceful I didn't know
that
like a queen
kiwawa
bend your knee to Queen kiwawa lady
Chihuahua yeah
thank you Maybelline you're the best
what
like the legend of the phoenix like the
legend of the Phoenix
[Music]
keeps the planet spinning
we've come too far to give up Who We Are
so let's raise the bar thank you for the
pinky
[Music]
you thank you for being the inspiration
of fun at the very line that guide all
the kfb tour the bright future now the
next stage is for the eyelash but in the
3D Fest I will cheer you on always thank
you I really like the design of the 3D
adult outfit
yeah
I think you guys will like to see me
dancing in it
please come to see it it will be
marvelous
Majestic
cute beautiful
yes
it will be pure Idol
my tickets are ready noise
the incredible I agree
still hoping that I'll get a ticket
oh I hope you will I hope you will don't
give up
but don't you know
do anything stupid
I fly out in three days I'm so nervous
oh my God three days oh you're coming
like very last minute huh
are you ready
we have to prepare our bodies and our
minds for it thank you
broken man dancing
and we've reached a thousands by the way
thank you for the pinky quinoa my
Champion oh
your champion
thank you I made a champion of your
heart
cushion
[Music]
thank you sweet chicken
if I'm your champion
you're mine
you're fine you're my little
my little paw
s
oh
champ
[Laughter]
uh Nathan cotton thank you for the rest
of the chest it
thank you for a great stream danger I'm
sure you had a little Panic little
after you came back from Indo but I
luckily luckily our favorite chicken can
banish rooms and give us a great Freddy
with our favorite duck and wife singing
Duets looking forward to hologram the
rest of me Freddy thank you yeah all of
that was really great but
I don't think you could say I had a
little panic I had a huge Panic man
I was so scared I was so scared like on
the day before and even on the day like
a minute before the stream or until the
last second I was panicking I was
panicking and in between
I was also panicking doing the
transitions I was panicking the whole
time
I was panicking so much my bladder
definitely could not take it
I have a panic bladder
damn
you're panicking after
um
no
I was just really happy it was over
finally one thing
ticked off the list
the to-do list
anyway thank you Nathan
[Music]
hope you also enjoyed the rest you know
as you mentioned
and the mid Freddie
it was definitely a great time to be a
fan of myth mwah
also wait kenzoku are you also one of
those
Empire right
are you also one of those Nathan cotton
who like
Chihuahua and to assemba
damn wow wow
is there something similar in US
what is it what is it that connects us
because both were Idols good voices
towards Empire and two hours seems like
popular combo
hmm
both cute as [\h__\h] well
both hot as [\h__\h]
they're not like really good reasons
dorks hmm
doesn't really help me
good at singing ah thank you
has to be a reason you know well I don't
know I need I need there to be like you
know
statistics and uh and the
study a professional study to explain to
me
why
I like to
analyze these things
it's interesting yeah analytics yes
data graphs all of it all what research
is needed yes
research
and what was I thank you Nathan James
Jackson thank you
thank you I went for all the emotions
anticipation throughout the week worry
about your throat hell yeah relief when
you were okay anger when my phone died
and I missed
this same
what the [\h__\h] your phone is fired Joy
when I saw your amazing dance numbers
but what the [\h__\h] your phone is fired
like what the actual [\h__\h]
or should I fire you for not charging
your phone
I swear to God your phone had one job
one job
thank you though James Jackson I'm sure
you called up by now with the archive
thank you thank you for watching and for
the sweet words and for feeling with me
going through the same emotions with me
man
or at least a part of those emotions
oh
no thank you for the words of a chat
thank you
thank you for the inside this was like
around the end of the Stream
thank you thank you
mwah I cannot decipher decipher the
zipper decipher probably
but I feel like I agree I don't
understand but I agree I agree but I
also don't understand
yes
Ryan thank you for the Pinky and the
rest of the chat sorry thank you for
being you
oh wow you know that kind of fits
all the themes we've had today the
sappiness
thank you for you know liking me the way
I am for accepting me for supporting me
the way I am thank you
I'll fight to Prime
[Music]
you're in my heart
wait for example
absolutely loved your showcase your
dance moves killed it especially that
Lorenz was Perfection love your
performance and do you only downside
this new BlackRock shooter well come on
you know with how little of these
opportunities I get I can't repeat songs
that I've already done you know
maybe if I ever have like a graduation
concert or so
maybe then
oh my God I already hear them panicking
[Laughter]
[Music]
ah okay okay okay it never happens
I didn't say anything that's worse than
just
I'm so sorry I'm so sorry okay calm down
[Music]
hmm
quarter
are we good
[Music]
my God what did I do what did I do
but yeah sorry
um oh Halloween I'm trying
to chat slowly slowly
but surely my phone is losing it
anyway thank you so much Schneider for
watching it at such a shitty time and
yeah you must understand there cannot be
BlackRock shooter
you know but maybe someday
but yeah there's many other songs I want
to perform you know so many hello
project songs I want to do
so much I want to do
but I understand you know lack of
shooter is just Epic
we had that last year just watch my
archive from my birthday concert
thank you
I am
you are beautiful
it was so worth the wait you light up
the stage and you light up our lives
[Music]
sweet
it was so sappy as if you anticipated
today's mood
you guys Light Up My Life
I can't help it I mean neither
thank you we have a
Mutual feeling there thank you very much
thanks for supporting me
Lingus long thank you for the recipe
orange Hearts thank you thank you thank
you
next time feel free to add some more
words
you wonder why near super was red maybe
not yet I'm not sure but
um today I've been using you know the
numbers so you can go on whole laser to
find which number yours was
um
I didn't
for real
it just had 10 why did it die
oh come on
phone dead
you little [\h__\h]
I can't wait to get back to my enormous
streaming environment where this [\h__\h]
doesn't happen it's just like every
charger it's just too weak too [\h__\h]
weak
I just didn't catch up with charging I
don't know it was charged it was fully
charged but you know it just goes down
down down what I do now my phone is
fired y'all [\h__\h] my phone
bam
okay it restarted itself that at least
one thing it did properly but I will
like keep it like that I guess for now
so it can change a little bit higher
phone died of wholesome
you know my skin has been like so
[\h__\h] terrible these days these past
two months
I'm really happy I need I don't have to
take the stupid
pill every day
but the sacrifice man
I think once I'm back in Austria I'm
gonna go to the doctor and ask for it
again it's just so bad like holy [\h__\h]
I have the worst
hormonal acne
it's hormones man
I thought you know oh it shouldn't be so
bad but it's really bad
it's really bad
don't like it at all I feel like you
know really ugly because of it
confidence is kill
I was feeling pretty decent about my
skin while I was taking it you know
I guess I'll take it again I was just
too lazy to
keep on getting the the recipe because
you know every time when I get the
recipe she wants to check what's going
on downstairs and I don't like it
I don't want that
these ladies doctors always want to see
what's going on downstairs man
because they kind of have to they're
like not allowed to give the recipe
um
just like that
they have to do a checkup at least I
think uh once every half year
if you don't you need anything you could
just you know Skip it forever but if you
need something they will make you do it
prescription yeah it's a recipe in in
German
yeah I guess I'll go again
it's their job yeah it's so annoying
though
this is so annoying
also because it's cold
it's cold
laughs
okay no I won't share any more details
uh yeah Como likes to do the underwater
thing it's so funny ah
no it's so funny when she does that
[Music]
oh is that so they can't get it unless
they're really is that a thing
you cannot buy it in Pharmacy no no it's
you have to have a prescription
help
oh I'm under the water wow
what
uh
should I am
I guess I'm ordering or I'm going to
combini
late night company I guess so
[Music]
I'll just continue
let me check
how many has good food though
oh wait this one's
let me see
Katsu
um
[Music]
oh there are still
open ones
but I would say mostly
um
maybe like 11 11 P.M
wow
wow okay
for real
for real for real
okay
[Music]
uh let me check by the way what my
friend who wants to meet tomorrow is
saying ah baby booby Bobby
um
where should we go tomorrow
I asked her to suggest suggest something
because I'm too busy to think about it
but I'm not happy with the suggestions
how about this place
do I need reservations for this place
right now yeah
cute
foreign
[Music]
something
I can't get in Austria
all right all right maybe that works out
tomorrow
[Music]
guys I love you
I love you
love you
you and my cats
you have to share is that okay you have
to share my heart with my cats
is that okay can you share
I guess so
of course it's an honor
there's room a little bit
no choice thought we were on a lower
plane from them
to think we even have a chance with cats
yeah for real for real
even better deal
I can compare to cats
yes you can of course
will they be a schedule for this week
yeah did you not read the community
board thingy
Community post I wrote that uh no
schedule for now maybe one later later
in the week maybe
anyway but no stream tomorrow
how to read chickens can't read hey and
how come some of you are replying to me
though
well yeah okay
so I didn't get a notification you know
what I've noticed with YouTube and this
is so ironic so Community posts supposed
to be pretty good with the algorithm
right they show up quite nicely normally
especially poles but
the irony that when you post when you
share
a YouTube video or stream
as a community post
not some not a video from outside of
YouTube no ins within YouTube
it doesn't show it at all in your
subscription box it's it just gets
completely shadowed
that's why whenever I do that you can
see the difference in likes and then see
you know you can guess how many people
saw it I think the only people who see
it is the people who just go directly to
my community board and see it there
or people who hear from others
it just doesn't get shared to my
subscribers
because I'm sharing
a kind of a link
but it's within YouTube why does that
kill your algorithm
yeah it's so weird
well what yeah what the [\h__\h] you're
right I know I'm right I know check my
community board whenever I'm posting a
video when I'm sharing a video
the algorithm is kill
I'm trying to share it so that you know
some people
see like for example the 3D uh collab
was on the whole live English Channel so
I wanted kfp to know it's not on my
channel it's there please go and look
for everybody who doesn't use Twitter
but I already knew it wasn't gonna help
much because YouTube just doesn't share
these kind of things
so I would recommend
to check every once in a while unless
you don't have Twitter if you have
Twitter then I think mostly you will
always understand what's going on I've
been trying to help the non-twitter
people a bit by doing more on the
community board but it's just you know
it's just
smarter to get Twitter for you guys
if you want to stay on top of everything
[Music]
mama
foreign
taking a Twitter break right now so I
appreciate the community posts
YouTube mobile users if the notification
isn't on Twitter then nobody doesn't
exist
oh
great for comments but the notifications
are cred I miss stuff all the time yeah
so don't rely on the notifications
because you cannot rely on them
should we change bgm
guys
you feel like changing
man I feel so comfy right now
this bgm makes me feel so calm for you
I don't know if you guys feel sick of it
I wouldn't mind having something else
but it's also comfy equally comfy
[Music]
what should I look for maybe other PG
RPG
hey
waffle
[Music]
what's up
that's beautiful
oh man
why is RPG music so Godly
nothing can beat it
[Music]
okay this is it let's see how my phone
is doing
11 are you for real you were just at
like 10 percent
why are you not charging I had you like
I had it closed
[\h__\h] I'll use it anyway
I'll use you anyway
[Music]
yeah it's charging
[\h__\h] sake let me read a little bit
though
it's just it really depends on the cable
and how I'm charging it
stop the stupid
[Music]
where was I Lingus long oh yeah I
already read them on so let's keep
playing thank you for the recipe
I'm one very proud chicken right now
I've been a it's been a very bumpy road
but this has been so worth seeing it
happen for real so many laughs so many
sweet interactions you're shining out on
the stage it's so hard to look at you
it's hard to look in because I'm too
shiny now on to the fourth Fest we keep
going thank you
maybe I should have worn sunglasses that
should help next time maybe
have some sunglasses ready sunglasses
merch when
actually I guess sunglasses are not a
too bad idea because
usually they're pretty much one size
only
could make sunglasses merchandise
well there's other things I want to do
too so hmm
it's definitely a little thing that
could work but also I guess certain
types like shapes just don't fit certain
types of faces so that's the problem I
mean fitting as in like not
size wise but like style wise
[Music]
Santa Santa
oh you know what
Ina
the other day janma gave me Ina's
merchandise birthday merchandise
so that I would give it to her
um and I just kept on forgetting to give
it to her
just headed in my apartment the whole
time
eventually I finally gave it to her
but for some reason like we talked about
which kind of merch is useful and this
and that
talked about each other's merch
forgetting no for real though
and then I said like I really like uh
the idea of her
um laundry net thingy
because I I always feel like I should
get one I never use them but especially
for things like tights you know tights
are kind of like long and elastic so
when I put them together with other
things in the washing machine
they like wrap themselves around for
example a pair of jeans and a sweater
and they like
just entangle them they tangle
themselves
and it's just really stupid and annoying
and I think it just uh
doesn't help with the washing process
so I always feel like I should get these
it's like in Japan I feel like everybody
uses them not everybody but a lot of
people use them it's pretty common but
in Austria honestly I don't think many
people use it because I don't see it
being sold normally either
um
and yeah so I was you know saying oh I
really like the laundry thing you knew I
should get one myself and she said
[Music]
she said do you want it
I'm like
but it's yours it was it's supposed to
be for you and she said no it's okay I I
bought one
for myself because I knew I would
receive it pretty late if I relied on
waiting
for the company to send me mine
so
she gave me hers
finally I have a
a laundry net bag for my
delicates
I mean I would have just spotted that
like a Daiso because they have them
there too
would have just bought a couple pair
if I wouldn't have forgotten I would
have probably ended up forgetting anyway
[Music]
trying to think of the most practical
merge I've gotten must have been one of
mine
watched your clip video comes on
[Music]
it
hi sunny
is
a blanket your blanket is amazing
I can't wait to have a million cat hairs
on them by my cats they will love the
new blanket ah I'll be
you know chunkers doesn't
um need need
she doesn't really do kneading
um but smoothies this movie likes to
need you know what's so cute was the
movie
you know when she lies on my bed with me
when I'm watching like Netflix or
whatever
I know how to activate her knitting
like in certain positions when she's
like lying sideways
and she's in a good mood but sleeping
if I place like if the blanket is a
little bit Out Of Reach if I like move
it
and then put it like on on top of her
paws a little bit
then she will immediately start kneading
she's like oh thank you that's actually
exactly what I needed right now
and then she said
[Music]
like I literally cracked her
sometimes she's just she just happens to
lie close enough to the blanket and she
does it on her own but when she doesn't
often I just like move it over and then
she starts kneading
exactly what you needed
purpose
ah
I can't wait to see her need the
blanking
ah man [\h__\h] I don't want to think about
it makes me sad I miss her so much
I miss my cotton so much
um I wonder if they miss me
I'm so clingy you know and they're used
to it
oh yeah my brother sent me a photo today
of them chilling
um this movie was chilling on the
ironing board which is still you know
open
standing there in my office and my
brother has been using
um my PC on like a different account
[Music]
so chances was like sleeping on the
sides table which I connected to my um
PC table
taking up all the space
and smoothie was sleeping on the ironing
board
swing swing or until he didn't put it
away nah he just leaves everything the
way it is
also I forgot to cancel my hello fresh
order for last week so
he got a free
filling I was like I'll I'll just eat it
and then I forgot to cancel it again
so this week again
surviving
on Tuesday tomorrow
oh yeah I definitely cooked it he will
not let that opportunity in
be wasted free food free food that's all
let him cook yeah I'm letting him cook
oh man I love you guys
I love you guys me
you guys I love you
mean
man
quavo
[Music]
Mommy you're so titty means
[Laughter]
oh parasocial no
wholesome
um
not good at English I'm sorry that I'm
not good at chatting no problem
worry
[Music]
cuazo
why are you so sweet why are you so
sweet
no you
you pull over race card
king of cards did you see in a new Vice
Schwartz
[Music]
uh cards huh
the one with the hookah art is really
cool
that's a sick
design
it's signed too yeah but like printed
if you're playing right tracks go get it
and if you don't play wine slots it
might still be nice to have it
can you is it like I wonder
I wonder if it's easy to like can you
like order order it from
the white spots website or how does that
work
I hope the shipping is not stupidly
expensive
[Music]
hello to Brazil
hello
[Music]
they're selling bags
those cards are a game yes what of
course
[Music]
I hope it's easy to get even overseas
seen them on Amazon
my local card shop sells packs pre-order
the Japanese box in an English language
box
getting a box with Expo too
well hopefully they'll have mine in it
must be gym right
love RPG bgm
[Music]
ah
I had no idea they made with cards they
announced him like today
you
yeah
[Music]
um
you guys want to see
did I retweet it I feel like I did not
retweet it let me see
how do I find it
how do I find it guys
Maybe
advice
[Music]
it's not on their Twitter
is it on the whole live Twitter
[Music]
okay
oh cute
oh that's a cute fan art wait wait
[Music]
ah it's on the Japanese restaurant
oh wait there's like Anya card too
oh cute
I guess
they're like doing maybe ideas
announcing one by one
I look
video jump scare sorry for me too
come on
please go Get It Go Get It Go Get It oh
and the left one this one doesn't show
it but it's supposed to have a signature
I guess maybe some of them have a
signature I don't know I don't really
understand
sometimes they have a signature maybe
it's like a rare special
really SSS
the left one is super special
Castle
they're really rare oh I wonder how many
they
oh
I wonder how many there are
nice
[Music]
oh yeah Callie's like illustration one
is sideways
it's also interesting
she's not part of the system
okay [\h__\h] I should probably read some
super chats I'm just so chill right now
and what was I am
so let's keep it thank you
[Music]
spectacular Showcase from beginning to
end Chihuahua as expected from Burgers
to Idol dancing
love the doll always nice to see the
hard work and efforts of someone I
admire pay off congrats on your 3D
showcase tangel proud to call you my
camera thank you yeah I tried to like
put in basically everything I mean I
didn't have like a really
sick fighting scene like Cali
I guess that would have been nice in
hindsight
but you know in terms of background
I decided to go for you know the fast
food theme because I've just been
putting so much
into that
it's difficult to put like some to
create a really cool fighting scene
maybe another time
maybe me and Callie can have a
a battle Showdown someday
that would be cool
let's keep that idea for no time
but recreate
in 3D that battle
where she cuts off supposedly my arm
do you fight a sci fighter man
sounds tough but thank you
I'm happy I'm here
please let me continue be that for you
please wow
thank you for watching until then thanks
for the pinky thanks for an amazing
showcase Angel it made my heart go Doki
Doki mine too you look stunning your
moves are mesmerizing and your content
is always so fun and exceptional love
you thank you you're the best bag you
thank you thank you thank you I'm glad
you enjoyed it
thank you so much for your support
Anton m
[Music]
thanks for being there
I love you too
now that hard Sipes are actually bad
weapons oh oh it seems to be a
common
opinion
damn I guess they just look badass but
they're difficult to really
do something effective with
and on Japanese people
the gardening tools well yeah well
[Music]
why have they been
you know try why did people try to
transfer it into a weapon is that only
like within fantasy
I guess it was never really used as a
weapon in real life
only like in fantasy looking games and
so on
[Music]
definitely looks cool
peasant battalions did that
um
I guess when you have nothing else you
know to protect yourself why not Martin
hey thanks for the words of a Chad it
finally happened the legendary 3DW
congrats Sanjay it was great it's been a
very long wait but we finally got orange
and pretty yeah
and just like way back then the original
Hollywood film yes by the way it was
right there was no cheese on there but
right
like for real
[Music]
man
that was like mind manipulation
they were manipulating me all along
[Music]
for like really like they made me stack
something that was literally unstackable
foreign
like for real for the for the turkey leg
slash chicken legs
um I was using you know empty
Maracas that's what you call them right
so it was actually round and for the
patties and all the other things I was
using you know like something that was
just you know Square
so I couldn't even properly I didn't I
thought it was just you know a
decoration because in like the rehearsal
uh there was an example but the example
did not involve the shakasaka
yeah it had real objects yeah
they put like tracking markers all over
them
and I had to uh you know calibrate every
little thing I had to hold it
in several positions
[Music]
calibrated during rehearsal and then
also before the real stream
yeah yeah yeah I could actually hold it
the chicken also
um
[Music]
the broom tool I was holding a broom as
well
what is the castle on your head because
for the sword I was holding a sword yes
was Jimmy real yeah
yeah Jimmy is real love Jimmy
I love how Jimmy is now like it's like
the default name for when we talk about
a chicken now
ever since I did that one drawing
that's when it started
anyway yeah I'm often so we can
definitely say that it wasn't quite fair
but I'm okay with losing because for me
that had a comedic effect
and honestly like I wouldn't say my
memory in general is that bad but when
put in a situation like this
where I'm under pressure then yes
I can not remember at all
thank you Martin
[Music]
socks Junior dancing
congrats on the 3D showcase the real
Phoenix power is full released all the
show and guest was awesome love kfb
background and cute transition thank you
Wawa I'm so proud of you my Oshi thank
you
yeah I think they did a good job
recreating the
um restaurant
I feel like
um
maybe there's still some things that
would have liked to be added but in
general
I think they did a good job it's real
okay if he's real now
it felt authentic yeah
just wish you could have seen the back
well I guess you did in the transition
and the one where I was like you know
dancing
[Music]
should have focus on the onion rings
know which salad is which yeah I didn't
tell I focused on the on the cheese kind
of no no I didn't like I was just like
you know salad in that moment and then
afterwards I realized wait there's two
kind of two but the other one is more of
a cheese than a salad
[Music]
uh I don't know about using the
environment as I said last time and I do
agree it's kind of a waste but
it won't be implemented in our
application so at least that's the
current like
system they just don't do it I don't
know what the reason is
I feel like you don't even have to make
it available to everybody you know like
those certain backgrounds like the the
the beach
and the photo studio Etc like some some
of them are available to all of us but
how about you just make each person's
individual background available to that
person's account
that would be fine like in case the
problem is that it's too much data you
know
what if it's just like one the one that
you own because like you put work into
creating it don't you want us to use it
I might ask about it
hmm
I would like to use it
it's good
[Music]
yeah it really feels like a waste
otherwise
hmm
created from for one stream and never
used again what the hell
[Music]
no well oh well anyway thank you Nini
diesel
Nina you're going are you going to
uh four fast I feel like you are I feel
like I
heard you are
so enjoy
please
for the sake
of all the kfp who can't go
please scream at the top of your lungs
and you know I think like even with you
know a guy the chant guide it will be
very difficult to
get it across to thousands and thousands
of people who are going to be in the
actual venue audience
so I don't expect
people to like follow a guide
properly yeah it's okay you know it's
not the concert is not only about me so
it's impossible to get everyone to know
how to chant but I do
want to support it
um
just uploaded the call guide oh okay
I will retweet it
[Music]
and I'm still planning on making a
little video
before Fest
chanting aloud in the venue this year I
think yes
[Music]
returns yeah no I don't know maybe just
me
might just be me
because I think I won't do it in VR I
think I'll just do it in home 3D
[Music]
thank you
and Maxwell the first action hlg
dinosaur image sticky thanks for the
pinky
and long last we can officially say
congrats on your free DW potential it
has been quite a journey up to this
glorious moment and all and the weight
was worth it Viva La Canada thank you
it's crazy that it even took
like a year even since third Fest
you know after fruit Festival was like
oh maybe soon TM
now that we showed it off once hopefully
soon TM
then they said oh you can use it for
whatever you want now even though you
haven't already debuted yet and I was
like well
I mean it's not like I really have the
means and materials to do it though to
use it
so thanks I guess
at first you know I was still holding
back I didn't want to because I was
hoping that the 3G debut would would
happen earlier
maybe in summer or so
it's like still hopeful and and I wanted
it to be like not too messed up but I
didn't want to show my 3D model too much
before the actual 3D showcase but
you know
woke up so it took so long to get to you
yeah and even with that it would have
been [\h__\h] there's no way I could have
done the Showcase in that suit
yeah the whole birthday live thing that
was
just connected with so much sweat and
struggles
and being sick like oh man technical
problems a [\h__\h] ton of them it was rough
it was so rough
Emma said though that nowadays you know
things go smoother in terms of like
motion capture at her place
she says it's smoother now it's been a
quality
so I believe that you know back then it
was like the first time we set it up
we had just set it up
and still trying to figure it all out
[Music]
why do I always get sick right before
these important things man what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
hmm
I mean no I didn't get the sea thing
from stress
that is just unlucky
next time I have something important
coming up I will quarantine myself three
weeks before I will not meet anyone
three weeks before whatever happens
I will not go outside I will close my
curtains
and live in a dark room for three weeks
I will only eat things that come from
conservendos and
pickled stuff whatever
everything in the in the pantry
[Music]
hermit quinoa
no no Uber Eats no no I will not even
open the door
no
[Music]
yes apocalypse mood
for the like button no
hello fresh will be canceled
[Music]
thing will be received from outside the
quarantine boundaries
oh
[Music]
wake up
much
I feel like we can finish you super
chats I'm like chilling let's go yeah
thank you but no words why why why
thank you
so sweet of you thank you for the
support
action really big appreciated
thank you hope you're gonna continue
supporting kiwawa
sea bass thank you for the red super
chat
um
congrats on the Freddy quinoa so glad to
finally see all your hard work and
action thank you I'm glad you guys could
see it I'm glad I could show you finally
no I also want to like reward you guys
and show you guys something different
every once in a while you know of course
I will thank you
hi
hey you're here to pick up your fresh
Super Chat order
anyway thank you see Bass
I hope I can continue
giving things back to you as you guys
give to me thank you thank you
[Music]
Ronaldo shoes
we're back to 10 percent
but hey was it 11 so it lost one percent
really slowly
[Music]
um
what's that
now
um
[Music]
foreign
thank you thank you thank you for
watching it means a lot to me thank you
[Music]
dominique.com
one second
[Music]
and wonderful Freddy showcase it was
clear that you worked very hard for it
thank you for everything you are doing
you always brighten my day
well I'm glad I can brighten someone's
day really it's nice to have that effect
on someone thank you very much
I'm glad
I hope your days continue to be the
brightest every day
thank you whenever you feel like it's a
rainy day just come here and watch me
you're always welcome
myself again
thank you for the pinky congrats on your
pretty W koala thank you for being there
for it
thank you soon I hope you enjoyed it it
was a special occasion doesn't happen so
often so feel free to re-watch it
soon fried squirrel thank you for the
red super chat I love the prettiest so
much quinoa seriously you have so much
chemistry of subordininity and the dance
moves oh my God I waited so much to see
you dancing Freddie again kiwawa you are
the best thank you
yeah I just I'm happy to have some
special friends
in her life
cool you know treat me
like a friend
it's nice
I hope we can do more things together
there's so many members but
and I want to be friends with all of
them and that's kind of impossible to
like keep up a a proper friendship with
all of them
but I want to cherish the ones I have
thank you fried screw for watching
I'm known thank you for the recipe chat
too
congratulations on the 3D debut okay
Wawa I'm so happy
uh what I'm so happy it finally happened
you seriously are so incredible you
truly are amazing my ushi there's no one
else that is amazing as you are you are
the best YouTuber streamer Idol ever
thank you unknown you're always so
[Music]
so much for supporting
thank you soon I don't know how to say
thank you soon anymore
there's just so much wholesomeness thank
you for being such a sweet supportive
chicken all I could ever ask for thank
you
[Music]
soon thank you for the pinky in the end
it was a Christmas miracle that you
recovered as fast as you did
well I guess yeah because you know
Christmas apparently was in in February
according to me
I guess that's not so far off make sure
to rest after this as well so you can
finally tell that Dennis story which
totally didn't reveal that Nanny would
be there
[Music]
oh I did tell another story
I did I did
[Music]
how did you know
you looked into the future
[Music]
totally didn't reveal it at all but
honestly like I don't know I don't I
don't care you know that one time when
she I think she tweeted you know dance
lesson today and I'm like uh oh that's
weird I I I was uh I was doing that too
today or something like that
totally knowingly
to be fair Ina hinted it before you did
yeah just by like her saying that you
know
[Music]
and Kiana met in studio okay
I see
that explains or like spoilers at all
but you know I don't really
I mean certain things
where management says keep secrets okay
but these fails you know where I have
the judgment
I don't really mind
being honest with you guys and like not
hiding everything from you guys it's I
don't think it's always necessary
yeah I think it was pretty predictable
just by judging or like thinking about
who are Ki what was closest friends in
real life who would she get as a guest
I wouldn't miss out on that opportunity
the moment I saw that ID had guests in
their showcases
I was like all right all right okay okay
okay okay okay okay
I want guests too because before that my
plan was still with Outcast so I didn't
really realize
um I think a lot of us just planned
without guests first because we didn't
know and then ID all had guests I think
it wasn't
too common before that I think mostly
for the showcases
were
am am I wrong I think mostly they didn't
have
many or any guests
[Music]
I think so according to my memory oh my
phone died again
um
yeah ID even had themselves as guests
which I found interesting because like
for for example the Cali thing
the stages were like floating ghosts
it didn't seem like an option to have
them there in proper 3D so I guess
that's just like a branch thing where ID
is more
like open to doing that like whatever
I don't know I don't know I don't know
why
because like for
for Cali for example you know Ina was
there but like you know already debuted
at that point so if you think about it
you could have already shown Ina and
Freddie
but then she would have also had to you
know wear the whole like for the motion
capture suit Etc everything and set up
everything
and then you have to like calibrate her
too and Cali already had other guests
who also had to be on standby in the
suit and everything yeah like I said
like just uh
uh makes everything especially if it's
live like Cali's was live then
it makes everything a lot more
complicated if it was pre-recorded you
press done that
totally
hmm
I'm stuck let's keep it like that for a
while I guess podcast Style
the debuts I have seen didn't have
guests right
I feel like oh
I don't think it was ever prohibited but
hmm
[Music]
now it's your store I guess
you know we want to guess because I
guess we don't have many opportunities
to do this stuff and to begin with so
hmm
yeah just Collins yeah and the passive
was just called and it's like trying to
get them to do poses
um
[Music]
I mean they didn't ask me to have guests
I just said I wanted to it's not like
they said okay okay can you guys tell us
who who you want no it wasn't completely
up to us
[Music]
what's up
I've just read that quantum
[Music]
Hustle
waffle
quack
Le
[Music]
looks
I found my
I found my soul mate
[Music]
puzzle
this will come up and looks like puzzle
[Music]
she replied again I have to stop the
chain
[Music]
Council
foreign
[Music]
wow
so far
[Music]
glass
ES
[Music]
are we back
I was just chilling
I know I'm so comfy
I'm so confident right now
[Music]
hello
let me finish your super chance on
we went back into croissant wing and
then we sent each other console remote
[Music]
okay well once I by the way
ah here and I've ever read this one so
now this one maybe repeat condition for
the recipe chat so proud of you you've
probably talked about it already before
seeing this but just in case what do you
think of that yes I did of the studio
motion tracking for fast dance routine
like Sparks
anyway you killed it with your
performances congratulations thank you
I think like the
camera work
kind of
was able to hide
some of the things I felt was lacking
but then again also it was also hiding
some things I would have liked to show
more
uh you know like there's they like to do
a lot of close-ups but I like to show
off my choreography
so
um like for example for the the good
thing about pre-recording it and why I
like it too much and will probably
continue to have things more
pre-recorded is because for example for
the energy one
um you know
they sent me a preview
of the camera work
and I was able to change angles
so I said for example for the dance
break it was on a close-up and I was
like can you please change that to like
a full body angle where you can see both
of us dancing in sync and they changed
it
yeah
so stuff like that
can be changed and other times when
maybe I did a mistake I can hide it
by changing the angle
and that way I can also ensure that you
know it's a better viewing experience
because if it's live so many things can
go wrong
especially in an environment where
everything's so technical well when you
have to rely on everything going well
there it's just I feel like there's so
much more than can go wrong then
for a real performer like a real human
performer on the stage
so better viewing
um I think I'm happy with sacrificing a
better viewing experience
uh the other way around
sacrificing the life thing for better
viewing experience but I still want to
like mix in some life parts of course
and yeah we'll just act as if it's a
life throughout the whole thing
[Laughter]
I think you know there's so many upsides
so many
there's only good things about
pre-recording it in my opinion
I know it's not tracking I know it's
dead
it's [\h__\h] dead
Pro sad way the cons exactly
I mean I don't even I don't even know
what con there would be
[Music]
for something like that
or if it's a stream on YouTube you know
if it's a stream on YouTube like what
the hell
if it's like an actual venue concert
ideally it should be live it should be
live so that you can interact with the
audience
and feel it
and then you know whatever mistakes are
fine because it's it's a concert for
[\h__\h] sake
I don't mind like mistakes for a concert
like a real concert you know
[Music]
making a difference here hmm
imperfections can be good exactly that's
what I also keep on telling the myth
members
um when it comes to dancing
[Music]
you know
I say you know I feel like it really
shows personality and like there hasn't
it doesn't have to be perfect you know
this this is cute it's [\h__\h] cute
[Music]
yeah
character shows also that you you know
you tried
your best
[Music]
I desire more Perfection for myself
though because well dancing is
supposedly my thing
yeah
okay continue
[Music]
where was I
did I read this one
ah no I didn't okay Merry Christmas
thank you I still went into the topic
nonetheless
[Music]
I waited so much for this day I'm so
happy at the very beginning my idea was
to send my first Super Chat at the 3DW
well things went in an unexpected way
thank you for this amazing party you
made it happen my beloved thank you you
would have had to wait very very very
long
but you know
thank you so much for the generous
support
yay thanks to you I can do this properly
take back what I said in that Super Chat
what do you mean no Oh no you're not
serious are you you still love your
ocean right
[Music]
oh
come on
[Music]
okay yay
didn't seem like a very
happy okay you know
[Music]
why I have hyper chat on why is it dead
I still see it moving in obs
you the cuazos I'm sorry what
what
does that mean
let me write it again what
yeah I overdid the questions I'm sorry
you're sorry
I overdid no
[Music]
um do you really think that
is there really an overdoing
[Music]
I I couldn't stop myself
it helped me with my depression
[Music]
okay
well now you make me feel
bad about it
I was just having fun
[Music]
you're joking well you better be you're
gonna make me cry
[Music]
okay
get out I won't stop
Jim Tracy Duncan Love Tonight
[Music]
thank you
sorry wrong line you were incredible
transitions were funny thank you I know
right
man
I need to remind them to send me the
transitions
should
[Music]
it was so cute I'm such a genius
double demon Fang
no but for real I had so many ideas man
so many ideas
I want to do more wanna do more in
Friday me
you know the one where I was like lying
down on the table
was so exhausting though
because
um
[Music]
oh
oh it it was really difficult I was like
physically
in a really difficult position
it I don't know man
there was like kind of an imaginary
table that was I was hovering over more
or less
and
what was I sitting on
it was just like kind of weird because
of the height difference between the
imaginary table and the
the the thing I was sitting on the the
the the the yeah
and I was leaning forward a lot
man and stayed like that for a while
until they said cartoon
[Music]
no I was I was um kind of downwards
actually I don't know I was kind of
leaning downwards
I don't know what was going on there
[Music]
but I was low-key watching like how it
would look on the screen
I was adjusting to it
good exercise for the legs I don't know
I don't think so
anyway thank you for enjoying the
transition yes I've been in the call
thank you
Islamic fellow thank you for the red
super chat that was the vine marvelous
and amazing you rock the stage songs and
chorus were pure Phoenix fire I hope our
around the Simpkins who were present
there cheered for you as much as we did
here you were here too I saw you you
were one of them all of you were one of
them you were there
my beloved Jenkins
so round
as round as they get
[Music]
beloved timkins
where we yes we were yes
don't guess like me
I know you were there I know
you were raining from the sky falling
down onto the ground and you were you
were you were with your flop you fluff
caught you gently
she right though I know I was right I
know
I know I know okay Wawa always right
[Music]
and then you got swallowed by the Earth
yeah yeah we were like on the ground
vibing
thank you static fellow also I you were
also a European gang so thank you
for being there at such a terrible time
I appreciate it very much
Super Snake Mario dancing induction I'm
thank you
that was 10 out of 10 amazing great job
10 so you're probably dying while
reading this oh no it actually looks so
doing so well I've never done so well at
the end of such a long Super Chat
ringing
I feel so good
I feel so
titty
so keep up the good work you nail the
attention oh thank you so much for
always trying your hardest and giving us
an amazing show thank you for having the
patience to support someone like me
ma'am
no
you guys every single one of you
has a spot in my heart
next to my katos as I said
you can cuddle up with them just be
careful they might when you sleep they
might take a little yum yum
from you
I like your
I like your whale thinking Jake Edge
monkey
[Music]
your cat already does that anyway really
are you sure you don't you have a house
cat sounds more like a wild cat
[Music]
we have to cuddles move Arena and chunky
monkey
I guess
but I also get to cuddle them so we're
cuddling together
okay what will we do for the other 397
super stream pods well I mean maybe not
from this stream but I will continue
reading super chats in the future so
action
celebrity thank you
wait let me read some of this Ito sun
says I'm so happy it went all great in
the end this was amazing for you show
because you really worked really hard
and those moves were amazing and also
some were the cool friends and guest
names for your hard work thank you
so stupid says God I want to say more
than I ever could in a super chat about
how much you want to know so I guess
oh I guess I'm gonna expect a letter
from you thank you
thank you
Renato guimara says knowing what you've
been through these two years is really
heartwarming and it's hard not to tear
up
you cannot be my OC huh but I'm crazy
happy for you because you really deserve
it a true Idol
what do you mean I cannot
why why can I not be why is it
impossible what is that what
okay
why is it impossible
I like this guy
because I already have one but I love
you anyways oh is that
[Music]
the planet Earth it was Sun but Sun
wasn't Sun as a dangle
Santa's oshimark wasn't it a dangle
oh it's okay though like at least you're
watching thank you though
it's all good
Osama was a planet why did I think it
was a dongle
okay
it was a turn oh
for some reason you know for me Sana
I guess I thought because of her hair I
thought it was Dango
[Music]
so I guess eh you you're uh you're a
Santa light
holding on to it that's sweet
not swinging yes oh
well thank you for supporting me too and
being here thank you soon
it's all good you know
and you don't have to like or see me
that's okay
I'm glad you're still supporting me
nonetheless
thanks for being here
[Music]
Brandon thanks for the pinky worth the
wait would attend 3D showcase again 10
out of 10.
I don't think there will be another
but other kind of fruity things
looking forward to them already let's
not give up hope let's believe
let's
you know
do our best working towards it
I will do my best I will push
push
[Music]
I thought I was watching a clip no it's
live
thank you thank you Brandon Wow Wow for
the 10 of the 10. I need the
full
what what's the maximum you can get on
Yelp
it's on Google it's five stars right
what's it on Yelp
I don't use Yelp so I don't know
um
no idea nobody uses Yelp
is it 10 under 10
whatever I just want the maximum then
10 out of 10.
why doesn't any no one uses Yelp
[Music]
wow
yeah
meets
[Music]
help
Yelp needs help
they blackmail restaurants what
my God no way
[Music]
cry for Yelp
[Laughter]
[Music]
girls didn't thank you for the rights of
a Chad the wait was long but it was
amazing you proved once again why you
want my ooshy
entertaining an amazing my heartfelt
gratitude at you putting so much work
into the stream and giving us friends
yeah you've promised to be on stage but
it was perfect
one of you
that's all I'll say I was very wholesome
thank you
and last but not least sir 956
best 3D showcase I've witnessed glad you
were the first [\h__\h] about I got to
watch debuting a 3D stream so-called
being amazing keeping amazing whiskey
well thank you
done holy macaroni
I finished it I mean I could have
finished it ages ago
awesome
I reached the end
wow wow wow wow
foreign that took a while
[Music]
but I did it comfortably
yeah thank you guys for all the support
in super chats
I'm really appreciate it
let's wrap it up yeah it's like getting
close to midnight I'm gonna
order some food now I think
and then tomorrow I'll meet a friend
and yeah no stream
onboard
[Music]
this weekend something really exciting
is happening
so
we have to get mentally ready for it
guys whatever it takes dude
thanks for attention today thank you for
listening to piwawa
[Music]
is
I'm gonna try to finish the super jump
before first yeah I did do you mean like
the others well the others shouldn't be
too tough
I did the biggest mountain now
thank you for the croissants thank you
foreign
[Music]
Ty messaged me
like two days ago and I was so happy
about it
because like out of nowhere like we we
don't really you know ever since I moved
out
more and more you know we kind of like
you know
lost communication but you know it's not
like we're not friends anymore so
um but
she reached out to me
when she was like Chihuahua when do you
have time I want us to hang out again I
miss you and I'm like huh
I
[Music]
I rarely ever hear that from somebody
from Friends
like no one ever says that to me
it was very rare that someone
goes out of the way
to ask me
to do something and messages me from
them
from their side so it felt like so
special to me you know
that meant so much to me it's nice to be
like for once
contacted and not always be the one you
know
and and it kind of reassured me you know
that
she wants me as a friend that that's
what it meant to me
like
if it's always you reaching out then how
do you know that that person really
enjoys your company you know
that that person honestly wants to be
with you
and it's not just like accepting your
invites because it would be
disrespectful or rude to not accepted
so I was like so happy
and he we immediately like I I replied I
was like oh my God
I'll be back in Austria soon
ah so let's meet and then she even is
open to going on a little small vacation
again together
um
not a full week maybe just half a week
somewhere in Europe you know like like
we did the grease thing I think the
Greek Greece thing was a week I think
hmm
but she wants to do like a small one
and I'm totally up for it
yeah just a short short one within
Europe you know we can just quickly go
somewhere
and come back
she's
like
my one
Austrian friend who doesn't have
financial problems so
it's uh you know
quite nice to have someone who who can
you know go somewhere with me
without me having to
necessarily
pay for it or or we go stay in an Airbnb
that's like really shitty
um
it's just nice it's nice
also it's not only that but like my
other my best friend she just doesn't
have time she's so busy she like gives
herself so many tasks
[Music]
she just has so many things to do
I feel so bad for her like girl give
yourself a [\h__\h] break
she's been doing that for like forever
[Music]
well you know
her boyfriend tells her the same thing
RBF
we like
we have the same thoughts about her
boyfriend and me we both always sounds
you are taking on too many tasks
should take a break
you are too stressed out
wait I thought Aria was BBFS
RBF is my best friend's boyfriend yes
you hang with a lot of Workaholics
um
do what
it's just Kelly and her no
Kelly and my best friend
[Music]
I guess I can think of one more
workaholic friend that I have
[Music]
it's RBF single well no obviously not
Gemma well yeah I mean it's not like I'm
hanging
with her as a friend she's just you know
work so of course you know
but I do see Grandma
like kind of as a friend
you know
I'm very close with her she's a sweet I
love her
yeah I feel like even like one day if
this ever ends I feel like I will still
want to be in contact with her for sure
[Music]
I wouldn't wanna
like
you know
lose contact
in my life
I wonder if she's listening
I don't think so
I think she's like on her way home
from work
if you don't need them if you need
someone to push a button no no I have
RBF for that too
but yeah
[Music]
on my way home this late at night yep
yep
poor General man
[Music]
glad to have lots of button pushes in
your lap even my cats
turns off my pc accidentally even she
could push a button she doesn't even
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
man when your cat is more capable than
you are
okay well since I just roasted myself to
death
I shall now vanish in shame
so thank you everybody for watching
on short notice and thanks for the Super
Chat to always big support
such a special occasion thank you so
much
I will see you hopefully soon
and but please be a little bit patient
okay
[Music]
and I would say after four Fest
finally everything will be back to
normal so thank you for your patience
really
I am so excited for that
[Music]
I you know all this very exciting
and there were many fun memories
a lot of them but I just wanted to be
over now
Metroid Prime let's go yeah
um
can't wait for sports Fest yo yo yo it's
forfeits not Sports Fest
don't make me do Sports now
I am not into that
[Music]
it was nice having streams at a good
time for a little while yeah you'll be
back to suffering soon
I'm sorry
sea viewers
the CD with my cover of Ghost rule is
apparently coming out with uh before the
Fest so
you guys should be able to listen to it
beforehand
nice
[Music]
in two days apparently
I get mine Wednesday oh
yeah go through
[Music]
yeah okay so thank you so much sorry for
the croissant and in German we say Alf
[Music]
read us in
cuantosine
[Music]
bye-bye
thank you
[Music]
bye bye
thank you
[Music]
foreign