borei and I want to kill
you tonight Lads we
go let's
[Music]
party
I'm you know what here's a little C free
style if you want to fight me get
wrecked you kidding me I'm pretty good
like Grim Reaper what do you expect this
about sounded cool I would say so I'm
inclined to agree this is my line of
work this what everyone wants to see
bird cute K them time to redo the fight
this is called being a Pro Gamer I won't
die right try
aiming I want to cry you off he's right
though
[Music]
die hands weapons of mass destruction
half HP in a dream boys this Fest me and
my natural essons I'm a workaholic by
Hobby I'm cooking I need to teach you a
lesson say less howdy this is the
westboy sheriff's the best I'm going to
get a B jump ESS anything to achieve
that dream let's go Al korei heart
palpitations on stream
just let it end just let it end my
friend plays the recorder better hey
your
[Music]
friend hey guys two quick
questions number one what the am I
looking
at number
two are you
ready
go that's aori
fing me the ball that's a Mori yes
that's a Mori check this
[Music]
out yeah baby that's what I'm talking
[Applause]
about hey everyone I'm Kio pami and I
want to kill
you tonight l
[Music]
it is finally
time it's finally time to slay some gosh
some gosh dang gosh darn diddly diddly
dooo zombies are you
ready I think everybody might already be
in the game do you know this game is
kind of like rust oh my
God
already no freaking
way get in my
party hold
up Ally everyone Ally everyone that was
much quicker than
expected be friends everyone be friends
with
[Music]
me hi um I'm not in the Discord yet but
I'm very happy to see
you whoa is that a
gun who is this chiseled lad can you
hear me no I can't hear
you but you guys could hear my sniffle
can you hear
us oh I can hear the twins are you guys
around here we're in the party chat I
think
now hello oh you scared us so bad we're
using party chat right now we're
probably going to use Discord pretty
soon let's add each other I am
with unfortunate what do you mean
unfortunately I'm beautiful what are you
talking you're
my nice beard okay you wish you could
throw an
amazing
behind he you excellent let us head in
the direction of the
survivors okay let's do it okay hold on
let me see wow you
buff yes I know I've been working out
let's let us
fly the zombie apocalypse huh yeah I
guess so oh yeah come to bble to
bble you look pretty buff yourself
everybody looks buff I'm
sure looking good well I mean you have
to be a certain level of buff in order
to survive the zomb apocalypse I think
is true although this is too buff like
you would want more fat but maybe they
can't because they don't find food would
make sense makes sense to me
hello
hello nice everybody's everybody's
joining that's huge overturn trailer
whoa hold up hold
up we probably shouldn't loot this
probably there will be plenty of tra
have to find you guys or am I going to
spawn have to
us so come to B and for
Mo well we'll meet where we're
at all right looks like everybody's
Gathering I can't tell where the middle
is go to bi boo
we're meeting at the bi booo meet at the
Rock get it cuz it's be's The Rock get
it oh hold up that looks disgusting
where the chat is
horrific there we go I fixed
it where CeCe let's punch the tree
together okay yeah maybe we shouldn't go
up this rock
okay yeah beep this
tree yeah take the anger out
hold they're already punching trees
already punching trees I see that's good
where we're Gathering resources while
you guys try to arrive also did you
punch
me what are you doing M for map
a the Tre I thought we got all bloody
from punching the
tree oh boy
the party's already
begun oh boy CeCe can you swim CeCe can
we
swim you know if we can swim
CeCe that stern look says it all yeah
sorry my my mic was yes you're good
let's
go I tried changing Pusher talk and it
didn't work work that's okay it just
doesn't seem to work no like voice
activation I think it's just push to
talk yeah no no I me I tried changing my
key I didn't realize you guys were in
voice chat already actually we're using
uh the party chat but we'll probably
move to Discord
afterward yeah okay oh I see minutes to
die did you
die yeah I died like 7 Minutes in
ironically
that's hilarious oh hello
everyone hello oh you're also big
Mano
strong lady wow you have makeup on how
do you have
makeup wow you hello also
a hello dear sir hello sir nice
beard we said we weren't going to RP but
this is kind of fun from to you also
very clean and nicely shaven head I
wonder how much time that takes you
every
day no I'm just naturally bald I don't
have ha it see that the voice has a long
delay a long delay maybe of the Ping
maybe maybe we sh hop in a
Discord let go to Discord okay let's go
to
Discord what the
hell sorry this is not a joke so sorry
now the zombie will take you hold
up I didn't know I could actually punch
you okay I think we're moving to Discord
voice chat hello
hello oh I think we're good
yay this is much better not having to
press the the V button I will say why is
my mic's so low that's weird let
me oh God kind of quiet oh
God I think we're okay F volume t
t can you hear me yeah I can you you
okay thank you yay we're figuring it out
together little by
little together all right I'll turn up
the game maybe that'll help why is it so
quiet okay uhoh
bow bow see I can bow bow too St let's
get some Stone ladies we got to get
those materials like a a maximum of how
much you can carry in in terms of weight
nope sorry guys sorry sorry sorry oh so
you can just carry as much as you want
that's great it's just slots it's
there's inventory slots that are
finite wait there's a house over here we
have it well the big goals for today are
to find a place to to chill out in
together um a base even if it's
temporary um well yeah can we take over
this house this looks nice this is
actually a really nice house we did get
lucky this is like a The Walking Dead
house oh there's a pool table what is
happening we crouching I don't think so
we may have to take out the enemies here
though I'm like
crouching what happens if we die yes
you're crouching then we
you may want to make a bed roll really
quick thank if you make a bed roll
you'll SP in this house there's a PC set
up I can stream from here that's huge oh
my gosh Hol Ian streamer
house get get
him in the house though there's there's
baddies Reon I
just no
yay zombie noises don't B me I thought
you
was do you want to come with me to them
uh I'm already trying to make my way
towards uh people apparently that's
where we're meeting c c so I'm slowly
making my way there we are we are in a
big house that could be our home base it
could be our home is it upstairs B do
you want to go upstairs with me go this
first people okay what are you scared
are you scared is that why it is a nice
house I called the bed but it had a
giant view I don't know I don't know
about the Integrity of this
house not sure might just need to fill
the hole and then we'll be fine but yeah
you're right zombies can easily come in
here out yeah that's
true o don't hurt my new friends I'm
running out of s so
easy they went upstairs
where they
go he's got a bit of reach on him okay
it's just Dark Souls it's just Dark
Souls oh he
fell
I a lot of
room f m bunk beds down
here I'll take the couch
is there a way to improve the stamina
somehow I'm sure up or
something it's evil stop being jump
scared by
me on the C
there I'm going
to
Temporary the crap guys I'm going to go
on a little trip to find clothes I will
be back to this house oh temporary base
okay you you can craft clothes by the
way yeah I'm going to make some armor
actually yeah we don't have to stay
naked forever and I'm going to start
cleaning the house cuz you know you guys
know I'm a clean freak I'm sorry it
can't be helped yeah this house is very
mess you already you already found your
yeah you guys can come check it out it's
we got really lucky actually yeah come
downstairs sounds there yeah what do you
mean like this is so
broken what works it works for
now but it's so broken we're going to
have to rep so much oh you think we can
find a better stronghold look at this
kie colie look at this giant we block
it there's a pool table Cece Cece
there's a pool table there is a pool
table that's a good point that be so fun
us playing pool together yeah that would
be really cool I you know what you won
me over you know a pool table pretty
good that's a pretty good I think so too
it's a
fixer we just got to put blocks like
crates and stuff yeah yeah a lot of
blocks a lot of crates a lot of
blocks there's snakes in this game oh
yeah snakes and they're not zombie
snakes they're just normal snakes oh my
God yeah there's got to be normal
animals blow it up like in Shrek and
make a balloon out of it
oh I have okay put that there and then a
the does anyone know how to get plant
fiber H smack grass yeah just just punch
it smack it oh there's a water P bottle
in here that's can we pick it up water I
think the one thing I remember is that
it's really important for us to find
water and not to like save it like save
it and not drink it and figure out how
to craft like water reservoirs and
water water yeah mky water will give you
tummy egg probably but yeah it has
dentary in it oh oh that's good you
think this will work if we
just nothing up here
oh gosh
yeah maybe not miss the upper
right what does that click mean does
that mean it's not
working see look we can totally block
this
hole CH is
done we have no wood left you see what
I'm where I'm getting right you guys see
what I'm getting at yeah I think this is
a oh I found eight doll guys anyone want
to sell me something box they still have
money infected water economy
uh can you can I buy
wood I do I have 12 it no I don't can I
have two okay for
$8 wait let me double check if it's
two yeah it's two yeah for $8 how do I
how do I drop something this one's like
a little nicer the wooden
block IIA and F I'm still waiting for
you accept my friend request oh sorry
you got mine right Kara no accepted
everybody and got everybody except
Cil
dos how do
I a thing like a
stack you can craft more than one oh
nice how you split the stack off yeah so
I can give you
two oh I found it totally going to
survive you guys hold drop the sweat
okay here you go I dropped it CE look
what I did I'm so smart I'm a builder
CeCe I'm a
builder oh Wonder build already need a
helmet this is not safe with working
environment I don't that may be she's
already got
drill just plugging up the holes ladies
pluging up the
holes I guess I can craft multiple
okay I already forgot how to play this
game okay time see now the house is well
fortified cuz there's no hole anymore oh
nice the Builder this oh my gosh this is
going to be our streamer house we're
going to stream from here and it's like
a dream come true one pcoc that we all
have to share there's multiple PCS here
multiple even okay yeah kind of tough
all the off
collaps off colls so fun
for I'm so hype let me move my bed roll
oh sh I mean even in a zombie apocalypse
entertainment is
important be there we can get him we can
take him
okay him Bonk him Bon
him yeah kill him make him pay making
pay we such a good team no never I need
to punch a couple more plants never make
sure you guys do your challenges by
pressing y Kiara where are you did you
find your way
here I wonder if Kara is still making
her way here use my fist if we made a
stone we should use it instead of the
one yeah Kiara and Gigi are pretty far
away
she's making her way downtown walking
fast face is past and she's home
[Music]
now have to do
this I think they can see where we
are satisfying down the
tree but we'll just work on fortifying
the base here
I need to gather Pebbles Pebbles give me
yourselves Pebbles oh we can probably
Salvage this car you guys can salvage
anything by the
way sorry I didn't listen how do you
salvage anything any just hit it oh this
put the stuff you find in a crates I'm
going to put some crates in the house so
we can put stuff in there okay okay
okay keep out condemned
yeah
yeah how many more plants do I need to
punch I mean we can do whatever we want
but for the magazine I think it's
probably best to like keep them and then
see who wants to go into what because
otherwise they won't be enough like if
everyone just uses everything no one's
actually going to level any skill
they're really rare and you need like 10
of one type in order to get a level and
stuff sometimes great then let's have
like a magazine crate or something I
personally going for
strength chicken hello eat it to death
guys there's a Farm close
by yeah with crops and chicken
seeds I just got a chicken I just caught
a dinner seeds what do I need to build
my first don't need
rock my first my this is a good spot
potato dinner time
baby we can make a bone knife soon
too uh-oh if you find corpses on the
ground hit them ladies hit
them zombes kind of
cute need a little further away kind of
a strong zombie I don't know
by the way uh I
have how do
you fix the cut off the arm oh you're
infed
oh put down
where are you hey I am here I'm here
wait where is she I'm here hello I'm
here I'm here where is here where is
here IND hell hi okay I'll help you with
the
infection
[Applause]
no actually it might be worse at the
beginning she's wait where is she going
to respawn is she is she going to
respawn
no the
beginning hey ladies
please ladies no you been I'll just tear
off that limb people we can talk about
it I pleas no fighting no fighting we're
all talk about it okay okay listen I
want to help I want to get materials I
want to I want to help you guys to fight
zombies and I behind you behind you a
zombie get that bone knife oh we know
where
the lit right there don't want to S the
hello oh okay but maybe you guys are
empc oh
well
kiaha kiaha made
it get that big boy jumpy can hear me
[Music]
send get him get him get him I'll get
him from the back I'll get him in the
booty now keep hitting him he's not dead
he's not dead I need to figure out how
to leave this other party I'm in that
I'm C
I'm I'm not muted I'm not
muted maybe can't hear
us get B Big Boy nice one
[Music]
kill absolute not have to leave a party
that I'm in I am hurting I can
tell some but I made a a bow and I got
us meat you guys I got us meat so I'm
going to make
wait I have a question how do you
actually wear the outfit uh you click on
the item and press W
oh oh our house what you have the best
house
ever freaking rocks just got to figure
out how to fix the door right
click how do we put a crate here oh okay
make sure we have I'm not Naked Anymore
yeah don't be naked naked's
dangerous we can make two two crates
this my bed now
okay getting some cotton
plants could have sworn I made too oh
here we go all right I'm finally where
you guys are I think I I'm I'm there kah
welcome
[Music]
homecome I see you she's here welcome
probably keep here for now right spoil
or anything right yellow the papa
residence yes the papa that's our
streamer
house welcome am I CL all of us you Che
it out
yourself of iron nitrate
[Music]
powder hello
more did someone put that building block
down there and I accidentally take just
to block the
door
okay even the are here know there go
this place is awesome so we put our uh
bed rolls in here somewhere I think do
that already yes you should Kiara pick a
place the bed right anywhere there's
actual beds in here there are yeah
that's bed
yeah you build those beds over there
just
bu for us oh my bed's by the pool table
put you you have to craft a bed roll and
then put the bed roll where you want to
spawn
so I'm taking the master bedroom hey the
master bedroom someone sleep in the
laundry room make it
too how do we does anyone know how to
make like chests or something yeah I
just made them they're in the living
room living room check them out see I
have a food chest thank you I wonder if
I can put right something on it but I'll
just put all my garbage in here yeah
sure just materials and
such I'll sleep here on this couch
you'll get to sleep on this comfy bed
nice lucky right oh there's an
upstairs uh I think I got a building
Cube from the house I'm sorry that's
okay I'll re I'll reog it other click
right click how do you place a bed down
right click right click click okay but I
don't I don't know how to turn it this
is a cool house can't be on the top no
oh I guess I can't
toilet mky
water uh if you guys find Murky water
you can uh you can boil it in a pot over
fire to clean it what I
see time out I got kicked
out did we all get kicked out not me no
no W I can see did okay I'm going to
sleep next to the PC then I sleep next
to the laundry so I can put them in the
washing machine we have EGS no don't
punch the stop making
sure should you what's wrong with with
burning some murky water some some peee
water maybe I do want to burn some peee
water huh land claim block oh we might
need that
there was a thing we could do outside
oh there's a visitor at our humble AB
Bo yeah a good
one are they nice I don't know but
they're not talking is it just a randoom
NPC uh is it the shieldy group
shieldy did you just attack me I like
this room I've claimed the land
oh
nice press e to use
um anyway we claimed this land with this
block so this home is ours now you my
beautiful
girl a see oh sh is
[Music]
here had
ADHD took us a while stoping
me we have someone evil this
this stop oh the chaos I have no control
I don't have no control of my the chaos
oh hello jailbirds welcome wonder how we
can fix
this you look beautiful look this is my
this is my PC setup do you like it oh
nice oh I can sleep on top of it
actually opening theame okay or maybe I
cannot I I uh got this place it's pretty
Co I sleep I'm going to do you like it
very I mean yeah yeah it's co what
happens
if I
have it
too think getting anything from it does
anyone want to come I want to go try
going to a farm yeah I'll go with
you set up home here really quick let's
go okay I come I actually know where one
is it's right down there well then let's
wait for shy shy did you say you want to
you come with us or my bed roll okay
okay got to set that
spot let's wait a
second and there a tra here or you guys
Trader
lless what did you say a Trader near
this house don't know you we haven't
found one yet we haven't done
anything my hat I like that even in the
apocalypse trends thing and we all
wearing the same style I accidentally
clicked Fashions even fion by the way if
you guys open the map you can set a
marker for where home is open the map
and then right click on where we are you
can set a marker that's
nice this is our home now I'm sorry
every time I all tap back in I punch
someone oh that's what happened I don't
mean it stay
okay truth truth then truth please don't
touch me you don't touch me
truth Ratt
[Applause]
Ratt all right I'm
back yeah get him get him
get yeah oh we're crazy
okay this way I think was the fall Yep
this way wait wait who am I following
everyone looks the same I'm a little
hungry follow
everybody follow this the the the FL oh
dead corn okay but I'm going to have
ADH any you
want
there up the can we make stuff out of
this can we cook cuz I got some meat and
potatoes so like dead corn and green
corn I think was real cor yeah there
is there is some good corn too ladies I
feel like we should probably oh they're
dead let's go yeah there is real corn
here and there can we get can we get the
to sorry I stole that from you we have
po I don't
know got to be a good
farmer I'll be finding a tree this
apocalypse with corn that's all I need
I'll survive the corn or de yum yum
corn they just can't eat the the people
what just
people okay this area has three three
skulls on it I don't know if we're ready
for that yeah it's kind of like danger
we're going to die yeah at the green one
the lot's probably really good but I
just don't think we're ready
yeah images so I noticed that the green
cor actually contain seeds too probably
oh they do we could set up a place by
the house they have something different
we could set up a little farm by our
home with like
a an area to plant like a
seed there's a house over here too here
I see you got this is be careful this is
the three Skool area yeah it's a pretty
intense
area there zombies everywhere run run
run you got to run Sur what are you
going to do it's okay I'll be fine what
are they going to do huh much
[Laughter]
corn all right I hope the corn be
like maybe a farmer shows up and take
care of hopefully oh it's good be night
pretty
soon
the going back I think so nothing I
don't think it gives you anything can I
eat okay we can eat wait don't leave
me so we just need the big
ones or the green on we
found who wants to focus on getting food
maybe we should split into like yeah
good idea grou o gatherers this is just
like Hunter Gathering and stay at
home let's go
organize I found a land claim block we
destroy this oh I think someone put that
down I just put that there for the
quest I don't my land is so if you put a
land flame box down
apparently um it applies a hardness
modifier to block
so it protects it protects damage on
something apparently oh good for your
home so like you're safe in the zone I
guess or something like that or the
player who put it down is safe in the
zone it's like you're L now would house
yeah we have one of those I put one in
the living room oh
okay oh we're in the same uh Ally group
too so we should be good to go yeah it
won't be harder for us to destroy each
other things exactly thank goodness for
that party I have a question um um no
party Ser is
six how do you level
up I think you got to kill oh killing
zombies okay if we find a Traer he gives
Quest and he gives a lot of exp from the
quest I got to get the tra go with me on
an adventure to see if we can find the
traiter I know he is he's really far I
want to find I have one on my map too
yeah oh okay is it the wide river yeah
yeah this way point if he wants to trade
he should come to us that's right he's
not going to do that I think but then he
won't have any business G be your face
by the way or he's GNA stay hello oh
hello oh I found
people welcome
welcome welcome you guys are all wearing
something why aren you wear where's your
hat there's a hat yes put your hat on
what you should
probably F kill
it your I will craft you a hat oh oh
wait no I see a hat oh thank you yes put
it on oh yay
civiliz
split I'm
not um he's far I don't know how to
share the way Mark with you guys what
what if you send like a scre oh I can
send a screenshot gloves I'm missing
gloves pie oh that
works I eat the CRA anything just
yet land claim
box I can make us Char
meat me me is this our base this is our
base
yeah it's about to get dark by the way
what is this land claim block uh it's so
that we've claim the land our home base
now basically zombies won't spawn around
you you see it I put it in the channel
of the map
what if we all put our land claim blocks
like around each other so they willon
spawn within a yeah let's protect the
house where do how to make land claim
look oh I have a land clim Block it's
pretty easy I don't know where to put it
though uh it won't let me put it
anywhere they already claimed this land
please give me my char to can only one
person claim a
land I don't know how are you cooking oh
this is my I'm
cooking oh here Tre the right there
figure out where to put this oh yeah I
can't put the land clim yeah it's a
pretty it's a pretty large put here I am
dying of
hunger I found Place
need all right W claimed this land
see if we can cook some more for
everybody how much meat do you here oh
we need cooking items oh we need cooking
oh I like the the placement of this fire
right we place some fire just people
place fire just anywhere these days you
just put at the fireplace can't believe
it we should probably try to find um
like a cooking pot and a frying
pan
okay yeah how about we split into teams
to do different cooking a grill outside
the house I don't
know near trees is there a town
nearby uh there's a town very far
away that's
water ooh that the
hell I'm going to eat scary food oh by
the way it's going to be night time soon
everyone um here's the idea you guys
have a nice campire out here
wonderful the idea that I have is that
VC one is for the home and then all the
other ones are for like going out on
different excursions together oh that's
a good idea nice
idea that would be great
here she's
here I don't know what to do it's about
to be night
though I'm
Focus you guys go CH too if anyone wants
to go on an
next stroll I'm going to collect items
I'm going to gather stuff so I'll stick
around the
house okay okay I will debate on what to
do
I's good
too
SK skill tree I'm pretty sure what is
the cornmeal oh can I eat this
oh oh you need water to cook that's kind
of rough yeah realistic it sucks huh
finding water might be a good idea for
us I can't oh I can find more
Stones how do we get like purified water
boil it in a
pot water
eliminated how
evil
terrible I think you need a pot how do I
get a pot a
bed have to find a
pot I can craft
cornmeal yeah me too oh there I am bed b
i
violence between our allies is
concerning very concerning yeah let's
not do that how I know when I'm not
hungry how much do I have to eat but I
have harvested SP what the heck okay I
think I'm scary sound did you hear
that it's night time the zombies s
zie I'm sorry I don't mean it what uh I
don't know what to something really
sounds like a zombie I don't need it I
don't need it are you trying to get in
oh I saying that about my stomach it
really sounds like a zom can't zombies
I'm going to try to like build walls or
something yeah it might be a good idea
to stay inside at night time oh we're
not supposed to sleep outside but it's
so beautiful the stars are beautiful
they're coming in they coming stop
talking about stach that way how'd you
repair those doors that's awesome
I mean to be fair we don't have both
doors nor windows can
we oh uh that's
not who did this to
me what the anyway I think I build a
building block I
hope this how I change the to something
else how do you fortify the door what
the heck
I can't man building is
hard if I just destroy this at this
point how bad is 12% dentary can I hand
that that's 12% bad compared to
Zer that bad double oh nice Archer so
much
wood good sniping item that place maybe
I can snipe too
I'm hoping to just put a block here so
we don't have Windows that people can
see us through good idea people yeah
these zombies can't watch us yeah and
think about us and think weird thoughts
about USS what kind of weird thoughts
you know weird thoughts can you name we
thoughts or weird thoughts
girl I swear okay that's a building
block okay um can I open the door or
no help I need there's a weird
zombie M there's a weird zombie outside
M it's scaring
crony uhoh I have a candle what this to
put dang no fear huh ladies I know who
to
Woo you're not afraid of
anything there you go I hope she do we
need any more doors
anywhere I think we're good I think
they're they all look pretty
healed how how' you board them up
Kiara I just want to place a door
somewhere
um this is
Minecraft
yeah
oh the acoustic guitar how do I craft I
have a
kazoo I'm sure that here we can eat
unless it's a zombie deer come here dear
a don't don't e the deer can we just nap
it ran away you cannot sleep like
Minecraft
sadly you cannot sleep through the night
oh no it's evil Minecraft
only just need one more Stone nice I
just see I get the Traer
Quest do I heal if I sleep at least no I
don't think so I think nothing happen
what's the point of having a
bed I just want one
happy
things I'm low on stamina and I'm
thirsty how do you use this so much is
wrong with you this you guys experience
thirst and hunger got turn it
on God at the right you see a bunch of
wood make sure it has fuel and then you
just turn off
this
oh does this building block even do
anything we have curtain that should be
good put some corn in
there how do you tell what you need to
cook something I have to join a party a
recipe I think how do I join the party
can join we'll invite
you definitely uh allies wait no party
a invite
meori can invite everyone right wait I a
party invite oh sick can I get one too
I'm currently not in the party I can't
aim thank you and then you press just
press buttons
yipp you need a party or you good oh do
I need a party I I think I'm in a
party yeah Cece and crony
yippe
yippe probably stick around and uh
Harvest things around here but if people
want to go explore I am thirsty my
character is like
neverful might need to find experience
hunger you have a hunger bar too crony
it's just very hard to see it's a green
bar beneath your
inventory so privileged yeah how lucky
for you my
invent oh now I'm hungry
okay Welcome to The
Gang This is good for harvesting bodies
if you use the bone knife you can
Harvest bodies like in
Rust is it safe to go outside yeah it's
safe yeah go out okay yay one it's not
too bad right now yeah because it's day
one probably do a little
we die though there's a dog glowing eyes
you think that's I'm so excited I think
so are you sure it's not
hoko bow
bow oh that's not a good
sound shift a click or shift
click bu flamed area unless they allow
it you have a
curtain oh can you not build in the
house
area somebody in my chat just wrote yeah
we can't place anything in a claimed
area but I don't know they can allow it
I play
stuff play random blocks oh hold R okay
let's try with this one no it just
rotates animal oh if you like do this
small st hey that's my stuff wait I I
thought it turned into a wooden
block I'll just I'll just pick it up oh
I got to repair it
I'm sorry get animal
St I thought it turns into a wooden
BL I'm just to cover up
uh yeah yeah if you want animal fat Kara
kill an animal and then maybe use the
you right click with an axe I don't see
any
animals to up yeah I'll go hunting wait
really find that bunny I think so you
just need a stone ax
don't you need to like upgrade with
stone really I have the axe yeah Trader
Quest I got Quest
oh oh you need more wood I don't have
enough wood I guess I got uh I have
oh so thirsty anyone got a
pot no we don't do pot around here here
I'm out of here not in this
household you will all starve without
that
pot all right who wants to go find a
pot I can't Stone
hey how do I pick this
up I can't pick this up what are you
trying to pick up grny get stone anyway
oh oh a block this block that I placed
down punch it punch
no I have no oh here you are try try
using an
axe God damn it I have to break why is
everyone dying
oh
night maybe there's a house the farm I'm
thinking that too maybe we should go get
a
pot yeah yeah we should you ladies want
to put together a team wants it to get
the pot
pot let's go to The Farmhouse and see if
we can get a
pot at night what if we die well that's
a good point when the sun comes up let
oh my God the zombies can crawl on all
fours okay I'm leading it to you see you
guys she's Le well I mean I think that
she already knows this game pretty well
getting down God I don't have stamina oh
are you
down no no I'm just really tired she's
just a little eepy don't worry about
there's my base I'm weepy weepy peepy
weepy everyone's
dying yeah it is nice
having just want to fix my stupid Stone
ax why did I just make a new one so much
easier oh it's just gone now that's why
I need Stone
ah look get some scrap
metal is that you hitting the car oh
yeah you know it girl
you and your vandalism oh yeah this car
is in my way I'm going to destroy
it man what if it's like from Pixar
though you're going to get us in trouble
oh lightning what was his name I forget
they're so many watch F you black
sedan
why I I got a magazine for like making
cars from a
zombie oh nice good job
that in a crate maybe oh I already
learned I'm hungry again oh my God all
right you're the car person now that's
your job I am the car person now let's
go that is your job now your end
supp that's not a good
sign
scary I have too many things all right
I'm at the farm you're there anyone also
wants to play Harvest Moon Harvest
Moon look for a pot I can see a moner
there
yeah it's really scary probably oh it's
breaking it down oh that's a big one
uhoh someone trying to get in the house
maybe defend the home base that's a big
end it's a big one hey crony can you
defend the home base why people dying
yeah I'm trying now make a stone axe oh
God I mean I could have fixed one
probably um I think it's over
what's wrong what happened there's think
he can have it he can keep it not our
house I'm shooting him I'm shooting him
hit
him
o oh he's dead away oh no he's not dead
okay he just faked
it how many arrows can this guy take ow
all right I'm heading back there oh God
okay I didn't want to use this but I
suppose I will
oh I'm I love the corn response okay
hope I don't miss
this who what the wo you have a gun I
know how to use it you have a
gun where my other Arrow what the heck
sto all
the oh sounds like a
clicker all right I'm heading back is it
a lot of zomom
no we got rid of him he's gone now there
a
big what are these noises I'm
so oh yeah that's the dud that was
chasing
me oh crap I'm out of
stamina it's a little hard to see
him oh no you get I get I'm infected
jeez jeez what you're infectant we have
to kill you now yeah you got to die
sorry I have
I'm ined with ligma what's
ligma oh come on what's ligma I want the
one of
is here get some maybe I'll heal you
that's a big Bo think it will I doubt it
but I but it tastes good we can eat some
popcorn some corn corn or some poporn
time to leave M yummy sounds really good
all I broke into a house you guys but I
want tote till it's daytime before going
in there cuz
there's I trust you even though you're
infected oh thank you I think in the end
we'll all be infected eventually
probably that's
sweet that's good to know he's giving us
for
legma yay you don't want it oh I it for
already have it I mean you already have
it GGY no it's not yet I haven't been
corrupted yet
all right then it's about time must stay
away from me I won't get L much today oh
I found coffee seeds oh that's bad a
screenshot you seem very knowledgeable
can I borrow you for one second in the
voice chat okay I am moving to three
okay oh I hear why do I hear
grunting that's
me place yeah F bro what what are you
doing here the papa res the papa
residence that's where we
live I don't know you sound constipated
thank oh no I'm I'm thinking right
now wait she's not in
this oh no CeCe oh
no well CeCe did managed to get a
backpack stuff I hear them nearly oh no
see them huh
okay must have been the wind must have
been the wind oh they're inside the
zombies inside that's not good that's
not good how do I drop this I place this
down uh guys we went on an adventure but
we didn't really find anything so we're
back a a I'm sorry to hear that sorry
well welcome back you did good well the
good news this really our home
yeah I'm back I'm back the good news is
uh I found a house that I think we can
break into cilia oh really yes why did
you get your backpack why did you farm I
thought that was from
the SE in daylight no no I thought it
was for the zombie I thought oh my God
this guy has a lot of loot
wow
[Music]
no was so de composing I read your I
read your magazine again H you read the
I have no clue where the Traer is we
probably should go to the tra you know
if there's a backpack that's surv well
yeah if I if I find two more magazines
I'll give them to you I'll donate them
to you no worries no worries it's okay I
have a question yeah yeah how do I get a
daylight iron how do I get I don't think
any of us know yet not sure about that
probably have to find a rock
and it maybe maybe like do I need stuff
in here just a stone pickax your junk in
there ladies Stone a I
guess it's the community chest pickax or
something maybe what you cute frame oh I
can make grill for now I go find iron
then how can you make the grilled corn
baby um I use a magazine to learn
cooking skill and now I have cooking
skill up you can make
all find a magazine yeah you come then I
need a cooking grill but if I if we have
a cooking grill I can cook the corn I
think there was we need the the cooking
grill at the fire so everyone can cook
then yeah yeah I think the best way to
go about the magazines is probably to
like share them in the sense that like
oh okay one person does all the cooking
one person does this because otherwise
we're not actually going to level
anything yeah I have I have two skill
points in cooking already so I guess
I'll cook she's going to be all cooker
let
me I have corn I'll drop yeah so give
give me your corn I will also around the
chest the
chest come with me I'm around I have no
points come on give me a point
please I'm going to the farm if anyone
wants to come to the farm with me uh
come to V see too I'm going to get
materials if someone wants to come with
there there we
go Mory is in VC
too and we can break into that house
finally my axe is about to die though I
don't know how to repair it I
wonder can can you can ask a question
can you make another
V another one how many VCS do we have we
have like three ah they did not make
another one huh let's see if it's not
enough I can ask I am not an admin
sadly okay I can ask myself don't worry
about it I'm so sorry no problem I I
seen a no worries see you
dang you would think that maybe we'd
have a couple more click on the axe in
inventory
okay ah
repair nice okay well now I have two
axes that's fine I'll take
it lots of zombos running around here
that's all right for my
team even if it must be a solo Adventure
I almost got into that house I bet 's a
magazine or something good in
there it's probably going to be hard to
you know do a decent
job um if I just stay close to the
house
so it's time to make a make our way
downtown walking
fast is Pass open the challenge window
hold tab to open the radio menu select
challenges to open the window
oh nice that's
helpful hi I'm coming too oh cool okay
I'm on my way wait wait can I act as if
this is a this is a
walkie-talkie I'm on my way hello
everyone over uh which direction is the
farm over hi guys what's your favorite
manga
over I like noi over I love hos no Kuni
so much
it's up to the news um
uploads hello I'm almost at the end I'm
just trying to be brave enough to read
the ending over I haven't even got I
haven't gotten to the ending either it's
it's it's despair but I hope it'll be
okay I hope so too
over okay over hi Callie what's your
favorite over was that please repeat the
question over uh what's your favorite
mang over it's a secret over it's a
secret why over
what do you mean is a secret is it that
type of not manga no no no it's like
that type of Chad stop stop outing me is
it it's it's berserk it's berserk it's
berserk over oh oh okay okay okay also
JoJo's over I I really want to read
berserk over because of uh because of
Dark Souls I heard it's related I think
you like over but I I heard I might be
traumatized over
you might over be careful it'll be like
trauma bonding over trauma bonding is
actually very effective in Zombie
Survival especially
over guys I don't like zombies
over the Grim Reaper doesn't like
zombies either do we really need voice
uh the walkie-talkies when we're next to
each other ladies over but look how far
away people is over can
you I'm I'm I'm entering a tunnel I
can't hear this I'm in a
tunnel over oh my god oh this is a new
house I didn't go in here but um we can
check this out oh hello hello zombie
okay watch out there's a zombo I'm being
attacked watch out watch out over
there's a couple of zombos this item
needs repairs I got your Sak over hold
up I got to repair this okay so I have
one dream I want to pick up vehicle
stuff
and uh maybe medicine stuff I want to be
AER maybe maybe uh so if you guys want
anything let me know and I'll I'll I'll
hoard the magazines for now and then we
can like exchange
Okay cooking I guess since I'm the cook
now I'm going to be a fighter I just
want to fight and farm if you don't want
to you don't have to but yeah I like
cooking okay okay then I'll give you all
the
cooking over please give my farming
stuff and uh strength stuff that would
be F that sounds fun strength let me see
I'm going for strength fortitude Hammer
okay
okay uh I hear a zombie uhoh oh they're
mad I don't see it but I hear he's here
I see it I see it it's a lady over angry
she
B over oh two of them
okay whack C behind you another one
there's actually a lot of them
everywhere uh be
careful
over behind you too over it might be
over over for us we got this no we got
this we can get
him oh that's a really big those dudes
are really strong
actually it's okay it's okay we got this
what if we lead them away and then and
then
scavenge no I think we we got them we
got them yeah we got this we just keep
hiking yeah yeah there's one one's
already down it's the name of the game
it's called seven days to kite yeah
seven days to
kite true yeah King is my favorite
stamina one second I'll just stand for a
moment you think my arrows are doing
anything to
him
ow they're almost dead
over good job over nice ah but then
there's another over
you got this over ohz it's over it it
might be over for me over no no no it's
okay where are you I'll help
you are you inside oh there's someone
yeah she zombies are pretty
beefy some beefy zomos that they still
this tank she's dead give me my stone
Arrow please there's still one guy the
skele man if we all gang up on him and
Bully him we can get him
wait there s person here oh it's
cron oh nice crony let's
go oh a nurse oh doctor
doctor it's over for me over we'll find
some stuff okay protect us
please oh that one knows how to
jump nice one good job ladies need to
jump into voice or oh she's running away
should I okay never
mind it's fine it's fine it's fine let's
see what kind of loot we find in
here find all I think I mean this must
have been worth it right oh for sure I'm
climbing a
trash I'm inside of
you let's see must be something good up
here parkour
another
ladder oh maybe it's the other way the
other side whoops we're really smart
huge brain people
cute oh no I'm a zombie a zombie a
zombie oh up here what more could he be
hiding sorry I may have you
ow kick him while he's
down I I get nice o drop what's
is it's a blood bag ammo weapon
flashlight Mar SCH you can take it
really I found a bunch of stuff to in
the leather trunk there's shotgun shells
which I definitely will need uh there's
a first aid kit uh an installated the
great Heist volume two is this for
agility maybe we can give it to an
agility friend oh I'm an agility friend
okay you could have a hello hello hi hi
what are you guys to killing stuff
supplies I found a sh and a medical
journal I may I have the agility book
please yeah sure let me find a way to
give it to you hold on let me drop it
okay agility and then I found a medical
journal do we have a medic yet oh I want
it to do medic if that's okay of course
I'll give you the medic use it I I'll
wait until the until we reunite it with
the others because maybe someone else
already than you you're welcome keep it
for now Okie doie I'll hold on to it for
now okay do you guys want to try going
you know when you look at the map the
road do you want to try going further
east and see if you can find any
buildings sure well there's still one
house that we haven't looted that I
actually opened in this Farm maybe we
can hit that first that's our base where
is base and then we can go you trying to
head back to the base
croner
yeah the base is um do you see the red
green square on the map map where we are
like right next to it it's like a really
big
Square yeah a rectangle looks like a
Swedish flag or
something and then you follow that thin
Road the thin road to the west and then
there's one a little building with like
a little Loop and that's where our
building is our house oh okay yeah thank
you nice I think I know ladies if you
want to follow me I can take you to the
place that I busted open okay okay wait
for me I'm coming okay we'll walk
slowly I have a c we going to RP walk RP
walk so how long have you been surviving
in this in this zombie apocalypse over
over oh man about 30 minutes oh why am I
not moving that's kind of weird hold on
my body stop moving minutes wow you must
have this this must be like you you fell
into a coma and then you woke up because
it's been 20 years for me 20 years in
the zombie apocalypse hey a pig e it's
alive it's alive oh it's oh it's alive
it's going to attack you probably I'm
going to die I need help I might
actually be dead you are infected take
antibiotics to avoid symptoms
uhoh um where did you guys go uh look
for us on your map we're at a big house
I tried to break down there's a sofa in
front of it but might be able to move it
or so hit okay I see oh there's a lot of
isn't this like a three three skull area
yeah but I beat I beat up a couple of
the zombies that were here already okay
let's try I'm coming to you guys and
bringing a pig with me oh it sounds fun
is that a
pet is it is that going to be a pet um H
sir
sir you yes he having a hard time oh
okay just kidding the zombies have
awoken all right uh time to lead them
out of the
house well we can like get the stuff
around the H oh we could try getting
into the house maybe one person can go
in try getting the zombies and then
another person goes in tries to loot
yeah sure sounds good do you want to
loot I can just lead them away I can
coral them away I'm currently in the
basement trying to be sneaky oh there's
the pig oh God yeah yeah the pig the pig
I have zombies and pigs to De okay to
deal with okay okay I'm coming
upstairs Pig please I have no quarrel
with you
stupid Pig hi stupid
Pig yeah stupid dummy Pig hi dummy hi
stupid dumb pig hi Sil he going to be
dinner he's going to be dinner uhoh
There's a Zombie he's kind of a strong
one he needs a big bunk oh the pig's not
stupid oh the pig's very smart oh the
pig is very very smart oh God he's after
me a run pig is too fast kill the pig
first Focus Pig
get him ground get ground take turns
take turns doing
[Music]
shots please let me use this I just want
to use I'm getting eaten first aid
that's messed
up maybe I can use this kit I feel bad
but oh I killed the pig I killed the pig
oh nice job three HP and a pork dream
going to get some bacon today nice you
got some good food Cece
oops so I think we need like a knife or
something to to get the meat of the PE
so but that might be good a bone
actually a bone knife that might help oh
okay you should do it then okay I have
blade specialty
now nice maybe you can get like extra
for it or something nice I'm getting a
ton of stuff off this pig though with
this knife nice we have food guys we
have secured food with the with the
gatherers no with the hunters Hunter
Gathering yeah yeah that's what we
do okay I'm going in ah I'm going to try
getting them out and just oh uh-oh I
hear some R watch out behind us B
there's another one I'm going up oh okay
I do have four HP so I'm not
sure maybe we should lead him out
first okay a lot of the doors are locked
it seems okay I'm leading them
outside don't detect them all they'll
lose um
aggro okay also I'm pretty sure the head
is is like
just
point oh that's bad it's easy I'm
watching over your
[Music]
body W he's not going to reach on
[Applause]
him no don't eat her you piece of [\h__\h]
don't eat me don't eat me or you eat her
so she'll be distracted okay well head
drama I can give you my my meat for that
I'm watching over your backpack oh there
you are you'll get you'll get new me
anyway back nice yeah dead I don't like
how they like trick you into thinking
they're dead when they lay down on play
in dead it's a classic and you just like
classic move they should be smart enough
for that careful there's a big guy let's
just ignore this one he's I'm going to
go back inside see what we can find and
try to kite them
out it's in the
basement
okay so I got into a room o I found a
gun
magazine um not be oh my go I found a
cooking pot we yes let's go I knew there
would be what I
[Music]
did okay kiting kiting
kiting okay just got a
kite so there's three of them oh well
that's a little Troublesome taking them
on yeah and it's like a small room so I
can't like really kite them oh hello I'm
about to head towards your location oh
excellent back up support us in our
battles I found a cooking we can we can
corn when I get back oh oh yummy
corn I also found some be corn people
need pork tons of food oh pork
meat but we need water I think it's not
the issue oh I see there are zombies
in what you do about that to be honest
yeah okay I got up oh a there's a bunch
of people oh my God
okay there's a lot of shipping crates up
here there's a lot of stuff so if we can
get them somehow then we'll have a ton
hiping them outside so if someone wants
to go all the way up there's like a lot
of stuff I'll
try okay I'll I'll go look
around you
guys I think one of them no one of the
houses but like there's a lot of zombies
around are you okay I see I see never
mind I'm skipping that far
well that's
bad actually maybe I'm going to kite
them so they come down yeah are you on
the second floor too CeCe I'm on top of
the roof oh that'll do it here I'm
pulling some of these dudes
out H all dipped
out oh my goodness just can't be afraid
jump down okay one went back in and two
jumped
down okay okay and I think they took
take
what we can take him see that guy that
guy's nothing he's
nothing oh there's a lot I went I got oh
by the way there's some more people
coming maybe like four zom zoms just let
you oh just kidding people as in Zombies
never mind a big one okay there's only
one with me upstairs right now so I'm
going to just loot everything yeah go
for it take what you can take
um I found a pain oh I'm dehydrated oh
that's a big
boy yeah there's also two like right
behind me can I drink this water I will
uh do this technique you are W the
medical
journal nice nice found some vitamins
hello does anyone
have wait I think I'm lagging oh I think
the server's lagging yeah she really
I was going to say they're dumb they're
caught in
the oh whoa waa wo
hello all right
want I have no stamina enough sounds
like sing cuz I'm
hungry I hear a lot of zombie
sounds maybe that'll help me a little
bit here he's after me so you can
probably hit him during that oh cool
that's a good idea can make I can make
tea with that flower okay here we
go give him up wow I have no stamina a
reinforced chest and I will spend some
time on I'm enforcing it I'm enforcing
it up up up enforcing it do what you got
to do oh he can jump out here now yeah
there's only like two zombies who take
up a lot of it yeah
right click on the zombie
heads man he has so much health I'm
going to kill the the zombie that's
upstairs for youc I'm dehydrated I'm
dehydrated too actually we need to find
water well there there's some water here
it's just do bad we can't just eat the
snow I know wouldn't that be great if we
could just eat snow eat the yellow snow
isn't it like the energy you take to
melt snow if you have a human
body what if
Linate sorry I'm not that into your
Jewel of emotion who there what no of
emotion I didn't I didn't mean I need
the yellow S I found an egg to cook
something lemonade business with it I
don't know if I've play my Char is tired
go away zombie I can't okay time for me
to drink m i don't have murky
water oh that's how you do it press W
going to take some time with heal
oh okay I'm at 3,400 out of 5,000 oh
he's finally dead it's fine he's not
dead I lied it's fine oh I got the
trader y I finally got the Traer oh my
gosh oh you're up here
hello I will help you oh now I have a
lot of skill points oopsies okay I'm
just going to leave this guy to you guys
hello help use use your axe oh my axe I
I'm like to weak in
[Music]
general no you're strong to us you can
be like mentally strong even if you're
physically weak it's okay bro I'm tired
my character is
thirsty this guy is like too he's too
big in
health okay I'm leaning him towards you
good
luck so uh what you do before the uh
zomb ibie apocalypse
C uh I was an an interior designer
actually oh wow so what did you design
like like houses yeah mostly like yeah
mostly like for like you know rich
people they would hire me and then I
would give them like very high prices
for very minimal work um but like
like oh thank God that guy would not
leave me alone you did the majority
floral vintage
Aesthetics ooh sounds fancy and then uh
I was pretty lonely for a while uh in
the zombie apocalypse but i' you know i'
found groups like this before but they
are never they never last they never
last um this one definitely will on my
own for a while and you know I'm ready
I'm ready to take another group I'm
ready to open up again we're glad you're
here thank you thank thank you I I feel
very welcome to be honest so I'm very
happy about how you what did you do
theie I was a m Society I was I did I
was unemployed I had no job I freelo
loaded so I'm kind of glad Society fell
during this zombie apocalypse so
everyone can start over and be equalized
because I was this like scum of the
earth you know would you argue your life
is better now than before yeah my life
is better now cuz like everybody
everybody has nothing so we're all in
the same like playing field now yeah
it's great okay don't you think usually
you would want to push yourself up
instead of bringing other people down
well well now now I can now I can you
know oh so you feel like you've gotten
this this is this is my second chance at
life yeah and now you've become like
morally very positive and supportive and
exactly before I was just like you know
unemployed looking at w all those rich
people with their um switches and ps5s
and I was really jealous but now nobody
has anything so you're like a
vtuber no one has PS5 kind nice what is
a
PS5 what is it what is but no I
understand that's good I'm happy that
you got to put on a leave okay I'm
opening it oh repping for fun one first
eight kit pipe baton if anyone wants a
baton
banded armor plating mod um I'll take
this scrapping for I'll just I'll just
oh no someone else can take it I'm over
water from here please does someone want
to be a nerd I have electrical traps
magazine and a medical
journal a medical
journal yet okay I don't want to be a
nerd I'm stupid yeah me too I'm a big
want pick this up
I'm oh okay staing for
fun bandage armor oh crates actually
maybe I want scrapping instead of
medical I don't want to make decisions
before we talk to the others maybe they
already made it's raining it's raining
hold up let's rain Reapers zombies
Hallelujah there's a house
there all right let me keep looking
around that my
[Music]
camera I found some good stuff oh
night we still have not found
yeah water's the big concern
here I'm
cucumbers we have to oh okay I can take
the rest I'm cucumber I'm just going to
I'm just going to put some seeds and
flowers she's over
cucumber okay I think there's like a way
I don't know how but I think there's a
way to craft like a water like I need
help oh yeah just a zombie I can
get I'm trying going to reset
my I just put some random stuff in the
chest oh oh your phone I want
that it's raining
Moy that's weird why is it not receiving
me it's
raining okay time for the camera to not
work feeling what time is it does anyone
know what time it is oh 2:00 p.m. only
we can go we can keep adventuring if we
want to but we are pretty in cucumber
maybe we should head back to the farm
just
once to the farm uh not the farm sorry
our home okay okay okay okay let's head
back home put all our stuff back and
then if anybody wants extra arrows I put
it in here cuz I don't have any room oh
nice I need arrows okay nice nice nice
I'm going to arrow for where'd you put
them bi boo in this chest okay I'm going
to grab it sorry you guys are going to
have to
not see me for a minute um as I'm
resetting stuff oh
nice I'm over cucumber trash
pile
Trash
Away
PL oh I can still hear her
voice I'm
here I'm here
here's
air okay I'll go back for now okay oh
there's a fireplace this house is kind
of nice actually it is pretty good I'm
not going to lie and it seems a little
bit better well well whatever but the
other one has a pool table Yeah the pool
table is the main attraction and the and
the and the what is it called the TVs
PCS yeah the PCS it doesn't work but
it's still really cool oh
yeah all right we didn't go underground
oh she is here okay she proba miss
everything did you root
everything no I just looked around and
killed things okay let me yeah yeah so
the general rule is uh vc1 is our home
base and then all other ones are
different groups that are going out on
excursions
together yeah cuz we don't really know
if proximity tat really works in this
game it kind of does the best
it was really weird because it worked
the other day when we tested it didn't
it Kelly yeah it did which is extremely
strange
so maybe it's based on if there's like
less people so smaller amounts of people
could
work we were the same though we were
four earlier and we were four the other
day as well so yeah I I tried it earlier
during testing and no one could hear me
when I was out of the party it only
worked when I was in the
party yeah and even then it wasn't
proximity in the party it was just uh
General chat General yeah whatever like
a
radio yep oh well it's okay I feel like
this is working especially when we're in
the little bit smaller groups oh I think
so too yeah little groups I found
gasoline oh
nice oh he's alive beware of dog I'm out
put some food in here okay I found
pumpkins and I found eggs and so much
meat there's 30 raw meat bi boo cook us
something delicious please okay I will
let's me cook and you can boil some back
at the base so I'll jump into the other
VC for a minute if you guys more
adventur I'm down yeah we can maybe do
one after we
regroup yeah okay
okay hold on I'm having to reinstall a
new camera you guys sorry about that
okay
[Music]
I will go I will hop over when I get
home
boy time to cook some got some stuff you
have food yeah we found f yeah 30 meat
we we Hunters we have the meat yeah as
as
the I I will say you are the the leader
of this group am I wouldn't you say it
would be very much smarter to like move
to a house that is closer to the trader
yeah I think that's a good idea I think
for now this is an okay first base bro
you guys are blocking my
way you're
welcome oh no sorry yeah maybe we
shouldn't get too comfy here because we
have a crate that's full of food for
example we're going to need to move
everything moving is
hard maybe we can make a second house
yeah a second home basement slowly move
everything
yeah yeah I'm going to keep these
shotgun shells though yeah any goodies
that you find just dump them and I think
everyone should get um a bone knife at a
certain point cuz they're really
useful M bone knife and then I'm going
to make a magazine crate and please only
take the ones that that you think you
want to kind of minmax yourself on I
personally am doing like a fortitude
strength thing but for example there's
like a medical journal I have an
electrical journal for nerds
okay if you're a freaking nerd what do
you guys have you have you found any
other journals so far an academic
one oh for intelligence right she's a
she's a what do it call she's a scholar
freaking po Dexter all righty she she
did she's the winner she's the winner of
the spelling be so of course true true
does anyone want to try going to the
trader so we can do some Trader quests
because I feel like that's where the
food and stuff will be get and
water water would be very nice I
definitely need water but first can we
get a snack can get a little snack first
I'm very hungry can you guys who you're
at the house when you go to the trader
can you bring some food with you to
share the only one that can cook from us
is B and I don't know where she is right
now so yeah we need more chef and I'm so
thirsty oh I'm so thirsty I have one
water I so thirsty feel so bad but I am
about to die take this take it take it
okay so we let's wait wait let me ask
what you's doing one sec I'll be right
back oh thank
God what I feel so much better
desolation please you know I could
probably cook some eggs though yes eggs
are easy to cook o how do you like your
eggs I need water dang it uh
Benedict Benedict's pretty young batch
what oh nice how we get
there all righty I love my eggs like
that also ladies I am a farmer so if you
find any Farm relating things let me
know cuz I'd like to start a farming a
little farming plot okay but probably
won't start the plot until we're
actually at the trader area you mean
farming magazines or something like that
no uh farming yeah farming magazines yes
you're right that's correct thank you
okay I do have one blueberry seed by the
way yeah seeds collect as many seeds as
we can we're going to need them I have a
potato nice you have a potato potatoes
you have a potato all this time we talk
about hunger and you have a potato
there's a couple potato potato yeah we
could share this potato should I split
the potato like what we all take a bite
yeah it's dire times please potato
fam okay I have big
is on her way and she will make us all
food yeah and then we can go on an
adventure to the trader and see if we
can you know find oh I found
coffee you have coffee we're starving
and you have coffee we're starving and
you have coffee
St me bu like 30 meat or who was that
was it you yeah I have 30 meat I put it
in the crate
30 you have 30 it's uncooked this
reaction is
genuine the other ones they were fake
this one this one's genuine this one's
genuine wait so how do you get water
from a river and you just like how how
do you drink it but I don't get any
water yes you punch water to punch it oh
to get water it's when it's raining look
up and then you start drinking we've
been through this
oh Lord that's a
spirit yes ladies yes you were even
there when we've been through this and
you judged crony for it what what these
other people in this call don't know
that yeah I don't know what you're
talking about what do you mean you
talking about yeah no you're just
telling what what what did I say
actually happen or are you guys messing
what I have diarrhea like it did
happen I
see you have a lot going on with yeah a
didn't know you were going to Dr that I
was just reading out I what it said
somebody have Golden Rod flowers yeah
actually there is a golden rod flower
safe space
everyone about there oh my God there's a
diara icon on the screen well I don't
want to see what that looks like
jeez oh oh I want to see that yeah try
eating some more sham
sandwiches you'll get
there I'm back sorry about that sorry
for the long way wait wait but just the
flower is not enough right you have to
you have to boil it you have to oh also
I'm infected uh I need to take
antibiotics okay we'll cool you when the
time comes no for infection I've just
been uh eating honey from the tree
stumps it's really efficient good idea
I'll go grab some I see the diarrhea
symbol now di let's go diarrhea gir
yeah let's go diarrhea
mating yeah let's share a toilet
together I not to that far I feel like
we' all been like isolated as
survivalists for such a long time that
it's hard to gauge is that is that
romantic are they flirting I'm not sure
I think it's bonding for sure
yeah it's dire times get it I don't
think I understand so
silly oh welcome home
[Music]
I I brought um girl ever ever coming to
the I have I dropped like 30 meat on you
I can make bacon and eggs and I can make
boiled meat so I'm going to God blessed
the heavens yes please
I will bake
it to let me cook we're so lucky that we
have B to make bacon and eggs for us
yay can you make tea too
bio um let's see with the golden
flowers oh oh I found a golden rod flow
oh I cured myself with the honey thank
you for the tip oh you can make you can
purify water as well oh please make we
need that yeah
if if you have murky water I can purify
it I have that too it's in the crate I
think we have some there's one murky
water that's cool I found it in a
toilet bacon and egg have two U murky
water I'll drop it for you here go
yay look at how cute our house is all
natural murky for the murkiest reasons
it's a nice first house but we
definitely want to get closer to the
Traer yeah actually it's okay since
we're near a river with our empty
bottles we could theoretically go near
it gather water and just like boil that
endlessly I hope wao you guys have
bottles yeah I thought the bottles
disappeared infinite water trick you
guys get bottles open your mouth just
open your mouth look up you can't why
would they do that
what about how split a stack I'm blind I
think right right I'm just going to do a
quest now then okay
okay oh I figured it out okay thanks
have you seen the Traer yet Kiara oh if
anybody has any more cooking books uh
please give them to me yes I will give
them to you I do think I don't actually
know if it's like super important to be
honest I don't want to I don't want to
Railroad and be like oh we have to be
super careful when I have when I don't
know but this is just like my
inclination but maybe I'm wrong so
just yes I am at the have Golden Rod
flowers can you boil them so that I can
drink him okay that we can drink him
okay thank you how do I share cup I'll
just drop it okay and I'll also craft
armor so I'll read
this I'll go for medic if you want to
give me the medic
thingy expens oh the medical journals I
put in the journal crate
which is over here it's right here next
to I need I need one more level in
cooking if anybody has
any cooking magazin mag we might find
them somewhere
else
okay the trader sells the tea that
you're making for 144 coins what I don't
way to get coins yeah how have to be get
coins that's crazy that crazy my
diarrhea is going away on something
thank you sir anyway did I take the
cloth bunch of meat right now I found
some acid if you think that could help
your stomach
problems it would help with the liquids
I guess potato actually really oh beep
do you want to put the the cooked food
in this one the storage PL which one the
right one and we should try to figure
out how to make a farm the one that the
one that you're looking at yeah are
where I need to go for oh my fetch Quest
when did you take this Quest oh I think
you're sharing cuz we're in the same
party I'll compl it for you don't worry
well how are you already there oh I was
just walking wait I don't think I can do
it for you doesn't let me okay oh so you
coincidentally there the took it what oh
you can label the
boxes okay I'm on my way what you
cooking Vil oh we can make we can make
glue I can eat glue maybe we should do
that no no no that's not idea I'm just
growing meat at the
moment it's like a big
sleepover surv yeah I love it you look
like the L how do I instead of watching
one item instead of all the items guys I
don't I also do not know
sadly oh control right click water yeah
sorry I got to drink some that's okay
I've been dehydrated water
control am I finally like not as
dehydrated water
heck yeah yeah yeah why can my skin not
absorb the water from from the skin why
not cuz you're dehydrated the glass bar
just disappear works that's
stupid you eat them why why would the
glass STS disappear after using them am
I just going to crap out glass like CS
now that eat you ate the glass you
filthy glass eater guys it's raining o
how comfy too bad we can't drink it yeah
can I open my mouth just right now yeah
not opening your mouth yeah
yeah yeah you just have to look up at
the sky oh my God drink all the
water maybe it'll gather a ditch I the
quest oh yeah I think you are please I'm
so thirsty and so unwet
we do be thirst am I
drinking I can't tell if they were
kiding maybe if we eat food no we're not
you just you have to wait it's very
incremental there is some moisture
inside of food I've already Dr
oh oh my God it's the best over should I
do is there anything we can do at night
probably stick around the general area
and O cry I love crying me too find
supplies in here I hope the mushrooms
grow inside there golden rod seeds where
seeds
seeds I love zombies what's wrong
there's here okay where I love seeds is
he stuck uh no I think she's doing a
quest
oh I'm on my way it's really scary it's
it's dark and found an
empty oh maybe I can't Farm
here I probably need a farm plot a
rotting
flash yeah we need a farm plot if we
want to
farm this might be all the twin stuff
man I can't make my hops does anyone
want to go to the Traer for Quest not
it's totally
fine I didn't want to I didn't run a
rush I just thought if you going to do
something else I was waiting for food
from people first
um the food is going to take a couple
minutes to cook but I put I put food
might be one upstairs it keeps saying
Char meat B
boy no no no no Char meat is the food it
is the food oh really Char meat W
is at
cooking that's the
option that's all I can make right now I
need one more to why I take both I don't
want to take both it's okay it's
okay here I'll put one back challenge
each Char is
complet you're going to eat my Char and
you're going to like ited eggs o it's so
nice and dry okay I'll cook some eggs
too I'm ding I'm dying you have water
wait why are you dying should I not be
here is it you should be here you should
be here what's happening don't worry
wait should we go into to a VC the quest
yeah we can go okay yeah which one two
four what okay Cecilia you wanted to go
to the trader right I'm ready whenever
you want to go oh I want to go to the
trader too okay I'm outside choing Traer
team what VC should we hop into do you
think oh there's a bunch of VCS now we
can take four let's take
four okay we're in four now
yeah yeah yeah think I could eat a raw
egg does this take place in America
maybe it's not I'm making boiled eggs if
you wait like a couple minutes oh cool
I'll just go put this egg back in the
crate then we can go oh it's no longer
raining my free water is gone what a
shame I know they hate me they just want
to dehydrate my butt so evil oh I found
some murky water in the toilet
oh good give it to me and I can purify
it awesome that' be
huge B I'm going to put it in the food
actually here I'm going to drop it on
the ground I really need water actually
so how can I unlock this drop okay there
you
go that's huge that's a really big
deal always check toilets ladies toilets
are full of water that if you boil it
you can drink it okay it takes one
minute to cook let me cook I am cooking
okay and then we can definitely we can
go to the tra the Trader's pretty far
huh yeah it's an adventure adure it's
already 9:00 p.m. we might die but that
is
true well just prare your spawn points
you got your beds already yeah true also
you know we did it last time it's fine
it'll be fine just have a little water
drink and then we can go go sorry if you
guys is water still you guys have enough
water you guys have you guys decent on
water I'm starving and hydrated but it's
okay maybe we'll find rivers on the way
hydrated but I am hungry oh there's a c
i see how cooking works there's a is
that why your meat is
charred charred meat's pretty good
actually no it's dry he's going to be
serving us up sirloin steaks pretty soon
I Know It wait oo I can't wait let's go
my Gordon
Ramsay oh does it go in into like
straight into the storage cases if I
take it out it shouldn't that's kind of
strange by the way was I meant to head
to
the I'm heading to the trader now I hope
I don't die okay we'll go we will go as
well but if you want to go ahead J do it
I car I'm getting D okay hold
on before it hits night okay here you go
here's some water all right ready to
go thank you so much bioo right let's
run ladies let's run close the door
maybe let's go just
walking just walking there this music
now though repair my
club o there we go my map got marked
with a
traitor
yeah are they sus we we don't know yet
we have to meet actually the trador is
very
hot hot as like he's on fire no like
she's a beautiful lady oh
beautiful yeah hey Chad how do I drink
with my hands just won't let us live
with her yeah I know what a shame right
I
know oh I hear them I'm on me way zom
not I wish I had a car empty hands e all
right hope you guys catch up yeah me
too do you know where you're going I'm
just following you I have a mark a
marker on my thing it's not really
working but I'm also dancing with a
zombie right
now get
[Music]
him you have to
be every has
died uhoh people dying never
mind is the marker for the Traer is for
you guys is it the uh the orange
one it's called White River citizen for
me okay yeah me too everybody at home
died what happened uh-oh they weren't at
home right I thought they were doing a
class running I just passed the
river Let Me swim to
you oh I'm wet
all you need to do to make a do
collector we should figure out how to
make a do collector
uhoh say it you
won't you're challenging her I
won't you really think I would fall for
that trick you are yes how um oh oh oh
hello everyone guys I feel like it's
important for a social hierarchy to find
out how guy how old everyone is in the
zombie apocalypse
oh that's not you guys that's someone
else you never ask a mustache man his
age a man I thought one of you
over don't even think you first
over oh okay I'm
actually um
I'm okay Ellie I said I've been in the
zombie apocalypse for yes that was a lie
it was a it's just my beard makes me
look kind of old uh I'm actually
only when when did the zombie apocalypse
start 30 minutes ago 30 minutes more
like uh 2 hours ago actually what really
yeah I found a wolf should I kill it
over can you take it over I don't think
I'm running away over oh shoot that's a
sh R the wrong
way that was FR I'm actually uh I'm
20 forever 22
[Music]
but mentally I'm 38 I'm 38 guys I'm 38 I
would like to be 2 you to do things for
us then I'm I'm 47 I'm I'm your
senior then I'm 48 so I'm older than I
am I then no I'm 40 you didn't you just
say you're 30s I'm 47 40 oh yeah I'm me
well I'm I'm I'm your age plus whatever
that is plus four just so you
know dog
though I guess you are now guys I'm so
stupid I keep like taking my hand and
putting it on my you know like a phone
oh yeah I keep like getting confused
it's that muscle memory my hand isn't on
my
mouse I'm
stupid muscle memory hello oh oh hey
hello I just killed like so many things
on the way let's go where's the traitor
up here I can climb this mountain yeah
thought I did it yeah we got a Skyrim
pretend you're a goat yeah I did
it or is it just you wait do goat go
back I don't know but they do now
yeah no more thirst issues though I
found the settlement did you did you not
that that there actually goats and sheep
hybrids and they're called
Jeep
oh
Jeep Trader wrecked Trader
wrecked isn't the trader closing isn't
the TR it closes at night actually so
we're
B yeah uhoh better find a place to hide
drink the water if you guys if sh if you
look up in your map I I found like a
whole like house area maybe that would
be nice whole neighborhood sure nice to
meet you there yeah since I think the
trader is closed I might be let's head
toward the CC Mar sure yep yep go
towards cc go to the CC maybe we could
even find a house there all you can eat
for only
3.99 sorry you activated something
inside of me when you said
that I don't
3.99 that's pretty cheap oh I found some
charg meat oh this reminds me of B's
cooking do it tastes like B's cooking
though no mine has a special
touch yeah she puts like hair in It
Special Touch what what do you mean
hair hey just just because I shed a lot
doesn't
mean it gets in the
food that
often yeah I have a lot of hair she
sheds hair she's a wolf yeah I shed like
a dog
o okay we're here I'm almost there okay
I am here go around I'm in the in the
garage the garage hello I hear a bunch
of zom zoms yeah there's two at the door
they do be
crawling oh yikes they're just there
everywhere why did R do that to crony
little fast ow it's kind of M maybe she
wanted to
die I need to heal
wait why why is the door closed all of a
sudden I closed it so that we don't get
ambushed from the other side I think we
might get ambushed inside though yeah
but it's safe it's okay all right I need
make more
bandages nice fine though CeCe now I
will close the door freaking
go out of
stamina
okay there's a lot of res here we have
less space
inside okay I'll open it yeah it's not a
good
idea definitely going to need to get
prepared before tomorrow's
run oh they're really trying to get in
there huh is that the house you guys are
in the Washington residence guess I
could help we're in a Goldsmith house
right now the Goldsmith residence gotcha
yeah you know if we took over this area
we could each get our own
houses wouldn't that be great we could
each have our own homes
W I see how it
is you know what maybe I'll just turn
around leave I found a hidden basement o
what's in
there zombies I hear them we should kill
him hit him with my Bon stick oh I'm
going to make more bandages I cannot
make more
bandages
uhoh help you
okay big
Bonk good thing my strength is UN
precedent oh nice I've gotten much
stronger I found I found a to
oh uhoh that seems bad you okay I fell
in a hole you're really get your shock
huh oh I fell too not very safe yeah my
leg is sprained there a lot of people
here keep
keep they're all really F she's very
strong wa it's night time so I guess
makes sense but
okay you can drink the water oh crap oh
crap there's two of them on me I'm going
to die guys I you good night
[Music]
night's I should have
put for
me no I'm dead there's two of them in
the garage as a head dang
it I can backpack spawn me the
backpack the backpack's going to be cool
area beding that's cool ah I died it's
over it's okay you found a really cool
area though I did find cool area I'm
cold and naked is it safe to get my
stuff in the G I think so are you guys
in a garage can you pleas a cave oh my
God if you're in a hole my stuff is in
there I know I'm in the hole but there's
like three zes in the hole so just be
careful okay coming up they're fallowing
me up the
hole
oh
hi my stuff is in a hole you guys look a
little
different wow the whole place is just
trapped
completely yeah search back
everything uh-oh um well we just spawn
near don't wor I'll kill him I think
it's I'm
infected F I'm stuck I'm stuck between
like five zombies this is not the way to
go I don't like it we get back up
Goodbye Oh
shoot go TR actually I'm trapped it was
a good good
call it's this wooden chest
okay well there is a way to get out yeah
yay bit of a cool world oh hello can you
hey can oh is that a
zombie all right sir i' would like to
spawn near my backpack again my dude is
still in a dream sake eater get out of
my
way someone leave me
alone someone make me a spear because my
back
again I think we're all dead yeah
everyone dead yeah am I the only one in
here I can't see
anything oh jeez oh that's a big boy I
think the tactic is to oh shoot oh shoot
what is to leave the house what is this
the tactic is to leave the house this is
oh
God this is very interesting okay I'm
taking I'm taking all your stot and I'm
running okay I'm out okay
should thank you thank you thank you
you're welcome you're
welcome no I can't spawn near where you
guys are get my items down there I think
because you took my backpack backpack
I'm so
sorry ite I'll run I'll run back over
there I'll run back I'm it what is
happening it'll be fine it'll be fine
you're not that far actually yeah
I got to get my items again um you guys
just get your items and get out then
maybe we can come back as a group yeah
maybe during daytime cuz it's cuz it's
on the Upper Floor and I can't reach it
okay I got my stuff I'm going to leave
never mind I'm totally dead no I don't
want to die now because I have Calli
stuff all right I'll wait until she's
back I have to go and search I believe
in you no chat we already have a base we
have a base but we wanted to make one
closer to the
trader that's embarrassing I don't want
Sak night time does feel very long that
is true okay yes it does
don't sucks we got this we got this yeah
we'll be
fine this was very cold out
here thank you very much oh they broke
the ladder for the
redirect oh my God thank you I don't
know if I can collect myself myself in
the I'm just going to kill everyone in
here
do what you got to if I have to die I
will die again and again and kill
everyone and take them down with me it
could be morning soon you
know all right I'm coming back for you
guys back my
words that's some interesting powder
I'll drop all your stuff here okay all
of it yes thank you so much for picking
up my
stuff no I'm sorry for making
me you're good
would you be able to make me a a spear
then I can help a little bit yeah I
think I can make a
spear
oh
hi I don't actually
know I'm just punching them all no okay
let me see if I can make you spear real
quick Stone spear craft I got
out that's good I'm punching all of okay
here you go even through all the
pain all right I think they should at
least be out at least I hope they stay
that way nice I got a spear okay okay
I'm back I already have a club I didn't
need another club it should all be
outside hopefully uh can one of you put
me out of my misery you want to be
killed thank
you always never hesitate to ask guys we
all support each other here it is Callie
put your clothes on oh shoot you're
right I'm naked
thanks for reminding me of nak oh
they're after you they're after
you
actually that's your I'm actually not
sure where my after me is anyone going
to come after
them I got an
arm are you still in the house fast no
no I should oh is that you oh that's you
yeah you okay going inside getting my
backpack yeah okay okay just keep
running so keep running like like 5
Seconds keep running oh we got a lot of
exp that's pretty good must mean we've
done something
good okay so you said they broke the
ladder oh yeah I got to go back there my
no I
me
my I got my stuff nice I got my stuff if
you can get my items that's good too the
bottom the hold
the bottom of the hole I am like all the
way
upstairs that's
fine I can't
see oh she's dead nice job team oh
there's a big boy I sacrifice myself for
you okay I'm going to try to get my
items you're kind of quick I got a I
found a sniper magazine
I if anyone want
gun gun would be fun yeah I want a
shotgun it's a shotgun please let me
know magazine
for all my items are covered even if I
die I don't oh I'm
dead thank you forting them not bad I
mean thank you not bad heck junky Tech
Planet I'll take the sniper magazine I
kind of want to be a sniper okay okay
yeah I'll give it to you if you guys
find any shotgun mags please tell me oh
what is music get out of here it is
morning time which means the zombie
should slow
down no there's still one after me if
you guys want to help I would love to
let me get my
back oh there you go
I well technically we've taken this
house is just the floor sucks right so
we need to rebuild
it I don't know if it's a good idea
living here though isn't it kind of the
put all our blocks down then it could be
okay
yeah yeah okay stop
spawning should we take this whole
neighborhood to like crouch on the floor
do you sometimes see those like tiny
holes do you know if you can do
something control but it's not much of a
Crouch yeah yeah it's very pitiful we
could also build our own home near the
trader but it's kind of nice when
there's stuff building is the beginning
is going to be very hard right yeah I
think so I think it's best to like y a
house okay you guys want to go to the
trader then or do you want to stick
around here a bit longer sure let me go
there my two Health oh no Che out of a
misery did we pick everything here did
we loot everything I don't think so I
still hear them in
fact hi my hello oh gosh the floor is
lava certainly I know I think you're
probably you guys go back inside oh you
guys are back inside yeah I got to get
my
here ooh Ronnie flesh yummy yum yum
favor I
know I am a bit over encumbered if
anyone has space and would like to share
the burden no space I will I don't
really have space either I have like one
FL open I can't run
anymore it's over maybe you should eat
all your corn I don't have any
corn oh an archery
gun o guess I'll use that I could use
it someone's cucumber y
this eat my
cornmeal stay nice and strong I know
heal my five health
yeah I was going to say like oh I
haven't been hungry in a while it's just
because we've been in a death Loop yeah
maybe maybe it's a good tactic though
the punishment of death it might be
shame that's about it that's not I don't
have that yeah what's that of it there
are a lot of houses around here right
for the picking though especially in the
morning time yeah I mean if we can
respawn your backpacks I think it's
worth doing it um more you should put
clothes on I don't know where they went
accient have your clothes I think when I
picked up your backpack it automatically
put on your clothes on me Ah that's okay
I'm just making new ones no worries I
can I can come down I'm just getting
some loot real quick made it I'm
good spam mail what do you think is in
this house o Urban
combat who wants to learn oh this is oh
Urban combat's good for everyone
actually Okay who wants to excel
ourselves I might go for archery oh I'm
going you want to give
me okay come here come this way I'm not
I'm not going for strength to anything
but I'm going for I want to go for
strength I'm going for speed I'm The Bu
farmer
speed that's like my aesthetic you know
look at you guys killing over I can't
believe you eh whatever
hello uh beam I think I was call
something else call I'm
bleeding almost
apparently now go collect your Urban
combat thank you I'll take your corn in
the
meantime I'm a bit low on health just a
bit respawn your backpack so it's fine
one sec I I'll be right back one sec oh
yikes oh that was very I didn't want to
see that supplies in the bathroom a
pg3 stream oh my
God we're going to do it P paper there's
an option to turn off Friendly Fire yeah
we don't want to do that it's more fun
this way it's fun oh man I have way too
much
crap maybe we should really look for
another base closer to the trader
huh eat all the food that you have I
cannot walk so I think I'm going to go
back home because like I can literally
not walk yeah I might do that too do you
guys want to do that yeah
let's let's loot this house if any
search for this house and then we can go
yeah
I have like two slots left so I can't
like I cannot I'm just going to go be
cucumber he's waking up I'll go because
I can't Sprint so I'm going to be slower
than you guys I'll just go home it's
okay I'm going to be slow too we're
going to all be
slow yeah I'm cuum nice
yeah B crotch shots don't work on
zombies what a shame they would be
hilarious
I don't think they can feel their
crotches what in there
nothing oopsie they can't feel the love
tonight play A Dangerous Game there I
don't know what you're talking
about what a small
house oh I got a little achievement for
eating Char the house that matter you're
welcome now complaining about my cooking
did I complain or did I say it's uh
wonderful beautiful
amazing guys pick me up isn't that what
I said didn't I keep praising her about
her great cooking and how much I love it
oh yes I I remember I remember
that the 2 of September no I don't
remember that anymore actually Prett
good I have
amnesia but I don't have real Amnesia
have plot Amnesia so it's okay plot ask
I don't know what's going on apparently
charred meat will make you thirsty
though so be careful that makes sense oh
no you need you need something to wash
down your STI are you ready to have back
sh yeah I'm just going to equip the
medical thing um I learned medicine just
now because I don't want to be in
cucumber okay when do you when do you
want to head back make that my house
let's head back yeah let's head back the
Malone residence will be mine though
eventually just not right now oh can
weite to the party so I can see your
marker better oh yeah you bet oh I'm in
a different party how do I leave the
party there I sent you a a
request oh okay is this technically
cheating on my other party no us right
now they'll understand they'll
understand is it this one oh wait how do
I join your party how do I leave a party
oh I guess I got to got to kick people
out here I'm makeing GG leader yeah see
see you guys there you
go excellent and then how do I how do I
leave
party that's a good question oh
here okay okay let's go I can join a
party now you might have to send me the
thing again okay let's
see
okay thank
you great now let's head back to home I
suppose I hope they don't think I'm a
home wrecker or technically you guys are
the home wrecker I guess so that that is
I mean have your relationships in that
party been family your relationships
already well well fa put her bed next to
mine oh oh my God that's a bit a
different situation and I put like a
candle in the room I haven't had time to
like sleep next to her yet though cuz we
can't really
sleep that is messed up though I can't
believe you would do that to her oh I
didn't do anything you guys a home
record technically didn't like commit
yet they didn't sleep next to we
sleeping her on and that's mess I didn't
do anything I think you guys are the
home record look at you didn't do
anything we didn't even know you were
sleep next to each other buddies you
never asked now you have to take
responsibility you to put your
best oh no they're sing
not remove the guilt from your life a
bunch of squabblers there guilt it's
okay I'm fible today more eggs for biu
to cook for me ya yeah I will cook eggs
oh yeah that's a good idea she's the
killer cook cook oh wow we did catch up
to you yeah I told you I'm really
slow oh you mat you're not slow you're
great oh wait no that's
C that's fine we'll catch up to
eventually we've got cooking sniper and
shotgun farmer I do need to find a
shotgun though you're actually closer to
the home than I am I think because I'm
really slow oh
yike man I'm growing tired because
you're
cucumber I am I am I am cucumber oh I
didn't even know that we could hold more
stuff than we have it just makes us
slower yeah it just makes you slower I
didn't know that I thought it depend
wait too
probably guess that'll do it this music
is actually kind of nice
you have
music yeah I mean it's part of the
game in game music yeah why don't we
meet cc to help her carry some stuff
where let me find let me see where is
she no it's okay I'm almost slow she's
not on my she in front of
usell oh oh is she
actually man I feel like a like a jaguar
or something running for home yeah
you're really bounding bounding for it
yeah cucumber animals have
homes I don't think so I think they just
like sleep wherever well I mean some
animals have dens but I don't
think those that big cat does have like
a den I think those are we should ask
yeah we should
ask do you think she just roams around
steals internet from people yeah just
like
beep can't believe why oh my god oh so
you did say that you were like a mucher
in your past life didn't you oh oh yeah
I I was a street
rat
yeah but it's but she's turned off a new
leap but it really talks about how much
you feel that you're openly talking
about it you know yeah yeah that's
beautiful hi from us we still don't know
what and did before so you know they
might be hiding
something they might be hiding something
you never know
let me ask kaha for the book uh or maybe
they're out on adventure still we make
gunpowder sure oh never mind they're
like really
far please let me
know all right we can eventually shoot
things I can't
wait yeah we definitely got to talk to
the trader though cuz that's going to be
a big a big Point turning point for us
so we better go go to the trader soon
yes yeah in the next 2 hours or so cuz
that's about all we have
right yeah maybe we can make a little
list in the Discord of like magazines
that people want that might help yeah
yeah I want to be a farmer oh yeah we
can want anything deck built related and
cooking
okay I want to be a med and maybe
something like I haven't decided like
Electronics or mechanics or something
maybe mechanic I'm I'm not sure yet that
we find oh I have a I have a tech
juny you're back oh you're really
huffing and puffing oh you are panting
I'm telling you okay uh the sniper I
don't remember who wanted the snip I'm
putting it in here I want I'll give you
hard farmer I'll give you this magazine
it's a tech junkie that might be good
for yeah okay electrical traps is that
the one
or look that's ND that's the
intelligence bu I don't think this Bas
pulled out for like seven days oh hey
the tree screw up seven days to die yeah
I see what you
did did you end up making new clothes by
the way armor piercing ammo okay I'll
take
that all right should we head out soon
to the Traer so we have like plenty of
time to loot as well yes in one sec I
have to like organize just since it's
morning time let me see if I can make a
a better
Club you going to go clubbing I
wish on pipe pistol pipe shotgun how do
we make that oh glue short I need four
short iron
pipes I think we have that think in this
one in the one I'm standing in front
really oh my God I'm interacting with it
one sec 9 mm what what you say is 9 mm
how can you tell like pistols
maybe also we should try and go after
air drops there should be one every uh
hour but I don't know how to track them
oh they can leave us supplies but they
can't pick us up oh yeah sadly it's
messed up
right yeah oh iron pipes yay and then
what was the last one it was glue and
wood there so much stuff in Orit
overwhelmed
um pipe shotgun
yay I'm making a pipe pistol nice cuz I
have bullets for it
I do we have a box for like bullets that
I can put it in no I don't think so we
can make one I'll just use the one with
the magazines then if you have if you
have 9 mm you can give it to me I'll use
it I put it in the Box okay this is big
how do you name
boxes um hold e and and then there
should be a rename option I think
oh here let me rename the food
one there you go
food how do how is the Box what's the
name so I can make
some huh what is it called in the in the
in the in the building
menu oh to make a box a CRA hold up
building
block I think it's and then when you
place it down I think if you hold R was
it yeah hold R it can change it to
different shapes
oh okay I also was able to do it using
the crate thingy I think is this one
yeah okay thank you oh yeah yeah okay
I'll just throw all my stuff in here and
then if you have like a lot of items for
it you can upgrade the building blocks
oh cool look iron building block at some
point yeah maybe we want to make we want
to really fortify our home for the first
rush so finding out iron how to make
iron blocks might be really
big we were we'll have to look for
it oh and what spike traps I'll put some
here in my B in my you might want to
make like traps and stuff like that as
well to put
around yeah that'll be
fun what's
wrong did did you fall in your own Spike
trap what
happened what that was such a jump scare
huh did the game glitch out no no no no
I I one shot I one tapped you in the
head with my gun why did you do that do
that you criminal I didn't think you
would kill her like instantly I didn't
you someone
the you so messed up
humans
beo can't believe you murdered your
friends messed up you thought you were
going to cook for meor you served me a
meal a five course meal of death thanks
a lot here I'll give you I'll give you
some meat sorry take take my I accept
your one charred
meat
UPS oh your life is only worth like one
charred meat yeah that's horrific I feel
really sad about
that oh
well yeah I just had to test it one time
okay the intrusive thought took over I
didn't think going to kill you kill you
and people thought I was bad
huh let's see where can we put spike
traps probably around the house maybe a
little distance though yeah just a bit
of distance I'm going to try to make a
balcony so we have like an Escape Route
or a place to shoot
from good idea
we rotate it oh I can technically make I
still I can't really heal yet I need one
more Med kit medical and then I can make
first aid bandage oh nice that's huge
nice but I think I'll probably wait I
can't Wheels bicycle chest bicc I five
medical okay I like how we just forgot
okay I'm ready whenever for when I'm
ready okay okay okay just don't get in
my way or I might accidentally shoot you
by accident wow accidentally on purpose
these are crossbow bolts not
arrows I was recommended I scrap
them do this yeah complet a
[Music]
challenge yeah iron iron y okay we got
to do something with the iron though we
got to figure out how to cook it or
something like that
I think you can make a furnace at some
point
O
potato I feel like we need to find a way
to like be able to get
regular water drinking water there must
be a way to mass produce water I think
that's like collecting like collecting
water you know like a rain collector
stuff like that ah oh my God the the
spikes but we also get water from the
tra when we do quests he gives you like
rewards and you can pick water I think
water every single time there's only
five shells there's only five shells I
really all right is everyone ready yep
ready to
go okay pleas that an enemy I must not
let my blood lust take over oh we can C
we can craft a dual collector that's yes
we definitely need to craft one of those
so yeah if we do that that would be nice
yeah it's we need something called a
polymer something or another
workstation I we have we have po oh yeah
workstation uh so a certain skill will
unlock being able to make the
workstation it's a robotics where is it
oh we need like aund scrap Advanced
engineering yeah I see well let's get to
the tra for now okay and then try and
get the advanced engineering skill under
intelligence you guys that'll help us
create Workshop or workbenches okay
let's go why does why does someone put a
random door in here who could say say
who could say they're being a little
silly all right Trader
time guys ready to run a kilometer
together yeah yeah this is a Bing
experience should I sing a song you guys
want to sing a song sure sing a song
I'll sing a song in German uh and then
we all do it together wait how does it
go you know it's like there's 10 bottles
on the
door I Wasing that there's a be
bottles on the door but and tonight will
be the night that
I
again Chang my
mind another door
here um and then um
I miss you where are you where are you
and I'm so sorry
sorry I cannot sleep I cannot eat
tonight all the will be the no I
will make a song that's like related to
us so we have the Shaker this is a
school trip this is a school trip we
have to uh right oh I just heard am I
crazy I felt like I just heard someone
join the voice call never mind let the
ghost get to
you voice maybe yeah I was like yeah I
thought so too
right Pap rabbit kill it kill it kill it
kill the rabbit kill the rabbit kill
what the rabbit the rabbit where' he go
that's messed up I can't believe you but
it's food I miss you oh it's too fast
for me to shoot I miss you wait where is
it where is it where'd it go he's he's
up it's uh over Over
Yonder oh wait how do how do
I dang it really worth
it how do I cancel Maybe not maybe the
meat isn't that worth it m yeah I don't
think it's worth it to waste my bullet
on of bunny yeah let's not let's not do
it yeah dang it I can't even my you got
away all right sorry about that anys
leave it's the Ping okay I missed
because of the Ping it's it's it's F
don't worry about it I believe it scroll
wheel what I tried just a silly rabbit
I'm pressing
doubt um this this server is not close
to me there is definite ping here but B
but b haven't you I mean the shakera
haven't you learned about your past
experiences it's okay to admit weakness
sometimes it means growth that's what my
dad told me admits weakness but it was
definitely the pain of okay so this
you're admitting the weakness of the
server that's the server is weak it's
like a sideway step I I I get it you
know my dad told me when I tried to play
the bass in his band one time he said
you know myy it's okay to admit when you
suck at something a
so so you know it's okay to admit when
you suck at something but that's not
nice that's not nice but that's the
world baby ad my flaws like I will
definitely go for the beef and
fall oh understandable yeah I've seen
I've seen you have tweets so I believe
you they with the Traders Traer wrecked
wait wait this is not the Traders never
mind this is BB bar field oh that's a
little different yeah whoopsy doodle oh
we can collect corn here though yeah
corn I'm
hungry Carl wouldn't we go to Carl's
corn Carl Carl
Carl Bob's bors and Carl's corn are they
friends my friends
go we become one with a
corn corn they're
Corning they be cor the corn is
cornering her hey I found people it
looks like they're digging their grave
oh really are they NBCS as in like real
as in as in W and crony are here digging
their graves that sounds like why are
they digging their own Graves that's a
little yeah I thought they were like
real people anyway I'm going to the
Traer I also like get distracted but
I'll go to the Traer as well okay I
wonder what they're digging maybe
they're getting
items oh it say think they're preparing
their
grave I'm at the board barn or something
Bob is I have to get stop getting
distracted I'm coming Carl's
cor am I supposed to go to the
barn you can avoid it if you want this
is a nice house though not saying that
we should take it is a nice house nice
house and there's you know a farm
already here
magazine it's really nice when the
Farm's already here it's not nice any
why they're keeping people in cages that
is M that makes it even nicer actually
it's like a
holiday yeah incredible when they're
like well fed and taken care
of yeah it's like a spa experience have
you never wanted to be in a you know
just
like Grace be behind bars I mean you've
done that not really can't say I've been
in jail enough I do not want to be in
jail again can you believe bi's been in
jail that's crazy to
me are you sure you can't do you do you
really think that's crazy when I shot
you in the head Point Break and killed
you I mean but that's in the game right
right no we're talking about in the game
oh look at the piggy wait aren we don't
kill the piggy I like the piggy a never
mind kill the piggy kill the piggy uh-oh
having some trouble with the boards
thingy deserves death now where can I
even put the chat oh my God I'mma eat
your body tonight
baby good job I'm going to skin this pig
Hold up okay you shank it she makes a
good
point
yummy oh maybe way I'll see you guys at
the traitor I'm going to head right to
the orange oh what is this there's a pig
in a cage I leave this pig for now you
Piggy look like some Gordon ramsy recipe
picking a
cage fancy Gordon ramsy recipe I also
all right I'm
indors it's
Smokey why is it so okay I think if you
guys follow kie she's like basically at
the trade out right now sorry we went in
this house we're doing some looting
first they're looting yeah I got
distracted loots are shoots distracted
again oh they have oh wait there's
another Pig bees prepare to kill this
pig I can't mean but for now for now
maybe it's okay oh I think it's just
eing I heard there's a beautiful lady
here for now but
I oh there's a
zombie are you kidding me where's the
hot woman I saw I guess I can stand your
smell wrecked gu that's about that Miss
somehow okay now I got it there was a
hot girl in the in the the trailer not
the trailer the the beginner's course
video who is this guy sorry only into
like fictional that's just an honest
independent business OD okay you have to
stop being
he's got a lot of good inventory but do
we even have any money oh yeah s what
did you think of
Leon oh he's oh oh it's here he's cute
oh he's got a shotgun Messi feel might
have a thing for a so I can't trust a
man who might have a thing for someone
else though verion oh there's a cooking
grill oh oh we with
you [\h__\h] don't just stand there with
die I only have anyway all right I got a
buried treasure Quest but got money oh
can you pass me the grill I'll hold on
to it yeah here I dropped it thank you
we can make corn now n i SCP money it's
nearby so I won't be too
far actually that's crazy good finally
food sh yeah finally we have like a
regular food stores with the grill thank
goodness for that I already made a
shovel all right ready to dig wow I
don't know what happened in this house
but I there's a story oh so they weren't
digging their own Graves they were
digging for for buried
treasure it's part of a
quest I like the idea of them uh digging
their own Graves though pretty silly I
have a I have a weapon for for you story
this one's better probably here oh thank
you oh I actually have that too I just W
use it I'll use it
now oh that one's like not
broken okay what I what should I get rid
of sometimes a zombie might spawn though
if you
dig
careful candles look for that supply
Crate yeah Diggy Diggy Hole eat this now
all right are we done here
sorbe now all right I'm coming we're
coming to you
guys it's the four more
days w a lot
ofers a big you
hear uh I I'm outside of the FL I'll
wait for you though oh wait how do you
how do you get out what's the best way
to get out jump I jumped out the window
that's a good
idea I
will destroy my way out
actually give me give me five seconds
maybe 10
girls girls what's up too sleepy I think
I got to go to bed I was going to ask I
you be yawning a bit Yeah
s I'll join again tomorrow playing you
thank you
have a good eat see you tomorrow good
see you tomorrow home recer
home what's up oh here come
here huh oh hi anyway I was going to go
the other way but now that you picked me
up I must now go with
you I had to leave in style you see I
had to leave my mark in this territory I
see oh treasure must be in
there okay go to tra I too must eat my
D how how long do are we going for
tonight until we got another hour and
30ish
minutes
hi I get
it I don't get it
is that it down there how am I supposed
to get out of the hole fin the trader
can't wait to go to Trader
Jo's actually it's
Traer that that would be Trader Jill
then oh oh my Char TI sandwich murky
water Rotting Flesh and wrecked cuz I'm
going to get wrecked wrecked yay no
zombies spawn y lucky me oh it's not a
cute girl what do you mean myy no I
thought it was going to be weird that's
not a cute girl at all I know I was lied
to I was
scammed I'm as disappointed as you guys
are there was a beautiful girl in the he
talks
oh wooden shovel he's kind of mean too
but you know yeah he just said he's
going to cut my God bapon
throat no I think we need him
guy he's got a lot of customers right
now know you got to keep in the bullet
put your pist so much stuff I guess I
can't shoot him please don't put your P
stuff either I guess watch your
back watch back how long does it take
for me to feel
full working stiff
tools see that's the girl I thought we'd
see she's not here though can I can we
at least loot his house no we need him I
think you can try well what he doesn't
have to I don't want use can food that's
actually important compared to Corn what
is that button on his
overalls block
oh wait no that's not any better bun of
fragments what does that say guys don't
don't worry about
it there is stuff you can loot they say
do we really want to loot the Traer
though
I don't want to make him mad look at him
he looks like he could kill us looks
like he's got three shotguns oh actually
there's a bunch of stuff to take Co hand
but I bet you got disent
Terry okay oh I found oh no he has a
land he has a land claim block I think a
a fetch Quest I hear that sound when you
try to destroy something oh look who's
tired of eating out of dumpsters and
whatever all right are we going to
give you but you better not disappoint
what does he want us to dig I
guess I got just a job for simple like
you oh I wonder what we should
do you do i' say it's been honor to work
with you but it would be a
lie okay I got a fetch Quest I think did
you guys get the buried treasure Quest
yeah we're going there right now okay go
yeah do that not that I was paying
attention but yes
oh there here's the fetch Quest it's way
over here actually it looks like yaha
and them were doing
it tier one the F oh buried supplies
is nearby okay I'm going to go to the
ber with supplies first cuz that me too
cuz I already Mar wonder if they're
going to do fet fetch
Quest too bad we can't just take like uh
credit for their hole they already dug
it can we see our Quest on
our oh yeah I dug I dug the hole
already
oh but I still have the quest to do I
think oh thank you for the redirect
hello
CeCe good night
CeCe yeah good night CeCe put your bed r
next to
mine I thought I thought you put it next
to fire different locations for oh no I
didn't she did it she put the M on me
yeah wow sure makes doing quests
together kind of difficult but oh
well we'll just have to work together
kind
of wait do you guys have the ber
supplies in this area near the farm oh
you have it in a different spot I guess
so it's the near the place of the p
they were okay yeah then I guess we all
have to do it individually yeah sadly
that's okay we can still you know talk
to each other if you
want fck you want me to socialize Yeah
well yeah socialization is good even in
the zombie apocalypse we need each other
you know talking to people how do you do
that my what if there's an awkward
silence your parents used to what oh
they used to force me to socialize I
like it oh really yeah yeah they made me
join like freaking clubs every Sunday
made
you
yeah oh I see you want to join
us I guess we can
merge all right I'm digging I hope this
is it I'm digging too I'm hungry oh my
God eat
corn get the corn they're normally Auto
shared with party members progress if
they're nearby when you interact with
the big yellow exclamation
point why did she do that to
her maybe she needed to get put out of
her
misery he quests are Auto shared with
party members that doesn't seem right oh
does it yeah yeah yeah yeah I can see
your fetch Quest so if you wait for us
at the fetch Quest yeah I'll chill start
it all at once together okay so let me
just finish the digging one I'll wait
for you guys and then we'll come over we
can fetch together oh this is going to
be such a long digging Quest and I'm
like
tired my character oh this one gives
water I'll eat it
now it was not enough water I need
rain I'll just chill around here
around where the fetch Quest
is
okay I wonder if we should just help
each other with our uh digging to make
it go
faster if I finish first I'll come to
you and then we can go to car together
that's strange you guys have different
digging quests yeah I thought we would
be in this we would have the same on
since we're in the same party sh I hear
them I hear them but I can't see them
time for a
swim you are wet uhoh I see them
now actually there's a question mark
near a tree oh I found the treasure nice
that's good okay and then I will come to
you
after oh I see the very first Quest
cannot be shared but after that the
quest can be
shared okay I think I did
it yes okay okay I think I need to dig
at this hidden section I'm going to go
back and turn it in cuz I'm cucumber and
then I will come to you I'm not going to
drown don't be silly wait what's this
E I just I just pressed e oh now I dig
okay oh wow you're far I
know let's get a little wood on the
side when you get here I would
appreciate if you cut down the tree so I
can see
[\h__\h] okay
thank you see you're
welcome wow just like in a
Minecraft just like in my Minecraft
oo o I'm a goat I'm a
goat I'll wait at the yellow exclamation
point for
them am I just like digging this entire
area like how deep was yours beibs it
wasn't it was pretty getting close it's
in the ground in there if it says if it
says you're getting close uh dig
sideways oh I think I see it little
perception for the outskirts actually
okay I'm go in
ail oh I'm
tired I get this level up so since you
since
you have the fetch Quest already yeah
you already took for us right
yep since we're in the same
party so all we got to do is gather at
the same area where the golden
exclamation point is okay cool and then
I won't start it until you guys are here
oh all right I'm going to help sori
first and then we will come over okay
take your
time might just see if there I was close
near Treasure but my character's just
way too tired and I can't even drink
glue oh no not even
glue yeah that's rough buddy did you do
the thing as a kid where you like put
glue all of your hands and then spent
like an hour peeling it off because it
was fun not because it was fun but
because I had to do it yeah oh you had
to do it well I mean yeah if I used a
lot of glue and it got on my hands I had
to peel it off but you never like put it
glue on your hands on purpose to peel it
off not
purpose it was going to happen it was
going to happen in arts and crafts
anyway true enough oh good God my
character just so done to and
tired dang you need stamina this letter
do I drink this murky water I guess I
will good oh
yummy cardio for gear but you still ow
us
is cardio like stamina that's just
sprinting yeah cardio is like running
and jumping and sprinting and hot so
stamina yeah I need all right I can't
afford it anyway actually oh yeah I want
more bullets to
gun definitely got is the outline Circle
this
one I thought this was just like the
circle
uh getting stuck I don't know where I am
actually it's within the circle yeah I'm
pretty sure I'm within the circle
maybe I'm
hungry I feel the zombies are our way yo
are you here yeah yo
yo H I'm out of stamina it is so
horrible
gosh darn I'm actually I might be
stuck I think I'm stuck hello
diving please help me my Brave One my
character is just such a
princess and you sure it's not in your
inventory if you press tab you don't see
a box in your inventory or anything I
still see the outline Circle so I don't
think it's here actually I think I'm
going beyond the outskirts from there so
you might go this way which way this way
okay uh what whatever I'm looking at oh
I see it I see it look look look I see
it it's right than
God oh I found oh nice you found
it oh a sandwich and murky water oh huh
yummy huh what was that oh I think I
nicked your leg with the shovel this may
take a while I see okay how do we
uh all right now
sir o hated that walls may be faster
actually you're right hey why he so fast
oh oh he had loot
who maybe the zombies you have it it's
the guns and for steel grass I don't
have uh okay I'll take it I will drink
my murky water let's go getting my kind
of an unlucky place oh we got four de
out of that that's cool I got he's doing
it himself he's helping
me all right I guess I got to go back to
the tra yeah and then we'll go come on
zombie we can do it all right I'm going
to head there all right my diarrhea sets
in I'm going to break these CES real
fast all right o breaking your own t
can't get
broken oh I see him hey there buddy I
guess this is what B is feeling
she was not feeling
[Music]
fun feeling
fun owie
owie
what getting kind of
cheesy now I got 28%
diarrhea wait you're actually actually
diarrhea is actually a thing
yeah yet
you think it was just a myth a legend
beeps
yes diarrhea I've never heard of that
before
dang she joking oh a
dentary this is I've heard
of she's joking you won't know if it's
fun until you try it so let's go find
you some food to give you some diarrhea
I guess
oh
hello I should lead them out this way
all right
trador trador here's your darn
Quest oh that's a lot of zombos actually
let me lead them
away I think I better take a
pistol I meant I meant diarrhea in the
game by the way I she has to clarify for
having to clarify I have I feel like I
have to clarify because for some reason
people actually believe that I didn't
know what diarrhea was but okay what
what silly people silly all right I can
go to the fetch Quest now okay let's go
to the first Quest I started the quest
no I didn't
rest the easiest way there
maybe a different my headphones
hurt see tier one fetch Quest C okay
maybe it was a different quest for some
weird reason that's odd we all get
different
Quest oh I think she accepted a
different Quest that's why oh oh cuz it
it shows up for everybody the clear the
area Quest yeah oh yeah that's a that's
the new one I just
got B on what was
closest understandable but I'm going to
go do the fetch Quest yep we're coming
okay wait where we even fetching I don't
know not sure
yet oh no now I have the D Rizzle too
that's a y welcome to the Riz Club I
just wanted the Sham
sandwich well you got shammed it was a
sham you got sham W I feel silly
where you know what would be like funny
what if all this time um our Discord was
muted for one of
us that would be pretty
silly I know it's going to happen
now I am not shio
silly it is getting kind of Darker out
here huh oh dang R just killed crony
why does she keep doing that do you
think um probably like past memories of
being married I don't know oh I got
Casino oh I got an actual
pistol nice
oo sandwich begins at 22 that's very
frightening I'll open that
later can zombies drown what if we hide
out in the water until daytime I was
thinking that might be a good idea we
can yeah they don't have lungs ah
true well yeah but they might be slowed
down by the water and then we can kill
them from afar maybe oh yeah there's an
idea I wonder what happens if your your
diarrhea percentage is like super high
does it affect you or something I wonder
mine's going down slowly so yeah mine
too like I don't know how it affected
me yeah maybe it just like makes you
hungrier or something like that maybe
you just feel
you know oh this zomb is about to get
real
fast no thank you I do not want but
you're the jewel of emotions you have to
be emotion of
Shame
that's I I feel I'm empathic for you I
feel bad for you but I don't you feel
bad you feel bad well I want to feel
your emotion not your not your physical
ailment that's not how
yo myy how did you get there did you
just swim yeah I swam
across dang look at you my little buff
buff
girl buff shotty shoty Master can you
shoty oh God feeling fear feeling
fear oh they're coming out oh they're
can't swim well it's night time well
like very poorly actually but zombies
can in fact swim
yeah oh crap I think I might
drown I'm good you'll be okay I'm is
that my
tum my
Tommy your tummy my tummy go go
go wow I guess it makes sense that you
can uh fall in the water when you are
out of stamina
let's see oh I haven't collected enough
O2 get my
rewards ooh I think my character is
about to crap
themselves
yeah craft a wooden door wait don't do
it yet I want to see oh cob that's up to
my body I can't control that BS I want I
want to see and laugh at you oh you know
as the gem of emo then I'll throw all
the
result never mind is messed up are you
sure I don't know we got to SP oh no I'm
good I changed my
mind how
sweet yeah you can you can join too I
guess you and I are suffering the same
issues you know I'll pass I'm okayoh I
see I
see away foul
Beast yo why can't I L him on fire
swimming this
you don't think they can swim
right well I'm slowly swimming towards
there you know maybe they can I hope I
don't
drown trying to think they can
swim just slows them down a little bit
oh God yeah what's
wrong where's a bunch of zombies I
really hope they can't
swim uh
[Music]
yeah oh wow this is like a big
area now he's doomed to live at the
bottom of the lake he's coming oh my
god oh
man is this place
closed let me
in oh you can you have to press e guess
I got to run your stamina goes down as
you're in the water oh I I have a b am I
in the right place oh good
God wait am I not in the right place so
where am I oh
no where
[Music]
my oh well I guess if I di matter too
quiet yeah you just gra the backpack
yeah oh no all right time to go back in
there oh no now I have diarrhea yeah
it's a pretty common thing
dizle the
diaria
dizle going to die place here we go oh I
have to I went the wrong place I am near
you though what is
this I'm not far enough away to sneak
yet
have you guys seen the video of the
Japanese aerobic s going I have a bad
case of diarrhea I have a bad case of
diarrhea no I have I have not seen that
okay I'll send it to you guys later no I
I don't really know if I'm
interested no it's it's cute why do you
think they made to say that they're they
they teach they teach you English words
through aerobic dance and one of the
useful English the most useful English
words is I have a bad case of diarrhea I
tell people that yeah how often would
you use that number one number two would
you yeah this this like your
introduction to people be okay oh hey is
this you yeah oh hey anyway I might
bring some here oh no you bringing
zombies like tell someone that before
you know it happen just to give them a
warning you know right you don't want to
just do that and without any warning
so Chad says how do I don't know that
one yeah it's it's a big it's a big meme
I'm not with the times okay well I'm
going to have to send just say I need a
bathroom quick that
works or like I'm just going to the
restroom I don't even give them details
you know yeah going to the restroom hey
wait why should should we take this
Quest now like what's going on actually
waiting for Bio I'll
she's swimming in the water like a fish
okay this is a huge map but I mean good
you
know one me I like where is this like if
you're about to talk to someone here's
some tips that you could talk about like
giving topics and then you kind of just
crack under the pressure and say I'm
going to
labor what yeah yeah that's what happens
when you panic talking to someone
interesting but you can do a U-turn and
you still bring back the conversation to
the original topic if you bring up like
box
manufacturing really what's a box
manufacturing how to make a
box I don't even know anything about
that is a
thing I don't know but you got to think
outside the box okay so do I just make
stuff up like talk out of my ass like oh
here's how boxes are made yeah that's
what I do all the time
yeah I don't think I get it that is that
maybe I'll try it next
time try it try it right
now
so you know cardboard boxes are crazy
because what are they even made of like
I know paper's made of trees but like
like cardboard how do they even make
that stuff you
know uh
uhhuh
oh Oh I thought you I'm here by the way
oh she's here okay okay lot of zombies
crawling around but oh yeah I didn't to
spawn out of
nowhere hey I leveled up hey level
Ranger Station Delta shall we start the
mission yeah there's a lot of zombies
need to start the quest I like how this
just a Giant floating exclamation mark
falling members are out of range will
fail here we oh uhoh oh there they are
oh boy um now what now what I'm
dead what I did have very little health
they're very
fast yeah they're quick okay yeah
quick can't be
helped where's my bad
part oh no I
level nice
job you shooting
them yeah shoot oh oh there's too many
of
them how about I this is maybe not the
best idea doing this at
night uhoh H okay K not working however
we can do it your Brute Force oh yeah we
can I've been waiting to use the shotgun
oh you can't escape
either stop beding I'm dying
bro okay I'm about to get Nom nomed uhoh
I just hope it's looking behind me
shotgun is pretty strong I got n nomed
and infected oh no the quest failed it
failed that's what for me we can fail a
quest I guess if we all die oh man
that's harsh that is harsh but okay I do
need to get my backpack back he has loot
though oh he has loot I'm taking
it oh
boy oh you can't dang I ran out of I
don't have bullet so quickly there's so
many of them let me lead them away okay
I'm out I guess we got to go back and
retake the quest huh that's a
lot you better are so
teleporters all right how do you get
back
o guys it's not time for The Rush you
had
zombies yeah let's go back together yeah
let's head back okay maybe you can do a
different Quest that's closer
yeah are you swimming beeps what are you
going to do time for some
swimming where where are you my let's
swim together yeah I'm going back to the
Traer oh they found me I see you getting
chased actually I'm next to they'll
never get
[Music]
me Let Go they'll never get
you uh Quest fails for players as soon
as they die okay that's
good it's little hard to survive though
yeah well for now I guess let's just
take quests that are you know not too
tough yeah and not too far away supposed
to be a fetch Quest by the
way about
that we were supposed to grab something
I
think I'll be okay don't worry about out
of stamina on the water I'm
fine I can handle it yeah we're like
mermaids oh hey there's a
zombie cool kill it cool this is murder
it immediately was can you build a
bicycle not yet I think we need to do a
few more
quests okay hugging the shore the more
quests that you do I think the better
Vehicles you can make eventually oh
shoot oh really let's make a tricle
found me that's
rough yeah old
tricycle yeah okay I found Callie I lost
you that's okay I'm making my way
towards the thing anyway I'm hugging the
uh the islands okay yeah we can still
pretty much see each other on the map
so
yeah D I do not have a lot of bullets
left only two shots but I mean they do
damage they do great damage do you have
a shotgun yeah I have shotgun bullets
for you you do yeah my
hero thank you hero
Academia am I over encumbered no I'm not
I'll read one of these arm I come here
and take them cuz I'm over cucumber over
cucumber okay let me see if I can find
you oh there you are you're a cool
looking and cucumber maybe I need to
give this to someone else thank you okay
here you go read it
so thank you wow
bullets bullets do you have any 9 mm at
all let me see I
might people under yeah I do I'm with my
arrow I'll drop and then here this is
also for you you might want it it's an
armor magazine I already read it so it
doesn't do me any
good well if you you you know you can
there's multiple levels of it right oh
really I use it oh it's okay when I used
it before cuz I tried to use it again
and it just disappeared from my
inventory and nothing happened
[Music]
so kind of weird wow we're swimming
together
[Music]
I can't wait to not be sick anymore what
is that infernal noise
it's sounds like a pig to be honest oink
oink dang multiple volumes of the
magazine the the zombies
feelings this Lake Vibe is very
spooky I feel Fair going the right way
it's the cleric
[Music]
Beast it has it has that clicker sound
and like
the it was behind me this whole time
ow oh no blast
them oh it's one of it's
jumpy jum for me I did find a house nice
but I'll probably we die on
the nice you got us exp oh there's
another's no
one wait should we just like stay at a
house or something the camp guys I
wonder isn't he traveling at night isn't
so bad but Quest at night is probably a
noo I'll just like
[Music]
St oh yikes I'm getting really beat up
no you're supposed to save people not
destroy them armor
oh yeah the nurses it's pretty rude
huh oh my
God these things do not die oh I'm
[Applause]
dead
no don't eat her no don't need my body I
see your H dwindle away I killed it
that's okay
thank you Baboo that's all right I'll
just I'll be back in a minute your
body I'll be back in I at the
Traer I want to wait here and check
this well yeah it is night time after
all but yeah I mean it's 2 a.m. or
something yeah um this is where I'm
going to go and uh end it for me okay I
hope you guys have fun yeah I'll see you
tomorrow or whenever I play next heck
yeah see you around
yeah good
night
bye-bye were you headed toward the
trador huh oh I was waiting for you for
your stuff oh thanks I'm all good I'm
good to go okay let's go good to go
let's run it maybe after we get back to
the tra we can head back home so I can
start cooking corn for everybody
okay I really hope we can find a place
that's closer to the trader might be a
good idea at least build a bike or
something
yeah oh yeah cuz she already left I
think the the quest failed that's okay a
next time next
time feel has disconnected from the
park why am I leaning like this am I
leaning to the side right now you're
leaning it's kind of
weird like I'm going to fall over or
something the world is getting all
spinny is it a bug oh I think you might
have gotten bitten by the the jumper
thing cuz it makes you it makes you
dizzy oh it's getting worse oh
boy thank you very much for the redirect
Shi hope you guys had
fun oh goodness I'm very dizzy
my inner ear ah I didn't I didn't even
know people can see like this I'm seeing
different dimensions I'm I'm losing
it oh shoot that's a bad time for a
zombie to see me at least it's about to
be morning nice morning yeah the morning
looks good yeah so we have a little more
time to
prepare um we got to really fortify our
home I feel for the first night oh we're
actually close by everybody oh nice if
you look on the map like everybody is
kind of close by the trader yeah
everybody's doing Traer stuff it would
seem no which is
good and do a barrel roll what's
happening I'm just waiting it out I'm
waiting for it to stop do you have a
timer on it no no there is no
timer maybe that's just you're sick
forever that would be really terrible
honestly maybe I just got to twist over
one more time oh yeah are are you seeing
the if this number gets to 100% does
that turn me into a zombie what number I
don't know what number you're talking
about I have like a icon and a
percentage and it's at 1% right
now oh I don't
know I'm not sure
actually why fix if you die what does
they mean are we sure this isn't just a
bug you guys
oh I am here I at the trader okay me
too it's a bug this is a bug for sure oh
God that's a
feature I can help you with the bug oh
yeah how would that would you kill me
thank
you big up speo thank you I Don't Want
to Waste My Bullets appreciate
it me out of my oh they got it flipped
oh thank God that was killing me now biu
killed me thank you bio you're
welcome big up she's the bug
squasher thank you so much for squashing
the bugs you're welcome oh let's see
where on Earth is my backpack oh there
it is it's up here oh his his stuff is
open all right wonder what quest how
much money we have
oh yeah we completed a quest before
right so we must have a little
bit I want the shotgun Messiah magazine
before the rush but it might be tough to
get all that money oh it's it's these
coin thingies I only have 10 dang wow
that's rough he really does not pay a
lot of money huh how I empty your
pockets let's see would you want to do
like a clear Zombies one that's close by
yeah if you want job for me you better
not F this up or I'll cut you godamn
throat take a look but don't expect me
to hold your hand through it I have no
money all right well let's do this your
ass right out of my
store Quest is started let's do
it if we're together we can surely get
them and I got my
gun they're going down this guy is zero
chill oh there we go
there's
beautiful let's do it I hope I can find
more shotgun shells before the rush
tomorrow are we going to the oh it's
that both at the same place okay yep
let's go let's
go let's go it's really not that far
thankfully we should do these closer
Quests for
sure yeah
did I spend my skill points mhm I've
been spending them I might have like one
left over try and spend it
again okay I have a question for you
yeah can you tell me the entire history
of Warhammer lore right now no
impossible you watched all of it
impossible it's not possible wa give me
give me a 30 second summary okay um the
year is 40 is 40,000 uh um
and and before that even before 30,000
there was this dude he's the emperor and
he's like savior of all mankind and
stuff like that um and then they use the
emperor's DNA to make like a bunch of
other dudes called primar and they're
like the emperor's sons and then those
Primark DNA I think the genan seed or
whatever is used to make the Space
Marines and then and then some of the
primarch though they they turn bad they
like go bad because uh one of the prim
marks named Horus he gets all corrupted
by like these chaos gods and the emperor
goes yo what what what the f what the
beep is wrong with you Horus you are my
favorite child and Horus is like f you
Dad um and so then they fight um and
stuff like that and Horus nearly kills
the emperor um but then uh the emperor
kind of like sacrifices like All Flesh
and stuff like that to put a stop to
Horus and then disintegrates his Spirit
um and so so then Horus is like Gone
Forever he's super dead like he's the
most super dead out of all of them he's
the most dead ever yeah and then they
put the emperor on a throne on a Golden
Throne like barely alive because they
need him for space travel and so they
put him on The Golden Throne and he's a
Skeleton Man and they're keeping him
barely alive oh
boy do you guys want to you zombies want
to hear about the war hore I think they
do pretty much I'm new here I still
don't know much about the Warhammer lore
but I'm I'm I'm trying to learn the
basics so so so horse is dead dead but
the emperor is like semi dead yeah I
mean he's he's still alive he's just a
skele man you know like he's
deteriorating and here's the crazy thing
they have to sacrifice a thousand living
Souls a day to keep him alive because
you know my space travel and stuff like
that what that's beeping messed up yeah
it's crazy right but you know space
travel is real important to
him yeah and then uh the there are four
chaos gods and they're they're insane
they're like super crazy dudes and there
are all these other races out in the is
that heresy yes yes anything that has to
do with with chaos Gods you just don't
mess with them or else lest you become a
heretic ah
yeah a thousand psychers yes it's the
psychers specifically it's the psychic
ones that have the brain power they big
brains oh wow I really I really can't
believe I missed that thank you
why why can't they just get a new
emperor for space travel cuz he's the
chosen one he a lot of high me you
understand he's special he's
special he's just special
yes we love the emperor don't speak such
heresy no bab that's
heresy he's also crazy powerful uhoh
here come more oh shoot this gu but he's
dead isn't he no he's not really dead
he's he's aive alive but just barely
alive is the
problem he's like alive enough to do the
space travel and such wow really maybe
if I hit him in the head he could have
[Applause]
died are you kidding me I need help call
your aim this is why I hate shooting
zombies cuz they they move so
erratically lead your
shots oh you got a shotgun all you got
to do is get
close all right I got one of them he's
dead can get that guy yeah I think we're
really close I think it's in here oh we
did we did we you got a
parkour oh
h o nice popping pills sealed shipping
crate medical supplies medical journal
and painkiller
an
owam ooh I found hobo stew shotgun
Messiah Volume 7 and I got some 9 mm
I'll give to you here's the 9 M
mm hold up uh drop H here's some shotgun
shells thank
you I'm going to read shotgun Messiah oh
can we break this crate might be able to
there might be stuff in here yay shotgun
let's see
uh watch where you swing in that thing
oh search lab equipment oh it's just
yucky paper and Stu and such oh we need
we need the polymers though oh is that
the quest that's for uh that's for the
thing to water true for the water
catcher all right I guess we completed
the quest we can go back
now okay how do we go out maybe we just
follow the oh that's a really good
question maybe we should H let's just go
back where we came okay I think that's
going to be the better way all right
poor parkour Hardcore
Parkour okay continuing okay Emperor is
semi alive but they got to keep him
alive yeah he's a skelan so a thousand
psychers bioo a thousand and those are
people that are tapped into the warp the
warp is like this this it's basically
space hill it's kind of like um an astal
plane sort of where like all these
horrific space demons
they're these they're psychic people
that like tap into the warp with their
powers and and stuff I don't know the
details but they're connected to the
warp you know they're they're super like
cool psychics and yeah they're connected
to space hell in their minds their
brains they connected to the space hell
space Wizards okay space Wizards yeah
yeah space Wizards and then they
sacrifice a thousand of them a day bi
boo oh did we not start the quest no we
did I got the quest is done for me oh
maybe because I took it again oops maybe
we have to start your quest we can do it
again right press e to start money not
available until
8:52 oh okay let's turn it in then 852
oh yeah you're right let's let's just go
back I don't want to do that Quest again
let's do some new Quest
yeah all right so
War day what happens when they run out
of warp people cuz that's a lot of warp
they don't they don't run out of them
what how they keep making them I don't
know Deb beats can you guys answer are
they like breeding psychers and Mass to
sacrifice to the the emperor cuz I feel
like that's something they do in the
Warhammer
Universe I feel like they would breed
psychers just to sacrifice to the
emperor like that would be the smart
thing to do right they have millions
ofers are R there are trillions in the
Galaxy but but that's a lot to day yeah
mankind has a lot of people not but the
Imperium of man is millions of worlds
bio millions millions of Worlds the
Imperium of man humans are in the
trillion bajillion it's the year
40K okay bajillion trillion people they
just gather them poor people but space
travel people space travel we have to
travel in
space but like what if you're picked
because then then you just get how do
they pick them I'm not really sure how
they picked them but you know you should
be honored to serve the emperor in such
a way psychers are rare among the
populace though yeah see here's the
thing though bi the emperor dies no more
warp travel no more no more fast space
travel and you know what that means all
the planets that have that have people
and different like things and beings on
them all across the Galaxy gajillion
trillion light years away from each
other they get cut off from each other
they become
barbarians so but that's still the price
of people oh look it's colon AR I mean
yeah but you sacrifice a thousand of
people a day so so that trillions upon
trillions can continue living every
day she's been fully indoctrinated look
I'm just I'm just telling the
facts can I get my reward please not
bringing counterfeit money in here are
you I'll take the crafting
magazine I don't really like any of
these rewards to be I'd rather get
money do you want to go say say hi to
crony and R and see what they're up to M
this time yeah let's go hang with here
just get the [\h__\h] out of here oh wow
that f word was real big when he said
that let's go jump in there we see
okay hello there Travelers hello oh
hello you guys doing some quests are you
CL in yeah yeah you want to CL
together heck yeah
cool let's go he says he doesn't have
any any quests right now
though oh it it says the same for me but
then I joined uh like in the crony's
party it shows the
quest in my list as well so maybe if we
make one
party oh we can share the quest yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah let's do it woo okay
I'm going to invite you then
cool
uh people and well you better get your
ass to crack a book cuz you're dumber
than
dirt
okay
um I have to leave the party first uh
can you invite me one more time of
course oh God it's so
expensive okay I'm in Lori I think you
have to leave your party as well so
leave it yeah yeah okay how do you leave
oops uh so click on the party icon and
try to click on leave okay I players oh
NOP I'm not in a party right now oh let
me TR invite
again
yeah I got I got a quest just now as
well oh yeah Quest started got Quest
started okay okay I see them dumb ass
stumbling into my shop what's the matter
can't find you click on your
quest see like of my [\h__\h] you're paying
double you hungry or something why won't
he let me see his inventory take a look
at the [\h__\h] I got but don't expect me to
cook it for you are youed again I don't
know what's going on that's fine let's
make more money together and then maybe
I'll try and buy something okay you got
about 30 minutes after all so let's do
something hi together
okay do something together shall we we
shall ladies ladies let's
gooo I guess we're going this
way is this a clear Mission we're going
to kill
zombies heck yeah oh I love that let's
go oh yeah I finally found a cooking
grill so I can make grilled corn what is
this like Tick Tock boom
effect I don't know what you're talking
about you hear something strange
wait uh my can you kill me first because
I have very little health and I'll do it
I'll do it I'll do it all right
VI you sound oddly excited about that
she's a murderous type tell you what oh
can you kill me actually I'm also low
okay yeah I'll do it thank
you awesome this is why Friendly Fire is
on friends it's very helpful sharing is
caring sharing is is scaring you don't
need to kill me though I'm good I'm good
really yeah I'm good although I could be
at full
health think about
it yeah know you could be at 100 HP yeah
you know go ahead take me out grony take
me out back together yeah bash me what's
your what's your health right now
68 okay get 69 thank
you um my ladies I can always trust them
I can always count on
them now I understand why you guys were
killing each other it all makes sense
now
yeah we were doing it out of Good
Intentions oh wow how sweet what a what
a kind world we live
in all righty on my way
back yay oh are you guys doing a little
handstands together making a little
human to totem
pole it's very cool yeah can I join oh
maybe I can join it's a little difficult
with three
people but I bet it's possible oh why
don't you jump on me and then you jump
on people oh good idea oh yeah oh yeah
oh okay here I go oh that was an awesome
idea now look we're
three can I can I jump with you guys on
can you
oh it t it kind ofit let me try
Okay no look at us effing around when we
have a freaking Quest going
on can't be helped can't be
helped also oh there's apparently an exp
debt from dying actually so you got to
be careful oh what does that mean pretty
sure that you have to get a certain
amount of exp Before You Can level up
again but I don't know if they took that
off for our server oh hm I hope so we'll
have to
see they might not have only after level
six okay yeah be careful after level six
you take a
penalty it's you lose XP on WE level
three yeah be fine wait how can I check
my
level press Tab and go to your character
oh okay thank
you all right we're here
here yeah it's in the mines the mushroom
Mining Company get my gun
ready for some
reason okay oh we here oh yes ladies
time to go oh y okay I'm ready I too am
ready let's
go let's
go let's go
happened e it's like a blood big blood
bag bursting yeah it's like gushers yeah
didn't we just do this one people yeah
we did just do I guess we be careful be
careful be careful watch
out what
[Applause]
out yeah killing only
my yeah hell yeah be careful to don't
die because I think you're going to fail
the quest yeah don't die if you die you
fail the quest it's very bad ow oh nice
one okay oh there's still another
one yeah good job
ladies now the next team yeah what the
heck where do we go next down here bble
knows the
way uhoh it's
crawling he's oh
mushrooms oh my oh no I need to repair
my by Bon stick hold up I love
mushrooms oh whoops oh
Yik good job
team lots of shies around
here we Harvest them oh yeah mus cook
make a
mushroom uh oh here's another
boy another boy Mario actually doesn't
like mushrooms so anyway
what are you talking about oh no nothing
nothing oh yeah four people this is no
problem Mario the guy doesn't like
mushrooms watch out there's two over
here Mario doesn't like mushrooms oh I
mean I guess that makes sense because he
keeps like killing the people yeah it
says so in the Mario movie yeah he's
like I hate
these
ow Friendly Fire I some shotgun parts
for you you can have them really thank
you
peopleo
yeah that's best to play with a team cuz
we can help each other with the things
that we all want to individually so you
know it's nice
yeah oh I guess we can go up from
here wait
what there's a ladder there's a
ladder wait oh get those mushrooms for
our Roto bio
okay
uh-oh
sorry little bit of Friendly Fire oh do
what we got to do it's okay my vision's
blurry oh I'm losing blood alive wait
what the
heck no it's okay it's okay
people you get that band I got an
achievement for killing killing 10
zombies shut nice get the goodies ladies
wait wait for me a splint oh I don't
think there's anything oh we got to
destroy this one this one gives you
Goods you think so yeah this one you got
to break
it o ni motor Tool
Part pears oh there's a lot of shotgun
ammo here really oh yes thank you oh
these do armor parts I'll just keep
collecting
them thank you
y good job everybody we completed the
quest
y let's get the F out of
here
ow please don't hurt each other
ladies I'm on my last leg oh God
it's okay we'll be fine there should be
no zombies on the way out it's not night
time yet or even close so we'll be okay
yay please I want to go down the hole
okay there we go nice job L first oh yes
okay wow I'm a
lady that's
right just just ignore my giant beard
and bald hat
yeah it's just a look right now you know
it's the highest fashion at the moment
for a high class
lady let's go get some money let's go
get our rewards yeah I I want to get the
I want to I hope I can get the magazin
to learn the
workbench workstation oh yeah that' be
very
useful I'm looking for it maybe the
reason I can't accept any more quests is
because I already accepted this Quest I
want to do it one more time Quest
already probably I don't know how to no
I didn't Quest
either I know why do you guys see the
Arrow return to Trader now yeah it says
to go to the trader so let's go say
Quest exclamation mark yeah but I think
we did the the quest anyway let's go to
the Traer yeah let's just go back trust
the proc yeah yeah yeah
yeah it's cool it's cool place of
interest is on cool down oh top right
okay gotcha daily limits to Quest oh a a
I see can't have us getting too strong
too
fast guess it makes sense o wood all the
wood we got to really fortify our base
tomorrow before the rush that's going to
be the biggest thing we got to do
fortify the be I think the first thing
I'm going to do tomorrow is just cook a
bunch of corn so we just have a big
supply of
food we have com combination of what to
do tomorrow yeah so there's going to be
a rush I think that we need to stay at
the house that we've already established
and fortify it so try and just protect
it as much as we can gather as much ammo
as possible and pray we don't
die ton of SP TR it starts an hour
earlier correct yes okay hour earli oh
okay okay thank you for letting me know
no problem an hour early I thought it
was an hour
later no it's an hour earlier so that uh
Ki and Cecilia can join a little
easier but you can you can join whenever
you want it's just that's when the
server will open for okie dokie you
think you're pretty smart now don't
you pay
Einstein wow it's really not a lot of
stuff in here tools digest what's
that harvesting tool yeah I need
that do we
do I can pick a
got the clear zombie maybe or fetch what
is fetch I don't know we tried to do
fetch but we died before we could figure
out was okay I do clear
zombie water cooler oo large pipes
Plumbing fixtures appliances ooh a real
stove to cook on maybe
someday okay might be nice okay nice get
a
beer okay
I'm going to hold on to my
money there's nothing I want right now
we already have all this
stuff wow he cursed at me yeah he's
really
mean a mean guy you say that so
casually guy he's just a mean
guy s off shotgun mod schematic that'd
be really
awesome well
need a little more
money who wanted to be a farmer did you
want to be a farmer next time all right
here I'm Dr this for you oh thank you
what's
that oh a farming book
oh yay I've unlocked tier one cotton we
can grow
cotton stone tools quality
too oh nice three out of 20
[Music]
yay a paint brush
nice I got two points
available
Lu lter is
good okay I'll get this one
then o Harvest more crops that's big
this is also big pain
tolerance
healing need them now this is also
big pack mu nah I'm just going to make
pockets all right that's nice skills Yay
good job do we have time for another
quest uh what
time what time is it Clos and a little
over 15
minutes I think we can do it though
didn't take too long yeah I just can't I
can't collect any more quests sadly oh I
have another Quest okay let's do
yours it's
uh to
clear you want to follow me heck yeah I
do okay okay let's go let's go it's not
too far right no it's like 600 M away we
that's not bad yeah yeah all right let's
do
it yes for
survival what kind of weapons are you
guys using I'm using the bow I like it
oh do you want bow crafting The Archers
I have you have it it's okay I forgive I
forgive you for being an Archer hey here
you go very nice of you thank you's got
she's really Scavenging she's got all
the goodies yeah yeah I'm picking I'm
picking the crafting books as rewards
nice so we can up our skills smart can
someone kill me oh sure you're not level
six right I live yeah no I'm
not okay I will give you an honorable
death oh wait a gun would be a waste of
ammo
okay it's a good point
nice sick thank you I'd love to be able
to punch zombies in the face yeah but
I'm more of like a club girl more of a a
shotgun
girl what's wrong with archers well when
you're far away and you're trying to
attack them and they shoot you with
arrows and then all their dudes fly
forward with big swords and there's a
freaking archer in the back it's like
you got to aim for the Archer first you
know I don't like archers I'm sorry I'm
sorry I'm just really not an Archer fan
oh but I like archers why why do you
when you play a game and an Archer is
like after you I have ammo oh and
they're in the way back of the pack and
they send all their buddies forward with
their swords you're cool with
that yeah as long as I'm on you know
their side oh well yeah if we're on the
same side that's one thing
but isn't this the same one we just
did is it is it yeah is it
oh or is it one further that way
out of range and we fail that's not true
they're all right here well let's go
toward the one you have R which is over
there the one the one the
ra
has this way is a different place it's
over
here follow me girls follow me oh a
trailer you think we can eliminate the
stuff in
there look at that cool trailer
try goodies are in there
oh this would be a nice place there's
nothing there's nothing
here wait wait for me I'm a little bit
behind it's okay I'm behind the trailer
the trailer doesn't matter wait I'm also
behind oh yeah it's here it's here I
think we're all behind right now I got
distracted by the Traer cumber so I
might be a little slower that's okay we
got to make Pockets wait no the quest is
actually over
here what yeah it's the orange
exclamation point right it's over
there
what follow
me wait no I'm in the wrong group what
the
heck it's another ar oh yeah these are
different people yeah I was like they
all look the same so I was confused oh I
probably made it there I'm going to wait
here for you guys where are you guys at
oh
uh over here this way this way yeah yeah
yeah yeah where is this way oh you guys
were with uh who else is there is that
oh
Kiara and is fauna with them I
think I wait for you guys here yeah
we're just chilling here all good they
fell for the same group that's really
funny oh that's why they said hi
ah you got confused with other people so
[Laughter]
silly that's
okay keep an eye out for bird nest for
Mass producing arrows oh yeah if you
like if you like to shoot uh arrows as
an Archer just keep your eye open for
for bird nests cuz they've got all the
feathers in them yeah yeah get yeah yeah
yeah I will take any 9
mm I will take all your shotgun shells
to
[Music]
guy oh this should be pretty easy The
Smoke House all right I'm ready we got
to smoke them out oh yeah I'm going to
hit him in the head this time I promise
guys I promise let's smoke them
yep oh yeah I think we're all here I
think yeah I'm I'm I'm I'm looking here
are you wait where are you oh there you
are we're up here there we go Quest
marks yeah right here yes exactly do
it yay time to clean maybe we got to get
him to get
angry they walking around getting all up
in their stuff up in their Turf
maybe oo ooh there's a crate in here
search wooden crate oh there we go there
they're the red points on I'll take
everything and show you Wast
Treasures oh R Points on the map there
zombie Birds oh okay oh boy hello
grandpa yeah head shot Frank oh boy oh
oh not the
birds get the okay nice o what's
this o that was very scary
nice there should be another one
yeah there's there's one in the tent I
think oh this one maybe oh this one yeah
yeah this gu this gu ammo pile pipe
shotgun I found some 99 mm bullets B
will give you oh thank you CH uh sorry
which which weapons are you using I'm
using pistol so I need 9 mm okay if I
find I'll give you o is that some corn I
have bullet k
bio I found home cooking weekly oh that
would be useful yeah
oo also a five shotgun here if you guys
want I already have one so I'm good but
thank you let me dump some
trash hobo stew no okay we're done with
the quest by the way vehicles
throw that throw
that hey bi boo where are you come here
I'm behind you okay right here so you
don't get confused with the other items
this is for you uh let's see some 9 M
and here's cooking thank you here's a
trick I harvesting more lead and Brass
from
St I can make I can make tea now we can
have my tea yay tea like Wasteland
Treasures Volume
7 I I know I think it's about
constructing things does anybody like
building
stuff building stuff any Builders
here oh is it pipe shot level two oh
wait what is it a better one oh we get
honey from this this is awesome a where
by chance did you find the shotgun from
before from the quest oh did you get it
as a reward yeah you get to choose which
weapon you get to have oh heck yeah
that's what I need to get oh there is a
pipe shotgun in here oh where'd you find
it B uh here in the tent
yeah on this armor pile or yeah ammo
pile is it level two it is level
two okay well I'll grab
done that
repair there we go wow I didn't know
there were different
levels
interesting okay well we'll hold on to
shotgun so we can give them to maybe
people that don't have weapons tomorrow
during the big raid yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay IDE nice job everybody let's see if
we can clear this uh Quest back to the
TR team yeah let's go back to the
trader good job team we did it we save
the city good job yay yay
y
y got to find a more reliable way to get
ammo though for sure yeah
yeah if we can craft it that would be
good oh surely there's a recipe
somewhere icraft ammo you just got to
find the magazine for the specific type
of
ammo yep it' be nice to be able to have
a forge yeah maybe we can build one
though there should be some time maybe
tomorrow oh apparently you make shotgun
ammo with paper so I guess C watch
paper I didn't know that I just threw
some paper out of my inventory dang
it oh well we'll get him next
time oh we have some paper like at the
main base oh yeah let's go yeah paper
and what else I wonder maybe we need the
recipe for
it yeah well we'll see I wonder like if
there is a fastest way to uh Craft um
sorry to raise your Pawn
for the skill tree like maybe farming
zombies is a good
way that that's to level up your stats
stats but like for like skills like
crafting um and unlocking crafting like
recipes that's
magazines yeah what about um the
challenges though the daily challenges
or not daily challenges not dailies but
if you press y all those challenges
there yeah if you complete them you also
get exp for your skill trees
well spamming spamming these quests seem
good too because these these quests have
uh magazines as
rewards
yeah quests are the best that's the
that's the thing to remember is quests
are the
best especially if you want to to do
Friends by the way like I think doing
quests with part is way easier yeah oh
way easier f way easier to level up I
think at least what didn't we agree your
first job was going to be free damn
gunpowder I'm finally here
yeah what the hell do you want this
time just taking a
look what you got big hitters I could
use that for my club wielding I want
magazines okay so I got
gunpowder I got gunpowder I got we're
gonna have paper eventually and then
pellets I wonder if he has pellets ooh
trip wires trip wire post that could be
good nerd
outfit
yeah let's
see get the job
on I'm almost interest in shotgun
bullets oh I'm level four W congrats
does anybody here needs bullet casing
this definitely give you
diarrhea not yet but I feel like we'll
need it if we were to craft
ammo yeah going to get some
bandages I got tomorrow cooking weekly
cooking magazine B Bo if you need oh
okay I drop it
here I wanted to give him a present
you're going to give him a
present wait no that guy
sucks I I met I met the other Squad
oh but I think they're a little bit
weary of me because I pointed guns at
them
understandable do you have
any I'm getting lots of lots of ammo
stuff I wonder when we can make ammo
though that's going to be big yeah
that'll change the game did you drop the
thing oh yeah I here it's here one of
them is just trash though don't get
knuckle wraps for punching bullet casing
just in case it can be used to make
bullets oh yeah yeah I have the
inventory full that's why I had to put
it
there playay soil good job everyone
today good job you guys did awesome oh
yeah we got a we only have about 4
minutes left but good job
everybody yeah
you guys are doing
great it's very fun s that nice getting
some good
money P PCH P PCH PCH very excited to
continue playing with you guys
yeah well I'll see I'll see I'll catch
you guys on the flip side then know
whenever everybody's
right see you guys tomorrow okay see you
guys tomorrow see you guys tomorrow
bye-bye
everybody
[Applause]
[Music]
you
by again it's like no you hang up no you
hang up no you hang up well I'm going to
head out of the server so that the time
doesn't continue on but we made progress
today we made progress and that progress
being we learned how to play the game
we learned how to play the game we
learned the basics I know that it was
only about four or so is hours but it
feels like we learned so much so huzzah
for new members Kell yes new members we
have a bunch of new members too thank
you guys so much for joining oh my God I
have to post members things immediately
after this is done my apologies again
for that I'm very sorry as soon as the
stream is over I am I am I have a couple
I have an hour until I have to go to the
my doctor's appoint
I had to make a doctor's appointment
yeah because there was a cold snap and
uh the dry the dry air made me cough a
bunch at night and my lung pain
increased severely so I'm going to the
doctor uh for another x-ray we'll see
what happens um cutting it close you
know anyway uh better to be safe than
sorry no humidifier I eventually did
turn on the humidifier but I had to wake
up at like 3:00 a.m. and go grab it from
the storage room and bring it all the
way back up and then reload it with
water it was very
annoying but the good news is um doctors
exist yay maybe not always the best of
news for grim reapers but for this Grim
Reaper thank goodness um as for what's
going on uh every time that I stream
this I am going to be playing sometimes
at nights but at nights I won't be
streaming that's Nights jst by the way
so like K CC time I'll be playing at
that time to help them out but I
probably will not be streaming um but I
will stream pretty much every day I
think um and then I might do an extra
stream after those streams so please
stay tuned for those and uh yeah
everybody Take Care thank you so much
for joining us on our adventure very
excited to see where it leads us next um
and yeah we'll see what happens but I
hope you guys have a great time very
excited to continue this Saga and
survive against the zombies together
with friends it's going to be great I'll
see you guys around thank you so much
bye everybody take care
pizza pizza pizza