[Music]
thank you
this is
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
hey hello everybody
[Music]
uh apologize that first of all I had to
change the stream game because
[Music]
um reasons let's not get too deep into
it because there is behind the scenes
things that happen and yeah uh but hey
look dug out
with great monitor from the last time I
used it was like a year ago
nice for Halloween yeah and currently
it's going Doki Doki because of the
person right next to me
why
am I ever are you saying I I scare you
[Music]
I mean
come on
tell me who you are my beautiful verb
okay I am
um the wife of the beautiful
takanashikiwawa the volume from hololive
[Music]
sitting on a train
yes I called Elena to support me
originally because when we were gonna
play Fatal Frame or when I said I want
to play Fail for him I was so Elena
played it before and really likes Fatal
Frame what do you like so much about
Fatal Frame
ah I don't know good graphics
I think it's like also because of the
lore like basically the story there's a
uh it's always very like Japanese
rituals and stuff like that yeah and I'm
like a sucker for that too so it's
really interesting the story I would
recommend okay well maybe we can't play
it today but surely enough for time
yeah yeah I love dragging out horror
games even after Halloween yeah yeah
yeah yeah
it's on the Halloween after party yeah
yeah
but yeah I I was gonna like
um
just you know play Wii U version in case
the PC version could not happen but then
I don't know on my way my Wii shop there
was only a test version and then the
other one was Project zero two so Fatal
Frame two and that one I needed some
equipment that I didn't have apparently
so I'm sorry guys I tried but here we
are with the mortuary assistant which
somehow was the game that came to my
mind when I was thinking what else
should I play hopefully I will not
regret it
it's all right you'll be fine I also
played this game before yeah you were
supported by Kobo right yes yes yes yes
and now did she support you well
I guess so a little bit misleading at
some at times but mostly was all right
who was more scared
um she wasn't scared I know I think oh I
was scared at the beginning because I
didn't know what to do but then as soon
as I got the hang of stuff it's no
longer very scary I guess oh so you can
do it okay
well in my mind I I saw a little bit of
this game in
um someone else's stream uh a certain
fairy and for me this looks like or it
it seems like uh it's basically a scary
uh surgery simulator to me
it was fun it's like a management game
okay okay
says it will be fine but my chat was
very worried about me so we'll see how
it goes and also my my heart rate people
say it's healthy but the currently
currently around 70 is like where it
usually is when I'm feeling okay I guess
so keep that as a reference I guess it
probably will not go over like 120 or so
I don't know I don't think it will go
very high but that doesn't
matter okay I could jump scared by
literally like Mario games I
I remember when you don't know this
probably but when I played Minecraft
um for the first time like in the first
couple of streams I got jump scared when
my pickaxe or so would break from The
Sound oh my God I know oh my God that's
relatable though you know listen like
ice cream more in Minecraft than any
other legit horror game it really is the
true horror game you're fine you're fine
[Laughter]
okay that's um
convincing wrong against horror games
and then you you crumble when it's about
Minecraft what
I mean technically it's because you know
there's Zen loss you know Zen loss is
scary but in higher games
in most horror games there's no Zen lost
you know if you die you revive that's it
you know
so you'll be fine the most terrifying of
them all okay so then you see the screen
right yep I do okay Lauren is watching
it in real time on Discord
um yeah well let's let's let's have you
played Atlas before
um yes I have which one is more
um
I think Outlast is more scary and at
first when you don't understand what's
going on but of course Atlas has more
action right did you finish out last no
but I got pregnant
oh okay but I mean technically in
Outlets you have to like run away and
stuff right so that's where the scary
part comes from like this one you don't
need to do that okay okay
um start though
um
no wait George we're just doing surgery
or something like that on dead people so
it's okay it's okay
okay and there's no need to be scared
right it's not scary sounds like saying
no you didn't congratulations
in Connecticut
there's nothing disturbing about it
she's pretty I'm proud of you
I really am
what there's story in this game
a pretty much I don't even I didn't even
remember anymore told me what's next
will you get a job it's too quiet for
always sorry guys I actually have
everyone they need but my old teacher Mr
Delver sounds a little bit like crony
finalized
well that's good yeah imagine it with
her face where is he located are you
moving away from me what no this could
be Fatal Frame it has pretty girls
around here yeah it's like Fatal Frame
but not Japanese take some screenshots
and then it's basically the same game I
know I've heard things
it's a little bit different though
there's no think of stories do you know
the ghost in Fatal Frame they're like
very pretty I mean Chad says they're
pretty like girls yeah
sorry
I have no idea but is that her mom to
give you this I guess so
mommy like basically she's like changing
jobs and moving out and stuff like that
you know
oh [\h__\h] what is that I I don't know if I
want that why just take it please
it should be yours anyway is it cursed
is it from her dead uh father or husband
or I don't know I mean coming from the
mom I think it should be reverse cursed
like this brings you blessings hopefully
when is all this happening when do you
start
I've actually been there for a few weeks
now
I will use tomorrow
[Applause]
quiet for you
you probably hear it differently
oh no no I hear it just fine okay
okay
it's from her grandma dead father you
guys say different things wait what the
[\h__\h] suddenly the game changed uh screen
size what the [\h__\h]
yeah
it's huge and my extreme is lagging
because of it
oh okay what the [\h__\h]
why is it suddenly so sweet bigger than
one monitor why did it holy crap what it
changed what it was on uh like y'all
people behave no spoilers did your mom
not teach you no spoilers
uh what did I have it on I think uh yeah
um
I had it on
[Music]
why the [\h__\h] did that do that okay okay
uh resume me
what's going on can I move no
oh
hello there all right shitty assistant
oh girl protagonist yeah
oh wow I already forgot that the
protagonist is a girl oh look at me I
guess it would make sense see coffee is
that coffee coffee oh [\h__\h] oh do I have
to hold that oh it seems like yeah a
Simulator game like those simulators
okay oh pretty oh God ah I wish it could
stand like this forever
oh the Halloween decorations are gone
without played this it was October and
they had Halloween decorations it was
you know it was pretty festive why am I
here
why am I it's your job okay okay so
she's really a mortuary assistant okay
okay yeah she is it's okay um you will
receive guidance don't worry do I take
these reports or what what is this
used to sign paperwork left on the door
uh-huh
what what what what what quick inventory
access quick inventory and choose the
item you wish to use most but not all
places where items can be used will cost
you but well I don't understand anything
um okay so just close it and then okay
if you click right Mouse button
see that's the pencil and then you can
choose the pencil ah thank you okay what
about this
can I take this
no okay why can't I can pick this up
Rebecca is Rebecca one last thing I
forgot to give to you please grab a
pencil from my desk inside thanks Joey
good luck yep okay
where do I sign
you just paper
and where did I sign
that paper the highlighted one
I'll choose the pancake I can't use that
here she can't use it right here
[Music]
mm-hmm
yeah
decoration this seems
[Music]
differently music to my ears
wow yet Rebecca
please wheel them back to Cold Stone
I hate you
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
did I already go to wall over 100.
wait wait wait wait wait what I can't
see your heart oh my God 100 that's nice
it's nothing
[Laughter]
[Music]
moving the deceased use the gurney by
standing behind it and pressing the
gurney it's called a gurney Gurney
Gurney okay and then walk backwards with
the granny down the hall okay oh God I
have tears in my eyes
what move the gurney here yes you see
you see that's highlighted yeah
[Applause]
see don't worry I get jump scared but it
sounds a lot as well
hey
cold sore to bring about it in or out of
Cold Storage open
the bay with the body's name pull out
the rack then move the card over like
everything I'm reading does not enter my
brain
okay okay it's okay it's just tutorial
okay to bring the body in or out of the
cold storage yeah basically yeah
whatever it's okay you can brute force
it
uh where is okay and then yeah see it's
like that is that guy also Dalton
and then you you arrange it so somewhat
it'll it somewhat lines how do I turn it
right
I don't know uh
I can't really I feel like it'll
eventually snap or something okay
go in
go in uh was something of a left Mouse
button right
open oh no open that
go in Sir Mr what's your name
okay uh Oswald I think yeah okay uh yes
yes left Mouse yeah and uh it's also
pretty difficult to turn stuff uh so
yeah that's all right why it needs to
line up a little bit it really can only
go straight that's unusual
you in
parallel park it said someone in the
chat okay
I feel like a parallel
sorry guys I can't play this game wow
that's a wow
going
that pull who can rotate it how oh wait
oh
no you can't uh you have to like
manually do it yeah
yeah yeah yeah really a little key I'm
rotating it yeah yeah like that like
that isn't it so shitty like
shitty
yeah you have to do it like that
I guess it's realistic maybe maybe a
gurney cannot be like uh turned easily
yeah I guess it's like heavy or what
okay and now go in
left Mouse button or what I don't know
uh
[\h__\h]
go in
pull out the rack
thank you ah what what left left Mouse
button left Mouse button
I've moved a little bit oh is are you in
the way now Mr dolphin
is he in the way
huh
how do I
what what
I understand the controls on this game
hold it I'm holding it
I'm trying to drag it out
huh grab not good oh wait now why is it
only like step by step
is it because he's in the way like I
have no idea I was doing it but I hold
and walk
oh my God oh my God okay okay you don't
remember this part
I did I did everything with Instinct and
it all worked out okay okay okay okay
okay uh oh okay Dorothy page oh God
she's already in there how long has she
been in there okay do we close this now
[Music]
I wonder
the lady from the thumbnail
okay nice to meet you uh
oh okay okay okay nothing's nothing is
scary so far yeah nothing scary at all
no no no no no it's not scary not scary
yeah wow you put the you you close the
door back and stuff like I never do that
well professional
fashion obviously yeah so we're bringing
her to the middle yeah over here to the
table yep
okay use the granny you're gonna rotate
again turn turn turn turn
turn okay okay okay
I mean for a dead person I gotta say she
has a good body I don't know how much
body changes after being dead and how
long she's been dead but it doesn't look
too bad
I think that's because they all right
toward her in the cold storage right so
why don't you grab the clipboard and
start recording identifying marks
is I would feel much better about that
oh
okay clipboard useful forms and keeping
track of Mortuary test large item okay
so clipboard aha don't repeat page 87
wow okay one two seven years old
I want to look like this with m87
oh
in the cold storage
[Laughter]
between the body like not bad another
I mean okay so uh she has something on
her right shoulder what is that I guess
a wound from being shot how do I Mark
that
way
um so you I just so you click the bar
yeah
okay yeah the game does pretty a pretty
good job like with the tutorials what is
that
what is that
I don't know a snake bite actually I
don't know yeah like some condition well
it's like something that's smoking why
is she smoking because if she has a
smoking hot bunny
smoking where
I see some smoking from like
like here oh oh I see it and I think
it's just because she's cold
these old windows never stay loud what
the [\h__\h] man as long as you're still
here I'm good okay okay you want the
Elena and the guy or as long as you're
here all is okay okay well I think
besides that
she looks fine to me oh wait no what is
that
that's I don't know
you can see the clipboard and then it
will list all the stuff oh by the way
that's not smoke I think that's like if
something's in there there's something
down there Colossus
I'm gonna look that up
uh Google what is keratolysis
um pittance characterizes a bacterial
infection that affects the skin on your
feet the condition causes a foul or the
lower and itchiness you're most at risk
if you have sweaty feet and wear shoes
that don't offer adequate airflow
did you die from that what
oh no she didn't take care of her feet
enough and something called a a Hammond
gloma what it's hard to read that yeah I
don't know I can't read that either okay
I think she's done
now don't look at that
[Music]
um
no she's not done yeah will the game
tell me when I'm done looking at her
what about the face you haven't checked
out her face well it's a creepy as [\h__\h]
God
she looks okay can we turn it so like
like 360 did I see the back completely
360. yeah though you can see the back
you can see the back she's dead already
so yeah you can you can 360.
what that looks at everything okay good
well what about the right stuff you have
look at everything
a three out of five what
let me just see I mean her face looks
fine to me but I guess I'll just point
on her eyes because they freaked me out
no okay no no no what about the other
shoulder
okay I thought
normal skin problems when you're 87 but
apparently that's a thing here that's
still a thing not really it looks I mean
I've seen 87 year old people who have
that on their skin so okay maybe I
should let them know they should go to
the hospital otherwise they will die
apparently
okay okay okay okay okay okay uh well I
mean
maybe her feet
no not I want to see the back of her
feet
okay maybe the back of this hand
maybe yeah okay ah there we go we got
some pimples some blisters on her hand
great climb on anything and put
everything into the red
don't forget to take the print out his
voice is really loud yeah
acoustics what did you say I wasn't
listening I was listening to her Dana
what did you say nothing important [\h__\h]
I oh shoot yeah I think like what did he
say what what's he saying what did he
tell us to do chat
oh oh maybe we can talk to him again PC
I'll go to the computer I'm gonna input
the data basically and put the data of
the patient why does he have such a like
creepy
screen thingy huh
okay he's staring at us in
disappointment
I didn't say anything
thank you you all right did you hear
that
in my ear so that'll die sorry
piece of [\h__\h] well even if I die he
doesn't know I'm a phoenix so I don't
give a [\h__\h] if I die
yeah
okay that work how to to enter cadaver
information click the record system icon
to open the program uh-huh um Master
sections on your clipboard to the
corresponding sections on the computer
this feels like I'm really working a
proper job this is
see I told you you'll be fine
once all findings have been entered into
the system click submit to print out
embalming records then file the records
up front to begin the embalming and
balming is like putting some cream on
the dead body or what
huh
yeah it's just like putting putting in
all the data and making it like okay
submitting the report because there's a
German word
um oh okay and I thought it was like
like lip balm you know putting some
balls all over them but I don't know
okay okay
don't you like like put some stuff on
them
yeah yeah embalming stuff lip balm Maybe
not maybe nice okay okay uh
you click from the paper
huh
uh-huh Dorothy pay yes ah this is crazy
fun yeah head has arrested this is
really just a rash I was saying like
that's just normal but okay
uh hemangioma
is on the right shoulder yeah and
keratolysis is on the right arm
s
on the left arm that was pimples man
keratolysis on the left leg there we go
yes
okay
it's so loud he's like turning it down
[Music]
oh yeah
does he even blink
it doesn't even breathe
he's like
eyeing you make sure you don't mess up I
think he meant himself when he said
you'll die okay
I left the printer over there eh
it's showing you the way oh when I come
back he's probably gone huh oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] okay just go fast just go fast just
go fast okay okay
and then you put the report there
ah
huh yes with the clipboard
I have no idea oh no you print first you
print the thing
first after doing the report you have to
print the thing in the computer I
thought I printed that I heard a
printing sound
I grabbed the paper ah there it is uh
okay okay that's the thing that's the
mistake I made because like I haven't
grabbed the printer and the game is
already showing Footprints and I'm like
wait what am I supposed to do okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
we're fine we're fine we'll diesel but
we're very very here put that in uh
time to end
it's embalming time
okay and now
and now you go back
shut everything out so you can just go
ahead and get started I'll be monitoring
everything's on your list there if you
need it um
my clipboard oh oh yeah
yeah no that's the real business
okay interesting we we have to start by
wiring her jaw shot so she doesn't talk
when she's sleeping like who wants to
walk past the grave and hear someone
talk you know that's [\h__\h] freaky okay
uh
wait with what
needle needle injector and settings
needles I
guess
[Laughter]
uh how do I know what is what what is
what what was this needle injector There
It Is We're hammering setting needle
barbs into the skull terrifying
absolutely terrifying okay take it
okay and what the uh is this maybe no
that's a Trope nope oh [\h__\h] why do I
press that
uh what about this PVC tubing
uh
uh is this Flex bag hold anything else
what
yeah see you're yeah okay that's
interesting
you're only able to carry two large
items of the ones
okay well where do I put it
um I suggest you drop the tube because
you don't need it
um
if an item can be dropped a drop button
will appear ah okay
drop
okay
okay and I forgot what was the other
thing
no we don't need this not that one
setting needles that one yep okay you
need
oh God
pull the manipulator up and press the
injector button to drive barbs into the
skull then twist wires to shut the jaw
you should try it's pretty therapeutic
what the [\h__\h] what do you mean I should
try it on myself
on in the game wait what's happening
ah
oh I can't use that here I can't use
that here I don't know what I'm doing
yeah you um you click I think yeah
yeah what if she still we shouldn't be
doing it
well you know
you know man
well she's definitely
be very happy when she wakes up after we
do this
oh okay
um
if my mom's watching this it's just
gonna make her not go to the dentist
she's she has a trauma and this does not
make it better oh it's closed yay yeah
yeah
okay number one done yay
okay nice uh insert eye caps to keep
eyes shut
Oh eye caps eye caps this thing oh
useful yes yes hello
can we put that on my face because I
don't want to look at anything Lena you
can look at stuff and you tell me what
to do okay placing eye caps use the
manipulator to open the eyelid
completely interact with the eye to
place the cap then close the eye cool
thank you Nina okay
um done
no you're not I am what why why does it
you
you use the eye cap oh I didn't I didn't
come okay apparently I thought I picked
it up ah I have to press e okay okay
that's freaking yeah all right
but like a sleeping mask on top of her
eyes
why why do you have to put something
under the lids
it's so they look nice I don't know
actually
so they don't open so it looks nice make
some bombing fluid in the pump glue oh
yeah like cooking blah blah methanol
humic tent
formaldehyde what is this a tank yeah it
looks like it oh you put all four stuff
all of this okay
hmm
sometimes we get chemicals that haven't
been stopped and it can make them pop
like that real [\h__\h] just keep doing your
thing
I hate you
oh my God
I can't hold anything else ah [\h__\h] you
yeah yeah you just pour like two
that's not it I'm sorry
is it thrown away then the bottle I
guess so yeah it's like one time use
[Music]
my tent whatever that is glue Tara lit
dehyde
uh-huh
and
formaldehyde oh wait no see
huh
you should store that [\h__\h] properly so
it doesn't [\h__\h] pop you [\h__\h]
and now now and now
okay make an incision in the car camera
artery and jugular vein with scalpel
okay yeah what the [\h__\h] where is that
there we go
okay now we're playing doctor you need
the you need the tube as well oh tube
this PVC tube
okay where exactly
I think so uh in the the neck maybe ah
oh four steps four steps you need four
steps as well look at that do you have
forceps four four no
four four steps four steps forceps
forceps there you go there it is yep for
ah the tiny the scissors are forceps
okay
never heard of that it looks like four
yeah looks like the beauty scissors so
we're gonna cut her throat
yep what's first forceps name no I can't
use that here I can't use that here
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
she's like becoming like
I don't know with tubes in her body it
gives me like anime vibes
I don't know why
okay okay okay I did that I think oh wow
easy engage pump and let the body drain
yup go go
painting with you do it do it drain the
body yeah yeah yeah you can do it let's
go
pump it up pump it up
did you do it no I'm engaging
uh wait sorry engage
congratulations you are now engaged
oh [\h__\h] what you're draining the blood
yes yes yes
wow I'll send that blood to Meadow
senpai
I think you'll appreciate that how long
does she even drink blood
she's a vampire okay okay
you're good
there's still some stuff coming but it's
not really red anymore
I think it's okay
okay turn off pump remove tubes close
incision okay
okay do I have to do this all by heart
next time or do I still have those on
the clipboard is still there don't worry
okay
that
uh fill an empty IV Reservoir bag with
cavity fluid and insert Trail car into
the abdominal cavity
what okay
I saw that
oh that was cute though that was cute
kind of cute some something cute
watching me
uh I think we need this
and
there
um what else
uh cavity fluid and Trail Clark troll
car we already have why do I press that
but we don't need this uh you don't need
it yet what is this other thing we need
I guess maybe here cavity fluid okay
mm-hmm
that's not the bag
okay okay
feeling body cavities insert troll car
until it stops to begin the flow of
unbounding
fluid and are you making those sounds
I think you made some sounds you're
freaking me out
oh sorry I was just adjusting myself in
the okay
I'm playing a sound sensitive game here
you know that so
fine I'll be quiet
once the cavity is full pull the choke
our back rotated rotate and then
reinsert until there is okay I'll just
do whatever
hello
rotate right and what oh
it's kind of like an HP bar if you look
at it like an HP bar it becomes more
entertaining
okay
I thought she was already you know empty
and drained
well then she needs to be empty on the
inside as well okay
oh no more here a bit oh
really
there we go oh it's telling me to go
there is that really okay
mix cleaners in bathroom closets to
create tank cleaner then pour into the
embalming pool okay okay okay
jump scare coming in three two one
no no we're good okay uh
okay you pick that pick one of those
and you fill it with that one
yeah fill it yes that's it once you
check it it already becomes tank cleaner
whatever it was
yeah okay okay cleaner
yeah it was a little bit confusing
because there's like no prompt or
anything okay but yeah you just do it
like that
oh you're filling her up I see
okay
okay okay okay okay okay
uh pour into the embalming pop okay was
it just pop
this thing right
was it this thing
yes yes
four that's to clean it
okay
a little bit noisy
conversation or something because like
it's freaking now he's like looking at
you
[Music]
why can't we just talk
Ed
it sounded like a dork was closing or so
okay
um apply moisturize let's see I told you
yeah they need some more information
okay turn off the lamp I mean not the
lamp the AC okay
um mm-hmm
the moisture
moisture oh move the wipe across facial
features while holding down it to
interact until the lotion is usable okay
yeah that's what I'm talking about why
only on
but not scary
they're moisturized it was not really
working for some reason it's not good
for her skin oh
are you sure I just got here
don't worry you're doing great I'll get
the last of your paperwork sorted today
call you in for your first shift okay
okay expect the moisturizer I feel like
the expiration date is
over
bye bye
go ahead it's fine
I'll give you a call when we get someone
in oh okay but my list is not completed
yeah it's all right and he's offering
you to go home and you ignore you do you
mean you take that yeah I'll gladly go
home yeah chance yeah oh yeah
foreign
[Music]
well okay that wasn't so bad oh it's
fine oh really weird my home so some
stuff fell over that's not a big deal no
I know it wasn't even my fault but he
sent me home right after that
I'm just really worried he was supposed
to finalize my stuff today it's a cool
apartment
yeah
it just didn't feel like he meant it
like he just said it to get me out of
the building mm-hmm I feel like he has
you know that kind of fetish oh hi
Michelle look if I did anything wrong he
wanted to kiss the dead body
to leave
yeah it's like yeah you've seen enough
I'll take care from here
oh
come on three new bodies
oh love it yeah are you sure I mean of
course
nervous laughter
okay I took care of the rest
of the longest
okay okay I'm so excited wow I'm on my
way right now I hope you feel better why
why does she suddenly feel not good is
one of the bodies his own hmm holy [\h__\h]
that was him he signed me oh she's so
excited he needs me to come in tonight
wow can you be so excited about this it
was fine congratulations
congratulations like right now I'll talk
to you later I guess it would be way
more like happy go lucky if it wasn't a
setting like in Scrubs
there's like this dude what's his name
he always like he was he was really
useless as a normal
um uh doctor so they moved him to the oh
to the mortuary place and he seems to
have a lot of fun down there I guess I
can't a fun job maybe
I mean when when there's no um Shady
things
um do we bring oh did we bring anything
besides my peas
hmm that's a tiny apartment but I like
it it's kind of fast like the the size
of a Japanese one-room apartment and
also it's kind of built like the same
way
yeah like the kitchen and stuff I'm
gonna look inside the bathroom
you can I like this one okay rent enough
for the bathroom this is so fancy like
this this wall I I like this wall
are you stalling
[Music]
let's go yay
wait
wait exciting we're driving to work in
the middle of the night why can't we do
this during the day man
I have to drive oh no we're done driving
driving would have been fun
It's Raining Men
Hallelujah It's Raining Men
Let's Get It Started there's no more
there's no Halloween decoration yeah oh
foreign
I need help someone's outside the
mortuary huh how does she know I didn't
yeah me too I didn't see
what this is very sudden oh
I guess there's something there sorry
see actually
let alone
oh
look this isn't funny stop
hey
I'll just leave I'll just [\h__\h] leave
okay
what am I supposed to do then
most bodies
it just so happens
staying focused stay focused stay
focused okay
oh
I mean normal and chill
this is so stupid I'm just amazing that
was probably him though calling me from
outside trying to Spook me play along
and do your job he's just he's just you
know teasing me okay Rebecca okay we
have a tape recorder
what do we need a tape recorder for if
it is not for recording our last words
before we die
and some keys okay
Kiara okay
and that's pretty much it and we what
was it again we take like one of these
things or no no first I guess we just
know we just open this
with the hulky
don't be scared right now there's
nothing to be scared about
mm-hmm
[\h__\h] quitting tomorrow
wow what a change in Attitude yeah
he's like she's like Yay oh yeah yeah
[Music]
hello
yeah I'm sorry but this entire thing is
extremely unprofessional if this is how
you treat new hires I don't think I can
work for you this isn't funny
he's the only way to say
a demon before
that is the Damon
notated Psy I wish I
wish is the demon in the dead bodies or
this is the one outside how do I get him
and maybe offer him like a coffee or
yeah so there's like a cassette tape
there
phones
yeah no like after this we can't trust
the phone
you're in the Demon's name join the
correct body
I'm sorry yes
insane oh man
professional one grab a body and get
started
okay there's several tips oh
mini cassette tape as well because
number one night shift system
okay leg shift database
yeah I mean this is interesting most
important
it's important
[Music]
or look it up
you can listen while you're doing your
job oh okay
come back
okay
okay okay okay okay okay this one's done
we can listen to the next one
I mean number three the process of
possession oh I skipped one
yeah so don't take too long
time time restriction
I'm not really time restriction but
yeah I would if I were you I would just
like try to quickly get things done
[Music]
yeah it is time technically what is the
thing
again
[Music]
listen you first first there's the
there's the train looking thing right
okay you drag it and then get the dead
body start working
some sit-ups why
pick it up and start putting the dead
body on there and oh
[Music]
okay
I'm here we're turning in which one do
you want to take first does it matter no
it doesn't really matter um I don't know
I do it systematically but yeah
um
it's okay you can do it you can do it
oh
yes and you put it there
so he's smiling it's very nice
Mal
that's crazy
stay calm stay calm as long as you do
your job properly you'll be fine
[Music]
you know what see like the more you
panic the worse you will do
[Music]
baby
let's check you out okay checking you
out okay
um you don't look so bad you died really
early I suppose where's the the like the
here there we go yeah there it is
at least I can keep track of things but
do we maybe want to close the doors sure
do it
okay
she's so scared she's making me nervous
as well
scared
hello
hi what's up man lay down
I'm getting out of here
no oh there's like another tape
oh and remember okay
okay number two where is number two yeah
and then that will be all the YouTube I
think
it must be bad
and that's what the pizza oven is for
three objects
three options entertainment okay do this
I'm getting back to work
who ghost hell yeah
oh wait he got some scratches on his
chat uh uh uh uh cheekbones
oh wait I'll have to go closer
to this cheeks what happened there did
you get attacked by like a wolf or what
a cat to meow
wow he owns a cat perhaps
oh
did his cat kill him
oh my God
did I look at this yeah I did
uh what about here
that looks fun
oh I feel like I saw everything oh wait
no here oh
and something on the other side
um
there we go oh there it is okay
okay put the data oh yeah in the PC 29
damn
that's too early to die
record system Curtis Leach
29. it's mild abrasion
Hemangioma on the left [\h__\h] on the left
shoulder okay
uh blemishes on the right arm blemishes
on the right leg blemishes on the left
leg
why are you not been putting it what oh
yeah good question why does that not
work left leg oh that's that's there
okay
it's kind of acting weird okay
there we go okay
[Music]
yay and I see you I see you you print it
I'll have to bring this to the other
room again right
I need to file the copy up front
don't worry Rebecca I'm scared no no
need to be scared no
[Music]
um
the thing is
um every person's experience playing
this is different hmm
so just because I played it it doesn't
mean I know what's gonna happen okay you
know
so I'm just as nervous as you the
difference is you know I've played it
before so at least like the procedure
and stuff
la la
I'm sorry what's next
uh why are Joshua okay
uh
the stuff is not where it was yesterday
it's not where it was yesterday so you
have to memorize them as fast as you can
I guess like the faster you do it the
better
what no oh and did you notice like it
says something else in the um
yeah see every agent in the old cabinet
don't forget to put that
okay why does she
[Music]
why does she uh settings needles okay
okay setting
ignore yeah it's just the wind it's fine
um
just like the faster you go the less
yeah okay the the longer you take the
scarier it gets so it's kind of like oh
I have to get this job done before the
demon gets me kind of thing you know can
the demon get me
[Music]
I don't know that's why I tried doing it
so fast because man I don't want to get
scared
yeah
that's why it's okay if you do your job
properly it won't get to you where if
anything it's the best motivation for
your job
[Music]
if you don't want them to get you just
work faster
[Music]
can't be nice I'm sorry
I think those are the eye cups yeah okay
okay yeah you can do it I'm not scared
I'm not scared it's all right it's all
right it's all right it's okay
uh got it oh there we go Open the Eyes
First
oh there it's it's okay
oh there we go okay yeah right
there we go okay okay
fluid
I think uh one of them was probably this
one
is that you make tent I think I think
that was one of them
okay
ignore it it's nothing it's nothing it's
just some fun sounds okay
the reagent don't forget later
okay
and they're usually if they're not in
the same there may be inside the cabinet
okay formal behind
[Music]
I should go back to playing Luigi's
Mansion
uh yeah isn't that horror as well isn't
that like dealing with ghosts so scary
you don't even know but the thing is
like I actually did get like one or two
jump scares from that so oh really yeah
but it's not so bad obviously okay okay
[Music]
oh what's that oh
it's event it's event it's event how do
I how do I live no no no you you have to
go there no you can't hide you just have
to go it's uh you have to watch it
oh my God I never saw this event
[Laughter]
yeah I guess so maybe I don't know
[Music]
oh it's gone it's okay look
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh no it's not there
[\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
with everything bleaching that's not it
no
I took this
take that
hmm
maybe a top cabinet did you check the
top cabinets oh there's the cabinets on
top it's not only under no on the right
on right
ah in there oh
that's it oh and then before mixing
don't forget to add the reagent okay
reagent in the old yeah in the old
cabinet is that one that one I suppose
baleful reagent a bottle of onion liquid
used to identify a demonic tendency
yeah exactly so we will know whether or
not he's a demon or not yes yes okay
um
oh make an incision in the Carotid
artery yeah yeah okay with a scalpel
scalpel I saw that I think in here oops
okay and I think that was around the the
net did you did you turn on the machine
oh yeah oh you didn't I think I have to
do this first yeah you have to put that
first my bad no problem
huh huh what's that that sounded so
friendly
but like really friendly was like uh I
already died please or something like
that that's what I heard
not ignore it nah ignore it nothing okay
uh four steps to clamp tubing okay
uh what is this
another car for the stomach
when you know everything by heart
forceps this one yeah and I was
concentrating so hard when I was playing
this game
um oh wait is this the tubes no flex bag
oh God oh God oh God
check the bottom shelves if you haven't
the bottom shelves are you in here
yeah here and there oh God it's hard to
see
it's so dark okay maybe it's like on the
other side
on the uh not not that one
here but already looked here no uh on
the other side right across that
ah there ah there's the tubes okay
okay let's let's put that right in there
no yep forceps ew and
okay Thunder you can't get me this time
I'm nothing because I'm scared by you
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
at some point you need to access this
and then
there's a code and the code is like you
you should technically listen to the
tape
but oh
I did did he say it yeah the code is
like in his card or something the card
is like in the other cabinet oh okay
okay
turn up front remove okay okay
I'm just like waiting for the next jump
scare you know
it's can't come soon enough ah save two
got cut off
okay we should re-listen to tape too
a good color
can I listen to it again
here
yeah
the objects in this cabinet
okay yeah
is that just we usually boards Stones
it's called
oh
my smaller piece
oh wow second
and then you know this was such a
phasmophobia kind of game
yeah it is that's why uh
I never saw this part of the game before
I only saw like the the surgery part
yeah
and you see that paper grab it when
you're like doing nothing and walking
around you should do it you should like
always bring it grab what
there's like a paper
once you are certain the demons in the
old cabinet wait something's happening
oh yeah
I think it's okay
it's complicated
[Music]
foreign
open the door
yeah open the door and like look for it
okay and then it'll eventually explode
revealing a sign
calm down
okay and then nearby there there should
be like maybe behind the door or
whatever uh
and near the the dead people door
okay see there's a symbol
that looks like a hiragana mall right
like remember you're gone
huh
you don't see me anymore is my room gone
or is it just you gone
um I don't know over here I see you
okay yeah first you put it there she's
a cheater
it's okay
it's not okay
and so it's okay I will just leave that
here now right yeah for just for now
leave it
yes
remember if you're out of just do your
job and remember if you're if you need
to wander somewhere oh bring the strip
okay uh fill an empty IV Reservoir bag
with cavity fluid and an intro car okay
uh bag okay I have um I think the bags I
saw them somewhere okay okay
you need the troll car right yeah I
think
um that was this this thing yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh my God
oh my gosh what what what what
I hear something but I don't know what
it is that's just rain oh my God
[Music]
it's the flex pack that yeah okay and
um cavity fluid okay
um
then you can turn off the echo you're
back to life now
okay
oh yeah yeah suck it suck it suck suck
second one
I'm coming I think we're like reverse
sucking we're like throwing up the fluid
also some demons tried to talk to me I
didn't hear him though nah ignore it we
just keep on
one side like did you watch
like did you watch the anime like music
if you if you ignore the ghost they will
realize you can't see them and they will
like leave you alone okay
okay that's good and sounds good
okay uh and then in the bathroom oh God
we have to go to the you need to mix
cleaner okay don't forget to yeah okay
okay
we'll use the letting strip yep okay
uh wait what am I bring am I bringing
something mix oh do I have it yeah it's
clean yeah yeah it's there it's there in
the other room okay
yeah it's gonna Burn yeah yes yes yes
yes yes yes it's gonna burn
I'm gonna be oh it's not there that
means okay
but I did it I think yeah you did it
maybe check the tank cleaner yeah tank
cleaner okay
okay there so where is it look around
look around
oh here ah there it is it's like a g
like a g okay capital G very effective
very effective Lena
um let me put that in there and then we
can dial it's like an old phone you can
like turn there it is
this one right look at that yep it's
that one okay wonderful beautiful
um
and then pour that into the embalming
cup
yep
uh
uh apply moisturizer oh I didn't take
off that first thing yet but I guess I
just have to wait
go look around a little bit more here I
think um while we are waiting I think
you should check out the you know to
access the night shift program the
program with the passport the password
oh okay uh yeah
yeah you need a password that's why you
need in one of the tapes it said that
you have to get his ID the password is
on his ID
in one of the cabinets like on the left
side there the one that you don't check
out
that you haven't checked out yet this
one yeah Raymond All Access
no ignore ignore it ignore it
doesn't have a number though
okay maybe check the other one
limited X
or maybe it's on the Note maybe it's
you can rotate the card I think
oh
yeah oh oh yeah yeah
okay I have to stay on it okay three
zero two one three four three zero two
one three four three zero two one three
four three zero two one three four three
zero two one three four three zero two
one three zero two one three four
excellent okay what is this
yes
have the banishment
do we do something with this now
um yeah technically uh look at the top
right there's like categories
oopsie uh see yeah yeah that that
identifying demonic tendency I saw my
text
where's the tldr
what is this
it loads so long what if it's hunting me
and I'm like about to die and then I'll
die because it loaded too long
[Music]
yeah oh okay well anyway there's
different marks to identify different
ghosts so you have to identify the ghost
s
first it doesn't finish the body or
um
play with the little wipes
I saw them
saw them before whoa whoa what it was
just a door opening calm down Elena
hmm I think like
my sound thing is being weird or I don't
know if it's like this chord
is the game sound too loud
no the game of sound is like kind of
like crackling a little bit now it
doesn't really matter that's why I was
like kind of surprised even though maybe
on your end there's like nothing I
finish the body
nice should I bring another one of the
thingies
even though I'm going to the same place
yes
I already have one of those oh I still
have it oh my God hold on okay um I
think I should like get out and then get
back in okay
this sounds
can I hold it while I'm moving this oh
nice multitasking
such a professional
hey dude you're done you're going to
afterlife now I hope it's Heaven not
hell
uh oh yeah we turn you
ourselves close they look open
oh they must be closed
the door closed oh yeah
guys
that's an automatically closing door
probably don't yeah technology
technology yeah
I mean those really like I think they
just
open
oh
yay
[Music]
um but it doesn't react to my letting
strip here that's unfortunate yeah
because the uh the one in here is
already you know
okay
so it was nice getting to know you dude
too bad you died so early but maybe it's
better to not be alive in this world
because it's [\h__\h] up anyway
oh
hey oh
okay and clocked away close it
next is the next Sean Lawrence oh what
kind of name is that
I have like some
older lady again it looks like
maybe here
and here we go
just like an amusement park ride
uh-huh
is this one amusement parks parks in
Indonesia are like
what what do you mean it's not like this
in Austria
we don't really have any cool amusement
parks I guess unfortunately
all right
oh she has like a cute bikini top yeah
no running in the hallways
watching
[Laughter]
I think we're already dead right now
because we can go through doors and
walls
or it's just her I guess
um
oh thank you okay why can't she go
through when I can't
because you're not dead
all right
um
uh
uh first of all she's 85. let's look at
you
got the same marks as everybody else
what's going on with that seems to be uh
an ongoing theme let's see
nothing here
at your face
smiley grandma
[Music]
okay okay
why everybody had the same marks
I don't know because they're the same
species
I'm like oh claw marks it's like um
Everybody owns cats I think there's more
ways to die but it seems like in this
game there's only one way to die
okay uh so put that in the PC okay yes
you're getting it hey
do you see you can check them quickly
later entry two lashon Lawrence what a
name it's kind of cool name but a lot
shot lost shot I've never heard that
before
mm-hmm
bad weather
oh someone was knocking hello no I
ignore it ignore it it is fun it is fun
it's okay left arm there we go I think
that's it
and then we print it
I'm gonna hold this again because I've
gotta go
uh yes okay
um
okay
easy
okay we're starting the whole thing
again
we are wiring the jaw shot was that you
did you say something
oh no I said okay uh we need the the
needle injector and the settings needles
um what was this here needle injector
foreign
[Music]
I forgot where that was again
ah wait this thing oh is it packed in a
package so it doesn't really look like
what I need okay
a little bit close oh her teeth are not
looking as good as the others
you need something she's already dead
it's fine it's pretty old actually I
guess at that age like it might be
pretty normal to have like um fake teeth
you know to put in
what what do I know
maybe I don't know what's normal at that
age I am
from that age
yeah not even close far too old or what
no no no no farty young farts yeah my
skin
very the the peachy peachiest Phoenix in
them
country oh something's happening
something's happening
what's up
oh yeah yeah yeah when like the screen's
like that
is it like hunting or
bro I don't know but it's already gone
like it's so fast
uh uh sorry God I don't remember uh eye
caps
like cups
oh wait they were in here I think
at the bottom yeah
okay I will eventually notice by heart
check sanity what there's seven nah just
do your job it's fine that's just uh
phasmophobia right
if you don't have Saladin
scribble on Notebook
what notepad what what what Notepad
what I don't think I even saw it
the notepad the game has a timer
but doesn't really
I never checked it out
it am I like
um especially slow oh God turn the
lights off they turned the lights off my
Mom I'm Gonna Do My Thing make some
bombing fluid okay yeah just do your job
it's fine just do your job okay boss
two Mac tent
uh not this
gluten gluta glue gluteral black
foreign
[\h__\h] up my home
oh god well that sucks
did this happen to me
the mail
wait no it does I didn't see this I
didn't see this exclusive DLC content
yeah
all right it's gonna start without me
I'm happy with that I don't want to go
to your stupid party
sheesh
what do I do
what am I missing I'm not this is a
dream wake up wake up lady
it's a dream
oh
God what
nice that's adorable
oh
I'm gonna drown in here cool okay swim
swim scream
oh these are oh oh whose body is that oh
someone's
what's my homework
oh my God
this never happened to me what I
remained unfazed I'm so proud I did not
feel scared by that
that does not happen to me
wow oh wow now you see the good stuff
for dinner
so can we turn on the
[Music]
okay I was mixing you know my cocktail
um how's your cocktail yeah is it
methanol alcohol
I don't think that's alcohol we're
making a cocktail
Cali would be so proud
um formaldehyde the last one was um yeah
like I got some events myself but
to be honest my gameplay I don't know I
didn't see that I didn't even know that
there was that unicorn kit
don't forget the radiation she's a girly
girl oh reagent okay okay
this stuff I'm still missing like two of
the stones Lena
how do I get this okay this is like two
body out of three okay did you get it
oopsie I didn't
the second body of the free yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
no
yeah everything's done I have to do I
have to open her up again first okay oh
yeah
and then I remember we need scissors
right and the tubes
wow
[Music]
you're doing great is there ever like a
different procedure or is it always the
same
same procedure
easy then
kind of could get bored with this job
eventually I guess but I won't get bored
if there's demons floating around
already
uh while you're waiting you might want
to check out the night shift article so
just like read about the oh oh yeah
never mind something's happening here
right now okay okay where is it
maybe maybe in the drawers
ah you know your stuff what is that like
a like a letter z
okay
okay I think at this point yeah that one
the Z one oh okay yep at this point you
should look at the night shift website
website
everybody calm down
um oh should I you see like look at them
maybe okay
yeah see you have to decide what name
oh I don't know how maybe it's the other
pages
because they kind of show you like what
what symbol is what demon or something
oh
okay this is not important whatever okay
oh there we go
um
Let's see we have I think yours is
balmet yeah we have I I can I yeah I
think we have the three these three
we're just missing this one so now I
know the name already
um do I call him on the phone or
like hey Bob what's up
wanna maybe come in for your coffee or
chilling outside there this is way
warmer inside or yeah it could just do
your job it's all right and if you need
to walk don't forget to check out the
thing the paper thing what did I do but
do I know the name for then
do you have the paper with you yeah but
what what is the name for
I forgot you burn uh
yeah I need to
and then what you have to do uh and uh
remove tubes okay
oh
[\h__\h] yeah oh yeah and then uh so there's
three bodies you have to basically find
out which body is the demon oh okay I
put the name on the body apparently
uh symbol order ah yeah yeah put the
symbol order on the mark yes yes yes
simple water on the mark Oh you mean
that no no no no no no no no that's for
that's for later that's for later that's
for later let's do your job first it's
fine
um
True Blood
empty bag
well no that wasn't oh my God hi oh my
God
you're shaking maybe you should wear
some clothes do you want me to say hi
who is that naked body people
foreign
oh my God it's just a game
[Applause]
what
oh man he's beating me up
but we're okay we're good
it's just a game see I never got any of
these
I'm getting a special treatment I want
to turn on the light here wait where's
the light
what the [\h__\h] is that I think you should
ignore the weird stuff and just do your
job like Justin just an advice from a
survivor
oh
um
where the [\h__\h] is that to Reservoir bag
okay uh huh yeah if the slower you are
the more like crazy things will happen
oh that's okay that's okay I don't mind
I I think I've come to
um understand that this is just a game
blah blah blah
actually yesterday I went to get a
massage and the lady
massaged my tummy which was really weird
normally when I get massages they don't
do my tummy so that was weird I really
wanted to go to an idol meeting after
that
I also had a massage like probably last
week it was like um I don't know I do a
lot of like dry massages you know so
it's more like about the pressure
instead of yeah there's no like oil or
whatever it's really refreshing just one
hour or something is enough
yeah yeah mine this time they did it
with some
some Aroma oil and I feel like she used
like uh like some pain relieving
um medicine uh like cream or so
because it was tingling on my body and I
think that's like one of those creams I
saw it in their closet so
cleaner
very nice of her to use that
I I got the cleaner
um I did that important to the embalming
pulp okay and then moisturizer and then
we're down
yay oh wait open and
then uh check the other houses why while
you're waiting
the other the other
the other no no no
um remember the types of ghosts there's
different houses houses there's
different categories
remember
you mean on oh my God I don't hear that
I didn't hear that at all see there's
like House of emulation and there's
House of something else
oh
yes okay yeah just like Hogwarts
there's invidious as well
okay
okay okay
it can also be called boss so you need
the other sign okay
uh
all right yeah
can I only get the sign with the letting
strip is that the only way yes that's
the only way okay then okay just do your
job to see your job okay
ignore it ignore it ignore it ignore it
just like do your job do your job okay
yeah it's okay just do your job it's
fine
no no no it's not gonna kill you just do
your job it's fine okay
it's okay
where's the lion oh
that was so loud they
know
yeah it's okay it's okay it's okay
concert
s
[Music]
[\h__\h] dead
push it let's push
and then oh yeah okay
the other body
um next we have German a German person
German a German person oh my God
hi nah whatever ignore it yep ignoring
as long as they don't know you're seeing
so many scares
and they're like oh kiwa's playing again
oh let's give her like the special and
treatment like she wants to have some
fun yeah she's here for the party hey
what's up
it's all right what
suddenly girl okay
of the light please I'm supposed to work
here man yeah the ghosts are very very
you know
so much
what the hell
yeah
I mean not people they like to bother
you so much
so I got a little shortcut I guess so
yeah
oh my gosh they're all they all die
young let me tell you what your problem
is
um the problem is you're German
all right
they're they're mad because you because
because of what you told them no your
poem is your German
[\h__\h]
why
can we make it stop
and when you have nothing I think this
this dude he he's a demon
foreign
I feel like Kiara is not even like that
slow thank you thank you I'm glad you
say that
yeah I mean like okay there we go
okay okay now he's like hurry up
I'm saving me fast you know oh man okay
number three German
Ayers
uh 26 oh that's too early man couldn't
even get into midlife crisis man
characterizes on the right arm a mole
what a mole is like
what I have like moles everywhere no
it's like no man it's just like how to
identify the body you know it's not
really like oh I'm always a problem
you're gonna die because of it no thumbs
up isn't really worthy of writing it
down I guess yeah of course like what if
there's someone that look very similar
but you can't identify it because you
don't know you don't do it at all yeah
okay
the gentlemen you're taking a trip so
don't forget to do the letting strip it
is true
some moles can be bad if they're like
cancerous that's true maybe it was a
cancerous mole that was noticed too late
nose
all right
walk in the park
we need like one last thingy please set
yourself on fire oh wow okay no it's
okay no need to be so actively doing
that okay
uh embalming report oh is there like
something you can get like in the desk
or something people are saying it but
like honestly I don't remember getting
it either
uh I can't take it no
[Music]
um
I can't actually take the thing no fat
on top I don't even know
oh there there's a sticky note or
whatever
um
the Post-it notes here can we just check
how far one has slipped into possession
oh
interesting I never have used that
before where do I look at that oh
does that mean
it looks pretty bad I don't know
oh
they say oh
man
all right all right all right all right
now do your job do your job see this is
why I'm not telling you to take it I
never took it and I was fine
um okay I'm too far but that's [\h__\h]
stressing me out that's not good yeah
it's okay no no don't listen
uh just do your job because whatever
happens your priority is doing your job
okay
um on this thing this thing
better Circle more possessed interesting
okay okay okay
uh and the bunk and the buckling without
you I could never do I'm I'm so glad you
were here it's all right it's all right
do your job and all will be well
I mean you're actually also kind of
stressing me out but
um
I think I need that otherwise I would be
probably stalling a lot yeah no the
thing is I think when you panic you
forget what you have to do kind of I
think yeah not you but like we in
general
so that's I don't know
I'm trying to remind you of the things
thank you
that you might forget oh God
okay eyes
open one and two we're gonna speed run
this now let's go baby
next up
I had a lot of fluids okay okay I think
one of them was this
here put in but what if I'm so by the
ends don't know the last letter and
we're between two names
you will it will show up after you pour
the reagent oh okay nice
all right
hmm take the formal very polite oh
um
oh my God the body is just like you
oh come on
can I continue working
my body is gone yeah and he'll come back
he'll come back yeah I guess he'll come
back it's just like me having this stuff
well you wait for him to come back I
can't okay
um can you please okay I'll follow I
guess
no what I guess we all right fine do I
have to
no letting strip you don't need it yet I
mean it's all right I don't know I'll
see you
[Music]
stop it and I close my eyes oh and you
you said why don't you tell me what's up
why don't you just mix it first
[Music]
oh you can't okay I guess it's a
cutscene what's happening
oh oh look at that look at that look at
that
no no no open your eyes open your eyes
yeah but what the [\h__\h] it's the cutscene
it's cutscene not cutscene technically
but like it's one of those like things
pretty cool I guess wow I also didn't
see this one so at least like everybody
sees different things
it's mine I know that
the floors
open
okay
oh I go back I go back okay
[Music]
no no what the [\h__\h] stop
hi risk I feel like him yeah yeah I'm in
high risk you know you feel like taking
some risks
oh
can't open I can't
yeah that's where I came from
let me out
oh
is this not where where did I come from
I'm lost
yeah I've never seen this before as well
so I'm not iris is here
I read Cyrus hello no I think it's
because we said high risk did I
this is where I came from
a high risk um funny
all right so I went I went that way and
then
um I guess this way I wasn't here before
oh what's that Hills
antidepressant
oh we are taking those yeah it seems so
um oh I can't like take it though I can
only look at it
this is a long cut scene what the [\h__\h] I
feel like I'm lost forever
oh I'll try again
[Music]
why
I can't open this I can't open this the
um this thing I couldn't interact you
put away the strip first oh okay
I'm stuck follow the light oh oh yeah I
guess that's what you do when you're
about to die but yeah the light is here
and
um still
but still locked different light
oh what about here Administration I
promise but then here's also like
oh I need a key for another pill no
that's the same oh that's the same thing
key
oh wait this is a door oh oh oh oh
what's that oh look at that a fridge
keys to the high risk Wing okay I took
them I took them
okay nice nice damn this is pretty like
wow
yeah like I don't know like when you
have time like you can like skim through
my playthrough it's so what
hi who's that
oh I'm playing hide and seek
I just like scooched
yeah by the way is like a crab piece of
crap person
oh that's gonna be oh geez what okay I
mean Rebecca
Rebecca you didn't have to do that no
you had so much like
stuff in your life to do
I thought about how I'm going to write
this over and over paper of the paper
front oil this is quite triggering man
sorry Grandma I tried I really did
please know who you were look at this
herself yeah she sees like her oh my God
Rebecca
oh yeah yeah it's Rebecca yeah
so it's like us it's me yeah imagine
you're seeing yourself like that like oh
you're sitting here holding your coin
right now wondering if I'll ever have
one of my own what would the point even
be even
so what coin
yeah you don't know technically necklace
oh yeah the necklace it was [\h__\h]
cursed five-year coins oh coin sobriety
coin oh is that like when he's sober for
five years I guess that's what that no
maybe
all right um I saw that thank you for
showing me this is like um
that I didn't get that the Christmas
thing goes that shows you your future
and it's very sad a very sad future so
you have to change like how you got to
this point oh wait there's one more
thing
okay well thank you for all these notes
they are very depressing thank you soon
um thank you soon can I go now click the
body oh
oh this one
ten years yes her own sobriety coin okay
when you had a chance
you won
what oh my God okay
oh no she Burns oh that's good that's
good that she burned she can turn into
ashes
we good now
you're nice
um what are we doing oh yeah see the
body's back look
yeah long long cutscene
I got something completely different
ah sorry oopsie uh what are we missing
methanol
what is this that's it I already have
one of those oh [\h__\h] oh yeah right okay
back to work man my boss is gonna be so
mad at me for taking so much time
um what methanol methanol don't forget
the reaction okay thank you
okay
yeah like I got something much more like
less scary and more sad I think
yeah
more sad okay
stupid buttons
what kind of stuff did you get
so I mean it's kind of spoilery I guess
but it's like I don't care she's also
guilty okay
I don't know somehow like she hit a
person's head with a rock
or something I don't know that's
probably like not literal but you know
okay scalpel uh oopsie scalpel and the
scissors and the tubes
I'm just for five minutes I want to be
able to work in Pace for [\h__\h] sake
true true
okay
yeah uh engage pump okay we're ready for
that
and
[Applause]
should I walk around
or
I'm not sure
the body was talking find the lesson
okay okay
[Music]
whoa there we go
hey I'm happy oh yes yes yes look at
that it's a good time oh not there maybe
oh
what is that
oh okay okay in here no I guess maybe
over there by the desk maybe yeah okay
oh there we go
[Music]
there's like like a j oh
okay that's like a j and then like
another thing oh something's happening
okay check check now check now
yep I think my face
hello
I don't know
[Music]
yes it's not cool I don't know it's the
the other one we had the other house
yeah okay let's see let's preacher ah
[\h__\h] that's wrong wrong one
look at the stomach
oh no no no no ignore them uh check the
bodies oh yeah you need to get the order
right
uh G Mo zet
foreign
order here yes okay first you you you
should trade it with like some random
stuff first no no no no okay
trade it okay
yeah
it's like um Clubhouse game okay 51.
yeah um
[Music]
where's G straight G is still here yeah
yeah okay
I'm gonna take mark
take mark
yes that's the right one okay
okay and then finish your job
oh yeah damn that's it that's the ghost
I'm gonna finish your job okay
[Music]
um
finish your job and then put a happy
ending please
hmm
feeling empty finish your job first
that's that's the point okay
will it let me finish my job
yeah I mean the fun part is doing your
job I'm pretty sure it's not not fun not
fun not fun
um [\h__\h] I'm like uh
uh the back the back the back the flex
back this back I can't hold anything
else
what are you holding you uh oh well I
know that
uh can I put it somewhere
[Music]
I can drop it on the stomach oh I can't
uh I'm missing something you missing
something don't worry just put this is
I'm not finished
my work he's talking to me though
quiet
yeah I mean it's up to you you can
finish your job if you want to
technically if you're so super sure chat
is saying you don't have to but me
personally I don't know I finished my
job okay uh trucker
that's not it
oh it's already full okay
don't be nervous it's fine
sheesh
get in there get in there there's so
many cuts on his body now you
yeah
looks like there's some
some
insects or whatever
inside eating his body from inside yum
why does he have the demon what did he
do
why what does he do to deserve that
oh
to the bathroom
it's a mix okay let's go let's go let's
go let's go let's go let's go let's go
go go go go hurry hurry hurry hurry
hurry not scary not scary not scary oh
oh wait I don't have any more
okay
okay and then you got the tank cleaner
now okay okay okay
it's been actually hey he listened to me
he's been quiet
yeah no it's been like five minutes I
feel like
um four and two and bomb okay
apply moisturizer okay what did I do
that now before I do the other stuff
I'll just try oh no
I have to wait for that okay we have
everything we have the name right it's
like vomit or what was it vomit
[Music]
we have helmet okay
yep
so we're like done I'm gonna make him
super extra moist
all right so when you know yay what the
hell what's happening
oh no
ass
so I burned this [\h__\h] right yeah
back to the normal Place yeah you burn
it in the freaking incinerator
like Rebecca yes stop talking crap ghost
you don't have to train him like all the
way around
I don't know
I was so close to buying like a high
heating Pizza Oven last night because I
found like a pretty cute looking one
like yeah
the thing is though I think like there's
scratches so it has to be the body but
when I was doing this
push it
um
don't I have to like open the door maybe
closer
oh a little bit even
I can't get closer hmm
oh
[Music]
my God yeah it has to I don't know I
forgot push pull it out push it in again
Bravo it doesn't fall it locks in back
it up and then press button
um I can't really help you because I
forgot I don't wanna
I don't wanna lead you to the wrong way
put it in storage First Look Behind
what no wait what was this cremation ah
Ah that's for something else but yeah
no not at this time I'm like finishing
this head first but this is like
um saved like can I like leave the game
and come back and then no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no at
first
really
why is it so picky but the the moving
thingy the touchy thingy is in the front
at the head so no no no no no no no no
no no it wouldn't make sense of his head
first you if you if it's head first you
will get in the incinerator yeah no
don't listen just chance don't listen to
chat my mom just trying out things right
now
okay okay hey I tried that a million
times go go go go go go go go go go
Chad is demons trying to mislead you
[\h__\h] you
[Music]
[\h__\h] you eat that maybe I hope it's the
correct one of course the correct one
it's the only body with like the claw
marks yeah that's
it
I guess oh
okay
wow that'd be talking like that right
yay Oh yay now you
know no touchy
that wasn't so bad it still can be the
wrong one that's what a demon would say
you could Rebecca
[Music]
[\h__\h] Raymond
is it over
but you deserve
you survive what do you mean can I leave
I want to go home you
once an entity finds you all the houses
of Hell will
to get back to you wow
sorry but it doesn't end here damn why
did I sign up for this there was always
a chance this will happen again
no matter where you are it will
literally happen every shift I just want
to leave what do I do
let's try a good ending but there's no
oh there's a bad ending if I put the
wrong person in probably
yeah I'm guessing so
this is definitely easier than
phasmophobia like Investments
not even close
the front line of something larger I
don't do this for some greater good
either face it
or fall to it
I wish I could claim to be someone
better
suffering hell to save us all
but I simply want to live another day
just like everyone else
when I first not something these people
the dead people can say I could not
spend the rest of my days in fear or I
could learn to face it
like acting as if he's doing us a favor
yeah
yeah you're the one
I was so true nebul but choosing between
a life of fear or control
hi hi you're the first person I've met
to face this hell and survive
oh your other assistants all died is
that the thing damn work the night shift
but I know
yourself a chance and a life
it's not
Fair
I don't know what you experienced but I
know it uses the worst parts of you
against yourself I want to experience
the more you'll confront the darkest
parts of your life
but through it
you'll become unbreakable bad ending he
didn't die I'm offering what
there's an ending where he's offering
you the tools
tools yes I've got all the tools
I am the tool
she's the tool well he's a tool oh hey I
was never possessed I wonder how does it
were you ever possessed Elena how is I
think like I think possessed is just if
you lose you will be possessed hmm oh
technically this is like
you can continue like so many days and
then there's multiple endings but this
is just like
um basically new shift C shift two shift
three I only played one shift oh because
I thought I didn't want to play it again
yeah because it's scary I I'm I'm happy
to play it once so because I when I saw
it you know from other people I felt
low-key interested like more than like
Outlast because like Outlast
horror games where I have to run like
that's just doesn't make me happy at all
but this is okay at some point I was
able to completely like be unfazed by
the things that were happening
[Music]
wasn't so bad also thanks to Dana for
being here you made it quite a bit
better and you helped me understand the
game see it's like you know I'm very
strict I'm the top that's gonna be like
if you panic like no like remember your
responsibility do your job it might not
be the kind of instructor or assistant
you want but it's the one you need
[Music]
you know
Chihuahua you know the important thing
the most important thing for me is that
you make it out alive you know sweet
that's the most important true that yeah
I will be nice to you after we survive
well okay I'm sorry again guys for not
playing Fatal Frame today we'll figure
it out and and probably play it another
time maybe not next week because like
okay
so many horror games in a row that's not
my style
but eventually we'll play Halo frame too
I promise okay and uh yeah that's pretty
much it I think that's enough two hours
of Mortuary assistance I think
satisfying pleasing enough
yeah
um tomorrow
uh I'm playing ah that new Portal game
that's not portal but if you guys like
portal you should watch me play it
because I'm also giving out free game
codes tomorrow for that
um so if you like portal I'll see you
there
um uh and
yeah
I'm sure Peace Center yeah
you should play portal it's fun oh I
actually did I played one and two
when
like quite a while back I think on
stream
on stream on stream
did you like it yeah
I did I did I did I like two better than
one though because one made me a little
bit motion sick oh well well well Elena
um this might interest it too there's a
new game that's unrelated to portal but
obviously very inspired by portal and
looks like portal coming out or it came
out today or so and I'm playing it
tomorrow and oh no you could get it too
for free
interesting oh
[Music]
Elena did not play Portal 2 single
player oh you only oh yeah only for
portal 2. yo you should play the single
player
go go
maybe maybe I could I could I could I
had a blast with that portal art was a
good Arc
[Music]
okay well thank you for staying up so
late for me
[Music]
no problem
everybody subscribe to Adina her channel
is in the description and subscribe to
me
subscribe to the Quran turn on the
notification Bell the Subscribe button
leave a like and write a comment
also stream for blood yay yay
[Music]
I listen to it and holy [\h__\h] you you two
sound so good together and you know the
the song that it you did it had like so
many like really fast lines right but it
was flowing so nicely both of you did
really great
thank you thank you thank you
yeah
she releases her official cover for four
blood yeah
[Laughter]
everybody and in German we say
I have a perfectly spooky night
everybody
see ya
[Music]
foreign