[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
okay
wow
[Music]
come on
work now yeah
[Music]
sorry I'm talking to my cat
one second
[Music]
hello
that's junkers by the way
[Music]
oh my God hello
hahaha
you know he's on my table now
in front of my camera
oh you're joking
bye bye bye bye
no baby don't go
hello
oh
God uh
it's a Sunday it's a Sunday oh my God
foreign
does this look weird
maybe the other way around
how are you guys doing
and I guess the angle
[Music]
huh you know those people who can eat uh
swords I'm one of them
ah so much for being weak against what
was it still
iron iron I don't give a [\h__\h] about iron
swords sword swallower
I am sort of I don't know how to hold
this knife
here wait does it
um
does this make sense
this makes sense
on this side on this side
does this make sense
maybe don't think too much about it
maybe you have it like this
makes sense
no wait this doesn't make sense
no this doesn't make sense this is this
makes maybe more sense
on it
yeah I can remember it I already
mirrored it um
maybe I turned it too much
maybe more like that
okay
uh PNG
how what about what if I hold two
at once
we're gonna be finishing this game today
by the way
oh I left some weird markings on the
side when I was cutting out though
green stuff no oh well you don't really
see it
I can hold too I'm a dual wielder
how's how's this look though
do I look like a dangerous Kitty
I'm gonna slice you up baby you're gonna
be my dinner tonight
yeah I'm sick of chicken and tuna every
day I want some
human flesh
[Music]
foreign
you should take a look at how sharp my
blades are I sharpened them just for you
so that it won't be too painful
yes
but I'm a chicken eh no humans in here
only chickens
well that's boring I don't want chickens
anymore my owner keeps on giving me
chicken and tuna and beef and all that
[\h__\h] I don't care about that anymore
I am Young
that's a good pun
E
I like that okay that's that's the wield
two two two blades it is these are from
uh CK pun on Twitter thank you yourself
I need to drink some water first of all
[Music]
oh
yes as you can see we have played this
game for 10 hours by now
um it shouldn't take us that much longer
just normal normal length of a stream
today I would say probably I
I think what what could it be four or
five more hours shouldn't be too long
unless I play really really badly today
killer
foreign
I will kill all of Wonderland today
yeah yeah yeah yeah my normal yes yes
this is about six to seven hours
kind of toned it down a little bit I I
checked my my streamlines and I saw my
Tales of arise streams were usually very
very long because I just I just couldn't
stop
um yeah but recently we have been doing
shorter streams
a bit more which I feel like I'm not
myself anymore I feel like I'm an
imposter
ha who Am I who am I I've lost myself
midlife crisis of being in whole life
after one year that's where you start
your midlife crisis as a YouTuber we
wonder you wonder
all right
do I remember how to play this game
do I
oh we're here you're right it's pretty
place
okay uh I see some teeth
a shot uh
uh wait which direction do I go is this
where I came from
yes I guess so
can I destroy this yeah oh my team
okay how to play this game do this how
do I dodge again uh how did I set my dog
oh wait this is the Dodge uh
uh I meant something else uh how do I
make myself small I like that okay
shoot shoot
what was the
uh what was the button to switch the
weapon the how do I get to the teapot
again
oh this is uh something else
ah this is focus
how do I ah you don't hear the game
I was trying to figure out the controls
uh
how
uh how how how how
uh
nothing seems to work
I thought it was the mouse scrolling
on it it doesn't change
oh yeah let me see
configuration
controls
um
I've been pressing R select t-con left T
kind of left shift yeah oh
yes so wait so so so so I've been
pressing R nothing happened ah okay now
what happens all right all right okay
but I was asking for this one actually
so left shift okay remember that game
sound too small really
okay uh
um
[Laughter]
that was too loud
what a bunk Hallelujah
I click into the game and it's
immediately a huge Funk maybe now
wow that's that's also very loud I'll
just lower it here a bit and uh
[Music]
I'm I'm not quite awake I already have
breakfast and stuff but my energy is not
there yet
okay this is
just uh
to wake up to I guess you guys are tired
as well what
oh did this open for us last time and
and they set me back because of the safe
point I think yes
[\h__\h] what happens
wait what happens
something
moves
do I need help probably not
where did I just woke up good morning
oh wait no
why are there so many flowers here
foreign
yeah probably activated some Bridge or
something I don't know
uh
yeah yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
uh R okay what
there's two of them
ah it for this one it shows me what it
does for the other one it doesn't okay
but you want me to wait is that an
invisible Bridge no
[Music]
so
ah I think this one activates the
invisible Bridge
and the other one opens it but how
but now it's closed over there no
then
ah this one starts moving up oh and then
maybe I can enter from the top because
like how would I
be quick enough to activate see
[Music]
hey
how would I be quick enough to activate
both of these buttons so this one goes
down also very quickly
gotta go fast
platform first
then door
[Music]
but by the way how long does uh after I
activate the the platforms how long do
they stay like let's say I don't use a
bomb
see it goes down
and let's say I don't use a pump I go
away and then ah it goes up right away
can I even have two bombs there what the
hell are you going
at the same time
two at the same time
but okay maybe it goes down fairly
slowly okay so I just step on it
and then hope that I can make it in time
okay okay
let's do this
ah
I'm already annoyed
did that work
hey wait wait
yeah but no how can I make it
no no no no no no no no way
hey
[Music]
yes meow
how how
your money to show
[Music]
what
Ah that's so kitty kitty
I
don't oh you let me go back thank you
uh huh
we tried again
so first we activate the platform then
we try our best to move over
okay run run run
I wish she would uh Dodge over to
wherever I'm moving the camera towards
I can't make
[Music]
it
wait wait
[Music]
[Applause]
I made it because of the because I made
myself small okay
okay well that was already
annoying from the get-go
ah okay let's see if we can
uh feel more motivated
later wow
[Music]
what is this place
is that one gonna make me bounce too
yeah
nice okay and now aha
[Music]
uh okay you blow me up
you and then
we put this down but wait wait what what
did I do
oops
but I understand
uh everything
[Music]
what about over there though wait oh
wait wait wait I got distracted
I don't know what I'm doing
I can arrange it anyway though
I can't do it wait
oh hello what is ah
understand though
you guys are really quiet today
[Music]
oops uh no sorry I want to what was it
again shift hello left shift
on it now it's with the wheel at in the
beginning of the stream it didn't work
with the wheel what the hell is going on
uh
oh there you are
Peppa
we're just chilling you're not you're
not allowed to chill
you need to
have fun with me
the shop
something feels really off today
uh
are those
when she jumps like that I just peacock
feathers uh because they're like the
color is like so green and blue and she
looks like peacock feathers
I just realized that now never seen that
before
uh foreign
such a weird level but I like it it's
quiet and it's serene
every time you jump it in a dice
wait
the map is so beautiful it is oh
my God that's like a roller coaster
boy what the [\h__\h]
am I going there okay okay my
oh I couldn't jump
it what is this there's a rumor about
being able to do endless jumping but
apparently it's not true because I can
never do endless jumps
lies it's lies
um
sometimes there's just some weird things
happening and I don't know why it's like
I'm in a in a mystery movie
but they're not called mystery movies
see now I couldn't jump again
one
I did one jump guys
what's the matter
what are we staying
[Music]
um
why why would it leave me
and hi
hi
okay I'll just jump one stand and glide
it's not like it's not like I need to
jump more often I just try to make it
more comfortable for myself I guess
what the hell
it's just a little bit faster
if uh if I can jump more often rather
than gliding
anyway yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I made
it keyboard son my keyboard is really
old I need to get a new keyboard but
um the reason I'm not getting a new
keyboard is because this one I got in
Japan and it has the Japanese oh
that was it
oh oh
it's so dark now I liked it before but
look at that oh look at that new outfit
girl
I like it cute Kawaii
Clothing Design is American McGee's
passion I think
edgy I like the red yeah
red red is my color
yeah so it has the Japanese
um
like letters on it
uh which no I don't think that's simply
getting keycaps would do the trick
because oh what the [\h__\h]
I did a flip
Flip Flip
uh because you have it oh oh yeah I'm
I'm okay well too I can go through this
okay ah I was saying uh
[Music]
because when you use a Japanese keyboard
and stick it to your PC
um then you actually have the oh wait I
can
thought they were
I can't pass for them I can sorry I'm a
bit confused at the moment what the hell
what what
did you see how I was not able to move
forward
I'm confused
um there's on Japanese now it works
on Japanese keyboards uh there is
usually on the top left there's a button
yeah
it hurts there's a button that makes you
switch your input from English oh for
[\h__\h] sake oh for [\h__\h] sake this is a
get them all type of thing
it switches the input from English to
Japanese and uh
uh and now it works what the hell
um yeah so it's kind of like already
programmed that way you can know what I
mean
so getting a normal keyboard you you can
totally install your uh a Japanese like
language pack to a Windows
uh
oh
so the Windows computer and then that
way on the bottom right of your taskbar
you would just have to click every time
you want to change the the language
input
but with the Japanese keyboard and you
don't have to click you could just push
a button and it's so much easier that's
what I'm trying to say
your handiwork returning to the scene of
the crime
said so you'll say
Red Queen cannot both survive oh she is
a cancer in your body
essays her or perish I never heard of
this word excited I only know exercise
you picked up her crown but now you've
put it down you must speak to her what's
left of her anyway
Queensland
oh interesting one I think it could be a
bit louder right
let's cut remove
all right uh wait so the queen is
already dead right
I killed the queen before oh dear
um everything's falling apart as I'm
moving or with the time I want to go
down here
oh
yeah I'm hearing voices
foreign
the first game that happened ah
oh voices is is her ghost haunting me
and what if I go straight
I don't know which way to go
hmm
it goes up
I'll go left again
you can hear the voices too oh well at
least I'm not alone wait did she just
say you're unwanted here I think I
heard the queen saying that
that's rude
I just want to be wanted somewhere I
just wanna feel like I belong somewhere
Queen
please be nice to me I'm a good kitty I
don't eat humans no no no no no never
said such a thing before come on I'm a
good kitty trust me
nice nice platforming takanasikiwawa
what what what
okay uh how to fight I forgot
okay no worries all good all good it was
just a simple warm-up
just a simple warm-up that's what a
monster would say
you know what I learned today in
Desperate Housewives monsters are
created by monsters and I feel like I
yeah yeah I missed something
let me go up no how do I go up
I wanna go home
oh
thank you for showing me that again I
want to go up there though oh can I go
later no
maybe oh
I hear it too
[Music]
I hear the snoot but I can't reach it
from here
well yeah yeah I know I know I want to
go there
maybe I just oh wait wait ah I should go
from here ah
yes yes Alex likes to hiccup every time
she uh
becomes small Alice she does her little
hiccups because she's uh drunk
reassign the jump key why it works but
it just doesn't work always I don't know
if it's like a actual game mechanic or
if it's bugging around
okay and now jump jump
huh the first jump didn't work okay
okay now I was able to do three jumps
jump jump jump jump jump
anyway I got the bottle uh this place I
guess is inaccessible wait there's
another thing up there where the snow
this but the snoot where is this notes
I have yet to find the snoot
um
bouncing off stuff counts as one jump
uh-huh so free jumps
is maximum but some other people I don't
know they said you can jump endlessly
maybe from here aha
oh
kind of a weird angle but
nice meets katayo
okay so from here
thank you have mercy
um
don't worry guys we're just gonna get
back into this
oh gotta find our Vibe again last time I
finish that was really good at it well
huh
why do I have to get it again
wait hey it keeps on loading in here
and I have to get the memory again
okay
fine I guess okay
somehow my uh chest hurts my my the
inside of my
just
don't make it weird guys you know my
problem what it
let's do it right yes yes
you're being like that sometimes yeah
okay okay
oh okay I do support the monarchy in
principle I'm sure the queen is very
good at what she does
but is she not a person just like
ourselves
I
guess I got no problem with that either
can I kill you oh it's already gone
whoa pretty gate
a heart
[\h__\h] nice
is there a secret here
ah it's that those things uh the
endurance uh battles or or it could be
one of those 2D Platformers again
all right
yes thank you I hope it will uh go away
on its own as well
oh challenge hello
cat there you are Alice yes
it is me comes next in the sequence
three four seven eleven
um
let me think
what do you think okay
let me think one free there's two in
between
uh and then plus one is four
and then three
and then four
wait
one and three ah wait I think
I think I think I get it so
um for for the number three
um plus one the number before the three
one
uh
uh three plus one is four and then four
plus three is seven and seven plus four
is it
wait wait wait wait wait can you say can
you ask the question again this is
confusing me this is a two
ah
oh no 11 oh 11. okay okay yeah yeah so
seven plus four is eleven
suddenly it looked like uh those um
Greek numbers to me okay I did kind of
get it right so seven eleven plus seven
is eighteen oh my God smart hello
oh my god wow
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh I didn't even have to fight for that
just had to think a little bit
big brain hours thank you thank you my
brain is intact it's just my my
gaming skills which are not intact today
it hurts
foreign
[Music]
how did I get here on it
ah down here
we'll be fine
oh yeah
is that a chess figure
what what
oh card guard you look a little bit
different from what I I know you as
are you difficult to fight a bit I don't
I don't know how to fight anymore oh
wait that's easy
more
yeah
okay with the hammer it's really easy
though
yeah give it to him
okay okay okay so far very good very
good the hammer is literally rocking
this us
yeah give it to them nice
all dead hey young
[Music]
hard dead Pizza
okay I don't know if that was the
intended way to fight them but it was an
easy way to fight them
I saw the sea thing not there
what what am I seeing I assume well this
figure
is that what I'm looking at that those
are chess figures right that's the the
tower
that's maybe uh
the king
is that the king
that's the horse over there
that's another horse I like that are we
having a chest theme now
the bishop ah oh that was a bishop oh
the red Kingdom's in Ruins but you're no
better off oh is this the king when you
defeated her I tried to reclaim the cost
I was set upon by her monstrosities the
malignant royal [\h__\h]
royal [\h__\h] get inside the only way in
is through me sacrifices must be made oh
those who say so usually mean they
should be made by others cynicism is a
disease it can be cured once inside
Beware of the outsized killer who
patrols her domain never confront him he
is Invincible now cut me loose I'll show
you the meaning of sacrifice I like him
he's like he I don't know something
worried about him the way he acts than I
like
you mean like this oh no
oh so sorry but yeah you sacrificed
yourself so that I can kill your royal
[\h__\h]
oh man
to a computer design exactly that's
literally what we just learned
oh
very pretty
I really like the color red and dark red
with sparkling white princess
oh is this a warning
ah cute oh interesting
oh I'm scared yeah I'm scared
it's gonna be a
tough battle
I like the interior and the architecture
you did a great job Queen
good sense you could help me out with my
apartment perhaps
oh yeah
oh y'all oh dear
oh
we've infiltrated the castle
is that the queen why does her face look
so [\h__\h] up
Panda she has no nose
story will tolerate a book without
pictures when you were a girl I still
don't really tolerate books without
pictures
look you're gonna look closer well who's
who's writing to me
ow oh
sorry just a chit chatting with the next
Holo talk guest
and
should I go here first
can I even go here first I don't think I
can
all right unless
unless this activates something in the
back as well
no it didn't okay
yo yo
you
oh I hear is note
um
where are you
behind no wait I'm scared to go in there
[Music]
yeah there's um not so much choice you
could probably guess it uh on it down
here
no wait there's a
look that tells me probably that there
is a memory down there
is this notes
wait for you
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait one more time I don't
understand where would that bring me is
that just a way back I guess it is
okay well for forget this note for now
unless it's here
all right
eat this
you need to be seasoned oh
oh
okay
uh now I can use that oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
well uh we can think about how to get
back later
[Laughter]
there it is
Abominations in the house it means the
creature's dignity
no idea what you're talking about but
okay how do I get back yeah
I'm fine I'm fine okay
so
we can go down but is this nothing
of Interest no
okay here we have uh two different paths
to go I guess the first one should maybe
be this
little little lag
okay
and then the second one
here we move on
accidentally profession of stuffing
animals
let's
that sounds
so um
peaceful
I think of stuffed animals but you mean
you mean those uh the ones for example
that people hunt and then put on the
walls
ah okay okay okay okay okay
so the job of stuffing them
no no no
yeah that sounds uh disgusting
sounds disgusting
wait where are we going
down
I guess something happened on the other
side
so we do this again
it is disturbing
well
I mean to to uh
what what's the what's the saying again
two uh I forgot what it's
yeah then that's uh so I know
creature on yeah yeah I mean it's
freaking weird but twitched around
uh wait what no no I wanted to someone
said in the chat I could upgrade my
weapon
good idea
I got 842. oh like we can do any of them
hmm the horse or the teapot Cannon what
do you guys think
people do it for their pets sometimes
okay that's a whole different story
though I think
tea plant
okay
difficult well though the teapot oh
is it just strong enough okay what can
it do now
um
on it it doesn't switch the weapon again
I'm scrolling and it doesn't switch
that's it
no way no no it doesn't switch
[\h__\h]
let's not switch
hmm
no left shift was for
the normal one hand
oh no oh
right now I switched it with my mouse
whale now I switched it with left shift
now I switched it with the mouse wheel
but I can't go back to the teapot with
the mouse wheel I can only go to the
teapot with left shift
and I can only go back to the the is
this normal
yeah I feel like last time it was
different I could go to both of them
with uh the scroll wheel
huh
configuration controls
um
what if I do
okay
I can only have one of them okay that's
weird
but what if I just scroll down then
is this not how we had it last time
perhaps
because I'm pretty sure I was able to
just switch freely between both of them
with my mouse well okay whatever
oh
what does it do now
does it have a bit bigger range
oh sure and then
this one I was able to switch with what
with r okay
sorry it's been actually quite some time
yeah but
like
more than a week
have them in flavor I actually really
don't like peppermint flavor also like
chocolate what was it chocolate
chocolate mint chocolate
the one that everyone loves
I don't like it
tastes like toothpaste I don't
understand why you would want to eat
toothpaste ice cream and stuff
earthquake and laughing bunny but wait
on this side there's also something
um
what's down here I know that's where I
came from
that's where I came from right oh my God
my brain my brain hurts
what about Dr Pepper a Dr Pepper what's
with it it doesn't taste like mint or
toothpaste
doesn't taste like it at all
nice
huh this is where we came from
oh oh [\h__\h] uh
no problem I got my strategy for you
Buddies
nice out
can we eat your own people exactly
exactly
my favorite ice cream is like vanilla
chocolate berry kind of things
oh
what
uh executioner
a mix between Cali and Ina is this Cali
and Ina's love child
okay how do I fight you
I'm an idiot don't acute he had a better
chance with his windmills and without
risk of reputation a prudent exit is no
list oh do you like that you like that
what
I feel like it doesn't do anything yeah
I don't see [\h__\h] okay I have a feeling
that
always uh I can't fight him from the
front oh wait no also
if hearts are so no
I can't kill it
you can't find wait what am I supposed
to do what am I supposed to do then
uh wait uh
wait wait for this Hammer Hannah Hannah
[Music]
how would I how was I supposed to know
that normally when you're confronted by
an enemy the choice in this game is
never to run it's always to destroy and
kill everything
how would I know that
the king told me they really
where where will I be running to I want
to establish that beforehand
uh
hello executioner what up uh wait which
way are we going this way this way is
not open right
he had a better chance with his
windmills and without risk of
decapitation oh couldn't exit there's no
less
no no it's open okay I was supposed to
listen or what
I guess we're gonna have a problem too
if stairs are able to hold you back then
I don't know how to work with you
oh my God
excuse me what the [\h__\h] what is this
camera why why am I running can I turn
this camera around no really
apparently I can't what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
what
what are you going to monster there give
me some HP thank you
oh [\h__\h]
is really mad at me
oh God
what is it
God rarely beats his food
well thank you
oh wow thank you what is that bat over
there
is it like kind of leading me the way
snoot yeah I feel like I missed
something I thought this was the path
like the side path but not the main path
but it looks like it's the main path
after all so I want to go back
and I see what I missed
I feel like
when I came out of here and and see yeah
there's a some more stuff here
oh
aha I knew it I felt that something was
off
icer ultimately it's only as good as the
person who really
oh
interesting interesting thought oh is
that a organ I don't know what the name
is in English what was it again
is it though
look at this kind of like a atlas
fantasy version of an of an organ oh
yes yes very similar name then I need a
bit more help that was not enough for me
mother HP attention
I I didn't hear a snoot though
we didn't hear or see us nude so I think
we're fun
fly Alice flying yes
So Graceful and we're fighting again
but we're gonna get our HP back from
these guys oh hello you brought some
other Buddies
mm-hmm
[Music]
there were so many laying around it's
not cool
[Music]
you [\h__\h]
oh no what is
it okay
[Music]
come on
I'm not done
can I have a moment
[Music]
um
oh well it waits let me test
oh wait is he killing the other
one and the other one is burnt out
later
oh maybe I can get him to destroy the
Wall
come come here come here come here
you kill kill this thing
why didn't you stop
what
hello
I'm here
hey
come here come here
you're so stupid
oh my God oh my God oh my God okay okay
here here can you destroy that is that
what they're they want me to do
no I don't think it is is this bugged
okay kill me then I guess so I think
this this one enemy
they still consider it to be alive
can kill me
okay that's just stupid
that's just stupid
where am I
now
okay no when he runs after me like this
I really cannot change the camera angle
it seems
great I lost a lot of HP testing that
out
[\h__\h] sake we gotta fight faster now
though oh my God can I try again
can I try again please
oh there he is
Darius
[Music]
I should have used the teapot Maybe
I'm continuing
very typical camera angle was the first
time that and that it shows up in this
game so it's kind of uh out of nowhere
oh yeah
let me prepare this okay
it's confusing too because now in this
angle I have to push s
like going back going backwards even
though I'm going forward
okay so uh hello
uh
uh okay
whatever
foreign
oh
God
oh my God
the memories
can we
yeah so it really opens by him even me
or him killing everyone
and that one time it really bugged out I
think we know that now
okay I'm ready I got the weapons that I
want
example
okay hello where
where are you looking at
[Music]
foreign
guys are on the ground I would have to
switch to the
um
I would have to switch to the the hammer
anyway because once they're on the
ground so the blade won't reach them I
tested it out
oh
okay he killed them nice thank you thank
you for the help I'm gonna ignore
everything what lies behind me
and
Let's Escape
yeah what is it cats do I look like I
got the time ignore her blood sugar
cabinet
that was great Kiana are you sure
are you sure
that was a tough one man
oh now it moves
oh it moves uh very slowly
at one time
hello what what
under what conditions does this start
moving
oh is it my weight
I want that one tooth
uh-huh
oh no go go back up
oh yeah
well now it goes this one goes up oh
yeah ah with the bomb Oh smart smart
thank you thank you so leave a bump here
do you really think that has so much
weight to it but I guess it has
hello
and
what do we have here
am I going up there later or what
are these moving too yes they are
but I don't care much about that
[Music]
snoot
oh really
wait for me
snoot I don't see it
maybe behind that wall
and we can get some healing
yeah if she weighs as much as the bumps
then even the bomb is extremely heavy or
or Alice is extremely lightweighted
oh a picnic box
okay I need that platform to come back
please
a gimmick like that yeah yeah that she
weighs
not nothing but almost nothing right
how do we get up there just a normal
jump really
laughs
did he just revive what
[\h__\h]
and now he's dead I killed killed him
yeah but wait
whoa safe landing oh but uh
how how low are we going how do I go
back
on it wait
it doesn't allow me to go over there
right
okay just keep on jumping keep on
jumping keep on jumping keep on jumping
and maybe I'll leave this here yeah yeah
yeah
okay
weight distribution
no
unbelievable they stole my teeth and I'm
gonna go down on
how wait I do have to do this again
I throw my bumble
no okay
well I'm goes here
nice knives thank you
oh someone who
is so innocent and to new they don't
know what I'm up to yet the perfect
victim
don't tell him guys don't tell him
or it's gonna be you next
what's up
what do we have here
pool level ah does it open the door of
course it does
please don't tell me the dude is gonna
come after me again
I don't wanna
nice room though gonna play some chess
the field is a bit too small now
oh
this move the pawn along the chessboard
to uh the opposite Pawn mirrors your
movement oh there's a I guess a
something missing here Aha and
we want to kill the other Pawn
complete the chest puzzle by getting
both pawns to the goal at the same time
ah rocks will block the Pawn's path at
rocks Rooks
uh-huh avoid the nights as they will
destroy pawns no
chess puzzle must be completed within
the displayed move limit but if it's
like last time you can also skip it no
probably if you fail once last time I
think it told me like you can you can
quit if you wanna
uh
uh wait there's only a tower not a
another horse scene
this is the goal
did I not do it already add to the other
one
oh [\h__\h]
oh I did it
I did it oh
there's more than one oh
I need to go to to this one
and he needs to go to that one
or the other way around
well
um
um oh why don't Whitefield okay
stretch
what what if I when I when he's here and
I'm there and I go left he would go
right but does that like uh him bumping
into there do they do they kill him then
or
oh wait maybe
[Music]
he won't be able to it blocks him so
then it should be fine no
I hope so oh yeah it's fine oh okay
okay that's so easy
and that was so easy that was so easy
you could have uh upped the difficulty
of that a little bit more
I love this room though
I like that marble
with that Rosy touch to it beautiful
that was the introduction to the
mechanic oh
will there be more like this
oh there is there's gonna be a temple oh
okay nice
oh I gotta call Ollie for that chest
reveal Ollie help me out please
okay maybe Charles
let's say Charlie maybe Ollie wants to
um
do a review of this one as well yes yes
here
well recently you've been hiding so well
but in this room you're not hiding very
well dear snoogie Sun
trophy Chase only Charlie
what about that tooth
you mean a tooth
wait what just opened up ah here
oh
another golden tooth it's so quiet here
a locked room is little more than a cage
and present by another name I despise
concealment of any kind
that'll be fine Alice you're gonna be
just fine
as long as you don't meet that
executioner anymore wow
oh pretty I like this
not funny not funny
oh
is he coming is he coming what's what is
it
you were saying
uh what you think the queen wants oh
I didn't even see that
oh it's really by accident
but there's nothing in here
ah
I almost didn't see that
well that's really well hidden
what the [\h__\h] is that
what was that knitting away as deserving
heads
those were good
who is that who was that
no way
really
are they like connected to them all
why would
how why why
do they have like it
well why did they put a reference in
there did anyone work together
uh he's just a fan oh really
oh wait where do I go first
here hold on
foreign
[Music]
looked pretty good to be honest but I
don't know are you guys interested in
that
I still don't have my PS5 though so even
if I wanted to play it I can't I have a
feeling he's coming again
okay it's someone else uh nice to meet
you
foreign
does that work
sounds like it's somewhat working
oh whoa
I'm not sure
oh it did work
oh there's more
but wait there's more
nice double damage
I don't know if only the teapot is
working or uh
if the hammer is working on this armored
guard as well
ouch that kind of hurts
oh wait do I have to hit his backside no
well now he's dead so never mind
[Music]
I have PTSD now
oh wait
um
I hear snoot
wait was I supposed to go up or down now
because now we get the cutscene I
thought going down was the the side path
okay he won't
he won't come after me here
it does not overstake a perfect guess
stays
perfect
oh then I'm the perfect guest because I
don't want to go anywhere except to
Japan when the time comes
yeah maybe I should have gone up first
onion
can I even go up now
maybe I can whatever
whatever we're not even trying to do
Collectibles so who cares oh I should
have uh left uh a weight again perhaps
damn it damn it damn it damn it damn it
damn it
damn it damn it damn it
I want to visit Japan too yeah how many
of you are planning to visit Japan as
soon as the gates are open huh
I think for rabbit tourists are still
gonna take a while
yeah this is this is this doesn't seem
like the place where he would come after
me
um
me me one day maybe
go for it
don't let your dreams be dreams
wait no wait I want to go up there let's
go
aha
I probably never visited oh well why not
don't don't limit yourself like that
beautiful music
closed caskets though I'm told your
sister could have shown to Advantage and
the flames never got to her
and all the flights depending on where
you're going can be quite expensive but
besides that what's holding you back
gotta save some money then for your
dream
there's some cheaper ways to get there
too like if you don't take a direct
flight
yeah I remember though I think actually
the price
of the flights went down over the years
to be honest because I remember it being
way more expensive when I first flew to
Japan but maybe that was because I flew
of
ah no you know what I think back then
that's like so many years ago
um the thing was that there weren't so
many choices as there were now so I flew
with Lufthansa
and it was pretty expensive
but I think
um now there's so many more choices like
oh my god
um
and oh wait did I miss that oh is that
where I would have landed if I would
have gone uh up instead of down first
[\h__\h] oh well whatever I was saying um
yeah there are more
more choices now you can instead of a
direct flight you can go through so many
different airlines
and all go to Japan one way or another
so I think in that sense
you at least have more choices so it's
kind of cheaper
oh who's what's what's
what are you doing
oh my God yeah now of course like there
is barely any flights going to Japan
because well there's no need for it
foreign
can that one kill you too
yeah I can okay
KLM oh yeah I I really like KLM for
flying to Japan at least I used to
because it was uh it was cheap it was a
nice connection
and the the staff the flight attendants
and the food
we're both top-notch
I really liked KLM whenever it was
possible I I would fly with KLM
although I mean of course uh there's
even better ones if you can fly with the
Japanese Airlines
wait wait
ah okay okay
I I remember did I tell you this before
I flew back from Japan to my country
before with with uh Ana and uh
it will see where the flight from from
Osaka to Tokyo or the order flight from
Tokyo to Austria but but I remember I
was like really really really really
dead tired and I was so exhausted I got
into the plane I had a seat in the very
very very back and no one was sitting
next to me so even though it was daytime
I immediately
um blacked out I laid down sideways
uh and I noticed
the A9 flight attendance the stewardess
she put a blanket over me
while I was half asleep it was so sweet
it was cute
no
I'm so cute
the traveling alone Phoenix sleeping
alone blacked out in the very back of
the airplane
she saw that and she was like oh cute
I'll be her mommy now
oh I have a bad feeling
I have a bad feeling here
to the Royal Guards of this realm where
are you all victims in Waiting where are
you
I don't know where you are
huh
what
okay
and down there
no
oh [\h__\h] I messed up I messed up
oh
there are some Airlines down that I will
never fly with again
but I will not say which one
I did mention to you guys once that uh
there was a bomb in my plane before
right
right I didn't mention but I didn't say
any details I think
is he gonna come down because it seems
like he wants they want me to fight
[Music]
oh
I can stop him a little bit
[Music]
oh
thank you
thank you it's clean up buddy buddy
let's clean
up
yeah give me sprinting
I'm invisible
I'm Invincible I
don't know you missed the spot not me
not me
you missed someone
ah okay whatever maybe I have to get him
to
ah does the next PATH only open up if I
if we kill everyone
I'll help you
oh whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa what happened
nice so we're just gonna brush past that
now yes yes
to elaborate
I think I did mention it before though
right
this is so shiny
um
[Music]
apparently you did according to chat
yeah I did I did ages ago probably
though what is this doing
what does this do
what
teapot
shoot the teapot ah I see
um
yeah
oh higher
how high do you want me to shoot
like this
um
no
[Music]
This Time come on
does this really work
it doesn't go that far
[Laughter]
I don't know if I should
what's going on it flies so weirdly too
it was a Target oh oh
okay okay then I don't need the teapot
though I can also wait a second I need
to put this down and go over here yeah
yeah yeah
Rachel and then shoot shoot
there was also a different time that
really pissed me off of a different
Airline you know I've literally I've
been to Japan with literally every
possible Airline except American
Airlines
perhaps and maybe I don't know Canadian
Airlines or whatever because
there are so many connections that you
can take through Europe
uh
we're sure so many I have used pretty
much all of the European uh Airline
Airlines I've used uh
uh sea Airlines
please talk about the bomb
yeah you wanted me to talk about myself
no I I I like I don't think I should
elaborate
actually [\h__\h]
beaches
then those are weird leeches they're
going up and down
um
uh no I'm I'm not sure it might might
even be fine but uh I'll tell you a
different story uh
what
what does that mean
does that mean
s
another t-point
ah
I mean uh if I activate that I should be
seeing something
oh wait oh wait oh
okay and now I can chew it for me aha
so I never really random
story of an airline pissing me off
was uh I was
I was traveling alone once again from uh
Europe to Japan and
from my it wasn't a direct flight
and uh
uh got it
not as fun as the bomb story but
I was sitting again kind of in the back
every yeah
of a plane it moves up and down is this
not my weight
or maybe
oh no oh I thought it was my weight I
thought it had to be click okay so I was
uh at the very back of a plane sitting
uh alone there in a three-seater
next to some guy
and uh
um he he was from the country of the the
the transit country
he was not Austrian
um
and uh
he he was
on the phone like
forever and he was talking so loud and
because I already had one flight uh
behind me
I was really really uh-huh I was really
tired
and I just wanted to chillax
um and he just he just wouldn't [\h__\h]
shut up on his phone
um
and then I noticed that like I was I was
trying to
uh sleep really I I had my I had there
was like a sticker that you could put on
top of your seat
you would get like three different
stickers that you could choose from like
uh don't disturb me or disturb me when
there's food or uh whatever do what you
want
don't leave us alone Alice
so that the flight attendants would know
if they could wake you up for the
for the food or not which I think is a
great idea because I don't want to miss
my food even if I'm asleep
please give me the food
it's the most important thing about the
flight the food
so
I uh I was trying to sleep it was still
the plane obviously didn't take off yet
anyway this dude she was so loud he was
talking talking talking talking talking
talking
and uh
well this is a long time ago I don't
really remember the details but there
was a stewardess no
um uh not as stupid as a flight
attendant mail
behind we were in the last row and he
was standing behind and he was after I
think this was already after takeoff
um he wasn't on his phone anymore but he
the dude was like talking a lot and very
loud and aggressively with the flight
attendant oh my God
with the steelhead yes
um
and it was interesting because
I got this feeling that this dude was
complaining about sitting next to me for
whatever reason
I know the reason
um turns out a little bit later
he disappeared
and he was taken to the
he was upgraded to them business or
first class or whatever
and I was until the end of the flight
alone
in that last row yeah
funny isn't it
funny I didn't do anything I literally
only was trying to sleep but I know what
the problem was
oh two pass
I'll go here first wait there's more
there's even more paths
oh okay okay
yeah it's just it's just yeah I I would
have liked an upgrade to the quiet first
class or whatever too I would have liked
to get my sleep too instead of hearing
someone rambling and and fighting and
discussing right next to me from the
beginning on all the time hmm would have
been nice for me too to get an upgrade
for that but no I'm not the type of
person who complains to the to the
flight staff
forever and ever and ever
so this was the second path but this is
also is this the main track or what are
we looking at uh
I might
this is the main path what is this
what's that mean
s
[Applause]
one and two
ah
okay
gotta release your inner Karen nah cause
you've heard a bomb
this is
foreign
because then I think I had three seats
to myself
three seats guys
free free t-h-r
uh E Yeah free seats
what
do the numbers mean Mason
one two three four but before there it
also was saying
what do they mean
I guess the story ends well yeah no but
I decided to never fly with an airline
again
[Laughter]
because I didn't like the
their attitude
so much choices so what the hell what is
all of this
money
wait am I supposed to put a bomb down
here
and then
no no no no
what what
What's Happening Here
what's happening
do they want me to go there place a bomb
then go all the way over back there
I don't know
what happens when I do that is that one
going up or am I just going down
wait
oh yeah
it's not going back though well
okay or did that one go up maybe
hmm you're going down
what are we doing
it
no no no it did go up it did go up and I
was supposed to
or no where am I supposed to leave the
bump here
let's try that then
come on
what the
know what ah because then I would reach
boom that that one that one I wanted to
jump up to that one I think
oh [\h__\h]
I think that's what what they wanted me
to do the platform on the left Kiana
what
yeah okay wait wait
tomato
I'm trying I'm trying
okay okay okay okay okay okay
[Applause]
[Music]
and then okay from here I can go to the
Apple ones the numbers however seem
useless to me
I don't know what you're trying to tell
me jump on this one first well that's
obvious isn't it yeah yeah
I want to go up can you do that
but that's so I don't think that's
reachable probably like a snooch
involved or something like that
ah should I have left the pump yeah
it's fine
uh it's
fine still I was thinking of telling you
guys a story today
remember long time ago in one of the
first uh whole life
English
a whole myth streams and
oh I'm gonna go over there for the
Memories
remember where we gave like facts about
ourselves
um
wait I want to solve this riddle
I can't reach there
no I can't
oh
platforms what
is
what
let's go back here maybe I'll leave a
bomb somewhere after all
maybe I can make it go higher yep
maybe leave a bomb here
yeah it's going up
uh
but then I'm missing the memory okay I
don't care about that one I guess I
could have gotten that if I put a bomb
here and then go over there to get it
but I don't really care about it to be
honest
yeah okay let's get it
wait for me
wait almost there wait what there's
[Music]
on it
yeah it bothered me and leaving it
behind
it bothered me after all
hi
okay let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go
[Music]
so I said
that
I
uh one of my
why can't I
oh
I'm never gonna be able to tell my story
wrong timing
well now it's pissing me off
laughs
we'll get there eventually
I won't make it I won't make it I won't
make it
oh will I
oh I'm
yeah baby
was that not even worth it I'm not sure
okay so I said I said back then that I
was in my previous lives a flight
attendant right
and never elaborated on that did I
well well well I want to tell you about
the or the whole process of the audition
if that's okay with you
how I got
the job
I will tell you today
yes yes yes that will probably be
interrupted a million times but um
yep you guys are used to that right
I need to go up there can I reach it
was there one of those the sign did say
ah
that doesn't do the trick does it
the sign did say that there's some
thingy
um to
attack
over
um
do I have to put a bomb on there for it
to show up again
yeah 10 minutes sorry turned into 80
minute story that's it
of course I know what yes yes hi hi
okay
uh no wait no no no no no no no no no no
no no
no so
um it was at a time where I was going to
school
and in school they let me and my uh
my gen mates
know that
there is going to be an open audition
for a very very
big Airline very uh well-known good
Airline and that the interview would be
[Music]
um
in the city
and we could go there and try our best
if we want that job
yeah and I
I honestly
didn't really think I would make it and
there was one big reason why I thought
so
now
I am currently
um
I haven't haven't just put myself uh I
haven't mentioned myself in a while but
as far as I know I am 1 meter 64.
yes yes yes yes
as far as I know
but back then
you Tom well
it's smaller
wait a little bit
upgrade weapons
okay
piano was a little bit small only a
little bit and I think that you know
every Airline obviously they have like a
minimum of height that you need to have
puppy eyes
let's go
and I don't quite remember what it was
for this Airline at that time but let's
just say yabby
why is there a fairy flying with me
now it's gone
did I always have a fairy flying with me
wait do I have to do this again
where am I who am I what
no I don't have to do it again okay uh I
was saying yeah yeah so depending on the
airline they have different minimum
requirements minimum height requirements
and I I remember that I was
really unsure about it because in my
passport it said a certain size oh God
appeared again
again
what do I do
and once when I want the [\h__\h] other
gun I
I don't like this
what the [\h__\h] it
[Music]
why are they here
well then you know what I'll use it to
my advantage then [\h__\h]
he did
you bastard boom
yeah
you can't catch me you can't catch me
now
[Music]
he's fat
is this even gonna kill him eventually
it might not
do I have to come back do I have to
okay I'm coming
I'm coming
um oh yeah I forgot how to use the
umbrella was it
um how do I use jumbo oh what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] hello
give me a break how's the umbrella work
again
what is there was a button for the
umbrella oh what the hell is that what
is that
it's done
oh she was just holding it differently f
uck no
I does it only do it when I'm focused
yes okay okay
laughs
okay
um so we're we're back at the like uh
same spot where I already killed the
others or no I see one running around
at least he's not
following me [\h__\h] I'm so sorry I'm so
sorry Goldman
I'm having a bad day okay
it's not my day oh no wait wait so eat
out [\h__\h] I'm [\h__\h] yeah good job Kiara
good job
yeah nice
but wait I can't
get anything like that this is so weird
standing in the air
[Music]
wait is there did I have to like
activate this thing in order to get
there
no no that was the shooting
wait
it's a bit difficult when he's like
right there attacking me
okay
[Music]
oh
he got a lot of 18 what the hell okay he
did
okay
hi Mickey monster oh no
oh
my God
on
what is it
it's more reality
then a reflection what sometimes what
what
Trace what the object that it echoes but
what is that what is this
where's my interface
uh
are we gonna play more chess now oh we
are
Style
okay bring it on baby I know how to play
chess it's my specialty
especially because this isn't even real
chess okay so uh the horse
again
how close can I get to the horse
what about it moves
if I would move one uh straight right
now would it kill me
I think it would oh
I think I'm good oh
what since when can a horse kill what's
right in front of them
eh
Eh
man no money I don't know
it's not real chess well that's voice
that's even worse that's confusing
okay
okay so going straight was an option too
what if I go here but then he will kill
me again so I'll go here
what what
maybe while I'm here force him to go
oh I know he can't
so this is daijubu
ah what if I go here
oh
now I was right next to him but because
he wasn't facing me he didn't kill me so
as long as I'm as his as long as he's
not facing me while he's right next to
me then he doesn't kill me
okay
and
uh
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I'm so close
that was uh a wrong color huh oh I'm
supposed to go to the other side
oh
[Music]
[\h__\h]
ah
I recently
[Music]
this is how I did it before
hey but how do I get all the way over to
the other side when I'm when I don't
have so many turns
can't go through the the towers
it doesn't matter right
yeah I don't think it matters
actually
we just
have to
um be there at the same time we have to
reach it at the same time
so
uh if I go to the left now he will go to
the right and then if I go straight he
can't okay so go one more
now if I go to the left he can't go to
the right that's maybe good is it wait
or maybe let me try
and then
[Music]
what if I go one more
and then I go straight and then I go
like that oh
so smart
so smart so so so smart so smart
oh my God
thank you
thank you smart kitty cats smart kitty
cat smart kitty cat yeah baby
I feel like he's gonna chase me no
maybe I'm okay
okay
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you okay so
continuing on my story
uh I was missing like one or two
centimeters
[Laughter]
um and my mom and me we were discussing
how we could gain one or two centimeters
to make sure that when they measure me
on site
that I would make it and
laughs
uh I I got because my passport said
um something different than uh what my
doctor said when he measured me when my
doctor mentioned me I think I was
missing one centimeter but my passport
was actually which was measured way
before like years before the doctor
measured me the passport version was
having
um
uh enough uh but but the doctor measured
me like one or two centimeters less
which which which would
um mean that I lost
one or two centimeters
uh and became smaller which makes no
sense right so it's just inaccurate
either any somebody is inaccurate I
don't know who
or it also depends sometimes on
um the daytime I suppose and also maybe
the poster who knows but I was trying to
stay very very straight for the doctors
um measuring
anyways uh where do I go first [\h__\h]
do I go this way oh there's a challenge
up there let's go
maybe I'll look at the math problem
again that I can absolutely nail
time are we gonna fight
no time no time
no time and yet I keep on talking about
all kinds of things okay we just need to
survive
survive survive survive survive
foreign I
know I can survive
maybe I cannot
wait I wanna I wanna I wanna
I'll wait I want to change my weapon
[\h__\h]
okay um
[Music]
I
pressure
stop falling
[Music]
off following me
this is exactly the same like last time
this is a pro Strat
you're welcome to copy it from me
oh man I need help
I need some help
to help she needs so
um
[Music]
what is this sound it's freaking me out
the train
sounded like a train Maybe
um oh damn it
um uh
uh
oh
I was even thinking about
like doing maybe like putting a
putting some kind of
um
Soul into my shoe but like something
that you could even like
uh
like no
no oh I only have half a heart
ah yes yes yes how many hearts do I get
uh
like like yeah like an insole but oh God
I still only have uh half a heart do I
how much how much do I have
how do I see it
there oh wait I gained some more okay
um oh
uh but like something like maybe out of
silicone in a skin color so that even if
I would have to take off my socks they
wouldn't notice you know
I was hoping for that oh come on
Siri
um
oh but actually you know what I messed
up messed up the the order of my story a
little bit actually that came later yeah
the worry of being measured came a bit
later
so anyway the big big interview was
happening
and
girls try not to die oh wait wait wait
oh [\h__\h] red weapon
uh
I'm just gonna I'm just gonna cheese it
what they imagine with shoes on no no no
no no no you need to be a certain height
without the shoes uh
foreign
who are you fighting
[Music]
sorry I'm like really really
spread today kill monster hit that
assault imagine that let's go in here
can they hit me when I'm in here oh
[Music]
okay okay calm down calm down calm down
Kiana
it will all be fun
same timing huh you want me
the heartbeats are the same perhaps
donkey donkey
I'm gonna break your back
um
Okay so
so uh my story back to my story
I can't fall down there but I just
wasn't allowed to fall down there
but oh
for the mother what exactly does that do
first maybe we should take care of this
one
um um okay and I I I was wearing my
lucky dress I have a lucky dress that uh
up until then brought me good luck
at least
um at least once and
um
I was hoping that it would bring me luck
again
normally I don't believe kind of things
but that dress
while make making me look like fire
so serious and it's just a great dress
you know
it also brings me luck
so I was wearing that dress While most
of the other people who are there they
were wearing like
even some kind of suit or there were
also some of them were wearing a dandel
the classic traditional
uh Austrian Australian oh
[Music]
dress
I didn't have one so I had to wear my
lucky dress which was not a dental but
yeah
I don't understand this oh
wait so there's a lever in here well
where where
I see a candle I don't see a leather
what
is
wait what if I am
wait I'll put a bomb here first then
hopefully it was too slow yeah
you're gonna come back already
I'm confused
throw the bomb
bro
oh how
I can only like put it down like that no
close
close one
[Music]
Maybe
use the bounce back oh
okay okay one more try one more try
okay
come back up
give you that
yes that was smoother than before
and there we go
let's go up go up go up go up Edge oh I
made it I made it
yeah
yeah okay so this thing was was really
um interesting because it was like a
huge event they like really advertised a
lot about it
and um so many people went there my my
friends from school they met up before
me they kind of went in a group and I
joined in a little bit later I was kind
of alone
um
and uh
I I don't yeah none of them really made
it very far there was like three rounds
or so
three rounds or so
Russia
yeah no [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
do I have to do the lever again
I hope not what exactly did that
activate again
wait yeah
okay okay okay okay okay yeah
[\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
uh
what
do you mean
what do you mean with that Super Chat I
don't understand your logic
oh it's saving scares me he's gonna come
isn't
he's gonna come isn't he
oh no more chess
only if you find the way um do you know
that way
they do something
ah
free rounds and now we're talking about
my story how I became a stewardess
this looks similar
hmm okay
um
more time
so I can't go straight I have to go left
however now
I can't go straight anymore so I have to
go right
now he's looking to the left so that's
okay I can go straight
and
um straight
oh now we got a problem
I will go here okay
okay ah but no he can't go straight
if
I go right he will go left
yes
yes I made it
that's mild
yeah
flexing my chest skills on you time for
a rematch Amelia Watson
[Music]
what's gonna happen
oh wait are we done with this world with
this level
why not
because there's a door
thank you Chad thank you
you guys say act as if you don't want to
see that but I know you all want to see
it I know you do
lidel
I'll tell you more of the story
afterwards
what
don't get stuck in the fire
Lizzy hated locked rooms her room was
further from the fire than mine smoke
could not have killed her she never
locked her door and besides she knew
another way out of the house out of the
window okay someone incapacitated or
killed Lizzie then locked her door then
took the lamp downstairs and started the
fire to cover up their crime their plan
was to kill us all
we're about to learn the trolls oh we
got another
yeah
which means we got another chapter down
so
we how many more do we have one or two
are we done with that executioner I hope
so
want to go
one of the finals I heard that the last
uh chapter is pretty short so we're
getting there but I still have barely
any help I would like to get some help
please
when I why do I hear Boss music not done
with this one oh I guess we're still in
this little world yeah
um
is he gonna come after me
when I hear a snoot
all the door closed my hair is snoot oh
there you are
um outfit didn't change yeah
okay oh can I get some healing here
a little bit tiny bit I would appreciate
some more
Italian oh you see that thing over there
I might zoom in again I know that was
like a zoom in function
what is that
we've been seeing it all the time and
it's been flying away from us
there's two more and this one's half
done
um
next chapter is long not that short okay
whatever oh there it goes
confront what frightens all of them to
Reckless or insulting talk should never
go unchanged ah
oh
oh oh wait what
what
yeah I really needed that it's a heart
like a bad heart wing with wings this
answers
anyway okay so uh I don't remember
everything
um
100 so bear with me but so I was in I
went there and I I think I just the
first thing was basically giving them
your
basic documents
basic information and they would decide
whether or not you would just
uh make it through the first cut
and apparently I did there were like so
many people and I I was able to go up to
the second floor
and the second floor was where like
everyone was who made it through the the
first round
and
um it was kind of weird because
the people who were there I felt like I
felt like such an oh God oh God Outsider
yummy
where did they go
I didn't want to go here
oh no
no no no
yeah
okay
because everyone was like looking so
social and
um
and handsome they all looked like
they were very intelligent
and uh
they were already tall and beautiful
very fancy looking people
pretty sick
and also mixed in between all the the
participants was also um
uh the stewardesses they picked some
stewardesses
uh from the airline
find me come throw that Bible at me yeah
oh
[\h__\h]
there we go
and I I don't know they all look like
supermodels they have a perfect makeup
perfect hair perfect everything they
were tall and slim
they look gorgeous to see what this is
and they were kind of like there to
um you know uh uh calm down all the
participants I feel like I missed a lot
up there but whatever
uh and give them advice and stuff and
they all just had a chit chat and we're
getting along so well
I I just felt so out of place like I I I
was I think I was mostly quiet
Alice but cake occupies a special place
hell yeah I agree
uh
I think I missed something important
over there
whatever
I misspelled dessert oh did they
write up a bonus oopsie
okay
anyway
um so everyone was basically waiting
their turn uh because I think they were
like
um like solo interviews after that and
then
I I guess there was like a role play
thingy
I'm not sure what they did in the solo
interview but there were definitely like
two more steps there
um
hello
what
oh it's the it's a maze
what about here though
so
uh I was really
really nervous about it and I really
didn't think I could make it I don't
remember the interview part but I
remember the the acting part and by the
time that I was uh the time that it was
my turn for the acting part
um you might question yourself what what
would you be acting would you would you
be role-playing but it was like a
um they wanted to see how you would act
in certain situations so they would be
like okay you are just the flight
attendant now and I am the guest
in the middle of a flight and they would
like recreate difficult situations
just with like talking nothing really
besides that and they wanted to see how
you would handle it with your speech and
with your mannerisms and stuff
um
and there were like two different
situations
uh
I think one of the situation
that I got was a passenger sitting next
to a family with a baby and that
passenger was really pissed off that the
baby was so loud but we couldn't change
the seats because
um the the flight was fully booked so
that wasn't really an option
and
um so I offered I think one of my my
first
try was I offered them headphones to
listen to music and and to the movies
because I really blacked out I didn't
know what else to do
and they acted really like a Karen like
it's like a really really difficult
passenger
um
and they were not happy with my
suggestion of just using the headphones
so I I really couldn't come up with
anything else I tried but the passenger
was like no no no no this is
unbelievable I can't I'm I'm exhausted I
don't I don't want to deal with this
this sucks
yeah and
um yeah as I said I really didn't know
what to do so then the dude who was
interviewing me kind of gave up on me
and he was like all right I'll help you
um so the solution to this would have
been uh to find someone to switch seats
with
I guess I think I think that was
um
what he wanted me to do
I think
and then there was a second situation
and I don't I don't quite remember that
one but I also kind of failed that one
but I think
think
he that wasn't it wasn't like
um that was like my
my downfall because
I think he liked the way I stayed still
very polite and and eager to learn you
know
so I think I was forgiven for not
finding the right solution and I think
he also understood that I was freaking
nervous
and
um so I left the room and he was like
just wait until they they call your name
and uh
and decide your fate and by that time it
was really like not many people left
more and more people were being sent
home and I swear
first they were like in this whole uh
building they were like at least 200
participants and by the time I was done
with this uh acting role play thingy
which was the last thing we had to do it
was uh only me and maybe one more
maybe one more
um person left who is still waiting on
their
um result not because only we made it
but uh because some people made it
earlier throughout the day this was like
for throughout the whole day and maybe
six seven hours
um but I don't think many people made it
so whoever made it was then brought to
another room shown like a inspirational
movie and so on and then they were sent
home and be like I will contact you
later thank you for participating but
besides that also a lot of people were
sent home so around the end it was like
me
maybe another Randall and uh
10 or 15 really really pretty
stewardesses
and they were having a chat with me
because there was no one left
and they were trying to
um help me deal with my University oh I
finally
[Music]
I was waiting to
move on I knew it up
[\h__\h] kneel it
oh cake
[Music]
will I become big and stomp you
will this make me bigger okay
yeah
yes now I can destroy him squash him
like the little bug he is
like the scum you are
oh that's funny his face and how he
dropped the weapon
and we changed our dress so I think
we're fine we're done with this chapter
now I'm
fine
[Music]
I can fight like that with wild giant
Alice can attack by stomping or pounding
oh my God attack the Queen's house to
expose her heart
breakdown castle games that blocked
delay
okay
okay oh
so
you have to imagine like first of all I
was really nervous about my height and
then I was nervous about
um some other things like maybe my
school education wasn't good enough
because I heard like I was listening
into the other people's conversations
and they were talking about like yeah I
went to I went to University blah blah
blah and
um and then I was nervous about
literally messing up every part oh my
God wait what do you call these kind of
games
this seems familiar
ah okay
can they hurt me a lot
Dynasty Warriors
oh I like this is funny
uh what about this no okay
um yeah so I messed up all the role play
so I really didn't think I would make it
but yeah and it was getting so empty I
just felt they were gonna send me home
because so many people were sent home
um and I waited and awaited and I had
Chit Chats with those two witnesses oh
no more chests now
you can make a
makeup no more
you think I'm stupid or what
done all this [\h__\h]
it's over
angry Atlas stomp stomp stomp stomp you
could just walk normally Alice you don't
have to walk like this just because
you're big
doesn't mean that you have to walk like
this Walk Like a Lady will you
Okay so
actually
at some point
finally
someone came up to me and said Kiana you
made it you made it
uh into one of the most
prestigious and popular uh
Airlines and honestly for me
that was
such an accomplishment
because otherwise like my plans would
have been very different
I I was thinking like this was oh my God
how am I supposed to find that I thought
this was a huge upgrade to
my original fans and and and oh my God
and
really a big
big Improvement on it oh I can't I have
to fight the thing
roll roll find the power
uh yeah beer yeah are they endlessly
small how do I fight
you can't
stop it
stop it and I was also so proud because
you know my friends didn't make it no
one made it except me I was the only one
in my school
who made it through that interview and I
was like bye bye [\h__\h] after I'm done
with school I'm going to work for this
Airline and it's kind of a dream job
because I saw it also as a way of me
getting to Japan regularly
because I told them obviously that I can
speak free languages German English and
Japanese and I was hoping that they
would use me for long distance flights
to Japan you know
which I think is just an obvious thing
to do
yeah and they said yeah definitely
that's possible but you kind of start
out with uh doing short distance flights
uh how do we fight this
oh
hey rip it out yeah
you start out you kind of get trained
and
um but but anyway after they told me
that I made it they brought me into a
different room where they showed me this
really inspirational
movie of yeah you're now team of our
Airline congratulations you're gonna do
this and yeah you're gonna travel to
these places and you're gonna inspire
people blah blah blah
it was like so much it's like it was
like very dramatic I felt like I was in
a movie and I I just won a huge Prize or
something but honestly it's a [\h__\h]
dream job for a lot of people I think
stream heart Stomper
yeah and I was so happy I was crying
I was so proud of myself for making
something that once again
seemed impossible at first
um
yeah and I had to actually for that I
had to move to a different country slash
different City
and uh yeah I prepared all sorts of
things I still had some time I had to
get some stuff done like some uh very
specific vaccination and uh
um I had to do this doctor's appointment
from the airline and uh I don't know all
kinds of things
and and yeah lovely blue
long story short I made it into an
amazing Airline
I'm just gonna say and and end this
story by saying it didn't last long for
very stupid reasons
um but the fact the fact that I made
me so proud of myself
um but yeah it didn't last long and um I
uh
I had to um
oh someone's coming out
how do I block that
okay
so many teeth yeah I think I can maybe
upgrade something again
there's one little
bus trying to fight
oh
wear that lucky dress every Mario Party
stream oh yeah that once again proved to
me that dress uh is my lucky dress yes
yes
um
[Music]
foreign
doctor's appointment from the airline
right uh
in the at some point oh my God
is it gonna hit me again stop hitting me
please
and that's where they measured me and I
was really really really really worried
about that but turns out
turns out so uh
uh it was all good I was the exact
perfect no I think I was even half a
centimeter above what they were asking
for
yeah so I was really relieved about that
that was the thing I was most worried
about my [\h__\h] height
yeah even though when I mentioned myself
at home I wasn't uh high enough I wasn't
tall enough but when the doctor there I
messaged me I was apparently half half a
centimeter higher than what they asking
for so wonderful all good
and there was also like an a science
test and like just a general Health test
um and then there was a I think there
was a breathing thingy test
which the doctor was very confused about
why I was doing so badly we tried again
and again and then at some point she
just gave up on me and she probably
thought I was just doing it wrong maybe
I was just doing it wrong but
um
it was weird
you know when you when you um blow into
some kind of device
crashed
acrossides
[Music]
hmm
yeah which is another
um reason why I feel like maybe I do
have asthma I don't know
my lung capacity is really bad
anyway anyway
it was fun I I it's too big
so where does that leave you
we are uh it it ended up failing because
of a different reason but I made it in
theory
and I
I prepared a lot for it but then what
the [\h__\h]
then I had to change my plans and then I
moved City and I
I got back to a normal job and I I
thought you know wow okay life is boring
now I I had this dream job I was
grasping it in my hands
and then
yeah
I had to go back to
normal life it felt like I was uh
in a dream and then the dream was over
and back to real life you know
and I moved uh to different City
I lived with stupid ass roommates not
not rmt
uh I was broke and I started this new
job but then I had this was the job
before
um going to Japan and before joining her
life
um any others I can feel from the Isis
what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] what
you am I gonna slide down that thing
[Music]
um
well I kind of just oh
oh
accepted the fact that
um I failed this for a different reason
not because I wasn't good enough I was
definitely good enough and I was really
proud of that
and I was somehow hoping that maybe I
could try again at some point maybe for
a different Airline
um but then whole life came into my life
and it was not necessary anymore to try
for that although
I do sometimes wonder how my life would
have would have went if I would have
really like continued working for that
Airline
um
I mean I would have probably had some
problems now because there would barely
be any flights
uh they're definitely struggling now but
at least for a couple of years I could
have had an interesting Life as a
stewardess and
yeah I don't know it sounds like uh
exhausting but fun job there was
um there were choices of like contracts
of like either part-time or full-time
and so on and it's it's a really
interesting system like
uh I I chose the plan for full time
and and uh it's like for for a certain
amount of time you fly and then you
don't fly and so on like you have you
have
some days where you don't work at all
and then you have many days where you do
work and all that it's very interesting
oh I'm back again
yeah I do kind of regret it I I wanted
to
live through that more but
who knows maybe it's not too late maybe
I could try again but I mean with this
current job it would never work it would
it would never I would never be able to
combine
this current job
move that obviously
but if I ever ever have to move on from
what I have now I'm not gonna say the
word then maybe maybe I'll give it a try
to try
okay I'm gonna try again
because I I do like the thought of that
a lot and
it's definitely against something that
I can do
because of who I am
that requires a special skill set right
so my language is and the education that
I've received and and you know
the character that I have my personality
and stuff
of being good in customer service and
being good and
in with like
tourists and stuff
um
I know how to deal with these kind of
things even though I failed to role play
holy [\h__\h] so many teeth wait a second
oh my God I almost got a thousand teeth
are they I can't do the weapons now why
did I already do all of them is that
what you're telling me no I didn't
maybe I need to wait until I'm out of
here
can't upgrade this because okay I
thought so
why are you
I'm the big tooth fairy
one tooth is not good enough for me
mama
couldn't
sign
rip it out
[Music]
so yeah that was my my stewardess
life story a life that
I I could have could be still living if
things would have gone a little bit
differently
um
actually I I can actually tell you the
reason why it didn't really work out in
the end because actually you already
know
part of it
ah what the [\h__\h] give me a moment
on it on it
okay
laughs
well
well the thing is
uh I kind of ruined it by myself you
know that's why I regret it even more
um
it was kind of unnecessary but I so I
went to this doctor's test when things
were already decided I already signed my
contract and I already got my apartment
uh in in that different country and so
on I was prepped and prepped and all
that and um
just had to do that doctor's appointment
and
I was told that they were going to do a
blood test
and I was worried
um
you know because I told you guys that I
have fibromyalgia or at least you would
think that I have it who knows maybe I
have something else we don't know for
sure but
um one of
uh back then I was trying to figure out
how to fix it how to deal with it and
one of the things that we tried is a
doctor prescribed me
um an antidepressant for fibromyalgia
because
uh apparently that's
maybe helps some people and I was
thinking if they see that
I've been taking that in my blood
then they might question me why I'm
taking it
uh
and either way if I would if I were like
if they think I'm I take it because of
depression then they probably don't want
me but if they if I say it's because of
the fibromyalgia then that would
probably also be a reason to
um turned me down because like I know I
know that I can handle it I've lived
with it for my whole life and I can
totally live normally with it but uh I
figured that if they would know
that they wouldn't want me and turns out
I was right but I didn't want them to
find out through my blood
uh actually turns out they couldn't have
found out for my blood because it
doesn't show up at least I'm with a
simple basic blood test like that but
but I didn't want to risk it I didn't
want to you know explain myself
afterwards so I did tell the doctor that
I supposedly have fibromyalgia and that
was the reason why they didn't they
didn't turn me down at the spot there
they they were like okay the test is
over we will let you know for a letter
later on if you uh pass the doctor's
test or no or not and then yeah I was
still preparing for the whole thing and
then
later on uh
I got the notification that because of
that
because of me saying that
oh yeah it didn't work out
I didn't have to say it I didn't need to
say yeah I was so I was so devastated
because I I or at that point I already
gave up my apartment in the city where I
was living I couldn't continue living
there anymore I was kind of stuck I was
at a point where
um
it was such a bad timing I I had uh I
already paid the the security deposit
for the new apartment and the old
apartment was already gone kind of like
I am the deadline of getting out of
there was like very soon after so it was
it was really really
uh a difficult situation and that's why
I ended up moving to a completely
different city
so yeah and got a different job and all
that
no I don't I don't think it's
discrimination it's just you know in in
a job where you use your body and and
you're stuck in a plane and stuff like
that and
um it is quite exhausting I guess
because you also have to adjust to
different time zones all the time
they maybe think that someone with
fibromyalgia isn't fit for it even
though I said that I can deal with it um
oh
I just wanted to be
honest about it I was hoping that
they would
not care about it but they did um
all right so that was that yeah I think
I think it's a physically very taxing
job but I do think that I would have
been able to handle it
um okay tell me there's a flower down
there oh wait I just came from there
huh how's my uh Health on it
town there it is okay it's full never
mind
um oh there's lots for excluding someone
for medical reasons
but I don't know it makes sense like
obviously let's say you have a
let's say okay let's say for example you
are in a wheelchair and you apply for a
job at an airline
uh isn't it an obvious reason that you
can't do that job
right right
so they
um
that's uh
yeah for Airlines they also for Pilots
it's even more important that they don't
have some kind of
uh disability or illness or whatever you
know where the hell am I where am I
going what
is
this thing here kill it
can I shoot it
oh I can oh
um it makes sense like I understand that
they only want the most healthy people
um
you shouldn't have been so honest yeah
my my mom said the same but I was just
so worried I didn't know like what kind
of blood tests they would do and I think
if you test specifically for these
things then you would have seen it in my
blood but
um
it was just a basic blood test but how
could I have known it I needed to make
sure
because if they would have found it and
I didn't say it because they were asking
they were also asking what kind of um
medications do you take and
if if I don't say that I take what I do
take
then I am hiding something and and
that's not not good either I did
where's the snoot didn't just say
there's a snoop here
don't forget to use your teeth oh yeah
thank you
wow I was just too honest yeah I was
just too [\h__\h] honestly
should I use the stuff no I don't even
use the peppercorn that much but I guess
I should
should I go to the pepper grinder
oh
foreign
okay
what I oh no it's not about the snow
that's just telling me to do that okay
okay
back to the game let's focus on the game
again
didn't think you would go that deep
uh what
laughs
happy birthday to whoever's birthday it
is
I guess someone from the Super Chat
well I'm here now what now ah
this is a new uh chapter no wait I'm
still wearing the stretch oh
is it still the same chapter
but it feels like a different one
because we're like completely somewhere
else
same job that oh
man close to the end okay
ma'am oh man
now that I talked about this I I kind of
feel very
regrettable again about missing out on
that opportunity I mean if you think
about it obviously this job
is
even better but it would have been such
a fun experience and very special and
and uh unique experience that not many
people
got to do
um
and who says who says that I wouldn't
have been in her life if I
would have taken that job everything has
a season
their flower blooms and Fades away
memories too have a useful life we
should eliminate the ones that hurt
yeah yeah I guess
now my job now is also unique yeah yeah
but still I don't know it would have
been really cool
to try that job
oh man
I mean for me of course the most ideal
thing is to not work at all it's the
most comfortable thing
but I don't know for for the flight
attendant job I wouldn't mind working a
little bit
I was like even though it's a very
exhausting job it sounds like a like it
comes with So Many Adventures
and
I don't know it's just really cool
let's become Neato
yeah
um
on the crows oh yeah right uh I I've
known someone before who did that yeah
for like one season a lot of people
who work in in the in that kind of like
tourism
um
business they do that for one season
interesting I guess like but how about I
just go on a cruise instead of working
for a cruise
maybe that's the better choice
yeah yeah I don't think
to work on a cruise I could
I could oh hello Queen
I could just go on a cruise that would
be more fun I think actually
I don't want to do that one day yeah
I can only walk right now by the way
[Music]
oh
wait are you a queen
I was expecting someone else yeah you're
cute you don't know your own mind it's
nearly a complete stranger what are you
playing not to know is merely what
you've denied
what are you doing with them you once
rejected my attempts to control Our
Lives forcefully is she me
allowed another to succeed in my role
I won't miss your tentacles
breath and unyielding attention of a
potent unreasoning unfeeling Hellraiser
I don't think so can you give me more
than a warning caterpillar said you
might help I'd need a better reason to
respond than what's currently on offer
if you don't we're all doomed not doomed
I'm confused or gotten I may survive
here
you see the pattern of Destruction I
know you do train is trying to destroy
all evidence of your past and especially
the fire now who would want that
it's from your mat the destruction of
Wonderland is the destruction of me
indeed and vice versa I've set it in
motion I can derail it this is good for
me
I didn't kill my family I am fine I'm
not mad I'm innocent I'm not I'm not
insane I'm fine
I didn't do anything
I hope you will come see you as a
tragedy the whole truth
this is fine this is fine
this is fine
I'm not mad my professional opinion
Madness is often a treatable disease
though perhaps not in this but I'm not
mad I don't either treat things
treatment
overthrown cruel to be kind that's my
technique as they say and she's as mud
as a heart you're not talking about me
over
and over forget it Alice I'm not Alice
forget it I'm not mad
what what no no
can't distinguish realities from
illusion remember your last journey an
elephant never forgets where she left
her trunk when traveling by train of
Elise
never bigger than your head I may be
wrong you're great [\h__\h] I doubt it's
Outlet again this is the Outlast episode
help me
is very hot help me
fuzzy and she's not helping oh no
humiliation I say I approve your release
and the [\h__\h] you come like a bad penny
reputation in religious evil talk Alice
I'm an old dog
no
loyalty I must never run away from her
stay Alice sit
the [\h__\h] do they want from me
[Music]
um
oh
what the [\h__\h] why are these places so
[\h__\h] up and scary of course you're
gonna lose your mind if you put gonna be
put in a place like Dad how can you heal
if you're in a place like this
oh no I can't
I can't go back to normal stuck in a
place like that
oh god oh no what no
no yeah
not man
here let me out
let me out
why is there
a Bluetooth on the floor
[Music]
quietly shut up you're gonna be quiet
please
trap trap
trap panning what what's that mean
uh
help help me everybody should watch your
day
what's their name again
uh
um help me
help me you wanna pick me up I'm scared
mommy
I swear I'll be a good girl I won't set
the house on fire again I'll stop
streaming Sparks
I won't start a fire today or tomorrow I
swear
please no
some mental conditions are relieved by
bloodletting doctor thinks it won't be
effective against your symptoms but I am
at the end of my tether and these
leeches need the work no because there's
a nurse let me put them on
all right come on yourselves you know
maybe they'll suck your fat
yeah
help me
I know and which way I was gonna say
your prayers don't interrupt are you
guys from Australia
yes you are but what am I I'll give you
you shouldn't I have nothing for you oh
please don't don't fall down on me I'll
be squashed
what where
where is the fox among the pigeons
talking gibberish nothing makes sense
anymore
quiet please shut
I'm streaming David
I haven't seen you in a while
you must soar above the Madison's into
your own mind I'm trying I'm trying
oh what a pretty waiting room yes I
might not to be as much honest in a
Bane is that asking too much I want what
she wanted
give yourself over to that trade the
tentacles for the train once it's all
together
for the train I don't know what you're
saying you're saying never a kind words
holy [\h__\h]
for Billy assay brought you out of here
if I poke that nose is there gonna be
juice coming out
Accord I told your mother dear oh God's
stubborn child to content in her own
world young women need to leave their
wonderlands the real world is not so
wonderful you'll need to grow up perhaps
the anchor tattoo maybe is something for
marine Senpai to think about but
appearances
that's not me
you've been in the Asylum again a long
stay under supervision I'm not violent
I
don't know me you don't know me at all
they don't know me I don't know who
they're dealing with
hello
are you
[Music]
never mind
and the knives the knives to
um cook I'm cooking dinner oh God
okay this is nicer I got my hair back
Hallelujah
follow the lights right probably
all the lights
she got evil
where's the light
what that's where it came from no wait
where did it come from maybe there maybe
I've gotta go there
okay okay I think I think that's the way
going
I can't help you anymore you're already
like why do you suffer
The Tyranny is just amazing I think you
lost cause
you come and go what the [\h__\h] wow a new
evil Reigns and this fiends malevolence
as it Clips the concrete Queens oh
yeah just please die just looking at you
makes me suffer
stop
oh
I can't save that boy it's oh
yeah
is that the house that
I sat on fire
are we gonna
go inside
oh the welcome to the dog
the dollhouse oh I'm cute
cute interesting not my favorite but
pretty adorable
new dress and new area
oh let's go guys
let's freaking go
no show
okay what are we dealing with here hmm
damn it
oh wait the the ground is made out of
made up of trash
it's all trash
what happened here
which means is this the last chapter
before the boss or what
let them have cake let me have cake wait
is this gonna be the item to get the the
teeth now cake oh it looks like it
laughs okay
the cake is a lot no no no no no it's
real
trust me
I know how to tell real and fake cake
apart
okay so we're back here uh I need to go
into that house now
what what for me
got four
um thank you over here
okay I think
um at this point
I am back
in the groove
[Music]
interesting children's room
a little bit creepy here and there some
details are kind of weird but mostly
it's cute butterfly
butterfly what happened why are you
bleeding
oh this looks like I'm in the inside of
a cake
oh two packs again
difficult choice
I go here first
would it have mattered
maybe not
um
I'll go here
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
if you see a ribbon yeah I did what's
what's wrong with it
looks normal now
who's that for
oh good that I went good that I died and
went up here
okay okay that was the
optional path
foreign
on my dress what there's a weird face on
it so what
you don't like it feel of it
skull of a baby face
maybe yes maybe
oh yeah I see a
yep secret platform here let's go on
that one to get those tooth
okay
and
ah gotta go back up
oh
Oh Come somebody though thank you I I oh
I don't know how that helps but
I guess sharing sharing experiences and
problems
always help you guys can maybe connect
with me in some way
I've had a
a weird weird life until now with
so many different
um
chapters in my life and all of them were
very short-lived but
yeah
I have have quite some stories you
already know a lot of them but
um
you never know the full story too
[Music]
a human being or or a phoenix what table
walk what is that
what is that a leather let's pull it
Chef thank you
thank you thank you well as a phoenix
I probably still will live for a long
time I have a long life expectancy
so who knows maybe I can still give
these things a try
but they don't say what you'll find
yeah save us the children which which
children oh Ginger
what happened with you guys
whistle sorry
you look so delicious I don't want to
waste you I want to eat you all up
um
oh guys that reminds me uh speaking of
gingerbread man yesterday
and you know because I told you guys
that uh from Monday on
um my country will be going into
a locked situation
and and the Christmas markets literally
just opened up though
and they were supposed to go oh
until
um a little bit after Christmas
but they will be closing on Monday
oh
it's too fast too fast too fast
they'll be closing on Monday so I
actually yesterday
all alone I went to
I went to the Christmas Market they were
open basically today and yesterday some
of them I think some are maybe even even
longer but a lot of them opened on this
weekend
wanna regret it because who knows if
they will extend
s not
I was thinking you know they might
extend it
so
I wanted to go and and eat some of my
favorite Christmas Market treats what
the [\h__\h] is actually going on here huh
okay
what's going on sometimes I kill this
enemy in like five seconds and sometimes
it takes me a year
oh he died
yeah that took me way too long way
longer than I should have been
oh I'm getting mad I'm getting mad I'm
getting mad
okay
so anyway
forward resistance oh for Fox Say
like the real enemies
ew no don't get too close to them Alice
[Music]
the doll maker will deprive them of what
it is so they need care ew
oo Fair pain I would assist but is
sanity required for the job
you're not mad enough to be rejected
I can't look I believe I know that way
and I'd rather not travel further along
no no
secret over there no no no no no no no
no no there's a secret no don't go
please no no not again don't chase me
there was a gingerbread Thor thing and
then I had to crush
is this one also indestructible or
oh no it's not a running away thingy so
maybe
I think where was it
no it was not here but there's also some
stuff here
oh yeah
a feather
huh
this is not what I meant
well okay
about it
oh I found a memory
must have a very long spoon what
okay uh let's try to kill the doll it's
I feel like
we can do it because
it's not chasing me like like the other
one oh hello are you are you okay
[Music]
you like this oh you lost an arm there
buddy oh now you're naked oh no I didn't
ask for this it makes me feel
uncomfortable please wear some clothes
oh she can breathe fire
that's impressive
where'd you learn that
what'd you learn that
I'm asking you a question
it's kind of rude to ignore
whoa easy
oh I like my teapot
that is a
weird
enter but yeah this is this is what I
wanted to go
home now
oh
nice
what else that we miss
some stuff over here
just some cakes some tea
holy [\h__\h] calm down horsey
what's that
what is that over there
hmm
is that something I cannot reach hmm
did you just see the jumping
what if I shoot it
what if I shoot you are you like the the
Snoop no
it is it's so sauce
I don't trust it
oh there it goes again it's like a
lollipop wait can I can I go up there
oh maybe later through another door
although
and what is that
is that some kind of secret
cut content can't do anything to it and
what it stands out so much
Frog's way
oh okay hello
[Music]
I am a frog so I guess I gotta go to
Frog's way
Humpty Dumpty Dumpty oh the egg that
yeah that right there was an egg in
Alice
you guys are included in Alice's Story
how wonderful
I've heard self-reliance is a virtue now
you've heard it oh mama
Humpty Dumpty you look funny
is well-dressed though and has legs and
arms and she's quite
an evolved version of my eggs
um
creepy
is this gonna open up I suppose so
because the finger pointing at it
mm-hmm
so far barely any enemies still pretty
Kiara friendly
oh I knew let's fight
I knew something would come
yo yo
can we uh try with this one maybe
wait stop moving
I got him I got him
yes yes yes
[\h__\h] The View was really bad can you
come down from there buddy
[Music]
okay this one's down
foreign
last one
this ain't the challenge for me
I know how to deal with these by now
okay
see a little Keyhole
what's inside
that's a cute clock though
kind of has bunny ears
don't like that clock
oh no
it is the beholden duty of knowing
adults to fit every young person
so are we blaming uh Alice's parents in
the end
[Music]
oh cute shoes
I really like the themes that they came
up full of this game like there's so
many ways of
describing something creepy going on
here and yeah it's very creative I gotta
give you that where am I flying to where
am I flying to where am I flying to
where was I flying to
hold it did I miss something
I don't see any platform ah I'm going up
here
okay okay
[Music]
here before no
the cake
and then over in that room
oh
is that over there
can I go up there with this
oh
is first try
is that is that
a drawing of me as a child as the queen
who we just met before
is that supposed to be me
hmm
what
so now who is this oh he has no head oh
ah maybe I can find you ahead
sure
if you want one you seem happy without
it
maybe we can find its head
we're going higher and higher
I'm like a parkour girl
I see that over there no I can't go
there yet I gotta go here first
oh
boy boy
I'm reading the trivia on the Wiki of
this level and oh boy
it is am I gonna find out about it too
do I want to find out about it
mythology
oh
wait wait what what what what where am I
going with that
um wait what what
ah to the right side oh there's another
one uh [\h__\h]
yep
timing was a little bit off there
wasn't I trying to uh oh yeah talk about
the Christmas markets I actually took
some photos so that you guys can
understand what takanasikiwawa yummy I
need another try I think yeah
usually uh gets at a Christmas Market
took some photos I can show it to you
if you want
I wonder I'm sure that there's Christmas
markets all over the world yeah can I do
it one more time please
[Laughter]
but I wonder if you guys if your guys's
Christmas markets are
selling the same kind of stuff as ours I
mean
I love Christmas markets
me too me too
oh sure
you know I actually thought that because
I heard something started
they're like ah this girl she's the last
class we gotta help her out to reach
this space
oh oh girl girl calm down
calm down
you look like you need to
do I need to teach you how to do potty
I don't even know how to do it because
I'm an idol I don't do that kind of
stuff
no sorry
maybe your mommy can help you what
happened with your mommy
what happens
oh she naked
no ground pound please
oh
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] whoa
you're fun I can be in a plane uh play
this if you want I don't know how to
teach you how to go potty but I can play
with you
you're amazing
you hurt me when you played with me
ah okay now now it's time anymore thank
you
she's trying to tickle me but
all right she gotta stop you need to
learn when to stop
um
[Music]
what is this place
anyway
so yeah I thought I thought that it
would be way more crowded because they
announced that you know on Monday
everything will be closing so I thought
everyone would go now
oh oh
[Music]
nice save where am I going to where am I
going where am I going to
I know I gotta leave the oh
gotta leave the bomb on it
my father would be crowded but it really
wasn't that bad at all it was just like
a normal Christmas Market crowd
just as per usual kind of um
I kind of wanted to go today too before
the stream but then
I ended up
and being too lazy I made I made
croissants though in the morning I
bought this like um
this croissant thingy well which you
have to roll out and then you cut it
apart and then you form it into a Corsa
so I have six crystals I ate only two
though
anyway I want to show you I want to show
you
I want to show you the pictures of the
Christmas Market stuff
I really I really hope they're gonna
open up again
this one and this one
and this one
no I will show you now
okay
um
if
I sent them into our Discord again
I'm trying to flex on them that I went
to a Christmas Market I don't actually
only do that because it's the easiest
way for me to get my my photos from uh
my phone to my PC
so yeah that's actually the only reason
why I do that so normally when I go to a
Christmas Market what I always look
forward to what I always get is
um these chocolate
covered fruits
look
so I actually I got two I got the I got
chocolate covered strawberries always
gotta take those always always always
and and I got chocolate covered
strawberries and bananas like a mix
I love those so you guys have them in
your Christmas markets too uh
non-germans please uh answer the Germans
don't need to answer because I know that
the Christmas markets are like my
Christmas markets
so yummy yum
no
okay a lot of people say no why
what I feel like this is a classic what
the hell
you gotta have those ever since I was
small whenever I would go to a Christmas
Market I would always get these foreign
[Music]
I already ate all of them last night
actually last night I was thinking
anyway like what the hell should I eat
for dinner and then I realized wait this
is basically the only day where I have
the chance to go to a Christmas Market
so you know what my dinner will be
Christmas Market it's really expensive
like one of those costs four dollars
approximately
um but it's worth it and then the other
thing
uh that I always get is
now sorry this photo is kind of weird
because my camera was acting upwardly
oh for sure
look
there's all kinds of uh
no not uh roasted uh
almonds but I mean they also have
non-almonds they have like on the left
side it's like random nuts but I always
go for the almonds
and they had like cinnamon uh taste they
had vanilla taste they have butter taste
they have Nutella taste uh I think the
the basic one is is almost the best one
I got this time though I got the the
cinnamon ones and the butter ones the
butter ones were I didn't like them that
much
um but anyway I love those mmm they're
so so crunchy and so sweet the calories
must be insane but
um and see 400 gram it's again four
dollars it's pretty four Euros but
approximately the same it's really
expensive
because those are Christmas market
prices you really don't get much for
that but
I I need to need to get it every time I
go to a Christmas Market I still have a
little bit left over I should bring it
over it's in the other room
hmm they're even good on the next day so
Hallelujah
yum yum yum yum
um
and then
uh because normally I only get snacks
but I I got myself some proper proper
dinner as well
[Laughter]
and it's something that we cooked in my
streams before they have some um proper
Foods as well uh they often have like uh
they have sausages and they have a uh
they have some potato stuff and and I
got myself
what's up
Kansas
it's a really really tiny uh portion
actually that costed
7.50 Euro I think that's um like seven
or eight dollars
um it's really not big but but case
especially really fill up uh quite
quite well it's [\h__\h] expensive though
and I got myself
um also I got myself
um uh kinda punch
a punch uh hot hot punch uh you know the
stuff that people drink in Christmas
markets but I got the one for children
with no alcohol I don't have much Choice
the adults they have so much Choice with
their alcoholic drinks
and that won't cost it uh eight Euro
uh unless if you bring back it's like
really a tiny amount though if you bring
back the the the the mug that they serve
it in which is like a Christmas Market
mug
um then they give you back I think like
four Euro
it's [\h__\h] insanely expensive it's
really tiny
um but I kept the mug I think a lot of
people keep it because of uh like they
see it as a souvenir so I also kept it
um I didn't give it back
um
it's really expensive though yeah so I
ate these three things and I drank my
punch my children punch and I also
bought some uh some decorations and
Christmas decoration
so all in all I did pretty much
everything important
uh that you do in a Christmas Market
I'll cover the kitchen
thank you that was yummy thank you for
treating me for dinner yesterday
Christmas is
[Music]
um
you know what let me get let me get
those leftover almonds one second
let me get him
oh my God oh my God oh my God um only a
couple left over
hmm
yes yes yes
so are you guys able to go to the
Christmas markets this year
do we have Christmas markets in your
area
hello sorry I said hello to my almonds
um
I'm really crunchy
[Music]
mm-hmm
not my thing what what how can it not be
a thing
there's good food
no
hmm your hair
[Music]
mm-hmm big crunch
it's so sugary I love it
I'm going let's go oh wait oh wait wait
wait
um
okay does this one go away too wait
oh
ah oh that one goes away okay so I have
to go to the left side after that okay
speed run
I can do it run uh oh wait what
what what
wait I need to shoot that thing though
[\h__\h] I need to do that first
ah
oh wait that only shows up ah that only
shows up when this thing is activated so
much
should I do it first because before I go
jump over there
I can't do it now
oh just to stop them oh no it opens up
that side oh so I don't have to go up
there anymore
hmm
I'm not no I do
um
I'm confused
oh
we got games terrifying Stars adorable
stories everything in between yeah up
[Music]
and really bad gameplay only with a
little bit of good gameplay in between
not too much so that you guys can still
feel Superior to me
don't we all like feeling uh superior to
the streamer
I know we do I know we do we do
I want you guys to feel good about
yourselves that's why I'm acting as if
I'm bad at games
um
foreign thank you for your effort you're
welcome
you're welcome you're welcome might do
it for you guys
huh
well um
cute bed
thank you for the pinky
and here's note
foreign
[Music]
thank you
um
really boosts my ego when I'm better
than this dreamer I know it
I know I
am
what
foreign
laughs
man you're acting like you're bad so
well impressive
thank you
[Music]
huh
what does that do
wait a second
oh
these almonds are so good I want some
more
I'm running out
why can I only get these in Christmas
markets
why
um
so good
no shop
no I was so close I thought it was
already past the point where I need to
hurry
what
okay wait wait do I activate it again
come down was it on that sign
[Music]
can I land on the other side please
no
yeah I have to go back here
activate that now
uh
go here go here
go here go here no
no okay we're fighting
[Music]
I will find this thing first oh yeah oh
there's more
oh there's more
I don't know
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait can
we like fight somewhere else
okay let's focus on you I want to focus
on you
she's got now she's got some weapons she
was like no
no last time you killed me but I want to
play more with you please Kiana
is fun to be with
I know oh [\h__\h]
push push it push it
get that get the Roses yeah oh
okay
I am confident I can take care of you
now
come at me awesome yes yes yes yes
did that not work the way I wanted it to
work
Mommy
I killed one I killed one of the
Annoying bastards
and did it oh
yes [\h__\h]
oh why is this taking so long oh
okay okay okay I'm ready I'm ready
hey
oh
[Applause]
look okay one more one more
[Music]
oh for God's sake
hmm
I almost didn't notice the snooze I was
looking at this face and just
I just didn't notice
it Blended in so well
okay
you're sure
what happened to you
what kind of monstrosity is that
600 teeth I think a little bit more
maybe until the next uh upgrade
maybe a little bit more
food Alice discipline must be maintained
cleanliness is optional whatever you've
imagined about electrical current it's
not a half of it it could be a
persuasive teacher strict mind demanding
are you talking about what is she
talking about can I go over there from
here oh I can't oh nice try
I am a kid shut up and I'm a phoenix cat
I'm so powerful
I can live forever
hmm
don't you dare underestimate me
Panda vampire yeah
let me get those guys
yeah why is hungry
you don't want to deal with me when I'm
hungry
because then I eat chickens and that's
gonna be
a problem for you guys
another liver to pull
hmm
no yeah
what is truly sword is most often found
if it is findable
okay I literally only have a few pieces
of pure sugar
yummy
[Music]
that was good
that was a good snack
have you guys ever seen Rose and almonds
like that before
again Australians and Germans do not
need to answer
yeah I know we got them here and only in
Christmas markets so just in general as
well
yeah they're tasty aren't they
they're amazing yeah yeah yeah you get
me you get me
nuts
um
okay a platform in between let's go uh
now
yo
oh no not here not here
no God who's shooting me
oh there were one hit nice
you could I
mean what what what I don't see [\h__\h]
where am I where am I
you could give me those items that
you're dropping please that would be so
kind of you
owe
oh wait the time ran out so I'm um the
platform low on itself no
style already oh my God
thank you and yes thank you for dropping
the items
I don't know
okay well that was kind of inevitable
though because I had to fight them
but we can do it again and again and
again and again and again
okay
and jump jump jump
at the end of this stream I will be the
jump queen as opposed to the jump King
I don't know if there will be a hot babe
waiting at the end of this game but
probably not huh is there nothing else
here only those two teeth
maybe the real hot babe is
takanashikiwama
I
I don't think there's anything about it
here soon ah oops maybe if I activate
you something will be over there no oh
if you blasted that open
because Alice
at this point I don't consider her
a hot babe anymore she's freaking me out
especially after I saw her in that
Asylum
didn't make it any better
no no no no
no you cannot force me yes
wait what you don't like bald girls
remember uh didn't we like make call
Cali bolt before there was an image of
that before
[Laughter]
bald Cali
hmm no I prefer her with her luscious
pink hair
you guys remember that image
oh wait that came from a member stream
oh I don't even recall that
you're rolling
it ruined my perfect one
boy
today
oh ow holy ow
did he die he died
oh wait there's something down there
platform's right there
definitely let me see
down there uh but do I want to go down
there that low
I don't necessarily need to here we are
huh
what it what what
sequence
have your time I already used them oh
I'm yum yum Puzzle Time what how do I do
it how do I do it
uh oh you want me to collect more
I will do that uh BRB
ah where could they be
oh God
I wasn't focused
I'm gonna be on my period
I am okay
[Music]
okay
let's do it again this never happened
I'm starting with okay
four and a half okay
well at least at least I know what's
coming
oh you're you're bringing that out so
quickly
okay no time to waste time
nice Dodge
[Music]
[\h__\h] slugs
nice okay that was much smoother
I am proud of that
is
and there is a flower over there
[Music]
ah yeah I could have dropped the bump to
distract his lungs but there's just like
there's like so many oh [\h__\h]
it's too early uh there's just so many
uh
things to think about that you could do
that you don't 100 really need to do
and I keep on forgetting about
I think it's okay it makes life a little
bit easier maybe but but to be honest
for me it just makes it more difficult
to think of
dropping those bombs and stuff what is
lugs it's just rarely ever necessary so
I'm like whatever
there is a hot babe at the end of this
the catches that she's a figment of your
imagination isn't all of this a figment
of Alice's imagination so yeah
did we already get them all
is this all I needed
let me stand more
well
I have not noticed you until now
maybe there's another piece in here
oh
yeah
foreign
okay this could be the last piece I
don't know how many were missing but I
think we got them now because there's
not many more places where I could go
is this missing a piece is it still
missing a piece
a piece how do I how do I play with it I
feel like it's not missing any pieces
how do I play with it
[Music]
um because shouldn't there always be one
piece to open and it's this one in the
middle
okay one more
weirdo
I went
here
I went up there too
at least I think I did
I went through this uh little hole
didn't I
yeah I did
you know
if it's a slight puzzle I should be
missing one but maybe they want me to
bring one more anyway
and then they'll take one away
is it bugged because I can't activate it
post already
be working
[Music]
I'll go up again but I think I've seen
everything that was up there
well oh wait oh I ran past this one
[Music]
okay but see they are taking one piece
away
all right uh is this is this still
does this one go down
wait how does how does this work again
uh-huh
um
is the right cheek missing
oh dear what do we do here
this one
no
well this one's a bit difficult
wait ah oh
okay this part of the face seems
complete but
this one has to go up this one has to go
down
how would I go about that uh bring this
here bring this there
oh no actually oh wait
bring this here bring this there
bring this here
move
um the mouth
move am I messing it up completely I
don't know
this here
and then it's there and then move
ah wait this is on the is this okay on
the very left
I think it is this would go here then
uh
oh I used up
use some tries okay that was the limit
[\h__\h] uh I was getting really close I
think
um is is this supposed to stay up there
though I'm not sure about this one which
part of the face that is
or is that in the middle
this forehead piece
top left is right
I thought so too this one stays yeah I
thought but I I might have to move it
anyway now we'll see
um
but these two
uh is is this the right and this the
middle or the other way around
ah
yeah I think this is the middle and this
is the right one
where is it
wait but now I don't know what you mean
by the way
top right goes to the middle
this one okay I will try
so
go here ah and now I see it better okay
okay okay okay
wait I think I solved it
all right okay
don't cry
don't look at me with those puppy eyes
[\h__\h] Baby [\h__\h] baby
what you're gonna come here oh yes you
are
oh [\h__\h]
thanks baby
you want to find this baby
there's more
the [\h__\h] babies are following me
oh oh the [\h__\h] babies can get confused
oh my God uh wait okay did I kill them
only free
[Music]
okay where do I go from here did
something new open up
stop moving like that you're weird
Don't see A New Path
or was that the new path that where the
[\h__\h] babies came from
[Laughter]
ah what are you doing Alice
I'm losing my patience with you girl was
this close before Oh I guess it was
okay
uh where do I go where do I go where do
I go here
I think yes
uh oh come on you can make it
I didn't catch any of those teeth but
okay
morning Kiana good morning
good morning I guess
oh
more [\h__\h] babies
coming
[Music]
more [\h__\h] where am I huh
calm down
yeah
whoa whoa whoa whoa
where where are they are they done
yes yes they are
okay where were we
which babies are kind of distracting me
uh I go there and then to the right side
but where do I go from there
ah there's a cupcake cupcake over there
that I could get
let's try to
yeah go to that platform or another
[\h__\h] baby
oh
no it's malfunctioning no you lost
questions
the courtesy to die where I'm standing
at least please is there a cockroach
yeah did you see that there was a
cockroach in though
uh
cake disgusting
me
whoa whoa
okay and now
oh my God
one dude
he's doing like full loops
he's having fun well I when I was a
child I was too scared to do that
did you guys do that kind of stuff
dangerous
to be careful oh do I go here
same never did it
oh my little chickens are being chickens
oh
good
I used to jump on swing sets all the
time well jumping off
I think we all did I also jumped off
swing sets
I would call it being cautious hey
you can't escape the fact that you are a
chicken
even the humble funnel has a special
joke was I over there before
do I go down here
it's not
I'm gonna go over here
holy [\h__\h] uh there's this note though is
it in your face again no
oh I must be down there then maybe
no no now it's more distant
see your secret
oh oh oh oh oh
thank you the only friend I have in this
game
are those littlest notes the only ones I
can trust
the only ones that want to help me are
them
or they
what
oh yeah where do I go first
we have a challenge level guys and is
this the way back perhaps
[Music]
okay let's do this
let's do this
and we're gonna
welcome
rain pan here's a little something to
keep your brain the one that uses it
never knows the overlapped what is it
what the one that uses it never knows
what he that he's using it what is it
the coffin
right
yeah no coffin
what a dark joke
[Laughter]
never cease to remember
same to you sir are we gonna
leave I think
oh no oh we already got one last time
okay okay I missed that one then
continue
okay
yeah
what was I supposed to go here
perhaps
finally fried oh congratulations
how does it feel warm and fuzzy
I know it does
what sauce do you want to be served with
huh
I would say um
sweet and sour Vegeta
[Music]
susawa most hard sign
s
on it oh here
oh
do I know jump to oh yeah I could
already go here
but do I want to would I be missing
something maybe some teeth
like a perfect fit and I'm a perfect
judge time to put your new noggin to use
what's then
oh a head
who are we giving that head to there
were a lot of them who were missing it
what the hell
controlling
oh I'm the head
wait what
foreign
[Applause]
no let me go back I want to go back can
I go back
oh there's something coming what the
[\h__\h] is that what is that what is that
oh it came for me more teeth no
yeah what is that
it won't break
okay is this the end this was fun let me
do it again I want to do it again oh
I'll do it again I guess
thank you
whoa whoa
oh
oh how do I break those what are those
where am I going what
what
hold X is trying to release the fire I
don't know where I'm going but okay
X I'm holding eggs Oh you mean a
different button don't you
oh
wait no now it's working
another one
uh
huh what
that's not working again
what am I doing wrong
hello
[Laughter]
no I'm using uh keyboard controls
wow
let me go down let me go down let me go
down
it's a c it's not exit C
[Music]
okay now I know what I'm doing whoa
[Laughter]
whoa what's up
oh man
I can't only say that in German because
I think it doesn't work that well
in English
let me go over there
I need more
mom
I'm kind of stuck here man
okay so this works fine but I guess
okay okay go go go momentum
eh don't lose your ah that works well so
yeah don't lose your head over this
Alice
Don't Panic so much Alice
how would I get more momentum
Donkey Kong
[Music]
um
oh I made it
yeah there's more
I'll give me the teeth give me the teeth
give me the teeth
what the [\h__\h] is this for you oh there
we go
oh
it's like I'm the golf ball
I'm gold ball
I could have could have made it almost
over here we get another try at getting
some more teeth so whatever
you
this could be its own game
oh my God okay and then we go here and
then we go that way oh God
the angle switches kind of freak me out
but okay how do we do this one
go oh sheets
did I miss something no okay
what are these for
oh my God what
I'm so small
I mean I made it
yeah turn on the eurobe let's go
oh we're done really it's kind of darker
than before no am I imagining it
foreign
don't touch the hot coal don't don't
touch the hot cold
ouch don't touch the hot cold
[Music]
foreign
more please I'll go to the right side
now because I already picked up some
teeth on the left side
I guess why did I not pick up that one
too fast too fast
okay
[Music]
I love these but they're actually pretty
challenging somehow sometimes
I shot oh
foreign
[Music]
ah
hey yeah yeah yeah yeah
hey I hear snoots what is this
what is this
this place is getting creepier by the
minute
uh where do I go first
no I don't mean the other hair song
foreign
oh well how would I go through
oh do I break the glass
huh no
oh is this uh another speed thing like
run up and then
have fun I think that's what it is
okay put this down
I don't think I'll make it first try
was
yes
it wasn't even necessary
or was that too slow
what exactly
do you want me to accomplish here
in that short amount of time
do I need to kill myself now
[Music]
okay you can upgrade another weapon oh
is that so oh yeah we again got almost a
thousand well this time I will do the
teapot Cannon
and then we only have the pepper grinder
left next time
all right uh would you guys mind if I
quickly run to an idol meeting would you
guys promise me to stay
please please please
you shouldn't say no I got two knives up
here
I know
I don't know
okay okay promise promise you'll stay
pretty pinky promise
promise thank you thank you thank you
are you already starting the flash chats
I'm not even gone and you're already
starting got no patience I guess you
really wanted to go to an idol meeting
too huh already flashing okay okay I'll
be RV
foreign
[Music]
chonkers on a pile of towels in the
bathroom
my baby
I love you good morning
[Music]
no
I'm gonna give some hugs
she's like I just woke up let me back
let me go back to sleep Mommy
I want to sleep more I already slept 14
hours today but I want to sleep more
[Music]
can I get a hug too of course come here
come here everyone group hug let's go
group hug with chunkers
and kiwama
I know
Utah
okay bye bye bye bye oh bye bye don't
leave me don't leave me baby don't leave
me no don't leave me
stay good baby
[Music]
okay okay
we won't leave you yes I I totally meant
you guys
now you guys cannot leave either
you guys Gotta Stay
not only Alice but also me
I'm getting close to becoming mad so
I need you guys to help me stay sane
playing this game
[Music]
okay [\h__\h] this [\h__\h] again the stairs
like I want to be faster by by using the
Dodge thingy but it doesn't really hello
doesn't really help that much because I
get stuck
maybe like that
and then quickly skip that part and oh
my God
I made it
that's just brutal
I don't want that to happen to me please
uh
oh my God
okay okay oh my God oh my God yeah come
over here you can try
and then we go to the right side first
Maybe
Super Smash sisters
and Alice
collaboration stream
oh I heard someone die
so here oh
haha
um
okay this is where I wanted to go and
then from here
almost there
okay here we are safe right
yes it seems almost so
a train
are we at the end of the station oh I
almost missed this one
London
what am I using that for
oh I want to go there
why am I going down no what happened to
the bird
uh
what what
oh she cried this one now
oh God
thank you
I don't want to be squashed
I don't want to become chicken pot pie
think those lyrics are freaking genius
oh yeah I gotta make my I gotta do my
schedules today right
next week
next week there's quite a lot of things
happening again there will be a whole
talk
there will be a collab with some council
members one Japan member and me
uh there'll be at least two times
Pokemon one time Ori
and he not told us celebration
what what is it what's your step Alice
yeah
oh yeah the concert watch along yeah
concert I'll be doing that I am I gotta
get up quite early for that so this one
did it open up something at the top
rather than the bottom yeah yeah
oh
oh Quaker Quaker okay
what is that hand
is it gonna follow me
yeah oh that you know what didn't they
the Virgin today
a couple hours ago I released an
original song I didn't listen to it yet
I didn't listen to it yet maybe we
should listen to it during the Super
Chat reading
hey are you you're welcome to come over
here
that's what happens
oh God
MV looks really good it looks so good
really
[Music]
if you guys say it's so good I'm really
curious
oh
die
how about you just die
what the hell is the matter with you are
you bugged or what
that's
seems
booked to me
don't tell me I can't can't move on
without killing it I should be fine I
think
I think we'll be fine there's two
buttons here
this one does this and what does this
one do
huh
I actually don't know
oh is it the door behind ah
it's a door okay but so I will put the
bomb on this one and then I'll just
quickly run over that this one and then
run through hoping that I'll make it
okay and
go go go go easy oh gotta go for this
one too
pull the leather uh
nice
okay now it's open constantly
[Music]
oh again a room like this
oh I get a secret haha
wrong leather what do you mean
pull the lip what is this a meme this is
a joke
yeah by the way yesterday I wanted to
say guest done yesterday I uh I watched
a little bit of Amish stream she was
playing this Marvel game
and I was thinking I I only recognized
Groot and the the raccoon
but I really don't know any Marvel
movies man I've watched maybe three
maximum
I was thinking we should maybe watch a
couple ones eventually together if you
guys want to
hmm he's not a raccoon oh he's not
really all right I'm back here going up
now
uh-huh
movies are always better with you oh
same same here guys
oh come on Alice Alice come on
didn't I go through here before already
oh [\h__\h]
unless you better make it Alice you
better make it
or why am I back here
I don't understand am I going backwards
oh the dead baby is there again
oh wait this door wasn't open before
so it was like a circle I was supposed
to go in a circle right
oh
what do we have here
uh I don't think the wall paintings even
mean anything that's
in particular anymore that's specific
I think it's just me
going crazy
don't move
although I want you to move
this place is looking very interesting
everyone knows rocket is a rabbit
you mean the raccoon that's obviously a
raccoon or Tanuki or something like that
it's cute let's be proud of it
trash Panda why
don't call him that
on it
[\h__\h] what what the [\h__\h] was that what am
I doing here I need to go up no
what what what what what
do I have to uh
do I have to go over there leave a bomb
there come back here
I think I have to Masa
foreign
thingies I don't like them at all
because you always only realize after
having been there already and then you
gotta go back
foreign
[Music]
I will not go down there yet
where's your finger he's telling me to
go this way anyway
oh what one hit kill
that upgrade
is really strong
the final teapot upgrade
oh
[Music]
what do we want to activate first I
guess we'll leave one here
wait what the hell
thank you
I don't want to do this again
yeah
okay I mean compared to how I was
playing uh at the beginning of today's
stream I would say we have improved a
little bit
they die in one hit when you shoot the
face yeah
you're saying I just did it wrong up
until now don't say no there's
undergraduates waiting for a word from
Papa
yes oh come on
well if they
've dated me how can I shoot uh their
face
will you move
if I stand on you no
I feel like I'm missing
some ah now I throw the bomb on this can
I just do this
no
I can't okay so you want me to throw
this on here maybe
no I'm not that fast
now only pretending can we pretend
[Music]
I'm not really bad at this game
can we pretend
and I know what I'm doing I don't really
know it at all
where do I go
I forgot I need to go up there right so
in order to do that I leave a bomb here
and then I
what's the quickest route should I try
to take that air or air thingy
apparently it was uh Eve [\h__\h]
e Frank chicken a good fried chicken day
in Japan
today
and I guess then tomorrow is a twin tail
day haha
hot
that Fried Chicken day
that there is only
[Music]
but there is only the one the national
one in America where I decided this will
be my birthday
[Music]
wait what I don't understand
oh
wait wait how would I reach Dad up there
though
I don't get it
I don't get it at all or maybe I need to
go here but like what
oh what
well this brings me
back up but
wait I'm actually too stupid to grasp
how I can get over there
put a bump on here
then
[Music]
well
but I already went up to the left side
and then we concluded that I cannot move
on because this platform doesn't move
I'll go to the
go to the other side again
oh yeah
uh
ah you need to put the bump on the left
one while it is high
and then where and go where so I can I
mean in order to get that here
oh
are you winning Kiara no not right now
[Laughter]
what
me not wait wait wait wait wait wait
I already went right and then left
before
yeah bomb
you can try again but we already been up
there
because then I go here and then I'm here
and then
Oh you mean while this one is up
is this what you meant
go up go higher I don't know where to go
laughs
[Music]
wait maybe I can order
where am I out here maybe I can improve
that strategy uh
uh wait
uh so first
is this what we were doing I don't know
why is it so difficult
why is this one thing so difficult so
then I'm here
wait stay up there uh wait oh no can I
does it go down now automatically yes it
does
oh [\h__\h] I guess do this wait for me wait
yes and then what what how do I huh what
weather
what I can't if it doesn't go high
enough for me to reach dad
what what what what
[Music]
or oh wait
wait no no no no
foreign
[Music]
get it
I don't know what I'm doing do I even
need to put a bomb here do I even need
to do that and then
oh
ah
I hate this I hate this this suck this
was bad this was really bad
this was not cool
nope nope
it's not my fault
that was stupid
uh-huh
okay
well are these platforms moving yeah
okay gold here go here
um go here
oh pepper grinder
um
I want to finish this game today
please let me finish this I wonder how
far we are from the
Finish Line
that was dangerous
I felt like going down I hope that I
won't regret that
at least there's Keith down here almost
to the end not a lot left
where are we going with this oh huh
and back here
at least if we don't get many more of
these
uh
wait what
what what what what what uh
[Music]
ah
there's a whole invisible platform on
top of it
okay I was wondering
what did I just see
oh no
no
Crowley what happened with you what did
they do to you
hmm
well at least now you've got human legs
huh
[Music]
stand how she got her super sexy legs
man I'm so jealous of those legs
oh wait pepper grinder wait oh no I'm
gonna die
where are those Nails even
oh they didn't come back anyway I
thought the nails would come back what
did I activate with this then uh
probably no dumb
I didn't have to panic jump there
oh
maybe this platform
the void because I thought that the
nails were coming back
and Gonna Stop Me
slice me up make me into one of those uh
what's the English name again
barbecue
um
thingies
skill is yes
I have arrived
these time limits
are no problem for me anymore although
wait no one what did I come up here for
I need to go down
wait no I already put something here
before what did I do
what oh
ah
oh okay I see it over there
what there's nothing here
and there's nothing here evil besides
some teeth why do you want me to go
there I can't go there
what
fake wall
fake wolf fake wall
and there's fake pools
a dinosaur in there
fake oh that
that one
oh
it Blends in so nicely I almost didn't
notice
I mean I literally didn't notice if it
weren't for you
thank you
did you guys see that
oh but it doesn't
let me move on either that was just a
little extra
um
[Music]
thank you
that looks like me
it looks like I'm like my mommy
Mommy
what happened
what did they do to you mommy no for
real though what what am I supposed to
do
I'm like ah
I don't know what I'm doing anymore okay
we go
I guess it would make sense to go ah
I didn't see this little [\h__\h]
okay let me can I play some instead of
you showing me all these things I'm
gonna die once this is over uh once the
cutscene is over so can I please move
what the hell
see that was so close
kind of mean but okay
to force me to do that on it
oh
I want to go here but no that's where I
came from oh
app now ah
[Music]
everything looks
so familiar everything looks the same
right now yeah I've been here before
okay
is this new oh
good look
okay uh
that was you but hey wait the time limit
for that is way too short
eh
how can I be faster than that
I mean okay that's I mean [\h__\h]
I actually felt that me too oh no I
think it went off earlier because I
because I died it's actually a little
bit longer I think
foreign
there it is there it is
[Laughter]
[Music]
at least there's not many enemies in
this area at all
that's oh I was wondering it was kind of
far away but okay
disturbingly quiet it almost makes me
feel at peace and as if there is no
danger
to await me but I think
they're trying to fool me
are you guys looking forward to me
playing Ori as well
I
I already look forward to it just by
looking at the covers when I turn on my
switch
they look so pretty though the game
covers the jacket
it's really really pretty
Ori is just such a pretty game isn't it
never played it it's it's not a super
super well-known game but everyone who
has played it says it has a beautiful
emotional story
and it's an amazing game
I suppose you could say it's kind of
underrated
but the people who know it they
definitely don't underrate it
um
beautiful game very sad
break up a wall to the right into the
miss one
great metroidvania not very hard either
really is that true
is it not too difficult what the hell
um
foreign
[Applause]
okay you need to stop everyone
nice nice
whatever I did there just worked really
well
I think I'll use the hammer I'll use the
hammer uh
if you want Fried Chicken you gotta pay
for it at kfp I'm not the one that you
want to fry trust me
[Music]
kids that you can choose from
why is
it gonna be me
no
I know I look extra hot and spicy I know
I know
but I will burn you up from the inside
die already
ow wait when your heart is open do I
have to use a knife oh yes I do
or I can
what now you're still your heart is gone
and you're still alive what do you want
from me what else do you want from me
thumb dial
there we go hey what you're still not
dead
you [\h__\h] boss monster oh
when are you gonna die
[\h__\h] is the matter with you
I'm gonna die I'm gonna die I'm gonna
die unbelievable
foreign
[Music]
monsters man
do I need to kill her that's the
question
um
[Music]
so okay
this really I can't really kill you
Canada
can I
last try
huh you know
I can't kill her no they were not that
difficult before
I've tried every weapon
oh my God oh my God
okay no
that that sucks that sucks
okay what do we have
where is she
where's she
where is she doesn't even know baby
wait she's invisible
foreign
okay I guess so you got it I can't fight
you when you're invisible okay kill me
then have fun
take your time
oh she's really taking her time
can you be a bit faster I'm already
cornered it's not very difficult to kill
me now
so how's your day attention
um
you know I really didn't have much to do
because Hollow talk was mostly
pre-recorded so I had most of the day to
myself which was nice so I did my
laundry I cleaned the kitchen I wanted a
Christmas Market and all that it was it
was a good day today I'm mostly
streaming so I won't have much of the
day left
thanks for asking how was your day
okay what now
kidding me
you're kidding me
not you know you're not
kidding me
oh that will just be the same checkpoint
right let's try
oh what the [\h__\h]
she's not here
main menu
Alice we are returning to Madness it
seems
um
she's just not loading in
she was there but when she was there she
was blocked out now she's not there and
that's also a bug
we start the game okay
tomato
[Music]
uh
what a weird thing
[Music]
origin let's open it up again
let's hope this works the bugs are the
final boss yeah it's the worst case I
will try to fight her while she's
invincible
hahaha
there's some moments where you can kind
of figure out where she is which is
mostly when she's attacking you
true Madness
no come on I I need I need you I need
you to be there
I need you to be there baby
please
otherwise I don't know what to do we
don't know what to do
and I wouldn't want to end it on such a
sad note you know
I don't want to end it because of a bug
okay we're loading in and
ah
I think you scared me
look absolutely terrifying has anyone
ever told you that
wait a second I need to take care of
this Melissa's first and then Michelle
okay
it's time to clean up this [\h__\h] and you
better die this time
yeah she's naked already already going
well
okay okay okay that she's much easier to
fight now
I think
come on around turn around
whoa fire scissors fun can you look at
me
okay heart heart Challenger
he's just me look around
there we go okay I told him that's weird
that she was that difficult
I told Dad can't be I feel I feel it
when something's wrong
um
okay baby
the real last bus
we have killed her we're done
no more baby please
can I get all those teeth
are there some left here too on it is
this because I restarted but or or did I
really not pick these up
well
what
is this new
did I miss this one as well oh there's a
secret good that I came back oh there's
a challenge here too what the hell
foreign
that's some deep [\h__\h] bro
#philosophical Phoenix
all right give me a quiz give me a quiz
I like those quizzes
miss me
okay
kill or be killed uh okay
I choose to run
run
[\h__\h] up actually these enemies are
pretty easy to fight I don't mind giving
them a try out
out
okay wait I need some distance I need
some distance man
oh God
this gun
is so open yeah
yeah
oh I'm actually not completely failing
this challenge this time
give me some juice I need some juice
yeah you're in the way [\h__\h]
they spawn endlessly right I just have
to survive I think
so I don't need to kill all of them but
I'm doing a good job right now I would
say
yeah yep yep yep
no no no
no oh no this is okay this is fine I
think yeah I just respawn here okay good
I would have been kind of mean if that
makes you fail a challenge because this
stage is a little bit
difficult to stay alive on hey wait I'm
actually killing them all
because I'm killing them also oh
my God I did it was this the first time
I actually wanted like this
by killing them all
or was this challenge actually different
and it was really about either being
killed or killing them all ah
this one was not time Limited
wow where the others did the other ones
start uh with a different sentence
I had no choice
all right all right all right
good job then
um
did a good job on that one wait where am
I
oh there were two paths
uh oh not not this one
can you survive the past of time oh
that's the sentence that
you usually get when it's uh
I like the cards
Bros they're easy to figure out
oh yeah
this is uh looking a little bit like the
Asylum again
oh
I don't want to go back there
why are we transitioning into the asylum
no no no wait I think I forgot something
my sanity
no
no not the asylum
everything but the asylum
heal oh I guess so yeah
sorry and stupid
but it's okay my health isn't that low
okay what's going on here this looks
complicated
get some help here at least
uh which way do I go
on it
ah there's a lever here
it's kind of creepy don't watch me while
I'm doing this
hahaha
cute
I hear someone sharpening some knives
holy [\h__\h] the the horse is really like
so aggressive
intense and chains have
oh wait what did I activate
um
what did I activate guys
the door which door
huh
something in here
I don't know
ah no yes yes
okay okay
you gotta be careful here
together
where yes go uh oh
quick
wonder if I could jump
[Laughter]
I didn't touch it
unfair unfair
okay okay
uh do I want to go over to that side as
well
I can't it doesn't actually
move like that
okay okay okay
[Music]
made it for that part that wasn't as
complicated as it looked like
oh
from where do I shoot that
I think I know where
uh
laughs
here wait what oh no here
can I even shoot from here
uh
wait I'll do it again
oh
can I
can I does anyone know looks like you
can well
looks like I have to
okay so okay
yes it works
oh this door opens
oh did it stop it stopped
whoa I feel like I'm in some kind of
Carnival
whoa
at the Christmas Market they also had
some kind of Carnival things but only
for really little children wait which
door opened up this time
ah
I think this part wait
uh what do you move for okay
gotta go to this side
of course
you were stopped I thought you wouldn't
come out again
okay number five
is watching me again
don't look don't look I'm just trying to
destroy Wonderland
six
six from five to six six
things that's quite a big jump I feel
like I missed some steps
how do I get to 666
that escalated quickly you know I'm
scared mommy where do I go where where
how do I reach 666
yeah
no
um
do I need to go back to one
you go back here
go back to the level up here
uh
what is confusing where am I
ah
the level room what uh up here up here
how do I get pick up do I need to
uh oh
excuse me
oh yeah
yes yes oh
oh there's a lot of success should I be
worried
isn't that the number of the devil
oh
[Music]
wow
oh hello
nice for you to come back I'm feeling
kind of lonely you know
thank you for coming
oh this time you even brought me some
presents
how kind of you
a lot of flowers here
I must say the distribution from the
flowers is a little bit uneven there's
some places where there are absolutely
no flowers and I was I was really
struggling for health
and sometimes we're in a level where
there's barely any enemies around you
get two at once what the hell
oh wait I need your sneeze huh
oh I should have tried to keep my eyes
open
should have given that a try damn it
um where should I go there's so many
paths
oh God this looks complicated
[Music]
what's this
oh I just now noticed that arm
yeah okay there's nothing here just some
teeth
and then
I guess it's some stupid weight
distribution thing again yeah okay okay
we gotta get this one to go higher
so over on that platform we leave a wait
or do we want to go to both of them
again also gotta check out how about in
here
apparently not
thank you
took me quite some time the first time I
got here oh no
and you're probably smarter than me so
it's gonna take me even longer
so this one right I put a weight here
and then I go all the way over here oh
wait oh oh wait
nope almost almost had it
or she or
okay
I gotta go from
here I think
so close
okay should I wait until it's all the
way
up would that help
from this state
and then go
nice
well that was easy but I guess that's
not a home
I just joined welcome to the stream
we're gonna finish Alice today
things have been [\h__\h] our minds up oh
wait this isn't even open okay
wait so what happened
what happened
what are we where are we going do I need
to go the other way now
and leave a weight there I run over here
I want to first try this come on
let me be lucky one time well
oh
wow
Chihuahua
she's gaming
I did it normally this [\h__\h] I was so bad
at it
yet here we are 643 uh by the way how
much do I need for upgrade
700 okay we almost have them all at
maximum
okay what's this
ooVoo what's this I hear a snot
it's behind here
oh yeah
it's not
I don't know where it is
also I don't know where to go from here
oh I just saw some invisible
flowers give also too if I know but like
only two
I do not see it do you guys see it
no I don't see it oh wait there was a I
wanted to check out this path
that's not oh are you leading me to the
snook yes yes you are of course you are
there you are
It's Not Invisible It's Not Invisible it
wants me to find it
found you oh that's so close
okay going back
I'm going back up
but wait what do I where do I go where
do I go where do I go
um
no what
ah
[Applause]
yeah of course again it's late so
right we'll wait until it's all the way
over at the top and then we
do I have to go from Below
I throw a weight on it I go down for
that path where we just saw this note
go
what is that really the right path
because normally the snoot paths are
really only for the memory and not used
in any other way and I say thank you
but I guess I'll give it a try see where
it leads me
hmm
no
huh
upper path I'm seeing up a path
[Music]
do you think you're going to use the air
to reach
oh yeah but this is blocked no oh
why did I think it was a blocked path I
thought there was a glass there okay
never mind never mind
it's easier than I thought it was
uh although no it's okay oh oh wait wait
wait wait wait wait for me
now it's too hot
so you come down I jump over when you're
at the right height yeah okay not so
yeah not so bad
oh no it's Casper's family
the ones that I killed
with the poison
[Music]
that's my family what a rats and mice
always that naked they look like pigs
almost don't they have some fur are
there naked rats like this
is
it's a free Blind Mice yeah I have seen
it before
are they from the app from Allen still I
thought they were just generally some
kind of uh fairy tale
um
they are in the Alice tail really
they're from Tech ah is this another
oh
is this another reference
uh [\h__\h] wait what
wait wait what
I'm not even I'm just
it
what
okay okay come on what
um
what
I need a moment to grasp this I can't
even touch it like it's not even
the spikes aren't even touching me but
from the even from the front
what
can I wait here
I'm getting there I'm getting there okay
I'm gonna go here
Shrek didn't invent them okay so they
existed before so I guess originally
it's probably another one of those Grim
fairy tales okay
laughs
oh
okay uh
[\h__\h] it what
they don't go hold out at the same time
this this one goes then I go up then I
go and I wait there then I wait and
until it's up again
wait
yeah if I went here
huh
oh
that's what it didn't let me go I could
just walk straight
oh my God
I got stuck here
what is that noise
oh
interesting mechanism you got there
the spikes all through the meat okay
so I shall go now
and wait and go
timing
and patience patience is a virtue
whistle
hmm
what's so difficult about that part
those drawings they're they're all the
same drawings are they trying to tell me
something
we've been seeing them for a while maybe
they're just hinting me that the boss is
coming soon
[Music]
are they telling me to prepare myself
mentally or what
there's a cat there
um
no no someone else said
killing Wonderland means oh wait that's
the same thing I guess
somebody once told me if I kill
Wonderland I'll also kill myself
so if they say that it also means that
if I say for the land I also save myself
yeah it's the same thing
I love that song
okay what did I just just do wrong there
what did I do wrong the spikes the spot
the spot
hey let's just go in a circle
no I'm above this level now
ah
s
don't kill me
okay okay
I thought it was just decoration okay
oh
there were spikes there too
cute
oh snap snap
don't take mine you'll be you'll be
please
I need them
is that it
is that all you have to offer
um
upgrade oh are we at 700 now damn
the final upgrade
[Music]
it better leave some burning damage or
something no
does it do now it looks like it's on
fire now hell yeah oh wow
foreign
what is this
okay well that's fun
I don't mind that oh
okay
oh
you again at least you're not invisible
actually you look a little bit different
than your friends
foreign
I'm gonna fall down
okay and now I leave this here
I don't even see you okay
I want to try out my new pepper gun
tell me if that hurts how does that feel
how does it feel
s oh
maybe use the tea should I at least it
does AOE damage huh
[Music]
there's so much going on here take this
I hope that distracts you for a little
while
where is she where is she
there she is she's kind of stuck oh
she's naked
scare me
they make me feel weird
message I don't know threatening Aura to
them when they're naked
they're like I'm gonna poop
I'm gonna poop on you and pee in your
face
I'm gonna make you regret that you're
that you became a mom
I don't know what I'm saying these
babies scare me okay I'm I'm returning
to Madness will you expect from me
I don't know how to deal with this baby
oh but hey it's going well now
it's not like to be vomited on well how
about you stop vomiting on everyone else
then huh
this is what
when your parents grow sick of you okay
don't act so surprised
what is this angle
okay I'll just I'll just vomit somewhere
oh
foreign
but we still got some more friends to
deal with
let's see oh right in his face I guess
whoa
[Music]
okay is this open oh it opened up
victory victory
oh
what
can I is this an invitation to go home
oh
cute the stats are pretty cute for lunch
[Music]
okay
can I go home
can I
can I go home and play with my friends
uh
um
please
save us
trying to save myself first of all
priorities
got another bottle
this is actually creepy oh this is
creepy oh look at this I mean it looks
kind of cheerful compared to where we
just work
annihilate what threatens to destroy you
yeah that is an advice that I didn't
need because I was about to do that
anyway
thank you though cat
yes let's get
he thinks he's smart
showing up whenever the hell he wants
giving me these hints
stupid hints
well
uh I leave this
[Music]
lollipop hey
lollipop
[Music]
oh another challenge
there's no time at all no time no time
can you survive okay oh oh not you not
you not you
running running
by the way
where is he
get away from me
I mean just normal running is actually
just about as much
helpful
as dashing oh
what is this
no time for testing out new things
how much longer please are you done with
your tea time yet
I'm not even trying to fight like if you
tell me this is just about surviving for
a certain amount of time I don't even
have the urge to fight you kind of
messed up on that one
so slow
[Music]
one more
time
yeah that was easy
I swear I did not push
anything
stop walking stop okay stop okay
okay she stopped
uh
weird sometimes when I come out of these
levels
she will just do whatever the hell she
wants
sorry passing through
uh I hear monsters
oh big one I haven't seen one of you in
a while
uh eat this
how many new ones
hmm I forgot how to find this one
ah wait I know I need to he has like a
couple of faces gotta try to hit them
all
and then I can attack him normally I
think I got no one more
one more one more but I can already
attack him what the hell
that one on the side
here can you please
wait for me
thank you thank you for waiting
oh
yeah what happened
I hate you
also I hate this angle
what's going on
bye
bye now buddy
[Music]
stop it
no no
no no oh when will he die
hmm
what I'm doing it wrong somehow
oh no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no
[Music]
no what is
okay
foreign
I can't okay it looked like I could
yeah
[Music]
that was a close one
haven't had that enemy in a while so I
honestly didn't know quite well how to
deal with them but
it was quite the pain in the ass
um
did I activate this
oh
okay
I think I moved the other hand to my
side
but how would I get there
wait I don't know how to do this next
step
what happens when it's over anyway
oh it turns
back there all right
I am waiting to Angel no we are in like
the last hour of the game really
it's been five almost almost six hours
so far wow
wait do I need to activate this one as
well again
yeah I think
we have to enjoy
I'm not quite sure what to do after I
activate this though
um
how do I help
ah no no no no I need this to go back
okay okay
[Music]
make sure you stay hydrated I've been
actually drinking pineapple juice
oh
are we back here
now this one was closed before it wasn't
the the residence
uh
um
[Music]
really really
why you want me to go through
really
oh I saw you
what do I even need tea for now are they
even useful now at this point
well how about you don't know
that's one hit kill her too
I think yeah now they're
not necessary anymore
nice okay but I still pick him up
because I don't know it feels good to
pick them up I guess I found my real
purpose
being a tooth fairy is what makes me
happy
[\h__\h] off [\h__\h] off
so I guess uh that's it for her life
I found my true calling I hear a snoot
ah
okay and tooth fairy
and tooth fairy did you guys go to any
my NYC did anyone here in the chat go to
anime NYC
I saw a picture pictures of you guys
take pictures
I saw pictures of you guys taking
pictures yeah with uh for example me
like there were standees
nope nope me not me not me or no one yes
I did oh one person
one person
hold on
it made me really happy to see Victor
taking like like this memory
um photos of uh did you guys see them
like the frames the YouTube stream
frames with our standies
Dandy
um
and then
did you also see some pictures I saw it
from also from Momo's Twitter
of the omo cat and a store
they had an omo cat stand there and they
displayed
um the the black uh uh t-shirt and the
black jacket
from the whole live collection whole
live English collection
and also we didn't even talk about the
um there was another sneak peek of The
Collection the the kind of like pastel
colored t-shirts with the pixel art
yes yes oh but that's not all yet guys
there's still more coming again you
again
okay I'll obliterate you
I know that these the the pixel t-shirts
maybe are a [\h__\h] feminine
because of the pastel color I personally
love them
some I just heard some people say oh
it's a bit too feminine yeah but then
for those people who say it's too
feminine you have the black T-shirt and
the black oh god oh
I'll follow it oh [\h__\h] I was I was so
low on HP what happened
[Music]
oh God oh God oh thank God oh that thing
up there has been doing so much damage
[\h__\h] off
oh my God uh yeah yeah so the black the
black stuff is not it's not so feminine
very cool so uh have fun with that uh
well I'm coming up buddy
check
check it
okay
I'm not gonna die here no
thanks
no yes take your friend yes I'm gonna
use him as a meat Shield
go down
[Music]
baby
I'm coming for you [\h__\h]
I'm coming for you
[\h__\h] the hell out of here
go
[\h__\h] up
you got enough screen time this is
attacking us channel oh
nice movie hi yeah hi
hey baby I am okay I'm okay mommy is a
little bit anyway yeah
yeah I'm a little bit bad yeah
yeah okay I'm okay
yeah I love you too baby I love
thank you for thank you for checking up
on me
she's rubbing her head against my legs
so cute
you're done you're done checking up okay
she's leaving the room
okay
these bastards
baby are you you're not sure after all
yes sorry I'm not I'm not calling anyone
bastard mommy is totally fine I'm I'm
okay I'm okay
okay okay mommy has to fight now
mommy has to fight
intense cat break excuse me why am I
here
okay okay
how much
uh I started off with not even full
health so
understandable I guess
can I get some more before going into
the fight or no
nope
nope that's it
all right
um what's my strategy
can the baby go up because if the baby
can't go up maybe I should go up first
and kill the
the two mobs up there
before handling the baby yeah
that seems like a good idea
mm-hmm
okay I'm going in
hey Google
oh are you gonna do it
I kind of just bluffed too
nice
ow ow [\h__\h]
I'm concentrating right now
the motion is so slow
oh
oh okay
we're coming to you now uh maybe after
you do that
on my way oh thank you for watching me
like that
okay give you some poison to eat huh
shoot me something back it's like it's
like
a catching ball
yeah yeah
you know like a father plays with his
boy out in the yard
how cute is that
uh before we go down
let me grab some cockroach cupcakes and
[\h__\h]
yeah this way was probably the way to go
take that little tooth although I don't
even need the teeth anymore
I don't see her but
no [\h__\h]
yeah yeah your friends can't help you
now
where are you
trying to hide from me
impossible
okay I'm coming down
gosh you look horrible
oh
smack that butt
I don't know why it always shows me its
butt
this must be proud of it but
I want to get your height yeah yeah
baby's heart is a delicacy
it's look at me for [\h__\h] sake
look at me
oh
and up down
enough now
and some dessert
thank you thank you yeah going up was a
good idea
um
well now we can go there okay
nice
is this is this Alice's childhood is
this what we're trying to deal with here
trying to contemplate and come over
getting get over overcome
High Ground tilapia
get this woman some almonds oh thank you
actually the Christmas Market already
closed it's 10 p.m here I think they're
all closed
so no more roasted almonds
now I know where our super chatting
crying dead baby went
oh what a cute piano
oh no ribbon game let's go
uh no no I'm not ready but this one this
was the one when I last failed it I was
able to just skip it right okay
so you can just skip it I'll try again
but
oh [\h__\h] oh oh no that was the wrong
button uh
I push it but
kind of laggy
up left right left down left up left
right left oh one more
down up left down left left left down up
right oh
down
this is from the beginning no
then up left right left down left up
left right left okay
down up left down left left down up up
um no
I think it does make me start from the
beginning right
foreign
[Music]
how many are there
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah
oh
that could have just skipped it do this
outrage but I did it
little train station
[Music]
I'm gonna stop the train
dollhouse station
oh
is it coming
where is the train am I too late did I
miss it
hello
oh
this is just a lot of babies
okay
[Music]
um
hello
yeah I don't think you should be outside
here
go back
go to the whole house
okay which way should I go first
this one
oh yeah there's a challenge over there
okay oh I think that's so lost heart
piece
the last fourth
of the last
Rose probably
foreign
puzzle Challenger oh is this one
oh my god well I don't even need the
teeth anymore
did you expect me to do it I couldn't do
anything there
I wasn't able to get more momentum
what
explain this to me guys
I need you to explain this to me
it's not like I can jump
okay no I'm not I'm not jumping
because I can't jump
but wait I'll I'll try to okay okay
going forward yeah
oh
wait look
it's tough when you're that round
just can't control your body
or I mean why you don't have a body but
sorry sorry about that I know you can't
self-conscious about that probably
I don't need the teeth I don't need the
teeth
stop going for the teeth
foreign
[Music]
wait for this to go back up again and
then go straight
hold axle charge release the fire you
mean c right
where are we charging to
um oh
no that's not quite it but a bit
I don't think I should be up here
yeah yeah go back to where you came from
and
no wrong wrong I want to go to the next
one I suppose
um go
ah oh it works too
and then to here nice and
um
this is fun
and straight
oh
almost my turn is this like Donkey Kong
if Donkey Kong is like this did I want
to play Donkey Kong
it is really hmm
wait what is this angle oh
and
shoot
oh
hey
the barrels don't charge up but
otherwise yeah oh does it also keep on
changing angles or is it always this
kind of angle
until you go back between this angle and
first here I go back wait why did I even
why that go so are back
always this angle
old school retro game isn't it
Donkey Kong
oh
this really brings you back quite far I
was much more ahead than this
I don't like this part I'm gonna wait so
long for the right moment
foreign
okay
whoa
and
see we went so far back with that one
many games are like Super Monkey Ball
the barrel is only a part of Donkey Kong
oh okay
but I was playing this really old game
that I've never seen before
the other day just a little bit ago
I don't know I've never seen a game
before you know what I'm talking about
which game I'm talking about okay so
this is where I [\h__\h] up by the way
ape Escape yeah that might have been it
what the hell is that game how old is
that game where did she find that game
is that famous never heard it before
never seen it before
no no no no
no
I was on the Finish
today oh
ah
[Music]
it's a good PS1 game oh
now imagine the whole game like this
frustration that's monkey oh does it
also throw you back that far well if yes
then that's indeed frustrating
hello I want to go down there
on the PlayStation mini collection all
that that uh game
oh
okay I love you thank you
I love you too
okay okay okay okay okay
please I want to get out of here
please no
hi okay
not so fast yeah just goes into the
middle right thank you
yeah give it to me give me my juice
um last one
you need to drink more of the few
screams that I have been letting out
today
have been really scratchy kind of
Screams and really hurts my throat
oh
I mean pour some more pineapple juice
into my water
everyone
[Applause]
we are in the last dos battle last bird
up next week
why are you asking you're so impatient
I told you guys you could have if you
watched my Pokemon stream than you would
have seen I even already bought the
first one and the second one
why am I here
okay I mean I guess it makes it easier
for me
or rattle so we went did I go here
yes I did hi
hi he has movie
she's such a sweetheart recently yeah I
love you too I love you too I love you
too
I love me too you can come here if you
want here to on this trip
huh yeah you wanna go here yeah
you don't mind even if I'm streaming
then you can come no I don't want Monday
but if you're here
stay
come up here
no you do you
um
[Music]
she's getting like more and more
attached yeah I come here go up here
then
that was mine armrest
come up
yeah yeah come here what are you doing
down there stop cuddling with my
computer
it's not
here
I'll help you up
there you go oh again
just came out of one of these
oh
they really like implementing these
right now huh
yeah oh
[Music]
down we go
where am I supposed to go
I don't get enough momentum here what if
I
go back here
oh
I kind of [\h__\h] up there I could go
down here
throw some extra oh
extra teeth
damn it
uh let me do that again
oh yes yes nice oh no I can't make it
it's kind
of feel cold
but it shouldn't be too easy right that
would be too boring okay why did I go
down here
why don't I go down here no thank you
oh thank you
all right I didn't get that boost the
first time
oh oh this time
you can do it thank you thank you for
believing in me yes yes yes yes yes was
that it
o might want to change the angle I can't
change the angle in this point of view
unfortunately
but I mean this when it comes to this
game this angle is the best anyway
whoa
and oh [\h__\h] no I messed up I messed up
straight
and a bit more there no
okay
I guess that's for the collectors Among
Us
huh I have what I think I meant the
angle of the tradition ah
okay
um
oh [\h__\h]
no
it's moving she's looking at me
mommy is struggling
yeah
you just you just go to sleep here you
just sleep a little bit when you wake up
Mommy will maybe be done
no
um
why why
the angles should be correct
I just wanna finish this
oh please Alicia
maybe maybe a bit higher
oh okay
all right
[Music]
nice shot too early I should have laid
it
so the way that I'm sorry guys I'm sorry
I will not mess up again
I'm sorry I know it's frustrating to
watch but hey at least uh the Cannons
stay in the same angle
can I can I that was so risky
oh funky
funky
what I like these pastel colors oh yeah
I was saying uh before I was talking
about UMO cat collection yeah yeah yeah
I know some of you might think that the
the two black things and then the pixel
stuff that that is all but nope
look forward to more and more and more
I think she's just uh slowly one by one
introducing the collection audit why am
I back here
did I go in a circle
what did I do
wrong way oh
okay go go this way go this way go this
way this way
okay
this one we're falling down now
uh up this way
wait no no
no no no please don't make Marie do the
whole thing please please please please
please please please please please thank
you thank you
for having mercy on me
looks there
the corn stuff is cool already I agree
I agree very much it's very hype
I hope you guys will like it and find
something that
suits your style
and in terms of the size I think you
also don't have to worry too much
I can't wait to get my sample but but
the problem is that you know this kind
of merch
also like the birthday Merchant stuff
um we designed it in a way that you know
it looks good to us but we can't even
wear it ourselves
oh
at least we can't wear it outside so
that's kind of sad
that's all
right
what is that yeah like only wearing them
as pajamas it's like wasting their
potential
and I know some of you guys say it's too
embarrassing to wear it outside but hey
those actually really
the almost cat things I would say
no reason to feel embarrassed about
wearing those outside
the pixel ones also are very very um
not too much like in your face
and the Hollow myth the the black stuff
was also
I think you know very stylish so
right you you guys would agree right
yeah there's literally people who who
walk outside
t-shirt so what the [\h__\h]
uh oh yeah but maybe instead of uh
pajamas you guys could wear to
conventions right
wear it to conventions with pride please
the black jacket looks pretty dope
mosquito
um
uh what what is this for uh-huh
this is pretty long
a little bit oh that was too low that
was too low I'd buy any kind of multiple
that thing yeah I'll wear them to work
if I got them oh really
what kind of job you have like an office
job where they don't care what you wear
that's nice
there's people that go there with the
dakimakura oh yeah yeah I've seen that
before at conventions people who walk
around with their dakimakuru oh did you
guys see
did I talk about this
camera made a uh uh has been working on
a dakimakura and it's finished now and
you can order it it's fan made not
official but I approve I am proud
I have a problem
it looks so good
see I I just might I I didn't really
want to make a Taki makura for my
official merch because I just don't
really
um see you I I feel like I could make
more useful things that could have more
daily use like the slippers for example
um
so
I just didn't really feel like making
something like that myself but the one
that Akita
is so good
afternoon
foreign
shouldn't I get one more jump there how
how do I only get one jump from that I
go left now
I'm gonna like this right sign
I'll go here ha ha
see more show to cut here
nice nice nice you can do another
shortcut here
I'm the shortcut Queen
shortens
feel follow me one more try oh my God
not the baby not no two
oh two at once and this Battleground is
uh
oh oh there's one of those as well no oh
no no
[\h__\h] you
know I want this one yes
can I I think I and jump up to him
I should be able to I think
nice well I want to go up then
[Music]
oh man okay yeah I give up I guess
stop stop stop stop
subscribe
what if I make it walk over this will it
will it walk over this will the baby try
to walk over this I guess not ow
can we go somewhere else
here maybe
okay nice nice nice nice nice nice nice
oh there's some
there's something I'll guess I'll try to
kill it by just shooting up then huh
I'm pretty sure I can
chat but I'm sick of trying now at this
point
um
how many hits do you want huh
oh
there's another one I didn't kill you
yet no not you not you
oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh
my God
what what happened why cell muted did I
tap out no [\h__\h]
no
[Music]
I no I do not want to continue
oh
okay
eh
the [\h__\h]
why
why why why why why why why why why why
why why
you could have spawned me somewhere else
couldn't ya
sometimes it spawns me right where I
left off
and then there's other times where it's
like nope
Kiowa
Fu you don't deserve it
but I'm gonna take my shortcuts again
if I may
very carefully
they could have spawned me right here
oh yes let's jump right on yeah yeah
that's good spawn point
oh okay okay
okay
the hell
en
kill him
[Music]
that's what we want to see
oh it gets lower then oh there okay oh
you can jump here fun
I think this is how it's intended to be
anyway to kill that one first
wait then I actually want to go here
that's okay
oh okay
I just somehow didn't land on the right
platform in the beginning
but this is how they wanted it to be
probably uh
it's malfunctioning
what
what no don't make me okay okay
to the void oh one down
oh nice hit give me those Heights
here can I distract them with that too
nice nice nice [\h__\h]
stop ground pounding are you like a
relative of Amelia Watson or what
I swear these babies
so unnecessary
are we done
we're done
holy [\h__\h] oh my God
this
is really it
dragging me
the madness oh look at that bunny cute
anyone has its lashes done
hello
uh
uh okay
I really hope
that we're getting there
um
I I don't even know if I'll read super
chats afterwards
I think I'll take the time to just
uh oh chill and eat and make my schedule
afterwards so around 20 minutes left
okay Hallelujah
it's a great game but at this point it
feels longer than it actually is to me I
don't know
hmm
it's already holy [\h__\h] it's already been
six and a half hours
holy [\h__\h]
oh wait a half past 10 p.m I started at
4pm in my family's demise but but I did
not start the fire oh at least not today
in Oxford but a certain doctor did
Center I saw him a preening
undergraduate oh wow you got the key
that key is that the last thing
still enjoying the playful thank you I'm
happy to hear that I hope everyone does
oh we got five Keys now
wait is that a new outfit no that's the
same from before right I don't know why
it looks new to me now actually the the
blouse gives me like uh American fast
food restaurant vibes like Wendy's or
something like that
would you agree you know what I'm
talking about
it does right
those Wendy's Wendy's vibes
cute
oh I hate a train
oh thanks
[Music]
okay
so it says like a clock worn out with
eating time look at the station
that was a morning Muslim song by the
way speaking of morning Muslim uh
yesterday
was announced that Tales of arise is
going to have like a theater thing but I
I think it's like going to be streamed
online only because it says online
theater or something like that but
actually it's going to be like recorded
in a proper theater I suppose did you
guys see
and that was super super surprised to
see that the actress
for Tales of uh for for xion hotels of
horizon
that reminds me of something
uh he's
I think now an ex-money was my member
and
um
yeah I was surprised to see familiar
faces I think that the other actors are
like more famous but the only one that I
recognized was the the one that used to
be in the morning musina
got it [\h__\h] off
oh my God
don't annoy me
look at me show me your face
there we go okay
surprise who didn't audition it wasn't
an audition
and I mean it's it's being done in Japan
so even if I were to audition like I
wouldn't be able to fulfill my duties
but actually like hello project slash
morning Muslim members
they often get shows chosen to do this
kind of like Little Theater thingies
so it's nice to see them in in things
where
normally no one really knows them that
well
and I looked in the comments of that
YouTube video that announced it how do I
get there
and most people were like excited about
the other actors but really the only one
that I could really
recognize was this morning most of my
girl
oh yeah I'm looking forward to see how
she will do
hello project does their own musicals
too yeah yeah yeah they did a jean dark
one in the past that I saw
in the future actually in ikebukuro I
went there
and the thing is that the hello project
members they're like really well trained
like they're so good at um singing while
dancing like
not no other Idol agency in Japan
has that high of quality when it comes
to dancing and singing at the same time
yeah they don't rely on kuchipaku on lip
syncing at all
and you list you go to a concert and you
see them in action and you're like how
the [\h__\h] do they do it yeah
it's it's amazing so when you go to
these when you go to this uh musicals
that they do it's also really impressive
because
oh my God even though their idols
they seem like so professional
can I kill you
look at his nails
let's cut some Fancy Nails where did you
get your pedicure done oh manicure
what I meant
as an abuser and Prevail I've been
complicit with my sister's murderer and
the killer of my family as he this is
not a therapy session Alice
from the truth
maybe it is almost free from what you
fear
you could have forgotten abandon the
memory of my family
they they are dead and you should be too
you must begotten Abomination murderer
you blood sucking parasite the damage
you've done to Children the use
I provide a service in the great and
awful Metropolis appetites of All Sorts
must be gratified my family my mind
The Infernal train the train is your
invention your defense I merely set it
scheduled
the train is coming with a China
comfy seats wheels of stars
what a poet
I'll stop that train if it's the last
thing I do as you wish
wait what do you mean what does it mean
what does it mean what do you think it
means what are you implying what are you
implying that this is implying oh no
you're lost and where your body is your
mind will follow perhaps it's already
there
and baby bubble bubble
oh
ghosts
I'm in a ghost town
number eight oh this is the
children
um
is this is
a guy I
I'm mad
I don't know what's real anymore
I mean this could be real seems legit
oh do they want me to go down here
sorry boys and girls I got no time to
play
oh
what do we have here on the ground train
station
oh sir you were saying sort of depravity
children wearing their names around
their necks as if they're breeding
livestock a declaration of their
pedigree you could use one they're proud
to display their provenance
I truly can't remember who they are or
where they're from how many Minds have
you twisted into forgetfulness not
enough yours would have been a Triumph
still you're an insane wreck my work is
done I guess self good job
definitely is insane
and down the color we go
[Applause]
back to the basic outfit I guess
oh no you didn't cover all night and did
you just like completely change your
sleep schedule for me do you sleep after
work and then through the night you
watch my streams and then in the morning
you go to look and then after work you
sleep oh my God
oh my God
final area is the train hi speed high
speed she comes in
[Music]
a machine content in a while it's a
fancy one where do I go
wait oh yeah
am I blind
I'm stuck oh I just need to go in here
okay oh the interior beautiful and the
evil force that drives it
everything's a nail is it Miss
Hammerhead thirsty was
all segmented
never time
oh have your brains on holiday without
ruined oof now we're all mad here that's
a good excuse for going to hell in the
teapot but not
what your sense is oh no Casper
it's not then they call it something
else I'd like to forget what you did I
tried
is it inconceivable
oh we're back talking to him will not
destroy me
no the damage is done the old Alice and
her Wonderland Retreat are demons oh is
it Monday there already you know what
day it is what what kind of day this is
the day for lasagna TD have fun that
will be your dinner
oh butterfly oh
became a butterfly no I'm guilty of
something but punishment never suits the
victims of the crime abuse is a crime
visit on the week you're right abusers
are insufficient
those who witness him without seeking
retribution
I'm old at this point true
it's like Ina told me that she gives her
takodachi's uh cookies on a certain day
was it the first time but you failed to
me we should have Monday
from a raving delusional Beauty with no
memory of the past or no sense of the
future but you wouldn't forget you
insisted on holding on to your fantasies
you're mad like your sister don't
you didn't know her your sister was a
tease pretended to despise me she ain't
got what she wanted her teeth
give me key
oh wow she looks badass that is
the way she looks like right now reminds
me of
new outfit
you know what I mean
right
[Laughter]
yeah yeah I also had kind of crazy nails
too right and it was like so the last
boss kind of feeling and it had a big
big big big kind of
thing a skirt down there and stuff yeah
I don't know kind of like uh was very
Majestic oh
[Music]
do you know the answer to it's not
polite and that noise wasn't Lizzy
talking in her sleep
no
honesty and there are no centers in
Oxford make your survival mean something
all we are
Doom
Doom I don't know what's going on
next
whoa this is like the obstacle course in
Minecraft from the
from the festival
be amazing y'all
as expected Kiara shut up
he's speaking riddles to me
I've been really trying to understand
oh my is this the boss fight
okay uh I'll do my best though oh [\h__\h]
how do I find you know how my chat broke
just now
all right oh I guess I'll have to do
this without you guys
I see you going by and in OBS what the
[\h__\h]
[Music]
hmm
okay how do I fight you I guess the face
Super Smash Brothers
wait
that must be a reference no
it's not a reference oh my God I mean
the movements
am I doing any damage at all
I hope I'm doing some damage here
oh
down
please
where's my health why do I wait do I
have endless health
damaging okay
oh okay I think that did something
oh no hey here's my health
no I need to go to the other side
oh [\h__\h]
oh
no no no no don't touch me
out
what do I do am I doing this wrong
camera is so weird also is there any way
I could get health back if I [\h__\h] up
oh yes
thank you for your health
thank you
oh oh what the hell what was that
okay okay yes yes yes yes that's what we
want to see yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
where did you go what what is that what
am I focusing on here
oh he's on top okay
[Music]
oh his face is not covered up anymore
would you mind coming down
or maybe this way is better when he's up
there
oh they don't drop anymore
oh [\h__\h] okay I'm really oh there's one
there's one
I at least did some damage there oh
he's talking doesn't mean I I did one
stage
one hand down I took a finger up oh I
did oh you'll be over here do I need all
his fingers
got fancier Nails than I do man do I
need to feel less feminine now
I need some hearts
ah he won't give me what was that
hey don't show me the middle finger okay
oh [\h__\h] what is that I think I need to
jump over that oh
I I can't I was busy
that was good that was good I got also
quite a bunch of cards back I keep on
saying hearts even though it's roses but
I don't know it feels wrong to say roses
oh it's coming it's coming it's coming
yeah I don't know how to go
oh I think now I was able to dodge it
yeah okay I'm I'm getting [\h__\h] here
[Music]
no not the big one he said the big one
what the [\h__\h] why would you
[Music]
know wait the other one's just chilling
I could have been in there he hit the
camera right now so much
go go go go
oh my God okay
wait I should use my oh my power
[Music]
hello
no
no please no [\h__\h]
I hate it already
[Music]
how far did I get do I really have to
get all five
all five of those uh teeth uh you means
uh I can't even speak I don't have any
brain anymore
no
it's two hands oh that was the second
hand
huh
okay I've revived my chat
wait are we not starting all over oh I
don't know if I like that if I'm happy
about that because I have very sickly no
health
oh you stopped at a good spot here thank
you
[Applause]
stop this move
I don't see [\h__\h] yeah I don't know how
to stop that
foreign
[Music]
I can't I actually can't jump I tried
jumping uh because I'm focused I can't
jump
umbrella reflected
I guess I can try
foreign
when the face is black do do I do even
any damage
the one
know them
[Music]
guess not
time to tell
and it kind of corned me there [\h__\h]
no
no this doesn't really help me now
because I can't do any damage anyway
oh thank you I think the game recognizes
when I need the hearts and only gives
them to me when I'm like really close to
dying
[Music]
okay
ouch I was trying to get some hearts but
I guess you don't want me
[Music]
oh
oh it's gone the face is gone
what now
what's next buddy
next face
oh oh both of them
oh no not two at once
how do I fight them no no
no
damage
[Music]
how do I fight though
thing on it I can't
oh God I'm gonna die I'm half a heart I
have a
hearty
no that's it that's it that's not it
that's gone oh I got a heart thank you
ah
a
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you
wait how I really I bought his beard
he's [\h__\h] weird I don't know what the
hell it is
huh
am I what
I'm back
am I doing any damage to these uh hats
contender
oh this is so clutch
please I beg you I beg you thank you
thank you sir thank you Colleen sir I
can't I can't make it I can't make it
nah
no okay it's a hard time
eating right now okay
okay
no problem
thank you
no no no no I don't wanna no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no
crabby no no no no no no no no no no no
no
no okay
foreign
I'm really trying here I'm really trying
I'm trying I'm trying I'm trying I'm
trying I'm trying
Gonna Know
okay so at this at this face where there
are no enemies out and stuff only the
hands and I will just try to survive
instead of fighting them
but I don't know how to make them not
catch me
yeah
okay
foreign
why did it not kill him
he'll go a monster I want some HP please
no
oh so close
so close to death
so
disgust.com
holy moly
I'm like living on the [\h__\h] Edge
I need to go to the front
I think uh no
no
I'm busy I'm busy for [\h__\h] sake I'm
busy
stop I'm so tense right now
okay okay you can't get me you can't
catch me you can't catch me you can't
catch me
okay he's gonna come to the front
how many more times
oh drink drink
it's not over is it
water
that's it did I do it
oh
did I fight the madness
did I regain my sanity in prison some
halfway Bruiser will make you his
sweetheart his sister
[Music]
happens against a respectable social
architect and scientist my God Alice who
would believe you yeah nice guest and
believe it myself yeah
monstrous creature such evil will be
punished well no one else will punish
him then we'll do it
you're mad
ly
expecting your replacement
our replacement
who are you abusing now
[\h__\h]
oh
[Music]
I got the upper hand
yes yes
it's time
time to take a train ride home buddy
Alice is in control
good job Alice
mine to Gap he did not mind the gap it's
his fault
nice
nice my my health
why so nice and peaceful here
so colorful
I'm actually not [\h__\h] up for once
this is like
the Wonderland that we all dream about
that we all love so much
thank you
it was quite a difficult
quite a difficult game to be honest
especially for me who normally doesn't
play uh Alice can't go home it's kind of
Platformers
we are very few
and it's not only a platformer like
Mario Super Mario so
it's web combat
pretty forgetting
remembering it
recovering the truth to where the
suffering and our Wonderland though
damaged is safe in memory for now for
now pretty challenging I wanted to say
oh man
wow now you're ready for that oh my God
well
uh
I I really really liked the style the
whole aesthetic of the game
um it was it was creepy but cute very
much
and it was also very beautiful there
were many beautiful sceneries
that we could
explore
and so many deaths around uh like mini
games as well like the 2D uh paper style
thing for example thank you for the red
super chat and the the pinball style uh
one as well and all of the slides for
example yeah there were so many
different elements in the game
um
that were all very very fun I must say I
mean it was it was at the same time
difficult I had a lot of struggles
especially combat wise but I did I did
enjoy it most of the time
and for someone who doesn't do
Platformers that much I would say that
um
uh yeah I had many fails but I also did
a a decent job I guess
thank you
Mr Boss ending oh too bad thank you for
the pinky thank you thank you
we are very much a unique game
um
thank you
[Music]
I don't know
last episode I was somehow
different person last time we streamed
this I was really good and today I was
really bad it was just not really my day
I think I think these kind of games
there are days when you're better at
them and then there's days where you
worse at them and especially if there's
like a big gap in between the last time
you played it then I think it's
understandable that there's
there's uh some things that you forget
or that you don't feel so
uh smooth with anymore
um he totally crushed it no I didn't but
thank you
um
I don't think you're that bad
I don't know the the episode today kind
of crashed me but I think the other ones
were a little bit better
um the last times I streamed it
uh
yeah yeah yeah yeah it was a combination
of you not being at your best and being
in the final route it was the most
difficult part of the game so it was
okay thank you
yeah and maybe I think I should have
baby played it with the controller from
the get-go but I did it with the um
keyboard and then switching in between
would have taken too much time to get
used to I thought so that was kind of
challenging too I think I would have
probably had a better time with a
controller
[Music]
um
yeah yeah yeah it's it's a damn old game
so
oh here's Martian actress Who's acting
emotion motion is he in the chat no one
needs to ask for motion
just kidding uh um what was I saying oh
yeah because it's a really old game I
understand that you know
um we you can't necessarily uh uh
compare it too much to games nowadays I
think I think it held itself quite well
um yeah it's not like there's some some
things like um the bugs and stuff that
uh made me go a little bit mad
especially today
it was difficult playing with keyboard
yeah it was a little bit yeah for me at
least because I'm I'm bad at uh pushing
so many buttons and remembering so many
buttons
yeah it maybe wouldn't have taken too
long but I just I just felt like
well I'm already
um kind of used as a keyboard so might
as well continue with that yeah
it was still a really really cool game
I'm glad I picked it up
um because it's one of those games that
nobody really streams and uh people
maybe don't think much about it even
though it does deserve
um all the love and all the all the
attention and Praises Daniel
I'm glad I was able to
um stream it uh in this day and age
where
that many people pick it up anymore
and hopefully that will be a
continuation of this someday I know the
Creator is working on it uh for quite
some time for quite a long time and
hopefully one day that will really come
out and I can't promise I will play it
but uh I'm sure that the fans would be
very happy it's a good Hidden Gem yeah
yeah yeah we picked it up originally
only for like one episode on Halloween
um but turns out that it was hmm
uh short enough and fun enough to do a
whole series out of it
is
and
it's only four episodes but it still
felt very very long to me
will you try the first game in the
future not on stream I don't think so no
no also because I think it's not even on
on Origin I don't know where I would get
it this is it I feel like I looked it up
and it wasn't even
available like that
uh
uh I think
if I unders if I remember correctly uh
yeah yeah you can't really
uh
at least not online I don't know
something was there but yeah I think
we're fine I think we we don't need to
play the first one
if you guys are curious go ahead please
give the first one a try as well
um it will maybe answer some questions
that you have right now because there
were quite a lot of references and stuff
to the first one as well I think so feel
free to go give it a try on your own
yeah how about that whole my fantasy
music video what's wrong oh yeah we can
do that we can do that I don't think
that I'll be reading super chats because
I'm kind of exhausted now mentally and
physically
um
[Music]
still not a PC copy of the first game oh
you know what my mom maybe does too
maybe she does because she definitely
played it I don't know what she did with
all of her old stuff maybe she threw it
away
oh
yeah this was also kind of requested by
my BFF it's funny to me how my BFF and
my mom and gouda they all love this game
and we're really excited for me to play
it
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
we are surrounded by a woman of culture
yeah kind of I I'm glad that it is it
has so much appreciation in my friend's
Circle
it's good you ended up playing it
because now you have something new to
talk with them about oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah
I can tell them how freaking difficult
it was for me
uh play this game
and have fun guys I want you guys to
give it a try hopefully we can support
uh the the upcoming one as well
thank you for the screen going to sleep
now thank you
thank you and I'm gonna make the
schedule and then it will be uploaded
after the stream maybe after I also have
some dinner I don't know and maybe the
BFF is sick really good at someone from
before from long time ago
shall we wants to Envy quickly yeah
let's do it let's do it let's go to my
office
I hope my office is clean
looks alright
thank you
Musical videos
so
yes there is the chat
and
you know what let me get there was a way
to get like the thumbnails or maybe on
Twitter though maybe they uploaded on
Twitter and how do I find who tweeted
about it and what the [\h__\h] is that P
gate
oh
what the [\h__\h] is that I go on Twitter
and I see it
this
excuse me
I don't know what to say
I I appreciate the fact that you know
it's a very fluffy Garfield and I like
being a fluffy cat because I love fluffy
cats
um but at the same time
I kind of look like a
prostitute cat
[Laughter]
um
it's kind of weird
but it's the vampire outfit
what
I thought the same thank you
she's pimping
ah
this this little cat lady is being paid
in Lazada
also I mean look at that look at that
face
and look look at the way she's holding
the lollipop like a cigarette oh my God
he gained
again I think you need a little trip to
the usual room
okay maybe if we go to Home Alone live
uh official Twitter
yeah is that yeah that's that's uh
nice
it's a cover
tonight
let's do a live reaction
I'll put this up on on this TV
and uh
currently watching
there we go
all right
everyone looks beautiful yeah I like
their outfits it's very fantasy-ish
mmm
the concert
soon it's exciting
all right uh where where did I find it
uh
what
is
what does it say what's it called
interactive Fantasia
why is it in hiragana
to look cute huh
okay stop I wonder I could probably play
the audio because it's a whole live song
it would probably be fine but since you
guys are gonna watch it together with me
I guess I'm not gonna risk it and also
because so that it won't overlap that
you won't hear the audio twice I guess
let's try to
yeah I gave it a link here it is
and on zero okay on zero on zero we
watch it
I say three two one zero and then on on
zero we cook
okay
uh are you ready don't be okay
you watch it later okay okay
free wait what is that I have a DM
oh
oh oh
okay three two one
zero
oh
hey hey
wow
um
[Music]
their voices sound so cute together
oh
louder
hey hey
[Music]
oh butterfly
oh
that's huge freaking carrot in the
background
oh man
oh
hi
there's so much going on
[Music]
running
Lucia
[Music]
foreign
's room
oh this [\h__\h] what
wreck which is normal
what happened
oh the beach
oh holy [\h__\h] whoa whoa whoa whoa
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
whoa
I need to listen to that a couple more
times because there was so much going on
and I want to listen to their voices to
give us some more because
it this is I feel like correct me if I'm
wrong but this is kind of on it
this is the first uh original song
together
is this the first time I'm hearing the
voices together like that
it is right
all five of them together
unless they were singing a song all
together in one of the concerts that
that I watched but I can't recall right
now I feel like almost they must have
performed as one gen together before but
no they only did like smaller units in
those concerts like they mixed everyone
together I don't think they did full gen
performances in the
in the whole office to
I don't I feel like I would remember
that
um
oh I mean they probably at some point
sang together before but yeah this is
the first time it's like probably
properly mixed into a song like that I
would say
did they do it in on in the first
concert ah I think the first one I
didn't uh watch I think because that was
before I joined total life right yeah
mm-hmm yeah and it was pretty dope
I need to watch this again can we watch
it no I'm watching privately again
probably then
um
but I need to I need to learn this song
properly so that in in the in the
concert I can
together
[Music]
um
I wanna
um practice everyone's original songs
that they're probably gonna perform I
assume that everyone's gonna perform
their original songs
um
and then they're gonna do some some
Duets probably and some and some trios
and some songs to all five together and
all that I wonder what they're gonna
sing
um but at least they're original songs I
want to get down get down
[Music]
hmm yeah as usual they gotta gonna have
some pairings I assume and some solos
and all that yeah pack around brain no
need to practice that one I already got
that one down
[Music]
last time when I watched one of these
concerts I I didn't know most of the
songs so I felt kind of bad for about it
and didn't didn't know how to Vibe along
so this time I'm gonna gonna Vibe along
knowing the songs
get down with the dance in 3D when you
have your 3DW I want to do that hell
yeah remind me again when I get my 3D
that will definitely be a definitely be
a [\h__\h] post for the future
yeah although I don't know about the
copyright of that song hmm
worst case I'll just do like
[Music]
and hope that it will be forgiven
um
so we finished Alice next week
continuing with Pokemon and or starting
most likely with Ori mm-hmm
no worry we'll edit it in post oh thank
you thank you
yeah
Pokemon's so exciting yeah I've had so
much fun last time I want to play so
much more tomorrow I will be Pokemon I
think I'll be playing for a while given
but only if I if I get enough for us
today oh man I feel so exhausted again
why absolutely Boomer Boomer cat
ah well look forward to that tomorrow
I actually I caught a couple more
ponitas
um
because I was I actually looked up
um what's the best uh
um
trait personality
character
for that minutes and I I saw it's Jolie
so in nature yeah so I tried to get a
jolly one and I caught uh four uh
ponytas none of them had Johnny so I
gave up
I don't care that much it's not that
important I guess yeah I I had a rash
one
and uh
now you guys can choose which one you
think is the best one out of those
um the first one I got didn't even have
any like special attack up or down or
anything like that it just was like
really really neutral
and the other ones I got
if I do I have adamant uh I'm not sure I
forgot
I feel like maybe I didn't
but I'll show you tomorrow
I'll show you tomorrow smoothie uses
cuddling super effective and it always
is
why care about Natures in Story play
oh
yeah I don't know I don't know I wanted
to impress you guys with uh with a
Jolene Ponyta
um tomorrow but after catching a bunch
of them I was like ah whatever
yeah I I I don't think it's necessary
either to have like all these perfect
stats they seem perfectly good enough
when they're just random Pokemon
hmm
just break down no I don't I'm not the
type of Pokemon player that gets into
that kind of stuff I I don't feel like I
wanna get into that
um
you're asking about natures and what
that's impressive to me already are you
sure
I I just I just wanted to play Pokemon
yesterday without like continuing the
story because I just really wanted to
play Pokemon so I was catching those
ponitas but then I realized oh man I
can't really do much off-screen without
moving on too much so I stopped pretty
soon afterwards I I uh
um buried some berries and that was
about it I didn't want to grind either
because I was already pretty high level
so
yeah I don't think I need to grind at
all in in uh
I I should I should be doing the
opposite
Underground
yeah maybe maybe today bgm yeah I know
there's no big gym but we're ending now
anyway
um
yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay thank you guys for watching I hope
you all enjoyed Alice madness Returns
and I hope it didn't make you guys too
mad while watching me
foreign
[Music]
thank you guys I will read them in the
next stream if that's okay
um
okay yeah I'm pretty mad now don't go
please I gotta go I'm exhausted
[Music]
I'm gonna eat frozen pizza now yeah
oh man
oh man oh hey you want to hear something
I made some I made a doctor's
appointment for I decided to do a lot of
doctor's appointments now
um next week
um I'm going to the dentist
I found a dentist close by that takes
that that does a online uh
online appointments thankfully I hate
calling and then being like you know you
know can I have an appointment I hate
that
thankfully nowadays there's like
um places that take online reservations
yeah
and then y'all you know in the night the
last night right after making that
appointment I had a dream about
um
my teeth falling apart
no they don't hurt at all I just uh felt
like I should go
um
sometimes I have those dreams that that
my teeth fall apart or break or
something and it really freaks me out so
much it's like the most scariest dreams
that you that you could have
I have those too really
yeah good that I'm not the only one it
was not really scary man a common dream
common nightmare
yeah it's so freaky man it's so freaky
holy [\h__\h]
it feels so real
like what the [\h__\h] would I do if that
happened in real life oh my God that
would be a horrible
do you grind your teeth at that that
usually causes those rims I wouldn't
know I don't have anyone to check up on
me my cats don't really tell me what I
do at night
I have a feeling though maybe I maybe I
do because even like even normally like
right now if I were to um just chill and
close my mouth and not talk and I feel
like I'm
I'm putting a lot of pressure against
like you know the upper and the lower
jaw I think anyway what the hell why am
I talking about this
um
dentists can usually figure out if you
grind your teeth
oh well last time I went they didn't
notice anything
like that yeah
get a mouth guard no
no
no no no
and the string Tango and why are you so
mad why are you mad I want to chit chat
a little bit
now this one will just be uh
uh like a a talk session and then I'll
make another appointment for whatever we
need to do hmm
and I also I I think I need to make an
apart appointment with a a skin doctor
because I think
a birthmark I think I scratched it open
and I noticed today last night when I
looked at it it's like on the back of my
thigh and I looked at it and it's just I
think I scratched it open quite a while
ago
um and and looking at it last night
it's like I don't even see
the the birthmark anymore I only see
like a like a crust
you know what I mean like the the
scratch Crest thingy
and I think that's pretty a bit it can
be pretty a bit I heard that if you like
scratch your
um birthmarks that badly it can
uh do some bad [\h__\h] yeah so yeah but now
that it's like kind of gone I'm like
was there ever One to begin with no I'm
not sure so I'm like should I go to this
doctor or not should I have that checked
on or not the dermatologist I guess I'm
just gonna go
yeah better
better to check it I guess
ten Choice crusty let's go
crusty chicken instead of Pho crispy
chicken
uh the other thing no don't have any
update on that uh yet also my my
physical therapy is also not starting
yet I'm gonna start starting again I'm
not sure I think they'll well uh
oh was it next week
when am I going
ah
not not this week next week no no no not
the next week but the following week
after that is when I start my favorite
therapy hmm
your legs feeling better Oh you mean the
cramps I still uh when I lift it or so
in certain ways I still feel the cramp
from yesterday
but it's no problem no problem should
let birthmarks get checked periodically
anyway all right then I have a lot of
them so you just don't see it they're
they're hidden they're hidden in some
places there where you don't see it but
I have a lot of them so I guess I guess
I have a good reason to go there
do I I hope so
[Music]
um
you had a scared shitless when you had
that liquor I watched yesterday I I
rewatched it the moment
and I just had to laugh at myself
because
it really just sounds like I'm giving
birth to an egg or something and you
guys your reaction was so funny too man
and it was so long
oh man I I got myself worried too I was
trying to really
get help but I didn't see any helpful
comments in the chat I was
devastated oh yeah I saw I saw a clip
that said I was I was turning super
saiyan and that was funny
see to be honest it's kind of
embarrassing but it's also really just
stupidly funny at the same time so
um
I guess it's okay
um I I don't I don't mind I think for it
to be clipped it's okay it's
embarrassing too
but it it's also just funny
so it's okay
it's okay
stretching yeah well now now I know for
next time I should try this dress but I
think in that moment I wasn't able to do
anything I just wanted to perish
yeah
nothing embarrassing embarrassing about
it no it was embarrassing because I was
like
I've been paying so much you're
screaming and screaming
um
need more potassium
massage the leg oh no you didn't watch
what happened yesterday you don't know
how bad that was that was this is
impossible it was like dying
you can mute next time I didn't even
that moment
didn't think about that but uh
hmm
I'm a streamer
I share my life with you guys no matter
you know how how painful it is
fruit for thick and thin we go through
the bad times and the good times we go
together
yes
and now kiss
and in German we say
see you guys tomorrow yes
[Music]
um
shall we should we make smoothie think
that I'm done and and wait how long it
takes her to come in
let's wait
wheel
she's taking a lot of time she knows I'm
still streaming
no even when she's sleeping she knows
she wakes up
ah
baby
mom
oh sorry Chris what are you doing
wasn't even waiting for you
oh
hi
oh she's you should meet out while
yawning
okay hi junkers wrong cat
no I love you too no come here
okay
hello did you sleep
oh
no
where is your sister huh
where are you sister
movie
she's not even purring but I have her in
my arms right now
petting her belly
she doesn't really like being held like
this
where's Dad what
what
would you like to say something to the
audience
hmm
they're so cute
you're such a cute baby
oh she's such a baby
all right I guess smoothie disappeared
into the void I bet when I go to the
ending screen she's gonna show up
bye-bye
foreign
[Music]
animals
uh they were like owls and locals and
cats and stuff like small figures that
that were like really soft
had some kind of
um hair on it and I found some that
looked like my cat so I bought two of
them
[Music]
yeah that's pretty cute thank you I know
YouTube YouTube you're pretty cute
[Music]
no