[Music]
[Applause]
for
[Music]
do
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
for
[Music]
to
[Laughter]
[Music]
for
to
[Music]
for
[Applause]
[Music]
ch
for
[Music]
[Applause]
ch
k k k you got to come close on the
you're so far no I bet they can hear me
look my voice is so loud n they can hear
you but you're like acoustically
f sit up like a normal person here I'll
do it too we'll do it together my bag
we'll sit up like a normal person please
we both have back problems you can't
make me sit up straight yeah yeah yeah
we can we can I think for you it's even
like impossible to not sit up
straight
still oh look behind you in the Box
smoothie is in the box smie smothie is
in the Box yay Trap Photos yeah yeah
just a couple of them just a small
gallery that will be running endlessly
now here's the thing wait you don't even
hear the music barely probably can you
hear
this wait what the [\h__\h] is this this why
is this all the way here and no no
that's just weird and I will I I can
barely hear myself ah there we go it's
better okay I'm loud
actually and can you hear to bgm now it
sounds quiet so this N I thought so how
about how about
now
H wait now your reaction is the light wa
what is my what what did I set as my
okay okay ultra low ultra low latency
bjm good now better all right okay well
K I'm
Takashi from H life English myth and hi
you Darlings this is Hol life English
Advent dou Diva the one and only narissa
Raven
crft wow wow wow wow wow so she's here
back in my room mhm from from Austria to
the males back to Austria uhh we are
back back we are so back right yeah so
back are
you this kind of a weird question to ask
because I
mean I think it's a yes and a no are you
happy to be back yes yeah but for me
it's h it was way too
short only cuz what we got rained in 3
days
right two days it really was a
problem the end of days I I still got to
do things so like even snorkeling so so
yeah uh we went to the mall te together
it was so fun yeah yeah yeah it was like
a 9h hour flight from Austria which we
flew in economy very uncomfortable well
at least the flight the flight to the m
was fun yeah yeah cuz we had a seat
open uh and yeah it was a it's a little
bit far away but it's in in a
tropical environment with Islands many
many little Islands as you know and they
are all really focused on Resort and
tourism and it's a destination where
people like to go on their
honeymoon or anniversary or whatever and
we went however honeymoon as friends for
honeymoon totally our friend
honeymoon friend yeah friend friendly
Moon friendly Moon friendly
Moon I was I was wondering at some point
like oh where do the word honeymoon come
from and you taught me and I'm like why
the [\h__\h] do you know these things you
have so much like Niche knowledge that's
that's my thing that's my secret is I
just have Niche knowledge of things that
I really don't need to know and then I
can hold on to those but then the
important stuff I don't remember
that yeah yeah I remember that's so true
because I remember doing the whole
loacation I I like I tell you something
like a schedule of the day or so where
we're eating tonight and what we're
doing today uh and it's like pretty
simple information there it's not so
much it's like three things and then you
immediately forget it and ask me several
times throughout the day yeah I'm so
sorry you don't you have I guess you
have a bad memory I have a goldfish
brain yeah narissa has approximate
knowledge of many things is that a like
a
compliment approximate knowledge what
does that mean I don't
know did she tell you facts about Rome
no she didn't why would I tell you facts
about Rome or is it or you asking if I
told her facts about Rome cuz I've been
to Rome beener done that okay show
off oh speaking of Rome okay this is so
Random the main thing that we're going
to do today today is we're going to read
the journals that we wrote about each
other uh or like generally about the
days that we spent together and how we
perceived it but since we just mentioned
room
um uh narissa met my mom
yeah and uh my mom loves Italy you know
and and so she was like talking to you
about Italy a lot right yeah and about
America you had some heated discussions
there was no heat I was not heated I
just want to be clear I didn't care yeah
yeah my mom is always heated uh I guess
the heated part was her it was very it
was very fun it was very she's very nice
to talk to she's very passionate when
she talks she's a a tangent a tangent to
just like us mhm yeah she started you
know she was just there to like um like
show me stuff that how what what things
are in my apartment when we came back
and also to say hi to narissa because
you know when us two get to meet a a
lovely colleague of mine yeah yeah she
took it she took the advantage and she
cooked something for us so yeah really
sweet welcome of my mommy yes it was
very it's very very nice and she can you
describe um her
English she swears a lot I mean so do I
yeah you know where I got it from now
mhm I got it from my mommy I got it from
my Mommy what's one is that I got it
from my daddy side
[Music]
what Mr P I like to say p because like
if I just say Sai it's so short and I
don't know what I'm talking about but
it's Sai thank you English yeah for
makinging the P silent yeah what what's
up with that it's like
Psychiatry a but that one at least is a
longer word yeah I guess so it's okay
mama told you ask why you two aren't
married yet no she doesn't ask such
questions no I mean she she follows my
streams quite actively just like your I
feel like that's like our our families
are quite similar because both our
families seem to watch our streams
constantly yes my parents love to at
least watch Clips if they can't get to
an actual stream MH which I'm just like
you don't have to and they're like we
want
to and then you your your family also
has been on your stream mhm just like
mine well for me it's just been my mom
but your mom hasn't been on your stream
[Music]
no I have siblings too but I don't
really I don't think they're interested
in making a cameo on my stream yeah
they're more on the like distant side in
terms of my job my my brother is the
same way he's like I don't want any part
of what you're
doing oh well that's fine right because
like you know do your thing and all that
you don't have to uh closely observe
honestly sometimes you know um I forget
that my mom might be watching and then
afterwards I realize and I'm like H
these things I talked
about do you get the same feeling uh-huh
uh-huh when I make whenever I make make
an inappropriate joke and then it OCC
does she say something no I don't think
they get it okay I don't think they
understand the innuendos I make
sometimes oh
sh sh was streaming at this time oh
what thank you for the
raid I rarely get raided I only ever get
like raided for from foku if it's foku
morning and that's it that's all the ra
i let's go
thank you
what I didn't realize you
can yeah y can you guys hear chunky
wonky yeah she screaming you love chunky
wonky don't you I do I love your cats
I'm going to take them home with
me no no no no so basically let's let's
get into it we're going to talk more
about random things if we if need be
later on but like I journals I
originally intended for it to be
basically just observations of each
other's traits and habits and this and
that but uh I don't know about you but
for me it automatically because I like
like to go and like explain the
situation it ended up being like a
complete diary yeah yeah I am not good
at stuff like that and if I don't write
it down immediately I won't remember
things as we mentioned I have the
biggest goldfish brain I can't remember
what I eat for breakfast most days so I
I just ended up I think mostly just
jotting down like small observations and
what we did throughout the day for the
most part so it is it is kind of very
much just diary esque but very simple
yeah simple okay okay and we like I mean
nissa's first entry was shorter but
after that we I think we both wrote like
two three four pages kind of longer I I
did at least I think two per day yeah
rting down she's cute over and over is
that what I'm going to read I debated it
I was like What if I just wrote a whole
page where I just write she's she's cute
she's cute she's cute no yeah I thought
she wouldn't like that so I didn't do
it that I mean that is very flattering
but I I need there to be yeah she [\h__\h]
substance yeah substance well I can tell
them something funny that happened today
oh I I was laying in my bed and and
Kiana came in the room and she looked at
me and she told me to stand up and I was
scared I I don't know why I thought she
was like going to beat my ass or
something I was Gana maybe but you know
what she did she gave me a hug she and
like I was like oh how
cute she's so cuddly I I thought you
needed a hug maybe you need a hug I just
give you random like unexpected hug so
she does so that so that you don't like
get cocky
I don't okay I still want to hug you but
I don't want to like give you too many
hugs and like too too regular like
scheduled hugs or so they're like random
to surprise you out of nowhere you she
laid on my lap on the plane ride home
yeah which was I mean uncomfortable cuz
we only had two seats this time yeah
yeah yeah but I need I I I was so unable
she was there for like over 30 minutes
though so it couldn't have been that
uncomfortable really hard breathing it
was really yeah hard to breathe though
yeah but your lap and ding sideways was
worth
it yeah yeah okay but we're like getting
all over the place again so we're going
to read like day by day of each other's
Journal we may have troubles reading
don't stop reading it we may have
troubles reading each other's handw
wrting it is okay to interject and ask
about certain things
or if necessary defend themselves for
things
I don't know what you write what do you
write about me I don't know I mean I
only wrote the truth for nothing but the
truth I
see well objection
denied yeah uh who wants to start why
don't you start cuz by shorter okay yeah
cuz the first narissa page is short n
nissa's observation of me page but but
okay okay one last before we start so I
needed journals right so uh in we didn't
get any until the departure day uh the
the two mold departure day so we were at
the airport and I was looking for a
bookstore because I wanted to buy a book
and these journals and then eventually I
finally found some that are not
extremely overpriced and they I want to
upload a picture afterwards on Twitter
of just the the the books next to each
other yeah they're like floral like
tropical flowers which is I think
fitting and then I bought another I
bought a book that I wanted to read in
case I was lounging on the beach lot but
I wasn't all to going to beach a lot at
all so I didn't read it but man but
narissa paid for my
book Thank You free book let's go I'll
read it on my break though I I'll have a
lot of time yeah and then I'll report to
you it was good well I didn't read yeah
well I was I bought I bought it with the
full intention if I
had you know chill time on the beach but
you know sometimes it just doesn't work
out that way we just didn't we didn't we
didn't chill that much on the beach in
the end we chilled more in our beds and
then fell asleep it was a damn good naps
that we took many many a naps naps will
be mentioned a lot in these journals
yeah was dropping oh no it's okay okay
so uh I shall read wait maybe I write it
down what I'm reading who's reading what
and is that here's what is this fashion
okay uh now
reading
um Thea
Journal I'm of me of
kiar maybe like that it's so confusing
kiar is reading nissa's Journal about
kiar you know yeah very very confusing
as You' think she
would do you by any chance this is not
this is perhaps by any chance not the
first time that you're writing a journal
about me do you have an actual Journal B
me no I actually don't write as you can
tell from you don't write I don't read
you don't write
amazing oh someone asked if any of the
photos on the vacation that are showing
were taken by me ah oh yeah all of these
photos are an N photos because my phone
literally died yeah it's terrible before
like an hour or so no no we were outside
yeah and then the phone died and we're
like no big deal we get back and we'll
charge it yeah we'll just charge it it
won't charge it will not charge and Thea
looked it up for me right I've been
looking up Solutions all day okay not
all day uh the later half of the day
yeah and I can't find anything like that
works we even tried like with her phone
charging my phone cuz it said that
wireless charging would be good yeah it
also said I came back and I checked it
again it still wasn't working so I read
up some more solutions it was like try
charging it on a PC or in like I'll try
that later like slow charging I I tried
it already on which here mhm that's why
your computer was on oh uh and it didn't
it it didn't work I left it for like 10
minutes need new battery that's [\h__\h]
up though because it's not an old phone
yeah it's like a new new phone yeah
Samsung Ultra s22 and like I really like
it like why the [\h__\h] does it die like
that yeah like the the thing is I'm
trying to get onto the um what's it
called the like the screen so I can try
clearing the the cash it won't delete
any of your pictures or anything just
like app info
and it's it's not the cable we tried
multiple different cables the cables are
all charging my phone Char we have the
same
phone we tried different plugs it so
[\h__\h] up man I need my phone so we
can't we we literally can't get anything
off of it yeah that was right before the
stream yeah so turn it it's off it's
it's the battery is dead so yeah but I
feel like I feel like I maybe had this
happen before and it came back but I
don't know not like this I guess and and
you said that people on the internet
said it's like a common thing with this
phone yeah apparently not thing needs a
new battery but I don't know if the
battery can even be taken out of these
phones can I mean I'm sure it can yeah
yeah I mean but then you avoid the
warranty don't you what don't you just
avoid the
warranty oh I don't know I don't know I
never care about
warranties yeah I need to go to repair
shop no that's so [\h__\h] up that's so
annoying why why would that happen what
why I was always talking good about this
phone I know I'm so scared now I'm never
going to let my battery hit zero yeah
it's so good because like my case is
like a warning for you well obviously
though people are saying just get a new
phone but like the pictures and stuff
yeah it's about the DAT she wants she
wants the stuff on the phone what the
[\h__\h] I don't want a new phone because
you know what that what will happen cuz
I'm already constantly keeping my
previous phone that I have I haven't
been using for like I don't know 2 years
or so I'm always keeping it around
because there's still like one or two
apps that I'm automatically logged in
that I just can't like you know
comfortable it's more comfortable this
way so if I get another phone I'll I'll
constantly be like even though one's
dead I'll be keeping one around still so
I'll have like five phones at some
point yeah I was already making fun of
her for all her
phones yeah but one it's don't work it's
not that much it's like one work phone
and one private phone and one old phone
for you know two apps but yeah we'll see
if we can fix it well maybe we'll look
into it more tomorrow if it doesn't
we're going to leave it plugged in all
night but for everyone's saying to hold
down the buttons I've already done every
done every button combination literally
have you triy turning it off and on
again yeah literally the screen will not
even come on it's just constantly black
screened it was weird because it showed
that it was like charging except with no
percentage and now now it doesn't it
doesn't even show that right no no it
doesn't oh yeah it stopped showing them
mhm so like now it's just a black screen
no no matter where we put it put it in
right it's
not I don't think it's a it against the
wall have you tried spitting on it have
you tried hitting it well great great
advice I think you can put it in the
freezer is that a serious um no I looked
that up too and people were saying
there's nothing to prove that that
actually works but that would maybe
imply that it got overheated or so but I
think it overheated at all it didn't
feel hot when it done yeah no it
definitely wasn't because you
know man yeah cuz it was cold microwave
it uh-huh uhhuh okay okay I'll try all
of that later give it a more yeah guess
what read yeah okay enjoy and there says
photos as a backdrop sorry that they're
not great they're fine they're
pretty the weather is just not so nice
oh well okay here we go wait I'll change
your
BTM maybe a bit louder guys what do you
think for the
atmosphere a little bit still really
quiet okay day
one yeah yes yeah checking checking for
balance okay okay day one today Ki and I
arrived at the males the first step
to make
it to the
island was to board a sea plane damn
girl you're riding yeah was originally
planning on taking photos of these pages
and showing them on screen but I don't
know would you have allowed me to do
that you handwriting
is
messy uh oh it's not is
it oh why did I stop it accidentally
okay um bought a SE plane which she did
with conf
[Laughter]
confidence however she was silent the
duration of the flight literally due to
the Roaring engine yeah it was too loud
it was super loud
yeah next she received a
woman a wolen necklace yeah yeah yeah
and was greeted by her Butler m is our
Butler okay um yeah they gave was like
little necklaces uh made out of palm
tree leaves or something like that
probably yeah that was nice they were
like playing music and all that too he
gave her a coconut drink which she
took
one
sip of before leaving no it was a bit
more than one sip it was not she took
like the littlest Sip and put it down
and then we
left no it was more than one sip I tried
cuz like I would I I the first time I
drank coconut juice and I was kind of
like like kind
of okay so we okay here bit more detail
cuz you started out with little detail U
but we went to this like check-in Lobby
uh where they gave everybody uh like
Shain or some bubbly alcohol right and
we were like the only ones in the room
that were like I'm sorry um can you give
us something non-alcoholic like no no
alcohol please no alcohol F please no
need to bring out these champagne
glasses and they brought us just the
thing that they probably normally give
to the children uhhuh so a full-on
coconut with a straw inside and this is
something that I you know it like
screams beach with kitchen right I've
never had that before have you had it
before no so that's like fascinating
right so looking forward to that even if
it's not like my favorite thing to drink
it it was just the experience of it was
amazing yeah real coconut real coconut
yeah real coconut were like like very
different from each other I do think
they added like uh yeah orange juice I
think they added orange juice into it I
I feel like it didn't taste strong
enough like orange like I it just tasted
like a tiny tiny bit but yeah but I
think that's because it was like the
straw went through an orange no that
would not have made the whole drink
taste like orange it was just very
slightly well either way she didn't like
it no well I did not dislike it I just
didn't like
it I didn't like it much did you like it
yeah I drank the whole thing but you
just drank it out of fear of it leaking
well that too but I liked it too cuz
yours was leaking a little bit Yeah but
they were beautiful
aesthetic
um before leaving before leaving it
behind for her Island Tour my Island
Tour mhm our Island Tour it was because
I was writing it as if I was observing
you from the bushes without being part
of it yeah I think I think it changes
like halfway through the
journal yeah they took us on a little
like a card golf cart thingy our Butler
like yeah remember how we had a butler
last time all I think in all these
Resorts that you get like a butler
assigned to
you who may take care of you or may
ghost you oh my God like ours we we'll
get to that yeah we'll get to
that
uh I'm going to write a Yelp
review after she settled into her nest
this is so funny I didn't expect you
to write in a similar style of me oh no
me I thought you would write so normally
but damn it I thought that was a genius
it it becomes more normal as it get
along I became less creative oh I tried
to stick to it as much as I could but
this start this is pretty good so far
very objective mhm after she settled
into her nest for the week uh changing
clothes is that a
period week per period changing clothes
period she wetted herself no she w w she
walked a great distance for lunch she
walked a great distance for lunch in
sandals it was cute it was cute they
were cute she ate a tuna wrap and
blueberry cheesecake before
taking taking a a bus back to her nest
sorry it's a bit hard to
read uh the Curious bird was eager to
enter the water so she didn't I I indeed
did I observed as
she what as she um looted looked at her
um wait looked at hermit crabs yes yes
and you looked at hermit it looks like
crops but okay uh crabs I collected I I
observed as
she looked at hermit crabs i' collected
for her to find as well as when she made
angels in the sand sof soft soft white
sand sand on the beach on the beach I
did make I rolled around the first day
because the sand like the closer you get
to the shore the
wow the smoother it is it is so
nice I had to roll around I was like
Marissa come over here join me in the
water and in the sand but you didn't
join
me um after washing up she made her way
on foot she made her way comma on foot
comma wow to the buffet to find some
dinner after eating her fill the
beautiful bird made her way back to her
nest for the night setting up some
streaming equipment I suppose looks like
I watman
though or I what
mer equipment before returing to bed
though she did stay up quite late
surfing the web dot do Dot and day
won now hold on
hard to read uh thank you for day one I
wait I will I'm looking forward to what
else you have to say please okay my
first day has like three or four pages
are you going to edit the now reading
now reading thank you guys by the way
yes what a story sorry K can't read my
handwriting not my fault okay I think
that's kind of you fault but it's okay
not my fault I could read most of it K's
Journal of Nissa
go I hope you can read mine what if
mine's shitty on my first day of
observing narissa the bird I began
my the rest of the bird luring her into
a comfortable environment louder please
to migrate to upon our arrival in the
Maldives the nerissa birds seemed to not
handle the heat very well while I
perceived the 29 celius as Celsius is
rather Pleasant before boarding a
mechanical bird to go to our final
migration destination slower slower
slower we rested a while in a lounge oh
the Nissa bird baffled me with her
incredible F incredible what thirst
thirst gulping down bottles of liquid in
one go emptying one after
another however she seems to not have
much strength and much what much what
which
what strength strength yes and kept on
asking me to open her bottles and other
things I wonder if this lack of strength
is a common thing among the narissa bird
upon longer observation it became very
clear to me that she the narissa bird is
an incredibly inquisitive Spectre uh-huh
Spectre species species
sorry I just can't read um species when
I asked her when I asked her about her
inquisitive nature she asked me what
inquisitive means surprising to me as I
was almost seeking confirmation to my
correct usage of the term yet this
american-based bird seem to be rather
clueless look I know what inquisitive
means but I also like don't do you guys
know what I mean like I could use
inquisitive in a sentence but if you ask
me what it means I can't tell you and I
think I told her that in the moment too
I was like look we're going to have to
Google it cuz I know what it means but I
don't know how to explain it to
you
roasted to defend myself
yeah objection she's bullying me
throughout the day she would several
times burst out in song regardless of
her surroundings especially in German
sounding songs this seems to be part
proof of her being a song bird but why
German but why German I asked about the
origins of her song and I learned that
four years ago she was in Infested by
German Paras oh [\h__\h] yeah I never
touched upon the parasite afterwards
anymore damn it I forgot about the
parasite called Elisabeth D Musical and
to this day she hasn't been able to get
rid of it I wonder if I can fix her [\h__\h]
anyway we took the mechanical bird and
arrived at
our our cage cage Nest seems to be a
popular nesting Place Pig turn do you
guys wait
I'll yes I hear it
definitely
wow her first meal on the island was
beef steak with mashed potatoes but to
reach this since we missed the shuttle
cart cart we had to walk quite a bit on
foot and since the narissa bird's
luggage came in a different mechanical
bird she didn't have a fitting oh a
fitting walking attire so I gave her a
pair of my sandals but after a while it
seemed to have done more damage than
help yeah after this she often pointed
out the pain in her feet unable to take
a bird bath in the ocean I took a small
dip without her after the narissa bird
enthusiastically spread protective
lotion over my body we didn't get much
sleep in the night before
enthusiastically H I was not that I was
normal about it what do you mean I
thought you were like happy very happy
to do it of course I've never had anyone
ask me to do that for them cuz I don't
usually go to the beach oh well I just
asked you to do my B and you went out to
like spray all over my body to help me
which was sweet of you yeah of course
it's hard to get the back of your legs
yeah I
know we didn't get much sleep in the
night before so we ended up taking a
revitalizing nap under my supervision
sadly my mental strength was too weak to
take charge and wake us up continuously
extending my alarm letting the bird
hibernate for three with three
exclamation points yeah hours too much
finally I got a a hold for myself and
woke the Sleepy Nissa bird who suggested
to sleep even
longer I thus dragged her to dinner
which consisted of a big versatile
buffet or should I say buffet buffet
buffet even for the first plate the
Nissa bird seems to not be be able to
resist her urge for fresh cut fruit from
the dessert section we finished our
devouring of nutrition and go back I set
up the broadcasting station and schedule
while the bird more and more cozies
herself up in her nest again falling
into a hallucinating trance earlier you
did remember when you were like you know
how it is when you like like half asleep
and you're hallucinating cuz you were
like saying something to me and I didn't
even say anything I heard you talk talk
to me I wasn't talking she wasn't
talking to me but I definitely heard her
talking but I know what you mean it
happens yeah yeah like I was just like
because she was there and she was doing
something and I was so sleepy I was just
hearing her talking to me therea was
tripping yeah that happens to me
whenever like people are in my room when
I'm trying to sleep so like if my sister
or brother come in and I'll like
hallucinate sleep talking you were sleep
talking sleep
talking where were we uh way before my
projected hibernation time additional
observation the nerissa bird repeatedly
expresses her admiration for me
throughout the day is she trying to
seduce me is it mating
season is that it yeah that's it okay
that's day one is it Mating Season
Mating Season yeah so yeah I just love
you thank you I love you
too well sorry um there may be more
roasts
incoming but also prais
me
okay can I just say she oh one one time
randomly she said please she
said okay and I was like oh my God you
sounded exactly like that Meme and and
since then every once in a while she
kept on saying it out of nowhere CU it
makes her laugh every single time yeah
now I requested she like do do the and
like hey
okay and her face is actually so perfect
as well when she does it oh my God she
does such a great okay okay she's so
good oh my God good luck Yay Day two
wait changing the thing so the worst
thing about day two and onward is I
started writing more per page so that
means you just read about one and maybe
2/3 pages but now all the pages are
going to be long that's fine that's
great I appreciate but with my
handwriting oh yeah that's what I'm
saying maybe I should have given you a
typewriter yeah I love typewriters essay
coming up okay good luck thank you day
to uh this morning I was awoken very
cutely as Kiana pushed my kuromi plush
into my face
yeah uh I suppose being on my phone had
woken her up oops sorry w
we talked until 700 a.m. before deciding
to make our way to the buffet for
breakfast once there the orange bird had
quite a variety I like how I call you
the narissa bird and you call me the
orange bird
or uh the orange bird had quite a
variety of items like a pancake how come
you're riding also in this like like
David atam Boro kind of way like how did
you know that I was for that I don't
know I don't know we did not talk about
doing that guys we just we haven't
looked at all no yeah we haven't we
haven't looked no no no no it was secret
until now yeah um a variety of items
like a pancake with Nutella orange juice
and an omelette after finishing up and
she gra she grabbed her snorkling gear
though I'd never have been I decided to
follow after her though it felt a little
scary to me she had an amazing
Show me natural confidence I couldn't
help but Envy for lunch we tried a
veget you just you just completely
skipped skipped over your own experience
of the soing she said we went I was
observing you okay okay we we'll get
that write about me so I about you yeah
it's okay that's that's how it's
supposed to be I couldn't help but like
write observations about both of us okay
uh
I couldn't help but Envy for lunch we
tried a vegetarian place that seemed to
only serve spicy food she tried
something recommended by the waiter
which turned out spicy anyway after that
we explored a new beach we found and she
was determined
to swim to swim in it
tomorrow she
[Music]
re
relaxed yeah taking you a while to like
I got to start at the beginning of the
sentence to get to get started you know
she relaxed before dinner which was at
the
buffet h ah I thought the relaxation was
at the buffet no okay the dinner was at
the buffet she ate her f with an
interesting life
[Music]
performance what was that say happening
happening
so I can read your handwriting almost
better than you before retreating home
from the night oh dream what that was
only one page you promised it would be
more oh I know why because I originally
said we should write it at the end of
the day mhm granted not only you but
also me ended up writing it always on
the next day yeah but I have better
recollection of my memories so some days
A Min are like pretty long because I
wrote them throughout the day so like
after we do an activity we'd come back
and I'd take a break and I'd write I
Journal it and then it would be more
detailed but then for days when I'd have
to write it the next day I was like I
don't know what did we do yesterday yeah
but it's okay cuz my side will have
things more detailed okay thank God for
my journal oh no I'm scared how many
pages did you do about me so let's go
ki's Journal of niss
Red by Nara day
two Doo unfortunately we woke up way too
early today at 5:00 a.m. but I think
both the narissa bird and me were
excited to check out the breakfast bouet
mhm we both go for a lot of the same
things like fruit and Nutella crepes but
the narissa bird has a special craving
for bacon that's true especially the
crispy and dark type the narissa bird
curious curiously observes differences
in bacon bread and other Foods after
satisfying oh well wait no on that
that's because uh where I'm
from it tastes different the bacon
didn't taste the same and the bread
didn't taste the same and it wasn't bad
it just tasted different and you also
often like especially here in Austria
you've been like pointing out and like
being fascinated by calorie differences
they're like so freaking different
chunky wonky it's crazy what are you
doing here she thinks we're chatting
she's like mommy's not streaming she's
not streaming she just has a friend over
a friend over I can come sit by to
computer okay sorry let me
continue after a satisfying breakfast by
the beach we make our way to
the to closest snorkeling place to the
closest snorkeling place I convinced the
narissa bird to give it a try and while
she was frightened and nervous about it
with my help she conquered it and
quickly learned how being a bird doesn't
mean doesn't mean that you can't be a
fish can't also be a fish with this
newly acquired skill I hope to show her
even nicer snorkeling places yay her
first time
snorkeling terrifying terrify but it was
like right at the arrival dock you know
there's like a long dock that goes out
into still a very shallow area of the
water so it was nice it was nice because
we could control when we needed a break
and since it was first time it was
really great because I often needed a
break because uh it was my first time so
I was like of course foring how to
breathe and get my first time needed
some time to adjust to how to breathe
and all that it was fine but we both
like never really like at drank water
sea water and all that so I we did
really well no we did very well and but
it wasn't like in terms of like coral
and fish quality there were a lot of
beautiful fish but like no special
sightings usually so it was a small
coral reef yeah yeah
s Upon Our return to our Nest we wanted
to quickly rinse off our feathers which
due to our lack of patience I suppose
led us to taking a bird bath together
groundbreaking development that's that
one the picture right now yeah yeah
yeah um oh you made me lose my ground
baking development in my study of the
nerissa bird I think I have gained her
trust we then oh actually was it that no
this was like that was just a shower
this was
after the footprints okay um um so that
was just a shower okay okay okay we then
took another nice nap until lunchtime
this time I decided to go to a
vegetarian restaurant at the end of the
island hoping to avoid having to eat too
many of her fellow animal colleagues I
almost lost the newly gained Trust on
our way there because she wasn't sure if
we really had gone to the right
way um this made me doubt my instincts
for a moment until I regained confidence
and her trust as of course it was the
right way the nerisa bird impressed me
with her strength and tolerance for
spicy food expressing interest
in flipping the
page sharing a meal
with is a famous
uh what what does this what does all
this say sharing a meal with famous
spice champ
jenma spice JMA I hope they end up
making this a reality one day as I
cannot keep up with jma's spice levels
myself anyway after a lot of deep
conversations and a deeper Insight
who into the intricate mind of the
nerissa bird and a lot of dessert we
made our way to the spa for an
incredible massage among tasty looking
koifish the narissa bir and I enjoyed
the massage greatly we went back to our
Nest did you even mention a massage in
yours
no where was the massage you forgety
spaghetti I literally just forgot about
it because I didn't feel the effects by
the next day ah I did not feel relaxed
um it was still good though it was
really good we went back to our nest in
serious danger to asleep again but with
the power of tangents we managed to stay
awake until feeding time wow the
restaurant was disturbingly noisy from
not bird sounds coming from mysterious
dot dot dot pling plong machines yes
there was a band okay after the feeding
season we used our time to communicate
with my session feeding session after
our feeding session we used our time to
communicate with my chicken audience via
a broadcast which was a lot of fun and
immediately knocked the narissa bird out
a after
yeah electricity from my c okay okay
that was day two
two w w w w so you can already sense a
pattern of sleepiness and food is a big
topic and yeah she learned how to
snorkel yeah and I was hoping that it
would kind of like because you picked it
up so easily and you were so good at it
right away I was hoping that you would
like see it as a new like hobby at least
when you were out on a
vacation uh I don't usually go anywhere
with an
ocean that's a lie what about the Cruis
I've been on a cruise once yeah and I
didn't like that and it was by you
didn't like the cruise yeah my family
just wanted me to go Oh you talked so
well about the cruise though um that's
just cuz I experienced it
okay so but yeah even then I I only went
swimming once when I was on a cruise I
didn't even use the pools so no
snorkling ever again I mean maybe maybe
if I go somewhere that has clear waters
like the malds cuz I can't imagine
snorkeling in like California a place
like this where it makes sense yeah yeah
yeah I'd try it again oh yeah okay okay
okay
why are you
crying because M
because it's fun and but you gave up on
it soon after so
no I went on the whole tour with you
yeah but then you didn't want to go I
want okay what you guys got to
understand is when so when we were doing
it solo I did have a lot of fun she'll
probably talk about it in her journal
but when when we went on the other
one I don't know if you guys know this
but I got the
anxiety so um the moment water would get
in my mask I'd kind of feel the
sensation of drowning even though I
could still breathe because suddenly I
couldn't breathe out of my nose even
though I wasn't even breathing out of it
and um my mask felt really really tight
around my face too and obviously we like
couldn't take a break and they gave us
life jackets but they weren't inflated
so I was sitting there and I was like
trying to like take a break but I like
couldn't because I had to keep like
actively swimming so I'm trying to like
get the water out of my mask reposition
it and untighten it but all while I'm
trying to also keep myself afloat and
like it's not like you can just go back
to the boat and do all the stuff and
then come back like you have to wait
like what did it take like 5 minutes is
maybe yeah so like I I was starting to
get really panicky so like again if if
it's like a very small group and it's
like very like controlled and you can
easily get get out take a break I feel
like that I I really I'd really like
that because I really likeed looking at
the I really like looking at everything
but just the the act of like being far
away from the boat and like not actually
having an inflated life
s like made it really stressful for me
that I was like the next one's just
going to be like that too I don't want
to go cuz I I Kiana luckily was like I'm
feeling sick we got to get out of here
yeah I mean that's all into journal and
and called the book The the book over
but like for me I was I was so nervous
too because I actually had asked the guy
I was like Hey how do I how do I inflate
my vest because I was trying to explain
to him that I needed to
float and he was just like you're
fine and I was like bro but you weren't
fine I wasn't fine you were doing so
much I was fine because pretty much
immediately after you came over and you
like I need to call the boat I'm done
and I was like oh good I can I can hold
on until it get gets
here bam yeah but I I feel like I always
saw you like like you know just like for
example even when I looked at you under
water when we were both having our heads
under the water you seemed fine well you
know you seemed to like you you were
doing so well when people are drowning
it's not the way you think they look
like and people actually look fairly
normal why didn't you say anything to me
you were not close to me for the
majority of the time what do you
mean I was around she was she we'll talk
about it more when we get there why
don't we go to the next day okay day
three right yeah day
three the lovely bird awoke around 7
a.m. sleeping 2 hours later than
yesterday Oh you mean we fell asleep
later and we woke up later or
what we s we we we woke up at 5: the day
before so we slept 2 hours later than
the day before yeah yeah we we slept so
to say longer but not really total not
really after lounging we were on our way
to breakfast at the usual Buffet she had
EG Benedict and two Nutella crabs where
egg Benedict were kind of weird because
they were with salmon I did never had an
X benedict with someone they normally
have ham right yeah I mean I don't know
I've actually never had an X Benedict hi
mo hi
Mone
and two Nutella crabs of banana yeah I
guess I had two yeah you you were she
loved the grapes yeah but besides that
besides these free things I didn't eat
anything else yeah pretty much you know
I just went for like like eggs and
grapes things that they would make for
me there while you like mixed things
that they would make for you there with
your own own creations of
plates after eating despite the danger
she was determined to swim
danger you're not you're not supposed to
swim after eating oh that's what you
mean d to wait like 30
minutes uh a storm was potentially on
the way so I understood
she
grabbed grasped her snorkel and changed
before hopping on her bike making a way
to the secret Beach from the day before
she admired the hermit crabs before
taking to the water BFF snorkeling both
snorkeling and floating on the currents
she seemed to be enjoying the C the cool
turquoise Waters she took a break in a
swinging chair to soak up the sun as I
confirmed to watch from a distance
confirmed right as I continued to watch
from a distance after we headed back to
take a nap before going snorkling wow we
slept so much before a yeah when it came
time to jump in the water she was a bit
reluctant yeah I thought you were were
like you jumped in first and then I was
like I
can't yeah I I couldn't observe this
part properly because I had to jump in
first yeah and then I I you you like
like like recovered from the jump
properly and then swam like a little bit
away from the boat and I you weren't
like watching so I thought you didn't
even see this part I I I heard about it
though you heard yeah from
me uh W who W it was it and when it came
to jump into the water she was a bit
reluctant she carefully sat down and
pushed herself into the water no uh the
the staff gave me a hand and I let
myself down I'm sorry I didn't see it
okay it's okay there were uh bits of
tropical bits lots of tropical fish
Stingrays and even some tuna tuna she
got seasick
before leaving the water the bird
managed to get back to shore without
getting sick I was so close though yeah
I I was like she's going to PUK her
brains out but I
yay yeah even the staff like noticed and
and they were like they like look at the
Horizon yeah look at the Horizon and I
thought like he pointed over to the
Horizon but I thought for a moment that
cuz he didn't say anything clearly I
thought he meant just like don't throw
up in the boat if anything throw up over
there into the water I thought either
that or maybe he means the horiz yeah no
he's trying to help you yeah very nice
very nice and after relaxing a bit we
left to get a light late lunch she ate a
tuna Pizza which was quite foreign to me
yeah I've never heard of a tuna pizza
every time I talk about it on stream all
the North Americans and so on they're
all like
tuna tuna
Pizza what tuna Pizza is so weird tuna
Pizza what apparently it's thing in
Italy which you know which is the pizza
country right where it stems from where
it comes from so they should know what
they're talking about yeah but like I
just don't aspire to eat fish so why
would I want to eat fish on Pizza see
but you know how I don't really eat
seafood and all that either but I like
tun Pizza well I try to bite and uh
money you should try it before you say
no yeah yeah okay yeah you had a bite
but I I said don't judge it by this one
because it's like not yeah I I'd try it
again if Kiana took me to a place where
she was like the tuna pizza here is good
because honestly the the pizza there in
general wasn't very great like it was
pretty cheap crust yeah it was
fun that was okay but yeah I try it
again but yeah no it is weird but that's
just cuz like I've never eaten fish with
cheese or like tomato sauce like cuz
usually I I eat fish at Sushi otherwise
I don't really eat fish so um with ging
soy sauce or like eel sauce so it was
very very different and I already I like
tuna but not really cooked tuna because
I only raw I don't yeah I don't like
cooked fish because it makes me feel
like I'm eating cat food because of how
the the meat texture is so okay um yeah
I I wasn't I wasn't a
fan but yeah okay she ate tuna piz which
was uh quite foreign to me we napped
from then till dinner when we woke up we
rode the shuttle to the same Beach we uh
swam at earlier to be met with a candle
lit dinner she commented uh on the sax
player who was not really playing and we
chatted away yeah we think he was not
really
playing obervation I'm positive he was
not playing during dessert uh rain
suddenly started to fall and It
came it came
heavy it yeah it the rain came heavy you
say that like that in English it came
heavy I don't know I don't
know it that's what that is right I
guess
okay say it say
it okay
uh it came happy
we nested rested no rushed back to our
room as we had a stream but got soaked
oh my what the [\h__\h] is this writing what
is this it's like a squib
do we got soaked in the process to add
insult to injury our our Wi-Fi got
knocked out yeah remember the Smash Bros
stream that was here we continued to
play Smash where she showed great
potential
and I don't know if there's really
potential me me smashing you is just
well
lowlevel really lowlevel
skill
and I wouldn't even praise myself much
for that like generally like you were I
guess an
easy victim I'm never playing games with
you again I'm I'm going to find a new
Oshi no wow well it's okay because you
already have a you oosi I was never
really your true OSI I know now that I
was just a bridge to lead you to your
real oi Elizabeth [\h__\h] the empress who
is also Austrian what a coincidence I
just I guess I just have a type
beautiful Austrian woman type or maybe I
was just a tool all along no
okay where was I I don't
know what the [\h__\h] was I okay she showed
great potential and uh act actually yeah
actually kicked KCK my ass I'll be back
tomorrow for more observations that was
a hard read just because it fall
right okay so we back to Kiana's Journal
of n of the same day I think yeah yeah
enjoy day
threee day three we start this wonderful
day a little bit later than before we
woke up around 6:30 a.m. and went to
breakfast an hour later different
different record than yours your says
seven uh trust me well I think mine was
correct you're making up numbers trust
me no she's lying um uh whose Journal
has been not missing the massage
[Laughter]
I went to breakfast an hour later the
narissa bird gathered herself an
American style
breakfast happily yes I was a bit
distracted by sharks SL dophins in the
water I showed you the footage though
did you see it the did that was one of
those things mhm crazy so I couldn't pay
much attention to her unfortunately but
the bird really overestimated her
possible food and take sometimes
understandably since I apparently
inspired her to get a crepe with bananas
on her last plate but she also ate
yogurt with nuts but didn't you before
you got the crap with bananas didn't you
also get a normal crap with Nutella mhm
so you also got we both got two on that
day
yeah
yeah she also ate yogurt with nuts every
day very healthy well you were actually
wrong I only ate yogurt with nuts the
first day and then it was oatmeal every
yeah but you added nuts anyway of course
I yeah generally that's just you know it
look like something something but
oatmeal and yogurt are not the same
things well excuse me
princess I was right with the nuts
that's the point I I was trying to make
very healthy breakfast at least for that
part after breakfast I wanted to go for
an early swim so that the Nissa bird
tanked along only to watch me swim and
collect lots of shells we have quite the
collection now we didn't have an
appetite for lunch early so we took
a a light nap mhm
instead after that we got ready for our
snorkeling trip we went out with a a
boat a boat but not very far the narissa
bird seemed rather calm this
time yeah until under until the guide
said that we might see Turtle sharks and
manta rays wait sharks yeah that made us
a bit anxious H even
me but we didn't see any sharks in the
end thankfully once we found the spot
where we would snorkel they made us jump
out of the boat and the narissa bird
went first I watched her jump down
completely emerged even her head into
the water for a moment due to the big
jump and was astonished at her bravery
they told me to go next but I would not
show the same bravery and instead sat
down on the edge and had
then help me down how
embarrassing we then were guided along
the edge of the reef we did see some
cool stuff and the narissa bird seemed
to do so well some sometimes when I
looked at her under the water under the
water I would see her dog paddling with
her hands an interesting technique for a
bird maybe a dog friend taught her yeah
maybe full did after around 40 m of
Hardcore SNK snorkeling I was snorkling
snorkling I was feeling pretty sick so I
requested to go back to the boat the
narissa bird expressed her relief as she
wanted to go back to but couldn't say so
the narissa bird reported her dread
dread of the ocean and fear of drowning
drowning to me which surprised me since
she was doing so well but last she said
she would not join me on any after
excursions hence forth hence forth sad
my experiment has failed
failed after all of this exciting
exercise we went for a late lunch and
then back to our
place so
[Music]
sad the nerissa bird wanted to take
another nap until the dinner second nap
I think I did not r a minute but stayed
awake while she rested our dinner was a
barbecue at a beach literally the spot
where we went to early in the morning
there was I almost misread that word
with an E and A sax player who seemed a
bit fake to us but nonetheless the
narissa bird seems to enjoy like why did
you change it because I asked you do you
like
jazz and that's a purposefully you know
um a meem oh oh I see I see and I asked
you about the Bee Movie then and you
said watched it but I didn't mm seems to
like jazz the food was okay but sadly
not worth the $200 bill agreed we got
caught in pouring rain at the end so we
tried to get back as soon as we could
for our smashing experiment broadcast
sadly after all that uh hurry hurry and
effort I put into setting it all up our
internet died 10
minutes I was so disappointed and sad
and lonely we played a bit on our own
because I needed to see the vast
collection of Fighters she accumulated
impressive the narissa bird may have not
been a great fighter herself yet but she
seemed capable of building an army yeah
which is important too better be wary
wait wait
wait okay yeah better be wary of the
dangerous nerissa bird who can build an
army maybe she can't fight herself but
you know many kings in the past and
queens I guess they they just like tell
the Army to do [\h__\h] and they don't
really do anything themselves yeah yeah
besides ordering people around but you
have to be a a great only a great leader
is able to inspire a huge Army to do and
to die for them yeah only a great leader
can do that and I convinced SEO to be my
[\h__\h] and Cloud
stri poor poor [\h__\h] yeah you got to
change it yeah wait wait are we at day
four yeah day four
a day four out of five by the way so sad
what a short vacation
right I thought it was seven days but
two of those days were for travel which
I did not take in
mine
oops n is is Journal of Kiana read by
Kiana day four we both awoke rather
early at about 500 a.m. what the you
know this is so unlike me right me too
but I think it's
mostly because of you like me adjusting
to you like normally I think like even
like here I sleep I fall asleep so late
and I wake up so late and I sleep longer
but also I do uh I would say it's also
just like I guess the the Sun the energy
that you get from the Sun added on to my
ability to sleep less in the night which
I don't know if it's a good or bad thing
because it ended up making us take naps
all the time uhh and I did say that
especially to
you um what thank you smash Rock
especially to you you cuz you are always
like I'm I'm tired tired tired I guys
tell me if you agree but I think she's
not helping herself by taking naps
because she's just making herself
real in in regular times I don't take
naps ever so it's really weird for me
because yeah I literally can't and don't
take naps what so it was so weird that
like this whole this whole time they say
true though what that naps just Mak you
more tired and yeah but usually I don't
take them but like I think because I was
severely jet lagged because of the time
difference um and then like I was kind
of adjusting to Austria and then we went
to the malds and then suddenly there was
a 4our time difference well 4 hours
isn't much like a 4 hours is a lot what
do you
mean in America the most I ever get is 2
hours of time difference what do you
mean yeah but it's like compared to like
from austa to Japan or America to AER
where time difference makes up like day
and night it's still like mostly the
same
daytime yeah you know whatever whatever
whatever making excuses making excuses
for napping so much napping for up
sleeping all the time I don't
know yeah and and I I have to say I love
naps but yeah I think I was like a
little bit
like like temp tempted dragged into the
Naps not seduced to nap by the
seductress
nura yeah I mean we definitely got a lot
of rest thanks to the naps and I do have
to say I liked waking up up early
because we were always early at
breakfast so not too many people there
and usually early in the morning the the
ocean was calmer and I don't know it
just felt nice to wake up
Ear but I also wanted to sleep longer
like who the [\h__\h] wakes up at 5:00 a.m.
on a vacation like not [\h__\h] normal
people yeah that's not like what the
[\h__\h] I should be sleeping in and like
going to breakfast 30 minutes before it
ends that was the plan oh well so we
both awoke rather early at about 5:00
a.m. she laid in bed motionless for 2
hours leading me to believe she was
asleep but it was not so no no no we
rushed to get dressed for 700 a.m.
breakfast she got her usual Nutella crab
and tried their new fresh juice grape
grape juice they every day they had like
different juices I mean every day they
had orange juice too yeah every day they
had orange juice and pineapple juice
some days they didn't have pineapple
juice really cuz I felt like it was
always the mixed the mix mixed one that
got swapped out which was the red juice
there was definitely one day where I
didn't have pineapple juice cuz I was
looking for it and I didn't have it yeah
but yeah they had the the the mixed the
red looking berry juice yeah and then
they had the grape juice which I'm I'm
surprised never had grape juice before
but that was amazing that was really
good it was so good yeah Yum Yum Yum Yum
Yum and then I I was hoping to find
grape juice IRL but no didn't find it
yet there's no grape juice out there why
we'll find it you never had oh oh
two what some some Americans out there
are commenting never had grape juice
grape juice what I mean no no no like
fresh grape juice like we're not just
talking about like yeah the grape juice
you get from the store oh and
specifically the green ones cuz if
anything I only see like you know purple
yeah I've had plenty of like red grape
juice but usually in America they add so
much [\h__\h] sugar it doesn't really
taste like grapes anymore mhm and like
it tastes completely like this was like
fresh and it really tasted like green
grapes grap not not
like you know yeah like the grapes that
you turn into wine I guess well you do
turn green grapes into wine too but
anyway so yeah yeah yeah saw this n
grape juice grape juice tried the new
fresh juice grape was surprisingly good
after we went outside to look at the
water she spotted a family of crabs
traversing the rocks oh yeah then turned
to me like she wanted a hug she is so
cute we checked out the nearby pool
where she spotted a funny bird we saw
back on day one yes the twerking bird
finally as
we twerked no as
we walked back to
our she also took an adorable photo of a
gecko we arrived back to plan the day um
we decided to go for a swim and I joined
her this time yes she called The Butler
to see if he can help blow up our
floaties he did
um and we were on our way sorry that
looked
weird we decided to try a paddle boat
first my side was missing a pedal oh
yeah but we managed to managed okay okay
it was quite silly trying to get it back
though after we have after we hopped in
the ocean on our float not after we
hopped in hopped in our ocean what no
after we hopped in the ocean on our
floaties she had a donut oh yeah yeah I
ate a donut in the water no she had a
donut sh I will add words here shaped
floaty and I had a mesh peanut shaped
one no mesh yeah mesh okay like the
middle part was mesh right and peanut
shaped peanut shaped I didn't know how
to describe the shame yeah it was just
like a normal
like yeah yeah I guess peanut is pretty
good yeah was like peanut shape with you
have with like a net in the middle so
you can sit in it you know you all wait
a like what were you snacking on Peanuts
while riding this cuz we had peanuts in
the room and at some point you snacked
them my first time snacking on the
peanuts was
today I just yeah I just stole them
every time and put them in my bag for
later but you may have had peanuts on
your mind because of that
yeah she gently pulled me
out since since I had a hard time
paddling in in mine we laughed a lot
before deciding to try out the pool we
found that morning we found out there
was free ice cream in the facility by
the pool we both had two bowls and I
urged her to try the vanilla which had
real vanilla bean in it she liked it
Oo we floated for a bit and messed
around in the pool for a while and I was
acting silly to get
her to
smile it was funny
I I took some she she made like a what
do you call that pose like a I made a
crab pose I bent my legs so that like uh
I was in like a deep squat but like with
my legs spread and then I put out my
hands like in crab hands and then uh I
was lowered so only my head was above
water which then made my body look very
very small and my head disted yeah it
almost looked like I had like no torso
yeah and I thought I'm going to take the
perfect picture of this and when when I
showed you the pictures afterwards you
thought it was so funny cuz they turned
out so good you really look distorted as
F I'm glad I did it to make you laugh
and I'm glad that it looked absolutely
awful you're so dorky you're so
dorky that's what I do
[Music]
yeah messed out messed around in a pool
for a while and I was acting silly to
get her to smile we ended it by taking
some pictures and then headed back to
the room to relax for the first time
this trip our paths would divide as
she's going snorkeling but I'm too
nervous to try again I will rest and
suddenly present tense I will rest and
wait uh to her about what she sees
that's because I I actually stopped
writing yeah so I I ended up starting to
write in present tense
because you know I don't know because I
don't know after seeing her
off you you saw me off from the bed
right like not from the room basically
yeah yeah it's still seeing you off what
do you mean and I I kept on looking back
while I was walking towards the ocean
and like sadly like I wish I wish Nisa
was
coming I kep looking back like please
come with me
but yeah here comes the
twist uh after seeing her off I laid
down to sleep she came back it was
cancelled due to the wind we
had then I don't know so we went for a
late lunch we returned quickly realizing
we had a lot of bless you a lot of time
before our massages so we sometimes got
[Music]
stuck what wedding what
stuck watching trashy
TV realizing we had a lot of time before
our massages we some uh how got stuck
watching trashy American TV it was a lot
of fun we got long massages after uh and
went to a nice
dinner what the [\h__\h] is
this
um I what does the rest of it say long d
oh uh long massages after we went to
nice dinner D the part time portions the
portions were small okay that was the
end of day four two pages girl woo
that's good look it took you forever to
read that be glad I only wrote two
pages but you really want to read two
more pages like that yeah oh well it's
okay because we we um finish each
other's sandwiches yeah that's what I
was going to say oh my God marry me like
aren't we already married didn't we just
go on like our our no it was a friendly
Moon keep telling yourself that and now
reading K's Journal of narissa read by
Nissa day four the narissa bird and I
had a hard time sleeping
because I feel the
a because I had the AC I had the AC on
the wrong setting
sadly sadly so we woke up again very
early and went for the usual breakfast
after breakfast we exp explored yes the
premises because we noticed a pool that
we didn't make use of yet to my great
Delight I found a common
Sandpiper yes that's the name I looked
at up common Sandpiper cute twerking
bird I was hoping to find for my
separate bird studies after watching the
wiggling bird I brought the narissa bird
to do a pedal boating with me but we
quickly got bored of it and just swam a
bit with the floaty prompts that I
brought for us however the waves were a
bit strong and the narissa
bird was in permanent danger of being
swept away so I spontaneously suggested
to try the pool instead this turned out
to actually be a great idea great idea W
what does this one say great idea oh you
read it anyway what dides it say I just
read it what does it say as it was
pretty chill and they had one of the
narissa bird's favorite things ice cream
ice cream for free even for free she
especially loves the vanilla the vanilla
one was so good okay I need to defend
myself us usually I'm a chocolate girl
but like it was so creamy like compared
to like the fruit ones I really like
fruit ice cream especially like
strawberry but like it was very like it
felt like watery and even i' like turned
on and find ice crystals as to where the
vanilla one just felt very very creamy
all the way through like it definitely
didn't feel like I was eating frozen
dessert which is often ice cream in the
States because there's so much air and
like liquid in it that's not cream um
but yeah it was pretty tasty mhm um she
especially loved the vanilla one after
several skoops of ice cream we treated
or we tried out of the pool and had
great fun I even managed to take some
spicy pictures of her we also played
with a ball yeah that that I blew up
like a boss yeah that [\h__\h] took forever
you're amazing for that oh my yeah like
I I bought a little ball that I hope we
could play around with and then I tried
I started blow trying to blow it up and
it was kind of hard so narissa gave it a
try and she was like this is impossible
it's not working and then she left to do
what to get I was getting I was getting
something something something she wanted
me to go get something back from the
room so I was like okay you stay here
and you relax I'll go get it and then um
I I forget what I was getting though but
I remember I came back with the dut too
but that was not what you said yeah
maybe yeah and and then I was like okay
I'm going to blow this up anyway because
I know it works it just takes a while
and I blew it up and I it was hard to
breathe but it was done she did like a
boss after this great time at the
chlorine bird bath we went back to the
chlorine bird bath yeah we went back to
the nest and the nerissa bird introduced
me to a part of her culture American
trash TV I was not un unfamiliar with it
generally so I also I also showed her
one of my own favorites I almost fell
asleep on her shoulder but we had to go
to our second overpriced massage it was
good but maybe not worth
$220 per person yeah is that what you
wrote there p PE yeah per person wait
what the hello this I'm not turning in
I'm just kidding um we then went
straight to our dinner where we enjoyed
Korean style pork belly and lamb
fillet where she enjoyed
K and shared many stories of her life
with me we were both very tired but the
stream that we had
uh the stream that we then had was still
very fun and energetic the song bir
Nissa of course sang ever so
beautifully after that we finished
noticing watching watching the show I
got her hooked on and fell asleep in a
this time way cooler room thanks AC
thanks
I it was so nice when the AC was fixed
cuz it got so hot at night like the in
the day it would be fine but I think
being under the covers and being in like
kind of warmer
pajamas we got so she's so
cute movie is in the bo Sor she missed
her cat so much that now she's not
caring about me no it's not true okay
what shows we showed each other I was
showing her 90day fiance but
specifically the episodes with Ed and
Rose and I need to drag her cuz she was
like Ed seems like a nice guy she seemed
fine like I don't understand you were
telling me that he's so shitty such a
shitty person but all the footage you
show me I mean it was like I I I I kind
of felt for him I felt bad for him oh my
God can you believe it no
NE he's an [\h__\h] and she just did not
get it the white yeah like a little bit
white but he's mostly small yeah she
didn't understand yeah are you insane
well but the parts that she shot me she
was like he's right if she wants if she
wants him to shave his beard she should
compromise and shave her no no I didn't
say she should but like I thought I said
like it it would be a nice compromise if
she doesn't want him to have a beard and
and he doesn't want her to have leg hair
if you want to like date each other like
you have to make compromises in general
like you know if you wanted to be
successful you know I think that's just
fair you
know well but then she showed me
something worse worse tell tell about it
tell me about it worse well um yeah so I
I know my fair share of American trash
TV and there's this one show that uh
what was it called love at first kiss I
think yes love at first kiss i' never
heard of this [\h__\h] it's a pretty simple
show where someone stands in a wide ass
room studio room and and then another
person walks in and they instead of like
talking really sometimes they talk a
little bit but but generally the goal is
just kiss and then there is a second
date where if if the person one of them
liked the kiss they will show up if not
they won't show up
and then if they if they show up and
they also liked this date you know
getting to know each other then they go
on to a final date a proper date cuz
that one is just a the first one is just
a speed date sounds awful it's so funny
because they got the weirdest characters
in that show so there was one lady who
kept on appearing she first she was the
one to be kissed to wait in the room and
have the person come to her and kiss her
but she wasn't she appeared three times
first time guy comes in who wasn't badl
looking right all of these guys were not
bad looking and she's like no my God I'm
not going to kiss someone I'm not
attracted to I can't believe you're just
like are you for real like she really
was like that and then they they got her
in a second time later on on a different
day and person comes in yeah new person
same thing same thing again yeah she's
like oh my God like what like oh my God
and then the dudes are also like like
bewildered like literally why are you on
this show if like you know the premise
of the show is like Kiss just kissing
someone and then leave and if you're not
ready to do that unless it's the
absolute most perfect guy for you well
she literally stated she like I have
really high standards he needs to be
this this this this which is just so
unrealistic in the first place yeah but
yeah CU there were I feel like there
were guys who partially met her
requirements but were not perfect she's
like he was like short and then one of
them she was like I couldn't even tell
if he was a man and I was like what what
are you even talking about so crazy she
was so and she did that three times well
and the last time the guy really was
pissed off he was well he I'm convinced
that what happened is they were like we
need to get her off the show but she
won't leave so I'm convinced they found
someone from the staff who look was
literally her type with all the things
that she described cuz he was all the
things that she described he was mascul
he was tall like he like literally all
the things he was talking about
physically he looked like and he said oh
no I can't I can't and he come he he
this guy came back and he was like can I
just ask why yeah he he seemed pretty
salty about it yeah I honestly I didn't
interpret him as being salty I totally
thought that th th this guy was staged
and told to go in and if rejected to
confront her maybe cuz she was crazy I
mean honestly like don't go on the show
if you're going to be like rejecting
literally because you're not this is not
supposed to be an option rejecting
someone you can reject them after the
kiss like not go to the the whole point
is to see the chemistry yeah so wow free
times turns out turns off but the real
the real crazy guy yeah yeah yeah so
there was several crazy guys but there
was one I really wanted her wanted net
to get to know cuz there's one legendary
one who um yeah he he's really bad at
kissing but first time first time he
comes he's also one of the like people
who come in several times first time he
comes in to uh kiss someone and he's
like it's my first kiss yeah and then it
was like really awkward it was really
bad it wasn't the proper kiss he kept
his eyes open and so on and it but she
went to the speed date after yeah
because probably she was curious like
what the [\h__\h] was that yeah but then she
rejected him even though he was like
really excited then he comes uh in for a
second round because iess the directors
like him but he walks in to kiss the
lady and he just gives her a peck on her
hair on the side of his cheek cuz I
guess he like got really nervous and he
was like [\h__\h] like first he was really
confident in the interview he was like I
now oh that was his first kiss ever in
his whole life by the way yeah and then
he was like I now have kissed a girl so
now I'm more confident I can do this he
was really like yeah he goes in he like
gets really embarrassed I guess or
whatever shy and then kisses her on the
cheek and the lady is like what the [\h__\h]
isn't this like a kissing show what was
this yeah oh my God and he always kissed
with his eyes open yeah always and then
after this spectacle they get him even
though they normally don't do this they
get him a kissing coach cuz I guess the
directors really like him and they're
like I'm invested in this dead pen she
was so she literally came in she was
like talking like this and then she was
like I've like kissed like Italian
princes so I have experience and I was
like when does that even
yeah and she was on The Bachelor for
example too yeah yeah yeah yeah so she
teaches him uh what the one thing she
didn't teach him is to close his [\h__\h]
eyes yeah he never would close his
eyes oh my God so he he kind of like
gets better at it somewhat I mean I mean
I don't know I I would certain extent I
wouldn't know
[Music]
but I don't know it looked
like I I think if I was on this show and
I was kissing someone for the first time
I do not think I would involve tongue at
all just cuz like any first kiss I don't
think you should put your tongue in
someone's house yeah but I guess at
least for this show you should at least
kiss him on the lips yeah yeah yeah no
definitely kiss on the lips and it can
still I guess be passionate but like
sticking your tongue in someone's mouth
no so it's like but she was teaching him
to use tongue so of course so the next
girl he got sent in and it was the last
one right this because this was like the
finale episode anyway um they sent in
this girl and she's really cute and he
um grabs her by the back of the head
which is what the lady told him to do
and I can see oh my God for oh yeah I
can see him sh like shoving his tongue
down her throat they're both really bad
at kissing that's the thing that's why
they a perfect match they yeah I was
looking and I was like this looks like
the most disgusting kiss it was
fascinating though cuz like he kept his
eyes open and it was creepy but she like
looked like she was kind of like dead
she she looked like she was dead fishing
it but after she was like he kissed like
a prince
charming yeah she was so happy about it
that's why they're so perfect for each
other and oh it's also so funny cuz like
her her her lipstick was all over her
own face and his face yeah smudged all
over but also they they like
kept their faces completely straight
when kissing each other they don't like
you know flip it over no no it was
amazing so of course they go on the
speed date speed date was wonderful she
tells them about her dogs that are
really important to her like my dogs are
really important yeah I just want you to
know she has cats too but she didn't
bring him sad yeah yeah and then oh yeah
he already starts talking about maybe
she's the one for life every single
person who came in here and I'm sure
this part was scripted but every single
person was like maybe I'll finally find
true love like yeah that was this one
really religious lady yeah and she was
placed with this guy who's like I like a
lot of tongue I like when it's intense
and I was like oh my God they've made
the worst pairing already like they know
this isn't going to work oh my yeah but
then they go on the speed day that works
fine and then they go on the on the
proper date which was a picnic where
they again kissed
beautifully I mean I wouldn't call that
beautiful it was a sight to
behold it was indeed a to be and then on
a later episode even though this is
really not something they do they did
like a like a they met them again cuz
normally it ends there but they met them
again and he brings her to the original
Studio everything is like with rose
pedal and he proposes to her yeah and
they probably they they didn't say how
long how much time has passed but it
really didn't seem like much yeah it was
crazy yeah um and she was so happy of
course she said yes yeah so don't watch
love it first kiss what you loved
it what do you mean don't watch Let's do
let's do let's do the next journal entry
shall we sure
yeah Beautiful Trash TV so
funny so is a day5 yeah K's Journal of
Nissa
no nissa's Journal
of name Marissa's
Journal Kwa k
last this is the last D yeah but then we
have an overview later so yes okay day
five it's our final day on the island
and Kiana wake woke me up cutely by
grabbing my hand I was like staring at
you for a while before that okay hoping
for you to wake up no you didn't she
really wanted breakfast so we
rushed over to get it she had an English
breakfast and a crap she wanted to go
snorkeling after but I was very anxious
for her as the wind was strong yeah I
was going to go on a snorkling trip out
like a little bit more outside with a
boat and I was really excited for it but
it was kind of Stormy yeah on our way uh
uh out we found a Hermit without a shell
oh no a The Hermit oh
no despite me answering K's please to
bring uh
bring ah a shell bring one bring a shell
I think they were all too small more
sadly our what indifference in uh
interference interference
uh assured assured his death our
interference you started it you started
it keep
reading I thought bringing other Hermits
over would mean they would help him but
instead they attacked him it's so crazy
like she puts down the hermit crab like
somewhat close to him and then uh after
a while a hermit crab came out of his
shell and I walked walked over to the
hermit the The Hermit that hermit crab
about the Shell by the way he was also
missing several limbs yeah he had
already been attacked clearly so he Wass
over and then he like chills a little
bit next to him so we're like okay maybe
he'll maybe he'll help yeah at one point
it did kind of seem like he was even
helping like him into the shell talking
saying something yeah so we're like oh
he is helping and then he like takes out
his like hand and it looks like maybe
he'll help him but then he attacks him
yeah viciously yeah and we're like what
the [\h__\h] no so then we picked him up and
threw him we're like you [\h__\h] yeah and
then we noticed that like other nearby
cuz there were hermit crabs all over the
place other nearby her crabs were also
like having an eye on him like trying to
come closer you know
crazy nature [\h__\h] man
crazy and instead they attacked him we
FW them uh off of him but instead they
no what I'm looping off but realize it
was likely a lost cause and left him for
now Ki walked wanted to film an
underwater video so I tried my best to
assist oh wait no this wasn't the cruise
that yeah the cruise was the day the Cru
that was ccel was the day before I
wasn't mentioned at all yeah it was cuz
you came back oh yeah
okay wait where am I now kind of wanted
to film and I the want a video so I
tried my best to assist I it was really
I was really worried watching her enter
the rough Seas but she handled it well
it wasn't so rough it looked really
rough from my perspective it was and
they even had a red flag up and we're
like we don't recommend you snorkel but
we won't stop you yeah I I'm a bug us so
I'm a pro after we finished we sadly
turned in our snowling gear we still
wanted to swim and made our way to the
pool but alas rain began pouring we
relaxed uh in the building near the pool
eating good ice cream and listening to
interesting music how would you describe
that music '90s Euro music oh it was
like like disco music yeah Euro disco
music it was very weird I like
go um after the rain cooled
down yeah we made our way back to our
cabin to relax the cleaners prepared a
bath which I let Wawa enjoy alone we
[Music]
um what we lounged a bit hoping for the
rain to stop once it did she left to do
her makeup makeup interesting insisting
she need needs it despite her natural
lovely face shut up while taking some
pictures on the beach it suddenly began
to rain we rushed to a nearby restaurant
decided to have a quick lunch the rain
didn't really let up much though enough
for us to get home but not enough for
our cruise that evening to not be
cancelled yeah we had on the very first
day they told us you get one Sunset
Cruise for free uh which is like I don't
know 30 or 1 hour yeah I think know or
Cruise where you watch the sunset no
food but just like watching the sunset
and we were looking forward to that we
were scheduling it for the last day
because it's like you know great fin end
out the trip h a good way to end up the
trip
yeah which was a mistake yeah don't
schedule things for the last day because
if the weather is shitty then it's all
going to be
cancelled yeah uh where was
I can and said even not to be we made
our way back home and really just
relaxed with the rain there was not much
to do so we finished up packing K did
her member stream and then we slept
ready to wake up early for our flight
the next morning
yeah yeah we didn't do much on the last
day which was so sad yeah a little a
little upsetting but it's okay um now
last day of ki's Journal of narissa
right mhm read by narissa day five
Doo we start our last
day a bit later a bit later than usual
because the narissa bird was sleeping so
peacefully I had a hard time waking her
the weather wasn't looking so good
though so we were taking it slow the
moment she woke up the nerissa bird once
again showed me how fast she can get her
energy bursting out in her favorite
musical song and acting it out
dramatically after this in breakfast we
she sang her musicals every day I did
several times do that word say we and
would randomly out of nowhere quote the
musical lines in German in which I don't
understand uh tried wait can you shout
the sentence again after this in
breakfast we tried to rescue a
shess disabled hermit crab that I found
showing the Nissa bird great compassion
where other birds may just go and eat
the helpless crustacean as a snack we
had a little bit of no rain weather well
still stormy and it was the last
possible day so I really needed to let
my near rescu test my new research
equipment for underwater birds birds
also known as
fish so we head over to the dock
there sorry you're reading so like as if
I'm not writing cool things I'm totally
writing cool things no you are so we
headed over to the dock that had the
small Coral wreath but since it was very
stormy it had a real a red flag a red
flag out with a warning that said to not
go swimming now but my research was of
great urgency yes so I finally asked and
con I kindly
asked and convinced and convinced the
security guy to let me go in regardless
with the narissa bird's assistance I was
able to take vital footage of my
underwater sighting yes however when I
got out from
my last dip my last dip I was to yeah
told I had just told I had just missed a
turtle that literally swam like right
behind me o o in any case I proudly
ended my
research
to turn my focus back to my main study
we both returned our snorkeling
equipment and then in the hopes of
getting some more ice cream and maybe
even swim in the pool we went back to
the pool big pool the big pool but when
we arrived it started pouring like crazy
so we sat inside eating ice cream for a
while while it
calmed I wanted the nerissa bird to
enjoy the waterit more but it wasn't
meant to be at least the ice cream was
nice we made our way back and more
surprised by and were surprised by
another Bubbly Bath with floral
decorations and a writing that said see
you soon yeah since I didn't rinse off
the sea water yet I actually entered it
alone this time after that it started
pouring again but in the hopes of it
getting better again I did my makeup and
we both dressed nicely to take some nice
momentos here I'd like to note that the
narissa bird doesn't only prefer to not
wear makeup but also doesn't really own
any so she generally always is an all
natural in an all natural state she's a
natural beauty she does have a few bad
habits in terms of fixing things that
bother her but I shall not go too deep
into that she's however very focused
on can't believe you're dragging me like
this excuse me keeping her long luscious
hair healthy yeah neatly but healthy
also no I can't read uh anyway
anyway I let let me get back let me get
back to my timeline after getting ready
eventually the rain stopped so I rushed
over
or so I rushed over rushed us to a nice
spot a nice spot for photos where we did
that until it you guessed it started
raining strongly again we escaped it
into the nearby restaurant to have some
lunch I was hoping it would stop again
but sadly the rest of the day and night
was con constant rain constant rain so
with nothing to do we ended up getting
into bed for a nap until dinner surprise
no more naps which we also ended up
skipping because we weren't very hungry
and still super sleepy later on I did
one more stream while the narissa bird
was resting and then packed my things we
had to set up early and set up we
had we had to get up early in the
following morning to leave so it was
probably good to get so much early sleep
with a heavy
heart we left the island on a calm
morning but not before I cited three
more threee Rays I'm not sure what's a
general word for rays cuz I don't want
to say a Monteray cuz wasn't a Monteray
yeah they were like tiny baby like
stingrays it yeah Sting Rays or Eagle
Rays who knows mhm and a turtle on the
arrival and departure deck saying
goodbye to us was perhaps per and perhap
sorry for the bad weather this did cheer
me up a bit I think the narissa bird
only managed to see the Rays though but
it was a nice last surprise with that we
say goodbye males farewell and beautiful
farewell beautiful ocean the end the end
the end but there's I'm not reading
there's some final thoughts that I asked
Nissa and myself to write I said please
k up just write some final
thoughts um to kind of like put
everything in a nice
little bun yeah yeah and thank you for
the party party we're not quite done but
yeah that feel like the last day was
like cuz I I I really [\h__\h] love the
malds and having the last day after the
the almost last day before the the day
before the last last day also being like
halfway half of it being yeah so rainy
having the last day be so [\h__\h] rainy
like even worse too was really [\h__\h] up
cuz I wanted to do things I wanted to
get a lot of beach time in and get you
to swim more because I feel like overall
in these 5 days you you didn't swim much
that's okay with me that's not okay with
me my skin is so
ruined look at me it looks perfectly
fine I showed you the picture of my
sunburn before right that's a real
sunburn that's a sunburn that is
actually dangerous for your skin for
your health you're just I guess not used
to like any sun at all I'm not used to
swimming either I don't think I've been
swimming in a really obnoxiously long
time okay yeah but I just feel like you
know when you're on a vacation like that
you got to enter the ocean or the pool
you know I did I just still entered a
lot for
me I just wanted you to get your money's
worth and all that you know my money's
worth what being with you
okay so last one oh okay that's pretty
short huh yeah I I wrote one and a a bit
more than you she's a one page one page
one page she lies what one and a half
you wrote one and a half you wrote not a
full
page
okay okay nissa's final consensus um
about me and the trip I guess overall
despite the weather issues I had a
wonderful time in the males the
beautiful Waters fun activities and food
made it a very positive experience
really
mhm what you did say Cruise was better I
mean foodwise foodwise foodwise the
cruise was better yeah oh cuz you were
saying like I mean for that for that
amount of money with the Cru you get see
like just as beautiful beaches don't get
me wrong I had more fun in the malds
than I had on the cruise but compared to
how much money I spent on the cruise
that I went on versus how much money I
spent to go to the malds it it's not
even close yeah the money is definitely
you know yeah a thing yeah on a cruise
you know you don't have to leave the
boat so even if the weather is bad like
sure you're not able to swim but they've
got movie theaters they've got like a
ton of different activities you can do
that are all in doors so the weather
really doesn't mean anything and they
have multiple buffet style stuff that
have way more food options than the
buffet that we even went to and they
swap out for all three and you know
they're more to my taste buds cuz it's
the kind of food I'm used to eating not
like me trying the bacon and being like
this bacon tastes really different you
know um and like you can still get like
fresh eggs and stuff but like the males
stuff was definitely higher quality for
example like in the solo restaurants
that we went to um so no it's it's again
very
comparable Mal is beautiful okay she's
[Music]
crying however the highlight of the trip
for me was definitely K
herself her adorable bubbly energy her
explorative nature her great f passion
and her commitment
to
mating
to to making sure we had fun making sure
to making sure we had fun made me have
more fun than I've had on a vacation
before really mhm I don't believe it oh
my God should I WR your final consensus
I don't believe it it's not true I'm
just saying that no
she definitely pushed me to try things I
never I would I never but never had
never had
[Music]
considered before 10 out of 10 a
wonderful vacation partner and would
happily accompany her anywhere she
decided uh desired a travel companion
love
you can't people
Al I love you okay
okay why are you so sad what the
heck cuz it could have been better and I
feel like you didn't enjoy it as much as
you could have that's just
because I'll tell you later but let's
read yours yeah okay wait I'll change
the title don't don't put your eyes on
it okay I may have roasted you a bit
more on my wow
was an over I'm nice and she's like I
don't believe it and then she roasts me
no it's not really roasting it's just
stating facts and I'm still smiling and
like I love you kiaha what is this read
to review my studies of the narissa bird
shortly let me just say what did you ex
out I just didn't like the way I started
a bubbly and sleepy bird neverly and
sleepy SLE very sleepy bird sleepy is
important never says no to a nap
probably naps more than me yeah but it
doesn't take her long to regain her
energy and burst it out when she's awake
in the form of musical tangents and
songs has a few habits that may be bad
scared of many things like the ocean
birds and more but will give many things
a try a clear preference of food but
will eat things she dislikes anyway
speaks only one language but mimics
German constantly
both the decent pronunciation will
shower me with affectionate words even
when all I tell her even when I tell her
not to yeah cute expressions and a
beautiful voice takes decent photos of
others only decent that's a it's it's
I'm just being you know she hates me
it's so over no I'm a scientist and I'm
doing professional observations so I
can't you know go to like lovey Dum uhuh
uh-huh hydrates herself constantly and
healthily also you agree that my
pictures are they they they are but
you're like a photographer likes her
bacon crispy as [\h__\h] yeah has a love for
massages slash cats SL musicals sweet
Foods me her other colleagues Aesthetics
and pretty women water trashy American
TV and other cultures around the
world a sweet kind bird that will fight
for you if she likes you even if a bit
weakly due to little muscle mask wants
her hair to be played with uh hold gent
wants her hair to be played with yet
hold gently and treat with care to not
hurt her must
protect no not too much
Rose the bad so to say in exclamation
mark not exclamation the what do you
call this quotations quotation marks I
put it in quotation marks bad habits
just because they're I mean they're not
necessar my nails so you to say it okay
I wasn't sure if I should say it I I
have a really bad habit of I'm really
self-conscious about my nails so I'm
always picking at my cuticles and stuff
and like ripping them off yeah
constantly and then you also want to say
this oh I I usually when I'm home yeah I
trim the ends of my hair so I'll I'll
look through and I'll find the split
ends and I'll cut them off so whenever I
go anywhere for an extended period of
time and I don't bring my scissors I
become very uh annoyed because I see all
these split ends that I usually don't
see in my room because the sun shows
them better and I can't cut them off so
yeah it's like my fidgety nervous habits
so I either saw you like on your nails
or on your hair yeah I was just ping I
was ping cuz I'm a bird I was pining
sometimes you don't like rip it off but
you bite the hair off yeah yeah
sometimes the hair won't come off so I
have to bite it
off yeah and it's like I
I don't eat the hair though obviously I
get out of my mouth what fascinates me
though is that you you really like you
have a thing with your cuticles you like
what did you say you you you you you get
rid of your cuticles I ripped them off
and I'm not even sure what cuticles are
and then you offered me to get rid of
that you would help me get rid of my
cuticles and she barely has any that's
terrifying to me but I would help her if
that's what she wanted that thought like
doing anything to you mean this like
these lines here right like why would
you even even touch them then then
they're like for my impression they're
like stuck to your nails so like I can't
even imagine how you get rid of them
that's crazy that's crazy but your nails
are pretty your hands are pretty your
hands are so like I think they're like
more elegant than mine mine are sausage
fingers yours you do not have sausage
fingers looking her hands are beautiful
and she's sitting here my sa fingers and
also you may keep on picking on your
hair but it do be long and healthy
looking yeah you you all like you always
try to like keep your hair like to
together in like a braid or in like a
like a thing up here doesn't get damaged
yeah so it's like it's just like your
your hair is like pretty much never
messy and you brush it a lot so you're
always always taking care of your hair
you like I I said you're like AEL yeah
yeah ow you watched that in the airplane
I did that's was okay one thing I have
to say oh that you since you're you
arriving here until today and probably
until
tomorrow
constantly every day talking about
Elizabeth D
Musical made me lose big interest in it
and kind of ruined it ruined it to me
how did I ruin it what's it
about yeah about Elizabeth but what's it
about what happens in it well she
probably yeah she gets like seduced by
death you know cuz she has depression
and there's death you know and then
there's a husband and this that okay but
what happens then well I didn't watch it
yeah that's like the first 10 minutes
yeah cuz I didn't watch it why how would
I know it's 2 hour you basically got the
synopsis and she's saying I ruined it
yeah cuz you constantly like bring it up
and sing it and say to German and you
say and he a a d musical instead death
music oh like Elizabeth D musical so
much but it fascinates me cuz you said
you watched it For the First Time 4
years ago and I since you brought it up
up like every day I can only imagine
your whole life for four years all
that's in your head is Elizabeth that's
musical yeah and I think the only yes
yeah oh my God oh my God that's like a
legit addiction I think the only way of
curing this back to parasite is like
watching the actual musical in person
cuz that's the one thing you haven't
done
yeah I'm so concerned with
you it's concerning it's concerning it's
crazy I mean you quote other musicals
sometimes too but this one's crazy the
difference is also because I'm
surrounded in Austria by people speaking
German and my there are several things I
think of when I hear German which is
Elizabeth musical I can imagine or choir
and you've heard me also quoting choir
music because it just comes to my mind
and like it's like my like I'm like oh I
need to quote this my brain and I'm like
no you don't but my brain's like too
late it's already coming out of my mouth
I see how the Environ makes makes you
think about the music Mak even more yeah
so at first I listened to it on my way
here because I was like we renew my
German skills cuz I'll remember German
words wait on the way to Austria and
they play you watch Elizabeth do music
oh my God literally 2 days later on our
9 hour flight to the m you watched it
again for context I I you know we got
the YouTube premiums right so I
downloaded three
musicals and I didn't I I was trying to
sleep some of the flight so I was like
okay which of these do I want to watch
right now and I was like I don't feel
like watching Heather's a musical at the
moment because it's kind of intense do
you know Heathers no there's a lot of
murder okay and it's in a high school
setting okay don't even get you started
um but anyways it's it's crazy and then
the other one was falsettos which is
also one of my favorites and I did watch
that one but I watched that one later in
the flight after I woke up mhm but I was
like I want to watch Elizabeth that's
musical again because because the first
time I watched it I was watching it on
my flight to Austria as I was trying to
slip so the thing was I had the screen
turned off and I wasn't actually
watching it I was just listening to the
soundtrack basically because there's no
speaking it's just songs cuz you don't
need to watch it anymore at this point
cuz you watched it a million [\h__\h]
times I know it's happening the whole
time
yeah did you watch it on your way
back oh my God oh my God so the span of
like a week you watched it three times
and not only that you watched it like
fully three times but then during the
Mals you sometimes you would like watch
clips of it I showed her one clip of it
yeah and she was not interested no I
watched I watched it I watched watch and
literally you asked me do you know who
that is and I was like it's probably
like the like I wanted to say like the
embodiment of like her like feelings of
depression or whatever yeah so it was
death yeah I was like oh my God you're
right I was actually watching I was
actually carefully watching but which is
amazing cuz one time I sent her a
musical song from Dracula this musical
and she was like I don't care about this
but the thing is like the way you you
were in this one week watching it all
the time makes me feel like and talk
about it all the time makes me feel like
oh maybe she you know just recently
found out about this and is still like
so passionate about it but no it's been
four years you need an
intervention good
luck that's so crazy so I wish I wish
there was like an ongoing Elizabeth
that's musical here uh in Austria
because uh for the people who don't know
do you want to rough like in maybe two
sentences say what this musical is
about it's about the empress Elizabeth
of Austria it's the story of her
life you're my you're my Austrian
princess thank you um it's it's about
her life literally just like her life
story um told from obviously a slightly
dramatized view to be interesting uh
told from the perspective of her
murderer uh Luigi lukini actually which
is kind of terrible every time I think
about it I'm like he [\h__\h] killed her
and in her musical he's like one of the
leading roles oh what the hell yeah okay
I mean it makes sense when you watch it
in context great great great two
sentences yeah so exactly what I
expected it's about her fight with
depression and her desire to continue to
live for herself I do have to say I am
extremely happy and honored and
flattered that this one brain parasite
that you have that you can never get rid
of is about an Austrian historical
figure that's because Elizabeth is my
favorite historical figure of all time
yeah that's that makes me really flat
because like normally people don't pay
much attention to a you know if anything
maybe they love sound of music but I
mean yeah you you're like so [\h__\h]
into it and unfortunately there's no
like current Musical that you can watch
here but I did today take her to a
museum that is literally all about her
and that was great I I lived I was it
was so crazy I was
like she she touched this she wore this
she lived here in this room yeah I was
like oh my God so yeah and then you were
listening to every single audio guide so
eagerly so passionately I was so
excited I love that I love that you
appreciated it so much I love her
seriously I've been obsessed with her
for like a decade I'm glad I could like
show something that really makes sense
to you cuz you like museums in general
you said and then you're like absolutely
obsessed with this lady that is surpris
coincidentally also Austrian just like
she's the reason I have long hair oh I
did feel like yeah that was this one um
painting painting for painting right in
frs's study he kept a painting of her
yeah like two paintings with open hair
and one of the paintings of her with
open hair was really a a
feral yeah in front of her she had it
like it was like kind of wavy and flowy
and it was Loosely tied in a knot in
front of her chest so it's like you we
can do this with your hair it totally
will work I'm going to do this with your
hair yeah so we're going to do that
later new hairstyle for Nissa front tied
not you honestly could do that in a new
outfit as like a reference to her we can
make it look good I don't know I'm sure
your mommy can make anything look good
that is true mhm like look at that
hairstyle holy [\h__\h] that looks amazing I
love the like like the way it
intertwines the blue the blue stuff the
little
brand it's very cute just like you no
yes no yes no okay
okay so I brought her to the museum and
um because her brother ordered her to
look at to ordered
me indirectly to show you more Austrian
beautiful uh architecture he he he sent
me a message and he's like hey what are
you doing and I was like um I'm I don't
know and he's likees why aren't you
sending me any pictures of of Austria
and I was like bro architecture he's
like I want to see the old architecture
why won't you send it to me and I was
like bro I'm not even there right
now literally bro like literally my bro
can you can you do something for me me
can you imitate yeah my accent yeah or
this one or oh you really elongate your
oh oh this one oh this one it sounds
normal no you're not doing say more say
more
uh oh let me just scooch right past you
there that sounded so normal oh my god
oh let me just scooch right past you
dare the way you talk to my mom was more
like there was a moment where you oh
yeah when I was this is because this
isn't my accent this is a different one
oh I'm not from around I don't know I
don't know this one but she did oh yeah
when you talk like this you know you're
from a you're down from that one place I
don't remember the name of because who
wants to live there let's be real was it
the Fargo
place sorry faroan my mom mentioned
Fargo to niss yeah so I I did my best
impression yeah and she was
like
yes wait what were we talking about a
your brother your brother yeah yeah he
was very annoying I love him stupid
idiot yeah and he ordered me to show you
architecture like tell Kiara to thank
you places with nice architect that how
he talks
yeah tell her to take you places and so
you can send pictures to me I was like
of course I will I mean like right now
we're literally in the M
like yeah it was very funny so you saw a
lot of beautiful architecture I think in
the in the museum but then also I
brought you to the cafe that I literally
bring everyone too it wonderful we ate
so many sweets so many like 50 bucks
worth for sweets it's okay though
because I paid for it cuz I take care of
my woman thank you yeah and it had like
a a really beautiful ceiling really high
beautiful ceiling and yeah me and an
overview of the city and then we walk
and we saw cool statues that narissa
geeked out a little bit about we had a
little fight what were we fighting about
about Latin pronunciation oh my God no
we're not talking about this I told her
about how Latin Bros came for me when I
covered liliam because apparently my
pronunciation was wrong at some parts or
inconsistent to which my my defens is
your argument Latin is a dead language
No One Knows by the time people were
learning it no one knew how to speak it
it was already dead and you can say oh
well we have other Latin languages but
like English is technically a Latin
language and it's pronoun pronunciation
is not really the same as French or
German or other Latin languages like
Spanish so she's claiming that there's
no way to know how Latin there is
because all Native Latin speakers were
dead but I I would say yeah English is
not a Latin language a Latin language
though English is Germanic isn't German
no German German is I guess yeah I think
so I don't know but I would say my aru I
don't I don't wanted to look this up but
my argument is that surely like even if
no country was officially speaking Latin
anymore at some point Sur it was still
being like delivered from person to
person and in scriptures and all that
also in church in religion Latin yeah
but they have different pronunciations
in church versus what the they they
think German is not a Latin language
yeah but also like because Latin and and
old Greek uh is very very [\h__\h]
similar you would think that the
pronunciations are similar and you can
take that as a reference is my
argument what do you guys
say no yeah some English is is Latin
based what are you guys talking about I
don't know I learned when I was studying
English we talk often about how Latin
roots were in a lot of English so
I'm like we just steal from everything
in the English language we take a little
bit from everything and then pronounce
it in the funniest way possible hardcore
linguistic
flights that's fair but yeah uh kiata
was like well I studied Latin and I was
like oh my God she's about to go Latin
bro on no cuz I don't remember anything
mhm yeah
neither do
I but about English I don't remember
anything English is a bit of everything
because of all the people that came here
yeah MH so uh I'm sorry Latin is fake
Latin is fake what's the pronunciation
you're such a Latin I mean Latin is
literally what what made me change
schools at some point I love Latin I
think it is beautiful however I just
think that it is dumb to criticize a
dead language and be like your
pronunciation is wrong and I'm like how
do you know it's right are you Reviving
are you bringing Julius Caesar back from
the dead to correct my pronunciation I
mean I I certainly think that you
wouldn't or they wouldn't have
pronounced Latin like uh
Vin or like you know I don't know in a
[\h__\h] really weird English way or so I
feel like there's certainly like points
that you can take as a reference from
other oh no of course languages that are
closer to it than English but I here's
the thing though also I followed Google
translate I used Google translate and I
put the Latin in because it has a Latin
pronunciation for it so people are like
you were wrong and I was like I don't
know what you want me to do it's okay
it's okay I mean you know you
don't who knows okay who knows in the
end and it's not a big deal I think just
even let's say let's say one or two
words where mispronounced yeah it's fine
who cares she still sings beautifully
yeah yeah yeah but but well
Latin I almost got expelled for
criticizing a teacher's Latin
pronunciation see Latin Bros oh the
teacher the one teaching him Latin
probably can you imagine he got expelled
almost oh oh my god there yeah there's
two Latins there's two different Latin
pronunciations but apparently Google
does not distinguish between them
classical pronunciation is derived from
spelling and deduced from poem Etc we
can see what was subed to rhyme Etc
language can be reconstructed that's
what I was thinking I just can't say it
properly but the the rhyme the poem
thing makes a lot of sense cuz poems are
supposed to rhyme yeah and then you can
guess those words Latin words would
sound
similarly wow nice argument Mister
either way it doesn't matter because I
won't be singing um but I did like your
you as I said you have like a lot of
like random knowledge and you have this
like you had this Greek knowledge I was
like reading something about like a
Greek statue off of like
the the the plaque the plaque and it was
like n here I'll read this for you and
then you were you kept on correcting my
pronunciations of like uh like the the
Greek names or so I'm like how the [\h__\h]
do you know I'm I'm sure it's not
pronounced in Engish way and then like
it was actually technically Roman
because Neptune uh Poseidon is the Greek
equivalent so they were actually the
Roman gods yeah you did the all act
actually
actually but yeah so she's reading it
all to me and but how did you pronounce
the lady's name thetus that's thetus but
I would probably not how it's pronounced
but I don't care how it's pronounced
yeah you don't care
no I don't I don't
care okay cuz unless someone says it out
loud for me and I've only actually read
it vus no thetus t h e t i s yeah that
is just how I've always read it and so
it is confined to be that way in my
brain you
know fetus
Cletus but K Latin explaining I made a
joke uh before that I'm I don't mean at
all because uh you you I think you do
know more about uh it than me I made a
joke that cuz you kept on talking to me
about Elizabeth's uh like history yeah
and and I was like you're kind of like
you know how there's this word called
mansplaining I feel like your history
explaining me about my own country's
history but no I she hates me no no I
personally is so annoying I don't even
know a lot of the things that you say to
me so it's like totally legit that
you're saying these things to me but
you're kind of History explaining me
about my own
country okay tell me about
Elizabeth mom tell me about her give me
the lore that I don't know give me the
secret she was a woman who loved writing
I have fresh memory cuz we went to the
museum today nothing that we learned at
the Museum give me something new give me
some fresh well I don't know anything
that was out mum oh my God you guys see
this you seeing this
she's so cute I love
her my baby
girl one day I hope to make your wish
come true at least to let you see uh
Elizabeth D musical uh in Austria in
German and you will lose your [\h__\h] so we
probably need separate seats far away
from each other I won't lose my [\h__\h] I'm
very well behaved at musicals but I hope
I hope they bring it back I don't know
like if it's any they do it recently
someone said they were bringing it back
in June but yeah June I'm pretty sure
it's a yearly thing both here and in
Japan too always does a yearly one and
then Australia well you know you got to
come back you're always welcome come
back here and then we'll go there
together wearing cute clothes it's her
tutors what oh yeah
yeah I guess
so but yeah and then maybe finally you
can close the chapter of Elizabeth does
musical I doubt it you're probably still
going to be talking about it 10 years
later yeah she's my favorite I just love
her you love her more than me she's your
real a she I mean
nothing I've slept in the same bed as
you yeah I've lit we've literally
showered together what are you even
talking about yeah but if you had the
choice between showering and sleeping
with me and with her you would choose
her um no yes you would do you know she
slept with raw ve on her face held in a
leather mask you think I want to have a
sleepover with someone who does that
that is so not [\h__\h] normal well I
have no idea what you just said did you
miss that it was literally in the voice
thing no it's just like you go like blah
blah blah blah blah blah blah so fast
bring out some words and sorry is my
English too fast for you what did she
just say to me Elizabeth when she would
sleep she would take raw ve as in the
meat Ah that's s and she would put it on
her face and hold it in place with a
leather mask that's some kind of yeah
and she was convinced that this helped
her skin vastly why during sleeping with
someone yeah no I mean I think they did
not sleep in the same bed but oh while
oh while sleep I thought while having
intercourse what's wrong with you cuz
you said sleeping with someone no no we
slept together not in that way you
weirdo but I thought that's what you
meant no why would I be referring to
that I don't know maybe that's what she
did cuz you you keep on saying she's
kind of crazy you always say she's kind
of crazy she has I mean she's a
hapsburg they were super
inbr yeah so maybe she would who knows
crazy maybe she would wear that as as
long as she could cuz she really wanted
her skin to be pretty oh my God okay we
need to end we need to end we're getting
crazy no n also bought cute souvenirs
right I did I got cute stuff yeah you
got earrings that are that look kind of
like the one they do we looked at them
and I was like oh my God these look like
your earrings and she's like you should
get them and I was like bet and you
bought a nice uh C cookbook mhm like a
royal Austrian Austrian cookbook
Austrian Royal cookbook MH
and what else would you buy Wax Seal Wax
Seal yes so now I can seal things with
wax
exciting yeah s this s guys we do
have you can thank me for that we have
another stream tomorrow yes um man I I
had so many ideas the one more stream
that we're doing tomorrow as an off
collab I think we will do this because
it's a genius idea we're going to play
Sims
4 but not normally I have thought about
a challenge one of us like we'll keep on
taking turns in controlling the Sim uh
like maybe 10 minutes or so one of us
will be the angle one of us will be the
debil well I can tell who's who based on
my horns I guess so yeah because we can
be either your angle or your
deil right and and so the angle will try
to uh help the Sim and keep him alive
and you know know let them be happy
maybe even get them fall in love and
married and whatever but when it's
nissa's turn she's the Deb so she will
try to manipulate and ruin everything
maybe even you know get get rid of their
relationships fight get her in trouble
lose her job maybe get her killed get
her dead drowned in a pool you know I do
love to kill the Sims that is my that
was my number one hobby when I was we
have to make some rules because if you
have 10 minutes you could easily just
kill the Sim in the pool so oh well I'm
not going to do that you need more
interesting ways to kill them okay it
has to like not be like such an easy
thing yeah yeah so
you're Imagine The Sims shoulders turn
based Sims yeah on one shoulder is me
the angle Angela and on the other
shoulder is narissa the deil we'll see
how it goes I have a hard time being
mean but you have to you have to like
ruin everything that I build up and then
I try to fix it and then you ruin it
again until the Sim even dies best my
angle your goal would probably be
getting the Sim to die and my goal I
don't know maybe would be getting her
married and getting her a child good
luck I'll try good luck something like
that I will do my best to make sure that
doesn't happen doesn't that sound fun I
thought that you can only really um do
that when you're in person you're in
person yeah off my mom will love it
because she loves The Sims loves his
s yay sounds like fun right yes blood
for the blood good yeah look forward to
[Music]
it who will the Sim be you'll be
torturing I I didn't you know do no
no no we have to think about who it
might just be like a random like non Hol
life member
Sim oh yeah we could what if we made our
child um M um our child which I don't
think we have one we don't but like
that's what the Sims is for we build our
hypothetical daughter but then that
would be so [\h__\h] up you're trying to
ruin and and kill your child okay you
got a point so
yeah it just be maybe a random one that
we don't feel bad about St okay
torturing yeah okay chat it will be the
embodiment of you maybe maybe so will be
tomorrow probably around
roughly the same time again and yeah
yeah yeah yeah and uh I don't know
there's a slight chance that maybe I'll
do one more solo stream because before I
dip Dippity dip cuz I feel like there's
like things to talk about still that if
I don't talk about it before I dip I'm
going to forget it all and you guys are
going to forget and you will just be
like left unspoken mhm but don't get
your hopes up I think maybe I will maybe
not okay okay just uh yeah maybe okay
the butler that goes to you oh oh tell
the story about tell the story okay so I
generally was in contact with the butler
cuz um we are in contact over WhatsApp
they use WhatsApp and Nissa didn't have
WhatsApp so I did that from day one
whenever we had a message to like relate
to the
butler uh I would write to them over
WhatsApp and um
uh there the last day the the evening
before the last day he sent me a PD PDF
yeah an info about like when we will get
get woken up a wake up call which
normally in hotels uh happens over the
phone um yeah had the battle Court
guy uh how did you do that without a
phone I had my phone it's just dead now
yeah yeah it died today yeah um so a
wake up call and then when they would
like bring us to the uh checkout and
then when they pick up the bags and when
we actually uh like go H when we have
breakfast and when we board the plane
like a whole itinary
and so I I made an alarm anyway for the
exact time when the wakeup call would
happen narissa was somehow awake earlier
and then like doing stuff with her
luggage so we were awake a little bit
before all of that there was no wakeup
call but I I would still maybe excuse
that with maybe the phone being weird or
them doing it in person but we had to do
not disturb thing out there so I don't
know that can maybe happen but
then we we left our luggage in the room
for them to pick up later but then we
were going to go to the checkout and it
was really [\h__\h] dark cuz it was like
4 5 4 a.m 4 a.m 4 4 4:45 5: a.m. 5: a.m.
we left the room and I was like looking
for the checkout place but we only were
in there once when we checked in yeah so
we both forgot where the hell it was and
it was dark as [\h__\h] so kind of got lost
so we just went to the restaurant but
supposedly apparently we were supposed
to get picked up by the butler well but
we didn't find that out even until we
went to the restaurant so we walked
there because we're like we don't know
where to go maybe it's there maybe we
can ask them and they'll be able to tell
us but either way breakfast starts at
5:00 so we might as well get breakfast
we can always check out after um so we
get in there and other people who are
also leaving start arriving and all of
them are getting dropped off presumably
by their Butlers so we're just sitting
here like wait a damn minute yeah but we
talked to the waitress mhm and we're
like you know check where can we check
out she's like not here but but yeah
later a lady I guess cuz like the high
chuny wony the waitress like let someone
else know that we were like I guess
having problems
so that lady came over she was really
nice I think she was like another like
someone else's Butler basically Butler
Butler blood Lina I don't know um and
she like asked us yeah what's wrong BL
blah blue and then she brought us after
the breakfast she brought us to the
checkout thank she saved us and I asked
her what's wrong with our Butler what
happened did he perhaps over sleep and
she's like I don't know yeah some of
them tried to be nice and they're like
oh he's probably helping other people
but like we didn't hear from him the
whole time we didn't see him at all and
he didn't even say goodbye like even via
WhatsApp well we got to the checkout we
did the check out and then we waited a
little bit and then we finally went over
to the dock and the sun was Rising uh
and I saw some last cool things uh from
the top of the water I saw the turtle
and the Rays and all that and then like
until the very last moment the guy
didn't show up and he never rode back on
my WhatsApp even like after the flight I
never got like a message because I wrote
him like so son yeah um by the way so we
just uh got help from someone else and
checked out so yeah
bye yeah he never said anything back and
yeah then at the very end there was
another like uh guy who was like walking
us over to the plane and I was like so
do you know uh what happened to our
Butler I said the name too and he's like
oh it's probably sleeping then yeah yeah
that's what I thought uhhm slept over
our whole
departure that's kind of like sad cuz
they're supposed to be there for yeah I
mean the only reason I don't mind
obviously sleeping in but especially on
the fact that like it's a day we have to
leave and he's supposed to escort us and
especially like it would have been
convenient too because like it had been
raining so much so we're trying to
navigate in the pitch darkness of the
island and not step in these giant rain
puddles so like we didn't get a wakeup
call so if if we hadn't had set an alarm
which obviously anyone would but if
something had gone wrong we would
potentially have missed our flight yeah
if we relied completely on the Wake Up
Call yeah so
yeah yeah generally like the the
previous Mal's Resort that I was on
maybe it was because it was just like a
little bit
more so to say expensive like I think
this one was more expensive but back
then for being offseason and all that it
was like generally like more luxurious a
a little bit tiny bit Yeah upscale yeah
so the the butler lady that we had back
then she was taking so like care she was
taking care so well of us is that how
you say yeah and and like constantly
like helping us out and driving us
around and all that so this time we were
more on our own which is totally fine
generally like comparing the service
yeah comparing the service versus the
price just seems
crazy but it was still fun it was I wish
I wish I had more time yeah I wanted to
go out on more snorkeling trips cuz like
after that one big one that we did uh
out on like a on a bigger Reef uh seeing
like cool Rays eagle ray Eagle gray yeah
Eagle Rays zooming
around ah it was it was really cool I
got like better and better at
snorkeling and yeah I just I just uh I
wish I wish it was overall better
because like I have like generally a
good feeling about the males but it was
your first time and I I didn't want you
to be disappointed I wasn't disappointed
I wanted you to enjoy it yeah Kiana was
so anxious the whole time about it not
comparing to her last trip and I think
it was because of me but I don't mind so
much because I I have fun going anywhere
M so and I unless like I don't know I
just I guess it felt like you weren't
quite enjoying it cuz you slept through
a lot of it and you didn't swim so much
so it's like I didn't give you really
like the the suitable vacation if you
you you didn't do anything wrong I just
don't swim very well and because my hair
is so long it takes forever to dry so I
take I take my ocean time or water time
in general
very I consider it more carefully
I'm like do I really have the energy to
wash this out of my hair and then have
to brush it and then I have to wait for
it to dry and then I have to brush it
again and then I have to put it up you
know you could use a swimming capab
those don't work I used one before and
water just seeped through and got my
hair soaked anyway and I was so
disappointed she's not a strong swimmer
I'm not a strong swimmer
either but know I loved it and I had fun
with you so you don't need to like feel
bad or anything or feel like you somehow
failed it was great okay yeah don't tou
yourself okay my
queen yeah so that was the moldiv
and if you are a remember and you
watched um my member stream that I did
at the end there I had a crazy
Revelation realization at the end that
the males will not be a thing anymore h
or even 80 years later um so that's kind
of shocking and that's why I'm glad that
I've been there I still kind of want to
go again I'm just like kind of like like
now this time we went during peak season
that's supposed to be not so much rain
and even I asked at the very last moment
I asked one of the staff people of the
way this whole week went down if this
was a normal uh thing in January and he
said no this is totally like weird like
no we don't get this much rain usually
so I'm like okay maybe we were unlucky a
little
bit but so I don't know if I want to
give it a third try after like two trips
that were like so much rain cuz it's so
much money yeah for it to be like
there's still many beautiful moments
though
that maybe make it worth depending on
how much money you do pay MH um so I
don't know I have to think about it like
I was trying to make this a yearly thing
but I don't know cuz I also don't want
to like disappoint the person that's
with me and also myself don't worry
about disappointing me still you know
it's a concern like you know getting
your hopes up and then it's rainy as
[\h__\h] so maybe I'll go somewhere else
next time I don't know but there's still
so many islands that the M Lees has and
so many cool um uh Resorts that looks so
beautiful I I'll think about it yeah
I'll consider it I'll consider the
moldes in the future
again so
so we're getting tired here I think
yes so guys thank you for watching this
uh review of our journals I hope you
enjoyed it uh after this I will um scan
uh every single page that narissa wrote
and
uploaded on Twitter so keep an eye out
for that
no and I'll I'll be you know um be I'll
be the guide of narissa a little bit
longer yeah yeah yeah before I send her
back to the American land she's trying
to get rid of me and she's like go home
no no no but I want to show you some
more stuff and then you can go back I
think your jail Birds right really want
you back that's true I miss you jilbert
they miss you
too so
sad she'll be back soon so wait a little
bit I mean you have her here right now
you know yeah I still streamed a lot of
things considered just on your channel
yeah no we did also two on your but one
was only 10
minutes we did a
c we played smash for 16 minutes kind
of
yeah so tomorrow one more stream I'll
see you there I'll put up the
reservation tomorrow I can't say for
sure now what time and all that yeah enj
when you
say farewell
goodbye goodbye I hate to
say I hate to say
[Music]
goodbye I do want to take you on The
Sound of Music Tour someday I [\h__\h]
love the sound of music I did the tour
before take me it was
great yeah and another time this this
time we had the Elizabeth Arc next time
we have sound
music byebye guys tomorrow after the
stream perhaps I'll be reading super
chats I don't know yet but I do want to
still rate Super Chat at some point so
byebye guys byebye a good night what was
that [\h__\h] chat can you send Rissa back
to the usual room for a bit before she
go make her remember the old time oh
when were you in the usual room I don't
think I ever was yeah what you mean back
she's not going
there I literally heard it in my
headphones chunky wonky making that
scared me I thought it was someone
humming no it was just her I was like
someone's outside the door no she's
making sleepy sounds
a okay goodbye
KF okay okay okay you guys want that she
makes the best face for that it's
amazing okay bye bye byebye Sor I said
it already five times goodbye I'll be
the bye Your Darlings bye Your
Darlings
[Music]
wow