[Music]
he stopped
oh
cool
i was struggling to unmute it
no problem
i generally always feel so bad about
when i do collabs about doing my
kikiriki because it's like it's a
morning car right so it should be filled
with energy but like i can't just be
here and like
please do please do
no worries honestly i need a little like
morning cock-a-doodle-doo you know
to wake me up because right now i'm
feeling it
and i have no caffeine in the house whoa
good morning sunshine good morning
ladies
oh my god morning ladies how are you
it shouldn't it shouldn't be like that
it was good for a minute and then it was
good for a minute i just leave it like
that it's a stylistic choice
yeah okay they're already
messing with us yeah it's like it's
symbolism
it represents your declining mental
state
all right i'm going to change it to 720p
instead of 180. oh that's better oh yeah
it's it's true
yeah
you're looking very casually
having twenty people
oh okay let's go oh there she go oh
oh oh oh oh oh
no
um is that okay are you cool with that
i think i i think i am what color did
you use green and it didn't mess with
your feathers so really which green is
it can you tell me like it's just
green i gotta go back to the loading
screen two seconds
it looks fine on my stream but i would
[Music]
kelly are they moving on your side yeah
hello
you have to have their window open
at all times see here this is the stuff
that we can't actually check before the
stream for stuff that happens literally
during this break
it's not crazy it was working fine
and then we started streaming
it don't move for me when i stream to
them
um now it's just black to me
um did
also callie stopped moving for me too oh
oh oh yeah
kelly
is she
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's actually
[Music]
sorry are we okay now guys um well we're
gonna have to find okay
i think the final thing
i think it was badly when cali streamed
it because i
apparently
like it's [\h__\h] and i also
one more time leave it to me i got this
boy yes
one second
here we go live
is 30.
now go
we've got time
we're just gonna
go with this
because i want to go get some ghosts
i don't catch something for the
no
it's time for spooky it's almost
halloween
anyway thanks for coming to our stream
and now we end it just kidding
just kidding we're gonna play the game
now oh no can you do me one favor um yes
can you end your stream once and open it
again
yes
wait wait yeah before you do that
okay okay
okay is everyone ready to see the 144p
yo it's okay it just simply will
symbolizes the ghosts you know when
ghosts around technology doesn't work
that's true
ghosts yeah break
technology
exactly
they don't want us to hunt
anytime anything you need
this is a nice year
what here
yeah i have an ear right in my face you
have an ear i don't know whose it is
who's here
oh very highly right
hi oh babe
looking good i'm inside of your head now
inside of your mouth is scary oh here i
want to see it again no
check out these moves i can do
what you got my move
i think the scariest out of all of us
today is bae
like the the one that who's the most
scared
i don't like ghosts i don't
deal with ghosts okay they're ghosts
they're in another dimension
i like to live
uh the the rat life in this dimension
okay
can you tell me how you're dealing with
scary games that this thing that you
told me before the stream
obs
oh
[Music]
i don't look at the game screen when i
play scary games i play the game by
looking at the small obs screen yeah
that's kind of smart though you know
when it gets real scary in resident evil
in the basement
sometimes i've been known to look at obs
good job we should do we only have two
jobs really surprised that i'm not the
the biggest chicken in the room in this
bay actually
hey i can play other horror games kind
of not really it's just
it's fast
it's just paranormal stuff that i can't
handle oh really
yeah
i should try resident evil
yeah we're all not very good at it but
we're going to try our best here are our
options because we're great
yo
i have 66
what do i need we haven't
i'll go first hello my name
is fauna i am the hollow council's
keeper of nature
and i am extremely good at all horror
games i have never been scared in my
life
and i'm going to find all the ghosts
thank you very much
wow confidence
thank you
i can't i can't get no
are you okay
okay
um what's up everybody it's buzz hey
guys representing
chaos room council what's up hop doing
good um
we we stolen i'm gonna stall for as long
as i can okay
we're gonna catch no ghost today uh what
why did you invite why did you invite us
to play this game then because i know
you guys liked the game but it was like
from cali signed no bae invited me to
play uh fasmo
you said who would want to play and i
said kiara
like okay that's the team then
i know it's because you like the game
and florida likes the game and i was
like this girl who do you mean with you
with the first you who did you mean
callie
yeah
i've played it a couple times i think
it's fine i've played it a couple times
in the past it's it's spooky perfect for
the season
sacrifice myself
hallows hallows week hallow's weenie
game
you're saying right now you sacrifice
yourself so we can use it today as a
sacrifice for the ghosts
whenever we need to you know
see if the ghost is going to attack
we're just going to leave you in the
room and we stay in the position in the
room that's okay with you right
[Music]
[Laughter]
you need to everybody
hey is the new
that's how i'm gonna be this week when i
play a [\h__\h]
that's outlast up from transformphobia
you'll have a blast so
so not looking forward to it it's the
worst thing that's happening to me this
whole year
it's pretty rough
i just screamed a couple times playing
that game
yeah who's next
yara you want to take it away
of course um hello my name is
takanashikiana from whole life english
and i have set
the game's voice recognition to german
on my side so i will be talking to the
ghost and yelling at the ghost in german
today thank you very much give him a
little letter thank you
i can't believe
[Music]
yeah
all right
i love that
um
last and also least my name is maura
cliffy i'm the first grouper it's okay
you know it's all right you just let it
happen i'm the first apprentice of the
grim reaper himself which means
i'm also
uh when it comes to dealing with ghosts
really bad because usually it's my job
to make humans into ghosts uh when it
comes to dealing with the ghosts um
it's not good and i'm ready to face i'm
ready to live up to my family name and
face full life consequences i'm excited
let's go my specialty in this situation
when it comes to being part of the the
scooby-doo crew
um
is taking a bunch of items into the
house that i don't know how to use and
have no reason for using and then
leaving them there so uh we'll see how
that helps us out in the game no don't
don't leave everything that we're all
broke as hell in the game you gotta put
it back into the track lane there's
nothing we even
have enough money to buy flashlights for
everyone i i have one flashlight i can i
can buy a little bit i don't have money
we already have one though um how many
do you have money
four flashlights
one costs forty dollars
pretty expensive let me buy something i
have seventy four bucks
so i have 62.
we can hit the dollar store
i'll get us a flashlight
i got picked up i got some stuff here
you go
and
thank you okay we got we got all
flashlights now we got full here we go
we got a thermometer okay
do you have a ghost writing book
yes it's in there yes great okay then we
don't need to buy this spirit box a uv
light video camera one of the six photo
camera camera one of the free emf reader
i'm one dollar short for a thermometer
guys but we really haven't probably only
have one we have one excellent
great
um i think we're good we need another
video camera or something crystal
perhaps
a glow
why do we need a glow stick is there a
party here ghost writing book um it
doesn't look like we have a ghost
writing book it's a zero
is anyone oh wait we can buy why did i
buy four week flashlights i could buy
one strong flash flashlight what yeah i
know right and
oh wait i have oh i have some stuff here
oh i didn't realize what the hell oh
wait what this is all my stuff yeah
oh my god wait oh
what does that all happen oh wait no no
i have nothing uh i'm gonna add salt two
times that's all right
i'm gonna add everything
salt is always great job oh yeah and
everything you've got i'm contributing
yes
i don't understand this how this game
works sometimes yeah
yes
cause now
all right well this is fine equipment
list is looking good so let's just go
with it
um
all right ladies here the jobs that we
have
we've got edgefield street house allow
me to narrate
recommended team two a two-story
six-bedroom house with a basement we
have recently received information about
a possible haunting at this location get
there as soon as you can and gather
evidence for the ghost removal team will
have more intel when you arrive location
is small recommended items thermometer
and this difficulty is amateur
yeah let's start with amateurs
let's do it
sorry
[Music]
oh by the way guys when we're talking to
the ghosts and you're listening to our
stream like on our side um
um
and we start the game
uh
one okay when we're trying to talk to
the ghost you'll hear us speak double
because we have to input our voice into
the game we're not actually using bush
to talk stay in the duct tape
use the trucks
why am i alone
i'm on my way i want to load in here i
go
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
that's not my name
possibly frozen
possibly
it says loading game 90
that's how it was for me for a while and
it was a long time until it finally why
is based on the oh just kidding
everyone's sanity is kind of fluctuating
[Music]
has been angry with me i kicked it out
of my
my closet that i stream from and
my pc is angry now it's been
received after newfoundland house road
there we go ah
what i'm here hello
margaret anderson this ghost seems to
respond to everyone you should be able
to use its name to anger it and get some
paranormal activity
i don't like this this game is making my
game full screen when i don't give a
commission too
that's because you're supposed to they
want it to play
you're going down is that bleach can we
bleach the ghost
capture a photo of the ghost i like
picking up items again there we go
walk through salt all right ladies so
let's maybe split this up and someone
should use the camera someone you should
use the emf reader someone should use
the salt
uh video camera and salt
all right all right
how do you use ems i don't know what the
you can scroll in between those items i
think like free items is maximum
okay where's the moment i want the
um anything dang it did i change my
can't thermometer
buttons you're right
this
drink
drink some salt milk
i want the emf reader
oh i have the emf reader hold on dang it
[Music]
girls all right pickup is d for some
reason i have it as z
drop is x
flashlight is c gotcha oh this is for me
this is my personal settings oh i should
ah are we going okay someone open the
door
it's really dark
[Music]
margaret margaret anderson
we just got to figure out what room she
said oh that is very creepy
i need
wait there wasn't a flashlight for you
there's one there should be there was
only free flashlight
[Laughter]
give us a sign
no could you just stay in your house
please no i shouldn't let you come out i
agree
okay 19 degrees there's a dirty dirty
ass woman here living here oh
19 degrees i'll say that about her clean
up your apartment come on this is kind
of nasty
oh she must be upstairs then yeah you
grab the emf reader i don't like that oh
that's
where is everybody bathroom
that's a beautiful
um
[Music]
oh wait whoa
oh my gosh downstairs oh he's downstairs
he's downstairs
are you banging this
hold on are you like right here it's 14
degrees right here
oh let me see okay maybe she's here
do you see like um like cold
like fumes and stuff
that's not cold enough oh okay yeah it
might not be cold enough okay okay okay
sorry
gotta check every room though babe
because very clearly
sorry the plant looked like the hand oh
my god
how about kitchen
margaret thompson give us a sign
20 degrees not here
for the laundry room
give us a sign
where's this door this is his
backyard i can't open it i don't know
okay um
oh i found a bathroom
[Music]
my cat is being very needy today so i
might have to go afk from time to time
oh okay
this door's locked have you guys been
upstairs yet
yeah we went up there but we didn't go
in every room is the thing
hey come with me let's go check out
every room i have the emf readers so we
should work together
i heard a sound
i heard i heard a phone uh vibrated
where i went
i didn't hear anything
[Music]
oh it's okay it was great
oh okay no i'm not this real
anything in my ear
i mean not liking
are we all just like really
really bad horror game players might be
give us a sign
hello hello
margaret thompson
great placement
we should
what's here
this is a big house
this bathroom
oh
i'm just gonna put salt everywhere you
always gotta put salt everywhere mm-hmm
yeah very important
maybe in here bay is the real ghost
and
six the baby six degrees where where
they're often in the basement where was
that i wanted to check the basement i
wish i had a light on my shoulder
instead of
this teeny tiny like
it's so small wait where did it go to
six degrees the light went out and am i
out of salt
guys the light went out i'm going
the ghost was a little bit active it
seems yes yes i i see oh i see
i'm not getting any emf activities
though
it must not be a ghost that responds to
emf
well i think you guys spotted a little
name out more more often too
thompson margaret
get out here are you evil
margaret anderson oh oh
anderson that's the reason why the ghost
hasn't showed up
margie
[Music]
there's nothing going on right now in
the activity there's no activity
really
yeah there is check out that activity
that's a big
emf 4 ladies how do i place this i'm
going in i gotta you know make myself
stronger for outlast
yeah good idea
should we put a camera
across there we go
put it down i got a cross
dots projectors
please
[Music]
it's
i was just kidding
i want to put this down here
i want to see if i can get five whoa how
can i turn it in guys help me chat
it's like a party down here does that
mean it's in the what
it's recording right yeah the ghost is
at the entryway guys
margaret anderson
[Music]
for maximum activity
i'ma stand at the door so i can just
back out that is status quick
wow okay what
someone's playing with something a ghost
that's not that sound
what is this
we still have a switch the light switch
wait is that holy [\h__\h] who is that ghost
the ghost is gone
the ghost has gotten the light switch
oh man
oh no
[Music]
down here i thought it was by the closet
no we're not fine i'm a badass margaret
anderson [\h__\h] you
okay it's definitely in this
anderson
yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay it's definitely this front room
margaret anderson
and phoenix
[Music]
oh i don't even want to know what she's
saying
enough
nothing too
margaret anderson
i set up a camera a video camera in the
um
in the entrance room bloody mary
it won't you won't sally i swear to god
oh there is activity i'm running away
yeah something's happening
we just gotta quit being little cowards
and gotta get deeper into the house but
it's not just the others
are you sure did you see the ghost
no but it went down to three degrees
oh okay well then maybe it's a room
close by
yeah
well it was useful here what is that
you can't really see anything margaret
anderson where is this really the best
place
[Music]
my friend
camera
margaret anderson [\h__\h]
[Music]
margaret anderson
oh you just get the [\h__\h] out of me my
dude
is that you it's it's the ghost oh
yeah
you got me
if i'm outside i'm i meant outside the
house margaret anderson how old are you
margie margaret anderson how we are
marge
marge margaret anderson vip
get inside okay give us a sign
where is everybody give us a sign it's
over hundreds is that something good
is that is that good
i don't know i'm not pleased he's got
prince in the garage oh is that that's
so
pretty
please no i'm so scared no we're fine
babe don't worry about it it's a rape
this ghost is a little coward
did you hear that margaret you're a
little coward mason what do the numbers
mean yeah you suck i'm gonna go to the
basement
something
yeah oh yeah basement oh yeah basement
you can't open it
wait the ghost is hunting probably oh oh
guys the door closed the ghost is
totally hunting
right
it was me
goodbye
[Music]
oh
is someone dead
i'm dead
really died i've died
really congratulations
i didn't see anything is the activity
over am i safe
um activity wait did two people die
i heard the door are you alive
stop it
i can't open the door you're scaring me
which door are you trying to get out of
here yeah trying to get down
okay there you go oh thank you
you open the door
is good
i'm dead wait for me wait for me okay
[Music]
oh my god our sanity is all very low
except for base which means we're gonna
send bae in again
yeah
i was uh really not doing good in there
what did you guys see on the camera did
you catch anything no because the camera
wasn't positioned correctly we gotta
hold the camera right i positioned it
perfectly are you telling your senpai
didn't position the camera correctly i
wonder
what it was when she died
wait where where did you put the camera
wait what where
on the on the on the little table on the
entrance
on the little table on the entrance on
the little table
huh
yes on the little on the little table on
the entrance what
yeah right at the door on the right side
there's weird stuff on the car
oh wait do you have the um the other we
need the other flashlight you know the
purple flashlight that you can look yeah
this has a car you have it oh okay where
do you need it
the door closed again
oh god that's bad um the door is locked
um
yeah
i took the headphones down i'm not
listening
[Laughter]
all right okay i'm back i'm i mean i'm
dead but i'm back oh no but you can pick
up my items they're all at the door i
got a i got a photo camera and why were
only you killed
because i mean i am okay to kill yeah
also uh here uh who is that woman
character
oh no is it funny that's funny we're
ghosts
even as a ghost i guess ghosts we can
see each other
hey it's you and me now
you know do you want to know where the
camera is the video camera it's uh
yeah thank you stuff away
stay where you are look to the right
to the right that's where it is the
video camera
oh yeah the green one
yeah
i mean why don't you carry a picture
with you uh fauna is that you are you
shocking it's it's not someone it's not
[Music]
i guess the main all right it's up to
you now
um
[Music]
did you guys find freezing temperatures
no
all right so maybe no freezing
temperatures
i found fingerprints
gotcha
fingerprints yes
all right
youtube chat chat
we gotta see if there's ghost writing
okay
if you go into the van you can do it
actually i put the book upstairs
oh god
watch out oh my god
[Applause]
oh my gosh that was a scary ghost she
was going down the stairs
oh i couldn't tell who was a human and
who was um all right well let's try a
different job guys
it was pretty bad i think
we lost all our stuff
recommended team size one how about that
guys a small three bedroom single floor
house the perfect we've recently
received information about a possible
haunting at this location head there
gather as much evidence as you can to a
ghost removal team blah blah blah blah
blah blah all right let's go get some
ghosts guys
yeah we should add some stuff
man
oh
i can afford things now i want a strong
you got money
yeah insurance
wait i didn't have insurance
i'm just dead
you always regretted later on that you
didn't get insurance
head mounted camera should also be good
i'm gonna add a tripod
a little card level eight and we can put
the video camera on it nice idea
what was that green dotty thing that we
play that i placed in the hallway when
candles yeah what was that motion sensor
right
really
did that tell us anything
no how how do you
can we bring candles again yeah i want
to see if i can light up some rooms next
time
does someone have three otherwise i'll
buy some
i bought two don't worry good job we
have a lighter already
salt never have you can never have too
much salt but i think we have plenty
pick up plenty uh do we need a
thermometer
always good to have just to check yeah
let me buy one unless someone has one
i'll go buy
i'll ed you're right
englewood street house now we're fully
equipped again and we're probably going
to lose it all again well we can we can
definitely do this
okay chad we need your help at least i
need your help come on
we can do it we can do it the green one
crosses through it i saw that happening
actually i saw the green dots like dim a
little bit
oh and like yeah and change before i
died
you can see the ghost in it through a
video come ah
dots projector is the green thing okay
it should always be like combined with a
video camera the dots projector oh okay
well uh bae i know you're feeling not
ready but you should push ready in the
game
all right i'm gonna bring you guys
let's start
survive those have been known to target
those who are staying in the light too
long
okay we gotta move into the darkness
anna's taking her time again that's okay
no worries
oh all right here's what we got there
she is
only respond when people are alone
that's fun
james moore james moore isn't that the
name of some famous person
it sounds like a famous person only one
torch wait why would we only have one
two oh you already took one oh yeah i
don't want to block you you only have
one
not lucky guys i got one
there's one on the floor
you know one can have one on yours
a one on the phone
flashlight
james moore this girl also seems to only
respond to people who are alone you know
you heard that bae
you got to be alone where's the head cat
where's the head-mounted camera
i think bae is like mentally brain-dead
i don't put all my items in the game
did you lose your voice
all right
hey thank you
okay you heard me thank you
you're good
it's so quiet like a mouse
anyone know where a lighter
is uh lighter lighter lighter yeah i
could have sworn we had a lighter last
time
in there
no it's not this is really weird
i saw it no no wait no i didn't see it
in the list actually
so we can't do [\h__\h] with the candles
just leave the candles in there then so
that we don't lose them okay
going in
i have the ghost riding book with me and
that's torch and that's all i got all
right i got fingerprints
okay
there you go
echolalia
do we have a thermometer still or an emf
reader
uh there should be
like we definitely brought one
i brought one i have an emf
[Music]
i would like it to be in the kitchen
that would be nice
okay yeah let's go in here
monsieurs
what's that set this bad boy down james
moore
james we'll be streaming yeah i could
just not throw something
everything i touch
oh there's someone taking a photo i took
a photo of the bone
thank goodness james
you didn't even walk in well james moore
do you wanna
exchange letters with me oh
give us a sign
i always wanted someone to exchange
letters with
a little pen pal a ghost pen pal that
sounds kind of cute actually
oh my god oh my god i just thought there
was someone here monster's shoes i found
the board where is it
i have it in my hand
oh i went upstairs i heard something i'm
coming up with it right now yeah i'm
coming into your basement
i how do we use this are the doors
locked no i heard something
aren't they oh i heard something i'm
scared i don't want to hear anything
i heard please no this is cool is this
like a rare item something i heard
something did
i want to leave right now
well they gave me the sign i wanted
the luigi board
i have a loyalty plug but i guess we can
only use it inside
oh did you have
a sign
yeah the lights flickered in the kitchen
oh
no
there's i don't know
there's some running water
how do i use this [\h__\h]
oh there's dirty water in the sink is
that one
oh yeah the temperature just went down a
little bit
give us the sign
he's given us some signs
oh god's steak
okay
water baby is that a three
it's it's it's not cold no no no no
okay drop it do we have the
emf reader thing
how do i activate it it always falls
okay
i'm not getting any signs hold up let me
take a picture of the sink i'm coming oh
wait no no no negativity is that a two
ring
was the ghost is stabilizing
okay good
we can't even clear amateur stuff wait
where's my old jawboard i think it's
safe to say no emf reading someone stole
my old job board did someone take my own
child board did the girls take my own
life
how do you get the oh i got the bone
it's gone
yeah it picks up the bone
you get money apparently is this you my
duke
maybe it's the basement
yeah no
it looks like you're a pizza delivery
person only like reply to the old stuff
board like in the correct room guys or
anyway
give us a sign
[Music]
bloody
can you come to the bathroom with me
uh
how old are you
he's in the bathroom he's in the toilet
what should i ask him
are you okay
hold on i'm i'm using the oja board the
question thingy
ouija board
the game can't hear me i tested it but i
want to set up a camera in the toilet
is that james
um me i do oh wait the door closed you
guys are in trouble you should hide
as i ran i ran right into the ghost
what it really went from zero to my
headlight off wow
you asked him a really personal question
i guess i shouldn't move right i
shouldn't i'm just there now um it's
safe
now
all right i'll be lookout for you guys
where'd you die someone come back hey
come back in your little chicken
can someone get your tripod i want to
set up i want to set up the camera
you can pick up the camera where i died
which is
by the way the tripod the tripod is in
the truck you guys oh
it's in the way
are you getting a reading emf 2 in the
bathroom
emf 2. raw beast do
hold on a second um okay i'm going to do
something terrible i'm going to be brave
i won't come in here it only responds
when it's alone where's the ghost
james moore right now give us a sign of
this zero
oh god
it said something i heard it
i heard it i heard i heard it
you mind it
isn't it hunting
no the door's still open you're in the
clear how do i get out i want to get out
of here
[Applause]
[Music]
um my sanity pills are necessary all the
stuff though at the door
you should probably grab it go to the
van and then we just leave and make a
guess
how do i open the door
i'm gonna die wait i'll try to open it
for you it's hunting again
oh no
aggressive before
oh i see it it went into the kitchen be
careful right i'm the only one left
alive i'm just going to pick up some
items and put it in the truck
oh my god
we got uh
look at my body spirit box
oh yeah does spirit box work yeah
i don't know am i supposed to be able to
see the other ghosts
i don't like ems level five
so
who are you what about fingerprints
ghost orb do we get freezing
temperatures
what's happening
what was the lowest temperature in the
zombae
uh something
you guys good is everyone dead
bae that isn't demon crouching oh it is
got the flashback
scary
this is the demon crouching
oh it is why does it have a flashlight
why does have a flashlight wait oh and
this is me
is someone is any ghost in the truck
right now can we can you tell me like
what they can
all right the activity is low it's not
it's basically non-existent right now
oh no that's the dead body oh that's
that's not the ghost i thought that was
the ghost oh
this is it that's what his body oh
you can't save items wait what you don't
you don't have to pick him up you lose
everything
really
every single time you go that doesn't
seem right then we really should get the
right guess here and not keep on losing
our money
all right guys
what do we know about him no emf level
five i was everywhere up in that [\h__\h]
with the emf
reader and i didn't get level five so
none of that
but there was this i put the books
somewhere does anyone know where i put
the book
um
if we get ghost writing
let me just try to find
if the book again
if the book isn't written in then it's
only two it can only be
one of two
phantom and yokai stella you put it in
the basement oh dear let's see if i can
make it
which one are you guys going for i want
to choose something before i go in so
that i at least have
something here oh who is that someone's
by the door
it's just the dead body let's put them
outside of it
no no no you'll be okay so far kelly
oh no i'm in the basement is it hunting
oh did someone die here
you died
i'm gonna go with um
wait what what what did i do let me let
me read what did support the guys
run into spread feet no that didn't
really dead buddy all right okay
flickering lights
mere yokai spirit spirits are very
common ghosts they're for powerful
passive only attacking when they need to
they defend their place of death to the
utmost degree killing anyone with a love
it's very contemporary stuff but for you
smudging okay my spirit sounds like it
could be it
i can check the book guys
i can check the book spirit though i'm
coming with you it's killed three of us
you said it's in the basement your
sanity because you can take a photo of
you make it temporary
i commonly said someone from origin i
mean i did speak with the original board
a lot but he never answered me so it's
not a phantom i think did you put the
book where is the book uh and oh wait i
guess the ghost can go look too huh yeah
it's like the basement in the basement i
put the book like pretty close to the
like it's it's like
on the other side
i can't see anything on the ground yeah
we might not be able to see it
you guys can't see anything
[Music]
journal oh
i didn't even know this was a thing
oh well
uh on the other side
of the crowd you can't
oh there's nothing in the book
there's nothing in the bowl yeah but
apparently ghosts can't see it anyway
even if like you go so dead dead players
can't see it oh that's annoying
um
i'm just gonna go with
a spirit because this is the most common
and we're playing an amateur game i
don't know biologically there's like
temperatures
like there was freezing temperatures
what was there what was it freezing is
below zero
oh no there was no freezing temperatures
okay um most candles no emf right
i don't think it was the spirit
oh no emf okay
if there's no emf level five it's not a
spirit
oh
we've got spirit box though
oh yeah oh no
just because so
poltergeist phantom man
okay well i think maybe a yo guy
i'll choose phantom just to be
contrarian okay okay okay do we all have
to pick this guy
that are attracted to human voices they
can usually be found haunting family
home strengths talking here yo-kai will
angered increasing the chance of an
attack oh
yeah yeah it is maybe it's yeah okay
yeah let's try it
let's try that oh
emf level five is one of the evidences
but i crossed it off for the everything
yeah me too but it comes up doesn't it
well
let's try i don't think so i think it's
just spirit box ghost form and
it looks like this
because i didn't see it
should i do it i'm not gonna lie guys
my hands are starting to turn numb
are you okay
um i like how
this ghost is called huntu
because i'm like hunting
put your guess in the book i did
did i know it uh
press j okay
i did what and then what do i do then
you click on uh you can go to evidence
go to the evidence tab
i did i put you okay okay good then
you're fine let's leave okay all right
look at our super professional van and
we all just suck i love it
i really got really unlucky whenever i
played before the ghosts were never so
violent
it was a mirror
so we messed up some evidence but it's
fine i got two dollars
and photos at least we got some more
money
[Music]
i don't know there's something kind of
good
all right we're really horrible at this
one
let's do one more game if that's okay do
you have it in you better last
redemption
i'm going to get a co-writing book
oh i got my items i'm going to add a
thermometer and a tripod that's all i
got
i'm buying a stronghold wait when did i
get 30 bucks
a line a lighter okay now we have a
lighter
on the candle for the camera
so stretching i would love one more
candle if possible guys if anyone can
buy it
i will buy do we have i
[Music]
good stuff now let's see what jobs we
have how about we do the farm house
because asylum in prison is going to be
no way
the farmers isn't that pretty pink
uh size recommended sizes two is a
two-story three-bedroom farmhouse we can
do either that or the prison recommended
size three an asylum recommended size
four those are scary
can you like refresh that to give us
something smaller
yeah no unfortunately it doesn't doesn't
work what no
i think we'll be fine farmhouse then
yeah let's do it it's gone
nice
i'm ready wait we only have one out of
four flashlights you and one stronger
one had
more yeah i bought a strong one i buy
one you buy one bae okay i cannot afford
one
i can't afford exactly one and then i'm
out of money oh my god
all right someone just stay with
someone who has a flashlight you can
stick with me or babe you were gonna
have a show
now we should have yeah we have four to
four and one strong one
okay actually then wait wait wait wait
wait then let me can i uh how do i get
rid of one damn it
cuz we don't need five flashlights
good question oh well let's just leave
one in the truck go go go
bang you got it right now
no okay no start
let's go
we can do this guys i know we can
let's just we even believe in each other
and we just gotta test out everything
okay yes and the executive point hide we
gotta hide
yes go in the closet
you gotta believe
george robinson
seems to respond to everyone you should
be able to use its name to anger angry
get some okay we don't have to be alone
for this ghost
okay okay
smudge sticks i didn't bring any smudge
sticks a little
strong flashlight
we have smudge sticks right
oh do
[Music]
actually i'll start off taking candles
and then i'll leave the ghost writing
book here for now if somebody else wants
to use ghost writing book i'm going to
light up some candles in the house
oh yeah i i'm bringing the ghost writing
book cool
and the video camera uh can anyone
bring the tripod
anyone got some free hands um
otherwise i'll leave the book behind you
here someone someone get the camera i'm
going i'll get the tripod
oh okay uh i i uh i put the book wait
that makes no sense then i'll put the
book down you take the tripod and i take
the camera
[Music]
i was never in this one before
yeah this map is definitely scarier
yeah which is the strong flashlight is
it the black one or the gray one
uh the black one
what's the name again george something
what was it john robinson george
robinson
george
what got you
i think it's the one that you put on
your shoulder there we go all right
we're good
you got the double
no i put the weak one away
okay
my dude is winded after two stories
robinson
i want to set up yours
13 degrees uh
[Music]
if you find something sauce tell me i
want to take a photo of it you go
there's the candle one candle
i'll go get another one oh god
i'm just gonna follow you very bright
i'll check the activity
okay are you safe it's still relatively
i was i was shocked by bae
yeah nothing's really going on right now
i can't tell who is who
gasps we need a moment
[Music]
that means something no i don't like
being in the dark without being able to
see and i don't like ghosts
another candle
i'll put one upstairs
it hurts the soul
okay it's a bit colder upstairs
oh okay nothing suspicious yet
yeah i have no emf yet wait we're not
playing a mangas here i'm not looking
for anything i left the tripod hold on
we should why is the tripod there did i
leave that there
maybe apparently you didn't placed it
breaker's in a really easy to find spot
hello uh
with this door
i can't pick it up why can't i pick it
up house man
there's some big house bedroom nice hat
oh do i have to be holding it the whole
time oh i see
okay
george morrison where are you we'll be
still
george morrison
where'd you guys go george morrison give
us a sign
where'd you guys go
from the bedroom
looks like it's not here george morrison
vault
[Music]
oh maybe my dude was giving us a sign
let me
how nice of him to help us progress in
the game attic i'm gonna go to the attic
dad is very brave of you yeah i probably
should have put a candle up here
give us a sign
why would i see a fingerprints
um usually near where the ghost is like
on the door or the window or something
weird how long
oh yeah i hear that too what the hell oh
that's you
that was me babe what is that there's
like a table
oh it's one more floor the attitude i'm
going to add it's scary
give us the sign okay who turned the
light off everybody who meaning probably
all lights
if you turn too many lights on it will
um
flick the breaker
okay
um okay
oh handle
this
what else is this
fingerprints you need the the purple
flashlight
yeah oh okay okay
give us a sign
what was that
yeah you're good at finding the rooms
which room
it was that one which floor
you're right here right here yeah which
floor
the second floor
oh there's a bone on the floor
oh you want to take a photo where is the
boom
[Music]
wait the second floor is balloon
second floor bathroom there's a bone
okay
where is bathroom i oh
nice got it thank you nice
okay
wait wait wait wait wait mate put the
tripod down where you think it is the
ghost
i love
[Music]
you gotta grab that bad boy get that
money i can't i got four hands man
all right i'm in the kitchen
i uh
is it really up here
because i'm not getting any emails how
do you think so bae hmm
can someone put the camera on top of the
tripod here maybe in the hallway when
yes
comes out maybe
you have no ghost writing book so let me
grab this
oh wait i could take it never mind i got
the boom okay
uh wait wait wait wait where did you put
the tripod it's right by the stairs
stairs
on the second floor
on the second floor stairs down to the
first floor
okay
oh god it's so dark i don't see [\h__\h]
yeah i thought i turned on the lights i
hear this
there we go
uh turn the light on oh scandal is out
is it is it filming do you see it
hold on let me try you're in the
i'm going to go to the truck and check
okay give us a sign chad says they went
to emf 3 but i'd
my candles
see it or hear it
where
um
all right that's you
uh
there's not mine
okay camera's on camera's on
camera's on
all right walking right in front of the
camera oh what
someone is
right
give us a sign
what do we do with this cow we need a
light or when we gonna
switch
um all of the candles i lit up are blown
out um oh um what does that mean should
we take a picture of that because it
means something because he did something
maybe i mean i probably should just be
witnessing an event there's no activity
at the moment can i borrow i haven't
found the right one
wait i swear it was the bathroom do you
want the thermometer here yes please
well let's maybe go back upstairs then
okay i'm coming
[Music]
candles do go out on their own
eventually
maybe we should put a candle upstairs
did you put one upstairs too
i brought one with me upstairs
all right wait do you have the lighter
oh it goes right yeah i do
yeah i would like to run it
here where
okay right next to the book
yeah
there we go
[Music]
i don't think it's reacting to me at all
i think the game doesn't pick up my
voice but okay well i'm going to go
downstairs and check on your sanity and
just look at the camera because is this
is this
give us a sign
hold up
let me have a look all right well
it's fine
the bathroom it's the base
put the video camera down in the ghost
room yeah apparently there's a little
bit of activity but everybody seems okay
hold up
i see give us a sign
accept that stuff here wait was it the
other bathroom is this the same bathroom
no i think it's a different bathroom
give us a sign
james morrison
george
is that an orb there's an orb is that
george morrison
[Music]
wait george morrison victorian
the name is george robinson everybody
yeah
george robinson
where's your dad give us a sign
yeah he's shy
people mixing up those names yeah oh
here
yelled oh little cheeky it's pretty cool
yeah what's up um let's i'm gonna go
nice sanity going on there it goes you
had nice sanity
yeah no i want to try to say move the
camera into like the bathroom maybe
george anderson
wait for the found it what
i just want the cold temperatures
oh okay
three and that's the end for me
looking good
look at my lights
i think i'm dead oh oh oh oh oh
flickering like indeed it is flickering
ring flickering it is uh hunting is that
what it is
it's me i'm getting monkey
i'm dead again
[Music]
i always die first
wait okay so we got do we get freezing
temperatures
well i still can't manage to get any
ghost writing so i think it's okay to
rule that out no freezing temperatures
no freezing no freezing temperatures it
was just cold but not freezing what was
the emf emf just three i think
oh wait let's see
useless no no [\h__\h] five
i mean just four
down to three it's either a phantom
banshee or a yokai
like how do we do we have a spirit box
we have ghosts or what do we actually
have ghost orb and something else
um i don't know if there's a ghost orb i
couldn't tell
i don't know didn't someone say we have
a ghost orb oh we're going to have an
orb
i can't turn on the light
why oh it's walking around upstairs oh
it's in the attic you you creepy
that's coming for me even though i'm
already dead it's walking downstairs
it's walking down no it's not wait i
don't know it might be in the attic
still
are you in where you're going
downstairs how do i turn off the
flashlight
that's bad i can't find my flashlight
you are okay and that's not good creepy
man holding a hatchet
please i just want to get
yes
i don't know how to turn off the
flashlight lull
uh ttt let me open the door
i can't come here
come
on
where come here
all right so let's regroup and figure
out what we know
i know there's
ghost orbs apparently yeah
what
oh maybe let's see okay
there's definitely no ghost writing
because okay i was everywhere up in that
[\h__\h] saying that dude's name he didn't
he ain't coming to do nothing
so no ghost riding increasing
temperature oh goddammit i'm going in
the closest
are you kidding me
yara oh no
you can try to run or hide
in a closet whoa oh we see you in the
window i see you in the window
oh he's coming he's coming for you
are you taking pictures from the outside
are you taking pictures he's in the
kitchen
he's in the kitchen
he's done okay
while he was hunting oh really what did
it look like
we've been here though
for
[Music]
did we see fingerprints did we say
fingerprints because i was running
around
what did you take what are the phones
you took
uh i took some cool photos yo oh
i don't know if they count as anything
but they're funky photos whoa did they
have the ghost interaction we can have
fingerprints guys apparently
everything that i don't see
for me it's apparently a banshee if we
really saw ghost orbs
well interesting
what does the band whoa what did it stop
after you took the photos because
apparently don't wait don't phantom just
disappear after you take a photo or
something wait a little bit yeah just
taking a photo of the phantom kelly and
pirelli disappeared yeah it was about to
hunt me now
and i took
the air and it disappeared oh yeah
oh that was smart
i'm not sure if it actually disappeared
because i saw it in the kitchen
i don't know
it like didn't go into the room where
you were in it went into the kitchen
instead no but it was at the door right
um no it was it went down the stairs and
then went into the kitchen
uh
yeah no it has to be a phantom because
there weren't any ghost storms there
were no ghost swords oh there were no
stops
i thought you saw a ghost warp
i think that was
oh okay i think i saw a flashlight just
uh one day i'll leave you
a phantom
in the summer
the only thing we have is fingerprints
you can cross out you can cross out
stuff in the journal if you click it
more times yeah i did i did i did i did
it so we have phantom
that's a bad thing how you
idiot give me the uh oh
i'm gonna die
i just wanted to put down some salt i'm
feeling salty
yeah come and get me behind this salt
idiot ha ha
i'll leave you
a phantom
come here
yeah
it's my little salt garden you guys like
it oh
written here in this triangle
[Music]
i got the door i guess so okay where's
the door where's the door where's the
door where's the door where's the door
where's the door where is it
there's not a lot of activity guys i
think it's fine i think the ghost is
kind of sick of us
you guys all guessed phantom wait one
last thing let me check the door
honey
outside
it's activity is going up a bit
oh bye-bye
okay
on on the door or end lights which is
all
well
once again that was a
very uh
eventful at least we didn't we mostly
didn't die seventy-five percent of the
party is still here somehow
am i three for three right now
that means we won't lose the items at
least at least the people who what is
that
the people who didn't die
okay
so are we really going for phantom
i guess i don't know what else we should
go for yeah
it could
sorry maybe we should split
i'll pick banshee
okay why would it be banshee
i don't know because because the game
always is right and we did chase me up
the attic even though there were other
people downstairs
because the banshee targets one person
specifically
oh
interesting but wouldn't have
something about being alone because here
it says everyone well that just means i
will talk to you on the spirit
i see
well i'm gonna close the door now
everyone make your decisions
all right i'll just see what happens i'm
i'm joining the black parade today let's
see what happens
[Music]
all right
yeah you suck weird farmhouse
that dude was really yanking our chain
for a while mm-hmm
it was a yo-kai oh we were all wrong
i don't get it
i'll just get it
we just got to get good
we just got to get good at phasmo
it really
started it became really difficult after
that stupid update
yeah it did there used to be
couldn't get a single win right exactly
exactly and we had some some decent
ghost hunters i would say this is just a
game for like really elite game lords i
think which is fine that's great
yeah our timing was just a bit off well
maybe that was for the best timing yeah
[Music]
i love spending time with you guys
though don't get me yeah
and play dvd
i personally wouldn't mind not playing
it anymore either
[Laughter]
like
fun because you guys are here
yeah
me too i enjoyed having uh you guys
around and spending time with you guys
because i
i haven't had much time or like
possibilities to interact with the
council members specifically
um
yeah
cross-generation
my heart is still pumping
your heart rate monitoring
i've been trying i was gonna ask you how
to do it because i'm not kidding it
feels like it's coming out of my uh
coming out of my chest oh no
i can't feel my arms i can't feel my
legs is this this oh my gosh that's
really intense i didn't know it was that
it was like that you should have a good
rest
wow
there's so many other games that you can
play with four people
now you can say you've done it and you
never have to worry
[Music]
yeah i feel like i'm getting braver at
horror games there are no monsters under
your bed okay should mommy fauna check
under your bed tonight
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah tell him you tell him
oh i still had a good time though i'm
extremely hungry but i still had a
really good time with you guys i
actually have to i'm watching horror
movies quote-unquote horror movies oh
yeah right
popcorn what's your favorite popcorn
callie
theater butter
butter salty butter extra buttery
oh
i've had a time where i only wanted to
eat caramel popcorn
but now i'm back to like i don't mind
eating any kind like salty or butter or
uh caramel popcorn i don't mind anything
you probably can stick to that real
quick huh it no i i love the when it's
like the more caramel is on it the
better
it on it
the more you know the better yeah agreed
yeah fana what's your favorite popcorn
um i like classic buttery as well
oh oh good choice you got some good face
how about you being in the classroom
what's your favorite one bails what's
the question
what's your favorite popcorn
um
i like cheese
you like cheese popcorn
you're a wrap but i've i've only seen
cheese popcorn before in japan like i
was in a store where there's like uh 50
different types of popcorn and they're
they all sound weird as [\h__\h] oh yeah
like um like seaweed flavor and stuff
like that even crazier than that that's
that's still super normal for japan's
seaweed
yeah but it was really weird stuff
really interesting cool
that's tasty at least at least they got
different types red red bean flavor oh
yeah that's right and like spicy super
hot
strawberry flavor they had
banana flavor they definitely had banana
flavored popcorn
yummy actually
pizza
like pizza go fish
sorry nerdy out over popcorn a little
bit
i'm glad you're also a popcorn fan kiara
i wouldn't mind whenever i go back to uh
japan
you know what we should do we should
find that store and then get like 20
different types of that popcorn and do a
taste testing yeah blindfolded you guys
can't look at it it's a good idea
oh yeah i mean
would be nice to look at it but i guess
popcorn all looks the same most of the
time yeah you gotta guess the flavor
that's the fun of it
they are being quite sorry oh i had to
go
my cat was meowing again no i had to
check on
him
can you give me a cat fact of your cat
yes he is 21 years old so old how are
you more like an insider give me an
insider cat fact oh my old man
what's an insider cat fact
like uh like something weird about him
that he does
um he sees into the spirit realm
and yells into mirrors
that's adorable
whenever i pet my cat uh my cats on like
the part right above their tail they
lick themselves
oh
yeah
it always without fail it's very cute
fauna do your cats follow you wherever
you go like as soon as you get up from a
chair do they like run after you
not really but hold on i have to go grab
him
is that
you know what my one of my cats uh
smoothie you know what what cute thing
she does um
you know when i'm talking on my stream
like i talk pretty like
like constantly right so when i when i'm
done streaming i immediately stopped
talking and smoothie every time i swear
every time i'm done streaming she
immediately comes into my room because
she knows i'm done streaming because i
stopped talking she walks into my room
she says meow and then she falls down on
the floor and she rolls around and says
hello like mommy you're done with
streaming don't play with me
so cute yeah
she recognizes when i'm done streaming
it's so oh well he's probably figured it
out by now yeah yeah definitely
when mommy is loud she goes to different
room to sleep and when when mommy is
quiet she comes back and says hello
guys
babe do you like cats do you have a good
relationship with cats
yeah you are a rat after all
do you ever get chased by cats
yeah
yeah that's a good answer
well has a cat ever tried to eat you
meow
yeah i don't want to think bae is brain
dead
yeah i think so
oh well that was fun ladies thank you
for inviting me i'm calm i was calming
down i think
you guys had fun at least i wanted to i
just wanted to
i don't know next time we'll play
something not scary
when where are you gonna play scary
games
that's the thing it's just this game
because i can't deal with paranormal any
other kind of
horror game is not in the dark i can i
can somewhat and they call it
every horror game
it's fun
which horror game is not dark
literally
yes it says daylight so it's right
i mean yeah there's like a winter level
that's like pretty bright outside i
don't think it's i don't think it's the
type of scary game that
that you would freak you out bae so i
think it should be fine
i'm excited to play dead by day like
yeah it'll be fun
like first person perspective that makes
it too real yeah
is unless you're the killer but then why
would you be afraid if you were the
killer so yeah you'll be fine you'll be
fine don't you worry about it bae we're
gonna have a great time right okay
with that being said guys i guess we
better sign off huh okay yeah alrighty
that was fun
let's have fun
thanks for having me
thank you very much
uh maybe we'll see it might just and it
depends on how you guys approach it
because people think i have a grand
master plan but it really is kind of up
to you guys so which way the stuff that
you come up with is like up until now it
was always very scary and spooky so it's
like it's always halloween and you're
teaching everything
i'm glad you at least think that because
right now i feel like everything is very
clownish and very funny well yeah but
that's what those are pretty scary
people
yeah
yeah well i hope that you enjoy the next
installment you guys
looking forward to it yes gumbaz gumbot
going to be fun um anyone else got
announcements that they want to shout
out while we have a chance schedule is
out look at it
um
[Music]
coming out on saturday oh yeah
i'm sorry i'm still trying to find the
feelings in my arms um i hope you guys
will be there
um of course i'll be there it's a very
cool thing
yeah mm-hmm
wait did you say did you like spoil what
your were you you know putting out there
no i just said special release something
anything special like not but not that's
it that's all you said yeah
yeah so i know i know more than the
audience
me too
you guys do yes yes
i'm like gorilla stream tonight
maybe i don't know what you're gonna
play
minecraft
of course
very good for gorilla that's the
gorgeous game
yeah um
donkey
oh i don't really have anything
i'm taking a little break because
i streamed a lot this week
okay
amazing
yeah
let's see
we love you
thanks everyone everybody will be out
soon
for members and then
bye guys
[Music]
do
you