[Applause]
[Music]
he
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
he
[Music]
[Applause]
n la
[Music]
[Applause]
I
[Music]
l
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
kick KY howdy
hello sorry for the
[Music]
wait
hello welcome back to the Wild Wild
West the wild wild west where only Wawa
is the
best uh yeah
K we're back to LA not Las Vegas New
Vegas
YY I feel so hot oh my God it's so hot I
think I noticed um my
builtin cooling system is not
working I know I've been noticing for a
couple days
now well even if it was working it was
Pro it would probably not be so
significant but
[Music]
yeah
uh [\h__\h] summer yeah I don't know why we
don't have AC by default man it's just
crazy it's so hot and it's just June
beginning of
June and I even got like the blinds down
and all
that it's not even that hot hot outside
I think I went outside
to buy
groceries
yeah let me actually turn on the fan at
least a little
bit who it's so
strong let's turn it
down okay do I feel that from
behind yeah a little bit a little
bit southeast Asia is even
[Music]
worse I mean I've been
there few times
now I know it
is but that doesn't mean that it doesn't
suck here
too so yeah
uh I want to write down some tangent
memos just just in case I you know go
brain empty
again so uh Ian
concert uh which also I want to talk
about both the concert announcement and
the tour
announcement and going to talk about
that then we're going to talk about H
new outfit stuff uh predictions and
stuff I want to talk a little bit about
that then there was something that I
told you guys that if I need something
to talk about you guys should tell me
remind me of that right did I give you
any hint you wanted to address a
sleeping for sleeping Forest are you
here let me ask right
away but what was the other
thing wasn't there wasn't there another
thing that I think I talked about it
yesterday sleeping sleeping fors isn't
here right I don't
see them
around oh ah and I want to talk
about hellofresh versus no
hellofresh talk a little bit about that
you don't really understand what that
means right now
but probably too early
probably H what oh my God I just can't
remember [\h__\h] uh what else happened
happened what else
happened thanks for Super
[Music]
Chat
uh
ah
uh new
3D I want to talk a little bit about the
3D
2.0 that I showed
yesterday friend inbrook is one note I
had
nah why
I don't have a friend in ins
spoke
huh oh maybe uh I maybe I think I think
I talked to a
friend about yeah well that's so Random
I think it was something like I talked
with a
friend yeah who is I don't think I don't
think the friend is from there but like
at least they were from like not one of
the most common places that I usually
mention in Austria so they're not as
biased right and they also said inbook
is like yeah they really were like
condescending about it too like why why
is indeed why is insbook popular with
tourists like yeah and uh my friend also
uh agreed with me that sbook is the
better in spook it's not even you know
maybe we shouldn't even compare it but
yeah I now I already explained that
right off the bat not a paid actor
no this this friends here with us now
now no
no no my friend is not from southb I
said my the friend is like from
somewhere completely unrelated in
Austria just to once again uh
assert
superiority
okay the friend is not made up I talked
about I I was I told you guys that I
wanted to mention this ages ago so it's
a real
story oh
man okay I think these are like the most
important things can I think of anything
else can you guys think of anything else
that I should be talking
about today today
today I think I'll think of more I don't
know about that mirror situation what's
mirror situation landlord incident
mirror is this like things from before I
moved mirr that's how you
ask okay I don't think I can think about
what that was now I mean the mirror
situation have I not kind of told you
guys that besides not living with
curtains for the longest time I also I
haven't lived with um mirrors M bathroom
mirrors on the wall for the longest time
I told you that right
yeah that's okay that's okay we can keep
it at
that I still don't have
one it's still no bathroom
mirror man I need somebody's help with
that I just need I need help I need
help get get get some help so this is
this this is just small smaller smaller
memo don't even let me put a TI to the
hashtag but let
me
notes put that there
okay
okay oh let's
play fall out Fallout fallout Fallout
let's see if it will crash a lot today
if if today I become sir crash
aot I don't know why sir sounds better
because LS a lot crash a lot you know
it's a joke it's a
joke it's
joke where's my where is it
here ah should probably unmute there go
who
okay did I have it windowed last time
too I wonder I
probably I probably did have it window
oh okay let me move it into a good
[Music]
position
yeah here
Works always have to position everything
properly because tab out is a pain in
the ass so I'm just going to do it right
away okay are we oh wait you don't see
it yet God damn
it yo Mouse disappeared this is one
thing I will not miss when we are
where's my mouse
here it just eats up my mouse and [\h__\h]
like that I can't tell
about I will not miss this when we're
done with this game he I
know it's a feature
yeah
where's uh
game
okay come on I will be it will be the
wrong size I hey don't be so annoying I
have to tab in in order for the game to
show up right hello
there it is and now I have to Tab out
again Tab out with task manager fix the
size oh
man I mean yes I could have done some of
these things before the stream but I I
went to buy groceries I had all I did
today was I got
up I uh had breakfast I brought uh I
bought groc h I threw out some trash I
bought
groceries then I had one slice of
leftover Margarita
Pizza don't judge me it was you could
say it was cheat day but at the same
time I don't think I consumed that many
calories uh because I didn't have lunch
and it was only half a pizza what I ate
not even half I think it was uh yeah now
it's what's left over is a half so I ate
like
13 or something I don't
know and this is Margarita so anyway and
I ate that and now I'm here so I
basically didn't have time for
[\h__\h]
anyway are you ready to
go uh
yeah so
ready we
are yeah okay I've confirmed that we are
in the right place
uh we are in New
Vegas can I shoot at the balls no
probably not right what what if I what
if I did would they be angry at me if I
shoot at the
balls
don't save and
try oh no one cares okay
no one cares I did think people would
get mad they did not even
[Laughter]
care and yeah I feel like you know I'm
going to be kind of lost again so you
guys will have to help me out what if I
shoot the dog's
brain I do want to try
that oh okay that is
[Music]
very not good stream
content I
missed you want you want to challenge
[\h__\h] I just want to see the
reaction a you make me feel
bad skill
issue Rex good boy no hurt
it's not like I would ever do this IRL
bro I would never even touch a gun
IRL oh man I just want to see you know
if they don't react to the ball do they
react to anything I want to see this
explode I want to see the I want to see
it
shatter
[Laughter]
shter h
okay I'm I'm happy now I've experienced
the frill we can get started content has
been created so what were we doing how
do I
know okay pit
boy tell me go to uh what go to
of of course he would attack you yeah
that that is a given but I was just
wanted to see it I'm not telling the
legion [\h__\h] the
legion go to the old Mormon Fort and
question some injured locals about their
salant confront Benny at the tops
Casino uh which one of the this is the
main quest I suppose or is it no this is
the main quest should we do this one
first
then this will I guess what we need to
do
uh
what old Mormon Fort is that outside of
New Vegas I don't understand what that
is personal space meaning anything to
you lady hey I'm walking here as they
would say in New York right that's what
they say in New York New York
New
York hey I'm walking
here we're going to New York we're going
to be walking here to New York where's
the
exit everything looks the same guys you
can like even can't you even like
decorate stuff a little
bit so where where is the Fort where is
this fort
every new
yoran we're just going to follow maybe I
don't know where I don't is this outside
or
inside is
nearby we've got stuff we're not even
allowed to sell people only at Mick and
Ralph's whoa
go for it go get the rat Go Get It Go
Get It it's your dinner if you don't get
the rat you're not going to have
anything to eat for the next 5
days think about that little
boy you're going to
die it's rough out here
remember H I think this must be the
fourth because I think I'm walking
around
it
hello moim I'm very shoot friendly today
ah I'm in the time Loop Oh
no you're
welcome it's yours now
trouble oh oh for the Brotherhood what
are they fighting me
because you did that with your fists are
they fighting me because I took down the
rat that was his pet no way
what's what's with them did I create
chaos no that's okay that he's just he's
just doing what he
does
Sledgehammer outfit okay well
anyway Old Las Vegas Mormon State
Historic
Park open door to okay y
bit is this your
B am I going to get
attacked
oh is that a
ghoul oh I think it's a
ghoul howdy
howdy ah who are you I've been around a
while currently working for the
followers as a gun for hire but it's
getting rather dull aside from
protecting them from the occasional Thug
looking to intercept Supply shipments
there isn't much to do around here here
is it quiet by way one researcher I like
who I could chat up about got
transferred and the rest of the docks
are pretty uptight about my kind of
fun this is the only genuinely nice
faction AO all good okay what are you
doing with the followers I joined up
looking for a decent paying job granted
the pay is all right but they won't let
me kick back and slog a brew at the end
of the day I don't hate ghouls they're
worried the filthy drunkies and detox
seeing drink will cause an immediate
relapse I say their rehab effort here is
just a revolving
door by the way I watched an interview
of the Fallout main
actors together asking questions and
stuff about Fallout the show and all
that and in general Fallout questions
and I have thus learned that ghouls
probably do not
practice
C apparent I mean there maybe they could
maybe they could I don't know but
doesn't seem to be a thing there's no
children no ghoul children show me a
ghoul child maybe they do intercourse
but they don't birth children maybe they
can't I'm sure they can't
right specific specifically she can hey
yo what I talk about this topic while
talking to the one single ghoul that
can no way but they
said the ghoul The Ghoul from The
Fallout show he thought he kind of said
they don't do
it there's a ghoul child in Fall for but
was it born as a ghoul or was it turned
into a
ghoul after hm
he was turned oh yeah there you go
mhm he was turned that's that's
different
anyway I've been around long enough to
observe the patterns of human behavior
physical and mental anguish are
especially exciting to
explore hey who doesn't enjoy a little
pinch and squeal every once in a while
okay what do you have in mind
nothing oh yeah give me some advice life
advice please good bad the guy with a
gun makes the rules what about the woman
with the gun
H well you have more longing makes the
heart grow fonder you're like a fortune
cookie fan of hog tying my lovers to
make sure they can't escape fortune
cookie just has one you're a Chinese
restaurant because you just give out the
fortune cookies one after another
anymore longing makes the heart grow F
but I've always been a fan of hog tyeing
my lovers to make sure they can't escape
well oh wait new one beat a Man for free
and he'll be back asking for more damn
she is chines restaurant you won't hear
from him
again oh another one the only thing I
know for certain is that I don't know
nothing how many more fortune cookies
they going to give me
huh goodbye so what am I look looking
for here again uh question some injured
locals about their asence
okay you look like a doctor yeah is
there a oh no no one injured
here you don't look really injured but
you look you look nice they're looking
nice love those
tights oh I see injured people wonderful
ooh so stylish so Dapper hello oh he
gets up so
like B what what what what you were not
what you're not actually injured are you
there're just gamblers sleeping out
there alcohol
intake what the hell don't what's
up I thought you guys had actual like
injuries and stuff I got worried about
you you're just so freaking alcoholic
are you
where are the this person must be hurt
right it doesn't say
Gambler hello I'm pressing e it doesn't
work hey no no no that's not want to
what is it can't you see I want to be
left alone with my friend
here okay I can talk to you huh your
friend looks like he's in bad shape yeah
the doc say he's going to be laid up for
a while assuming he doesn't get any
worse laid up he's laying
down just I don't know questioning
English language
but um the king asked me to look into
your attack oh that's different then how
can I help I'll do anything to get the
bastards that did
this oh you guys found it
funny and do you remember anything about
the people who attacked you they were
big guys young too no old Geyers like me
hell none of of them looked even half my
age I was mostly faced down in the dirt
for my life when it happened so I only
got a quick look at him is it about the
quest well can you tell me about the
attack well it happened at night around
11: we' recently made some caps off a
bit of scrap we found and wanted to
invest it wisely as we were leaving the
Wrangler we must have taken a wrong turn
and ended up in the squatter side of
town from out of nowhere these big guys
show up and start barking questions at
us wanted to know we were locals the kid
there is about as proud as a local
around here gets and started yelling
back at him then all hell broke loose
kid got the worst of it sad to
say
mhm I hope you find the bastards that
did this if you want try asking my
friend Wayne over there about him he saw
more than I did
Wayne way it's okay the king sent him oh
thanks thanks bro app is that true did
the king really send
you yeah I am the king taking the crown
now they calling me king oh did you guys
like the opening The Fallout opening H I
forgot to say cow carrot made it I
actually kind of asked how car to make
something I was like hey you know you've
made some really cool openings for me
before like the others were all yeah on
on his own m
what how to say he just did it on his
own but yeah I I thought maybe it would
be cool to have something anything for
Fallout because it might go on a little
bit
longer and he even own volition there
you go he even made a freaking remix
again on his
own from Clipper to being able to use 3D
stuff and then making some remixes and
stuff like w what damn he's picking up
skills left and right our carrot carow
carrot cow carrot the
goat
yeah so cool I appreciate it it's nice
to have some specific opening for a game
series that's going to run longer thanks
for the pinky sticker thank
you
m
yeah eh he did any and anything you
could tell me about what happened might
help I don't really know what else I can
add there were a bunch of guys better
dressed than most frees Siders I guess
that
help not really well I don't know
anything else sorry hey wait I just
remember something I might have heard
one of the guys that attacked us call
another by name we had just about had it
when one of them said hey Lou we got to
go at least I think he said Lou might
have been something else now that I
think of it he said lose something
something with a t tenant that's what he
called him
he keeps probably I don't remember
anything but actually I do
remember I don't remember but I do
remember uh-huh so a
lieutenant I think you write that not l
u you write that l i e u t e n
hey no whatever it it's the first couple
letter that are
important
morning oh yeah yeah I know about the
gun thing I know I just don't really
care most of the time M okay wait now we
good to go return to the king with your
findings return to the king hello hello
feel like I'm playing a medieval game if
you just look at this out of context
this could be a medieval
game this kind of
structure this that's no but just this C
be
Medievil too yellow what do you mean
that's just a
lightting hi hi oh how polite of
you I guess they're still
teaching manners a tiny bit to some
people
here but it doesn't seem to be a
priority nowadays
Wawa is
back H
[Music]
King
do oh here
okay yeah the arcade somebody said it's
not really important right now so I'm
leaving that for another time
it's not even a real arcade is
it right that where where does it go up
ah
[Music]
man I'm never going to find my way
through these kind of places properly
easily so you weren't you also
downstairs very
confusing hi I'm back have you found
anything out or were you just here to
chat the local men were attacked by
soldiers one of the men was identified
by rank bunch of Soldier Boys huh they
usually don't come around these parts
since their big base is on the other
side of the strip if they're coming over
here now got to be for a reason I didn't
want to believe the rumors that they're
looking to take over Vegas but now if
something big is going down I'm sure
rumors of it will have spread ask around
particularly in the squatter areas where
the NCR folk hang you might also Mose on
over to the Mormon Fort and chat Julie
farcus up the followers tend to be in
the know about these things just don't
ask her what to do about it she'll
probably ask you to hug someone or
something hug someone hug hug is that
what what accent is that all right I'll
see you
later optional talk to Julie farcus and
see if the followers know anything about
the situation optional
where's Julie
farcus this the Elvis
accent well not only Elvis talks like
that right
Memphis she's in the fort aha okay I'll
do it I'll talk to
her what's
up what's
up back to the Fort
okay so guys have you watched the stream
the big announcement stream yesterday H
I think a lot of you guys kind of were
feeling like something like this must be
coming I I've been seeing people discuss
that like why was no Ian concert
announced yet it's
already oh it's
already freaking June and yeah if we
were going for
like maybe if we were going for the same
location same date is as last year again
then we probably would have had to
announce it
earlier but it's a bit different this
[Music]
time it's a bit
different yeah so I also stayed up
because I was still so excited from my
announcement and then man I stayed up so
late because like double hype double
excitement kind of triple excitement
even
cuz after my announcement came that
announcement and I watched the whole
stream because I I don't know I want to
stay until the end and see your guys'
reaction yeah and so for people who
don't
know in case you don't know is there
anybody who doesn't know the
announcement
uh Hey when's the date I don't remember
the date but we are going to have
another whole iing English concert and
it's going to be this time not on the
west coast but on the East
Coast yay I know people have always on
the East Coast have often been like you
know asking for stuff on the East Coast
hello cuz we've been doing like lots of
things on the west coast last concert
was on the west coast hello and now you
getting what you've been asking for and
I think it's so cool that we're going to
go to New York this time
New
York so cool so cool and so one thing I
want to say uh if you look up the
location then yeah it might be a little
bit shocking at first that um the
capacity is pretty low like half of what
we had before I think but uh keep in
mind that this time we actually have two
days two days
instead of one day only and that is
super hype so it's basically double the
capacity but at the same time I know
that's not quite true either because
some people will probably go on both
days and then that's not really doubling
the
capacity um but at least you have you
know you do have the chance
approximately the same chance I would
say hello for percentage wise of getting
a ticket as last year I don't know I
mean I guess not because maybe now more
people are actually trying to get a
ticket than last
year I don't know but yeah of course you
can always
stream and the cool thing I I guess I'll
just talk a little bit about it now
while I'm excited and I'm on the
topic the cool thing
is
that M as a kfp as a wa fan even if you
are not able to get a ticket for this
one you are in luck because Wawa Wawa is
part of the announced World
Tour which will be in several
locations uh over the course of a quite
a long
time uh you will see once there's more
details out I can't say too much right
now um um but for
kfp I'm I I hope that you if you really
want to see me live that you know you
you'll get one one opportunity
eventually sadly nothing in Europe well
yeah I also pointed out
like so much of a world tour when it's
literally just America and
SCA but
um who knows
maybe at the moment you see you saw uh
the the cities that are already decided
and
generally um I don't want you to get get
your hopes up but it it doesn't 100%
mean that this is the
final
outcome so still a small small chance
that something could be added but
anyway um that's how it looks like right
now yay so that's what I've been talking
about recently when I've been saying ah
you know I may not get this and that but
at the same time I'm getting a lot of
other cool
opportunities uh in terms of 3D and I'll
be very freaking busy preparing for all
kinds of things hey
so I am very very very happy to be
included in the world tour especially
and the whole concert I'm pretty hyped
about that
[Music]
too yeah I
I New York I I want to go I want to go I
want to go to New York I've never been
to New York I have I haven't been to
many places in America I I've been to LA
and maybe one or two more places
that's pretty much it I I would be so
cool if I could go to New
York your birthday life is is in
September yeah I won't even call it
birthday life anymore um but yeah the
summer is packed I really like New York
you're probably like midtown
midtown is that so
hey weren't uh friends and Seinfeld in
New York and like there's so many TV
shows that are you know set in New
York I want I want to I don't know get
that feeling I want to feel that feeling
and and I I I want to I want to check
out like popular food places and all
that if I can if I get to go
yeah visit Jerry's apartment hell yeah
Jerry Jerry Seinfeld where are you where
are
you Seinfeld was in Manhattan friendss
is in Brooklyn which is both New York
right those it sounds like city names
but I know Brooklyn is in New York
Manhattan too
[Music]
right salmon locks on Bagels oh yeah
Bagels is a big thing right I don't
really eat Bagels
normally New York
burrow Bagles and pizza I am New York
New York
Pizza I'm I'm going to go I'm going to
walk for this city hello and I'm going
to be like hey I'm walking
here and I'm going to be the most
obnoxious tourist
ever uh hopefully okay who are we
talking to I I'll I'll maybe I'll talk a
little bit more um afterwards after we
make a little bit more progress a lady
right you're not the
lady uh
are you the lady followers guard hey is
this marker no probably
not you you one are you here to drop off
medical supplies leave them with the
rest in the middle of the courtyard damn
that hair is not my thing that is really
not my style I really don't like it lady
but you do you you do you I
guess H do you know anything about the
NCR soldiers here in freeside only a
little a friend of mine Major Elizabeth
Kieran has been handing out supplies to
the poor a little west of here what
about
it the king thinks those troops have
been attacking locals I know something's
got them riled up but I've been too busy
with other matters to really look into
it if you're looking into the matter
talk to Elizabeth she's in charge of the
operations here in freeside though she
won't open up to you right away if
Elizabeth holds out on you tell her that
I sent you she should be a little more
forthcoming if you mention my name was
there anything else you wanted to talk
about
goodbye why are you so rude I thought
you were nice you don't even say goodbye
back to
me
elizabeta
elizabeta Major Elizabeth Karin
Takashi and mention Julie farus wait
Elizabeth is she in here too no right
are
you no major maybe she's just I don't
know with the
outside hello is wait I got two markers
right
Elizabeth she's outside
okay Johnny TS New York tourist tips is
that famous
well when the when the time comes for
sure oh which
way there's a marker here let me can I
check which marker is
which
uh I don't think I can
oh I don't think I can go to the right
one thank
you
here what in
inside wait you said right one but
from
this
really Stacy is fleeing what does that
mean who's
Stacy you go
Stacy who's
Stacy the pump the pump is property of
the
king the pump is property of the king I
don't know why I was so shocked at the
the I
no uh
uh
uh wait the pump is property of the king
that that friend over there you can't
call a chicken your property only I
can I I I don't know where things are I
don't understand I'm trying to follow
the
markers I guess I got to go back inside
probably can I go through
here no I think I think there's an
invisible wall
oh who are you
dudes that's actually where one of my
markers is
hello are you the Super Troopers that I
need to talk to hold up what's the
password ah okay this is without doing
the optional stuff I suppose though
right I could speech my way into it
is this the non option well we'll just
do it if you're here to see the major
then I suppose it's all right head on
through no wait major Kieran wait no
this is the optional thing never
mind yeah I'm dumb I hope this
helps
oh return to King well that that's it I
just walked in here and that completed
it oh wow
yummy yo
crabs no grilled
mantis h
H he okay bye bye no let me talk to you
though Elizabeth Kieran welcome there's
food and water here for any citizen of
the NCR please have
some oh I didn't even I didn't even want
to take
anything do you serve food to locals as
well no I'm afraid we don't don't you
have a friend you want to bring in
[Music]
no it's just curious well now you know
enjoy the
food yes was there something else you
needed thanks for the food you're quite
welcome if you meet anyone who needs
food or water in the area please tell
them about this place I'm so Charming
hello never forget to be grateful yes
was there something else you needed um
are you with the NCR military yes I'm a
major in in the supply Corp which is
where this food and water comes
from why don't you serve the locals
that's not really a pleasant topic of
conversation let's just say we have our
reasons
[\h__\h] Julie farus told me to ask please
tell me please you know
Julie not everyone in the NCR sees eye
to eye with the followers but they're
okay in my book mostly because of her if
you really want to know we sent an Envoy
to the king offering to coordinate the
relief
effort and
okay what happened our Envoy was
brutally beaten and only barely survived
my superiors ordered the relief Mission
scrapped I managed to get clearance to
carry out the mission anyway but with
greatly reduced support now there's not
enough supplies to go around even if I
wanted to serve the rest of freeside
which I don't H that's all in the past
now I should get back to work say hi to
Julie for
me
[Music]
oh okay I think we did
it think we did it I'm glad I stumbled
over this place that was hard to find
because I thought I was going completely
the wrong way and was about to turn
around investigate the J
a wait let me let me read it
though uh optional in the king that the
NCR previously sent an Eno to discuss
return to okay so it's some both things
now want me to go to the
king fine with
me so where are my east coast kfp East
Coast where you at are you excited that
we're coming closer to you this year hm
east coast East Coast
yeah I'm skeptical that I get get a
ticket yeah um it's a bit unfortunate
that even with the two days oh thank you
for the
raid thank
you it's a bit unfortunate that we still
basically have you know same capacity
was kind of hoping for bigger I think
all the fans were also hoping for it
because last year it was sold out right
away
and the at I'm sure I'm sure
the that's what everybody wants in
management too
hi but
well it to be like that sometimes I
heard that NCR Soldier lady told you
some wild story about them a messenger
to us work out some deal that's [\h__\h]
and it's nothing to bother the king with
more like they sent someone to spy on us
and he wasn't tough enough to last in
freeside so do everyone a favor and keep
your mouth shut about it
okay uh can I tell you if the two days
are different I think I can tell you
that um it's uh everybody will be on
every
day I was was told I'm allowed to say
that all of us will be on both days
which is cool um but maybe maybe one day
is a bit little bit like more uh a
little bit less you know like maybe you
know you know uh but we're definitely I
think it's you know relatively balanced
and and yeah
the it'll be different it won't be all
the same
no it's not the same concert
twice yeah yeah yeah yeah doesn't help
much on picking the day yeah uh I don't
think I don't know I don't know if
they'll ever put out like a clear
information on which day would be best
to choose uh for your OSI like I don't
think they'll go into that much detail
[Music]
I'll ask again though cuz I'm sure you
guys want to know which is like the the
Wawa heavy day or so um but Wawa will be
inv both so
[Music]
H can you tell us what song you're going
to be singing at the
concert oh yeah totally I'm going to
sing four blood
mhm my my my original song that I need
to perform again for
[Music]
blood exact predicted time
STS yeah yeah yeah yeah I will I will I
will I'll give you all the info I'll
give you every single piece of info that
I
can anyway uh sorry let me get back to
this
story
uh I still think he should know about it
that's a shame elv well do what you want
just don't expect it to matter
H I thought he was going to punch
me
hey ah he's here again okay I was I was
just checking good that you're down here
takes a while to get up to you when
you're in your room you find out
something about them Soldier Boys yet
sold
me oh c got
on um the NCR is Distributing supplies
in a building down by the ultra o
handing out supplies like food and stuff
that ain't nothing to get ruffled over
you find anything
else they refuse to serve locals ah that
would explain the goons they're here to
keep people like my friends away from
the food that ain't something I support
no sir no sir no no of course not sir I
agree sir you're so right
sir they said someone was sent to
discuss the issue with you wait a minute
wait a minute they said what they said
the man was oh completed optional
completed yay they said the mean was the
mean the man was severely beaten and
barely survived
[Music]
never
uh let's let's I don't know this one
that would explain why they're all wild
at us seems like we have a big
misunderstand what the hell
misunderstanding
Corner what
what what king we've got problems can't
move lay it on me what's going
on down the train station it's Pacer and
some strangers he spawn had issues
getting over here what is that fool
doing I need you to head out there and
try to Defuse The Situation tell them
I'm willing to cooperate
janky J Returns the king and head to the
train station in the Northwest free side
and try to negotiate with the an trans
station okay negotiation speech is the
one thing I'm very confident about head
on the atomic
Wrangler isn't that Charming the
jankiness come to mck and rals for all
your shopping needs a five check okay
okay if it can be bought it can be found
onto the train station is that it is
which which one's the train
station oh I hear shots
[Music]
gunfire is that because of my quest
hey bro hey
yo how's this
happening who what how
where scary are you good why the hell
are you here I got this under
control dead kid
ooh he's got some rounds o I'll take
them oh the the pistol I guess wait I
can take that too I
can I can
combine a mine's actually
already prepared but maybe you got uh
also one oh he's got a Magnum
revolver
interesting can I repair that
oh
yeah let's
go nice
thanks
y oh H hey uh please stop shooting for
me as I am making my entrance I'm
walking here hey I'm walking here please
don't shoot stop shooting please be nice
take down gun be friendly
is that is that is that is that is
that you looked a little bit shreky to
me or more like not shreky but uh
ory anyway hi Elizabeth what's up this
wasn't really a good time what did you
[Music]
want I thought I'd save everyone some
time and just kill you oh that sounds
fun
that sounds fun but no the kidy wants to
help with the relief effort like he
helped the envoy we
sent no
thanks that wasn't him he didn't even
know an Envoy was sent then he should
watch his back we know for a fact that
the envoy made it to their headquarters
still if the king's willing to deal with
us perhaps we can work something out
I'll tell my men to stand down H okay I
didn't even have to use my speech boy
ring return to the king let him know a
man I'm like running back and forth back
and
forth
okay at least I stopped shooting and he
can go
home to his
Priscilla Priscilla
Godzilla right Priscilla was the the
girl the
lady typical yeah I am a
courier right
forgot I can't complain about fetch
Quest at all for all your energy weapon
it's my
job
Indeed personal space meaning anything
to you lady I love when they say that
he's like hey I'm walking here that's
like the fifth time I said that today
I heard all about what happened maybe
it's time for a little more talking and
a little less fighting hell yeah you've
helped us plenty so I'll tell you what
just this once name whatever you want
and if I can make it happen it's done
don't rush it though toss it around in
your head a little you only get one
favor from the
[Music]
king the
favor what should we ask for oh we got
to level
up okay we have speech at six we have
science is 50 I think we wanted to go up
to 62 I don't know guns 50 lock pick
50 join them the dog get I can get the
dog
oh get some repair okay how
much 45 or so I don't know
well 35 and 5 55 okay
55 for something you guys are saying
that I don't know what it is
okay we can go
higher 50 at some point for
sure and then
what is this again this like the perks
right yeah
uh we have nerd rage you've been push
around long enough with the nerd rage
perk your strength is raised to 10 and
you gain plus 15 damage threshold
whenever your health drops to 20% or
below
wow
ner when the sun is down a n person
gains Plus two to both intelligence and
perception up to a maximum of 10 this
perk directly affects your internal
clock and remains active both this feels
like I'm playing a d andd game
man mysterious strangers
funny you've gain your own personal
Guardian Angel arm proof of fully loaded
44 Magnum with this perk the mysterious
stranger will appear occasionally in
Vats mode to land a hand with deadly
efficiency a
yo that is
fun so they'll not always show up and it
will be maybe a little bit more
motivation for me to use
Vats he one shots everything okay how
how often is
occasionally RNG one shot during that oh
will I see him
let's try
it depends on my luck you mean like my
actual skill points and luck
or are you saying my IRL
luck oh I got an
achievement the actual luck oh man
things have been a lot better since you
helped with those Soldier Boys soier
Boys in this what can I do for
you um where did you get the robot dog I
got Rex here from a salvager a few years
ago he was a little dinged up when I got
him but one of the followers fixed him
right up H do you mean that brain
situation is there something wrong with
him is there he doesn't see he doesn't
seem happy is that he's been acting
peculiar for some time now I took him to
the followers and had him checked out
and they said his brain is bad or
something
what is he going to be okay probably not
if I shoot him in his [\h__\h] brain like
I did before for now but they said
eventually he's going to get worse
you'll definitely see him around okay
cool can I help I don't know maybe if
you found a way to help my poor Rex here
I'd be much obliged your best bet will
be to talk to Julie farcus over at the
old Mormon Fort north of here maybe
you'll have better luck than I did can I
just adopt him
please oh nothing but a hat
dog about the oh
wait let's let's do the let's do the Rex
Quest first before I ask I don't know if
you can even do that now if you can even
receive Rex
already oh is it is this how I get
him
hey okay don't use the favor yet oh
okay good fine with
me we've got stuff we're not even
allowed to sell people only at Mick and
Ralph's save the favor okay you have to
talk to Julie
first in here
right uh you're be
Beatrix you're
Rando you right Julie fo is there
something you
need the king said you could tell me
more about his robotic dog Rex yeah it
breaks my heart every time I see him
he's such a good dog he such a good
dog can you not fix him no Rex's
condition is Way Beyond anything we can
handle he requires brain surgery and
some suff phisticated cybernetics work
too okay my goal for this game is is
leveling up to level 100 level 10 now
100 get my science and repair and
everything necessary skill level to over
9,000 or
so and then I will repair the
dog what do you mean I
can't no no don't ruin my
plan I'm trying to save the dog don't
stop
me I'm just joking anyway I know I can't
get that
far um so there's no chance he'll get
better I didn't say that while no one
here has that kind of expertise I do
know of one man who might fit the bill
there's an old scientist named Dr Henry
who reportedly specializes in this of
procedure he'd probably be your best bet
last I heard he was living up in
jacobstown far to the
Northwest thank you no
problem why did she not say
goodbye okay oh we're going hello back
to the king before we go to the
place I don't have a medical license I'm
trying to get one though for the dog
I watched this cute dumb dog video today
that almost made me cry and it's so
stupid because it's not such a big deal
it was just a a girl with her dog and
the dog wanted like a a duck
plushy from some
arcade and then it's a like a
compilation of her trying all kinds of
games to get like hundreds of tickets
thousands actually to get the pl plusy
and then they got the plushy and the dog
was so happy and excited and he was like
snuggling and sucking on the
duck and it was just so cute and they
had this emotional music
there yeah oh yeah seagull it was a
seagull you saw it
too and I was like damn dogs are really
so precious
man they are things have been a lot
better since you help with those Soldier
Boys thanks again soier boys what can I
do for
you um she said what she can fix it why
didn't she just say so when I was there
actually come to think of it I was
pretty angry when I went down there I
vaguely recall something about upending
a few tables maybe knocking out one of
our doctors anyway that's incredible
news only thing is there's too much
going on around here for me to make a
trip like that and I need all of my guys
just to keep things settled here you
seem to be awfully interested in my boy
Rex here and you've done some good work
for me already I'll tell you what you
promised to get Rexy here to that doctor
and I'll lend him to you what do you say
oo absolutely I can't thank you enough
now there's a few things you should know
about old rats here if you're going to
be traveling together first he hates
rats can't stand the things giant rats
mole rats doesn't matter he catches a
whiff of one and he's off like a shot
after him he's normally pretty obedient
but you might have to chase him some if
he goes after one of the little second
he doesn't like hats the people wearing
them don't ask I have no idea why maybe
because it rhymes with rats be an issue
other than the occasional bad spot when
his brain starts hurting him that is but
I'm hoping you'll see I wish you both
luck take care of my Rex now you hear
Rex this is your new master protect her
as you would me recently oh we're
already together
sheesh recently I haven't been wearing
my hat so often and and this this uh I
can't I I guess I could take it off
[Music]
but wait you really don't like hats wa
if you actually wear a hat in the game
does he react to it where do I see again
what I'm like
wearing uh apparel right I'm wearing a
helmet but it looks like a hat in the
picture so if I wear this Ranger hat
will the dog attack
me no so maybe he's
fine maybe he's
fine try and talk to him the
dog
oh what is it the Hat
how you
feeling let's talk yeah dog let's talk
about your
tactics what the [\h__\h] are you talking
about I'm not a
human enough about
tactics uh
I want to get a closer look at
you
oh oh the painting of The Bull on Rex's
side brain the brain case can I look at
the brain case Rex and no he that was
fast what why did it go away so fast
mechanical
Parts I canot read that so
fast what the
hell why is it automatic when nothing
else is automatic huh oh
well he was a legion
dog
what well sound like he had a choice he
was just being a good boy so I'm not
going to be mad or anything I'm not
going to blame him he's just a dog hey
but
interesting interesting
knowledge you mean the text is going
away so fast cuz I'm wearing a hat it
can be bought it can be founded make it
doesn't want to reveal too much to me
huh Stacy are you Stacy why is Stacy
fleeing again is this a bug that it
shows me on the top left like Stacy is
fleeing sick
boy good day Stacey is a
kid not
so not Giga Stacy mini
Stacy
hello where are we going I'm just going
to follow the arrow
oh Outdoors
right oh maybe
not wait let me
reach uh take rexs to Dr Henry in
Jacob's town
Jacob's
town I don't think I've been there
before wow it's really far
okay we're going on a little Adventure
so it's like it's that direction but
it's like around New Vegas behind it
okay Adventure
Time yay Everybody follow me to Jacob's
town
[Music]
just follow the
highway okay laugh a
highway I want to ride it all night
[Music]
long you're going my way then that means
you're going to Jacob's
[Music]
town but it's like it it's
going I'm
I'm guess let's go all the way over
there and then walk uh that way turn
that
way be wear the WASP with the orange
wings uh
okay
okay okay maybe if we're talk walking so
long we can also talk a while uh wait do
I walk through
oh I see our sharecropper Farms mhm all
it how do I get into that direction it
all looks
blocked it looks so blocked
off is that a new outfit no I just have
some pictures some pngs on
me go around H okay so yeah were you
guys surprised surprised about the tour
thing cuz
like I feel like the okay the concert
announcement it was pretty obvious um
that that was going to be well maybe not
that obvious H that was obvious
is especially the more time passed in
that announcement stream but then Ena
Ena is part of the tour which is I think
why she was then announcing it but I
feel like with her calm
personality it the way she said
it the way it was announced it was
announced like it wasn't a big deal like
it was so
like written off so fast like she just
said like two sentences really quietly
you could have almost missed the whole
announcement of the fact that there's a
world tour
happening I felt like he wait did you
just say it
oh what that was so lowkey it was so
lowkey
[Laughter]
right I love that auki is part of it
yeah you
know that hurts
that was so
unexpected
wait
y I don't even have s packs yep I see
that
[Music]
hey I need a
doctor
help oh I can use the doctor's
back
okay man that's s
you guys told me to look out for w but
you didn't tell me to look out for
[\h__\h] landmines
[Music]
again oh
man yeah let me
eat and drink and wait for my health to
go back up I could die any moment
now shoot the mines oh I guess I can
shoot them from
afar Bo yeah anyway besides lowkey
announcement from Ena I'm super hyped
I'm super excited it's so so so
so such an honor to be part of this tour
and there will be more details about it
but uh for
now uh I want to say just wait until
there's more details before booking
anything
[Music]
okay very soon in a few days they'll be
you know giving you guys some more
details if you're
interested we don't even have dates yet
exactly but I think for the don't we
have a don't do you guys not have a date
already for the first one
[Music]
do you I don't know I don't want to like
say anything that you shouldn't
know yeah yeah yeah yeah the the first
one you know right
uh-huh
yeah
okay so that's what I mean with don't
book anything yet you don't
know enough you don't have you're
lacking critical
[Music]
information
okay I think I set off every single mine
so it's maybe safe to walk here
now who it sounded like there's a
somebody's like dropping a bomb on
me I agree Rex thank you this is
terrible who made this who put all these
mines down here
huh really [\h__\h]
rude I'm a nice person I don't deserve
this kind of
treatment goodbye
Vegas I'm going to Jacobson
town you can spot m
minds of V
auh we're walking
in we're walking here maybe I should be
looking down instead of up what I'm I'm
I'm looking down I'm looking
everywhere I'm trying to
perceive
everything why do I is this a sound bug
I hear a lot of people
talking like I'm inside a hall heo
Oho oh the fiends what we're fiends
again didn't you guys tell me ah it's ah
oh wait fire isn't such a big deal right
where's my
weapon how do you use Vats
again is Veronica dead where is she
uh W shees who that's killed that
guy quickly wait that's ironica right
let's be
careful
it Critical Strike on cook cook
you're on fire Veronica and you're so
chill about it do you have Phoenix
jeans
h b caps his head I don't want his
head oh he's got a bounty on
him that's why there's a mini boss
that's why he has his head in his
inventory a metal
armor I think what I'm we weing
is oh yeah didn't we say like now we're
going to keep leather armor we're not
going to wear metal metal armor but
that's okay we're going to take it
anyway
um oh I ripped it
off you want to eat that you can if you
want you get more money for an intact
head o yummy
[Music]
H recipes cook Cooks fend
Ste
interesting a recipe he y oh oh they're
cooking human flesh dog meat ew
no I mean even in an apocalypse kind of
setting that's maybe where you should
reconsider all of your your
preferences but as long as there's
Brahman meat I'm going to continue
eating Brahman meat thank
you I think I'm
fine okay
okay should we stay here I need to go
this
way I think I think that was all that
was interesting oh I'm frozen
oh
okay w x could give Veronica does
she not have any on let me
see ooh got something good for me no
she's wearing is a dress metal armor I
guess we gave it to
her yeah she's good we can repair
her metal
armor
possibly uh
and give it back to
her you're making me carry the heavy
stuff aren't
you no actually I'm not I mean I'm
making you carry the heavy armor but I'm
I have yet to put a [\h__\h] ton of stuff on
you unlike the other companion that I
had anyway this will be oh enemies this
this will be the first time mhm oh uh
[Music]
fiends this will be the first time that
advent will be involved in a concert too
uh and and and
and will be bigger will'll be more
people I'm I'm excited for
that bigger whole life English
more members more
fun I'm not doing so well here
oh what do I do what do I do what do I
do wake up wa a they they they come back
to life on their own
right after a while oh I already hear
him oh okay you're
good man
panic it'll be fine
okay the micro Fusion cell was for the
laser gun
right I don't want to pick up
everything there too much to
carry but I I I don't know if it's a
good weapon is it a good weapon the
plasma thing that I just picked up too
laser
rifle good weapon but you need energy
weapon
skill oh wait wait can I open this no
one's
around
oh I just took it I don't know what it
really was
though but yeah I'm sure anyway that the
girls from Advent are super excited and
hyped I still
remember like when it was time for
myth's first
appearances that was after what after
doing so many watch alongs after
watching my Senai
time and time again and having the thing
is like we could have already been doing
stuff right but Corona was kind of
holding us back and that
felt you know regretful but there was
nothing we could do about it ooh there
they are oh
oh
woo
so eh I'm
excited that they feel that kind of
excitement now
oh am I
dead
fun are they that strong poison
damage I found no doubt
indeed you did warn me
yeah what I do should I try to avoid
them cuz
that's that's kind of rough
man just going back well it's that
[Music]
way
M uh swap
guns how does this work again
oh which one's good is this good I don't
know road down
below shall we walk around
it I pressed M to try to see the map I
wish that was an act ual shortcut man oh
oh you want me to take this road I have
to walk so far around it but
okay I'm happy you guys have your own
conert again
yay yay the logo looks really
cool I am excited for you guys to see
the actual key Visual and everything
and they showed uh did they show no did
they no they didn't show any merchandise
yet did
they I'm not sure if what I remember if
it's just what I saw you know personally
or if you guys also saw the same
things ah they did they showed the
essentials
pack there's a little bike cute can I
take it to go a little bit faster
no Essentials so light light stick and
shirts oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah so
the light stick actually doesn't have
the logo of
the um concert the Ian concert it has
the logo of the World Tour which is
interesting so they decided to kind of
put those two things together in a way
and therefore the the light stick is
like kind of shared merchandise so to
say is that a eupo the
[\h__\h] is shared merchandise between uh
the two events
yeah
mhm but that will be I think the only
shared merchandise thing minor red
poison yay did I have something to fix
that I don't
remember but it's just minor oh it is
kind of a eupo playground huh
cute R away R away the one that R
away red
x r red away I don't I don't have I'm
blind
good y
[Music]
oh yeah and I think another thing that I
can't over here uhoh another thing that
I think I can say
h is that the tour the members you see
on the key
visual that is
the set me Members like we'll be at
every location of the
tour I think I saw some people curious
about that so the more you
know yeah it's kind of like Vivid Cruise
Vivid Viv ID Ah that's my friend is it
is is
it oh what what what's this hello don't
crash on me
now
bro it kind of crashed I think oh there
we go okay oh that took a
while that took a while but yeah
remember guys when ID was like touring
around it was like uh who was it way
Kobo MAA
whu they had that super cute key Visual
and and they were in several locations
in
Sea it's kind of like that I would
say very
comparable what's this can I have pick
Barrel
Cactus where is it where is it oh
kind of
far oh good job guys if it's just one I
guess we're mostly
fine not the yeah yeah okay okay I'm
looking for the road is
it the one time that I'm trying to
follow the quest marker properly you
guys are like w
waah don't go
there and I'm not really sure can I
[Music]
just no what's that up there I'm curious
there's a little house or
[Music]
something
interesting oh yeah that will be merch
just
wait there will be merch
o ah the [\h__\h] Legions the legion
[\h__\h] the kaisar has marked you for
death and the legion obeys ready
yourself for battle
yay die Legion
[Music]
Cluckers go [\h__\h] yourself Legion
Cluckers
yeah die sick Hammer though is that your
tour cosplay oh my God I'm going to die
I'm going to die I'm going to
die I only have one HP what happened I
was too close to
everything uh wait I have a super stim
pack but I don't want to I don't want to
let me let me run around and [\h__\h] around
and and find out
where are I where are my do I have like
a a better weapon to stay further
away a
rifle the rifles are the submachine guns
right are they I don't know no the
hunting rifle for
example hunting rifle
maybe what do you mean I'm not hitting
him ah there is no
[Music]
way oh it's probably the fat armor again
uhoh don't don't you die now don't you
die I
mean well good job girl she's so [\h__\h]
strong where's my lucky guy I need my
lucky guy
good job teamwork so
strong is there anybody still still
alive Wally hello speaking of alive
people uh ooh
value
sheesh Ollie what's
up Ollie what's you been up to huh what
you've been up
to OE did you see did you see my new
outfit announcement you saw it I know
you saw it
[Music]
he
tomorrow tomorrow I'm revealing my new
outfit please everybody check it out I
hope you will be there if you awake
please please show
up I would be very delighted
antivenom oh would be good to carry
those around for those wasps I suppose
super Sledge
okay I got that super
Sledge super sled oh I'm heavy now no
come here Veronica it's
time I need you to carry some please
looking forward to the new
outfit thank you ollie had a dream about
K what she did
she
did you're making me carry the heavy
stuff aren't you did she say
so here you can have some
food cuz it seems like you have eaten
the other food that I gave you you can
have that
too uh where's the heavy stuff M here
you can use this grenade have fun with
it if you want you can have
M she doesn't need any proper weapons
though I suppose cuz she uses her
fists she's not going to wear the legion
armor if I give it to her
[Music]
right she dreamed of brushing your teeth
no
way no way no she didn't that would be
too weird of a coincidence last laser
and plasma rifles should I give that
those to her wait does she actually use
it you want me to give it it to her so
she uses
it she can't carry faction armor oh okay
interesting she uses the super oh
really I wouldn't mind her using it shut
the
mother yeah let's combine some things
uhuh already better already looking
better maintain there we
go perfect yeah we're fine we're
fine do you guys think they were looking
for me in particular when walking out
here declaring me so
randomly their biggest new enemy I feel
so honored I'm
so
flattered yeah they were oh
exciting I'm so important I'm such a VIP
the people are talking about me and they
fear me as they should
they have a ton of soldiers to
spare where do they get all these idiots
from where are they
from Nevada Arizona wrong
way no not really
I think it will go around the
corner oh right
way one
guide don't worry I was fairly confident
in my path
choosing it's so empty
here
a a thank you Studio r
I keep on crashing
today thank you Studio Rob M yeah that
song is so so so beautiful when I was
practicing it uh it's not the first time
that I felt emotional about it when I
first heard it I felt emotional about it
and when I was practicing it again I was
like when I when I think too much about
what I'm singing and look at the
video it gets me like
I can't think too deeply about it it's
it's a beautiful song
[Music]
man
banana thank you for singing it thank
you for
listening I feel like that k i i i could
have done a lot better I was doing
better during practice man but um it was
still fun it was mostly about showing
off
the the 3D the upgrade oh yeah let me
talk about that I guess
so H oh my God first of all that created
so many good screenshots that are
perfect reaction images now for you
guys oh the thumbs up and stuff like
that and the the oh the shook the shook
images are so
good the a yo
images we got some good
stuff out of that I didn't expect it
to be such great
material I really like
it yeah and
so uh I've been talking a lot with GAA
here and there and
so
um
oh I wasn't surprised
that
she uh was also very interested in what
I was up to
there I think um you know cuz am
actually she has the same kind of face
upgrade basically facial
expressions uh but she can use it in the
in the Holo app as I've told
you so I mean it's not something
completely new you know
I think I
think suicide Senpai might have it as
well for the sake of her concerts but
I'm not sure I think she
does but it's not completely new but
with me doing that whole stream on it
because am kind of has been using it
lowkey without making a whole reveal out
of it I I haven't been making a big deal
out of it either to be honest cuzz it
was more of a prise for you guys
y sick and
Rex but but I think uh I did get some
other members attention through it and
especially now of like pictures and
videos going around I think more and
more members might be interested in
doing that too getting that kind of 3D
upgrade for their expressions and all
that I mean they can't use it in the
Holo app unless they use a 1 million
wish for it but I don't really see a
need
for using it in the H app so far I'm I'm
come back
Rex so far I think I'm fine with
just using it in that external
application but yeah maybe you'll see ah
Rex [\h__\h]
died to those [\h__\h]
no a go away go away go away and Rex
maybe he'll come back in a moment maybe
he'll get up and come back no he died
again did he get up and die
again do we have to rescue him or will
he spawn next to me if I distance
myself rex that is not a rat yeah oh he
got up and died
again
uh this my strongest
weapon I know we do something else what
is
this he'll teleport
okay yeah anyway I was saying I think
you will see more
people picking up on
that I'm still going to try to
improve it oh what what oh okay just you
guys my armor condition is dangerously
low what really
can I repair
it like for example the eyebrows I know
you guys want to see the eyebrows I want
to see them too once I get the eyebrows
to work they the thing is like this is
also you guys actually should be used to
it a little bit by now because of my
music
videos when kanu does my music
videos my eyebrows are also not visible
in those it's like it's kind of a matter
of like even though it's the same model
data or whatever depending on what
program it's being
opened uh certain things are like not
visible I guess and getting them to be
visible uh in this case wasn't that easy
uh
apparently but I think we can make it
work and when Rex come
back when we can make it work then my
face will even more expressive where is
Veronica oh there she
is ah Rex you're finally back oh my God
you crazy
dog do you want some
food I don't know if you can like eat
and stuff to help yourself but
I
don't what do I give you I don't have
that much good food that's why I've been
trying to pick up some more
things here take
this cactus fruit good boy good boy
who's a good boy is this place dangerous
guys there's some weird looking things
over there
safe okay friendly really oh there's
Orcs you think Marcus could get us some
Min guns or missile
launchers what you really used to you do
act like
Orcs seemingly welcome to Jacob's Town
human wait you talk so normally fre to
walk around just don't stare at the
nightkin they don't like people looking
at them why do you talk so normally it
to yourself they're not popular around
here I'm not or am I not
officially docks inside the
lodge okay
uh what's wrong with the nightkin
nightkin suffers schizophrenia from the
Stealth Boys they're always using one of
the reasons I settled Jacob's town was
so they could be cured while they're in
town the nkin aren't allowed to have
stealth boys so their craziness doesn't
get worse trouble is the nightkin don't
like being visible either they don't
take being exposed too well
understandable marus is
goat go meet Lily who is she are there
any Town rules I need to know about same
as any civilized Town don't start any
fights or steal anything mhm we'll treat
you fair not a lot to ask okay sounds
fine sounds nice sounds reasonable I had
some questions about Jacob's Town such
as
uh what does the town support itself how
does it support itself big horners good
eating and we can trade the hides mm got
a lot of Wild Ones around here so it's
easy to restock the
herd and what about you who are you part
of a super mutant Army ran a town walked
the Wasteland with a tribal fre years Li
SP thank you so much you're the best
free
more
well depends on how things go if things
continue going well then then we could
work I hope that things will continue
going
[Music]
well you were a mayor town was broken
Hills bunch of super mutants humans and
ghouls all living together
peacefully well most of the time you
guys all know
[Music]
him long story so here's the short
version the master created the super
mutants and nightkin mhm the master
thought he could unify everyone no more
differences no more war didn't end
well we were looking for a GE to save
the village of a Royo eventually we did
nuked an oil rig in the process we went
separate ways after that I went East
into the Rockies looking for other M
understand what he's talking about is
this normal I got a feeling it turned
out all right in the end I mean not just
because I guess his references but also
all
right just I think it's generally the
the dialogues in this
game often
don't don't I can't comprehend them lot
of bad blood between Super Mutant and
humans goes back years some here still
got the scars in memories me I don't
really have a problem with the NCR set
their sights a little too high sometimes
but keep crashing
Legion that's another
story what do you know about the legion
besides that they're like the stupidest
Cluckers you could imagine kaisar thinks
he can change human nature most of the
Legion is following kaisar oh my God
stoping every two seconds when he's gone
it'll crumble might not happen overnight
might take a few decades but it'll
happen basic human nature greed ambition
start the app there we
go uh please stay like this now W and
with stay I don't mean crash
[Music]
tell me more them grow from a single
Town Shady Sands into the Republic
they've done good for the most finally a
keyword I
understand they expand fast if you got
land they want they'll take it
eventually H did it out West they'll do
it here they keep rolling over people
they'll regret it that's how revolutions
start mhm makes sense not really heard
of of Paradise in the Wasteland never
been there myself doubt they'd let a
mutant in amazes me people would come
from all over the waste to throw away
everything they've got in that
town
all see well they seem
nice oh and they got they got Snowy
Mountains here and that's a cool
building who
that is a nice place they've made
themselves a home
at uh
comfortable perfect for a vacation yeah
like a nice ski vacation this looks like
it could have been like a a skiing
Resort back in the day or do you think
they built this from scratch after
[Music]
everything like was destroyed it is a
skill
ah I've got an eye for it another human
one was enough is this a nightkin the
the blue ones are the night
kins so but are night kins just the
mutants but the mutants don't take the
drugs or I don't
understand the invisible
drugs yeah wooden building surviving so
well is impressive I guess they just
didn't really drop any bombs
here cuz everybody loves
skiing um the St for Makes You Blue
mm so many staring eyes sorry I'm not
trying to
look oh don't look at
me oh there's no
balls all right it's okay I kind of
changed my mind about wanting to play
anyway so many St eyes I can feel it
oh oh I can take
this snow glob mountain Charleston isn't
this one of those yeah yeah yeah yeah
like
Collectibles
nice where are we going what are we
looking for in here some doctor
right pre-war
book sensor modu
the book is
interesting oh did I take it
oopsie guess I did Dirty PR Park out for
the
Hydra ooh let me take that uh I know
it's a drug and I'm I was trying not to
take drugs but with how little s impacts
I
have and how little I keep on
finding I don't know oh that looks right
doctor I found you I assume this is
about something important you're
interrupting my
research more like a medkit it's good
yeah yeah I I I read it restores the
limbs and I might need that I need more
of this kind of
stuff and something's wrong with my
cyber dog I was told to come come to you
it's neural degradation biomed gel can
only preserve a living brain for so long
so you'll need to find a replacement I
haven't left Jacob's town in years but
there was one woman nice here and sucks
outside I remember her living with a
pack of hounds aside from her I know
that the fiends and Caesar's Legion
fight alongside dogs there could be
viable specimens among them if you can
get to them
uh-oh well I'm not friendly with them so
I could have
been maybe that would have been
helpful oh that's a lot let me read that
separately I'm surprised to find another
human here I prefer the Solitude and
having a bunch of super mutants around
tends to keep things safe and quiet
H yeah I guess they protect you quite
well those meat
Shields yes specializing in Neuroscience
both human and canine of course this lab
is nothing compared to what I had when I
was with the The Enclave The Enclave
what was that again yes but the
leadership and I didn't see eye to eye
so I left it was the right decision
since the enclaves oil rig was destroyed
not long after the
government wasn't there an enclave in
Diablo somehow the word sounds so
familiar from
there ah
different brains have different bonuses
for the dog
interesting the dudes whose head they
took it ah he were Ah that's that was
the government that's why it looked so
like proper so there is like a place out
there even in this apocalypse world I I
that is something I didn't think about
while watching the show because it was
like like only a small part of it
showing that place and I wasn't sure
like what it was and who the guy was and
all that that that place is so proper
and
like like well preserved and all
that you killed the president in Fallout
ooh
[Music]
oo do like most other factions are
evil the IRS
they were sitting on a big Oil ring oh
you guys are giving me so much info but
it's
like cyber doogs and the like it's not a
field I work in much
anymore so interesting you're like that
guy
that uh in Fallout lost his head and
that was a good guy cuz he wanted to use
is knowledge for the right people for
the right
purposes hello Dogg what wait I didn't
notice the first time I looked at you
nightstalker is that just this dog's
name or is it like this kind of
species the tail also looks
funny what is this combination
Cobra a cobra head show we also get our
dog or something like that
huh no I want him to look like a normal
dog
ideally search for an exceptional canine
brain among the fiends or the Caesar's
Legion or acquire a new brain for Rex
from one of old ladyes Gibson
dogs
and which one should we do what do you
recommend
Gibson is the quickest Gibson Gibson
Gibson
okay uh it's the non-optional one so is
my quest marker going to
be I don't know is this lady Gibson
because you guys say it's the quickest
it seems to be the
closest Gibson is by
Novak ah this one
ah
okay H I can't fast travel from in here
okay what about
here
oopsie
nice
nice that we have this little shortcut
you have a brain for me so you're back
now where
did actually let me first see if I can
sell you something I
know this
pipe this this for
sure anything else in here that I don't
need guys let me
know and the legion armor go bye-bye
casual wear Rider armor Ranger hat right
I don't need a hat I think
the 10 mm pistol you don't think I need
it we need stim packs oh yeah we we need
to buy stim packs please tell me you
have stim
packs
oh wait only one only
one
man um
[Music]
yeah for a lot of money
too yeah one stim pack for
[Music]
fine you have 100 St packs and you just
got into Vegas
what
how you really think I should sell this
sell all the energy
[Music]
stuff loot Goblin
yeah only Medics carry lots of stim
packs is that a are you roasting
them don't
sell submachine gun is
better I think it's good to have at
least for now the variety
I just
go another satisfied
customer okay uh oh actually can you
repair my let me have a look my
armor yeah how much
1,300
caps m
no
no maybe we'll just kill someone and
hopefully find leather
armor they charge you double for repairs
wow don't repair here is there a better
place visit move
Outpost okay Dr Henry now there's a name
I haven't heard in years hard to believe
he's still alive
as for your request it's bullish if you
ask me but Ray is pretty old and I'll
probably have to put him down soon
enough oh as for the price for this
favor 700 caps sounds about right raised
like family well for bra other dogs to
take care of this is America prices
After All America healthc
care ooh if only I had more barter then
I could get it for free maybe
no okay here you go I guess this is
realistic I mean it's a [\h__\h]
brain for a super dog something for
you that's so sad what she just
killed she killed the dog and ripped out
his
brain
damn that's
crazy you guys are all crazy
crazy one dog sacrificed for
another American
Healthcare wait let me I guess check
where's this Moab Outpost
again
oh oh isn't this this the place where we
started at oh no ah no it's this place
ah
yeah is the dead body still here
no repair in the bar or what I don't
know where to repair guys is it here Al
is there
[Music]
food inside the main building ah damn
it
okay by the way guys did I tell
you I think I told you after the first
episode episode after the first
stream that one of my friends one of my
closest friends has been was watching
the first stream and I thought that
would be it but then my other stream
coincidentally I
smartly uh scheduled it without knowing
on an Austrian holiday so my friend was
able to watch that one
too yeah I've been I'm surprised because
that's the friend that normally doesn't
really watch anything that I do in that
regard
anything there's a chance we are being
observed right now too
hello W friend big big Fallout fan h
H been doing a lot of good work out
there can you help me oh all right then
sign here here and here what am I
signing off my
life oh wait how much was it that
happened too fast I thought I would have
to confirm or
so but I I'm left with 250 I spent
700 on the dog brain [\h__\h]
it was
more I got [\h__\h] over I thought I I
thought I would have to at least confirm
something nah not cool this is before
right if I load
this right before I
think yeah okay
1,800 he charged me
1,800
nah that is Virtual
[Music]
Insanity oh my God now I'll just kill
some people and get their lever armor
I'll I'll I I'll find some stuff my
armor will be fine like for one or two
more fights right I
hope yeah or I'll buy armor from vendors
is there any shop in Jacob's town as
well
oh no h oh well I oh my God today the
app is so
[Music]
broken it's one of those
days K tomato now restarting
so
annoying the app is crashing more than
this game yeah oh I crashed again in
exchange for the game not
crashing I don't know I I I wouldn't
mind the game crashing instead of the
app or actually maybe I would depends on
how often anyway I brought the
brains oh God you look so terrifying
[\h__\h] again you interrupt me why scy per
what the [\h__\h] don't be so
mean very well show me what you brought
so that I can analyze its potential she
sells stim packs okay I got to buy
some all right let's see here your old
Pathways look good definitely a breed of
guard dog mhm if I transplant this brain
into Rex he'll be a bit more ferocious
in his attacks okay that sounds good
have a seat does sound
negative okay I did it Rex has gained
the faithful protector perk increasing
his attack damage oh that's good a we
fixed
him I'm so proud of us can I sleep here
by the way yeah
thanks and sell me those stim bags
please you guys said she sell something
wait May most of the time I'm Dr Henry's
research assistant we're looking into
ways to cure the uh I'm also handy with
tools and once in a while I Venture down
into the valley to trade the big Horner
hides and meet for supplies please shave
your gun before you shoot someone by
mistake I am honestly surprised that I
didn't do that yet until
now I I I'm constantly worried that I'm
I'm going to do that wait for a second
before you buy them
okay oh she can also repair how much
come
much also quite
expensive no thank
you all right I need caps to progress oh
yeah somebody said like 2,000
right well if I sell some stuff how many
stimpacks does she have 21
I guess I'm selling my
pistol
and well we can always come back and buy
more good trade just one
more okay uh I can get one more I
think what I'm
confused
okay still got money I can
get
two
yeah oh there's a cheat
I'm glad you're getting a real fall
bartering experience most people playing
this game completely breaks the economy
within hours what why what how through
bartering or what how do they do it
teach me your ways Fallout
Geniuses Guns Plus
10 give me a shout if you need
[Music]
I can get a lot of money for gambling is
it easy well now I kind of want to do it
too stealing gambling and
murder oh that's so cruel that's so
aggressive I mean this whole game is
called New vas I think you're supposed
to gamble
bye am I not
right you'll be fine without we could
have gamble at least once
[Music]
though
once how can I go to the fake virtual
Las
Vegas and not go gambling and lose all
my money and go bankrupt H where are we
going wait what's my quest that I have
marked
I guess we're doing this we don't have
to go back to Elvis and talk to him I
guess
not free sides North Gate should be
good I can I want to show him the
dog ch ch chill I want to show him the
dog I'm sure he'll be happy seeing the
dog even if I'm I'm not going to accept
any new
Quest but I want to show
him yeah yeah the quest is done but I
still want to show
him
Miss look at your dog it's your dog we
not even allowed to I'll continue using
your dog if you okay with it thank you
I'm sure he'll be
happy does my dog by the way if you
changed his brain
though are your memories stored in your
brain wait
I'm yeah right your memories would be in
your brain don't question
it about the does he not really know who
he is anymore and remember the king
but dogs are nice to everybody
right
wait I'm I'm I'm thinking about the
memory thing right
now that's actually a really interesting
topic I want to watch some YouTube deep
Dives about memory storage in your brain
and
stuff do we know in which part of the
brain memories are
stored we probably do right because
maybe it does it have like probably when
when researching for Alzheimer and
stuff oh Hipp hippo campus a campus for
hippos personal space meaning anything
to you
guys oh they have this concept talked
about in Fallout 4 hey yo no
way yo memories that's
interesting memories are an interesting
thing brains are an interesting thing
humans are an interesting
thing a [\h__\h] I went the wrong way
again yeah hippos have a campus they
have free
education free education system for
hippos you could learn a thing or two
from the hippos
every [\h__\h]
time I wish that at least to leave I
could just jump out of freaking
window a you're sleepy this looks like a
bed that you can buy in Sims
for pretty much exactly like
that oh hello sorry don't mind
me found your
room wow Rexy you look all better boy
his new he's a good Rexy get a new brain
got a
new he sure did you're a man of your
word no doubt about it can't thank you
enough yeah if you want hold on to Rex
for a little while long I will I'm sure
he didn't know that he doesn't remember
you
anyway sadly M yeah okay bye that's all
I wanted to do all right just for the
sake of
completion M I'm sure he has still like
a lot of other quests that he could give
you but I don't want to do that
now out of favor oh should should I ask
for it no what can I ask
for what what what what can I ask for
anything
no save the favor okay all right I'll
see you later will he like is he like
capable of killing someone for me for
example maybe and I should save it for
later when there's a really
difficult situation or
so ah to complete another Quest without
killing anyone interesting yeah okay mhm
okay cool I'll keep it
then
so
yeah uh at the tops Casino we are going
to confront
Benny
finally
ah I don't know how I was able to be so
patient about that that's actually such
a big
thing it's about time
yeah bring out your knives
kfp we're going to threaten him in the
only
way that kfp
knows how to do
business enough uh you guys will in
trouble come
on what what we what weapon do I have
out you like
that are you Enemy No
old Ben wait old
[Music]
Ben is there a new Ben are you the
Benny let me just check out the
Bodies
N
N old Ben
Kenobi okay okay okay
Chad you look new to freeside so here's
a little advice friend don't go past the
Southgate greeter without talking to it
first
oh okay why would why those Bots are
programmed to vaporize anyone who enters
the fenced in area without authorization
from the greeter
she then I think I would would prefer
the nude bots on
Twitter the name's old Ben I've been
living in free side since the day I was
born what's your story I've done a bit
of everything around here Courier
butcher crier escort gun for hire some
of which I'm not proud of but I do my
best to help around town when needed
H I used to be career before I got shot
oh yeah he said career right
what the [\h__\h] is a crier after a while I
made enough money to get a passport into
Vegas back then you could get aov for
entry for a fraction of what it cost now
o inflation I got a job working as a
crier outside of the tops advertising
for the local talent performing at the
casino that didn't last long so you're
like just promoting the performance
outside I guess they call it crier
because you're like screaming loud
it should be a screamer or so a
shouter well being a swaave young guy I
chatted up the ladies don't cry right
one of the manager's girls started to
take a liking to me I never touched the
woman but the jealous prick decided it
was my time to go want your job by
saying stolen from the casino that you
cry all the time a was missing from the
casino vault only manly bastard stole
the funds and figured I was a convenient
Fall
Guy that's horrible yeah but what can
you do I was stripped of my Casino
apartment and all of my belongings and
booted back into freeside from there I
didn't have a lot of career options as
my rep was destroyed so the escort job
sort of fell into my lap no pun
intended what kind of escort well I
suppose you could look at it that way
but I was packing a whole different kind
of heat oh no escort just sounds better
than Manore packing some
heat tell me more y I was damn good at
my job too after a while I just felt
like a piece of meat and had to
quit you felt like a piece of
meat okay let's make a joke about that
um
uh uh can't think of anything help me
guys make a joke
me a piece of
chicken spare
rips don't think you guys can come up
with anything good either huh well how
about we butcher that meat H my father
ran a butcher shop here in town piece of
meat to butcher that's
started sell strange meat at half our
prices that sounds odd but no that
sounds actually perfectly ironic you're
telling me not long after my father's
shop went under and he passed away from
the loss people around town started
experiencing shakes no one get shakes
like that unless they're eating human
flesh but no one would believe me the
sick bastard gradually went insane and
passed away wasn't long before someone
moved into the guy's place and found
half buried human remains in the crawl
space I didn't bother saying Told You So
mhm exactly one of the reasons I got out
of that job too many Shifty characters
looking to have someone else move their
hot
items he speaks a lot about meat and hot
and heat and it's just all the same it's
all connected when I quit the escort job
I had enough money to buy a pistol belt
and some other gear bodyguards make a
good honest living and I had the wits
and physical build to handle most thugs
after saving a few tourists from trouble
I got a reputation for being a stand-up
guy again and after a decade managed to
save up enough to
retire good for you all
right thank you Oben kovi or whatever
you guys
said he's got a lot of stories to tell
so wait what these are these Bots are
going to vaporize
me hey he was lagging critical
information I don't want that to happen
to me which one do I have to talk to
this
one the middle one oh oh he's coming to
me submit to a credit check or present
your passport before proceeding to the
gate trespassers will be shut oh this
where I'm going to spend
2,000 ah
oh man what's what's scientific about
saying robot let me pass isn't that even
a
typo you don't spend it ah you just show
you have it ah okay good good good thank
you madam you may proceed ah well then
no
problem thanks
thanks I got to say though I feel bad
for the for this bro he didn't deserve
that
it didn't deserve to end like
what that's it keep moving wow wait it
looks like a normal World here forace
even more welcome to New Vegas Oh this
part is New
Vegas well there's automatic music
playing here that I can't
avoid wow what are you doing here this
place is amazing where they start point
me to the tops Victor I've got a score
to sell oh it's
Victor sorry ramler I know you're fixing
to serve up some Vengeance I'm going to
have to point you to the Lucky 38
gambling Mr House the head hono new
that's they check the money to make your
acquaintance they don't want you to go
in here if you don't have any money to
spend
extra that makes
sense oh The House Always Wins I
is there more to that all right I'll go
there straight off yeah partner that's
the spirit he'll be waiting for you
partner those last five shots were a bad
idea wait so is that marked
now
no should I do that
first oh number one a part one ah
should we do house
first okay oh 38 Lucky
38 so we should always bet on 38 right
we're happy partner good to see you
again boss is waiting for you upstairs
so get a move on
okay thank you Victor I see you brought
some friends sorry partner no but
they're going to have to stay outside
oh okay scary soon now are we going to
we're not going to fight right The Game
Wouldn't force me to go in without my
trusted companions what what if they're
all I have in terms of skill and
strength I'll be
fine wow
[Music]
damn it besides like Last
Vegas so to say is there any other
places in America in the Fallout
universe that are as like well
preserved like I don't know in New York
for example
tell
me not really not
many oh chat was kind of dead for a
moment Virginia city in
California Vegas is a special
case h I guess that's how much everybody
values gambling enjoy all the Vegas
Strip has to offer okay elevator do I go
up
I
can't where is this dude I got to talk
to I feel like I got to go over with the
elevator can you help me out here where
do partner
oh Penthouse I
guess pouse
floor okay
oh
oh no one else here besides robots
what oh you're Mr House this meeting has
been a long time coming hasn't it you've
come a long ways literally and I suspect
figuratively as well he was in a show I
have to ask I guess he was now that
you've reached your destination what do
you make of what you see he's a p tuber
[Music]
YouTuber I don't understand
yeah he seems familiar but I don't
remember anymore like what how he showed
up in the
show he runs
rco
oh the VTech
meeting you mean the one where the wife
was being spied
on oh my God wait that's
him a
[Music]
yo what the hell are you a crude
question crudely asked I'll be happy to
satisfy your rambunctious curiosity at a
more appropriate moment but now I'll
repeat my question what do you make of
what you've seen you mean in here or
overall I guess in here yeah in here I
think
so yeah what's not to love it's pretty
impressive I I I like how you kept it
all running was nice very different from
the Wasteland oh come now don't the fool
Vegas has fools enough a superfluity of
them they're what makes it so profitable
I mean it though they come to chasing
Penny anti dreams of high living to feel
like their big shots like their
winners you see that you and I I mean I
know the rest of the sentence was maybe
not to dream that we're important we
are I meant it do I think it's
nice why the VIP treatment I'm just a
CER oh don't be coy you've been playing
a high stakes game ever since Victor you
out of the ground don't be afraid to
admit
it okay let's get down to business then
the business is this one of my employees
has stolen an item of extraordinary
value from me and I want it
recovered simple enough easy what is it
though what do you propose my only
concern is the recovery of the Platinum
chip Platinum what happens to Benny I
leave to your discretion Platinum chip
when you bring the chip to me sounds
familiar I will pay you four times the
delivery bonus stipulated in your
contract four times let's go what a
deal
oh damn so many times I wish I had
barter damn well I accept wait wait
thousand wait actually maybe that's kind
of low
oh well enough return to me when you
have the Platinum chip in your
possession any final matters for us to
discuss yeah what did you wish to
know what is the Platinum chip it's a
very special item there's nothing else
like it in the entire world it was lost
a long time and difficult to find that's
all you need to know about it for this
stage of our Enterprise fulfill your
contract deliver the Chip And good
things will come your
way you sound like a bad person oh the
more I know about the tip the easier I
can find it yay speech Let's Go you
might keep an eye out for any computers
that Benny's been using maybe even a
computer lab of some
sort oh a computer
lab house is
neutral if you say so I must believe you
I
suppose good good points me Pats myself
on shoulder if the Chip's so valuable
why use a single Courier to transport it
you realize you were just one of many
couriers the rest of them dummies so to
speak add to that many thousands of caps
worth of mercenary protection to screen
your Avenue of approach had I used an
armed Caravan to transport the chip I
might as well have been announcing to
the world this is important attack this
I supp I didn't want to attract the
attention of groups like The Great K or
the Brotherhood of Steel alas the real
threat was closer to home make it seem
less important I guess okay why don't
you send your robots into the tops to
arrest Benny frontal assaults on casinos
not good for business in any case Benny
would see it coming and all he'd have to
do is hold the chip up and point a
pistol at it our formost advantage is
that Benny doesn't know that I know he
has the chip let's not squander
it he means like holding it up pointing
a pistol at it like like you do with
like a person when you're like don't
come any steps closer I will shoot this
person that you're looking for like a
hostage chip
holding one single chip at gunpoint V
Miss Senai will
cry it's a joke it's a potato chip
joke that's simply not true I am the
only person to hold any rights
pertaining to the chip I designed it and
I paid for it dearly to develop that
chip I spent a sum of US dollar not the
bottle caps that passes currency these
days but a sum Beyond counting okay nice
for decades I paid salvagers to comb the
ruins for it and when it was finally
discovered tens of thousands of caps
spent to have it brought here we know
how that turned out complete your
contract and it will be the last time I
pay for the chip save your questions for
them I really don't quite get it yet but
I guess I'm going to get that chip for
you what else
how do I get to Benny it won't be easy
Benny is always surrounded by at least
four bodyguards except when he's in his
private Suite on the 13th floor of the
tops mhm private Suite 13th
floor how could I catch him off guard
sneaking into Benny's Suite on the 13th
floor would be very difficult but not
impossible go sneaky there might be
guards certainly there'd be a sturdy
lock on his front door so I have to be
good at sneaking stealth and lockpicking
I suppose but I'm good at speech so
maybe I want to take a diplomatic
approach if you were to approach Benny
in public you might be able to leverage
his fear of exposure to make him agree
to meet with you in private interesting
how do where does he go in
public let's do it that way
what else did you want to
know tell me about Benny Benny has led
the chairman ever since I recruited his
tribe 7 years ago until his recent
misbehavior i' planned to make him my
Proteg maybe if i' begun grooming him
sooner none of this would have
happened you are a
groomer you're not going to get to groom
me buddy if anything I'm going to groom
you
why did Benny betray you I have to think
that he found out about the Platinum
chip and mistakenly convinced himself
that he could use it to his own ends one
of the problems of a tribal Workforce
I'm afraid no intuitive understanding of
how complex Technologies can
be you guys are so shook why you guys so
shook I want to be your groom not not
that kind of
Groom that's not what I was talking
about
[Music]
but kfb and waa are getting
married one day one
day one
day I ain't signing no PR up what what
wouldn't that be helping you I don't
know wouldn't that make you feel
more
safe with
me thank you for the raid thank
you woo yeah baby okay what use would
you have for Port why didn't you
intervene sooner when bny Benny ambushed
me sure Victor interven sooner you mean
good Springs is a bit too far away for
me to reliably control the securitron
agent by remote I can send and receive
packets of data at best Victor's combat
algorithms determine the proper course
of action Benny and his thugs were more
than a match for a lone securitron makes
sense when he alerted me I instructed
him to approach the site after Benny and
the others had
departed I'm kind of scared of of these
robots now especially after I saw how
they shot that one nice guy
down what else did you want to know
[Music]
nothing actually didn't I already ask
this ah I asked it in a rude
way I am Robert Edwin house president
CEO and sole proprietor of the New Vegas
strip uh-huh I oversaw the city's
Renovations starting from 227 for onward
the three families are my employees
before the Great War of 2077 I was the
founder president and CEO of robco
Industries a vast computer and Robotics
Corporation yeah robco made the the
thing I have the little pit boy that I
have on my arm now
yeah and Rob co wait Rob co wait let me
let me let me try to get my knowledge
back everever robco and
voltech were two separate companies but
they like started working together or
what yeah voltech wanted to make the
Vault and robco went into that
business
H they just collaborated in a
technical sense I
guess uh they made him uh a a deal to
make a vault
mhm off
collab house hates
vaults
what every terminal you use is made by
robco so this tell me tell me all the
cheat codes please you appear to be a
computer not a man don't let the video
screens and computer terminals fool you
I'm flesh and blood not silicone huh
prove it to me prove it to me show me
that
meat yeah you are probably just a brain
in a
jar that's that's maybe meat as well but
not very
manly you've stayed alive all this time
let let just say it was very
costly but I was willing to make the
sacrifices longevity entailed financial
and
otherwise he's made of silicone like
those dolls
what what for real cuz I saw other
people also mentioning
silicone did they like make a doll out
of
him no no no
okay how did you establish New Vegas we
can discuss this in Greater detail at
another time yeah suffice it to say that
when my securitrons detected NCR scouts
at Hoover Dam I took action I recruited
a tribal Force to supplement my
securitrons and renovated the strip just
in time to welcome the NCR as it marched
into the region instead of War a treaty
was negotiated and the money started to
pour
in smart
businessman what else did you want to
know nothing I'm going
to I'm going to go that was enough
talk
interesting can I move in here this the
real
question
oh
snowball I don't have a snowball
Jane I found the girl right away well
hello Sugar Sugar Mr house is waiting
for you in his office I already talked
to him who are you I'm Jane one of Mr
House's girls we keep him entertained
excuse me we don't get any guests lately
perhaps we can entertain you as well
what do you mean with that what how what
kind of entertainment you're going to
play some Game of Thrones for me on that
screen that is also
spicy uh ah oh those snow globes I I I
didn't you say snowballs I was thinking
of
snowballs wait there's no question about
what kind of entertainment I'm asking
the real
questions I don't
understand not many people know this but
Mr house is one of the world's biggest
collectors of antique collect weird you
to find any out in the way plan you can
bring them to me and I'll add them to
his collection 2000 reward of course in
fact one of Mr House's favorites went
missing when we moved the collection if
you have a look around the Lucky 38 you
might even find it oh really oh my my
ear hurts
oh
oh weird random pain in my
ear uh let me give you one or two I
that's just wonderful I'll take them and
put them with the rest of the collection
let's go 4,000 oh I'll keep an eye out
for more if I miss one guys you got to
like warn
me 4,000 sheesh we can buy more stim
packs wait will I have to show the
2,000 uh uh money bottle caps each time
I enter this
place or I guess I can maybe like
teleport into here at some point no one
time thing okay okay
[Music]
okay yeah I I'll I'll talk to you more
some other time dot dot dot
indeed indeed dot dot
dot just curious looking around Finance
clipboard okay I guess I'll go to Benny
let good I think to go to uh
congratulations the boss has instructed
me to come you to the High Roller sweet
what you can bring your friends too be
like a little clubhouse for the gang you
put together just bear in mind you're
the only one gets to see the boss any
friends you got they can wait in the
sweep enjoy the digs partner they're
plenty fancy
nice wait my my what presidential suite
you mean that's my place I roller Suite
I'm never going back to the motel
anymore hey which one all of this is it
connected
oh today's
physician I got a little PC for
gaming don't think I can use it though
oh bottle caps bottle cap bottle
cap bottle cap nice
bed no windows installed nothing
installed in
fact chest board paper weight oh nice if
I need this place I'll come
by oh oh
oh oh
nice two
bathtubs does this all belong to my
penthouse
suet a little bit of
food
cool okay thanks where to partner
um a little casin do you have
Blackjack goodbye no no not goodbye why
is nobody playing here
anyway not here I can't actually play
here this casino is shut down
okay what a waste of
space that is
unfortunate oh I can send all my even so
the ones that I don't use at the M for
you H it's from Ambassador Crocker very
important here you go Crocker
who
who I wish to speak with you immediately
in regards to important matters I I
trust you have learned enough in your
travels to know that the new California
Republic is an honorable Nation engaged
in a beneficient mission in the Mojave
in general and New Vegas in particular
it is in addition a wealthy nation that
well rewards persons who dedicate
themselves to its National National
interest whether for reasons patriotic
or material allow me to reassure is this
like uh please join us
yeah I mean I don't know can I just stay
neutral or would it be beneficial for me
to
[Music]
join rece receive you at your
being poached I I can't only for a while
you
can I have to pick a
faction will I eventually be forced to
do
it you can for a long time okay you'll
have to choose eventually okay
[Music]
M
okay
uhhuh
Benny where are you that's
crazy oh dear I thought nobody has ever
been inside that
Benny what sleep in this place
I
ping
[Music]
Benny my friends I mean to pick them up
they said it was a clown I ain't a
person they were standing there though
no been married I thought they would
follow
me why you just standing there it's time
to
go follow me a just when the standing
around was getting
exciting you
too follow
me ready to go come on stop barking
around you're not
M you're not sure later I'm sure you you
can't control yourself little
doggo we don't want all the attention on
us is that
Benny you're not Benny did you know the
strips all stirred up
lately I want to know where Benny is
during the day just like chilling
hanging out
[Music]
somewhere inside the
building and the the tops Casino well
yeah the arrow is there but is this is
this the way that I want to do
it want to confront him in
public hey hey baby doll welcome to the
tops hotel and casino sorry I can't see
to hand over any weapons you might be
carrying keep hold out weapons what are
hold out
weapons from my cold dead hands
[Music]
my silenced pistols
oh let's do the hold out thing smooth
and easy just the way I like it don't
worry they'll be as safe as kittens till
you're ready to leave oh and a friendly
word of advice if you happen to stumble
across any weapons during your stay here
well just don't wear them openly you dig
now that we got that little business out
of the way what can I do to make your
tops experience the
tops so like don't
carry them around like I usually do but
press
R okay where did you take my weapons so
I may you know pick them up and then
shoot you all in your heads relax baby
the safest houses we'll keep them locked
up in the bank upstairs right next to
the money it's serious
protection have a good time baby baby
stop calling me
baby hey there's there's the High Roller
oh ring a ding baby ring a ding
ding ring a
lingling isn't that one of n's songs or
so ring a linger ring a
lingling okay Blackjack here we go how's
it hanging I want to
play let you must purchase chips before
chips
do are you selling chips how's it
hanging
no where do I get chips maybe at the
reception hey
there's
upstairs hey there's the High
Roller blackj is like the only game I
can play here pretty much uh what was it
again like you got to get 12 not over 12
you don't want to get busted right
welcome to the tops how can I help you
give me 21 21 oh turn it around and give
me give me chips how many chips would
you
like
please 500 potato chips just normal
salted sea salt anything else I can help
you with thank you that's it byebye oh
wait I can exchange oh how many chips
would you want oh wait how much do I
have do I have
this do I have this here's your chips is
there anything else I can help you with
oh
perfect make sure to save I saved before
walking up here after the
conversation so okay goodbye thank you
and enjoy your stay at the
Topsy
there's
21 uh how how how does this work how
does this work and increase BET right
now I put one one chip
in one chip
is one one chip is how much
money hey there's the High
Roller One tip is one cap
okay maybe that's a lot maybe that's too
much for the first time maybe they'll
start a little bit lower to get into it
uh bet max deal okay I press deal
now I got two queens wait how much is a
[Music]
queen
stay 10 so I have 20
now oh that's that's uh wait so what
does splitting mean I don't I don't
remember a splitting option in other
blackjack
games face cards a 10
okay but doesn't he then give me If I
Stay doesn't he give me
another uh another card wait what's the
difference between
hitting and
staying oh staying is like okay I don't
want any more cards I I forgot that you
could do that it's been too long if I
say hit he's going to give me another
card and then what's doubling down
again stay I'm good
okay uh hit gets card stay is as is hit
give me one more card okay double down
is high RIS wait what you get another
card and your bet is
double double dou w bet and draw
one more card and stay also double your
bed okay risky
huh one more card for double chips uhuh
but then okay I might lose a lot of
money okay then let's
stay yay first one
okay let's increase my bet to
125 and
deal six and an oh that's
[Music]
16 it's a bit risky but I feel like the
opponent might get more it's
17 but is it aces 11 huh Matthew Perry
is that a voice actor or
so 17 17 I think I'll stay what do you
think
AC is one or
11 how do I know which
one I'd hit You'
hit
okay
ah wait that's 27 no
I'm already like
over what do you mean it's still 20 what
why is it still
17 ah in case I get over the 11 turns
into a one is that how it works whatever
is better for my situation is what it
will
become and the queen was a 10 unlike the
a which would be a
11 but then it turns into a one okay
okay okay uh-huh so now I have 17 still
ah I'll take another one then I
suppose ah oh it's another one though
it's another one so now we're at
[Music]
18 I guess I'm happy about that I'll
stay I'll stay I'll stay I lost it I
lost him
no I lost them okay no problem
no no uh decrease decrease let's do 80
deal 10 and oh oh instant
win they applauded so I won right that
happened too fast I got a a a king and
and an a ass that was black
de nice let's go camping let's do 100
deal five six is 11 hit me 10
[Music]
oh a to the
Y A to the Y twice in a row okay deal
seven or
17 hit
me
18 same situation
what do I do Stay
Stay Stay
Stay I break even so I lost nothing okay
cool cool cool that
works 14
hit 21 oh no way no way quick math oh my
God what is this normal what the [\h__\h]
I'm going to lose my luck soon I feel it
it's not going to be like this
forever
W
stay
[Music]
good
four what what what what
oh is my luck Strat helping me with this
it's it's it's not like maxed or
anything I don't
know oh my
God yo it was good that we put some luck
in
there
W five now I want to double
down when I thought when when you double
dble down I think I misunderstood I
thought when you double down you still
like it is that the only more one more
card that you get I thought you can get
more cards even after that
[\h__\h] you only get one card I thought you
can still get more damn it we got to
make our money
back uh 11
hit 19
stay yay o I played 10 hands of
blackjack so far I'm going to get my
money back jok Joker and king that's
stay I break even for real sace for
20 uh that's um
17 kind kind of want to hit it I kind of
want to hit it but we usually stay with
[Music]
17 I kind of want to do it I mean if the
game is actually considering my luck
stat
then might be it might
work dude has nine oh is that what he
has oh I didn't I didn't really register
that as what he has with the I'm only
playing with the
dealer I'm playing with the
dealer he got a he he only has a nine
what's the card underneath
[Music]
that shouldn't he have two
cards we don't know oh oh oh well yeah
okay makes sense we shouldn't know okay
I'll
stay I win
okay good good I almost did a bad thing
so uh that's
hit
15 one more hit um I I'll I'll try why
isn't she saving I can save now oh only
if I exit the this current Table
Right hit oh 19 H
okay
[Music]
yay no I'm not going to save
scum we already won like 500 chips I
think
nice
deal that is 19
we can
stay no give that back to me right
away you're stealing my chips that is 16
was
it 16 right now at
least 16 deal got an ace is that bad s
oh 17 yeah yeah it's 11
[Music]
oh oh I got black check right 17 plus
4 got my money back 17 always 17 17 is
such a hard decision to
make
stay yeah I he had
20 11
I was so close to doubling down I should
have doubled down I was about to do it
but I didn't want to regret it ah I was
so close oh
oh
stay this is fun this is just going to
be the rest of the whole
stream 11 m
I want a double too yeah oh
oh oh my
God I I I should not be like this this
could make
me think this could Gaslight me into
thinking I'm actually lucky but IRL
would not go down like this would
it IRL Blackjack would be a different
story I suppose I should not get cocky
because I'm lucky in this
game I'm not GLI no no no I'm I'm I'm
aware that this is not how it would go
he got uh o he got an
ace wait my chat died I have to refresh
you I have to refresh you
okay I hope one day we have maybe a
concert in Las Vegas after LA and New
York I want to go to Las Vegas please so
that we can go just
kidding just
kidding we wouldn't do that we only
gambling
games the sphere I damn the
sphere okay where are we at nine but he
has he has some good stuff but I should
at least I guess I could surrender
but I'll I'll
hit oh wait uh
11 well that's that's uh 19 20 20
okay what what the [\h__\h] what was the
what were those
cards he had two Aces and two queens oh
I think he busted
right what they what does that mean
[Music]
splitting he busted yeah he busted
this okay let let me let me let me exit
once
well I'll save scum once
oh what I get experience from
that oh w w w w whoa whoa whoa what
should we do what was what was I working
on I was working on repair this
50 I want to I feel like I want to get
barter up cuz they always ask for
barter or guns ah yeah I don't know guns
or speed
ber can I yeah I mean 25 I don't know if
25 will even help me at this point like
everybody asks for like 30 or so I
think you don't need bar when you get
money can get money from gambling good
point good
point uh
can
I put some into
medicine you guys said that at specific
stages it like really increases what
what were those
stages 25 50 okay then I think I'll go
up to 25 for
now and
[Music]
one more
gun
sick
safe we want to play a little bit more I
know you already Hate Me by now's the
High
Roller there's the W hey there's the
high roll let me let me play one more
one more one more we already got yeah
885 earned yeah that's
good want to learn po poker I feel like
in this environment I wouldn't be able
to learn it I need to like learn it IRL
first I think like not in a not in a
casino just like privately what I didn't
press
anything hey there's the High Roller H
increase B
[Music]
to 100
no
10 m
if we get an
ace
yo double down [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] my
luck it lied to
me uh
14 uh
[\h__\h] at least I didn't double down yep
my money my
money
10 double
down I think he busted right it's
happening too fast I think he busted
because of that he had so many cards on
the
[Music]
table
10 could double down
for hoping for an ace they they kind of
they owe me an
ace looking at how things went so far
they owe me an ace the game owes me an
ace okay this is fine
too almost almost an ace yeah let's go
we're over a thousand over th000 can we
get over
9,000 10 m
10 double Oh Black Jack
baby we like to see
it 17 17 I hate that number I hate
it I think I'll
stay that's fine we win some we lose
some but we mostly win some he y
y
seven
H
uh
eight
18 18 or
eight 19 or9
yeah I think I'll stand at this
point he'll give me the highest in that
case right okay good good good good
good whatever is better oh I'll
stay oh man this is too easy this too
easy this is my
destiny I'm just fulfilling my destiny
here guys
I am Destiny's
Child
11 double down [\h__\h] not good I Break
Even though
okay
eight hit
stay my break even fine
fine that's a good outcome eight hit 18
stay I
[Music]
win I was born for black check black
check is my life
man wait wait oh my God wait this is so
I'm I I feel ashamed a little bit
because just like an hour ago or so
someone in chat was saying they like how
I have not tried to destroy the economy
yet by gambling whatsoever
but the simple fact that you told me
about that was then kind of making me
feel like I want to now I'm sorry I feel
disappointed in
myself you planted the scene yeah you
didn't I'm sorry I'm sorry that now you
can't be proud of me
anymore just a little bit more
St
yeah 17 Again why does Blackjack like
this number so much oh you're busting
you totally busting bro never take so
many
cards
13 I think I should
double stay what with 13 no now at
13 you guys are just a little bit
delayed
huh don't
double okay let's
hit 18
stay yeah I thought so I had a feeling I
had this feeling that that was going to
happen
oh oh 9 + 11 right
20 stay
[Applause]
stay it's too easy ah almost over 2,000
winnings uh
[Music]
10 give me give me an ace or give me a
like a special card please I double down
and I regret it I regret
it it's never it's never there when I
double down I only win when I just hit
most of the
time yeah uh
[Music]
14 ah
nice okay we're working our way back
up oh oh oh I was looking at chat I'm
just winning
automatically keep gambling till 10K bet
Max what do you want me to bet
Max oh 200 is Max only okay well we can
do that that's fine
14 hit 18
stay
yay yay
2,000 H
dou double double double
hit
16 we could hit one more
time hit me baby one more
time oh
oh good stuff thank you Britney
Spears
12 it
16 again Hit Me Baby One More
Time okay then at least we didn't at
least we didn't bust what day I know win
oh god wow she I can buy all the stim
packs that I'm dreaming
of man we're never going to see
Benny tabletop game oo have fun I it's
you
again well I mean if
you I I've had these moments in
different games before it's it's not
very unlikely for me oh to get into
gambling let's just uh remember Yakuza
oh looks like you've hit a lucky stre
streak there you must be thirsty by now
drink the house and keep on playing he
has a problem with that oh I you you
don't know that I am straight edge I'm
not going to drink the Vodka that you're
giving
me he wants me to drink it so that I
don't play with a proper sound mind
anymore hit the slots okay I want to try
how does can I use this one
I don't think I'm I mean it's not really
something to be good at I guess
Noh is it like is it reliable that like
when you think oh like if you feel the
rhythm or
whatever is that a
thing it is of luck okay well we got
some luck
um spin to Wi
orange
no
why Sprint to win again I guess this is
just how it goes a few failures for a
big win no what the [\h__\h] but 75 is
really
low I win how is it a
win how is it a win
also I thought you stop it
yourself are aren't there SL [\h__\h]
machines where you stop it
yourself maybe not Cherry uh oh cherry
cherries are WIS o I'm just going to be
a typical slot machine user I'm just
going to
mindlessly spin scen scen without I
don't even have to know how this works I
guess
I'm luckier in blackjack though what the
hell
Cherry
okay that's just video game or digital
slot I guess yeah casinos wouldn't do
that because then you're trying to feel
the rhythm and and get it at the right
time you
know maybe you could even take like with
your phone oh a slow motion video
if the if the owners are so see you
doing that well then you're out so close
right I was hoping for
it I need us to go have more than we had
before
please come
on no the lemons life is giving me
lemons right now
what
what you've been good to us baby now let
us be good to you we'd like you to enjoy
this private Suite as long as you're in
town they just want to get rid of me no
where's the High
Roller I don't understand it seems kind
of
nice yo 7,000 F the
oranges that's where it's at we're
orange after all guys orange Revolution
let's [\h__\h] go Orange
woo
orange no I'm happy I saved don't worry
welcome to the tops how can I help you
try roulette
interesting enjoy your stay at the tops
I I I I want to try I don't remember I
think maybe once in life I played
roulette before maybe did I not
sure I dig this crazy is this roulette
this is roulette how does this work I
just put something my my my coin on
something that I think will win I
suppose so it's like pure Randomness
right yeah Rad or
black what are these
uh second H what is this
I avoided the roulette first 12 numbers
12 BS
oh roulette is not affected by look
thatat no way no way
what what the Benny is around
here well we're just flexing right now
before we were like ah Benny I don't
give a [\h__\h] about you I actually just
came here to make money and that I am
doing indeed
let's do
red I want to do red here 200 on
red I guess if you just do like a vague
one like red or black you don't get as
much back when you win right but if you
put it on the number and you get that
one then I suppose you get like a big
return okay Finish bet
it was black
bro
[Music]
bro is it really not affected by my luck
then I don't want to I don't want to
waste too much in here I I'll try one
more time on red give me give me my
money if I lose again then I'm out of
here
it isn't oh
[Music]
no this got to be red now though yeah it
is okay so I get that back I get the 200
back
now I don't I'm not confident enough
especially if it's not affected by my
ingame luck then I'm not confident
enough to put it on the number
yeah there's like two two green ones or
what I don't have a favorite number you
can put on several how do I how do I ah
I guess like
[Music]
uh I don't know random
ones but that's not going to happen
there's no way N I don't I don't believe
in it I don't believe in rouet
I'm a blackjack kind of
girl but I I
guess that's yeah people who play
roulette I don't know something wrong
with them but I respect
it here let's let's put it let's put it
here I don't know incase bet I can't put
it there why not here this
one 100 on whatever first 12 I think
oh
huh
huh okay nice nice nice
nice 100
on 22 one what's
221 what's 221
hun on
black
[\h__\h] I hate roulette all my homies hate
roulette nah relet's not my thing byebye
I'm not even going to save scum uh
where's Benny oh there hiy Benny I
recognize you what in a godamn let's
keep this in the groove hey smooth moves
smooth he's freaked out
hello that broad everyone saw go in the
Lucky 38 that was
you oh [\h__\h] I'm taking all your money oh
there's your black widow thingy when you
shot me you run off so fast I never got
you spicy
spicy
Benny Benny
when you shot me you ran off so fast I
never got your name you making a pass at
me sister because I'm out of your league
H bro you think so oh you don't you
don't know me it seems like you don't
know me you out of my
league is it wrong to want a guy who'
shoot me
uh excuse me black widow very very very
very dump Widow this what the [\h__\h] is
this
R did those bullets scramble your egg it
seems so or you always been a naughty
broad not naughty n
what girls like bad boys and you've been
downright awful oh such a bad boy you
are Benny I need to spank you a little
bit you're one sick pussycat baby
there's quins and then
there's I don't even know what to call
you I don't know what you're saying I
don't understand the words but I'm
saying I dig you despite it all wait no
wait where is this
going what do you say what can you
actually like hook up with
him no way can you find
out keep going I hear from you babe and
all I can think of is a shovel how can
this be this ain't forgiveness it's
something
wrong I'm a curry I remember don't you
want to handle your packet all right
honey baby this is all kinds of wrong
but to My Sweet It Is 13th floor don't
keep me waiting wait a second isn't this
what we were going for don't get too
close to Mr
but this is not what we were going for
but this is one way to get to his suite
I guess I got my eye on am I going to
kill him
business I don't I'm not ready for that
yeah I have one gun right I have
one it's a silence 22 pistol so I can
kill him quietly in the suit without
people outside of the door hearing The
Gunshot I guess is that why I kept that
one
uh yeah
bit do I have to kill
him I can kill him with one button do I
do I not have to aim I would be very
glad if I don't have to aim and stuff if
it doesn't if it's just like a I will
kill you now kind of phrase that I
choose and then it happens I dig this
crazy slash you can do whatever you
want I'm going to get my career job done
first yeah why do you walk so slow come
on oh yeah by the way Benny I didn't
tell you yet but I'm inviting Veronica
you good with that she's coming with me
obviously right Veronica
yeah she's the real package that I'm I
want to
handle where you go
what where the [\h__\h] did he go did he go
through this door 13th floor right yeah
I think it was
13 there we
go that just sounded like a slow down
amongus sound effect this one it's a bit
quiet for you guys but it goes
like that's exactly how that one
goes is Rex yeah Rex is here that feels
awkward honestly I would prefer the dog
to be outside but uh they'll protect me
in the end we're here to kill
him that's that's what we're really here
for I think I think I don't know Benny's
going to show you the tops I hope you're
built sturdy you crazy
broad what's that mean is that was that
Riz I'm is this uh like 80s 7s 60s
Riz I don't understand what he was just
saying
let's see oh my God what you've been
hiding on that
Tex keep your pants on I've got
questions and need answers you fell for
this trap Hook Line and Sinker attack
Benny but do I get anything out of this
option
besides happiness or so I don't know I'm
not happy with that do I get like uh oh
I can kill him faster oh
oh super stealth kill oh that's that's
weird this is
weird this is weird no
no no no no no no no
no I'm going to ask questions first the
time for talk has passed honey baby
these Mals of ours have appointments to
be else he
now okay you tra sorry guys like I
needed another social disease any
personal
H uh where's my weapon can I pull it out
now wait can I pull it out while in this
menu
[Music]
[\h__\h] all right all right all right all
right all
right fine I should have shot his
package H I still so quiet Maria Maria
Maria Maria Maria oh he's got
[Music]
Theo Benny suit Benny suit and his suit
key oh I'll take
it I don't know even though it's a game
I I felt
like I don't want you guys to think
that's how a waa would do these
things like even like thinking as like
putting myself into my character even if
she has the black widow trait I don't
think that she feels the need to do that
like you can use your RZ and all that
and make him think that's what you're
doing just for the sneakiness and all
that and for that approach but I don't
think my character would really feel the
need to go through with the ACT you know
I think she she just wants to kill him
but she also feels very very strong uh
as a woman to have seduced him
successfully [\h__\h] idiot he was quite
resistant at first but still idiot to
then kill him that that is I
think the proper way my character would
do
it but You' shoot a dog and that was
different because I was going to reload
anyway it wasn't you know you know it
was just a he was he was switching we
were going to switch his brain anyway we
were switching his brain anyway it was
all lead leing up to that
M okay H oh damn that's a big package
though
you
cute is are people going to show up let
me
save uh but I mean they're not going to
be mad at me right I mean if anything
aren't they on my
side bro yes man you're
hi there good to meet you are you like a
personal Butler today like a butler for
the penthouse suits and all the other
sweet sweets suits suits sweets search's
room in the tops were close talk to
yesman about how to take over Vegas what
what are you doing here good question my
function is to monitor Mr House's Data
Network and to code his encrypted
Transmissions allow me to introduce
myself I'm a pdq-8
securitron but you can call me yes man
he's not what I thought he was uh
shouldn't you be working for Mr House
how'd you end up here did you get stolen
kidnapped robot napped robna as I
understand it I used to be just like all
those other securitrons out on this but
then my neuro computation if you Rob if
you kidnap a robot are you just robbing
it
I mean that's actually kind of Genius
Matrix was completely reprogrammed to be
nice very very
nice yeah I guess you are noise have you
seen this Platinum chip before sure
Benny had me look at it a bunch of times
H it's a data storage device kind of
like a holotape but a lot more advanced
as for what's on it well some of Mr
House's data transmissions made it sound
like the chip could upgrade his defenses
somehow oh that's just a guess though
the Chip's a proprietary format thanks
for you need special Hardware to read
the data on it there are two locations
with non-standard Hardware on the
network the Lucky 38 and an underground
facility at fortification Hill I'd look
there what did he just
say I my brain was zoning out sorry
uh what was Benny planning to do with
the chip oh he wanted to kill Mr house
and use the Platinum chip to copy my
neurocomputational Matrix onto the Lucky
38 main frame that would give me control
over all of Mr House's defenses most
prominently his secure talk to house he
explains better I just do as I'm told uh
the only thing I understand stood is
that Benny wants to kill him dror not Dr
House Mr
House you're very forthcoming with that
information
I was programmed to be helpful and
answer any questions I was asked I guess
nobody bothered to restrict who I answer
questions have been a passw that was
probably pretty dumb huh
true oh say I wanted to take over New
Vegas myself what then then I'd have to
help you I mean it seems pretty obvious
Benny wouldn't have wanted me to but hey
not my fault I can't say
no man I think robots deserve choices
wait I can't say that I hate
robots I should not be advocating
for yeah rights for robots I should not
be mm I almost got manipulated into
saying that by these robots ah they're
changing me they're changing me what are
the details of the plan again goal
number one is to eliminate Mr house and
install my neurocomputational Matrix on
the Lucky 38 main frame should I be
rival I also recommend that you get to
know some of the Region's tribes so you
can decide how you feel about them
interesting by the time you finished up
all of that the legion should be close
to attacking Hoover Dam and we'll
execute the last phase of the
plan say Mr house was going to suffer an
accident damn after all these years of
him surviving that be that'd be a shame
to go like
that m
so I should ask these tribes if they
support an oh I should ask these tribes
if they'll support an independent Vegas
oh no I didn't mean that who needs their
support huh the securitrons will be all
the support you're so confident about
that what I meant is you should get to
know these tribes and decide which ones
you like and which you
don't shape the future of Vegas choose
your neighbors if you like a tribe leave
it alone or or if a tribe is nasty or
going to be a problem go ahead and
exterminate it it's whatever you want to
do this sounds all very evil I think I'm
becoming
evil
but yeah it's just another case of
people want to save the world
but everybody does it in different
ways Which tribes should I get to know
any tell me there's a bunch
some of them you've already met like the
chairman for instance I think you should
visit the other families on the Strip
the omeras and the white glove Society
so you know what makes them tick and
there are some important groups farther
from the strip too like the Boomers the
great cons and the Brotherhood of Steel
heavy hangs the head that wears the
crown yeah like that Elvis Presley
dude he's also a
king I am also a King we're all
Kings let's talk about the tribes I
should get to know of course ask away
what do you know about the
Boomers they must be a really nasty
people I haven't heard a single good
thing about them they fire artillery on
anyone who comes near their settlement
at Nellis Air Force Base talk about rude
if they can be convinced to fire those
big cannons at the Legion or NCR though
well that' be neat wouldn't
you just it sounds like you didn't never
talk to them so maybe they're good
people they're just really defensive cuz
everybody's shitthe heads I get you I'll
get back to you about the
Boomers take anything else what about
the great cons the cons are just they're
a dirty people they live in tents like
animals tents are very they've been
kicked around a lot but no one's
glamorous not yet anyway
glamorous camping never heard about
glamping huh you don't know everything
robot you think you do you
don't they're not called Boomers R the
reason are they all old people for
real no way that's kind of cute and fun
I want to support
that old people being able to defend
themselves I respect it that's also
probably the smart people H but they
might be yeah their way of thinking
might be [\h__\h] but they they could also
be reason it could go both ways uh
anyway how have the cans been kicked out
they were one of the tribes The Three
Families pushed out of Vegas a whole
bunch got killed so they settled at
Bitter Springs but they kept being so
obnoxious the NCR had to kill a whole
bunch more of them so then they settled
at Red Rock Canyon there's just no
getting rid of them
this this robot sounds very racist to me
can a robot be programmed to be racist
you set the pace anything else I can
help with for sure you can what about
the omelets h i remember that Benny used
to pay a receptionist at Gamora for
information maybe she knows
something just that Benny didn't like
them he talked on and on about how they
couldn't be trusted and this is coming
from Benny well but if Benny their
Casino said it was tacky and he thought
they were up to something because he
said they always are oh wait no okay
they also have a casino everybody does
everybody have a
casino I'll check into theer you
anything
else there's so many okay oh Brotherhood
of Steel some of Mr House's data said
that he' lost a bunch of securitron
Scouts near Hidden Valley Telemetry
showed that they've been attacked with
energy weapons just white pretty sure it
was the Brotherhood there must be a
bunch of them H up there not a good
place for a robot to
visit what do you know they go around in
big suits of power armor and they have
lots of energy weapons but there's a
downside they just have a thing about
technology they think it should all be
theirs if someone else has it they get
mad yeah all I'm saying is not much of a
chance they'll accept a Vegas that
polies itself with
robots nope anything else I can help
with but if we're
like like besties then we can share the
technology or I can become one of them I
don't know no from what I understand
they're perfectly delightful huh they're
cultured clean and super polite but
Benny didn't like them though he said
they were
creepy okay interesting that's all you
got to say don't hurry on anything
else oopsie anything
else you
bet let's talk
[Music]
about well let's ask this just just in
case you know as an option say Mr house
was going to suffer an accident how
would that happen or is this inevitable
anyway it makes me feel really dumb to
admit this but I don't actually know
I've never been inside the Lucky 38 no
one has Mr house is in there though it's
the central node of his entire network
no you can side with
house
H that will be certainly a choice to be
made you have wow that's amazing you can
murder Mr house whenever you want oh I
mean Benny was always scheming about how
he was going to get into the Lucky 38
but you already took care of that I'm in
wow the other thing you're going to need
is the Platinum I have it you know the
one Benny killed a courier for over near
good Springs yeah
me I have it remember of course you do
sorry about that and it's wonderful that
you do this AI man the Platinum chip is
the key to overriding and exploting Mr
House's defenses did I just say
exploiting that's not a very nice word
why the [\h__\h] does Mr House trust me with
it see I'm already thinking about
killing him he does not have a good
feeling in who to trust it seems sorry
if that was getting
B right it's one of two locations on Mr
House's network with nonstandard
Hardware my guess is it has a that
and who knows what else maybe a giant
robot or
something he paid you like thousand caps
for it he's a bit crazy that's not even
that much you know how much I made in
the casino in in one
hour that's nothing actually that is so
nothing I should just keep the I don't
need the money
anymore I should keep the Platinum chip
ha
[Music]
H I have to admire your prudent nature
why get caught up in action you know and
results yeah
why why why why would I do that let
[Music]
ask if something happens to miss the
house I may be in touch I'll be waiting
right funny
locksmiths reader what is this ah gets
me better locksmithing for a
moment activate broken
terminal
uh how does this work
again I don't think I can hack these can
I it's broken
okay well well
well very
interesting I guess we can just can we
just walk out of here like
that H guys yeah come out
please
sorry so what what do we do
ah
ah okay how strong is that
one
17 oh it's very
valuable okay why I feel like a secret
[Music]
agent
crazy I'm James Bond guys I'm James
Bond unique gun aha okay I'll keep
it uh where am I ah here okay okay
okay there's so many choices I don't
know what to
do I don't know who to side with if I go
back to house and like show him the chip
does that automatically make me side
with him
already I'd go of house welcome to the
tops how can I help you
not what currency would you like your
payout non-cap currencies will have
fractions paid out in
caps in caps Place caps it is will there
be anything else no not for now thank
you and enjoy your stay at the top I got
so much money who was selling all those
stim packs ah the the the the place with
the with the mutants
right oh man so it doesn't immediately
make me go the eyes of the mighty kaisar
are upon you he admires your
accomplishments and bestows upon you the
exceptional gift of his Mark any crimes
you may have perpetrated against the
legion are hereby forgiven kaisar will
not extend this Mercy a second time my
lord requires Your Presence at his camp
at fortification Hill his Mark will
guarantee your safe conduct through our
lands what made you feel like this oh is
it a trap
what can I just like ignore him and walk
past him that would be
funny I just want to ignore
him oh it's script it when I get to this
point to give me another chance huh to
rethink my
options the mighty kaisar has bestowed
upon you his Mark and guaranteed safe
conduct if he wanted you dead you would
be dead dead already tell him to go
Cottonwood Cove south of Nelson the Cur
lulus will be waiting I'll come for you
guys one day but I will not come in
peace let me tell you
that Render unto kaisar hell
no oh hell
no okay we're going to go to the man of
all mans who is barely a man because all
he is is a
brain oh help me get
in wait it works there you
[Music]
go where to partner don't forget your
weapons where are my
weapons did I get them back oh they're
back you worry
me you worry me pres no
Penthouse wait actually do you guys have
a house
floor let me sleep for a moment I don't
know how I managed to have low AG lowish
HP
but apparently I do what
happened ah it was the the Benny shoot
situation hi roller sweet
okay he did shoot me yeah he was right
in front of me he got me he got me so
easily this eerie music all the time
man
spoopy well Mr
house I
suppose it is one of the easiest choices
so Benny has been handled and you've
recovered the Platinum chip let's have
it I kind of want more money for it
though yeah we need to discuss
payment our terms were clear now that
you have the chip in your possession any
attempt to renegotiate payment would be
10 them out to Blackmail yeah that's
what I'm doing because you know I just
kind of ruined the economy and then then
inflation happened in the time I was
gone I was the creator of the
inflation but so basically your fows and
chips are worth nothing to
me damn but I don't think I don't think
we can get any more out of
him yeah they're going to attack me if I
miss step Don't won't
they damn it
such a small thing okay it doesn't
matter and yet so capacious I can get
more money in so very
dear Decades of hiring salvagers out
west to search for this little yeah he
paid me casin of a place called Sunny
Bale back then anyway that's where the
chip was printed on October 22nd
2077 it was to have been hand delivered
to me here at the Lucky 38 the next day
but the bombs fell first oh suffice it
to say the delivery was never made
oh a bad day for a chip delivery
huh what does a chip do some things are
more easily shown than told take the
elevator all the way down to the bottom
level and you'll see what I mean don't
worry you'll like what you see we have
much to accomplish you and I or he still
wants to be with me me be a team with me
uh
what is this step closer to the
demonstration area if you would please
don't make me regret my choices you're
well familiar with my securitrons by
now the titanium alloy housing that
protects its electronic core deflects
small arms and shra easily
enough it's x25 Gatling laser produced
to spec by glasting house Inc is deadly
against soft targets at medium
range and for close range suppression or
crowd control the curatron is armed with
a 9mm submachine gun it's been so long
thank you for watching you probably
already
knew what you did not know is that these
are the securitron secondary
weapons all this time my securitrons
have had to get by running the Mark 1
operating system which lacked software
drivers for their primary weapons all
today with the delivery of the Platinum
chip primary weapon behold for the first
time curatron running the mark operating
system up update the m235 missile
launcher gives the secon the ability to
engage ground targets at significantly
longer ranges a and a rapid fire g28
grenade launcher ensures the curatron is
deadly in close range engagements uh-oh
the software upgrade also includes
drivers for the securitron highly
sophisticated onboard Auto Repair
systems altogether the mark 2 software
upgrade confers a
235% increase in combat Effectiveness
per unit the city of New Vegas finally
has soldiers worthy of protecting it o
return to the penthouse now we have much
to discuss robot are taking over
trips to the basement are rarely so
educational don't you think I've since
broadcast the upgrade to every
securitron in range of my transmitters
and I must say it's causing quite a stir
down on the
[Music]
strip I do think that they could
honestly why show your hand like that
now your enemies know what you're up to
I'm surprised you can still
underestimate me after everything you've
seen I haven't shown my hand I've shown
one card I've given my enemies a single
provocative datum upon which to
fixate they have no idea what other
cards I'm holding it's a strong hand
believe me I dealt it to
myself can I see it
can I see it can I take a look see want
to play blackjack with that hand I have
a high luck
stratch to secure the future of New
Vegas I must have your assistance the
work ahead is dangerous but you weather
danger
well a very panicked manner usually
return to yesman
okay let me
ask huh
yeah I guess that's one way to end
our
relationship right then and
there man I this is actually
really giving me a
crisis what did you want to discuss I
don't know are you are you are you a
good person no obviously not
[Music]
so what are your plans for New Vegas
I've resurrected Vegas Spirit intact
what I need now is the ability to
enforce my rightful claim not just
against Caesar's Legion by the way in
fact the NCR is a more present and
Insidious
threat I like the NCR so far he wants to
kill and destroy the
NCR seems like it I mean yeah he kind of
has been saying stuff like that so far
no he likes them
too no yes no no he just wants them to
leave okay I think we can figure that
out how do you intend you to enforce
your claim on the city to enforce one
must have force a position of strength
years ago when I detected NCR Scouts
roaming the Mojave I could tell from
their uniforms that these were no mere
tribesman I knew it was only a matter of
time before an army appeared to take
control of the dam and I knew my
securitrons wouldn't be enough to oppose
them and so I recruited The Three
Families Vegas belongs to me because I
mustered enough strength to bring the
NCR to the bargaining
table wasn't the ncr's Army big enough
to defeat your
secur indeed it was and still is but not
without taking significant casualties
would Kimble and Oliver have traded the
lives of hundreds of soldiers for
absolute control of hooverdam oh yes
they weren't afraid of me they were
afraid of Caesar that attacking me would
leave them vulnerable to a legion
offensive and so they negotiated not out
of the kindness of their hearts as they
try to make it seem because the calculus
of power left no mind
him what were the terms of your treaty
with the NCR NCR forces were permitted
to occupy Hoover Dam and establish a
military base at McCaron airport well it
used to be one they recognized my
sovereignty over the Vegas Strip and
agreed to supply electricity and water
once their Engineers repaired the dam
written into the treaty were Provisions
that the NC R do nothing to prevent its
soldiers and civilians from visiting the
strip that's how I harness the NCR to my
Endeavor their occupation has been the
engine of my growing economy oh well I
do think
that he's
created
something good with New
Vegas and I I I think that's
h i mean it could also be mine you know
but in theory I think it's good that you
know like that he created
it and that might be worth
supporting
because in a in a [\h__\h] up Wasteland
like this
where there's so many parties getting at
each other's throats New Vegas seems
like the safest and most fun place to be
to me I can play blackj all day here
H definitely has a brain might be in a
jar for sure it
is what a blacking
Paradise yeah and it gives you like this
feeling that maybe you are in a in a
civilized
civilization they even have several
Elvis Presley
the Salient issue is that they will go
to war with give the chance there's just
one reason why the NCR hasn't contrived
some outrage to justify invading the
strip Caesar's Legion the final battle
between those two armies is fast
approaching I can't afford to let either
side win on their terms what else did
you want to
discuss what's the deal with the snow
globe collection that's so random oh
we're back to like the overall menu I'm
surprised you haven't asked what became
of Benny that's because he ceased to be
relevant when you recovered the Platinum
chip oh Revenge doesn't interest me
progress does sorry to deny you a moment
of primate Triumph but you'll have to go
elsewhere to sound your barbaric yop
what else did you want to
discuss what was Vegas like before the
war it was a place of Splendor yeah as
magnificent as today's strip may seem
it's but a shadow of the neon Paradise
that was Las Vegas I grew up not far
from here and though I traveled the old
world I thought they're just calling it
New Vegas for like copyright reasons or
whatever like just to make it seem like
something that existed in reality but
don't make it like they still make it
their own thing they do call it Las V
that's
funny
okay I know I I know it's not
copyrighted or so and they could use it
yeah but that's not really what I mean I
thought they were just trying
to hint at the real thing while still
making it their own thing because it's
their own universe or
so World extensively I never found
another place like it
funny you say that you saved Las Vegas
how by 2065 I deemed it a mathematical
certainty that an atomic war would
devastate the Earth within 15 years maal
every projection I ran confirmed it damn
I knew I couldn't save the world nor did
I care to but I could save Vegas and in
the process perhaps save mankind
interesting I set to work immediately I
thought I had plenty of time time to
prepare as it turned out I was 20 hours
Short [\h__\h] well that tells me I should
have I should have gotten better at math
in
school
uh Hoover Dam is an actual
Dam I believe
you what preparations did you make to
save Las Vegas on the day of the the
Great War 77 Atomic Warheads targeted
Las Vegas and its surrounding areas wa
my networked main frames were able to
predict and force transmit disarm code
subsets to 59 Warheads neutralizing them
before did they come
from inside America or outside is
it
other
countries that shot them from outside
okay for impact laser cannons mounted on
the roof of the Lucky 38 destroyed
another nine War the rest got through
though none hit the city
itself a suboptimal performance
admittedly if only the Platinum chip had
arrived a day sooner
sorry well it wasn't me though but sorry
for my PR pre previous Cur cers the
Platinum chip was printed in Sunnyvale
California on October 22nd
2077 the day before the Great War it was
to have been delivered by Courier the
following afternoon but by then the
world had ended the chip contained vital
software upgrades but not just for my
securitrons every aspect of the missile
defense grid would have been upgraded
too given that I had to make do with
buggy software the outcome could have
been worse I nearly died as it was I
mean so
far he sounded really evil to me in the
beginning and sussy but the more I
listened to him the more he
seems just like he's trying his
best and he wanted to protect a nice
city that he loved very
much so and like why he he he worked so
hard for
that he's a great character he's he's
more like green
gray
H in a way where he's on top
yeah yeah I mean yeah but at least he
Tred to protect the whole city you know
I mean even if it's for your own gains
in the end you still did
something or tried to do
something that would from the outside
look like a heroic Act
yeah it's his version of himself yeah I
guess other people would talk [\h__\h] about
him and then I would be like oh man Mr
House
sucks that's the only thing that matters
here that he's not
Caesar software glitches set off a
Cascade of system crashes I had to take
the lucky 38s reactor offline lest it
melt down for nearly 5 years I battled
power outages and more system crashes
until I finally managed to reboot my
data core with an older version of the
OS I spent the next few decades in a
veritable coma but I survived obviously
and eventually
thrived what else did you want to
discuss I mean you guys say I don't have
to decide yet
Goodbye Oh I don't have to the side yet
right so I can still like listen a
little bit to the
others I want to
see how the NCR holds up against
this or is it not really a choice
between what are my choices because it
seems like within New Vegas there's all
these choices like me taking over New
Vegas and and choosing uh different
different groups family least but then
outside of New Vegas we're talking about
Legion
andc
Etc oh okay it's NCR
Legion house or the Yes Man which is
me yeah me taking
over okay but if I choose like me the
Yes Man then it would be like also
choosing these different families or so
right
M well definitely I can tell you this
one's easy I'm not choosing the
legion although maybe as a
European maybe I maybe it would have
been
interesting quite somewhat little bit
patriotic to choose the legion close
enough right but no [\h__\h]
them uh what do we do do do we want to
get medicine up more
[Music]
or more
guns pump speech to
70 okay 1 2 3 4
5 I'll pump several things
perhaps
yeah I don't know and what do we have
robotics expert with the robotics expert
you do an additional 25 damage to any
robot oh this is good probably if I want
to go up against
house yeah uh you gain 20% Health bonus
when using St packs
oh nice
uh check
finesse you have higher chance to score
a critical hit on an opponent in combat
equivalent to five extra points of
luck
sure not bad yeah if you guys think it's
good
[Music]
okay did I yeah I cannot not choose a
perk right we had this discussion
several
times okay then I shall talk
to the Yes man I
guess P house
floor you can talk toino
Cesar kaisar
N I don't even want to listen to him I
don't need to listen to him I don't feel
like
oh excuse me but are you The Courier who
caused all of that trouble in the tops
who are
you oh great the Followers of the
Apocalypse well some of us anyway have
been interested in Mr House's technology
how he stays alive of course no one else
is allowed inside the Lucky 38 so no one
knows what's going on well except for
you I'm special one only good
faction yeah where are my people where's
my dog and my Veronica eh h
H right we just want to find out what
sort of Technology Mr house is used to
stay alive for all these years I don't
really it could be of great benefit to
the people we try to help many of whom
suffer from hard to diagnose illnesses
oh I see so you like scientists and and
and me doctors and
[Music]
stuff I if if me helping you doesn't put
me into a bad uh position with house and
you really oh I wasn't expecting you to
agree so easily that's great here take
this packet sniffer it'll allow us to
intercept data on Mr House's Network
house doesn't care you might have to
manually remove the encryption from his
Data Network but hopefully he won't have
too much trouble good luck thanks well I
need to get my why this so annoying why
do I have to pick them up each
time you just like follow me when I
leave this building just when
standing no no no don't
no did it it can't did it use
anything I was like clicking it by
accident it wasn't it didn't right I
don't think I I don't think I uh uh lost
any stim
packs hey have you've been able to bug
Mr House nwork oh my God I just it's
been 12
seconds okay no rush but the sooner the
followers can learn girl wait I mean i n
let me go to the Yes Man
first is it difficult do I have to be
sneaky to bug sure later the place
she has no chill easy oh okay it's
simple okay hey hey baby doll welcome to
the tops hotel and casino I'm going to
have to ask you to hand over any weapons
you not
again have you guys found the dead body
yet
huh well I don't need any more weapons
now at this point do
I well I I'll keep them smooth and easy
oh and now that we got that little
business out of the way what can I do to
make
your did you say something important
sorry I thought you were just going to
say the roller the same things again as
ey roller
[Music]
hey
and that quest line shouldn't have
triggered
H why not
uh hope Swank's smarter than
Benny
oh hey I'm gambling here
I send you to a couple locations around
the map asking to plant some
things yeah they don't care about Benny
being ah sorry
sorry oh wait it is Benny's room huh
okay I was like I I clicked on something
red yit oh he's still there okay I guess
no housekeeping came in don't you just
love that Platinum chip buzzes with
power and possibilities
if I were you I'd almost want to deliver
the chip to Mr house just to learn all
its tricks well I did that is unless you
want to bring the NCR or Caesar's Legion
to power I wouldn't want to tell you
what to
[Music]
do I can still change my mind they say
so why was I supposed to talk to you
wait what's my let me look
at let me look at my quest
uhhuh uh kill or disable Mr
House very very
direct Quest the Caesar Quest can I just
cancel a quest cuz I don't want to do
it talk to the and G aboutta
activities make contact with the
brothers of Steel yeah all kinds of
things what should I do
just ignore
mhm it'll fail when you work against him
ah okay well then let's talk to these
people I
guess yeah make contact how do I do
these things there's several goals will
it show on my map
yeah I guess
so all right guess I didn't have to go
to you yes
man byebye
hi talk to the NCR I want to I want
[Music]
to I do want to talk to them I'm still
like not decided
yet I first I was definitely siding with
the
NCR I feel like there crazy scene or
what for me I'm
feeling Mr house is even more susp
supicious
but I
also kind of feel like he might be worth
supporting the NCR to me so far like
what I know about them it doesn't
really like TI me off that badly you
know what I
mean what am I there's
a there's a marker
here wait am I am I on there
no over there ah the ultral
Luxe is this the fancy mcy panty
place with the white glove
people oh whoa oh you also want my
weapons oh I can't keep my whole L
weapons
okay are you supposed to have a voice
bro
[Music]
yeah
goodbye voice actor is on the toilet at
the moment please everybody excuse him
they they're also just humans they've
got bodily functions of
humans uh okay this is the white glove
Society I think talking to one of its
leaders
[Music]
leader leader leader doco
so quiet I need some
music Gambler
Gambler who are you you're just a Greer
too right sound is bugged yeah I think
so
too maybe the lady at the bar can help
me
out welcome to Top Shelf the drinks cost
twice as much during happy hour but they
draw twice as attention
too
ad ad you
now let me see if it fixes itself when I
go back out and in
again
oh did we have an AO oh wait never mind
oh oh wait it m interesting
it uh on OBS I see the game capture it's
moving on my screen the actual place
where the action is happening it has
since not
moved it's interesting when that
happens I suppose it's
over let me
hope that we have a good auto
save uh where's my mouse I don't see my
mouse where is
it it ate my [\h__\h] Mouse
again
oh how do you find your mouse it's like
legit I swear it's
nowhere I go task manager and then it's
just
oh control shift Escape Control Alt
control
shift that did nothing I
think out
F4 oh that doesn't do anything either
interesting [\h__\h]
okay uh well I closed the task manager
but but I don't know in what window I'm
in I don't think I'm in any window right
now how how do I choose a specific
window
again when the mouse is not
working alt tab
what the game kind of broke my computer
alt tab doesn't do
anything Windows SK and
tab no
uhoh no
wait I mean I I can I can open the task
manager then oh I I I can't find my
mouse but I can wait I can close it I
think from
here how do I delete okay okay I closed
the game and my mouse is back one or two
of you guys were already telling me to
restart my
computer don't give up on me so easily
so
early and restarting my computer
streaming is not
ideal
okay going back in but I don't think
we'll play that much longer I want to
read super chats and I want to cook
actually no wait I still got the pizza
tomorrow I'm
cooking tomorrow I'm
cooking all
right got a adjust the menu uh the
window again all
right you need to call Amy what
why why
what
ah very
good call her live back your pardon but
could I TR you to turn over your weapons
ah you fixed
I'm fine I fixed it guys I fixed
everything The Voice works and we didn't
get reset to a weird place all is well
now I just need to find a special person
to talk to a
leader
oh oh oh the cashier is here does this
lead outside or oh
good Mor Mor how may I be of service
Madam you must take off your hat my dog
is not happy with your hat please take
it off at once or I cannot guarantee
that my dog will not bite your
ass excuse me did you listen to what I
said no not from the likes of you I'm
afraid I don't think you'd have the
stomach for it better look
elsewhere I just I just are
you my such a popular question I suppose
it is only natural to see us and wonder
what it is that makes us special the
white glove Society has only just made
itself known to the public of course but
our pedigree was established over
Generations were we always so
refined I'd be lying if I said yes but
I've always felt we were destined for a
place at top modern society
and now here we are think you guys are
weird not everyone can wear the finest
clothes and eat the finest Foods
obviously what's wrong with you that's
just the reality we live in but surely
we can agree that the most tasteful
sophisticated people are the most
deserving that's what the white glove
Society is all about white
glove you're weird like if that's what
you're all about just like looking and
seeming rich and sophisticated
that's that's so weird indeed you have
like no purpose really no no
seemingly
sensible find out more about the
oh I've heard that securitrons are
nastier than ever
wait I think in theory it's completed
unless I want to side with them is that
what's
happening uh
go back to the
bar oh they we to raid thank you for the
raid that's a Great Gatsby yeah yeah I
guess
so kind of something I look up to I
suppose no not really though I just like
the the architectural
[Music]
Aesthetics okay
let's go back to the bar and speak to
the dude as you guys say I like this
carpet carpet's cute they have crowns
here also this is this where I came
from I think so Bath House Bath House
whoa
whoa does Caesar have a freaking bath
house for his people because if you're
cosplaying as Ro
then you need something like this
too
oo I can't drink it man that's
sick you don't think they
B evening
hello there's nobody in the water are
you guys scared
H weird
but that's so
cool okay the
bar oh wait this is a dining hall wa
wait okay I like the aesthetic though it
looks
nice but this is this is not what I'm I
should be looking out for this is not
the purpose not the
goal I shall not be sued by beautiful
Aesthetics that remind me of the great
gats
beam find a dress for ironica oh is that
is that a thing there's a wardrobe here
does she actually want a cute
dress I passed her I passed who she
she's with
me what I I I kind of I kind of am lost
hello there she
does can you give me your dress I know
Benny was murdered but if you ask me the
real crime was that checkered
jacket where would I get a dress
here should I kill this
person I
mean I have a no I don't have the
silenced
gun not at the moment anyway more than
I'm lost help
me ah that was a to catch you okay okay
okay I found my
way can I still one while they're
wearing it did you know the strips all
stirred up lately welcome to Top Shelf
the drinks cost twice as much
during why why you guys want me
to go to the
bar pleasure speaking to you yes I'm in
New Vegas up
lately the cow oh this one this one
don't no that's heck Gunderson beg your
pardon stranger but I'm looking for
someone you ain't seen a young man with
dark brown hair and a white hat on
lately have you that's
really vague there's many people like
that but I guess I'll
say what oh my God
where
uh never mind I was
mistaken Ain't nobody got one darn piece
of news about I want him running off
into the bath house for nothing of
information I'd feel bad got one Brahman
unaccounted for across a dozen ranches
but I'm here for an hour and my own son
just up and disappears on me oh your son
what you lost your son my boy Ted he was
right here I didn't leave him but a
minute I told him to stay put while I
talk some things over with the white
glove folks he was never one to stay
tied down to a spot though gets that
from his mother got most of my staff out
looking for him now I'd be out myself
but I keep hoping he'll show up back
here of course if he does that I'll
whoop him till his skinny hide turns to
leather for putting me through this but
that don't mean I wouldn't be grateful
is that a side quest guys help him he's
a decent dude certainly it seems like a
decent dude but I don't know if I have
time for
this I'd be more than happy to have you
heck I'll hire anybody with
a one good eye at this point there'd be
a lot of money in it for you if you can
get him back to me safe and if he ain't
you can bet I'll pay for the names of
the sons of [\h__\h]
responsible uhhuh
okay you guys say it's a quest for
thiso if you want to get help of the
white GL Society well I
don't I
don't I will
go
and talk
to wait I wanted to talk to Mar
Margery man I got I got distracted by
that Cowboy by you guys telling me to
talk to him where is the Margery
person that who I want to talk TR you
to my deepest apologies for the
please thank you so
much I'm the area that's who you said I
missed I thought I would had to go to
the bar somebody said I got to go to the
bar back to the
bar
okay the bar the
restaurant was it here no the other side
here we go can we actually eat something
here I wonder do you have a
menu margerie who looks like an
important character you you you dude no
never mind I guess
not margerie
[Music]
margerie
margerie I've heard that I miss how is
this possible margerie no margerie Mar
margerie
margerine the marker I have the markers
hey M ah you're just like here at the
reception welcome to the ultral Lux I do
hope it exceeds your every
expectation well I guess this is
probably for the
cowboy this again I thought this was all
settled I answered every one of that
investigator's questions to his
satisfaction and gave all the help I
could I know our reputation hasn't
always been spotless but that's all in
the past now how some people can't get
over it is beyond me for the last time
the white glove Society has never and
will never consume human flesh for any
reason it's written in the
charter oh that's not what I was getting
at uh
did who did you you used to eat human
flesh now didn't I already tell you that
we don't do that sort of thing we do not
engage in cannibalism here under any
circumstances though we haven't always
been the white Glo Society there was
another time a dark time when we went by
a different name but that's all changed
now the can bistic Society pass such
base impulses since settling into our
new home I've seen to it that those days
are behind
us it's okay I ate people too you can
tell me the truth you disgust me how
dare you say such a filthy thing in my
establishment I ought to have you
arrested oh you'll kindly mind your
tongue or we sh speak any further should
I mind my tongue because you want to eat
it as a delicacy why is that what you're
saying
lady there was an investigator who came
through here last week he'd been hired
by a young man whose bride to be went
missing during their stay here well you
can already guess what probably happened
can't you it seems perfectly likely that
she got cold feet and ran off and that
young groom just didn't have a clue the
poor
dear okay I'm investigating someone else
and he just recently went missing a man
well then this well this can't be two
disappearances in my hotel what will
people say I'm going to have a word with
my staff about Security on the premises
whether these people are found or not
our guests simply must feel safe in
their own rooms oh you seem genuine
about that
okay can I talk to the investigator well
yes I think so if he hasn't checked out
yet that is this person is
compliment room for as long as it took
for him to be
satisfied you see the white glove
Society Remains The Very picture of
courtesy even in the face of such
impolite accusations we have nothing to
hide
here H that's something that people
would say who have something to
hide inqu with Mora okay T
[Music]
toally uh more there you are you're M
right yeah good day how may I be of
service
Madam I've heard your group Dy on human
flesh it's like I'm teasing them but I I
feel like there must be something behind
this rumor right ah yes I've heard that
one too jealous people say such nasty
things I feel sorry for them he's not
offended interesting I feel like I would
be offended if it
was true oh and on this time my lie is
supported by speech okay I too know what
it is to feel the craving how can I
support your cause good and you know
what it is to be discreet in matters of
nutrition heyo perhaps you can help me
I'm in a bind I've been planning an
Exquisite Society dinner but there's a
bit of a problem with the main course
he's got a powerful and temperamental
father
oh
oh the main course is a person yes the
wrong person we scouted the right one
for weeks the heir to a mertile Empire
sort of a black sheep he cut ties with
his family and left their estate to
wander he was ideal cornfed and well to
cornfed like to miss him if he were to
disappear unfortunately the Trap my
subordinates set for him he's not a
chicken as he escaped he saw their faces
don't call
him what' you do I asked for a last
minute replacement and they stole the
son of the most dangerous Brahman Baron
in New Vegas while he stayed at this
very Hotel needless to say which is the
cowboy be a disaster if things aren't
put back the way they should be and I
still need somebody reputable to serve
for dinner strictly speaking we're
no rep
reputable what they only eat fancy
people
what they have like they only they don't
only want themselves to be fancy they
also want their food humans to be fancy
too high
quality they got to have class well yeah
yeah it can't be like budget
humans
wow
wow allowed to eat people but I'm hoping
the right person and preparation might
sway margerie to see things my way oh
margerie actually doesn't really want to
do
it tell me what I need to do I need a
replacement and I need the boy taken
care of the replacement must be healthy
and well bred m one can't very well make
steak from gristle with so little time
we'll have to go after our original
choice carile St Clair uhuh he lives in
a shack north of here for freshness we
need him alive wow if you could send him
here or knock him out with this and drag
him into the dumpster next to his house
we can do the rest I think what you guys
should do is create a cult where people
will willingly give themselves to you
wouldn't that be beneficial for you and
I feel like with how crazy you guys
already are I think it's
possible like let's not let's not you
know let's not do it this way like
kfp I suppose
so wouldn't putting body into to give it
a terrible oh yeah good point wouldn't
the body taste
stinky not this one empty h I don't
believe it's seen use since before the
war oh wow and what would the point
fancy dumpster fancy meat fancy people
used it but for our purposes it should
keep his body safe and hidden until my
cohorts can recover it well if I do this
Quest can I like [\h__\h] them over like I
don't want to really help them I'm just
I'm just trying to like
um like yeah [\h__\h] it all up for them
yeah okay
helping them is very fun
though how can you support something
like
that what about the boy you kidnapped
Ted Gunderson is his name it would be
simplest if we could convince him this
was all an unfortunate misunderstanding
but if he won't listen we can't very
well let him go you'll have to be
slaughtered and served then we wouldn't
need the replacement but you would need
to deal with his
he won't listen perhaps if you could
smear some of Ted's blood around his
father's hotel room you could frame
him what did you just say what what did
you just
suggest in any case you want him to die
we should just try it to clear it up
[Music]
normally this is
all very concerned
turning get the cannibal perk I yeah
right if you have the cannibal perk then
you fit right in these people
actually
oh live for what you wanted to do oh
okay Splendid Splendid the boy is being
held in the kitchen beneath the Gourmand
here are some keys that will allow you
access to him the Elder Gunderson is
staying in our Penthouse I understand
he's hired security so be careful if you
go up there and our Mr St Clair resides
to yeah makes sense he rarely Strays far
from his house and he's surrounded it
with booby traps booby traps it makes
sense if the cannibal trait would give
you a special dialogue
here what what my companion here makes
suitable replacement
meal an offering wow am I offering the
dog or a human probably human
right ironica does she actually if I
choose that does she actually get killed
and
eaten cuz you guys are reacting like
that's what's going to
[Music]
happen do I get to see
it I I just not the act of eating like
the whole is do I see how it goes down
kind
of I I just I just wanted do I see how
she gets killed or do I have to kill her
or I don't get to see
it I'm just curious how it goes
down killed off screen oh man then it's
not even worth
it I guess then maybe you feel less bad
about it uh you gave a free room to
private investigator what can I tell
private investigator ah yes I remember
the gentleman this was about the missing
bride such an awful thing I do hope he
finds her
whereabouts if I might pry have you
found something that will help his
investigation
uh I I'm on an investigation too I'm
hoping we can help each other
lie lie
liar liar pants on
fire I have some critical information
for him he's lacking that young man gets
some closure after all he's been through
now ordinarily we don't give out guest
information but I think given the
circumstances he'll want to speak with
you let's see he hasn't checked out yet
if you head back to the hotel rooms his
will be one floor directly above you
after you exit the lobby I got some I
hope we can put this whole matter to
rest
hungering maybe I should eat some humans
I
no as long as I have P
statues I'll try to refrain
from joining this
[Music]
fraction
although are humans low low on fat and
calories
H asking for a
friend think of your diet that's what
I'm
doing depends on the first I guess so
huh so what if they're cornfed
may maybe I should eat a fancy humans
too maybe that's what would help my diet
no although fancy humans eat
fancy which also means that I mean the
fancy humans that these fancy humans
would eat are also eating
fancy so fan therefore you're probably
eating better food better as in more
expensive as in more fat more unhealthy
partially maybe if you're less fancy AKA
more poor now although fast food is
really
cheap
[Laughter]
well it's okay I think I'm good I'm
going to continue I'm actually I
actually want to eat more more more more
fish because recently with the fish
recipes that I've been cooking I've been
like more and more opening my eyes to
how good fish is
yeah so actually I bought today at the
grocery store because at this week I
actually don't have a hellofresh box
because I didn't like the recipes and I
thought okay this week I'll just cook
things myself maybe I'll just uh try to
recreate previous recipes so I chose
some I chose some fish recipes and I
went to buy some
fish but damn it's expensive and I
thought I thought if I buy everything
hold ingredients myself that I'd be off
cheaper well maybe I would be off
cheaper if the fish was like I don't
know Frozen or so but I bought it like
relatively fresh one from like the
counter which I've never done before
I've never bought fish from a counter
like the fresh
counter I bought one from there and
because they didn't have the type of
fish that I wanted in the already
prepared section
H yeah oh yeah you know what they had
like uh ocean
asparagus or like sea asparagus or so it
was labeled as that and it looked like
really tiny tiny tiny asparagus I'm like
hey yo what is that I love asparagus
what is this I wanted you guys to tell
me what it is actually I was going to
Google it because that looks interesting
it's like small
baby asparagus I wonder if it even
tastes like asparagus see cucumber is
it I can't Tab out easily I'll look it
up
later I want to try cooking
it no it's not
seaweeds I I have to look it
up I think it said m is Spar
sparer I'll find out
but yeah actually that is one of my
tangents that I wanted to talk
about that I think I was like recently
considering quitting hellofresh soon but
in terms of pricing I think I'm it it's
hard to get this amount of food of these
ingredients cheaper to be honest I feel
like I've
kind of I mean I could go to like a
discount supermarket and buy only the
cheapest of the
cheap but if I like buy normal is
ingredients I feel
like from how much I pay today for my
[Music]
groceries I feel like it's we either
going to break even or it's just going
to be more expensive unless I try really
hard
that's like impossible I thought so
too maybe in Austria but not in
America I I don't know I have to compare
properly
but yeah it's also just how much more
comfortable it is man like looking for
every single thing and then they don't
have it it's just more more easy
obviously with hellofresh and then they
just deliver it to me and I don't have
to carry anything ah
man I've already cooked so much from
hellofresh I was like ready to
stop but it's just annoying to go out
and buy so many groceries and plan ahead
like thinking of recipes and stuff
no I might stay with hellofresh for a
while
longer maybe you won't really save money
by buying your own ingredients then
that's what I was thinking
yeah unless I learn how to fish and go
to a lake and fish my own
fish that would be sick I want to
actually get good at
fishing that would be so good but it's
not also not like I can get any kind of
fish here the good fish is the good fish
comes from the north
oh Dave the die I want to be Dave the
diver oh well anyway small little
tangent about me being surprised that
yeah but I'm going to cook h two fish
dishes basically trying to recreate the
hellofresh recipes some some ingredients
I had to switch out or like find good um
replacements
for Bo yeah I bought salmon I'm making a
salmon dish and another was it sea haake
or something like that Yum Yum Yum fish
I'm so I'm craving fish right now I
could become a pescatarian maybe if I
wanted to I'm really craving
it it's just so soft and smooth and
um and so easy to prepare most of the
time you just throw it into the oven GAA
is here again
go gab Goa
gobble gobble gobble that fish salmon oh
yeah oh yeah good I like
salmon right I have two salmon
filets you can have one if you
want fishy fish
fish ah yeah I hope she wasn't here for
the moments where I was just a moment
ago
considering that was just a joke though
obviously because we're on the topic of
cannibalism obviously I'd prefer to eat
fish
no anyway uh where did you say the
investigator's room was if you head back
to the hotel rooms his will be one floor
directly above you after you exit the
lobby okay so what do I do though like
what
uh indeed wait what do I do what do I do
now do I want to do both can I do
both what is the sound oh oh oh oh oh he
gave me all kinds of
stuff find Ted okay wait so Ted
is
Ted wait beyond the beef beyond the
beef get Ted back to his father if he is
if he's still alive so Ted would be in a
room
right within
the within the
hotel oh I should tell marjerie about
Mora's
plans I guess so yeah he did talk like
about margerie like oh yeah babe
margerie
knows wait where was
margerie here
snitch I've heard that securitron
welcome to the ultral Lux I do hope it
exceeds your every expectation and then
I can be matching with my bestie
OE that' be
nice uh but H I don't see any dialogue
option for that I do but one can hardly
call it work I think of myself As a
caretaker rather than a common laborer I
suppose it is a labor of love if it can
be called Labor at all we at the White
Glove Society are all responsible for
maintaining and as its founder I suppose
it falls to me to decide how we go about
it no they're nastier than she will not
find out I suppose I will find out and
the white glove Society will find out
later what happens to
them okay so wait where is he what floor
do we know what floor or just have to
find
him
hello
what come
on who who
who I don't have a gun
I that's not Ted
though my heart my heart get Ted back
my wait who wo everything's pounding
right now holy [\h__\h] man punch them oh I
I don't know how to punch people no wait
we're good oh good job Dogo what the
[\h__\h] it could have been why why couldn't
have been ladies I could have taken a
dress and given it to my lady man you
guys have seen nothing okay
nothing God that gave me that gave me
such a heart attack who are you you're
the other guy right wait are
you you're not the Ted guy
so sexy
sleeper
woohoo give her one got the dress this
one it will change your fem what this
will change the
female this one or
Oh you mean ah you mean dare
clothes
oh uh
oopsie but won't it was with your face
won't they find it weird that she's
wearing it like the
[Music]
people uh you're making me carry the
heavy stuff aren't you oh
well
uh wait what where' it go is it in
MK I I didn't pick it up I'm so
dumb all I guess he's still clo makes
sense here making me carry the heavy
stuff aren't you no you're finally
getting the dress you always wanted put
it
on wait you're making me carry the heavy
stuff aren't you put it on that's not
it that's not it does jumping at it with
my fist you're making me carry the heavy
stuff aren't you how do I make her wear
it so wrong dress
no man
I have failed I failed her I failed us
all anything interesting in here
no should we should
we what do we
matchbook oh the following is scrolled
across the back of the matchbook steam
room 400 p.m.
okay there's dialogue I need to get from
her first from
her what can I even talk to her oh what'
you think of Mr house I was surprised he
only had the two robot sex
slaves so you do think that's what the
entertainment was about Veronica
CU I I didn't I didn't want to like you
know I I wanted to believe in that maybe
they were just like used as TVs
or you know it could be anything really
also two I only saw
one one was cut from the game what and
she's still talking about
two there were never
to and
tell me about yourself I like long walks
in the desert and candle lit metal
workshops
romantic who no can I what are your
girls have have ever been in love ever
been nosy I was I have a no once
actually not much young not I like to
think it was
love maybe if I get a life Tod update
then I'll have a better nose
I don't know I don't have time for this
right now girl but I'm also really
confused as to what to do
um I just open the first door and I find
someone dead like what the [\h__\h] is up
with
that you're not dead huh good for you
not yet that is so but I'm still looking
for
Ted this is locked
okay well Ted wouldn't just be like
walking around here or having a open
Open Door
that was the investigator oh
[\h__\h]
Ted it's obviously not going to just be
lying
there a
basement I was able to enter the bath
house from was that on the same
floor whoa oh is this a steam
room wait what happens if I go to the
steam room at 400
[Music]
p.m. what time is
it 2 a.m. or 2
[Music]
p.m. I get ambushed oh God I don't want
to find that I don't want to what's
what's with all this like guys what's
happening why is everybody using the
[\h__\h] around and find
out words meaning phrases these days
today today espe
especially I find that very funny I like
this phrase I've picked it up recently
I've heard that secur are nastier than
ever thanks to Cody CO's
[Music]
video
videos and now you guys are bringing it
up and it makes me quite
happy I'll find
out well if only I could read a [\h__\h]
clock cuz I mean if if if we're in
America then the 2:40 without a. and
p.m. then I don't really know they're
inside so I can't see the daylight so
hard to
say you think I have to go there to
advance oh really you can press
T
oh H then let's find out ah ah ah ah I'm
drowning
help help doggle oh The doggo Wanted to
save me such a good
doggo
uh wait I'm so
confused steam room steam
room we're going to go there but
uh I'm going to
4: p.m.
right
one two three
4 should I is it let's
should I be wearing his clothes or
so
hi why are you in here in a
suit that's very
sus oh he's bug no I'll fix it after who
are
you uh I I'm the
detective I just it's just someone who
found a matchbook I'm looking for
someone who you face you don't know good
that's good they so they didn't send you
after me the game didn't crash a single
time today but we're getting these kind
of voice over
issues where's the gentleman I'm
supposed to meet I I am the gentleman oh
I guess that doesn't work cuz I chose to
be a female character
uh he's dead should I
lie I I don't know if I need to lie to
him let's tell him he's dead oh my
goodness me they must know he was
talking to someone on the
inside they'll be watching everyone
closer now I knew this was a
mistake what who are you afraid of
morning if he real realizes it was me
the investigator was planing to meet
he'll have me killed and then eat
me chop chop my time is up so is morma
behind The
Disappearance yes the white glove
Society strictly forbids eating humans
but we weren't always the white glove
glove
Society Mortimer and some of the others
have been regressed to the old
ways the good old
times they're taking many people over
the last few months but always from
freest side or secluded places where
they wouldn't be missed somebody for
sure we'll always miss
them it wasn't enough lately they've
gone for tourists here on the Strip even
in the
hotel I guess that's the hazard of a
cannibal becoming a
gourmet it's hard to please a refined
palet this is so crazy like I I've heard
of like crazy ass cannibals before but
I've like you know IRL like crime [\h__\h]
but can you imagine someone who's picky
about how sophisticated the the human is
that they oh my
God that
funny uh what about Ted
Gunderson age alive is far as I know
they're trying to keep him fresh MMA has
special plans for
him h
the white glove Society is a b b b
banquet b b every night at 7 it's a
private
section Mora wants to reintroduce humans
into our Cuisine since eating people is
a crime we punished by death he's going
to do it in
secret not very secretive I know
everything about it
now after everyone has eaten it he'll
tell
them oh oh
oh with no real way to punish everyone
in Mora's mind anyway their minds will
be open to the idea of eating people as
a delicacy after you made them
unknowingly eat it
oh it's like it's like those pranks
where on YouTube where somebody like a
funny YouTuber so to say funny invites
people to eat something secret and then
at the end they reveal that what they
just ate was uh just some bugs
but prepared by a amazing Chef to look
like a really really good dish
sophisticated
six-star five star Four Star
Restaurant
dish but yeah it's just a prank bro it's
just cannibalism but now you know you
can tot eat it yeah tastes just like
chicken or whatever
high on
nutrients oh man this is so morbid
today's humor thanks to this storyline
is very morbid
man I don't normally joke about
cannibalism
okay pork actually what you should not
know where are they keeping
Ted I don't know exactly I wasn't in on
it I think some of them have stopped
trusting me me Members Only section in
the Gand okay but you can bet they're
keeping him near the Gand our shf philli
has an obsession with oh my
God an obsession with fresh inred so
alive humans just say it like that is
that what you want to say it be backing
the members only section so you'll have
to be careful don't be seen and more
importantly don't let them see Ted in
the open it's guarded both at the lobby
entrance and in the access tunnels Le
from oh God is this going to start a
fight start a fight
today anything you can do to help me I
was sponsor you as an honorary remember
but I don't know that you've achieved
the level of status that would gain the
society's approval yeah even have have
not even like gained a little bit infamy
have I think I have perhaps if you were
to gain some more notoriety on the Strip
we could get you
in what do that mean do I have to do
other quests otherwise you'll have to
find some way to get inside quietly it
won't be easy can I talk my way into it
with
speech I mocked them a little bit I need
strip
Fame
okay no to this option two more quests
on the Strip okay so we'll like get back
to this at some
point
okay okay find a sponsor to help you
join the white gloves what what what's
happening oh the sound is like kind of a
[Music]
lot oh God like without any sound like
of hearing the gunshots maybe with it
would also been freaky but like
man
assassin bro now I have a
gun now I have a
gun bro it's
just just a normal day in New Vegas
bro uh God damn it what would I do
without my companions I swear I would
have died so many times like I in this
situation I I I I'm so lost I'm so
useless when the sauna hit just
right wow that was scripted though right
because I talked to him how long what
were they fighting only after I ended
the conversation I
wonder oh oh
[Music]
yeah is it really I think it's probably
broken well that's my second crash today
yay I was going to restart anyway
because of the sound but now I wonder if
I have to to have this conversation
again I hope
not
uh where will
I
ah yeah that's that's before ah damn
it who are
you you first
H he's dead I
[Music]
think wait is this is that what I chose
originally yeah I think so they've taken
many people it exp lately they've gone
for tourist Yahoo what about
Tad with no this is so crazy I can't
believe you're talking about eating
humans this is so weird
where are they keeping Ted you don't
know it's guarded both at the lobby
entrance you can do to help
me suggestions on how to get Ted out H
well they'll all be sampling pre-war
wines before the meal oh this is maybe
it's as simple as drugging them oh
although that wouldn't stop any future
kidnappings you'd have to expose
Mortimer but it's going to confess
anyway oh what if what if his Revelation
were a lie what if no one had eaten
human flesh but him you could somehow
replace phip in the kitchen and serve a
convincing substitute instead you could
walk Ted right through the middle of
that room after Mortimer speaks and then
he'd have some explaining to do has been
trying to approximate the taste of human
flesh for years he must have a recipe
somewhere is like trying to make so to
say a vegan vegetarian or maybe not
necessarily vegetarian but
like maybe the replacement is not not
meat but like chicken or pork or
whatever and you make it turn try you T
you try to make it taste like human meat
but like you know what I mean it's like
a substitute or
whatever double
prank yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah what what
Beyond me yeah know oh my God I spoke
German I rarely randomly speak in German
uh yeah beyond meat but beyond
human can I do that wait how do I do
that Strat
let's plan on
uhoh yeah get him get him get him guys
[\h__\h] him up Critical Strike oh I
actually did something oh that's
supposed to wait that's
the
okay okay that's just
bals why you flexing that pose on me
Jon his
soul oh oh I broke no I broke his poles
no okay but how do I do this
Strat how do I do that what we just
talked about drag the wine can I do this
am I capable of this no not the drag
whining eh the wine dragging get rid of
the Phillip of Phillip and cook for the
banket yeah how do I do this one I want
to do that one
can
I do I need some special skill for it I
hope not you can do everything really I
cannot do
everything do you mean I cannot do
anything welcome Raiders
hello you don't need to you have the key
to Ted H okay did you know the strips
all stirred up lately but then if I just
have if I free Ted then I'm not exposing
mortimore am I with the key to t wait
where which room guys can you just tell
me which room did you know the strips
all stirred up lately if I or is in
underground was
it it's in the basement how do I get
there is there I didn't see an
elevator where is the basement oh did
these stairs lead down at least
hey casino
[Music]
floor ah this is the members only
section
basement did I just hear an
elevator oh
that's a door that I don't know what it
leads to this an elevator to the
penthouse M only
stream no I already had one this
week
oh I prob be downhill all the way in a
couple years oh no Cas happy
[Music]
birthday I don't know how to get down
that door oh the the red door that
doesn't say where it leads
to this
one let's find
out it's past
margarine the basement is past margarine
really
evening that's the kitchen right
yeah at least this one I can
enter hey
yo
oh
wow and
H wait that just completed a one one one
thing what the what was
that what did I just
complete it's the right place that's
where I want to be okay is this the way
to the basement oh my God are they going
to mind if I'm if I'm here hi don't burn
me I'm just checking if the uh hygiene
here is properly taken care of in
infected infected ew not so gouret here
elevator to Alters kitchen
elevator
oh that is not
hygienic but maybe still better than the
stuff that we're eating oh you what do
you think you're
doing uh ooh speech Let's go oh we can
also do a repair huh
Morin sent me to move the kid thinks one
of his own might betray
him it doesn't really matter right which
one we
choose let's go with
speech first he's too trusting now he
doesn't trust any of
us it addles the senses I suppose
caution is the desirable course at this
point it's all of our necks if something
goes a
foul okay byebye
wait is there some cool
stuff oh he's watching
okay
inaccessible what's this wine seller oh
examine wine that sounds like drinking
wine that just sounds like a coping way
of saying drink
wine I'm looking for I'm looking for a
recipe I thought I was looking for
Ted I can oh yeah that's I guess how you
would poison the wine maybe but I don't
even have poison oh Philip why are you
standing still do you think the world
waits for you while you stand there
drooling get back out there and get to
work do I look like someone who works
here to you I guess just by being down
[Music]
here yeah there's several ways how I can
handle this I don't know what I'm going
for wow yes sir don't make eye contact
with me look at the floor and get back
to work yes sir sorry sir sorry sir
sorry
wa so can I do this without doing any of
the above yes
chef sneak me one shot ooh
yeah H so well Ted is somewhere down
here right
ouch hello
there safe
okay
teddyy
elevator but that just leads up again is
that where I came from no he's where I
came
from I saved I did he I'll save
again you can steal a recipe from Philip
okay will my companions mess this up no
right detected
uh
sorry how do you
fair don't look at me how to it be
sneaky I've never tried this before in
this
game just talk to him
okay I thought I told you to get
lost ooh ooh
no I just stop by the
Kill ah uh hey could I buy some of your
recipes do we just I guess we just I I
suppose read a medicine magazine about
time I don't think I have
one I thought I told you to get
lost well what do you want I'm very busy
here there go now we have a little bit
of a
speech yeah there's other options we
just got to get to them I think I saw a
rad roach in the pantry you should check
it out so he walks over there and then
wait are we still stealing it or are we
killing and stealing
it oh I can lock him
in but how do I get the recipe first I
steal just lock him
okay no it'll ruin my
ingredients wait wait wait how do
I how do I lock
it is it locked
already ah maybe for
here yeah engage
lock clearance granted locking okay the
you son of a godamn mother oh let me out
no you will not be released this is your
Forever prison you're going to die in
there for your crimes of
cooking human
meat even though he's actually trying to
find a replacement for it that tastes
like it without being human
meat I
guess ah
[Music]
D well do we need the recipe if we found
Ted there was some kind of massacre at
one of the ranger stations I don't know
which
one my Daddy's going to kill all you
bastards once he finds out what you've
done to me I'm not one of them calm down
I've come to get you out of here my
daddy sent you God damn it I almost died
in here what the hell took you so long
it's just one damn Hotel who did this to
me anyway over the head before I got a
look at
okay I mean I think I would be pretty
upset too if I was being like put in
here getting ready to be prepared for
becoming people's
dinner
well uh well there's no time to explain
I think we got to go no is there time
maybe there is what in the Sam Hell eat
me what kind of sick bastards would eat
a person I'll tell you what as soon as
I'm out of here and my daddy knows the
story you can bet there ain't going to
be no White Hat Society no more M sounds
good to
[Music]
me I mean maybe this is true that only
Mortimer and a few others are to blame
but might as well take them all down all
together you should have them all killed
it would serve them right
[Music]
honestly I don't care what you do I
never liked them white shoes in the
first place we'd be doing the strip of
service let's go I'll be right behind
you okay let me just I don't know if I
still need it but you guys said the
recipe is on the
table oh
hey s bag free s
bag where is this recipe
recipes Brahman wellon is that
it I've lost Karma no it's for a good
[Music]
cause that's it
okay uh
so let me
save but is he going
to was he okay with me walking out with
Ted like that
you don't mind do
you
okay I have to relocate re relocate
re he just got to go somewhere else you
know I'm bringing him to a different
kitchen Yoko no worries don't worry
thank you for being here
here whoa big fat [\h__\h] steak and
nobody there to eat it little
waste wait so I'm just going to bring
him straight to his dad in the lobby
there oh good that good that he's
leaving right as I walk
in is this
like this is too easy
I just I just I just walk out like
this I've heard that securitrons are
nastier than ever well maybe I can't
expose moreo but I mean I've heard that
securitrons are nastier than ever
they're going to do their thing right oh
my God Ted are you all right quit your
hollering I'm fine listen P we got to go
after the White Shoes yeah or whatever
they're called yeah they're the ones
responsible yeah go after them do your
thing I don't in in in 5 days I'll be
coming back here and I want this whole
place to be empty okay you do your thing
I did my thing now you do your thing
okay what's this about the white glove
Society kill him but don't don't involve
me in
it oh I can still like change the
situation well okay it was mortima one
of the white gloves who had tad taken
he's a cannibal well that does it none
of them Maniacs will ever do business
with he Gunderson long as they live hell
I'll put me together a damn blockade hit
them where it hurts they control the
food well there ain't going to be no
food not for anybody in this whole damn
town oh she it's a goddamn Monument to
inhumanity let him starve biggest favor
anyone's ever done this hell
hole that that's is what they want you
be driving the city to each eat other oh
yeah I suppose
so I don't like this place whole strip
really ever since I got
here this flooded my nostrils Society
but you got a point they're already
hellbent on depravity here all I'd be
doing is helping them along all right
well I promised you I'd make it worth
your while so here you are I don't know
try not to lose it all at the same
Casino what's the
outcome the strip has accepted
me but what's the did I help them in
some
way I still have the recipe can I still
like I'm confused there were just too
many ways of doing it
I've heard that securitrons are nastier
than
ever I helped the nonanal ones I think I
would like to say I did y hey
evening
well
well informed yes that you fixed the
white glove society's cannibalism
problem we didn't it
man today today I'm just
confused fixed it did I well game says I
did I think it says I
did
uh uh
where was it
I or we don't have to go to the Yes man
right away
right I don't mind going to the NCR but
I mean time wise it's actually too
[\h__\h]
late I need to go every time yeah you
can
[Music]
wait NCI is right around the corner I
got
so can I teleport to
them
uh would be outside of New Vegas
right
NCR sharecropper
Farms inside
ambassy I that one I see the
flag they have an embassy in here
interest I I guess cuz they have this
like help you
[Music]
agreement so
realistic uh
hello who am
I I'm so lost today man who am I
supposed to talk to is it no
um
[Music]
ail hello I got an
appointment
um welcome to the NCR Embassy how can I
help you I want you guys to convince me
that you guys are the good people it
will be worth
it Ambassador Crocker can be found in
his office through the door to my right
and at the end of the hall I don't need
an appointment you guys are that ma'am
open today
wow end of the hall she said which end
this
end I probably took the wrong
end wait
hello Crocker what is it what is it well
now I'm confused I don't know where I
came
from came from here right what did she
say back to her go to the left room her
right her right who
right which
what stood for
me
so
right my
left but the my left was isn't
here her right what my my left from
where I was originally standing you mean
right at this rate one securitron is
going to be enough to defend the whole
strip what is
it patrolling the Mojave you guys are
probably really pissed off at this
point where the [\h__\h] is he what wait you
mean not here but the other her right ah
you mean here I thought the left room
within that ah oh this looks nicer red
carpet sorry no fists
necessary I'm glad you could make it I
have something I wanted to discuss with
you it's a very important matter and I
have a strong feeling you're the perfect
person for the job your posters [\h__\h]
worse than mine are you good need a
massage cute flower though I'm sure
you've noticed that things are a little
tense around here with all the issues
between the NCR the legion and Mr house
it doesn't take a genius to see that
something big is going to happen soon to
be honest with you the NCR is in a tight
spot but if we fail now
it's the people here that are going to
suffer the most I'm not willing to let
that happen and I don't think you're the
kind of person that would
either
I the NCR really at this point in
time seems like the most
proper people the most
genuine and logical people
but I am sure they also have some
skeletons in their
closet
yeah can I see it be can I see the
skeletons before I make my
decision to the Northeast is a
settlement the locals here call them
Boomers Boomers they're sitting on a
munition stockpile that would be
invaluable to us I would like you to get
in contact with them and then do
whatever it takes to convince them to
help us unfortunately the Boomers keep
to themselves and are let's say hostile
to all Outsiders that's why I need
someone like you someone with your
background and reputation would have a
better chance of reaching them than
anyone I have available in exchange for
your help you would receive complete
amnesty for any past crimes against the
NCR as well as additional benefits and
perks well I haven't done anything you
think you would be able to do this for
me much appreciated once you've talked
to them come back and let me know if
they will help us
H
well what is that
that is that what I came here for
though that's not what I that's what I
came here
for that's the NCR route
okay want to play a hand of
Caravan So
Random I can provide a quick history
lesson if that's what you're looking for
no I just want to know what in 227
president K sent the NCR Army into the
mavian force with the objective of
occupying and repairing Hoover Dam not
like you're going Rangers and army
Scouts had confirmed that the dam was
basically unoccupied and could be
restored to an operable condition upon
arriving at the dam however they
discovered that a large force of tribals
in robots had occupied it this was our
introduction to The Three Families the
securitrons and of course Mr House using
his
security Mr House called for parlay he
claimed his forces had occupied Hoover
Dam in order to safeguard it for our
arrival and that he was ready to turn it
over to us so long as we could agree to
terms those terms became the Treaty of
New Vegas AG the treaty recognized Mr
House's sovereignty over the strip and
granted us rights to establish bases at
the dam and McCarron
airport the NCR is legally permitted to
send 95% of the electricity produced by
the dam to our home States the remaining
5% goes please
stop please I'm not in I
yeah I'm not in the right mindset
anymore
uh I feel like today was not much action
it was just a lot of yapping from all
kinds of people robots and brains and
dogs which is
fine but I cannot
think
anymore oh I don't even know which
buttons to
press oh okay
yeah I don't know Blackjack was
fun for me today the most fun part was
the Blackjack of
course yeah I don't know I I'm so done
sorry I'm sorry if I was kind of useless
today hopeless
useless I'm just n
it's like they they just threw so many
things at me today so many
options you can do this you can do that
you can do this you can do
that it's too
much
no maybe I should just like don't think
too much about it just make a quick
decision say NCR or say house and
just I don't know if I can even do it
that
simply but just like say don't don't
even talk to me anymore I just I'm just
going to side with whatever my gut
says you're not even locked in yet yeah
but that's the problem like I just maybe
it's better to just be locked in
it's not a snap decision it's okay if
I'm
undecided I I want to be decided I want
to I don't know not really feeling it
today I
think but you know what I'm feeling
tomorrow is my outfit reveal
yeah yeah yeah don't worry I'll still
read super chats but I just want to put
this up
here maybe I'll just stay on the
screen so that you guys can stare at
this got to make it as big as
possible yeah
tomorrow
actually around this time because
tomorrow minus 1 hour like in 23 hours I
would start the stream I
think
right so I hope you're going to be there
mark your calendars if you haven't
already it's literally tomorrow
though you're not doing predictions are
you so that's also a thing the
predictions I've seen a few already and
I think I'll show some on stream yeah
but
damn I think it's you know the fact that
the silhouette isn't too crazy and the
fact that it's obviously fever knite
related but
the current
predictions I've seen some that are
incredibly
close like in terms of clothes but like
there's not many clothes here you kind
of there's not much
choice but also in terms of colors and
all that so yeah they're not there yeah
I've kind of I haven't left much room
for you know imagination
[Music]
uh and that's okay cuz I I felt like you
know it's okay to have an obvious
theme um there's nothing wrong with
that yeah I just want to appreciate
fever Knight for what it is and that's
what this outfit is all about I wanted
to draw something but I want to make it
something that I know it is not yeah I
think some people when it comes to these
predictions they purposefully go make
something absolutely ridiculous that we
all know this is not what it's going to
be that's fun
too do what you want with it if you can
make it in time I'll uh possibly feature
it
yeah let me turn on some bgm
I'll try my best to make the reveal
everything up until the reveal
interesting
too I I I I decided you know since the
stream is so so late in the day I'll
just
uh think all about it and plan it all
out for the whole day until the stream
cuz the stream for me is 10 p.m.
so I've got a lot of time to think about
and get it all done get it all
ready no bringing your own BM to work
today no I like this one I played it
yesterday
[Music]
too will we get the 2024 outfit in this
year too at this point cuz we're already
halfway through the year probably not
but maybe like early 2025 like January
February could be realistic
I don't know I don't
know it's just everything's delayed my
2023 outfit was the one from 2022 and my
2024 outfit is the one from oh 2023
so
yeah I could have planned them
somewhat parallel is at the same time
but and I wanted I was going to do that
but then I was like you know thinking
about if I can
maybe use this slot for something else
you
know and that's why I've been
holding uh on to it and
waiting
stalling I just don't
understand why I can't
just like cuz when I when I first got my
1 million wish or when I was like asked
what what I
want back then I don't think a single
person had a 3D outfit as their 1
million wish yet there were not many 1
million wishes already like released and
all that in the first place why is it
not working so I didn't know it was an
option I thought it would be too
expensive and all
that and I asked him what can I do and
then they were like yeah whatever
whatever whatever you want but like I
mean not whatever you want but all kinds
of
things
and back then the best options seemed to
be a live Tod outfit also because Freddy
was not in sight
yet
but yeah I just I just didn't know what
the options
were and then I went for that and then I
see everybody getting freedy outfit and
I'm like ah what I'll never get it at
this point so then I asked okay okay
well there there's several people who
have gotten their wishes changed over
and over again because it was either not
worthy of a 1 million wish after
all or whatever something like
[Music]
that so can I do that too I can like
give up on my 202 for live Tod out like
I think that is like the most reasonable
and and logical way would be me saying
that dandle the 1 million outfit that I
got let's just say that takes up the
2024 slot I don't get a 2024
outfit and instead in
hindsight in retrospect please give me
Frey outfit and I've I've suggested that
several times man
I don't know why we can't just do it
like
that like keep on saying like I didn't
know I could do a 3D outfit you you
didn't give me like a list or whatever I
just thought it would be too expensive
or
[Music]
so I'll try
again speech 55 yeah my speech is on 55
now maybe if I try
again maybe I didn't have high enough
speech
level the barter do I need
barter should I have skilled into
barter no I skill
[Music]
wrong can I get a stat
reset
[Music]
please Koka shorts I don't think that
really would work for
me reach 1 million follow us on
Twitch oh
interesting I don't think that the
company ever thought about giving
someone a reward for reaching a certain
amount on
Twitch and even if we tried I think that
would still take probably a long time
[Music]
to no retr retros itive was not about
the 1 million wish but that's funny I
can't
R my 1 million wish I [\h__\h]
up I just want Freddy please forgive me
for my
mistake can I get
free
[Music]
instead h
funny well well well let's not waste too
much time I need to catch up with super
chats I think I know where I left off
yesterday yeah I didn't even have 3D at
the
time oh what how to how to read super
chats where were we where we was I
reading super chats from a member stream
right was I was I done with those oh no
I think I was already done with
them was I done with
them yeah
B not
done I think I stopped at a pinky
I'm scrolling right
now scrolling
scrolling if I see it I think I'll
recognize
it I know I realized how late it was I
found it it was a red one I found
it uh it
was the watch along the second one but
that was still the first at the same
time okay
so continuation it is late again though
it's okay tomorrow stream is really late
um and I don't even have to cook dinner
it's fine if it gets a little bit late
it's
fine cheese yum thank you wait for the
red super chat comes on let me take a
fro candy my fro kind of
hurts okay
wait
[Music]
s I'm grading you after work we always
there for you it's a long distance away
physically but I'm rooting for you right
next to you in my heart ooh I'm using a
translator so I don't know if this
message was conveyed no it was conveyed
perfectly s hey come thank you so much
for the reer chat oh I'm glad you're
still trying to watch my streams I don't
know if you can ever catch them live but
thank you so much all my love out to
Korea thank you for trying your best to
be a Korean kfp even with the time
distance time distance time difference
between
us
Gordon
py rude rules lbank
golden space waterfall D we guys we we
were all like so passionately
discussing which waifu is the
best unending arrogance D lunchbox Dan
space w
d of course it's shinobu for you
[Music]
thank
oh o o just don't that's totally fine
but just don't forget about the waa
don't change your oosi or anything now
that I introduced you to someone else
Plan F of fancy D un need to ch
thank you first timer oo mon first
[Music]
timer I really like the first season if
it even if it's uh weirdness mhm a
little bit favorite Arc snail and Cat I
think yeah yeah yeah so far maybe I'll
agree currently really liked kadu and
surprisingly sanua I really warmed up to
her by the end M
okay interesting your your arcs kind of
align with me but your ooshies don't
align with me at
all Jim Tracy D thank you you mik D the
gamer Creed than soon offer d space
waterfall thanks for the
pinky thank you for the fun watch along
and for showing me your favorite anime I
like it a lot yay I'm glad that you do
cute girls touching stories interesting
situations I like Hana shinobu and snail
girl the most good good choices they
could never beat the best girl for me
though you thank you I'm glad you like
the anime because
otherwise you would either have to sit
it out or continue watching it while not
liking it because we are going through
all of it yeah all of
it so you better be enjoying it that
would be the
recommended option
[Music]
Tassimo thanks for the red super chat
this was really relaxing watching with
you helped me to relax for my UPC
upcoming driving exam tomorrow oh did
you get it hopefully I bring back good
news even tomorrow on Wednesday thank
you all for the watch along it's nice
getting back into Mon special review so
how was
it tasim are you
here I'm sure you got it right I'm sure
you
did get your
driving
license oh I feel like you maybe oh you
didn't get it what you can try again did
you fail the Practical test or the
theory
test or both
oof big oof moment
yeah it was the
Practical did you not get enough like
practice time beforehand I wonder did
you watch too much Wawa when you could
have been
driving I hope you get to try again soon
and this time succeed I know you can do
it especially it's the Practical
thing yeah you'll figure it out I'm sure
pH look good luck you can do it
m man I'm sorry it didn't work out this
time I hope you don't feel
too
demotivated by
that don't don't don't let your what's
the word keep your head up m
g
[Music]
k Dan Master Dan Alexa Dan and again Dan
thank
you that's funny M for the pinky you
know what would be great for twitch
games of spoilers so you can make chat
emote only oh n it's not
necessary I don't think
I get spoiler that
often that we need to do something with
that looking forward to gr blue tomorrow
you got that would be good because all
the characters you girls are playing
have you got us in the mini game oh
really get some rest thank
you
yeah oh anyway yeah twitch
is that's not what I would I don't need
a reason for it I just need
to just get it going
well thank you so much though for the
support looking for the to Dan space
water Dan space Spacey paty sorry mixing
names
together py D and Cruz
D that's it
for monar super
chat now we
have which spring
are
uh this
one part
three by the way I followed them on
Twitter and now we're following each
other and they wrote me a DM thanking me
for like playing it and all that and I
was like no thank you Game is so good
can't believe you did it with like a
team of two people crazy yeah TI T whome
interactions with which spring
are yeah I think they've so far
retweeted all of my
streams and I think they they might even
be watching all the time I think they
said they were watching the first stream
that was after the first stream so I
don't know about the others
but yeah I think that's what they said
they're a PE a a team of two people I
mean obviously like the voice acting
there's that adds more people to the
team but we I guess we don't count them
as people of the team
H yeah it sounds crazy but some people
make games with tiny teams
you red than C
last Ed
unnown things the pinky I love
[Music]
you you guys you know I always say like
I love you to you guys whatever and like
marry me but when I'm put in front such
of such
a direct statement then I get shy when
when I'm when you say so directly and I
and I a try I don't I can't I can't say
it
anymore Attack 100 defense
zero oh thank you for being so Charming
unknown thank
you you're the best you
sweetheart my one biggest
sweetheart GL
Cannon
okay okay that's what I am maybe I don't
know whatever
[Music]
whatever red J jacob7 D Cruz D the gamer
great D just another kfp D Jim Tracy
with the red super chat thank you I
finally earned my armor now I can truly
serve Lady K and of Phoenix and chickens
alike but for real so cool that I've
been in kfp for 3 years now couldn't ask
for a better group or of people nor a
better oi and glory to kfp chy three
years thank you
Jim I feel
like for years is such a long
time and it's kind of crazy that we've
been like I been around for almost 4
years it's also crazy that you've been
with me for such a long time thank you
Jim Tracy for always always being here I
feel like you're here like every stream
you're one of those
people I feel like most of you guys are
here every
[Music]
stream so that's such a crazy thought
that
you make especially with this time
difference you make time for me every
day that's crazy we like
besties we talk every
[Music]
day it's
crazy thank you thank you for always
thinking of me I'm I really don't
understand how you not how you can't get
sick of
me how you always show up guys how do
you do it
oh my God
bestie I work here yes you do yes you
do you're that likable to you thank
God to some people at
least this is my first time being a
regular as you usually stream during
school hours for me me and I've been
really enjoying it oh oh cuz it's the
weekend United
school thank you for showing up and
thank you Tim Tracy you're the best
thank you so much I hope you will stay
until the end whenever that
is and even
Beyond until the end and even
Beyond hm
beyond meat becomes Beyond
Wawa you guys are going to change your
diet to Beyond Wawa at that
point going to be consumers of Beyond
Wawa starting new
business is it good
[Music]
protein not sure about the nutrients
it's a definitely a lot of vitamin
C
orange orange
[Music]
vitamins Studio Rob thanks you thanks
you thank you for the pinky the cutest
Witch is
the witches are cute I I I think I'm
doing a good job being a witch or nut
game maybe I'm ready to play The Witcher
too Place witch spring
R expects goes into which are expecting
something cutesy like witch spring
[Music]
R is visibly confused at how dark and
depressing it is where where the [\h__\h] is
all the pink where are the cute girls
what the [\h__\h] where's the chibi Graphics
what the hell I want to go back to where
ring up bring me back take me
back where's the
pie where's the warm
pie
yeah well not saying that you know I I I
I'm I I do want to play it at some point
but it's a different kind of witch game
huh very different Vibes we got get
mentally ready for it we're just going
to fill our brains up with all the cute
happy Vibes now so that we you
know can build up a
certain defense against the depressing
state of
Witcher okay
na thanks for
that tou a coin to you Witcher
a valley of
Plenty just like Las Vegas Kenny snaps
danan Psy danan idle business regulation
director thanks for the pinky yeah you
you've been showing
up sending some interesting messages
hello this message is to remind you that
your businesses will be shut down for
multiple health safety wait ah that
reminds me building code violations you
will have 30 days to address these
violations or you will also be issued a
fine and face criminal charges uh in the
meet and greet maybe it's even maybe
this the
person in the meet and
grade somebody came in and like
literally like roll
played like this
person and served me with a letter and
stuff a letter and something else oh
yeah the Cuffs M and they it took a
while like my staff because we have
limited time my staff was already trying
to you know say you going to go now you
going to go but but they really they
really really wanted to finish their
little
bit and then and then after that whole
bit the next person that came
in also continued the bit they were like
somehow
connected h
yeah it was it was funny but what do you
mean you what you have no right to shut
down kfp you come in here to my Mee and
grid just to shut me down what are you
going to do you're going to be jobless
after that this is not what you
want you think that's
him
O then that makes sense that the Super
Chat reminded me of those very moments
you know there's some unique meet and
greet people just like there's unique
super
chats well well well thank you though
for the Super
Chat we're still up and running you
cannot take us down that easily J D Psy
D T Mo thanks for the pinky man finally
time to relax I'm super exhausted I
cooked for like 10 people
today was this after your exam and spent
like four to 5 hours in the kitchen huge
shout out to all of you who cook a lot
it's exha FR in super impressed with
y'all time to relax with cute wiwaha
yeah I never cooked for so many people
before I usually just cook for
myself
h no so that
sounds so indeed that sounds like a lot
of effort I mean even just preparing ret
for like a group of people like four or
five people even just preparing the
ingredients like chopping some veggies
and stuff even that takes a while but
there's not not real cooking
involved just grilling on the ret Grill
I will always recommend that if you have
a big group of people that you're like
hosting for dinner or so and you don't
want to cook for everybody just do ret
it's
genius just do
ret you underestimated it next time you
got to do ret you just buy ingredients
and then you let everybody do it
themselves and it's fun and it doesn't
feel like a chore so it's actually fun
and I think people always look forward
to it when they're invited to a Reet
evening ret is the fun you thing ret is
the thing where there's a grill that you
put on your table and under the grill
part there's these
shovels that are it's like an oven on
those you put like potatoes and stuff
and maybe some I don't know meat and
then some veggies and just then top it
all of some cheese and put it under the
grill then you wait for 10 minutes or
five until you done until it's melted
and then you take it off and you also
take whatever you have on top of the
grill like sausages or shrimps or
chicken or some veggies that you're
grilling on top of the grill and then
you just you know add your sauces and
stuff and then you enjoy it it's so good
like we do it here all the time it's
very popular here
we do it especially for like Christmas
New Year's birthdays or so so whenever
there's a big Gathering yeah we did that
for New
Year's and everybody just has fun with
it it's like going to Yaki niku and
these kind
of eating activities where it literally
becomes an
activity like a social
experience those are always fun
and less effort for the
host
[Music]
yeah I guess you could do also the same
with like hot pot never did that before
but some people do like hot pot
parties or
whatever it's basically a grill party in
your garden but inside
and with a smaller Grill and with the
option to like melt
cheese yeah I know Japanese members they
talked about like hot pot parties
before na na party
na so moving on thank you
tashimo I would have love to eat the
food you made though I wonder what you
made JF thank you D for for the Super
Chat Miss f d as well of was the most
incredible con I've ever been to thanks
for performing I got to meet and so see
so many ooshies and fellow fans ooshies
oh the energy from the concert crowds
were absolutely insane and sweaty and
tiring and
fun
sweaty did you feel other people sweat
or do you mean your own sweat and you
also like sensed sweat from
others was it hot in that
room quer spel with meatballs with
meatballs interesting I love the quer
spel
though it was very very sweaty we were
tired yeah I'm sure it was tiring I mean
it was also at the end of the day at the
very very late end of the day did you
all have a room in the hotel guys is
that common that you usually get a room
in the
hotel that where the event is happening
cuz I was like getting worried the more
time passed and the more delayed it got
I was like are people going to be able
to get home if they have to take public
transport but I guess it's America so
all most people come come with the car
even if you're not in that
hotel near by a hotel okay okay as long
as everybody got home I got up at
worried about that but that's maybe not
so not such a big problem in American
conventions the rooms in the hotel were
already sold
out I thought so it's usually like that
no our performances our appearances
always get announced too
late Uber yeah Uber's always there but
money buses weren't running afterwards
so I walked oh I hope you didn't have to
walk for too
much after such an exhausting
day sounds rough hope you got home
safely
everybody you usually get announced for
anyone see after the tickets are gone
but as I as far as I know there are
still tickets not
uh not free day tickets
[Music]
but yeah only Sunday is sold out no only
Saturday so sold out I don't know but
anyway oh man sorry ghost sapling that's
unfortunate
that'll be another
time yum moon thanks for the red super
chat offy was an incredible experience
your concert was amazing and super
passionate you nailed all the songs and
hearing cimo and Spark's life was so
freaking hype meeting gfp and sing
together really enhanced the concert
like one big Cy
family thank
you the fact that it was hype was mostly
thanks to you guys hyping it up I'm so
glad that the Ian fan
Community picked up all of that stuff
like you guys you know you needed some
time to learn it it was a process but
you picked it up fast and and we're
really motivated about it and more and
more the whole Ian Community just you
know learned how to enjoy an idol style
concert in an uh Idol otaku fan kind of
way and that
that adds so much to the experience to
my and your experience to everybody's
experience like if you if I were to
perform in front of a crowd who has no
idea to how to vibe to this kind of
music how to vibe to us in in our
style Dam it would be so embarrassing
and so awkward they would probably be
super quiet and all that but I'm just
I'm just glad that you guys picked all
of that up and you know are enjoying
this kind of
[Music]
culture yeah you bring the energy I
bring some
too and together together we just have
the most
fun
yeah you guys are so passionate so much
[Music]
thank you guys you're amazing thank you
Moondog I'm glad you had a great time
I'm glad you were
there hopefully you can manage to get to
some of the tour or Ian concert
opportunities as
well chocolate and some thanks for Pinky
W I had some of the most fun I've ever
had at all by meeting new kfb reuniting
with kfb I've met before chanting in the
sea of orange during your performance
yeah it was an unbelievable experience
always a good time at a con with C be
and waa thank
you a wait so were you at other which
other convention did you go to or was it
the was it the Ian concert last year or
so cuz you say meeting them
again reuniting reunion with
[Music]
kfp
Boston you
know oh Anime Boston anime NYC front wow
so many actually you've been you've been
all over the
place you thank you for always trying to
reach me going to the places where I'm
at thank you so much for supporting and
showing
up I glad you can have a good time and
make good memories with the others and
me thank you chocolate
Insomniac you
are Patricia gutierre Salazar sorry for
butchering your name Dan Nathan cotton
Dan for the pinky I always hope you'll
do more me and greets I swear to make to
make it to one of these days you better
I don't know if I already told you but
someone else at least I told you
guys you have an obligation to come to
my meeting
reads I need to meet you guys also by
the way at the last meet and greets I I
I joke about it but I I'm not taking
pictures of you guys okay but I always
feel like I should
be cuz I need to like I want to memorize
you for ever but I'm not doing it I'm
not actually doing it so also don't
expect me if you come to a meet and GRE
for the second time or so please don't
expect me to like know your name or so
just by seeing your face please don't do
it please don't be like uh guess guess
who I
am it's really putting me in a lot of U
pressure very pressure pre pressured
situation
[Music]
sometimes even though I didn't see you
in the meet and greet before I'll I'll
still be able to figure out who you are
though but sometimes I know who you are
and then it's like on the tip of my
tongue and you're like expecting it it's
on the tip of my tongue and but it's
like I'm blanking out cuz I'm being
nervous and
like and I can't say it but I don't want
to disappoint you for not thinking of
your
name and I see
you expecting me to say it and you just
don't say it until I say it
yeah and and then I'm like yeah I I I
like I I obviously know you
but but my brain is like a completely
blank piece of paper right
now like I swear I know
but I can't even think it's like I I
wouldn't even be able to think about
like what my own name is what even who
am
I but yeah that just happens sometimes a
lot a lot of the time I I'm able to say
[Music]
it
yeah anyway Nathan you better make it
you better make it
sometime you
K thank
you were you also there in person def
Rex Idol business regulation director
Man
pizza pizza
Pome game recommendation for collabo
a
cute but does it have online co-op I
don't want to like get my hopes up again
for something that only has couch Co-op
but it looks like it would have online
co-op that looks cute a raccoon and a
rat
huh wait there's some other animals too
though wait it's not a rat it's a pum I
suppose did I just hear my username yeah
I read you super jet at least the
name Bay and Bonkers oh yeah Bonkers
Bonkers is
there looks like Co-op
tunic not
really I
mean the graphics little little bit
maybe yeah I guess
so it looks cute I'm going to look into
it actually you reminded me let me check
my own PRS again
and how are my perms
looking nothing nothing I also put in a
game permission request for Blockbuster
Inc and I would be so delighted because
that game is out now and and maybe you
guys know maybe you guys remember I
talked about this game before um the
movies which is now uh what was it
called abandoned wear it's been
abandoned it yeah but this is the
spiritual successor but when I was
younger besides the Sims the movies was
an absolute favor of mine and I think
other members in my family too that one
was so much fun as a kid
yeah and this game just came out and
they I think they're like very uh open
about it being a successor more or less
right the reviews are hard
oh no what kind of things do they not
like maybe they can still fix it I still
want to give it a try because I I the
way it looks like right now it really
looks very the movies
is feel like it can be a a nice
nostalgic kick for me and maybe for you
guys is there anyone who played the
movies back in the
day I I wish I could just play the
OG yeah spiritual
successor I did I did I
did yes I think my brother did oh my
best friend had it we had a ton of
fun I still have it installed hey y I
had it I might still have it hey yo send
it to me no but the thing is even if I
had a copy of it
uh the problem is how do I get the perms
when it's abandoned and there's nobody
nobody to
contact and ask for the
perms they should just stay okay abandon
like who's going to copyright strike
me or
so is it the great Zone like or is it
just because it's a banon where doesn't
mean you can like is it how does it is
there
am I late Yeah you're late but you can
watch the archive I'm going to end the
stream soon so then you can watch the
archive if you want
to Great Zone there could be someone out
there who says they have the rights or
they could get them later but like later
can you if if you buy a company or so I
guess you can't still retrospectively
strike someone years
later but at that point it's like
whatever I would
say that's something that literally
cannot be avoided anyway any company
could just get bought by Disney or
whatever suddenly especially when it's
Disney this Disney Disney is you know
they could just buy anything before you
know
it how can I tell if a Super Chat was
red
uh well normally here I show somewhere
on the screen I show the the stream of
which the super chats are being read
right now and then you just got to you
know
listen wait for
it I'm going by the you can like
actually read along or get a rough idea
of where I am if you uh read along with
h lier I usually start at the first the
earliest Super Chat and then work my way
to the old newest Super
Chat so when I read for example a red
super chat from somebody then you can be
like ah oh it's that one okay Naro then
my Super Chat has passed already or it's
coming up you
know oh yeah the the green messages they
don't count they don't show up for
me professional streamer
baby thank you Kon for the
recommendation I look at it is it new
did it just come out or so or it's on
Nintendo switch is it also on Steam cuz
if it's on Nintendo switch I have a
feeling it's just couch Coop oh yeah
it's a PlayStation switch m is
okay just need to find out if it's couch
Co-op
or online co-op
[Music]
actually well yeah with Steam remote
play but I don't trust Steam remote play
I
I the last two times I tried to use it
it was unusable really
so I don't want to rely on that at
all anyway space Water full D and with
that the witch spring are super chats
are
doneo ah the K ones are quite a lot oh
sheesh oh sheesh that is a lot oh my oh
my God
what let me read the ones from Fallout
today first
[Music]
W yeah now you better get out of here
wers n i mean I'm really
hungry but I think the Fallout super
chats from
today shouldn't be too
much it's not past midnight yet it's not
Cinderella time
yet not
yet yeah Jack 47 d m
[Music]
oh yeah let's go I hope you get a ticket
mafin Nathan coton thanks for the red
super chat oh all the excitement from
everybody after hearing about the
concert stuff Tel I just heard about the
concert announcement looking forward to
watching that but more importantly I'm
super excited for the world tour there's
actually going to be a concert in a town
near me uh so I'll do everything in my
power to make it to that for sure a
really thank you I hope you can make it
please wait a little bit more for all
the
information about the exact venues and
all that it's coming very soon and then
you'll know everything you need to know
hopefully yeah I'm so excited for that
too like the Ian concert is going to be
super super super special but the tour
is like several days and all that over
the span of yeah a long long time
actually
and I I'm so so honored to be involved
in it to be chosen I was so happy when I
when I got
the offer to be part of
it but yeah there's a lot of work for
that this is
also something that adds work to my
plate that was already quite
cramped but it will be worth it I hope
so
[Music]
H I got to ask if they're going to
stream it too or if it is venue only
because I think the the Vivid Cruise
ones were not streamed right but then
stuff like
the uh Australian one that was streamed
so
[Music]
H could go EV way oh weid had one stream
in VR chat oh
[Music]
oh
mhm let me ask another server but I
don't know if I can give you the answer
yet anyway but I'm going to get the
answer for now ahead of
time and little question are the
um
concerts going to be streamed
[Music]
online or is it Case by
case oh yeah don't worry they know what
I'm talking about we have separate
project servers for
it yeah
ah so thank you
Nathan let's get excited for what's to
come I'm very excited for it oh
obviously we all are so excited that a a
weird moth kind of fly just flew over to
me and I destroyed it with the
excitement in my hands yippee
[Music]
yippee Jacob 47 wait did I give Nathan a
kiss Nathan M Jacob 47 thanks for the
pinky recent news make me feel pretty
blessed to be New York
C now I just need to figure out how to
get from Javit Center to the king
theater with enough time to
spare and I hope I would wait why is is
Javit
Center the
NYC
venue oh
I think you'll be
fine and I hope I win the ticket C I
hope so too I saw the ticket uh theater
to get King theater venue on
pictures um actually I didn't I didn't
look it up at all until yesterday I only
you know I didn't look up pictures I
only looked up when they told us this is
where it's happening I was like okay and
I looked up the capacity and that's
about it but yeah yesterday I looked up
yeah the pictures and I'm like
wao yeah it does look rean it looks like
somebody's going to perform some
Opera Opera and
sing something's going to go down there
oh yeah dress code only fancy
people only fancy human eating people
just
kidding I feel like I mean it's
beautiful but I feel like the the
visuals the architecture all of that is
almost going to be like
distracting like
subconsciously distracting your brain
like it's going to feel so busy maybe I
don't know may Maybe not maybe not at
all but I look at that venue and I'm
like this is incredibly beautiful but
it's like so much to take
in everybody you know what to do
become
horse become horse you know what I mean
put on these like eye
walls put an eye wall on your
face so that you can only look
straight from chicken to horse yeah you
need blinders
yeah so that you can only focus then you
won't be like subconsciously distracted
by the
insane details in the ceiling and all
that I don't want you to get distracted
or like
overwhelmed and then
faint or miss some important
moments who knows maybe you're sensitive
to Too
Much visual data entering your brain
h
Wawa sweating
profusely
[Music]
smoy H where was I oh oh yeah good luck
take
up I wish you all the best I hope you
can get there I wonder all of you guys
feel like a lot of you went to the LA
concert but can't remember which ones
exactly so I do Wonder all of you guys
did you make it Jacob did you make it
last year will this be your second time
or will this be your first time I hope
that especially all the first timers
will get a ticket I hope if you really
want in would it would be great if our
venue would be so big that you don't
have to worry about about you know all
of that I hope as many people as
possible get it obviously but yeah first
timers I hope they get a ticket for the
venue and everybody who can't make it
can still watch the
stream for the Ian concert I
mean good luck y'all I want all of you
guys to get in obviously but with with
that small capacity it's going to be
difficult but but as I said for that kfp
is lucky because there's more
opportunities at least in waa
case and also for chickens one thing you
can do is just show up in a trench coat
stack the pwn each other on a chi
chicken totem
pole free chickens for
ticket easy you are Dan Zak L Dan thank
you road to than to the
pinky good plan
right sorry I was working during the
during the announcement stream ah no
worries but I was watching the VOD
before this one and got to you reading
my supas ah you sent so many also I got
the K light pens to work on my OT for
the
tour huh
what I got kiar light pens to work on my
ah you mean ah on your like UT gay
skills you want to improve them by
training with the pen lights you're
liking my tweet made my morning you're
welcome I'm glad I can influence you
positively yeah K light pens pen lights
do you mean the ones that they were
selling at
ofai cuz yeah people showed me at the
meet and greet one person I think showed
me they were selling I think like two
different kiar penl sleeves I guess yeah
not whole penls but
sleeves I didn't know they made all that
kind of cute stuff I mean it's fan-made
right but that's so cute that they had
even
variations a I was so happy to see that
you guys can get like really fancy k P
waah wa pin lights with that I it's kind
of it looks kind of girly but it's it's
so cute it's
fancy better than just plain pen
lights so cute but I mean you can also
decorate it yourself if you want to get
some
inspiration from how people do that kind
of stuff I didn't even know that was a
thing I've never done that to one of my
pen lights I think but for hello project
back in my day nobody did that I've
never seen somebody with a decorated pen
light
H could also be a cute merch idea for
you I don't know I think if anything I
would release a penl itself not a sleeve
for
it rather than that I would release a
penl I
think but those are the kind of things
I'm I'm I'm kind of still like holding
on to for the
tiny
0. 1% chance that I ever get a solo
concert because then it would become
obviously merch you don't want to keep
it for
that yeah and that's the same same thing
for some other merch but I finally given
up because you guys said you want it you
want it as part of merch even though you
already have fanmade
stuff so I'm working on
something well you will see anyway bro
toar thank you very much for the big
support thank you for the Super Chat
thanks for catching up with the VOD also
yeah and I hope you will be able to
participate in the
tour Moonlight the wolf V t d logical
Paradox thanks to the
pinky
uh Kik I'm continuing my simultaneous
playthrough a I've never been never come
this far before what will the new Vegas
strip bring if only the side quest could
stop distracting me what's your secret
to being a bird of sheer commitment and
focus I
was come on logical
Paradox I think maybe that was in the
beginning of the Stream it was very
obvious I was
not very focused I mean I could not
really take in anything
today we were bouncing around they were
bouncing me around they were like do
this do that do this do
that yeah I mean if you think about it I
guess I did progress the plot quite a
bit although not I don't know we made
progress we it's not like we didn't do
anything but for me the experience today
felt
very not overwhelming but it was just
like just follow whatever the chat says
and follow the the aimlessly follow the
quest
markers yeah brain
[Music]
empty I kind of liked it more when we
were just wandering around from town to
town on our way to New
Vegas but maybe it will get better again
for my
experience like I guess it was more
linear a little bit a little bit more
linear then and now it's
[Music]
like
Panic yeah very packed but it's cool I
like the place I like the place and I I
kind of for the few things that I was
able to take in with my small tiny brain
I did enjoy the how the story
was proceeding progressing I liked um to
learn about the Mr
uh not doctor house Mr House
yeah all these freaks all these freaks
man there's just freaks all over I have
I have this feeling there's no no
there's no choice
that would be
100%
good
right that's we have to make some
sacrifice that's
probably where this game is leading us
so we have to choose the Lesser
evil well logical Paradox I hope you had
a good time playing alongside
Me Maybe you did better than me today
you probably
did I hope you had
[Music]
fun know my choice after playing for the
game a few times oh well yeah you you
have seen it
[Music]
all it's gray on purpose to make all
options worth
picking mhm yeah I mean that's good yeah
making you
unsure the fact that I'm unsure means
that it's not
like so clear like oh this is a bad
ending this is a good ending or so
therefore you feeling obligated to
choose a particular one and therefore
making the like making it an illusion of
choice more or less
M oh is there no Canon ending I would
think there's at least a Canon
ending that some people decided
on I would think the NCR no probably uh
house house or NCR right if
anything for
sure there is after the show came out oh
well
okay we will see in the show Oh you mean
after the next season yeah cuz they're
going to New Vegas you think that will
help with the cannon ending you think so
but isn't the timeline
[Music]
different isn't the timeline different
though we're going to go to New Vegas
but is it before or after what we're
seeing in the game
same
timeline after the game okay so maybe it
will not help us with deciding what's
can oh I guess oh it will help us
because if it's after the game then
we'll see how it played out oh that's
exciting that's
exciting depending on who is leading New
Vegas we'll see
oh that'll take a while until the new
season is out and we'll get that
Revelation well doesn't matter whatever
they decide is Cannon doesn't you know
have to be your Cannon doesn't have to
be your
[Music]
Cannon they'll probably go with
house will that make
sense
probably and then I think uh Lucy Lucy
was her name she'll probably take house
down as well
I feel like she would try she would be
she would take down everybody who's evil
everybody in One Way or
Another okay now we got to hurry up
because it's Cinderella
time Hulu D Joshua Woodbridge Dan the
steel D MDK bmk too thank you for the
pink uh Super Chat sticker thank
you very very much hope you had fun with
the stream the ID business
regulation
[Music]
tant
ah Tanaka did you mean the
Wasps were you were you trying to get me
to die
if you find giant green bugs with orange
wings make sure you chase them before
they get away because they have really
good
items um you were trolling me huh I
don't think they had good items I looked
at the stuff didn't look good to me they
usually were just carrying one thing
which was like a gland or whatever you
little [\h__\h]
Tanaka okay okay
Tanaka cute little Tanaka chicken you
know where are you
going
no it's usual room I don't know that was
the most
fitting one month Tanaka one month not
Disney
World one month usual room T do we have
a yeah that's good that's good that's
good goodbye
enjoy or don't suffer suffer you must
Lord pan
God ala
D Studio Rob Dan for the pinky T I was
quite when m s m because of how personal
it is when Teno sang M I cried because
Teno is the queen of empathy Teno gets
it wait are you
using didn't I say that to you
previously Rec are you using the words I
used on
you and tabling the
turns using a no you card on
me feel like I said that to you Studio
Rob gets it maybe
not tabling the
turns thank you Studio Rob I already
kind of replied to this anyway during
the stream but thank you Mum is such a
beautiful song yeah
I feel like I can sing it better still
but at least the second try was much
better Alexa D Jerry dun na d d NL K dun
the steel dun ID G dun got two of my
friends into whole life after showing
them your video both of them said you
were their favorite well I mean if
they've only been exposed to
me I hope I hope you saying this because
they also checked out others and then
their conclusion was I'm their
favorite maybe you only showed them one
or two others if you gave them too much
of a big choice they might change their
mind but thank you I hope they will stay
around and continue watching thank you
for trying to spread the
word vus
[Music]
St the other two dogs were raised by
[\h__\h] in the me oh really all the
other dogs weren't even good options
okay good to
know rard
[Music]
than there are different types of memory
related to different areas of the brain
there's a ton of interesting
documentaries about a patient named
Henry Meson who had to have their hippo
campus removed and the effects it had is
it is it on
YouTube Henry
mes I'm looking it up
Henry
M oh oh I see a video that's 1 minute
38 oh there's a one from Ted at that's 5
minutes 26 oh wait there's one is 6
minutes
15 maybe I thought it would be longer I
guess it's just one of the short
ones
interesting thanks for sharing Ro toin D
you are danan night sparad Dan Lord evok
Dan AR Aran or archan of plagues thank
you thank
you he could be among us Mr house was
born in 2020 well he would be a baby now
watching skib toilet singing for singing
I don't think so he would be four years
old right now I don't think he would be
singing G for
Nisa maybe he would be dancing like
toddler's dance to
it but I don't think he would be singing
it not
yet 2020
huh
yeah got to keep an eye out for any Mr
houses Omar Simpson D Omar Simpson
D
oh oh you're asking if the if streaming
the casino mini games was against to
well I hope not cuz I did om Martin
Simpson D the steel D tro Rego D ah
thank you for a quick
Blackjack uh explanation ah I never
ended up using the splitting but you
guys never recommended doing that anyway
I hope I hope I think I used the the
splitting before either in Yakuza or in
Clubhouse games I think I did it
before but well we were fine without
thanks for the explanation though G CL
happy birthday
Fel
than Roar multi Travelers Dan NAD B Dan
the Ste D sphe Dan the Ste Dan the steel
D the seal
D no found
foot
Ste Al Benny and Veronica and B sleep
over what could have what could have
been was she in the room she was in the
room right the dog was also we didn't
still we did not want to traumatize the
dog after all he's been through
okay no no no
[Music]
when you go far
enough oh okay you get a warning okay
okay okay Mobius D the high Jugo
dun wow iron beta dun the royal pain
dun oh Sime and Dan thean jug D jug
action uhhuh
is that a mod cuz for every mod you know
I have to get permission and that's
pretty annoying too I feel like it's
been running fine so I don't see a need
there's been some crashes yeah but it's
not that
disrupting Jimmy Jack Funk dun and s
dun uhhuh bath house with certain mods I
see I see Kellog PP thanks for the red
super chat grats on the performance you
Kik killed it and the crowd energy was
great too I meant to mention at the meet
and greet part of my
weekend m a
minute Kellog's
P you were at the meet and greet I don't
think you introduced yourself to me with
the name Kell's PE did you did
[Music]
you did wait did you wait now now I now
I'm not so certain anymore either now
I'm gaslighting
myself
G in any case you should always if I ask
you for your name at a meet and greet I
don't want you to tell me your real name
I mean any name that I would recognize
you with like in YouTube chat or on
Twitter just keep that in mind yeah you
use your eye name right I would remember
if you'd introduce yourself to me as
Kell
PP I just want to know you're like onl
name so that next time I can like pay
attention and find you in chat or so you
know now I know because you sent a Super
Chat that works
too part of my weekend kiata watching
routine is that my dog loves his kiaha
my his kiaha blanket and always sleeps
on it while I watch he's on it right now
W there must be so many dog hairs on it
I'm glad your doggle likes it is it a
big doggle or a small
dogle I'm glad he can find joy in
it I I most of the time I don't use mine
cuz I want to preserve it well but when
I had it out a a few days this smovie
was
enjoying to uh make cookies with it she
was happy to because the one side is
really fluffy right if I offer her that
side then she'll need it little 10 lb
Doo okay lb says nothing to me but you
say little okay
anyway thank you so much for showing up
at the meet and greet and showing up
today I'm happy to see you I hope you
had a great time at o guy
yeah and I hope it won't be the last
time you're seeing me on stage
Mah 4 kogam oh that's just my my two
pink weights
together it's like
nothing although I need to actually
that's kind of what my cats weigh I
haven't weighed them in a long time but
they're like three four five well may
not five 3 four
kilogram about as much as your dog yeah
although chunky wonky uh chunky wonky
feels significantly heavier
but it's not even a big difference when
I last waged
them
chunky I love them so
much I love them I keep on falling
asleep with them in my
face huffing and puffing the the cat
fur and and hearing The Purge while
falling asleep and having my arm also on
on the
belly it's just
heaven heaven is not West
Virginia it's my Catos when we get
together watching
Netflix falling
asleep Dre dreaming of warm
kitten pause and cook
Keys W
Home Country W
wa what rhymes with roads what's what
what's an equivalent
wah wa
was wa was
loan for her
home that's not where I wanted to go
didn't want to sing about loans W was
toad no W was loes W was loaves W was
loaves take me
home to the
place where where cats me
out smoothie and
[Music]
chunkers sometimes they go
Bonkers take me me
home to our was
loaves
aw Song
complete Bonkers mention yeah even wow
smoothie and
chonkers sometimes going bonkers isn't a
really good
[Music]
rhyme thank
you appreciate it thank you
hey spank andhe thanks for the Super
Chat they eat each other just like C
people for real
yeah yeah who am I to criticize them
honestly I should be supportive of them
than is banking
hi death Rex
than mini nukes into the food is that if
that's possible or you don't know if
it's
possible I don't know man I think I
could have made some poison never done
it before though plan of light of fancy
danan in famous
[Music]
Dan wait you did
that cast form happy birthday again
thank you for the pinky I read you Super
Chat already but yeah uh uh happy
birthday it's already a little bit late
but still
you didn't tell me until now so oh
h ah well I mean how do you guys
pronounce the wise in Finnish just give
me that hint come on is it what say tell
me the pronunciation in like an English
way we also always have to make
clear if you're giving me an English
guide or germanish wi like oh like okay
H I'm assuming your is the same as
[Music]
our did I get it right
is not
bad new out let's go yeah
tomorrow yeah I got to put up the res
for that after the
stream do I just use this thumbnail this
picture I think usually I made a
different picture right a a different
thumbnail anyway
uh cast form did you say it was was it
good close really good y
yay that's a lot of s a lot of the same
letters
there anyway I hope your birthday was
good and yeah
let's not let's not talk
about going down hill man let's not talk
about
it Sean arving with a pinky ultimately
it's the factions are what keep people
talking about this game as the debate of
who to choose to support is rooted in
real world politics is it is this
similar in other games other Fallout
games do you also get so many different
groups to choose or is it pretty set in
stone who you are where you belong
to oh okay not
really l h then that's what makes this
Fallout game so special among
[Music]
them
n that's why they like it
[Music]
m that's cool water sound yeah
four is a lot more
[Music]
limited I think you know I I that's
that's one thing that in like tales off
games I really liked when for once in
Tales of cilia too they give you options
and choices when it's just like one game
out of a series where it's not common
then it's very very mind blowing and I I
loved that in gilia but it was by far
not as much as in New Vegas
obviously or not as I mean I haven't
played it in a long time you say there
was a crazy amount of choices maybe
there were but still not as much as New
Vegas I would
think not as many like dialogue options
I would assume it's been a long time
there were Bad Endings and I did get one
not even on purpose and then yeah it was
so
dramatic it was actually so
traumatizing one of the the one bad
ending oh no there was another one the
other one I think I triggered on
purpose oh yeah oh they were really
which one did you get okay let me try to
say it without spoilering anything but
if you never played the game then I I
think even if I say something relatively
not vague now you would still not
register it really
um but yeah there was this thing
with you know her and the two of
them didn't they
like did H somebody got killed it's hard
to
remember
uh
defend I don't know anymore there was
one where I mean the little girl was
involved and it was very sad and then
there was one where you end up I mean
it's just a bad ending it's not like you
can you know I think this it's not a
problem to say this but there was one
where and this is the one I had
accidentally I think where you have to
kill at the very
end it's like world end of the world and
you have to kill your whole
party right that's that's what that's
what that was one of the things
and it hurts so
much the whole party that you spent
hours and hours and hours and I was
with I was like I don't want to do this
slash slash slash SL stab stab kick I
don't want to do
this it was brutal that's the one you
were talking about yeah what was the
other one though um I can't really put
it into words I I imagine the scene I
have there's like a hut
a little house small house and I think
there was a lake was a quite quite a
Serene
place and that in that place that's
where the Another Bad ending goes down I
think e only had the maybe it wasn't a
bad ending it was just a traumatizing
event maybe it was just a traumatizing
event didn't lead to an ending I don't
know if you say there was only one bad
ending h could
be man I I miss tales off
[Music]
games I feel like we can play the DLC
sometime soon but I feel like it might
not
even it might not
even give me the same kind of feeling
I don't know we should just play the
DLC maybe it will help me get over my
tails off
craving I need to go to an idol meeting
man but I'm going to finish it cuz I
without refreshing I'm pretty much at
the
end wait I need to
[Music]
sneeze
go so
yeah thank you Sean offer the Super Chat
and
refresh okay it's not too much J Monkey
D oh really thank you wow then you're
going to be very happy with this outfit
un CH Dan thank you welcome
back oh yeah I was still on I've been
I've been up kind of late I guess sky
[Music]
thank you space thank you and Omega
gaming chan oh thanks for the membership
thank you for the pinky before I forget
I sent you a thank you letter a while
back and I want to apologize because I
yapped a lot in it you mean an actual
letter and I wasn't that good at talking
but I still hope you like it if you get
it when you're in Japan love you bus I
might I might be able yeah I think I
should be able to get
it h usually JMA just gives me like a
whenever I'm in Japan she just gives me
a package of gifts uh not gifts letters
that have arrived in the past months
sometimes one or two still slips through
and I get it in a later package later
[Music]
bundle thanks for the membership
welcome okay we're done with super chats
actually but yeah thank you for taking
the time to write a letter I'm looking
forward to it and don't worry so much
about
it I mean it it probably will not crack
the record of longest letter I've ever
received so I can't be that much
yapping thank
you I am hungry and I am about to
[Applause]
M I don't think that yagaru record ever
got
broken or passed or whatever the word
is I think that must have been it it was
like
20 Pages oh no
33 really was it that many
[Music]
and then I think wasn't it even like
computer written uh printed so you can
imagine you can write a lot more in one
page on the PC than if you write it per
hand so it was a
lot it was 33 oh
God that's a long time ago
[Music]
you can take those 3 free pages and
probably
um present it as your like final thesis
to get a doctor's degree or
whatever I don't know how long are how
long do feises have to
[Music]
be yeah Master feces pH
anyway guys you're going to show up for
my new outfit reveal right I hope it's
been it feels like it's been a while but
I I think the warrior alter outfit isn't
even that is it it feels like it's not
that long ago but actually it probably
is quite a while
ago when was
that when was the last
one was it
summer it's been a
while last August September July it
wasn't summer yeah
so almost a
year wow July 20
oh oh that long ago
wow
wow so it's been a while it's time it's
time to make Fever Night
real if you guys still have any
submissions to make for uh
guessing prediction
then submitt it under the
real and I'll take a look before the
stream and choose a few ones to
feature
um yeah damn you can I feel like you can
see my butt
[Music]
cheeks from like you can
see you know what I mean
beautiful beautiful oh by the way have
you guys
noticed this is the first time
ever that in a new
outfit I will be standing in a different
stance let me just uh here make this
clear the legs and the arms
yeah normally this isn't really common
because it's I guess more effort cuz you
kind of changed the base I think in the
past it wasn't even
normally a
possibility but it just so happened they
just did it I'm like it really we can do
this we can do this we can change the
stats and I'm glad we did because well
this looks I think you know especially
for this outfit I feel like it looks
more natural to stand like
that you know I mean
my there's some whole life members who
have from their default outfit have who
have an insane power stance I I don't
have like such a crazy power stance I
stand pretty normally by default
right but still I'm
I'm glad that we're getting a new pose
yeah yeah Ena has an incredible power
set usually only for like kimon no the
leg the legs will be changed because
mostly you got to have your legs closed
together for
[Music]
kimono so those were like exceptions for
changing the pose but I don't know maybe
maybe it was always POS possible maybe I
missed some update but the artist which
again I think I said this before it's
not hook Papa it's also not Mama loony
you'll find out tomorrow you'll find out
[\h__\h] around and find
out you'll find out tomorrow who the
artist is but yeah they they uh sent
sketches to the team and then they sent
it to me and I was like oh okay is this
this is going to be the post really we
can do it let's let's go that's so cool
H
yeah
uh I unfortunately I won't be able to
take down that arm from my hip at least
for now maybe in the future I can
request it but it will cost me some
points H but I think it doesn't matter
cuz most of the time I'll be cutting
myself off um like above elbow go around
where I am now so I think it won't look
weird if I always have my arms
there yeah so I'll see you
tomorrow for the new outfit reveal it's
so weird it's been so long I I I can't
even hype it up
properly it feels like oh oh I have I
have a new outfit for real oh it's time
already oh okay
H it's actually been ready for like one
or two weeks or so and I was originally
going to reveal it uh one week later
than now but some plants changed and
then I was like okay guess I'll reveal
it earlier actually I have no problem
with that it's just I originally I
wanted to avoid this weekend because I
knew that the concert announcement was
coming up and I thought oh that'll be so
much
hype I don't want to like have my new
outfit reveal be
completely like overwhelmed with the
concert news you know what I mean but
it's okay it is what it is uh yeah
overshadowed yeah I don't know it's fine
in whole life there's always something
exciting happening every day either it
is a big live 3D Live on YouTube
birthday live or is an outfit meal or
this and that birthday
whatever there's always something
happening so see you tomorrow and we
say out for real out for real F night is
real F night is real
yeah baby
[Music]
oh
oh wait this is wrong this is not from
well I was thinking we can switch to
this one though cuz it's
[Music]
summertime oh but I'm I I I've been
working on Clen commissioning things but
things are like getting delayed and then
I yeah I have had some problems
commissioning something getting
something
going so it's still going to take a
while until I finally change my opening
and
[Music]
ending but these ones are beautiful so
who needs anything else
[Music]
I don't know who to
R we can return the favor that but I
feel like returning the favor is kind of
endless because that was in a in a way
also returning a favor
from me me to fa FAA to
me H I wish I could split you guys
or
H I can't I can't
decide but I
maybe maybe we'll return the
favor and then maybe she'll return it
again to me at some point but that was
so crazy yesterday I was like what you
what do you mean b is raing me
huh makes no sense why H how is this how
how is she done before me I was so
[Music]
confused have fun