[Music]
is you saying these things to
me she's like
n
no why is this Korean website like so so
oh my
God they're watching me they're watching
every step they even posted the pre
[Music]
chat
defending herself now oh my
God I'm so
[Music]
distracted I can't even I can't even
like do her give her the favor back and
um react to her reaction of me but
because you know we can't do these kind
of streams where we show what's going on
on on the
[Music]
screen so for you guys it's like what is
going
[Music]
on
y yum we should just collab right away
this is the
ridiculous oh sh what was that I don't
know I have to turn her off I have to
turn her off because
[Music]
other what was I what was I
doing
[Music]
h
oh what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] I am so I'm overwhelmed I am uh
okay for everybody who doesn't know
what's going on let me start right away
with an
explanation
[Music]
uh okay okay okay okay history time oh
but wait why is my Nintendo switch not
working history
time uh come on
[\h__\h] the uh you know the those vtu
Awards and then I said something about
uh one of one of the nominees that were
nominated with me and and her name is go
go she's a Korean YouTuber and and she's
on Twitch and all that you know and I
looked her up when I saw the nominations
I was like looking up like who is this
and then and I learned about her she's
so cute and then I said that in my
stream and then like a couple of days
later um she found that because there's
this Korean website where it's like a
combination of Reddit
and let's just say Reddit and um uh they
put so much information there I think
like like most probably 95% of Korean
people check out neighbor and you can
find anything there like it's everything
it's it's like five websites in uh in
combination uh oh wait no oh wait that's
not even neighbor that's her own website
oh okay it looked like neighbor to Me
Maybe it's like a like a maybe H maybe
it's like in Reddit like how you can
have your own board I don't know
whatever uh and then and then and then
like recently we've been like like I
followed her on Twitter and then uh I
said something about her on Twitter I
think and then like you know these
things keep on getting covered over
there she finally it she like reacts to
it on her stream um and and and and then
I watch her reacting to it and then I
react to her reacting to it and then she
reacts to me reacting and then there's
this whole you know it's been going on
and uh then I I I adopted her she
followed me back finally and she's also
been replying to me
finally and now she's live on Twitch
right now and I was watching her and she
was reading this whole article I didn't
know this article existed the the Korean
article about me is I think way more
intricate and detailed than the uh
English article the English Holan Wiki I
think there so much so much information
very very recent information cuz the
article even already had the information
about goo and me in it it's so up toate
oh my God
and um yeah now now I've been watching
her because she's been reacting to my
music videos and stuff and I got really
excited because I I wanted her to rate
my Korean I don't know what she thinks
about my Korean is she watching me
now so now we're we're we're going to I
think maybe one day we will collab but
but now we're doing this awkward thing
where she talks about me in her stream
and I talk about her in my stream and it
goes back and forth and back and
forth and now I'm so distracted and I
don't know what what am I doing why is
my capture card not
capturing I'm really stressed out now
[Music]
okay go go go say go say go please
please um it's okay you don't have to
feel obligated to react to me right now
you can go back to doing your own thing
and I'll I'll do my own thing and then
and then and then we'll collab and then
I I I will I will dance with you
okay why is this C guy not
[Music]
working she stop okay good okay good
good good good good okay I feel I feel
so
observed uh capture
card let me
just yeah she watched the Korean Doo yes
yes yes yes yes and then she made a big
I can't even do the face that she does
but she did the shocked face uh when she
saw my
butt no wait that was fire was it fire I
or do you she's watch watching she's
watching
again I'm not
um
[Music]
let's Papa
go and collab collaboration soon okay
okay okay oh I'm not
moving did you know Wawa owns free
muscle cars tell her tell her how I
rescue you guys from that storm the
other day uh oh my God I got kicked out
of my
app I'm
being kicked out right
now
to I got logged out
great why does this always happen in
times like
these collab with go yes please I have
to log in again why
[Music]
why
password password why why why why why
why do you guys do you guys want to know
my
password [\h__\h] I can't type like
this oh
if I give you my password you give me
your credit card
information okay save good good
exchange oh I think
[Music]
I
okay okay let's go come
on you're broke damn
it it's okay oh yeah let's go I'm back
I'm moving again okay and then why is
Cap card not working that is my final
question yeah t got to hired me when I
was homeless I mean I mean I did you you
all are my employees and I'm giving
thousands and thousands of jobs she
likes my 2D is she still watching no
no no God please
no um is it like uh is my switch not
attached is that the
thing AC adapter no it is it is it
is she's watching now no this is like
the most ah there we go
y y yeah she said possible possible
finally okay my my techical struggles
have been observed uh we can
now play the
game
many people may be surprised that I am
playing another Mario game I am also
surprised just like
you is there supposed to be game sound
ah oh I heard something
okay she was reading so much up on me
man she knows so much I need also I need
I need an English Vicki of
gugu but uh people on Twitter have been
teaching me so much and keeping me
updated about the twitch streams I don't
even have a Twitch account in the skies
above
peaches wo w
w wo wo wo wo wo this is happening too
fast
oh game very loud okay
really
really ha
T Bowser what is wrong with you
W game really
loud are you
sure the Hat the Hat kicked him
out the Hat powerful
hat what is going on is this like a
continuation of some
story oh no you
didn't R around time for
myio jealous
Mario oh she looks pretty in this
game looks
good you know which hat could beat that
one no shut up wait do we have to wear
hats for this I think I I came in wrong
with the wrong wrong
thing
uh this this maybe throughout the series
we can add more hats well what about
this hat
though and actually yeah I should be
wearing that
hat this is what I
need wait we're on the moon now [\h__\h] I
was putting on hats why is there F like
this kind of weird felt floor on the on
the hat on the moon oh it's grass are
you why are you touching me what do you
want what do you
want Oh the Moon is over there
[Music]
oo let's go let's pickle let's pickle
let's pickle woohoo
y yeah the hats are haunting me this is
a game about
hats and the game about
death is the audio fine now the
balance yeah he does it just like in
Super Mario
64 the double jump in
then oh nice nice nice nice very good
that's exciting
oh why it's so
wobbly wobbly grass I like wobbly grass
wob
oh wobbly water is bad wobbly grass is
good oh oh
coin nice grass killer excuse
me it wants to be destroyed it wants to
be touched
[Music]
oo it's so dark and gray scale here
frogs oh I can jump endlessly on them
oh but I get a coin for the
Hat okay special awareness Wawa good job
so far good job so far oh a
sticker what where did that
go can you talk to me can I kill
youum oh I think he Dodges it oh there
we go
oh yeah guys by the way thank you for
the Super Chat so far um should I turn
it off guys when should I turn it off
you're not one of them are you one of
who uh you you all you get a Christmas
pole award then you get the Christmas
can I jump
off no way what that's my
money
what I didn't believe that that would
work okay game does not really seem to
have invisible walls okay let's start
from the beginning a very nice place to
start let's start from the very
beginning a very nice place to
[Music]
start want two
three okay just want to get all my coins
back okay okay we're back to free coins
but I was not supposed to jump there
yeah okay makes
sense oh ground pound how how
how okay I don't know but the game will
surely teach
[Music]
me I don't know if I find this thing
cute what wait wa
so sorry for running away like that you
startled me and I don't startle
easily I saw one happened ear and you've
been for quite the wringler ringer
ringer we've landed in the cap Kingdom
we've been under attack by the same
[\h__\h] ass monster that gave you such a
troun
thing and to make matters worse the
fiend has kidnapped my little sister a
sister oh oh it just turned into a crown
oh and she's on her head I'd hope to
give Chase to that [\h__\h] ass little SOI
monster in a ship of my
own unfortunately all of our airships
were wrecked in the
attack
Airship oh though now that I think on it
I'm fairly certain there's a functioning
ship in the next Kingdom
over I could get a dare if only I could
reach the top of top hat Tower which is
being guarded by the Bowser monsters
henchmen you know it seems we're after
the same thing perhaps we should team up
yeah I think that sounds good let's do
it hats have airships this is the Hat
Kingdom the Hat people the people of
hats I think that is very interesting
for us as you know I collect the hats
all of them this is where the chef hat
comes from this is where it family is
yeah
maybe let's see we can't help those uh
yeah my sister or or I don't like how
they write this is making me stumble
over my
words
Mia oh you become my
hat oh I prefer my old hat
will GOI go get a polar she didn't send
a a Super Chat did
she I can make her one though for
free not your style how about
this oh is he going to fix
it
wa he becomes that that's
better that's
better the riters don't check if their
dialogue sounds natural all it's okay if
you just like play this in your home and
you read it then you don't read it out
loud usually and then it's not really an
issue c is now my companion let's
go don't don't jump in there again try
throwing me with
Y oh you can also shake the Pro
Controller to
fro who I'm not doing that though just
pressing oh oh coins money let's
go okay to throw them here too a [\h__\h]
whoa oh it only does it one by one okay
mhm what's that up there is it a lamp or
oh it's a lamp cute Hat lamps
a oh look at those look at those
posters Bowser and Peach a royal
wedding wow okay it's happening very
fast sh y it
[Music]
water okay okay I got it all nice to
throw hat at everything what about the
lamps oh it works oh you can turn it
[Music]
on oh
n interesting interesting can I throw it
at the wobbly
water yeah but it doesn't do anything I
have to jump jump on those okay okay
okay
okay hat house hat house this would be
this would be a paradise for the the
aliceon Wonderland
Hatter what's with you can I talk with
there we
go welcome to of the
C action guide action guide show
me what what the [\h__\h] it brings me to a
different
screen oh oh Crouch
ZL it doesn't teach me how to ground
pound thank you guys oh God the super
chat but I should keep an eye on them if
they get too much you
guys you
guys Mama
Mia m m
Mia M Mia yeah uh if you if you don't
know what's going on the Polaroids you
can check the post on the community
board uh it's uh explained there we're
doing the we're doing it
again we're doing it again oh oh what
will the game teach me about all of this
cuz I don't want to read all of this now
but this looks
funny SL s what's SL I have ZL what's SL
SL and
Shake but I'm playing with the Pro
Controller should I use the not the Pro
Controller wait ah there we go
[Music]
oh oh I see this a lot in like actual
good players
playthroughs oh
oh my
God oh my God ew I'm dirty now
no yeah Pro Controller for Pro Player W
Pro
Gamer extremely popular speedrun game
well we're definitely not speedr running
it
[Music]
secret can I go here oh I get rid of
those oh
money let's
go I found a
[Music]
secret oh even more oh my god oh it's a
treasure Gro wow 99 we have 99 coins
now
go this is just a tutorial how how rich
are we we going to
get oh yeah he oh I can climb I had for
the top head Tower the entrance is up
ahead okay thank
you so basically I don't want to start a
whole big Series right
now um so I felt like well what can I
play cap throw and hold want to break a
whole second of hit a bunch press and
hold why to do a cap throw and
hold
oh can I still fall down
here
what oh okay okay okay um uh yeah I was
I was uh just looking for like a little
little bit of oneoff game but not really
oneoff so my solution is Super
Mario cuz yeah if we don't finish it
anytime soon that's fine too
yeah we can come back to it
eventually no um what how do I with a
cap I guess oh
wow
oh a this is a long game to how
long I didn't look up the length I was
just like I already have this on my
switch because it was on sale when I
looked at the shop and then ah oh no
[Laughter]
no no
[Music]
no no come on
no where's the safety
measures no why does it reset me so
far oh my
God so
[Music]
only around 10 to 12 hours oh really
well then I don't see that as long I
mean you know what kind of games I
usually play is it really just
that I lost like 10 coins yeah I could
get like even more back now this is the
game
Strat baby hours exactly yo you can Farm
coins endlessly if you just you know
take a little
dip you can turn assist um no no need
for
that thank
you okay this is already turned now
those little
shits okay
no okay okay okay okay okay
okay I'm already panicking with Goombas
can you believe it oh
flowers
flower flower oh no I stomp I stomp
stomped it oh I have to do them all H
what if I do like this oh y yay oh money
okay let me in oh wow this hat is so
powerful this hat can do
anything I find it really interesting
that to like start in this like oh is
area cuz I feel like normally Mario
games want to present themselves as
really really
colorful and yet this is not that
colorful but I'm sure it will get very
colorful later it's just like the
beginning the impression in the
beginning is important right but I don't
think this is a bad impression you know
it's just unusual and it's kind of nice
I
guess yeah bab not too cold okay oh
wobbly platforms oh we'll probably have
a lot of
them that ledge is awfully High m try
throwing me at a
frog
what you can control the
Frog frogy W what frogy
Mario what the hell is going
on
what is going
on M
frog my app is very unstable
today
[Music]
frog
y you captured a
frog oh my God I'm a
Frog wo wo that's like space jump levels
of jump oh oh oh I can jump higher
woo can I jump from the water like that
too how does this rock get the power to
jump like that from the
water okay what about you guys what what
do I do oh oh
oh they're like where where the [\h__\h] did
you
go ah just jump from one to another
endless jumping yeah it's my first playr
oh my
God can my app not be unstable please oh
hidden hidden
coins basically I played Super Mario 64
before and can you not jump so high it's
actually kind of bothering
me oh okay wait I can't kill
them um and I played Super Mario
Sunshine those two I played on stream
but I never finished them and then what
was the one that I played for one stream
and then lost my [\h__\h] what was
that cuz normally I just don't play like
Mario games like this but I don't
dislike them at all if anything it's a
more likely genre for me than FPS I'm
just really bad at it ah you Deluxe
Super Mario Bros you Deluxe yeah I tried
that for one stream and oh my God it's
was not a baby
game wait wait wait
heart oh my God the jumps are a little
bit hard to control
sometimes there we go practice makes
perfect yeah people said that if I'm
going to finish any Mario game besides
the RPG that we played
recently then it's going to be this one
oh I can return okay nice goodbye
frog no oh oh I can still like inhabit
him one one more time I want to oh
[Music]
container why can't I not
move all Mario games are baby games no
they're not I I take it back okay you
don't have to say that either what's up
there nothing oh
okay uh-oh uhoh the super chats
oh oh oh my cat ear's a b okay why not
what's going on oh there's a ship up
there oh it's a ah it's a it's a safe
Point wait did I miss one was there one
in the previous
level bad days to happen what you've got
to keep a stiff with what well can you
do something I'm doing it shut
up I'm on it I'm too scared I can hardly
move they are not
theu the first checkpoint flag you find
oh okay okay wait to oh wait do the
coins go
away I want to check down there if there
was a
secret no don't clap for me
is there a secret here no what about
this like there's certainly like a door
here
H suspicious Frozen W ya today unstable
I can change the app to a different one
that'll probably be fine but then I
can't put on this
hat I just got to keep on restarting
oh is it the first boss fight already
oh not friends right they don't look
like
friends boss would me there be a fellow
with a mustache coming along guess we
ought to introduce ourselves for the
wedding planners for the happy
couple the movement of the long one the
long boy is funny what's with
him the only ones who's like like
somewhat calm the only one who's
somewhat calm is the the
girl the
brutal oh we got the treasure we need so
we ain't got no more business in these
parts oh don't go Al do I have to fight
all of them like one by one in the
future of course roughing up goody to
shoes MERS was in the contract so I
guess we still got a little oh okay we
fight just you okay all right only if I
get your hat then oh is that like three
lives oh the
controls I don't know how to
control I'm really bad at this
game I'm bad at Mario games okay I did
it didn't I jump on him W I didn't even
do the ground pound thank God I didn't
have to know oh wait the corn though ah
oh heart heart heart container do I jump
on them
Yahoo okay easy easy to guess what to do
oh [\h__\h] ah wait did I fail because I
didn't get all the hats now oh
nice oh that's it that's
it
yay
oh first try first
try yay oh wait I go to this island or
what
move let's go what wait I became
electricity or what are you telling me I
became
[Music]
electricity do I still have to move or
is it moving on its own I think it's
moving on time strange
box okay let me eat one
snack I have um what's C again in in
English um
um oh my God
[Music]
Mario gingerbread yeah gingerbread
coated in dark chocolate and with some
Jam in
between really yummy from
B really yummy small
snack M it's so good it actually tastes
a bit like those cookies with
the chocolate coating and the orange Jam
inside it tastes pretty much the same
actually
yum I've never seen Mario games be so
easy than Mario
Odyssey okay okay you guys give me
confidence but at the same time I would
feel bad if I do
bad yeah like the jaffa
cakes bow and makes the best Jaffa Cakes
and this kind of tastes like that except
with the the cake thingy is instead um
gingerbread
yummy Cascade kingdom is my favorite
world it looks nice
already how what what what what voice
was it
um oh yeah what right and we made it to
the Cascade Kingdom sorry still a little
bit I'm from capturing must
myself oh that's cute he's like hyped up
from the
electricity what they changed what do
you mean they changed the voice actor
you mean
me there should be an old Airship
somewhere around here let's see if we
can find it all righty woohoo woo I love
doing that oh my God if you guys played
this game before and then you first
started playing and you did this jump
does this not give you
like this kind of feeling
like what is
this what is
this cuz it it's the same jump I guess
maybe he does it in all 3D Mario games
so maybe it's not you know special but
it's special to
me it's the famous music isn't it this
music I know
it I
know I I know it has good
soundtrack wait I want to read I know
it's surprising but let me
read music kind of low okay now now I
make it
louder travel tip homing cap grow after
thring your cap shake the Pro Controller
again to perform a homing cap Pro the
cap will fly toward the nearest tget you
can see it's super handy when your aim
is a little
oh okay who can we oh oh wait it went to
the other what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
just
happened is that what it was or did I do
something else because I looked fancier
than in the picture down there okay
let's let's throw it here okay no that
was oh wait oh that's like so that's
definitely something else okay cuz I
shaked it too much now when I shake it a
little bit less uh
oh a little bit less I'm going to have
so many so many Twitches I'm
twitching even though I'm not a twitch
streamer who so I guess that's like in a
circle movement wait he doesn't even
when I'm not pressing y okay okay maybe
I should play this with the The Joy
CS
[Music]
careful no go
down how do I let
[Music]
go there's no way there's no way that I
can make that oh wait I can throw it ah
it becomes the platform okay okay I
thought I had to jump on the on the
hats oh
nice oh oh no a
taco oh oh thank you oh thank you
w can I throw the Hat on it on him can I
even become
him I
can't pull oh wait w who who who who
wait we got to do that in the other
direction no no not that
direction he has a mustache
now nice thank you wait that's my first
moon
[Music]
Mo B great
no what what do you mean b oh B because
of the dog I thought I got raided and I
thought they're not
alive they're not
alive
hi GTO multi moon at top The Falls whoa
what the [\h__\h] is that like the aunt of
those brutal or whatever their name
was oh we found a power Moon amazing
what un lucky break this will come in
handy to power the Airship have you ever
seen anything like
that uh yeah when I look up at the sky
at
night get this one Doo Bow Bow Bow Bow
over here
mother come here
oh ah you can't reach it unless like
[Music]
wait yeah oh I got nothing out of that
okay then we shall move
[Music]
on no
all there it is this is what we're here
looking for it's looking a bit more
wrapped than I'd expected uh no it's
just an older model I'm certain you can
still
fly it's not an Airship doesn't look
like one let's give it a shot shall we
just throw me on the globe there
oo first I look at the
[Music]
surroundings or can
I yeah it's still so big they probably
let me do that afterwards anyway right
oh or maybe one yeah okay one will not
be enough okay okay
[Music]
oh
interesting a nothing's happening what
power that power Moon must not have
given the ship enough energy I wonder if
we can find more around here oh I think
so all right see now I have a reason to
go around and find more all
right it will fly event
actually the number of dotted circles in
the corner is probably how many moons
you must collect ADV oh really we'll see
about
that je what what is this this looks
like candy like disgusting candy
though any secrets down here
no what is this can I climb up oh is
there a moon up there no it's a coin
first I thought it was because it was
golden
okay life saers
what
oh
Challenger so yeah today is apparently
to some people still Christmas not
really to me that's why I feel like
already back to normal everything's back
to
[Music]
normal how to do a bigger
jump
[Music]
it's Christmas for me Christmas in an a
oh it's really not christas for
me Crouch them how do I crouch
I but he jumps backwards so I look
[Music]
backward
z r and then jump z z r oh that's also
crouching
oh oh I was really close really
close not as easy as I thought it could
be not delate to wish you it is not no
no no no you can still wish me a merry
Christmas Merry Christmas to you too
guys many
this is like it feels like it's falling
apart can I break
it cuz they're
crumbling
oh look at the size of that thing surely
it's protecting a moon right wait
it's I thought it was a fossil wait it's
real can we
oh
aha wait what do we want to oh I know we
want to destroy those walls over
there oh but we could have done the with
the dog too
no goodbye dog b
b what exactly should I be doing with
this is this the the right way to go
with with the
dino I'm a
dinosaur I can be everything I can make
my dreams come true it become anything I
ever wanted and never dreamed of oh
oh F it's a 2d Mario
[Music]
[Applause]
now really oh wait was that that jingle
wasn't telling me that I'm kind of done
and don't need him anymore but this
feels like dinosaur
abuse cuz like oh oh wait he's gone oh
just pooped
away toy Mario
cute but wait I kind of want to go
back kind of want to go back sorry
because I feel like there was still some
coins and stuff over there no like down
here wait that's ah it's also something
with 2D Mario oh it's cat
peach oh gives me a heart it's a secret
I
think let's go up
here oh oh
platforming wobbly clouds wobbly
platforms oh no one more
time so yeah uh Christmas yesterday uh
my brother and my mom came over we spent
Christmas the evening together as us
free and my mom was staying the past
days at my brother's
[Music]
apartment just last night she stayed at
my
place um but yeah she was like cooking
and preparing everything the days
before so when they came over
yesterday uh wait oh I can't throw my
cap now not at
all uh they just like
finished cooking Mommy just finished
cooking and made the dessert and all
that
[Music]
uh
oh wall jumps don't work back then
[Music]
huh what this dirt okay okay let me tell
you about the menu let me tell you how
do I get
this oh Pro Gamer
yo so stop moving
again crouching doesn't help really it
feels like I jumped a little bit more
maybe I
didn't okay okay but I got style points
for that
no oh there's more
a ack don't they go away after a while
once you activate them okay was just two
or was it more and they just you know
cuzz it's a Time limited thing
no I think so but yeah let me tell you
about the menu the Christmas manual that
we
consumed
um more and fast that's what I thought
yeah he so uh first we had a
soup um mommy made a soup from like the
the whole it was
a she made even the stalk from scratch
you know with like bones and all that
[Music]
woohoo there was something extra down
there well if it wasn't the moon then I
don't really care not going back there
now I'm so distracted already and I seem
to not want to move again
great so she made the stock herself and
uh you wouldn't attack a friend would
you
and so the soup was really good with um
pess
noodle
y oh they didn't kill each other okay p
nle is like a
dumpling an Austrian dumpling with like
some kind of cheese ah wait I get it
now a really strong uh
cheese strong SW strong smelly cheese
but good cheese I like it has this SM
I'm not sure how
to how to explain that honestly it's an
Austrian dish and you can eat it either
in a soup then it's a cast
super or you can need it in different
ways of
course not sure what other ways there
are oh we're fighting now
[Music]
already
oh my God
aunti what this you say you need to
repair some old Airship oh my I could
never be a part with any of my precious
power
moons it s to be like someone wants to
be a snack for my adorable chain Cho
kids go get
him get him
boy if I become him ah I became him oh
oh oh oh oh oh come on come on come on a
[\h__\h] ah pull pull pull
pull in her
[Music]
face B let me out of here oh wait
somehow that kind of worked to my liking
okay we got to do it again I so we had
the silk and then the main course was
uhad which is
um rolled
up with uh some stuff inside like bacon
and uh Glen gerkens uh and and stuff
like that with really yummy sauce fit
sauce that I don't know exactly uh what
was in it because I think there a lot of
things in it am I dying it
it it's the difficult surely this last
one is the is the ah is the last hit
that we need okay thank god oh I got
the what a again um um wait yeah what's
the real word for it uh what's in the
burger that some people don't want the
green stuff
one HP in a dream for real for real
yeah got the pickles yeah so it's like a
r up beef really uh soft it was like
slow cooked in my slow cooker the first
time we ever used my slow
cooker now I gave my slow cooker to
Mommy because she really really liked
the slow
cooker I'm a pickle
Morty no T well fighting no I have to
tangent you done it and now we've got a
multi Moon o it's as strong as free
Power moons combin it should get the
ship moving in no
time let's see if we can make this work
for me on the globe
okay is that all we needed three
more it needs four more [\h__\h] four
more okay
and uh so to the sauce we also had uh as
a side SP you know the oh wa wao wao
what the [\h__\h]
wa also had SP which is like maybe you
remember those like small like uh
dumplings thingies that you kind of make
with eggs and floor and flour and this
and that what the [\h__\h] is with
you
sorry what is the secret you're seeking
I know it I know it ha I can tell you
when I give you a clue jump through the
Rocks it's hiding somewhere and no peing
go find it go find it SC is he talking
about the
moon is it talking about something I
already
[Music]
did
use Dogo to my
advantage yeah
okay so yeah we got that H for the main
course was really good really soft
really yummy and then for the dessert it
was uh milk rice
uh milky milky rice what you call it
again yeah shut up I'm checking things
out
so milky rice
with a really yummy yeah porridge with a
really yummy um self-made from Mommy
chocolate
mousse
Co where do I go
first chocolate mousse
and
Mama
Mia
[Music]
to were you here all this time hi
Mario go my I'm doing a of Power
locations having trouble finding bons
no thank you I already have them all I
think I mean maybe there's more like
secret ones what f is
this hi Uncle I'm Uncle I me K I'm uncle
am place to make your greens and all
that yeah you got any amib no I don't
have a single one wait you get a power
moon for an
amiibo my
on and then a caramelized
pears caramelized sliced
pears with the Milky rice oh my God I
have to walk so far are you for real the
Milky rice and the Moose The Chocolate
Moose was the dessert which was really
good and I still have leftovers from all
of it so I'm going to eat it
[Music]
today it's very different from what I
posted on Twitter maybe you guys saw
likea was like tweeting about like
like she's hungry and she wants to find
food that's kind of
Christmasy
and I I don't think she meant like
serious like dinner type of foods just
like snack I think but then I I wanted
to reply to her cuz like I immediately
wanted to show off like the the yummy
food that we eat here for for dinner cuz
like in chapad it's so common to just
eat like fried chicken and a a a cake
usually like a cream cake
some strawberries or
so Fried Chicken I'm like so confusing
to
me
so I showed her what we would eat
although like I mean we can also eat
like all kinds of things things for
Christmas here it's not like set in
stone
but
oh it's not and stone but that's the one
I posted is like the like kind of common
for
oh a it's a riddle like an angle
riddle
yeah bilard it's oh my God this just how
I will finally learn how to play
billyard properly cuz I just oh moon I
just shoot things like randomly what if
I have more moons than I actually
need do they get like added to the next
world where where if like let's say in
the next World I also need like five
moons do I start off with
one first try of course it's per yes one
person says it's per
[Music]
world no they're just for
completion okay
then then I'm not going to do that next
time I suppose wait where is
the
wait
[Music]
Mama Mia can I get a mama M can I get a
uh
M I just walked off no well you must
[Music]
understand what
there that looked like I was going to
make it what is this what is this room
do I get another Moon here oh is this
what you guys told me like I could still
find oh yeah why am I doing this why am
I doing this I can already
leave
why am I doing
this like I'm playing two Mario games at
the same
time oh oh yeah do the job for me yeah
yeah yeah you do it oh yeah this is how
you
play this is how you play a Mario game
you use your enemies to your
advantage uh keep your enemies your
friends close keep your enemies closer
or something like that
right yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah okay okay I almost fell I almost
fell oh thank you guys okay I should
probably turn off the super chats holy
moly but will I will I no Will i Am no
no
Fergie what what she talking
about what what my choice I can only go
back
[Music]
then let's
go
[Music]
no well at least we get a
moon wait perception death
perception let me send one
to okay okay see I don't want people to
miss out cuz it's like limited time so I
guess I'll I'll just leave it
on cuz I don't want you to miss out
they're limited time and they're limited
edition oh thank you for the heart I can
get it the second time let's
[Music]
go we're at 97 w
already o like last time when I signed a
lot that already felt a lot to me I
think oh wait what is there what is
there oh oh
that I think I think I think I'm playing
it the right way not leaving
immediately but like being
C oh
oh I'm alive I'm alive oh I found
something else what the [\h__\h] is
that what is this why is that an empty
picture frame yeah
[Music]
why know what I think you're supposed to
like in the Mario game like ideally you
will try to find more than just what
meets the
eye what is this something for later
post
game oh
n what with the Scarecrow
anyway doesn't seem to be working oh
there's a [\h__\h] Moon there it's time
limited
time can I get it can I
oh W and now I fall down the water
because oh my God oh my oh my oh my god
oh water strong but I'm stronger
did I get this one already oh yeah I did
okay now let's go to the ship we have
plenty of
moons did I find all of
them yet or
no it says I need one more Moon I bring
him four now break it and make it
explode from the overload of moons
because I can't
math not even close there what
50 what okay I'm not doing all of them I
am not going to
[Music]
do you heard it here folks how yeah wait
there're 50 in one level like
this what what Odyssey is restored let's
go oh it looks cute in
color
oh
o see flat earther isn't this an insult
to you flat earther how you like that
huh how you like
that the Earth is round as [\h__\h]
yeah look at this this is proof Mario
says it Nintendo says is
it check made Flat
[Laughter]
Earth flat ERS can't even play Mario
games
now it's Photoshop it's CGI yeah I mean
this is
yeah but still I like ass says
la
imagine Flat Earth ver yeah making their
mod and making this globe flat for their
own liking their own
preference Super Mario Odyssey four flat
Earths yeah I'm sure lapas is also a
supporter of not flat ass but round
ass
that's just 2D
[Music]
Mario I think even in 2D Mario the earth
looks kind of
round if there ever is a an earth like
this I'm a pop-up figure nice you can
put them
together
[Music]
yeah round G
no since Adam was to and had a round
Moon there you
go sand Kingdom why don't you take the
helm just select sand Kingdom press a
okay there it is let's go let's
pickle let's ble let's
[Music]
ble take
off
thank you
oh
W Imagine The Comedy of it suddenly
dropping oh sorry we're
dropping it
wasn't ready to go after all he need you
need 50 moons after all
waa I'm a
captain
Ali thank you are you guys like happy
now is everybody getting the PO awards
that they
want we're not going to get much more
right you guys are you guys are like
done right with sending super chats
right everyone gave their order already
right no cuz I'm poor okay okay I I
appreciate that oh I like this
interior so how you like me as a
captain's hat pretty classy w't you
say now then where were we that monster
Bowser well we'll chase him down in no
time with the Odyssey seeing as how
we've got some time to kill and some
mobs enemies to kill have to review some
useful skills travel tip ground
pound now you tell me here about the
ground
pound okay SM to smash BLS or enemies
below you or to flatten out bumps in the
ground nothing beat the
ground nothing be to ground says
armor is this
where this is this
is
oh
oh oh my
god oh
oh oh you have no idea how my head just
exploded like
the universe thing
W I thought I don't know I don't know
I don't know what why what I thought I
thought maybe she came up with it
herself or
so I'm it copied it from Mario
Sasa
yo demoted no I I'm already demoted with
my actions from the Among Us stream
although I don't know I also protected
her I also tried to protect her by
saying don't kill her right
away
the beginning of everything holy [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h]
pickle holy
[\h__\h] oh my god wow I I don't know wow
this is too much information for me this
is like mind breaking holy
[Music]
[\h__\h]
don't kill her proceeds to kill
her it could have been anyone it could
have been
anyone that was you know just
random oh God the super chats oh God the
super chats I'm suffering from success
did you guys like the the Jimmy Super
Chat that I made I found a a a Super
Chat generator but it it's like Japanese
only
so it only makes it in Japanese and but
it's cute I made a Jimmy Super Chat I've
got too much power
now maybe that's where the the the
lesbian no more lesbian super chat came
from sorry my app is like doing
Shenanigans it locked me out
again jenma are you watching
still what the [\h__\h] is going on like
sometimes it's just weird I don't want
to type in my password again [\h__\h] no I'm
going to switch app say goodbye to the
Hat say
goodbye I'm going to
switch do a little switch
to kind or maybe oh sometimes this
happens when they update it and then
they don't let us know about the update
until like the next day to up to
download the new new
application
so I'm going to use the other one now
because I guess right now it's like
nighttime in
Japan
[Music]
oh I'm going to go for default outfit
and then I can't attach it but I'll put
it
up uh I'll put it on the hat
anyway jump
my default
Wawa oh she
exists she egg
assists
[Music]
t
okay Bal yeah wait for it uh where is
the Mario
hot mar mar
Mario
Mario Mario Mario
Mario where did I put my Mario
[Music]
hat
[\h__\h] I have uh
uh I see a different
[Music]
one I feel so empty
yeah Mario Mario what's the Mario hat
file name
Mario uh res you know what we really
want uh uh I don't know I don't know I
don't want to know
Mario can't find it this Mario hat
always gets
lost it's it's just always somewhere
where I can't find
it
well
okay
deal with it deal with
it there's a new one on Twitter what do
you mean a new hat did blue make me
one or what what you oh oh it wasn't
even blue who made me one oh but it's
not a PNG it's not a PNG I have to make
it into a PNG by
myself all by
myself
oh it's basically my Beret with the with
the eyes
on I'm going to do it all by
myself I'm going to make it into a
PNG it looks really high
quality too bad I can't put it on
properly today though uh o this oysy hat
do
[Music]
PNG uh you know it takes a while to get
to where we need to
go in this ship look at
this made by SE
poooo SE poooo s e a p u p u thank
you I've got a new hat oh nice nice nice
nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice
nice well then let me take off my
hat new
hat new hat let's go let's [\h__\h]
go
yeah [\h__\h]
yeah
exciting new
hat okay now we're ready to continue
with a fresh hat not stinky old hat was
stinky this hat good Mario possessed wa
yeah I'm currently possessed can you pin
it your head no because like the app
where we can do that is falling apart
right now okay use it and we have
another app where uh which is more
stable in a way but it doesn't have the
accessory
feature um you know so I'm using that
right now because it just kept on
breaking so whatever maybe next time it
should be working
again she the mustache now a mustache
okay next time next time next time I'll
dress up more okay the spash BL enemies
below nothing it's a grand nothing me
the ground
pound Oh Come you
thank you press that l in midair to do a
ground p and pulverize with your post
posterior is that a nice word for
butt
posterior fried screw oh my God
guys
y yo yo y y
y I don't even want to look at the Super
Chat
amount thank you guys guys ZL in midair
ah so crouch in the
air okay okay okay no no no leave me
alone with
that I you per
peruso just open the menu blah blah blah
we should discard the sand Kingdom
too H as you have no doubt to piece
together it is entirely covered in sand
[\h__\h] no all my homies hatte s and as you
can imagine it gets quite hot amazing
there's some ruin there and an artifact
called The Binding band that links
people forever like a wedding ring
oh and this Bowser seems like just a
sort of crep that would steal a PR
prices Antiquity Antiquity for his sham
wedding a thank you guys so please
stop please stop I will probably do it
in in several rounds again oh
wait that's like that's the like the the
the the Mexican thing
right that's the Mexican
thing yeah I know from that movie
yeah uh the the the Festival of like the
the the the dead people and then all
these colorful houses and the people
wearing the sombreros but they're dead
cuz they skelet
yeah that Pixar movie
yeah that's what that reminds me of cuz
I already saw the enemies with our
skeletons with the
sombreros yeah
yeah yeah is that not a reference to it
here I'll show you huz huz huz indeed my
friend oh I see you you've watched the
the great mmm I decare the maiden voyant
of the Odyssey the complete success um
but why is it so cold I thought deserts
the deserts were supposed to be hot the
top of that Tower is shining but how
could that be could it be a power Moon
yeah let's go let's go check it
out let's check out this
Festival he runs his tippity tappity
sounds are so
cute
look who is this not a reference
I can't kill him oh is is he
friend everything is Frozen all of a
sudden
ah oh no there there's people in friends
oh wait they have shaved
eyes okay it's kind of a Japanese
thing Frozen to the four wait can I have
some
ice oh oh sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
wait there's crazy cap there's
hats wait SL me get hat I also got a new
hat so Mario deserves a new hat too can
I get us some BR what the what why is
there Nintendo's
dog why is there a Nintendo
[Music]
dog
nice my Nintendo dog wasn't able to do
that
o I can actually switch oh give me
hat heyy we accept two kind of coins the
coins and the
coins you can use coins anywhere but
coins only right here hey o
oh oh it's not that expensive oh we can
go
n no way why are those the most
expensive ones why is it more expensive
to be n no
[Music]
this is a crazy outfit
yo sand Kingdom power Moon I can buy a
power Moon well I think that's like
something for completionist I don't
think I'll do that this hard to my
maximum oh I need this yes yes yes my
maximum heart containers please I'm like
on the bridge of dying all the
time oh thank
you what do you have
some bread W I like this outfit oh oh
this is for CI what is this a
[Music]
sticker oh wait what what would I need
this for can I build my own world let's
buy I'm
sure okay okay I'll go get
more I need purple coins the the
triangle coins
though
okay I'm I'm on a
mission I am on a
mission oh
flower W oh
wait it's so
cute this falling effect is so cute I
like it oh
hello have do you have some coins for
me you ever get lost you had four bright
glowy light okay oh that's it okay AR
shock
oh it gives me coin everything gives me
coin except for this C
oh oh kute Ked Ked I like how can how I
can touch everything oh oh there's a
there's a rocket in there how do I make
it warm maybe at some point it will be
warm oh
oh oh can can I heat it up with this
electricity wait oh how do I leave how
do I leave oh no how do I leave I want
to leave
here no let me go let me go let me go
that
out thank
you
ooh
nice there's a
hund
no ah
another
interesting exciting so am I played this
game really early did
she if if that phrase came from this
game she must have played it really
early on huh 2020 yeah I feel like I
like barely remember that it's been too
long
swee
a yes oh I can make
[Music]
flower long time ago I love how am plays
Mario
games I watched some of her Mario games
especially Super Mario Sunshine I like
to watch her Super Mario Sunshine
streams there a PR in the party room but
to find it you have to feel it walk
around feel the rumble let it move you
to the price it ribon
game feel the rumble I feel I do feel a
rumble I guess it's
stronger
[Music]
oh it's kind of stronger here but like
what am
[Music]
I going to do there maybe ground p
nothing beat the ground
[Music]
pound it's pretty strong
here you know it's the
strongest around
here
[Music]
slowly no
really
okay I was always pretty close okay okay
oh thank you my first one oo
I got it I got it I got
it oh I wa
the there's a power Moon here too what
the
hell I already got two okay move that's
a oh wait that's the that is the amount
there's not 50 power Moes here
huh wait I'm not sure I see amount I
will
need or the amount that there
is that's the minimum need okay oh I
found a few more
coins I only need to go to next Aron not
the M okay okay okay
n makes sense oh
oh there's a lock on here can I go in
that's like I party that's what we say
anyway but you had and clo need like a
okay okay okay okay will I get in if I
dress
appropriately that was my plan anyway so
uh I have 14 coins now I think that
might be
enough secret oh wait oh what wait that
didn't even noticed that when I was on
the other
side so can I buy from here you
surprised you scared the [\h__\h] out of me
on the shop use the front door please
yeah okay
[Music]
sorry you didn't know about it really
wait but like that one's pretty obvious
if you actually look at your
surroundings I guess but I didn't see it
either Mama M wait let me get that
coin okay wait
hey
no come on the middle the middle hit the
middle yeah
oh a the top ones I already
got now we can buy a cute
outfit I want this one this
Sombrero yes
please thank you Chase now
yes cute I can't wait to put it on yeah
it's so cute the P are so
cute no oh no I want to oh sorry I just
want to wear it now
bye-bye cute I think that's the best
outfit I can get
here probably they would already let me
in with just one piece of attire I would
assume but cute it oh my God it's so
colorful
m one piece one
piece why why one
piece who what who who was it what what
what was it with this by the way did it
grow a bit more than before I feel like
it did also he's
freezing what's at that flow maybe I get
another of those seats
eventually and then if I have all three
of them let me in
Snappy hat check Nancy Pono double check
you ready to party head oh I mean I'm
not a fan of parties but I want to be
part of
this you dance you dance and you dance
and I dance how to dance
[Music]
oh
oh w w wow I got a I got
a moon of of course I got a moon I got a
moon for
[Music]
everything let
go
nice
B nice
[Music]
okay let's move
on what the [\h__\h] how do I help
him I can break the smaller ones but I
can't break this big
[Music]
one at least not for
now I saw the craziest Couple come
racing past on their way to the runes I
fig they're still out that way okay
they're not a real couple okay don't
call them a couple don't you didn't you
see how peach was
struggling bows his Footprints
really maybe upgrade
head oh I wonder if that's a thing
totally a real cou
mhm merry christas I wish you nothing
but the best thank you I appreciate that
long jump oh I know how to do that I
know how to do
that and then I roll
oh the
[Music]
BTM
nice can I do something with this
no
yeah toast to toast Arina ruins entrance
all right we got the checkpoints we're
safe to go can I ground P this
hey my in
tuition checky check heck heck let me
check Oh I thought I could look through
it oh wait I Wrong Side let me
look oh I I need to become
[Music]
oh o what
desert bird flying they probably want me
to become the bird somehow somehow it
gives me bad
feelings but for no particular reason of
course no not not familiar at all not
familiar I don't know why that would
feel bad or or anything like that
[Music]
mhm double
kill oh
nice oh
nice what the get out of the way give me
those purple coins although I feel like
I wouldn't want to buy anything else
anyway but just well get them who knows
what I could use them
for no no no no no no no no don't worry
I know I know what to
do hey well only one coin this time
[Music]
lame damn I'm going to become so rich
for this game so much money to get
y
[Music]
F
no okay I really appreciate the that in
Mario Kart but in this game they're
stressing me
out can't look at
everything oh thank you oh okay well
just again as we said
before got to keep why did I jump I
could have sent my hat got to keep your
friends close but your enemies closer
and use them to your
[Music]
advantage okay please no
no let me get back please I can probably
ride wait can I become
them I
can oh
B oh to I can become anything except for
these
Goombas and bullets
yeah just like in Mario
Kart
yo come
here oh power moon in there I didn't
expect
that bey bey bey
[Music]
can I jump on that part
too no not really
okay that's
fine did you guys see the schedule for
this week people said oh hype hype hype
I actually I was kind of nervous about
putting the schedule out because I
thought there's a lot of short streams
on
there but oh
finally the uh design stream with eni is
back which is I think something that
people were hoping for and I was don't
worry I was also hoping for
it
y here we
go where are we going now let's go back
oh no it's
com okay we're down here now so we're
going to be
designing uh I think casual outfits for
Advent just like we did for Council back
in the day I say Council still
okay I say Council still because um uh
because back then it was without Iris
right oh wait did we design outfits for
Iris I don't think we did it was only
Council oh my God so many coins wait did
I not get these before they just come
back again and
again and the heart
too
[Music]
okay okay
okay oh oh wait what oh we did include
her
oh oh you're right I kind of turned her
into a
Barbie now I remember yeah I made her
Barbie iris is a Barbie girl in a Barbie
world who who does this Wawa who runs
after the coins instead of just going
the other way
me it could have been so easy but surely
there's a secret here that I'm going to
be happy about finding no it's just
stairs
up panic uh yeah so uh ah we haven't
started working on it yet cuz uh Ena is
going to make bases like NY bases again
for us to draw on top on so I'm waiting
for that but it's okay I think I just
need like one day I think the designs
last time I
also was able to do pretty
fast all right let's
enter and yeah tomorrow is a special
stream that's not on my
[Music]
channel it's going to be on go mak's
virtual YouTuber
Channel I will tweet it out so don't
[Music]
worry so you guys should hopefully not
miss out on it but it's going to be
mainly Japanese I mean probably only
Japanese so
excuse
me okay
no oh is there Moon
oh no way okay
oh basically I'm I'm so honored to be
invited though um basically I was
invited because I kind of like more or
less signed up to become a friend of
hers oh
wait yeah I want to go
here ni
that's yeah yeah yeah and um like she's
doing a stream where I guess some of the
people who signed up for
that um I think we're going to tell her
about youtubing stuff and this and that
I think uh we'll see you'll
see it's probably going to be like
typical typical collab length like 1
hour and and it's going to be it's going
to be probably I'm going to be like uh
nervous oh no fall damage
but I'm hoping to make connections with
her because you guys don't even
understand like what kind of a legend
she
is where do I go from
[Music]
here
she used to be a really active Idol
really successful really famous in Japan
now she's a
vtuber just for fun
because AG catches up with everyone at
some point I guess she did say like you
know stuff like
that and yeah it's like she's entered my
world and now
now I am going to take advantage of
that yeah I'm I'm I'm the sa but I'm not
going to even I don't have the audacity
to act like that like I am your saite no
no no no what do we do about this toxic
[\h__\h]
huh a secret passage goes up there it's
underground so they say
oh okay but what about the the bottom
bumps how do I get to those I need like
a bullet but there's no bullet here oh
what oh there's a seed here so far
back
to surely I'll get a moon for those
flowers then if it's so much uh work to
get them to the right
place imagine if she calls K sire I'm
going to no I cannot even let that
happen I'm not worthy you guys need to
watch like clips of her concert of her
performances back in the
day damn she's such a goddess like
wow oh it's growing it takes a while
huh takes a
while come
on oh I can oh I can eat it like that
too how long was she in idle for very
very very very long I don't know by
heart but very
long also started very young don't even
get me started with my idle tangents
[Music]
again oh man it's so
crazy it's so crazy to collab with
someone like that like in my mind she's
an absolute
Legend and I wish one day maybe maybe I
can are you going to lead me
somewhere maybe one day oh oh it
disappears we can even I don't know
dance and sing together that would be
insane that would be insane that would
actually be
insane what are you doing here oh it's a
Koopa and D you up for a challenge
everyone loves walking right problem is
most don't take it seriously that's what
what Trace walking is all about if you
can walk like a champ you'll win a prize
walk like a champ Trace walking what is
that oh just walk around and follow the
arrows oh okay like it's about accuracy
here's the fun part though that I was
disappeared oh it's like that Circle
game that I watched L
play so I have to make a good
Circle
yeah do will I see my oh will I see my
footstep no it's already
no I got to just stay stable like this
oh that's pretty
good
ah no I don't know does this give me 80
points let's do it again let's do it
again keep your mustage up my man you'll
get it next time I will I will I will I
will
let's try it again I don't even have to
like pay anything to do this
[Music]
easy okay how do
you I
don't
ah nah this is worse this is probably
worse ah [\h__\h]
ah oh yeah I mean
actually again the same thing
okay is there like a is there a
trick outside the last Bush right yeah I
need to remember like the the the marks
behind the bush right in front of the
Bush
okay
oh no this decent yo yo just that last
curve was a little bit too tight 96
points almost 100 oh w w wow
wow the Moon is
mine yeah thank
you I am proud I'm the proud owner of a
piece of the
moon woohoo what is over here I didn't
think I would find
oh real Tim Allen moment I didn't think
I would find something
here
woohoo what this here
for what is this place
anyway so weird let me read this course
you
know C jump hold I can jump on it can I
not uh hold on way after throwing and
your cap will spin a little bit for a
little while run into the cap and you'll
take a big bounce of oh
yeah big jump oh I shouldn't let go
huh I don't know if I'll be using
that I don't know about that uh what is
these another checkpoint this place is
kind of like I mean this whole map is it
feels kind of weird like how there's
like these areas so so far away from
each other so separate
too it feels like I'm I'm not supposed
to I'm not where I'm supposed to be
right now oh
[\h__\h] wait did it go get
smaller why did I get it at the second
jump oh no oh
what I thought I would control him I get
a
moon Two Moons in such a short amount of
time what okay well I prefer it that way
I didn't want to control the bird in a
desert oh is this ice I
baby I think this one I can break
no
no oh for
real oh oh
buddy what's his name
again oh what is this bus
station oh that's a cool bus
station that side oh
what that's not a moon what is
that
oh thank you guys birthday and oh well I
normally don't read uh super I I don't
read
these no
way
no wait I can just shoot
yep no h
redo so sing for you now because you
guys when you send these for the for the
polars please don't assume that I'll
actually like be reading it on a stream
um because normally I
won't so if you want like something
extra like that you should probably
count on it another
time yeah I don't read those normally
cuz like I spent like offc screen I
spend like hours uh writing
them but if I find something like that
while I'm writing it I might um
introduce it in a following Super Chat
reading cuz I'm nice like
that no you're probably going to moon
out of this but I say [\h__\h]
no actually it's it doesn't even take
that much time no I feel like maybe I
can do it can I climb up from here
okay
I can do
this no
no
no go back and this one EAS
no I hate
it oh hat jumping makes this one easier
that
jumping
[Music]
what
what that's
[Music]
mean no I hate it no I hate it
no the spin a deck I know I wanted to
try that yeah
but okay okay okay okay I keep on like
trying to give up on it but you guys
keep on like saying do it do
it don't don't jump off
[Music]
okay okay yeah wait get for getting up
there I probably need to do the the Hat
um throw jump
[Music]
okay
uh no no
no on the last [\h__\h]
[Music]
second that was difficult I was like I
was panicking I was shaking the
controller like crazy
okay somebody said something about use
the map how do I no how do I use the map
no thank you Game for not telling me
about the map you can select any
checkpoint flag you activated and then
press a to fly straight to it okay then
let's go here
maybe cuz it's so far
away y fast travel okay but we've been
there maybe maybe we shouldn't be here
but like
go
the ah great great thank
you okay wait I wanted to talk more
about like my schedule and stuff so
tomorrow we're doing the one with Mak
which is exciting and then the rest of
the day I'll probably be doing uh more
work on my sock puppets because when I
was was making them already knew that
it's very unlikely that I'll be getting
my sock
puppets when I W and when I need them so
I just kind of slowed down a little bit
I
guess so I'll finish them tomorrow
because the day after tomorrow
surely ah I'll have what the [\h__\h] where
did I where did I go I'll have access to
the post office I
think oh
then it will be open
again yeah I honestly don't know where
to go next keep going up up up up up
where wait I think I
found
oh what about over
there I don't know how to go more
up uh what was I
saying oh yeah and and then the ENA
stream shieldy and Thea will be there as
our judges I thought you know shieldy is
such a stylish edgy
kid that she would be perfect for that
job oh wait what
about that's the the moon right I don't
need it again
sorry and Nissa just
because why not I mean can never have
enough
narissa
I mean there's surely a proper way like
over
here then let's go this
way H I bought one of the judges oh no
no no no ideally they
ah ideally they wouldn't
know I don't know was it obvious last
time who made which outfit I don't think
it was too obvious and honestly I really
don't think they were um influenced by
that at all I think they just like why
would they
even I'm I'm confident in the girls that
they will judge it just by really what
their
preference of clothing
is I still love the outfit that I for
Bales so
much
heyo hey yo wa
gaming oh what's this oh
secret
[Music]
oh oh I'm faster and them yby
okay
interesting a there's a platform
there
great yeah and then we have
a no no we have another collab on the
day after it will be a lethal company
collab yeah Pomo invited me f ah no I'm
going to die here
no
wait I just noticed I got the sombrero
outfit
now I'm going to die no wait for me oh
okay now I have a good timing I think
yeah yeah yeah okay okay please tell me
there's no boss fight up there cuz I'm
kind of dead yeah looks good looks
good yeah leave company I'm going to
take a look at it with this
collab yeah and we'll see I asked Pomo
if it's like really scary she said like
if anything it's like maybe about as
scary as
um uh
uh blah blah blah phobia what was it uh
the game that we played a lot of times
uh phasmophobia and thing it's like that
but not really that scary more like
dorky so I was like okay I mean I don't
really want to you know turn it down cuz
it's a cute idea she asked if we can do
like a with narissa
[Music]
n Isa if we can do uh what the [\h__\h] the
what what is that okay okay okay
okay uh uh yeah and like a two nii girls
to two H it hurts me
too oh wait move okay I need you Holo
collab so then I actually I asked for I
asked for airra yi
cuz you know I I do like her and she's
uh she likes tailes off games too she
played them before um she even showed up
in my stream recently
remember I really like her she's cool I
like her singing oh my oh my oh
my oh my
God oh my oh my God so I was really
hoping that it will come true that was
so difficult
okay let's ignore like all these coins I
don't need them
again T no don't blame the
tangent tangent is
good so Leal company if I like it maybe
I'll join another lethal company collab
sometime if I don't like it then that's
the one time I'll be playing it but you
know for for a
collab I don't want to turn it down
because like oh mean one time like why
the hell not
I'm happy I was invited you know the
girls the Holo girls like C and so on
once we had lethal perms they like why
did I do that maybe I need it actually
they immediately started planning all
these Neil company collabs but I was I
think I was really busy didn't have time
for it and wasn't sure wasn't sure if
I'd like the game anyway so I just kind
of stayed out of
it and oh I think it's also because like
when when they started like planning it
um I already had a set schedule that was
like really packed and I didn't want to
squeeze another stream in there that I
didn't already had planned you know
that's that's the biggest reason why I
didn't
participate a piece of a power Moon oh
there's
pieces cut my moon into
pieces I do need four
more
[Music]
once you have all five together it will
be a big full
moon
spicy nice nice Papa
Roach cut my moon into
pieces what is that
thing Bower was just stomping can I what
is this can I
stomp what does it
do wait
what put on take
options secret paths but I can't go
there with you can
I oh wait so maybe there's secret paths
in that other section
[Music]
too
I the wrong
button
here
a become be
boo
nice so I don't see anything more on
there but maybe you see some
more nothing new
here
no is that platform secret too no or
maybe I don't need them
anymore
oh that's just a normal coin
right
M for
real wait that what do you call oh wait
there's a piece here what do you call
these
things like uh I know in Japan I I I as
Shibuya station there's one of these
things a yeah okay moo moai muai
statues
oh funny how they integrate them here oh
well I'm just going to guess it's a
straight path thanks burbs for helping
me
out yeah please just be straight path
okay maybe I should have looked up but
seems
good all you
[Music]
wait is there no path
there no
connection what did I miss wait dude
dude dud d d
dude I can't oh I guess I can bring him
here but what if I just look
up oh from the middle platform I can go
straight and then okay that'll do
Merry Christmas thank you thank you
thank
you you know what um at the end of the
stream I'll just look over the super
chats really quickly and and just like
breeze over them with my eyes and see if
there's anything that needs to be
answered like any
questions but generally with these just
know that you get the Polaroids but they
won't be
read I will not read them out loud on
stream I will be reading them off stream
though oh what is this flower over
there why is it
there thank you T you're welcome oh wait
I found the last
one is
[Music]
this ooh and now we get the full one
let's go oh nice and I only need three
more and I don't even know where to what
place I'm bringing it to I haven't even
found the place where I need
to bring them over
here there probably a bonus level on the
LED oh
maybe oh I just bring him back to the
ship oh okay
show down on the invert pyramid oh what
they're already telling me to go to the
boss find
oh oh okay I'll think about
[Music]
it Peach you got to wait
sorry I have some more things to check
out
a I guess from here is there a secret
path here too
[Music]
probably
not probably not ah it's h still frozen
U maybe after the boss fight these
Frozen things will become unfrozen
maybe what's
this what's
this what is
this yeah
cuz I already I already smashed
something there oh oh wait why did I
leave there's more than one platform
like this oh don't switch I just feel
the urge to switch cuz like often that's
what they want you to
do there's another moonbird above
me ow
unnecessary very
unnecessary Peach wait I found something
interesting again I'm distracted
again let's
go that's
pickle what the [\h__\h] is this ooh
control
okay ooh they even have lights
on doesn't hurt at
[Music]
all is this the right path o maybe
not no [\h__\h]
way
I might go
back with this
one cuz I don't know yeah that seems
like a dead
end I am stupid I know I'm
[Music]
stupid
let's
go o they they're slide they're so
[Music]
slippery okay have to take that into
account okay now Wawa does it the right
way because Wawa is not stupid after all
oh no
no sorry but that point of view is kind
of
[Music]
difficult yeah
B it's slippery everything's so
slippery
no I can
oh I can change it I thought it was kind
of
set fixed in this
case I don't even have to come back here
kind
of not work
no M actually let's get a new one
okay now we go back but we might want to
switch again over here cuz I don't trust
this one to make it all the
[Music]
way nice and the next one oh no
no I accidentally left the bullet
no I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm
sorry I
suck
no um I'm rushing I shouldn't be rushing
just
[Music]
chill
what
what why did I
crash I don't
understand
okay
Wawa okay seems we need to be slower
okay okay I thought I had to be faster
because the walls seem very
fast can I go game over just by dying
too often like game game
over no okay good
P five thank you
D I feel like I would be more open to
like shaking my controller if I was
using joycons and not the Pro
Controller all right we can go slow huh
uh which way let's go this
way ooh not close
oh there it
[Music]
is that's good for us Europeans oh thank
you you could have flip your circadian
RI honestly my my sleep schedule is so
[\h__\h] anyway like I I probably could
you know [\h__\h] it up even more and stream
for na audience and sometimes I wonder
if that would have been the right thing
to do oh do I have to come back here
again later now maybe I don't have to
because who cares about the
scare um
um but
like I don't want to make it completely
impossible for me to do stuff during the
daytime
so yeah I
think even if
my CCB is like lower because I stream
during European
time I prefer just yeah streaming during
this time and keeping us somewhat
healthy why is there
sheep
sorry someone help me sleep schedule and
lifestyle why is there a human being
over there what the hell and he's got a
car why I mean I guess Mario is a human
too but like this is a different kind of
human I've never seen a full-sized human
before in a Mario
game there's a triple Moon over
there well you should be at least
talking normally
though why does he look so
realistic the first game I think yeah
probably us Europeans are grateful for
you're welcome yeah I mean I've been
hoping to like grow a European Audience
by streaming during the European
time um for so long now but I don't know
it's just like European market not
really like paying attention to Whole
Life much I guess or it's just me maybe
they just don't care about me in
particular that's okay I have a couple I
have a handful of European viewers um uh
and that's fine yeah the twitch simcast
thing I I need to try that maybe 2024 I
can look into it after my break uh right
now I don't really want to use my brain
for that here in
Italy there aren't many people
interested in V yeah yeah I know I know
it's just generally like a I don't know
I think I think there's like potential
but it's just like it hasn't quite
reached Europe just yet still even now
I'm from Africa oh hello thank you for
keeping us company at this time
yeah you're welcome I mean I I know that
you know still my biggest audience is na
even though I stream during the
shittiest times for
na your na viewers will try to love you
twice as much thank
[Music]
you yeah I appreciate it
than as long as you cover ignores you
you will ignore
cover well
well
well yeah your vision would have been
great but not happening uh I said it
during a member stream but it's not
happening um which is fine I'll try
again next
time think of the animated emotes you
could have yeah that's really something
that's catching my attention but I feel
like YouTube eventually will add
animated emotes at some point I feel
like they
would I what what are you saying I've
got a customer waiting but from the
looks of this mess I'm not going
anywhere anytime soon are we just going
to ignore the fact that he looks like a
human just going to ignore
it no way why are these some of these
are so easy to get it feels
wrong oh a tire
oh is is this his
like is this the stuff that was in his
car
partially his existence raises so many
questions will they not be
answered what is this can I do something
with oh oh I can talk to it B talks GS
traveler and to your hat as well can you
answer my riddle what does the thiefing
Bowser monster desire from this
land a ring
basically ding dong yeah of course of
course yeah that was not really much of
a riddle oh thank
you it's so nice of you what's in
here is this a
trap what the eating
this I mean I don't know like don't
pyramids have traps and all that you
[Music]
know it's
real it's not a trap wait now I got the
full amount that I need
[Music]
y I can buy the naked costume I don't
want
it he he would freeze even
more poor
Mario
where is this ah it's here
a oh
go so should I
go there's still some interesting things
but what is
that he's dancing should I just go over
there
now the time is
they're inside oh man peit come back to
me come on use your superpowers use your
magic I know you got it in
you inside the inverted pyramid well
thank God my controls are not
[Music]
inverted
thank you for the Super
Chat Mario making a lot of cash in game
W making Cash Out game
wow
okay Merry Christmas guys I hope you
guys had a good Christmas I hope you got
some know presents maybe cuz you deserve
it Y what oh that inverts
me oh I can walk up there oh that really
confused me for a moment
W
interesting I like this
mechanic ah it will already be empty
when I get back to
it ah ah
whatever wo oh that's so cool I can
Crouch oh I forgot about
that I mean I forgot that that would
help me there that I would get small
enough for it didn't consider
it it's too quiet
here you know it was just Christmas but
you guys realize this Sunday is New Year
[\h__\h]
I need
water wait a
second I got curious about
something is this a secret it
is
wow there's a moon here
too yeah so I ended up streaming both on
the 24th and the 25th even though that
wasn't orig orig the
plan I was going to take off to 24 but
because of that I decided I'll just take
the full 31st
off um I was planning on spending time
with my friends celebrating and looking
at fireworks with my friends
a
and I don't know when they'll come yet
we haven't really talked about it that
properly yet oh you come out of it
too so I just like for safety going to
take the whole day off
so I hope you guys don't mind I will
stream on the first one though I think
pretty sure I will wait do I need
another
one seems like
it seems like it is there an opening for
more no I got a heart
container wait I need to bring that one
all the way over over is that even going
to
hold long enough maybe I got to ah maybe
I got to go fast hope you have a great
time with your friends your allow days
off for yourself you know yeah but I
don't know like I don't particularly for
myself normally I don't care
about sorry normally I don't care about
having these particular days off like I
don't I don't care like also if if if I
if I really want to celebrate
Christmas like why does it have to be on
the 20 uh 4th 25th anyway like I could
move it to the 26 if I really wanted to
the day doesn't really matter that much
I could I could just act
pretend that that was Christmas the one
that I feel like you can't really
pretend is New
Year's because then we'll be
fireworks
so can't really
pretend that one is time
sensitive speed speed
speed
ni I'm coming
Bowser
yeah but personally as I said I don't
care so I
mean it's it's nice to have like special
reasons good reasons to stream like you
know have themed screams so I like to
take that opportunity usual like
Christmas Stream New Year stream and all
that Valentine
stream it gives me a topic too and and a
reason to dress up or so or do like a I
don't know a themed VR stream or
whatever ever so generally I I like to
use that to my advantage so I like to
stream during those days oh hi Peach
you're so
small so small up
there how can I help
you I think it's too
late yep we got to deal with these
[\h__\h] ass
[Music]
hats we got the girl this time all
right she's
[Music]
bouny how do we fight
her oh can I become that Pokey spiky
ball oh oh
wait
that's oh okay somehow that that
work
bunk oh she became a
[Music]
youall oh wow okay just throw your hat
when in doubt throw your
hat m there we go here comes the big
[Music]
one no no let me jump on you [\h__\h] no
why why there we go last time she didn't
get up
[Music]
bch wait wait wait wait
wait no I I missed it
no she killed my rhythm cuz I once got
hit by
[Music]
it all right bring out the big
boy
[Music]
ow yeah nice
clamp easy clamp woohoo
[Applause]
yeah boss fights are kind of easy in
Mario games aren't they I mean I don't
want a jinxes but they generally
[Music]
are even for me like I suck at this game
generally did any of you guys
play the Pokemon
DLC cuz I watched my favorite let's
player my German let's player play it
and finish
it he still playing it it's interesting
yeah so there's two parts
right and so from what I've seene I
watch like the whole gameplay cuz I
can't play it on my stream so I just
watch
it oh there's a hole in the
desert that brutal slow us down a bit
but we're still racking up the power
moons ah how on inv pyramid is floating
and it's gotten so much colder it's just
more of that Bowser's doing I say he
does make trouble doesn't he okay let's
go there I'll walk I
think uh but
uh yeah going crazy
here what was I saying I want to say
um oh yeah the first
part of the DLC
apparently I I would
agree wasn't like that impressive on its
own but I've never seen D tendo so happy
about a um Super Mario and Super Mario
Pokemon game in a long
time combined with the second
DLC it's actually really good
and really
difficult like I haven't seen a Pokemon
game be this
difficult in a long time the
fights are really challenging in the
second
DLC
yeah even my even my let's play
Ori has been struggling a
lot so I find that
[Music]
fascinating Pokmon games like have been
so easy for such a long time but then
like
even
even such as experienced players are
struggling
so yeah like the the the the the fights
that you have in the second DLC the
second part of the DLC are actually
really challenging and they use like
strategies and they have really highly
leveled Pokemon and really strong
Pokemon so
yeah they're like competitive teams mhm
competitive
players so if you guys want to play
another difficult Pokemon game for the
first time in the million years
then I think this one's actually
recommendable yeah I mean
story-wise still like yeah it's all
right but the game play now
is challenging so
H it's more about Synergy than the
Pokemon just being powerful yeah yeah I
mean yeah I don't think they've ever
bought competitive play into the actual
story before yeah I don't I don't
remember it ever being this difficult
before so it was it was really fun to
see him struggle and for the first time
in ages give a Pokemon game like an
actual good
rating uh cuz like he plays so many
Nintendo games and like every every
Pokmon game but
yeah hasn't been able to say much good
about it in the past
years but this one this one it's just
nice to see someone be happy about a
game how come the hat is not pinned to
your onion head oh because the the app
where I can pin it onto it is kind of
broken for me today and this is a
different app where I can't do
it I really enjoyed
Aros that was my favorite Pokemon game
in the recent times if we're talking
like switch Pokemon
[Music]
games let's
go woohoo
[Music]
[Applause]
oh I wonder my
moons were they necessary to get in here
no right oh [\h__\h] that's so
slippery oh it will break it nice I just
jumped too early
no I need another
one
okay needed a bit more cook time oh yeah
a lot of these games need more cook time
cooking time they do but I still really
like AOS because it was so
different oh he does not he does not um
swe yeah they don't slip on ice what the
hell but how can I use that to my
advantage
[Music]
here no I killed him
a wait what do what was that for oh it's
making so
many big
rings did I just create endless
Rings oh oh yes give me those
oh thank you
Hallelujah
um no I lost one only one wait there's a
there's a there's a moon no
no so [\h__\h]
stupid these rings are really too much
for
me
okay we don't need to go there
again here we
go M get that sweet sweet money
back got to put them into my savings oh
wait this time it didn't do anything
this time it didn't activate the ring
okay
wait the Moon the Moon uh let me first
jump here again oh wait this time I
don't need the heart that's
okay this is where it is
oh
wait why am I too
short did I need the extra
Goomba no wait there's some up here
[Music]
hello
what and then we join see oh do I still
need the the first
[Music]
one right it looks like we can reach
yeah okay yeah cuz just the one would
not have been enough but those three up
there for
sure
oh
um Goomba token pole very
nice
oh
[Music]
nice
M would wouldn't it be funny I would
like it if we could like lay this whole
totem pole down like as a
bridge that would be cool
too oh wait no why did I do I could have
just jumped up from the Goombas well I
don't need them anymore
goodbye or do I oh yeah I don't think so
cuz that the floor is not slippery here
anymore
[Music]
anyway Merry Christmas thank you Richard
oh wait it breaks ah ah it breaks
my come here yes yes yes yes yes
yes was breaking my my my my my my my
why does it have a
hat my
Rockets
yumy well is good guys I saved
myself oh oh
wa ah ah no wait a okay I need another
[Music]
one no oh that was close almost got
hit slip slip slippery why am I so
slippery when there's no ice in the
air okay I made
it I missed the moon there I don't care
I have plenty I'm not a completionist
don't worry
not worth it oh deepest underground
wow damn guys this
world and this is this game is like a
couple years old already by
now looks really
pretty I want Pokemon games to look like
this that would be
dope this is the most polished switch
game yeah isn't it because it was a
release
Game and they wanted it
to be you know a good first
impression
are he
yo oh my God what is happening
yeah was a system seller I know I know
release Game almost release Game a okay
okay did you take ring no I didn't take
ring who was boun for that bastard no
wrong wrong oh yeah this one this one
break not
me not
me wait how do I get
up wait do I make the other hand break
the other hand it didn't seem to work oh
heart
heart to
too on my hat oh right my hat right me
yeah okay
wait here you
[Music]
go die please don't fall down okay it
sends me back to the middle very
nice
uh-oh
yum here here please
yles okay breaking on one of these
things right
no oh wait oh
yeah
okay in your
face
smash he must be questioning like why am
I punching myself why am I punching stop
punching
myself why can I not control my own
hand I got to clap oh no
oh no he got
[Music]
me no
way okay that was actually starting to
become a a challenging boss fight all
right good try thank
you try
again you guys
[Music]
don't oh yeah right I I can't go there
alone can
I he clapped something all
right while he was clapping me I was
clapping my butt cheeks clap clap clap
clap clap clap clap CL okay come here
now please I don't have time for this
all
day this was
important all right all right all
right we know the system now should be
easier
here ouch yeah that hurts doesn't it
those
[Music]
shards that'll teach
you try me come here
woo
W
oh here oh no I'm so stupid no no
[Music]
no okay I'll try to break a heart next
otherwise I'm going to
die go go go go go go go
oh
[Music]
oh I wish I could run
faster run faster feel so slow
sometimes I
can oh the rolling wait how do you do
that again
uh
like after that I can roll but I can do
it on its own too
right oh
well my
[Music]
coins oh I got it right
away
his face like no oh no oh no he's coming
for
me my actions have
[Music]
consequences oh clap it
clap
that didn't hurt oh wait it I HT both I
hurt both I wish I had two hats if Mario
only had two
hats surely that'll be a lesson to him
to get more hats so that he can control
more people more things this is why you
should have two hats yeah that's why I'm
superior
generally
[Music]
no
no are you offering me easy
mode okay it's not easy mode I think I
deserve
one of those things he's even selling it
he's not even giving it to me for
free oh thank you I I almost didn't take
it oh my God wait are these not forever
like the the blue ones
or are they like once I die they're gone
and then I'm back to
free
or it's not baby mode oh they're
temporary I thought I was getting them
[Music]
forever oh oh so I guess it's Baby Mo no
I thought it was like normal to get
more
oh but I'll do no damage run now anyway
so it's just for mental stability you
know
[Music]
you have
confidence is that going to disappear if
I don't collect
[Music]
it well I won't need to collect it
anyway so I don't care if it
disappears I don't need
it
uh-oh that doesn't count that doesn't
count that doesn't
count
hey
hey all right I did it okay one damage
is
acceptable yay yes I still got six
hearts that means no damage
[Music]
yeah yo so many
moons so many
moon I like they would look nice as a
necklace they surely sold it as a
merchandise didn't
they or like
keychains honestly would look pretty
cute what damage I have full health
exactly they still look like bananas I
guess so not very ripe bananas say oh
it's so hot now but I do suppose that's
where we were trying what we were trying
to accomplish if we keep up this pace
we'll catch up to Bo no time I don't
believe
that ah we do have enough it seems I
would say no but uh I am going to check
out some things now now that the ice is
gone looks like we've collected enough
we can make our way to the no
uh-uh no we're going to check out some
parts that are not icy anymore oh
what oh they're sparkling
now what I got a moon for each Oh I
thought I only got a moon if I get all
three of
them let's
go oh some are still like a little
bit I'm oh but oh I saved him I saved
them the ones that were stuck inside or
outside now nice what else was there
that I wanted to see once
it's okay no actually you know what
never
mind never mind never mind we'll we'll
go to the next world
because it's not supposed to be a super
freaking long
playr ah okay okay I do kind of care
about the human
a little bit the human was
like
maybe maybe somewhere over
there kind
of
where yeah close to the
pyramid well maybe he's already gone
maybe he already drove
off oh look at those zip
lines
is that really
faster wait he went to the
town so he did drive
off I love that sound hey y' what's this
oh that's how I can shoot myself up
there oh okay no never mind though I'm
good I'm good no I'm wait there's a
moon There's a Moon can I shoot myself
up there too
oh
[Music]
oh maybe oh maybe we can go up there
there there there treasure
chest I want to go to the treasure
chest yeah this place generally I I
still didn't figure it
out
maybe long jump I guess with a long jump
I could do these jumps but how do you go
up can I control
you
stop he's already
gone yeah yeah the underr H the
painting can if I go there now will
there be an actual
painting
[Music]
maybe will it be worth
it probably
not a gos are everywhere
now it was better when it was cold w
let's go to the town and talk to the
taxi guy that's all I want to
see W painting painting is on the
[Music]
pillar oh well
whatever it's not so important ah there
he is wait can I drive in your
car attack attack you pulled up finally
take me to the Metro Kingdom we sorry
about to hold up had some car trouble
you would not believe can't leave for
the Metro Kingdom yet though I promise
it'll get you there just got to decide
dice the ice the everything not the ice
now oh my God I should not be doing that
I'll just break your car even
more jaxie how are you doing I'm what
you call a jaxie you want to ride I'll
be 30 coins what you
say wait so you're like more useful and
that taxi right next to
you controls are snap break this bound
I'll take off as soon as you're strapped
in but what yourself I go quick am I
supposed to like do something specific
with
him who who who wo wo wo
wo can he go over the purple
stuff probably
not zooming
yo he can't
[Music]
bird you little [\h__\h] I'm going to eat
you there a
curve we need a big curve isn't there
even an
[Music]
opening we can go in there with him
m
y
y a he's so cute wait he's actually so
cute let's
go okay without the with the
dog okay this is quite the challenge I
see
already let's go Yoo
Yoo w
go
no no I'm so sorry do it's not a dog
though is it it's a lion right la
[Music]
la it's kind of
fun breaks are very important wa you may
never use them in Super Mario in Mario
Kart but let's a least use them in this
game what do we have in the middle what
what
[Laughter]
[Music]
this okay let
right
[Music]
no that's too difficult oh my God like
you you really have
to be ready for the straight line like
right away otherwise you're just like
juggling go I don't know if I want to
try it again
[Music]
oh
wait wait if you break really
[Music]
long okay
okay made it I made
it yo wait if I jump off of him he'll
stayer right
okay oh okay wait I thought that wasn't
really an option I thought it was over
when I leave him okay okay well then
that makes everything a lot more
chill are there checkpoints
ever okay no that kind of looks very
difficult
the Moon is saved there oh my God this
is
so
exciting I like it though I I like
[Music]
it having fun with the
lion let's
go thank you for the polar right order
oh my
God he's got the Zoomies this light on
got the
[Music]
Zoomies okay here I come
okay wait I'm not ready to go straight
ah
no what
not worth it not worth it just just
let's go to the lower
path why do I slap his
butt you know in German we say this is
[Music]
saying
do you say something like
this something like
[Music]
this just barely making it but like
directly translated barely uh scratching
the
curve means like baking barely making it
not baking
it
just break I don't think there's an
endless break
though I think endless break wasn't the
thing I tried it and then he eventually
just went uh and ran off I
[Music]
think oh wait I'm pretty straight
now let's go oh it was right at the end
anyway that was fun
ah the skin of your teeth
ahuh making it by the skin of my teeth
I've never heard someone say that before
funny
yo buy a hair
oh well now we know now we know how it
was possible to get in there oh but we
didn't get to the top
huh H well whatever I don't care go
next the pillar has a
painting it's
[Music]
okay it need 60 more I felt like what
what what you mean 16 more than I
already have but no I just have to give
it to the
Odyssey
I have plenty more than you could ask
for not going to get sticker for your
ship oh I don't know that's just a
collectible
[Music]
right the dog is outside the shop the
dog that I was just riding or the the
other
dog the other dog that was making
tricks spend your purple money yeah I
mean I guess what else are you going to
use it for
right well uh-oh we've hit a proverbial
fork in a ro which kingdom do you want
to do you think Bowser went to probably
the one that I'm not going to whichever
it
is there's a lake Kingdom and then
there's the wooded Kingdom I'll go to
the wooded
Kingdom Lake is easier L is easier
really I was thinking that was going to
be more difficult
[Music]
H what if the kingdom has poison what is
more fun but leg is e are
[Music]
open we'll see how much I
struggle can I still change my decision
later
on maybe
not can we get a new outfit too again
each
World wood has a
T-Rex
kid
Tiara wait her name is Tiara
oh she not she's not just a tiara she is
the
Tiara she is the she is
Tiara Tiara I have history with that
name
[Music]
and now with this Bing band he's got a
wedding ring and is he going to steal
the whole wedding seeing as how we got
some time to kill let's review some
useful
skills after throwing your caps shake
the Pro Controller again to perform a
homeing cap
for I already know that just don't use
it it's a choice it's a choice I
make giant Greenhouse D filled with
flowers is famous for his beautiful s so
bouquet ah he'll want the bouquet for
her I see I see I wonder what the other
world would
have ooh steam
Gardens
okay road to Sky
Garden okay I guess the purple stuff is
Po poison oh water PL wait do we hear
something no no not really do you hear
something that plant nice around here oh
look at
that my first purple ones purple
boys kicking the
stones did I find something over here
oh it's not a
[Music]
moon that would have been a sneakily
hidden Moon oh what is
this
oh what is this Domino
no take a picture of hint
art
no what is
his a hint for another time hidden in
the back of where you
spawn ah is it for the sand
[Music]
Kingdom okay well well
dinky
Cod did you guys enjoy the amus collab
by the
[Music]
way I think we had so much fun I just
felt it like I had a lot of fun but I
also I think I felt the others genuinely
have fun well do you have have a riddle
for
me I feel a little bit bad about amido
for real for real
I wanted to protect
her what does the Bowser monster want
from this Kingdom
flowers
yay that wasn't much of a riddle either
know was she amused
really I
wonder I just hope she didn't get like
sad because she couldn't play
much travel to backwards Som assault if
you're looking for the eest way to get
somewhere that I I kind of know how to
do that yeah yeah thank you thank
you is there something in here oh I here
uh normal jump can't reach
really what that's it that's
it
oh mic
I can't I can't walk over there can
I okay just leave the poison to me oh
you want me to throw oh wait you can get
rid of it a Super Mario Sunshine
Vibes oh nice [\h__\h]
music but yeah
amongus I'm glad so many were able to
participate I mean a full collab would
even greater but I feel like at this
point with this amount of
members
uh I think people shouldn't be expecting
it anymore because it's really difficult
and like some
members can be on a
break some members just don't like the
like certain type of
games I think
Shield I could have gotten her to
participate I feel like
[Music]
maybe but from what I hear she doesn't
really like these kind of games
anyway what what is it doing it has my
hat
[Music]
oh and yeah well like you know there's
circumstances there's all kinds of
circumstances so you know I
personally felt a little bit like
pressure like I didn't I I felt like I
didn't want to disappoint
people by not having everyone in the
collab cuz people were like opening for
it but it's just not feasible anymore
not very realistic anymore so I hope I
hope people understand ow what the [\h__\h]
oh it was the
po
die oh I got to go up there
[Music]
wait what if I jump
when no I don't get
it unless you make hor F yeah like I
mean for for stuff like that yeah surely
will we would be able to gather
[Music]
everybody but just like laabs that are
organized by a mere member like
me I don't have the
power
Yeah the more we get the more it's just
not really realistic
anymore
oh but we still had a big group and we
still had a lot of fun so I'm happy
with how it turned out and how fun it
was what the [\h__\h] is this hold be to
stretch
oo so so can I get
there wao oh I said how I was supposed
to get that oh
oh so it wasn't even realistic for me to
get
that ow no I'm dying
again why did I think of you was a
little bit more Invincible than
myself what is this thing oh it opens
things don't tell me you want to fight
[Music]
me wait I don't have my hat wait wait
where's my hat does the Scarecrow still
have it can I not get it
back that's bonus area no
hat there we go ah it's that easy okay
and we got a moon a blue moon this
time fire in the cave why fire in the
cave
why but yeah amus was nice
um like also so I wanted to ideally do
VR but maybe next year or like not even
for Christmas maybe for a different
occasion I'll organize
something with v cuz I
know I know how much people enjoy seeing
the H VR stuff
content well yeah amongus VR right I
forgot that that was a
thing
[Music]
M yeah
well in any case in any case that was
fun um I hope I hope every all the
viewers enjoyed
it I hope uh B's fans don't hate me
now
for for what I said to
B oh
wait no don't come here no
what I
died what happens in the stays in among
I I would hope
so wait what oh I didn't get those
before let me get them
now wait
woo and how do I intend on coming back
ah okay
game he sing the ISA was funny I was
really
scared she immediately got so
offended I think I can remember that for
the future if I sused her out and she
didn't get so
offended then she probably would have
been the impostor but her getting so
offended
h i see that's since she wasn't the
Imposter I can say that that is a tell
now that she is the
Imposter she was like what I talking
about ground pone jump oh I know how to
do ground pone jump let me to ground
pound
right why would I do that here also I
can be
lower
okay found something nice back start
it's a back start I don't know why she
got so surprised about
that Water Rising can I drown here oh
[\h__\h] oh
no oh no oh oh no oh oh no oh oh no no
no no no
no
there it is there she
goes am dead n to on oh I don't know
about narissa but foro yes and me too
though like oh I finally got impostor
once and of course I
crumble over under the pressure like no
one
else and of course I had to be imposter
with form the other worst
Liars but you know what I'm I'll say
it's a good quality to be a bad
liar yeah so it may not help me in the
game what the [\h__\h] there's so many
enemies oh there it is no I swear to God
that is not cool that
R
[Music]
rise the attempt gas like with be was
great I feel like if I was a better liar
I could have pulled it off
then but I'm
not cuz I mean who could say like Amed
was dead so she couldn't talk and say
that that's
wrong so it's one word against the other
word no one else saw but but I don't
understand why the others didn't vouch
for me I legit like we talked about it
like cuz I wasn't killing anyone and I
was like spending time with others alone
it's was like oh maybe you know they'll
trust me then it wasn't even on purpose
wasn't it was not even the goal not even
the intent
intention but I expected them to V for
me so
disappointed
was asking him I feel like I would have
even if I wasn't the Imposter I feel
like I would have asked for
that I feel like I would
have ah feel like that was pretty
realistic of
[Music]
me wa wait for me
no did you li to the police Le for a
friend what a friend you mean if they
did something and they asked me about
it y my friends wouldn't really do
anything like that I think but I don't
think I would have the issue but good
question I will not ask this for legal
reasons I will not answer this for legal
reasons I look get in
trouble I want to get in trouble oh I
broke the
nuts here we go nice that was a walnut
right that was a
walnut how do I get to the other
side
[Music]
oh I like the enemies they're really
original
too you little
[\h__\h] F to control
yeah what what do you think I said I
said Walnut huh
oh
need you need we need a little [\h__\h] mode
don't we yeah wait can I touch the
poison with this
boy I don't want to
[Music]
try let him let's let him
go why even a tiny bit
hurts
it took damage
as you mean when I was
not the spin move is really good for
poison I guess
[Music]
so oh I can move while doing this
too can I control him too
oh even the big ones are no match for me
I commission you commissioned when is
that a new thing and I or is it an old
thing and I missed
it maybe I'll use it but I I'll have to
get rid of a different one because I'm
maxed out Merry Christmas G Merry
Christmas my recension vibe yeah for
real I feel it
I love
it you have it as a Discord emote I just
never posted it you have unused emotes I
mean yeah old ones
[Music]
yeah
oh W it's a flower P wow it's
[Music]
pretty oh there's
more there's one's pointless I guess so
[Music]
yeah
this is
purposefully really long and actually
pretty
slow only in GTA what in GTA it was
useful how was it useful in
GTA can't
imagine it surely will be useful
the
opening well that's about it I
guess Papa seem a little specific yeah
cuz like yeah we used it when he still
showed up in chat but he doesn't anymore
which is
fine but because of that I guess yeah we
could get rid of it but it's kind of sad
to get rid of
it okay I was thinking about did I get
these oh oh y y did I get the purple
ones and then on then I fell down so now
it's
uh probably a good idea to get
[Music]
them
no there should be normal Mario here
huh
[Music]
maybe oh maybe not no I need I need it I
need
it
does anyone use nine actually it's it's
definitely more ed than certain other
emotes land on
it no I almost had
it no whatever I don't want it I don't
want it I don't care
anymore it should stay right I mean I
don't use German that much
but in in interestingly enough it gets
at least a little bit of
usage yeah okay so the chicken the
turkey leg can
go okay I understand I broke the N again
yay
oh I need the path to come back I
think oh we're going down
we're going down I'm yelling
[Music]
timber
again
night remember it there it is two Mo so
close to each
other nah no definitely the face palem
has to stay I like the pace Pace fo mhm
Pace B yeah sure Pace fo yeah that's
that's exactly what it is Pace B
the boss fight is already here I barely
got any moons okay but I have extra
hearts that I deserved okay I got them
fair and
square oh
[Music]
oh face bone gets very
rare I don't I wouldn't want to get used
lost to
the I can't speak rid of
it shut
up
oh
no oh
no
oh
wait oh really that that easy like oh I
mean not necessarily easy but there's no
like very special system behind it I
feel
like
[\h__\h] yeah I still got it oh wait one
more time yeah oh wait to
[Music]
the oh I can lead him
away can you stop oh I do have to jump
on him or what
[Music]
no jump on him jump
him no
please there we go
nice I did first try that let's go let's
go usually our identity yeah I think we
can keep the chicken one I
mean and it's thrown by me
it's a chicken in the brain of a waan
how how I imagine you guys to look
like I got a
multimon
get still need so
many but that means the boss fight up
this world is already complete or is
there another like big big big boss
fight like in the previous one
I am on the flower field I suppose yeah
the Big B why did you bring me back here
huh
why so we can observe Landing
huh what we become come of the flower
field oh don't worry about it w what the
f what ow grabbing one of these flowers
will result in a substantial Street
oh how
nice interesting what the hell is in
these flowers ow
wait I want
one yes no okay they're really hard to
control even more difficult than the dog
wait there's a bunny here Alison
Wonderland
much can I get no actually but Super
Mario 64 oh I got him he gives me a bone
okay this one's easier to catch though
this one's easier to catch than the
Super Mario 64 bunny
oh wait there's a shop there's a
shop oh can I buy what do you got do you
have something good
looking spend money oh explore outfit
yeah that's pretty cute scientist
outfit I could buy those I
guess do I needed though like in the
previous world I actually needed to
dress to impress
expl you need it usually okay oh I like
wait my oh I didn't put on my
hat wait can I
change is there a room to
change
can I do it in the
menu there's a closet in your ship in
the ship
a [\h__\h] that didn't
help what what did you guys eat for
Christmas what was your special
Christmas
dinner
turkey Tamal wait there's so many people
saying tamales
what
what is that a
thing plan on Duck but God like oh no
maybe maybe you can do it a few days
later is that my Lam kfp and tamales is
like a common Christmas food
there mushroom
souit KFC kfy KY T steak with potatoes
barbecue bacon hamburger
M very common but what what was tamales
again I don't recall
tamales a Tamala a Spanish Tamal is a
traditional meso American dish made of
Masa a d made from nalized corn what
does that mean we're just steamed in a
corn husk or banana
leaves ring can either be discarded
prior to eating or used as a plate wait
I don't really understand what it is
still what's
inside mix it as filled with various
meats or beans and cheese
M but is it like is it a fancy food
I feel like this this is I heard about
this being eaten more casually
too yeah no it's not it's not fancy huh
so you guys just ate something really
casual for
Christmas I mean why not just eat the
the food that you like the most right
like comfort
food
a we can move somewhere closer no
no I don't really have another
checkpoint
oh so is there any way to get somewhere
else like easier and
[Music]
faster interesting
jumps use the tank enemy oh wait wait
Che this one then do this section
[Music]
no that's why you have no
friends cuz you hurt people that are
just like you you should be friends with
them and yet you pick a
fight
when you see someone who's actually
similar to you don't be jealous [\h__\h]
okay don't be jealous [\h__\h] just
appreciate the
similarities and the mutual
understanding of each other
uhhuh this guy did he have like what
hints or what was
it I can't talk to
him
more fing for family events
than it sounds good I got to eat it some
day I've never had
it never seen it maybe in a Mexican
restaurant life a glass with wa for real
like one of my best friendships that
I've made in my
[Music]
life no what was I supposed to do with
this
[Music]
why I wa these
things
oh oh that makes
[Music]
sense how making hand can oh I don't
know maybe it was someone who knows how
to make them wouldn't feel very
confident about
it um P the level to receive a SE oh
thank
you I'm not wait
Pro so bad at this yeah but one of my
best friends in life we used to
be yeah not not on good terms we started
out as like kind of seeing each other as
a
fret
[Music]
and not even trying to be friendly with
each
other and now that we think about it
like it's just ridiculous to us but
that's just you
know
it's a
thing at some point we realized well you
know the reason why we see each other as
Rivals is because we're so similar but
we could also be friends and we could
help each other
out because we're so similar and we
could be each other's like support oh
there's a Goomba lady over
there yeah and I I do feel like
friendships like those are even
stronger like they start off shitty like
that but that's exactly why they'll be
even stronger once you give it a chance
[Music]
what's going on here charging charging
station patient expiring please hurry
I'm consuming the last of my energy with
my Panic cycle is it my turn yet is it
my this one died waited too
long can I help them why don't you use
the other ones guys can I move
them
surely I can help them
right I can't push
them can I turn them
[Music]
off I want to help him get down
down going to die no
we can't let the machine die oh this
gives me
Neals like an
abandoned Factory looking area with
machines have which have some sort of
intelligence we cannot
continue become as
God
manato was
great
those are the kind of games you wish you
could experience for the first time
again at some
point but I'm happy that at least I
could experience them for the first time
during a
stream ow you [\h__\h]
bastard how dare
[Music]
you okay lady what's up with you am I
killing your husbands right now or a ah
wait
[Music]
did I kill too many already no I can
already reach her oh she's happy she's
in
love but do I go up to
her no was that good or
bad no I needed one more wait can I redo
this or is it forever lost can I jump
down and
redo
no she's oh she's back she's back she's
back she's back she's
[Music]
back okay first I needed one more but
now I need two more I guess because I
killed
one
right oh oh
oh she's so happy she's
horny she's
horny horny
bunk for the Goomba
[Music]
lady oh we got tanks again or is it the
same no
why would you attack me I'm one of
[Music]
you
no did I just hear the the size
down found this
way but it's just me a
heart there is no such thing as sign
down wait should I not have gotten rid
of all the
stones I
wonder oh there is a moon there I
think
[Music]
oh
Mario P
Mario I think I've got enough of
[Music]
you I'll go
here
oh oh side jump wa side jump wait can I
even reach the Moon
oh yeah I should I should be able to if
I fall down
here oh
yeah let's go I got it two
[Music]
more okay now I got that one so let me
check out what's over here I mean surely
there is a moon involved oh my God
that's a big a big jump
jump oh long jump long that was a long
jump
[Music]
worthy did I have a checkpoint
somewhere I don't know is that like a
[Music]
higher
SP a jump on the hat
oh
not very skilled in
that where are we going oh what about
[Music]
this so many
possibilities there's a better
checkpoint
where where though why do I have to go
all this path
again this is the wrong way of course it
is
sasuga
oh
no you climbed this Sprout last
time can I not get there from here at
all there a
moon um
oh maybe with this I can get some more
[Music]
nice
whatever no it just brings me back oh
you say I have a better checkpoint which
[Music]
one try there we
go W that's where the Sprout is that's
what the Boom
[Music]
is yeah I feel like a long jump would be
better there I feel I can't jump very
far when I do
this
oh now the wall is back but it's okay
cuz we're taking this
[Music]
path reconc moons where they half gives
new coins I see
it
nailed
it I I expected that to
[Music]
happen is there a jump button
no this game has no jump
buttons why would it have
jump than
[Music]
you jump but butons are
for
weak but like when do I
jump I don't get it I don't get it I
hate it I'm going to do a long jump I'm
going to try a long
jump I think I know better how to do a
long
jump I'm going to probably roll off the
edge
wo got to let go of
[Music]
be is there enough room to run e there
will
be wait that L and
done know I know I know I
know
Mario that's not exactly how it should
be BL my head but I feel like it's
[Music]
possible although he does sink a little
bit doesn't
he
let's try
again deep
breath
Panic why
why why why why why
[Music]
oh o what's
this
o
[Music]
found something interesting but here I
can't go
further
[Music]
man here we go again
guys how many times will we have to do
this
another one another
one run said
lb I did it this time please tell me
there's a moon
there
oh what the
[Music]
hell
nice
nice oh
no okay forget it forget it don't go for
it not worth it Mo in the
nut there was a moon in the nut can you
believe it I need one
more let's go almost got greedy
yeah let me
yes now we know how to get there
beautiful and
now back up there there was a checkpoint
there to
there
to what did the name wait did I ever
touch the I didn't right it would be
red it's a little bit lame that I have
to completely do this stuff again but
maybe I can make my own
PA I don't want to think too much about
it we got the moon and bounce
unbelievable oh wait there's
a motion
controls he
y
that should be
[Music]
fine [\h__\h]
hell
o a
[Music]
[\h__\h] should have got the rid of all the
stones after a and then see I can do
it got to trust the
waa a little bit more than that okay we
got it Summit path
n oh I
see I
see
hotal and some coins
that is very nice thank you so much
that's fun Sonic oh yeah right doesn't
he also go for
Rings
y okay yeah I wouldn't mind doing it
another
time I wouldn't mind that at
all ah [\h__\h] I got to go to the ride at
the end okay but wait there is a the
middle path here that I totally wanted
to go to on purpose it even has another
checkpoint
what
interesting oh oh
flow but wait
why why does that happen to this
oh for you is it
you
[Music]
we should we should do the other P too
right that's probably like I probably
got a moon out of
[Music]
that wait there's something there
ah
[Music]
woohoo all the music changes into pixel
eight8 bit music too why do I call it
pixel music eight bits
oh fun fun fun I like
it okay here we
go I like the implementation of these
like all older looking levels older
looking yeah like old school
classic no
[Music]
why should be
reachable run a [\h__\h] wait I can
run
how do
I how do I
Dash welcome raidas
[Music]
hello oh oh wait
ah Hong Kong oh clown clown raid this
hold why
oh too
early we got
honk honk honk honk indeed thank you for
the
[Music]
W elban and ah up upwards okay okay okay
and we come out here okay but I actually
want to go
back as interesting as this
is I should be going
back
ah have a nice Christmas oh my Christmas
really is already over as I said for me
it's really just the
24th the
evening of the 24th we don't do the the
whole we don't do the whole morning of
the 25th thing here in
Austria which I'm glad about because
that kind of needs you to get up
early I don't appreciate
that I can stack the turbo
flow oh
[Music]
[\h__\h]
hey wa genius
I thought oh let's look around maybe I
need to shoot something for later maybe
I'll I'll be appreciating past waa as
the future
W if I do that there we
go oh yeah Christmas was nice um I kind
of wish I would have gone to more
Christmas markets Before Christmas
because now they're oh my God now
they're going to be closing there's
still some that continue after
[Music]
Christmas but most of them I think end
like tomorrow or
[Music]
so so that's a bit sad cuz I only went
one and that was because of the video
that I made oh damn it I brought the
pant with
me might be a good
thing might have been a good thing no
it's gone ah they want don't want me to
use it anymore more oh there it is
there's a new one
woohoo you little
shits no fire can hurt me I'm in a
[\h__\h]
paner those couple of
fireballs don't they stay open for New
Year's at least
the I think most of them are closed
after Christmas there's like maybe a
couple ones that are still open but
usually most of them are close
we're going
down [\h__\h] shouldn't have activated it oh
my there's so
many uh
[Music]
yum but okay I can still go to some it's
just I I kind of wanted to go with
friends and I didn't get to go friends
at all
but it's not over yet it's not over we
can pretend it's still
Christmas
season we got them on wait do I have
like one extra now
oh one more than I really need let's try
to get to the boss fight then let me
pour some water
really
quickly oh we already have two extra oh
yeah cuz I got
[Music]
the the more you get now the less you
need to get the
next oh I'll be needing even
[Music]
more
can we pretend that Christmas markets
are still
[Music]
working American Best yeah yeah yeah
yeah
so you may know cuz I talked about it a
while ago in the
Stream I have gained this
knowledge uh previous L that I may or
may
not have some interesting
Roots
um from long long time
ago and I now was able to speak to my
mom directly about
it cuz first I only heard it from
like my brother I
think
oh and I that it
yeah so I think I can tell
you uh the my my grand
grandmother yeah Grand grandmother the
the the grandma of my mom
right yeah the grandma of my
mom uh that was during during war time
right and um my great grandma
she
oh I mean
I I don't know should say it all but
it's it gets quite
historic but my great grand Grandma it's
be
fine uh
her
guy they weren't married yet I think but
like uh ended up being captive
in uh a certain country for a couple
years um and then during that
time Americans were in the city where my
great grandma was
in and
um they started a
thing uh and the child that was created
from that is the is my
grandma and then I guess the American
left and then the
original partner came back and then they
married and I guess they kind of adopted
my
grandma um but it's like what I found
really funny is that my mom didn't know
that for a long time
either and it's kind of a mystery
because apparently my grandma didn't
tell my mom much uh about this stuff it
was kind of mysterious about it and then
like suddenly when my mom was already
like relatively old like guess maybe
young young adult or teenager or so no I
think already adult yeah probably
already adult uh she
like found like a
picture you know back then the soldiers
gave like pictures to like girl they
liked or whatever I guess she found a
picture like that in the Box I was like
who is this to my grandma and then
grandma was really secretive about it um
like kind of started talking about it
but not really but then she mentions
yeah yeah and you know the thing is like
I'm adopted and that's the first time my
mom hear it she's like what you adopted
like
literally and she's like yeah whatever
and then she just doesn't talk about it
anymore like weird weird
weird but that that that's pretty
certain that it was like this but not
necessarily like there could also
be my mom says that she's the I mean
that's the most logical conclusion that
the picture she has it because of that
story yeah
probably yeah so I I I I might have a
little bit of American blood in me and
and I got so curious about it and my
brother is also kind of curious about it
and we were like joking about maybe
doing a DNA test and maybe even like
inquiring to like certain services that
have this kind kind of
information like we first would have to
find out the
name uh of
that American I guess like but I don't I
don't know like BL blah blue we were
like joking about finding out more and
then finding the family but
like that's all crazy talk so I don't
think we'll do that but I do want to do
a DNA test I do want to do a DNA test
for real
[Music]
h i just jump
down I guess
[Music]
so yeah I would be interested in the
percentage and O does it maybe even say
like which area of America I don't know
but that would be interesting oh no it's
taking all the flowers yeah wait
to
nice good that you're
here
W holy [\h__\h] explosion it looks like a
lamp nice it is a lamp isn't it kind of
flower lamp flowers flowers flowers must
have all the flowers oh my
God honorary American do not mess with
me by bipad
bad we be funny if they were from
Kentucky for why oh because of because
of Kentucky for
a I I like that we're playing this uh
nut
friend cuz I I really enjoy playing it
throughout the
whole world so
far oh no
uh I can jump right oh no oh wait what
wait what am I supposed to do this oh
wait I can't jump I just have to yeah
right I
forgot
oopsie I I tried the normal jump button
he was like no I guess I can't jump of
course I can of course I
[Music]
can I got it I got it I got it I got
it
this spice is pretty
[Music]
easy would have been even easier if I
didn't have that stupid moment where I
forgot how to jump but I can definitely
jump easy easy
easy I'm mean in the
zone no I don't even have to be in the
zone there's no Zone
necessary wait sorry I was looking why
am I here why am I here what how did I
make it up
there get me no wait for me why is it
moving
no there we
go wasn't working so I don't I don't
know how I made it in
there H oo triple Moon let's
go baby
[Music]
triple what was it not understandable my
story yeah it's something like that
yeah this
funny
yeah very understandable right I mean I
feel like there must have been many
cases like
that I feel like they
were doesn't change your thing I still
love you I mean I would have been
concerned if that was
uh a
nogo a deal AK hey you're a little bit
American
ew yeah let of overseas Affairs
yeah it was a
time for International
Exchange
I I had 36 moons but now it needs 58 no
I I I ended up having 58 what I had so
many what what wait added up with the
previous ones right right
right a total from
all I didn't sign up for American
tension for that reason
I'm well it doesn't really have much
influence I'm still very much European
very much Austrian very much not fluent
in English very much
myself no for real for real though
that's so many generations away we speak
German in my family
so I am
Austrian
yes we might just be related now we all
are
related in one way or another but yeah I
mean one of you guys could be my
family I love joking about that I'm your
sister I'm your no I'm your not your
sister I'm your cousin your your cousins
cousins cousins cousins cousin or
something like that right I could be dad
probably a distant
cousin explains why I can do valley girl
so well who
knows
what Sweet Home
Alabama my oh she is secretly my cousin
yo this could be a storyline to
a to to a manga or an
[Music]
anime let me eat
snack copyright that yeah copyright that
right
[Music]
away leg Kingdom oh we we we go there
anyway
[Music]
okay that was
fun
we'll be back after
short Merry
[Music]
Christmas
this likely makes your soldiers
descended to yeah I mean that's why I
got the warrior in me oh no but the most
interesting thing was that my my brother
and my mother were saying that if I were
to find this American
family that I have connected with I
could apply for American
citizenship and I'm like whoa but
actually no thank you I don't need it
like how is that how I'm not going to I
don't need it but it's
interesting yeah I don't want it
no yeah why would I want that that just
tax me more
no I mean as an American I would
probably appreciate a European
citizenship and then just move to
Europe and enjoy enjoy the the things
that come with
Europe I hear you get a free
gun here's your citizenship and here's
your gun
enjoy
y y
yum spin
Pro you only tell me things that I
already know
dude a
dress L lady dress
[Music]
oh from less you
mean I make sense in a while the
world yo I could become the US
president right okay that's a reason for
me to get the American citizenship so I
can become president a all right then
that's all you needed to say no you
can't of course I
[Music]
can now we're
cooking oh
funny the brutal they're here
too
my
guess
oh why are you
crying oh my God you look funny
actually reminds me of that
Pokemon fish
version my goodness that Monster's
minion just stomped in here
uninvited and they St are Kingdom's
finest L lady dress it's a tragedy
yeah she looks like a
muppet Muppets are cool you better not
be saying that as an
insult you have to be native forn
American oh really not naturalized
[\h__\h] God damn
it oh wait there's another one of those
notes this one could be
easier can I swim
[Music]
faster I think even a noral
speed oh this one's very
manageable M
yay count down like
short red moons all
right wait what are you
saying I'll listen again you're looking
for the water Plaza the way is in in is
right behind me okay no I'm fine here
for now that bird is
cute ah it's so
round it's so cute by the way so my mom
slept over right and uh I actually cuz
I I couldn't sleep much
until uh my family came and you know
Among Us kept me
awake I I think I went to bed at 10:00
a.m. cuz after Among Us I had to quickly
eat something cuz I was I was really
hungry so then I went to bed at like
10:00 I told them can you like please
come like after after like 4:00 p.m.
please um you would think that's enough
time right but I I don't know even
though I I was so tired I just couldn't
sleep and when I finally fell asleep I
was like really it was really really
light
sleep so it wasn't it wasn't very
good
um but anyway because of that I was able
to sleep really early I slept at
midnight last night and then I slept
pretty pretty
decently but then I woke up at 6:00
a.m. after 6 hours which yeah I mean you
can live with 6 hours but I can't really
function with 6 hours but at least it's
like not too
bad and I tried to fall asleep again but
then I know I had thoughts in my head
and I stayed
awake
but at 6:00 a.m. when I woke
up here's a smoothie update until these
6 hours these whole 6 hours normally
smoothie wakes me up after like 3 or 4
hours uh of sleep no matter when I sleep
but this time she didn't wake me up and
then and then 6:00 a.m. like she noticed
I was awake she she meowed maybe like
three times in in in front of her food
like in the living room and then I did
like the sound then she came back she
stopped me out she came back to me and
she laid
down and then yeah she stayed like
pretty quiet until I finally got out of
bed at like 900 a.m. I just kind of like
chilled with my Kito Catos and checked
stuff on my phone that whole time and
even though I was awake she's just like
she was just chilling yeah it was a
Christmas
miracle and me and my mom were saying oh
it's because my mom is here cuz like she
doesn't even dare to do anything
funny
while my mom is there I don't know if
that's true I I I might
even
consider the
possibility that maybe it's because I
did sleep so
early when it was dark and when I woke
up it was still
dark we'll see how it is tonight because
my mom is not sleeping with me
tonight sleep sleeping here okay that
sounds kind of weird does it sound weird
oh sleep sleep
here you know what I
mean you know what I
mean I made it weird I made it weird I'm
sorry I'm so [\h__\h] sorry they've
broken the stairs to the water Plaza
okay but like I I don't think that's
really going to be an
issue
no way they can't just put such an easy
moon in
there so do I want to go left or do I
want to go right I don't think I can
even go left can I
okay m coins golden coins stacked like
that looks so good what is this
who what
what what the [\h__\h] is
that is that going to be a common
gimmick in this
world oh my God I can't believe we are
in a water
world hopefully it's easier
then Super Mario
[Music]
64 water temple let's go back
back oh smovie was really good what the
[\h__\h] and uh chunky wonky is my fluffy
sweet baby as
[Music]
always they've been really good what the
hell is this can I throw my hat here
oh ow bullying not
okay
I will bully you right
back uhoh oh
[Music]
yeah originally I think we were going to
like oh I have a
fish oh my
[Music]
God isn't this kind of a reference to
Super Mario 64 cuz less was also
there um what was I going to say oh yeah
originally I think we're going to go to
Christmas Market and all that as well
but we ended up just chilling at home
and cooking and it took enough time
anyway
so it was good though had a good good
good time Chistmas
Chistmas
[Music]
andish
oh hi what are you doing
here oh the boat is right there can't s
that mon V henchmen they so are
beloved Lo lady
dress how dare he the
dress it shall be mine it belongs not
even to Peach it belongs to Mario
okay
o oh
[Music]
oh a music note ah [\h__\h] music note level
in a
pixel section let me retry
[Music]
please please
platform do I have to
reenter thank
you you seing movie must be talking no
honestly I feel
[Music]
like feel like there's always someone
[\h__\h] talking about me right
now this one looks tricky yeah
no I can't reach it by just standing
there
[Music]
right no
no no
[Music]
oh the last
ones don't for ah yeah
running already [\h__\h]
up E I don't like this one I don't like
it 1.5 million chicken spr me right now
wouldn't say that many right
now oh oh oh I I entered
[Music]
early
no no
no I don't like it I don't like it I'm
going to give up cuz it annoys me but
can I go there at least we get
something at least we get
something yeah he's okay okay we don't
need all of
them oh there's a mo
there before I like look at everything
in the water I feel like I want to first
look at everything up at the Top If I
can but I don't think I can go
there okay never
mind ignore the bottom not ah true I
guess you don't yeah
Mario like it looks
like
face I wish my 3D was as expressive as
go
go oh oh it's carrying a moon let's go
get
it the lake seems
noisy
you don't like it like that I'll try to
help
you you want the big old mouth I want I
want especially the eyes honestly in my
freed the eyes are so stiff you can't
even tell when I'm looking to the side
honestly but if I want more expressive
3D home
3D I have to use like a 1 million wish
for it but before I do that I think I
would get a new 3D outfit so I can use
it to
perform and I mean when will I reach
enough a 1 million
wish
so they have to be chosen wisely I
honestly like in hindsight I really
regret going for the
dandle it is it is what it is but uh I
really regret it because like life to De
off it's just like
I can get so many of them I could have
done it eventually without the wish but
back then I didn't know that it was an
option to get a freeing outfit and I
asked actually I did ask before maybe
I'll should try asking again I asked
before if I can like say okay okay okay
let's let's switch something around
let's say this year I don't get a live
Tod outfit okay and we say the dandel is
the one I'm getting this year you know
for
example can we like switch you around
you know what I mean you know
um I regret it cuz I just didn't know
what the options
were wait what what do we do about the
stone isn't her to
ask
[Music]
no I want another outfit so bad fre the
outfit in it
[Music]
oh you got a bird down here that poor
bird I hope no no accidents ever
happened here that destroyed this bubble
of
air oh look at that money wait can I
become the
bird
no what's the secret you're seing I know
it I know it I can't tell you I'll give
you a clue taking notes in the cliff
side are you telling me the that I was
just like working on and then gave up on
oh wall jump okay all right all right I
immediately found the solution to this
problem oh if the bird already has a hat
does that mean I already found the
secret he was going to tell
me no
way why does he always tell me things I
don't need to
[Music]
know
ah ah oh things resist okay if it has a
hat I can't control it
okay
oh if you travel all the way to Lake
Kingdom you should dress for the wait
you want me to put it on the
dress oh or a
swimsuit will let me shop oh that was
what dress was display that's really
pretty sorry that's a nice
display a that monster came and stole it
he stole a Kingdom's greatest
treasure oh here's a
shop M
mein did she just say
virgin virin I heard it I heard
[Music]
it
they look so dorky with those hats
on wait they look like me with that that
fan
[Music]
art Virgin Killer
sweater can't believe another virin
killer sweater
trend has happened after all these years
your okay you probably got the better
stuff than the other lady but I don't
know if I have enough coins let's see 16
coins
cute what a
Flo wait okay interesting H you only
have one version of outfit what about
you
da
[Music]
oh oh wait oh you actually have
a I'm not clashing you're
clashing mechanic off they they have
like the oldest stuff too in
[Music]
here now wait I said I don't want to buy
it wait this is my maximum this one is
for maximum right this one doesn't go
away
right it does
it no no is also the per the tempor [\h__\h]
I misunderstand this say
maximum
makes me feel like it's so permanent it
really isn't but yeah let's wear
this I happen to have the exact right
amount the outfits are so cute in this
game I love how they made a fitting
outfit for everything for every section
and like you need it that's why you also
need to collect those coins it's
wonderful
this is what me and Nissa will dress
like in the movies shut
it something cry
oh interesting interesting
interesting can I swim better with this
no lame
oh I love this what that's such a cute
gimmick
why not swimsuit it is a
[Music]
swimsuit is this cute
gimick why
[Music]
let's
later
di dip down
where are we
going he's so cute so satisfying
too yeah his walking noises are
different
now du oh
oh wait secret PA
here you thought I wouldn't
[Music]
noce I smell the
money I smell the gold it's
[Music]
toxic no do a round one roundhouse
kick
[Music]
I'm going to
die if I'm not careful
[Laughter]
ah
[Music]
no died from the
beginning and then I have to carry back
the the key so that was like halfway
through no I probably should kill the
enemies though because oh well next time
next time cuz they're going to be in the
way but these ones might not cross my
path
there's a there's a little C down there
than God
there can I go there with a long jump I
feel like I
could
no I mean maybe I can but it's going to
take a few
tries he get on to oh Dam jump
with the hat I need a hat for this
[Music]
one I don't really understand the head
jump
though
do a hat Thro and then dive at it dive
wait diving you don't mean the you don't
mean the long jump wait diving how do
you how do I dive again I mean I
literally am in diving attire
[Music]
but I should have just do
that
[Music]
t
whatever let's kill the
enemies I'm going to focus on getting
the key because I feel like that's just
an extra Moon that yeah would be great
to have but
y would be great to have but uh no
must
can hold the hat out yeah that mean
that's what I've been doing
right like this I know that but um I
don't know I feel like when I run into
it I only jump higher I don't jump
longer like
this
ha
hack they can't reach me but I can reach
them
oh I hate these goomas I ha
down
[Music]
probably don't even need to kill them
all I want to what's it this special P
here what is
this why is it not on the other side why
is it asymmetric why why or is it the
shadow no a
shadow it's a shadow why is it so
weird I feel like it shouldn't be
so it should be smoother and like
further over there but I guess it
depends on how the Sun is I feel like
it's not normal oh wait I don't have to
carry
the
key what this
[Music]
do that almost made me fall off from the
Imp
ped y' I swear I would have been really
triggered but the key would have
probably still been attached right I
would hope
[Music]
so normal jump is enough here
okay and there we go we got it y
woohoo all
right now do we want to try that thing
over there
[Music]
again
no just took a shortcut I just took a
shortcut who the hell is
crying all of I guess wait I have to
ride a tire now I can go uh through
where was it who wanted me to dress
[Music]
appropriately you're a top
right
you Trav all the dress I
did trouble you look gred to swim please
go inside y
[Music]
y oh we come into this room
oh well I
mean that it that's it that's
it
what wait can I become
[Music]
the
Pro
cppy I hav't trying that but wait he
holds on to
it
ah
what wait wait wait
[Music]
wait
there we
go took me a few tries okay I didn't
realize until you guys said that I had
to keep it on there longer okay so all
of that was just for one Moon H we need
two
[Music]
more let me
out I want to leave and become fish
There's a Moon there I know how to get
it it easy he's walking he's acting like
he's swimming but he's just
walking oh it's a moon piece oh yeah
right didn't realize I was collecting
those as
well what these fish call again uh what
are these called
again need to be myself for
moment Moon ah it's the other moon
piece oh yum
[Music]
oh my air my
air a team teams yes CH
cute yes Moon ghetto D maybe we go
straight to the checkpoint which
was
here because these enemies
are kind of
annoying
here you go here you go one
more is it it's isn't it less moons
necessary than usual like in the other
worlds I feel like we needed
more but I also feel like there are less
to get but maybe I'm wrong oh that one I
already got is that an extra temporary
heart container or just a
healing heart I think it's a Healing
Heart
[Music]
well I'll go check
anyway oh yeah okay so I just gave me
money probably because water level small
kingom so L okay I don't need to feel
weird about feeling like um not finding
enough don't know how to open that door
still oh what about
here there we go I found something
interesting
people
people what you what what youi you mean
to Lo this that's not a Yoshi that's not
what you mean right is there an actual
water
Yosi we're here at the
top oh
oh will it stay does seem like it okay
that's a shortcut now I guess to get up
there with the flower
it does have the Yoshi
face I do want to play by the way the
USC games from the
N64
um
[Music]
expansion
why oh the ship in the boss fight is
right there but I'm not ready I still am
missing one
Moon
there a secret here oh there's a moon
okay you get Moons for True right I
don't need to bring the moons to the
boss I can go there anytime
huh somehow I connected the moons with
the boss as well okay then we can go oh
wait but wait didn't I didn't I just get
a moon did it go to the start like to
the middle Central
Area I'll pick it up
later oh never
[Music]
mind no no no no no never
mind I'm going to grab some
hearts
somewhere I get healed by the moon right
wait no wait the moon isn't here where
did it go it went
up oh what's up what's where's up
where's up
[Music]
dog above the
hole
over there why did it go
there still forcing me to confront with
the Goombas who have it out for me like
no
other here we
go okay full heal
so no no no no no no no no no
B interesting
doorin oh those are supposed to be baby
goas oh
cute now I like them more can I kill
them
please
what what's that oh this is very Super
Mario Sunshine iy like those those sand
levels or
whatever
[Music]
rude I need
to okay hold on to them like this I'll
go left I guess ooh okay and then I go
right so left was the completionist
choice
and not really that that's what I'm
going for but nice every once in a while
oh got to go with the flow go with the
flow go with the flow ah
no I did slow down a little bit but oh
wait what no
no no my
money this is where the rage stars are
kicking no I mean I'm not raging
actually just realized one
[Music]
thing uh I'm probably going to end after
this boss
fight because tomorrow's stream is like
pretty
early I have to get the coins again
right
um and I think they said something like
they want me to be on standby like an
hour before for a
test oh come on they're too close
together yeah so poppets I can do out
that's
[Music]
fine yeah the stream is at 1100 a.m. for
me probably have to be around like 10 or
9 get up at 9 or
[Music]
so so we'll do that I'll I'll take a
quick look over
[Music]
the over the super chats oh yeah I want
to do it
again
okay and then I'll
[Music]
say oh it lifts me he he yo he yo he
yo okay I I cannot fail now oh it's the
end thank
God
I made
it let's go quick h x are you doubting
me I said I'll only freeze over them
because I spend lots of time with those
super chats to write the the signs
so I will hopefully stand by my word
okay here we go they look like little
chickens if you don't look too closely
like from the top chick Shi
Shick
chick you can't do this to me I get to
heal right before I go
in oh yeah
okay
uh so who's next the long boy
huh
we already got L lady dress and I'm
going to dress up oh no never mind I
guess have to give it to Bowser too bad
man I really wanted to be a pretty
lady oh he's got a flower hat oh
okay oh I land on him cuz he's so big
a interesting I couldn't reach him with
a normal jump so I have to go through
those measures o o
no maybe I don't have time
to difficult difficult to guess how much
distance there is
still throw throw it no
nice nice jump
wa
aim no no throw it
[Music]
again first try he's like goofy but
that's a
buunny
BBL oh
again pretty easy but I like the
gimmicks I like the implementation of
the flower
power
yay
CI c w i the winner Brut over the lake I
got the multi
[Music]
Moon
yay nice very successful it brings me
back to the beginning right yeah Yeah he
talking to
[Music]
me let's get after them no not now not
today uh do I have to save the
game wait is there no auto save this is
the first time I'm
saving is there no auto save in this
game like nowadays so many games have
auto save that I almost kind of assume
it you think there is pink
crabs
[Music]
constantly
okay you just know it's because the
indicator really sub yeah I haven't seen
it a single
[Music]
time okay okay
okay he also yawned he heard me but
that's kind of creepy Mario
that's kind of
creepy you may wonder about the Super
Nintendo but I actually just downloaded
the wrong thing I thought it was in
there but it was in the Nintendo
64 cuz the the Super Nintendo one I
think is free right but the Nintendo 64
one is not unless I'm wrong but I feel
like that's how I got confused by
it yeah Game Boy Advance one as well
yeah yeah I wonder if one day there'll
be like a DS one as well
do you know the 12 Days of Christmas
song If You Got Each gift for for the
song One patri Trav days which gift
would you get the most B Ron screaming
from the MTH wait I already had this
riddle somebody already gave me this
riddle and then I was like [\h__\h] no and
then we looked it
up are you smarter than a rock oh people
actually made an effort to figure it out
well how long did it take her H we
already had this though G skan but my
answer is I I would have said no if this
was the first time I would have probably
said mm- no not for
me
yeah all
righty let's read not really read but
like I'm going to read the non Reds and
I'm going to check over the Reds if
there's
something you know that I have to pay
attention to let's go to my office cuz
I'm in my uniform and we don't go to my
office so often these days and that's
kind of
sad um let's
[Music]
see my office I missed my
office I love this office we've had for
so long but like these kind of
backgrounds they grow on me you guys
like make fun of me of like having too
much stuff in my obs but I feel like I I
I even cleaned it out a while ago I
deleted like the the old super old
Christmas
scene where I did like readings of
German fairy tales
remember I deleted it from my OBS it's
still somewhere on my PC
though but yeah uh you guys blame some
problems on that but I'm pretty sure it
has nothing to do with it but I did
clean it out because I just had too many
scenes it was different ult to find them
but I need them like I can't delete most
of these because I need them I need the
girls talk I need the RPG office every
once in a while the news one is like
useful in certain times you know we've
used it
spontaneously I need Hol talk I don't
want to set it up all again whenever I
do Hol talk by the way sorry I ended up
not having time for Hol talk but uh
after my
break um yeah like I don't want to set
all these things up each time so I just
keep them in my in my OBS scenes I have
so many I can I can spontaneous go to my
kitchen I can spontaneously go to my
Ballroom to my winter shrines I was
really honestly if I if I didn't have
this the winter Shrine scene ready in my
scenes I would have forgotten about it
and I wouldn't have thought about using
it in the Koka the other
day I just complet would I completely
would have forgotten the existence so
it's also kind of a reminder to myself
that I have
it yeah
so there's nothing wrong with my
OBS don't let them pressure you if it
works it works it does work
like any issues are honestly really not
from that any technical
issues pretty sure about that anyway
let's put on some
bgm
you can delete the user room now we
don't use it uh I think I
deleted uh the old version no not the
old version but like the the Mecha
[Music]
version cuz in my mind I don't even
connect like it looks cool and all but I
don't even connect the usual room of
something like that that's not how the
usual room looks like in my
mind um yeah I think I might have even
gotten rid of the other usual room yeah
it's not it's not in here right now now
cuz I really didn't use it much in the
past
months yeah I mean I did get a little
bit tired of like constantly making
usual room jokes I don't want to
completely get rid of that but just
every once in a while I make a usual
room joke I I don't want
to constantly do that cuz I'm I'm not
really to be honest I'm not really the
threatening type of person and it's
roleplay and all that
but it's it's kind of difficult for me
and a little bit cringe too
sometimes threatening you guys with
stuff this it feels wrong to
me you don't deserve it
okay but yeah oh you know what we should
use as
bgm cow carrot the goat apparently makes
music
now and made a Loi version of the great
[Music]
Wanderer
huh can you get any more
goed what the
[Music]
hell oh so this is it what I'm playing
right now it's on his channel so check
it out give it a view actually I'll I'll
put it up actually I I'll cut the super
chats now and then I'll pin
the the link oh my God wait that's loud
the
[Music]
base the base was
strong is it still too
loud should I turn it down
more my own
desire
gives me to
you moving fter the light
can I'm in the
absence and looking
back then I lose my way I can't see the
day when I can reach you again can I let
go I can hear your voice
leing me through the vo fade
away to the
[Music]
gra walking
by my eyes alone the silence defening
till I'm reaching out to you con
sacrifice to
lie myself so I'll survive one day
eventually light it will lead me back to
you see me see
me
[Music]
wonder I am the
Wonder I am the
wonderer so good
I'm actually surprised I remember the
lyrics so
[Music]
much Loi I love lowii remixes cuz lfi
remixes are perfect for me to use as
background music I love
it did I lose my way I can't see the day
when I can reach you again now can I let
go I can hear your voice leading me
through the void fade
away to the
gray eternally I'm walking
by FL before my eyes alone the silence
stening still I'm reaching out to you
come
[Music]
back so I'll survive one day eventually
the light it will lead me back do you
see me see
[Music]
me but for for a moment I thought you
were talking about like a real daughter
can't wait for you to serenate your new
daughter like you do with us well I was
thinking about what could I collab uh
with her and because of the language
barrier I was thinking the bomb
game anything besides
that just anything that doesn't rely on
language too much so like a like VR
dancing exchanging stream but um maybe
that's like better for a little bit
later for a second collab or so but yeah
the bomb game is like perfect for
language barrier
people and then she could also give me
another Korean
lesson but I want to actually I kind of
want to polish my Korean
firsty is the sink off right now what's
this problem with my sink
[Music]
recently
um
I want to polish my Korean a little bit
before
[Music]
really getting sound right to me
oh should be right before getting into
into deep with
[Music]
her happy that you you found you found
motivation to keep with your keep up
with your Korean yeah um it's a good
motivation I mean I was going to kind of
get back into it next year anyway but
now I have an
urgent an urgent
reason ah damn
it it's really too bad that my Korean I
couldn't keep it up after those
[Music]
lessons how good is school s was English
or Japan jaes I heard her talk a lot of
Japanese today in that
stream like damn she actually talks
better Japanese than I speak Korean
that's for
sure
yeah yeah I saw she was studying me she
was reading this huge
Wiki and eventually I I wanted to know
what she's like reading about me what
she's laughing about so I translated
parts of it for myself and I was like oh
my
god oh they may have even a little bit
too many details about me and that
Korean
Wiki I'm surprised about that I didn't
know there was such a detailed Wiki
about me and Korean I had no
idea yeah who's writing it who is it
who's behind that
Wiki is it time for dingo again I don't
know I mean I don't really think dingo
is very efficient but I guess at least
as a
beginner I could give it a few more
tries
um yeah it's updating they're probably
updating it right now
yeah they write it down for the history
books h
yeah
so uh I don't know I I think I don't
want to ask right now because I'm like
right in front of my break and until my
break there's not much time before it
I'm going on a vacation and this and
that so there's really not much time so
if we collab and probably after my break
um and then yeah we'll see what we're
going to play I I'm I'm so happy
she uh she she's interested now because
in the beginning you know I followed her
first on Twitter because I saw her
reacting to me on Twitch so I thought oh
okay she seems really happy about me
even speaking very slightly about her so
I followed her but then she didn't
follow me back she reacted to me
following her and she reacted to me
liking tweet or so about her and writing
to her but she didn't follow me back so
I was like eh why why why why why is she
not interested and then I heard that she
is M said and she said something about
like in her streams she said something
like uh like she can't
possibly like more or less use me to get
M which um I I'm glad that she wouldn't
do that I mean that's that's a nice
thing to
[Music]
say but then I thought okay maybe
because I'm M and she's not interested
in connecting but then eventually she
did follow me back so uh and then she
replied to me and then she talked more
and more
[Music]
about maybe maybe maybe we
can let a friendship Blossom from
there and I'm going to do my best to
polish my Korean again oh
[Music]
fighting yeah I I heard she got a little
bit
emotional I I wrote I I read that in one
of those Tweets in the
kfp hashtag when she was reading about
me some some parts of the wiki where
making her a bit emotional
really like some I think some parts
talked about some struggles of
mine I'm honestly like really curious
about her Tech but I don't know if she
would tell me if that's a big secret or
so I'm curious I was like even
discussing with crony I actually I
didn't tell you guys
like there was um like like a couple
days ago
I um like some some parts of what she
says people translate for me but then
other parts like she talks a lot so I
didn't know what she was saying and I
asked crony crony what exactly is she
saying in this whole clip that like the
text is only vaguely translated help me
and then she translated it for me and
like uh I I asked her what what do you
think her intentions are do you think
she's interested in me cuz she's not
following me back do you think she would
like to do a collab with me and she's
like yeah I mean she sounds open to it
she didn't mention it but she sounds
open to it so I was like kind of like
asking for her advice and then we talked
a little bit about the tech I was like
look at look at this look at their music
video look at this and look at the her
just doing not even music video but like
normal streams in frd walking around
what do you think this is do you think
this is like accents or do you think
this is VR what do you
think don't worry we're this discussing
that yeah yeah really
interesting I need to get my accents to
work ah I mean it kind of works I just
didn't have time to like put it on again
ever
since it's not a school crash
no but she's so
cute and I actually I checked out the
other members of that group that she has
I checked out a couple couple of the
others and they're all really cute and
all really funny and they're like uh so
connected I wish I understood
more I need to practice more H I need to
watch like that Korean show again where
the dads take care of their kids because
they like the kids talk pretty simple
Korean I used to pick up a couple of
phrases from
there when I if you need help
translating oh thank you I I want I want
I don't know how long she's been talking
about me in total cuz when I woke up
after my nap today after uh my mom left
I I took a a huge nap wow that was a
huge
nap so good so comfy um after I woke up
I I checked my phone and like she was
streaming and she was talking about me
already so I don't know how long she
talked about me but ideally I want I
want a translation of all of
that I'm curious return of super man is
pretty good yeah yeah yeah that Wiki
even said oh kiar watched Return of
Superman Korean TV
show they they have all the
info oh yeah I need to watch that and
and I get my understanding my hearing
back translate her entire stream
yes
[Music]
I will try my best maybe I'll even take
up some oneon-one lessons again but I
don't know it already always made me
feel so nervous and pressured like the
homework and stuff was quite a lot and I
didn't feel like I
could keep up with it cuz it was so much
information each lesson and was
weekly and and I didn't have time to
repeat on my own time what I learned
mostly so I felt pretty overwhelmed with
it I wish I I probably could have
requested to go at a slower Pace but at
the same time I feel like if I if I went
with a slower Pace like once every two
weeks or so I probably still wouldn't
have gotten to really repeat on my own
time so in the end there would have been
more time to forget everything in
between
so probably once a week is better is the
minimum
honestly yeah it doesn't work any other
way really but um damn it damn
it Merry Christmas thank
you talking usually helps the most if
you could talk in Karin with cron or
someone
else honestly yeah I I didn't want to
like until recently I didn't feel like
like I don't want I I don't want to
bother crony too much but recently we've
been talking a lot and and and she's
like she's been
oh look
really there for me and and and helpful
and you know fast like for example for
like um Advent calendar videos the 3D
video I made with her and it and then
also the voice LS for the sock puppet
stuff like she would be always like the
first to give me the voice LS and all
that like she's so on top of it and and
really helpful and
and
and then like you know we had some
meeting where she was also in and then
like afterwards like after meeting she
just like dmed me like know talking
about it like oh oh she feels like
talking to me about that oh
interesting I feel really happy you know
you know I want to connect more with her
and I want to do more collabs with her
yes
honestly I'm so so so grateful to all
the Ian members who gave in their voice
lines cuz they actually did it on time
and I feel so regretful because of that
as well because H if only the sock
puppets were there I thought that it
would fail at the voice lines but no
they all sent them on time even though I
only gave them like two
days that's
incredible and I gave them such a cringy
script
too but they all helped me out and they
when then I I felt really bad when I had
to tell them that I stressed them for
nothing because the sock puppets aren't
here yet and they were all really
understanding of about it and and were
thanking me for like planning this all
in the first place and organizing
it it it has been quite a bit of extra
work for me both the ad calendar and the
okus thing and all that but um I just
wanted to bring something to the table
and and help make this season a bit more
joyful and connected for all of
us and yeah I wanted everybody to have a
good time
yeah so I'm glad I was able to
accomplish that and I'm both with Among
Us and the Advent calendar I'm glad that
I could create something that had
everybody in evolved and and created a
sense of
community and strengthened us again and
made us do stuff together yeah I'm
really happy yeah also the games I I
already asked some of them or like all
of them I got some of the steam friend
codes but not all of them so they don't
have their gifts yet but I I I'll be
working on
that
oh they announced the delay too for okay
cool cool cool
cool I hope everybody can announce it
once it's actually out
[Music]
there did you get any games the they get
you any it oh no no no no no but no need
like I'm the Santa nobody give Santa
Claus gift Santa always gives everybody
gifts but nobody oh poor Santa actually
does ever anybody ever think of Santa
nobody ever that's so sad that's so sad
that's such a sad
thoughts I feel bad for Santa but he's
not real
right Santa gets cookies milk and
cookies yeah I guess but that's like I
don't
know everybody gives in the same stuff
it's kind of
lame what Santa is not real what
well well let me read the super chatos
now um oh yeah we have amongus super
chats but
huh let's see when can I read
them there's a lot of collabs coming up
oh hi chunky
won I mean if they're not too many I can
read them
now let me
check is that
hi it's
you she's such a round blob she's
literally Christmas tree
shaped so cute oh and
unarchived I do have quite a few super
chats
oopsie she so
meet yeah her winter coat is so
thick my she she just sitting there oh
bye-bye bye-bye all right just checked
if I was still
here you'll need a Super Chat stream no
I won't need it
because I don't have to read the the
polar ones anyway you guys are getting
the polar wordss for
it okay let's go uh from the unarchived
[Music]
Stream
M there's still some Christmas related
fan art that I want to
use for thumbnails I got a lot of them
like on
Christmas Christmas related fan art on
Christmas a little bit too
late but I'll I'll use it anyway yeah
we're extending Christmas
steam stream steam oh my oh my
God what how did we suddenly get so
behind
what
o moving faster than the light
can I'm in the
absence alone looking
back and I lose my way can see the day
when I can reach you again can I let
go okay I found it I really like this
thumbnail that was a nice
stream an interesting one let's go now
many thanks for the pinky K ho ho ho
Merry Christ look you oh here's one of
he's enough for one copy of Call of Duty
Black
Ops it would be a great one to to stream
F like I already roasted you when I saw
that Super Chat come in you didn't
really think I would like want to play
that right right tell me you
knew tell me you
knew because like it's yeah it's a j
okay okay I'm relieved then because it's
really a really unlikely game for me to
play I am so not
[Music]
interested but you should understand me
more no no I don't
[Music]
care
it's a game for beginnner tend it's easy
huh for real oh a good for beginner okay
more than one person says that
interesting the numbers wow what do they
mean I don't know I'm going one two one
two three it tastes so so so sweet means
pineapple that's what that means take a
47 de he who eats face and than thank
you very much thank I appreciate that
more moral d py
[Music]
d thanks for the pinky hi wa if you're
looking for Steam games you should look
up my favorite Australian themed game I
love them
sauce is this like some kind of bait for
me to say something I love them
sauce I I love them
sauce
is I I I love
it is I knew it immediately even before
I started reading it because it just
looks weird M sa you little [\h__\h] it's a
great game lot of for mechanics and it's
got a great Twist Off you little [\h__\h]
also wow your hair looks good today oh
thank you what what was my hair like
huh that that honestly doesn't sound
like a game title m s
it doesn't even sound like it but you
got me to read it so success I
guess go did a Twitter space maybe that
can help you to practice your Korean an
idea what do you mean what what what do
you mean to the Twitter space what today
what do you
mean pyro H thanks for two pinkies oh oh
yeah oh yeah are you also going to make
me buy a certain game huh
greetings benevent tentu it's been few
days since your concert and it's slowly
getting uncomfortable so can I please
have my eye
back the one you catched with your
performance no pressure there what do
you mean I only caught one of your eyes
where was your other eye looking at
oh is this supposed to be some kind of
cute cute
flirt why why was only one eye looking
at
me h there not enough eyes on me all
eyes on
me all eyes on me eyes
one all eyes on me is the catchphrase
for that K-pop group all eyes on me I
one something like that all eyes on me
we are eyes
one
H you get it yua you get it
interesting well
anyway no pressure though you can keep
it if you really want it for real though
that was an amazing concert and you did
a great job also thanks for keeping me
sane when needed from work here is part
of my Christmas bonus oh yeah it's
Christmas bonus time huh love you my oii
oi you wrote it wrong is this how it
went it's been way too long since I last
said that sorry hey o o o o o o o you
should be saying it more often then what
theck if you even forget the order of
the those
words okay
2024 uh
your what do you call it again the goals
for 2024 what do you call that
again resolutions yes your New Year's
resolutions say Kam Ori or like say it
to yourself or fig it in your brain or
write a tweet to me one per
day so that you don't
forget how to write it and also who it
is your come
Yoshi
okay okay H thank you soon you can have
your eye back I don't really understand
why you used only one eye but
okay thank you and happy New Year thank
you for the support
hul and and don't use too much of your
Christmas bonus on me
you okay treat yourself maybe go skiing
or something if you
can I always F Kam in plant you have
more than one oh I mean not
necessarily I mean yeah you can have
many oshis and then one Kam ooshi but
you can also just have one oi and call
her Kam oi and just make it
clear but actually there's a word for
when you only have one o
that one maybe a lot of people don't
know it's called tan
[Music]
oi t a n
o hi baby chuny won is
B wait it's kind of like
tanos you would say k tanoshi you say
you kind of say it afterwards to state
that you are like kada only
you know k tanoshi i oh my style is K
tanoshi yeah that's my
style do you want to like chill up here
you can if you don't mind hearing me
talk it is very tanosy to have me as
your tan oi times are just more fun you
know
oh meow what is it are you like out of
Kibbles or
what come
here
y
y no
no come
on N stupid cat she just wants attention
you just want attention you don't want
my
heart and you want k
she was interested at first but when I
go to grab her she like runs
away you just want a Tanto you just want
a
tangent you don't want the super
chats maybe I should do a tatuan
stream you just want a tangent you don't
want Dy
shoes maybe I should do
only
[Music]
stream hi chunky monke is back again I'm
pretty sure she's out of Kibbles
otherwise she wouldn't be so
weird she has to wait she won't Die the
game El oliv wait H did you get a kiss
h b
spiral Starfire d Sean Louis
D The Humble Bundle wait I heard about
that before wasn't that even the thing
last
year they give you a code instead of
finding all of the oh the hum bule gives
you code the games are normally region
free and roughly the same priz as Steam
yeah but then I don't have a free choice
of what game I want
right a charity way of Bank
ah yeah that was a thing last
year
a interesting games yeah I do want to
play like Planet zoo and Planet coaster
i' I've had it on my wish list for like
two years I was like oh chunky wonky
jumped up the table okay okay she's
decided to sit here after all and front
of my monitor she's making herself
comfortable she making herself comy
she's so
fluffy okay you can be here I don't mind
enjoy I once in a while and FL flof
floof
you
H don't they have wish lists on their
same account oh
well then I would first of all have to
be friends with them and also I think
generally they don't really use that
function that much I don't use it much
either if I wanton a game I usually just
buy it I don't know why for Planet zoo
and Planet coaster I just keep it on my
wish list forever a she laid down
sideways oh you could probably if I put
my microphone over there you could hear
her
Pur no who's chunky wonky always Pur
tahok uh wait Nick the meme daddy dun
tahok thanks of the pinky potentially
breaking rules suggesting you but I'd
love to see you play Ryme absu or or one
of the valkia Chronicles games or as a
gift for the others happy holidays boss
sorry I didn't end up getting any of
those I don't even I've never heard of
the first
two
Ryu what the hell are those never heard
of them
[Music]
She's So Soft it's so good I wish this
was normal I wish this was normal but
then I would pet them too
much it's nice to have her there during
Super Chat readings though cuz I don't
need both of my
[Music]
hands you'd like valky Chronicles
probably yeah
probably most
likely oh you chin scratch
sure not not such thing
[Music]
exactly and Von D CH D for iron stke
gunvolt one it's $5 similar to games
she's been playing for the past few
years and for B it has to be stranger of
paradise e what's stranger of paradise
but I feel like for Iris we got a
perfect game and I feel like the game
that I got for BA is also good even my
my brother mentioned it yesterday saying
that he wants to play it or was it my
mom I think it was my
brother it's a good game the plague tail
game but Iris game is just like
funny and I hope she'll like
it
m
Yen Dragon oh and
Yen maybe get for didn't she like post
her like cart with like a lot of other
Yakuza games yesterday or so so it was
good that I changed and uh
like yeah decided to give her the other
one she did get all of the games you
could possibly get on
Steam which is what I thought she would
get and that's why I changed it
afterwards
mhm I'm I excited to see her play like a
dragon eventually I wonder which one
she'll play next
by Dragon
[Music]
Thanos than thank you m than Max the
first
than the rats are so legendary bad
legendarily bad it broke some people's
PCS uh yeah I don't think I
would I don't think I would give that
game to
Bells if there's a potential for it to
break her
PC you little
[\h__\h] tyen d
uh how do I read this
[Music]
name thanks for the r Super Chat early
merry Christmas Kima I want to recommend
two German Indie pearls to look into L
Lun Lun
Lun a 3D platform of inspired by old PS1
and Sega games and cross code a 2d
action RPG at least for the format I
know that the dev is pretty open to give
perms wait former former is last or
first
[Music]
former I know uh I knew crosscode
already the other one I don't think I
knew the first oh oh
no well I know I know the publisher of
cross code would probably immediately
give
perms uh yeah I know I know those
Publishers games pretty well and yeah
cross code is familiar to me although I
I I I don't know it's not really
something I would want to play at the
moment but yeah so many people were
recommending that one I don't know the
chat constantly was recommending
crosscode I'm like what why
why weird that was weird was it because
it's by German people and people just
really wanted me to you know after I
recommended
Orie they thought oh let's go German
games too
then yeah it's a good game but like huh
why why were people so stuck on Cross
code I do want to look up this other one
let me check
lunis however you
say oh there's a
cat what the hell
[Music]
they pretty positive
ratings I a Tanuki is not a cat nice
cute that looks pretty
fun looks pretty fun but probably not
for me because like I'm not much of a
platformer
[Music]
h no Tanuki is almost a cat even I have
a Tanuki that is pretty much a cat
or
raccoon
right and well thank you rock Mousa and
Merry Christmas to you too I hope you
had a lovely
Christmas thank you for spending it with
the Wawa once again
and I hope you gifted yourself some nice
games as well I mean that Steam Sale is
incredible I should have gotten into
stream stream sales more often now that
I know that there's one every season
every year I'll I'll be aiming for those
of course got some games ooh which
ones yeah I could imagine the winter
sale being the best
[Music]
one
yeah I'll just do a bulk sale of games
that I want to play in the next
sales maybe I'll stream
it and crayon Z thanks for the pinky hi
K first let me say that your concert was
amazing and it was the perfect way to
end the year secondly since we're
looking at Steam games right now may I
suggest saints road The Third for you
it's a GTA like
game I already got like
Mafia and Red Dead Redemption but let me
check it for
you Saint R I think I heard of
it roughly oh and it's my
birthday just don't tell anyone don't
tell anyone that I'm like 500 years
old or
5,000 oh
oh
game is unhinged it's goofy it looks
like it looks like it could
be looks pretty
good has anyone in Holo ever played it
because I don't think I remember
anything like
[Music]
that well I think for now I'm
like ah I have plenty of games stocked
up right now uh I think lot of people
are also surprised to see TWY in my game
card dur the day I can't actually I was
like planning on playing that eventually
at some point anyway and then I saw it
on sale I was like okay let's get it now
let's get it now and I even already have
perms for it so I think um in Spring
there's a lot of games releasing that I
want to play right and T has been
released for a while so I'm not going to
rush into it but in 2024 I think that
will be one of the games I'll play when
I'm when I run out of RPGs to play if
that ever
happens
yeah yeah because TW we if you guys
remember I told you before it was on DS
first and I played that a little bit but
I just didn't
really get far at all cuz I didn't I I
didn't understand the game mechanics I
think I really sucked at it I didn't
understand what I'm supposed to do so I
didn't get anywhere really but I I like
the characters and the whole style the
Aesthetics the one on stream is a sequel
oh is it oh well we'll play it anyway
even if it is cuz I want
to people were pretty excited and called
me biased when they saw
TW so I think it will be pretty
dope
you ignored parts of the mechanics you
could still play it then even if you
ignor parts of the
mechanics I didn't figure out
anything Al tenture doesn't know
yet no I thought it was like kind of
like a remake or
so H well I look up the story then um I
don't think I'll stream the
prequel so I would just get into the
sequel I think
it's a direct sequel It's the only one I
have perms
for so no the original is on the
switch whatever we'll think about it
when the time
comes Venom than thank
you oh Metal Gear
Rising oh yeah she would probably like
that EO e thank
[Music]
and you youon you than thank you for the
Super Chat promise I would try a certain
game for the end of this not only did I
not do this but I forgot which well I
forgot
too check for the Seven Nation fre black
Tech love
y yellow cake Jasper Garcia Anime boy Dr
Noise Anime boy Mo yuk Channel
[Music]
vus I am a beep black G space waterful
than Peter campy D temp D for the pinky
amazing streams anyways I'm going to be
out of house to celebrate holidays with
family so happy Christmas New Year and
any strange Austrian celebration in
between see you again in the next year
and and in German we say Al Joe
Biden yeah I love it when you guys write
that so
weirdly thank you so much I hope your
Christmas has been lovely I don't know
if you're still celebrating today but
take your time no problem I totally
understand take as much time with your
loved ones as you want you deserve it
and
yeah I'm happy for
you I'll see you again soon I
hope or maybe you're already back I
don't know but thank you so much for the
support and Merry
Christmas yeah and simply D so we're
done with these super
chats [\h__\h] I'm so hungry guys I don't
think I'll even get to
the
um to today's super
chats which is okay I'll check over them
in a different
stream don't
worry I'm so
hungry Merry Christmas C thank you Merry
Christmas thank you well thank you guys
thank you thank you thank you mer
Christmas to you guys as
well
y it's basically already midnight no
it's okay I'll read this one too don't
want to fall behind too much but
probably I mean tomorrow I won't get
super jets cuz it's not my stream and
then collab streams don't usually don't
get so much either so we're fine we're
fun ah
fluff gosh you guys I'm going to let you
hear her Pur in the
end so
sweet and Jacob 47 Dano Nene diesel
thank you for the red super chat sorry
for the late catch up but Fredy life was
fantastic finally po song
revealed thank you for your hard work
boss yeah I was pretty feeling pretty
Carefree during love
[Music]
Rush
psycho yeah I saw so many of you guys on
Twitter like the overseas people getting
tickets already like already um winning
tickets there's still more rounds so if
you didn't make it don't worry about it
but I'm really really happy to see a
couple of you guys getting stage one and
honeyworks
tickets I'm so excited that you guys
will be there
yeah so excited here I'll get rid of
this for you chunky
wonky and you can lie on my controller
you like that don't
you as your
pillow I might try if there's a second
round yeah I think there's like oh well
I don't know there's several rounds for
both overseas and non overseas right I'm
pretty
sure but many people got lucky with the
overseas tickets from what I
saw yeah happy for you guys and Nel I'm
excited for you too you even got both of
the stages where I'll be in that's lucky
as
hell
congratulations
T picture of a telephone that thanon no
it will never be X good uh New York
afternoon than soon or NY afternoon and
D can stamps d f Legacy D Sy thank you
for the red chat yeah I wish you and KY
merry Christmas happy holidays may we
have a good and peaceful time with our
loved ones thank you for the red super
don't go
no I called
her I can't go
[Music]
stay
meow just making weird noises yeah it is
chunky
wonky Ry
cat
H are you just here for the Kibbles in
the end not for me
H
okay don't go just
stay no I'm even talking more quiet
because you were here H okay I'll let
you
go I'll let you
go bye-bye byebye bye-bye
W so much
hair oh I got some of her
undercoat
okay yeah being tund right when our tund
chief showed up can I wish you and KY a
merry Christmas happy Hest may we have a
good and peaceful time with our loved
ones yes peaceful have a good time with
my loved ones AKA my cats but not very
peaceful those Kito C I wish it was more
peaceful looks at
smoothie thank you very much I I hope
you have the same I wish you all the
best Merry
Christmas
[Music]
holy py jus
lber
thank you for the right
chatut timing I manag to catch some my
break Merry Christmas t
y I'm happy to hear that even though
you're using weird words thank you very
much Nathan I hope work went well and
hopefully you got out of it
soonish cuz who wants to work right
before Christmas right [\h__\h]
that
[Music]
I did but like yeah well in Furia I also
worked on Christmas I very much
did but yeah I don't mind I generally
don't mind at all like I as I said I
don't really care it doesn't matter to
me if anything I enjoy working on these
kind of special days cuz we can
celebrate together
thank you
Nathan hope you enjoyed the little radio
at work
H me rocken or M Ken or I don't know
thank you for the red super chat I won't
be able to watch as many of your live
streams because I'll be studying abroad
in Canada it will be different time
zones for me and I'll be focusing more
on my studies Oh
Canada I will still make an effort to
watch your live if I have the chance I
love love you my
kamhi thank you wait so from Philippines
to Canada I feel like I
mean this if anything Canada might be
easier for you
no cuz I mean yeah it will be early in
the morning to like noon
afternoon but Philippines is like
usually when I stream is like night time
no late at
night or wait how much time difference
is there
probably class Yeah well yeah classes
yeah but at least you'll be having
weekends off
right off of
[Music]
school all so it is yeah that's what I
thought I thought it was around Japan
time I'm used to watch you at night
while
damn oh man that's kind of sad but I
hope you still kind of manag to find
time in between mean I don't want to
miss you I don't want to lose you so
please don't forget about me and good
luck that is a huge thing I wish you so
much luck and fun Oh Canada Canada I
think is a great place to go for
studying abroad so make some nice
memories
okay and let me hear from you everyone's
no while let me tell tell me that you're
still
around
good
luck exciting so exciting ah you must be
so nervous but it will be fine it'll be
it will be like oh amazing you'll have
the time of your life oh yeah yeah make
the most of it enjoy
Canada maple syrup straight from the
tree is how they do it there they just
like they all have a tree in their
garden and they just like put a straw
into it and drink it straight from there
that's that's what I
[Music]
hear Al ears D le ran Striker D is that
not how it is what is it that's how it
is
right is just tap it three times and
then it comes
out I'm from Vancouver that's true thank
you thank you thank you I'm speaking the
truth and you are my
witness
they use Taps not R oh oh I I thought
you meant tap tap tap just tap
on shut up they use either taps or
straws okay not everybody can afford a
tap in their tree straw is like the
cheap option okay what do you
know u marus menes d Mar menes again D
thank you I like it it's
cute Windows key plus period to ACC what
wait window ske
period wait I currently have the
Japanese keyboard on to the
mod oh my God marus
Meneses you taught me
something
incredible because like when I whenever
I type
something somewhere where like in a for
example if for example for Community
posts if I do it on the phone I can use
the emojis from phone but when I make
Community post on on YouTube on my PC
there is no way of putting like members
emotes whatsoever so that's whatever but
I can I can also not even there's no
button for normal for choosing normal
emotes either I didn't know for the
longest time until now I didn't know
there's like this combination of course
there is it pulls up all the Emojis you
guys didn't know either
H you know how I would do it sometimes
is I I I switch to ja Japanese keyboard
and then Japanese keyboard when I type
in like kooji which is the word for
emoji then you get like a lot of them or
if I type in in Japanese just the
letters Santa then I get a Santa Emoji
or if I type in hat then I get a heart
emoji and stuff like
that yeah but sometimes I don't find
what I
want oh my God so windows and period oh
wow
wow they even have these Japanese
emoies that's
incredible I didn't think they would
have Japanese style ones unless you're
on a Japanese
computer what the
[\h__\h] unlock your potential for real you
must Windows keep
new power yeah Japanese uh emojis are so
cute damn am I cute yeah [\h__\h] yeah you
guys are going to abuse this power
now nice think we all learned something
[Music]
here actually yeah not only I appreciate
it all these people appreciate it thank
you
Marcus Cruz than Grant c cbw d d thank
you for the red of chat for my birthday
today I want to give you a little
present and thank you for your great
streams and all the enjoyment you bring
to all your fans I'm glad I'm able to
call you my II if it's not too much may
I request a little German Happy Birthday
song of
course of
course happy birthday to you
happy birthday to
you one year older growing
Boulder happy birthday to
you hey even with
original oh wait it was supposed to be
German [\h__\h] I even made the original
Melody
no don't get St F click don't get Bo St
[Music]
okay now you got two
songs
[Music]
chisan thank you very much for being
here on your
birthday
y sorry I couldn't sing it on your
actual birthday but we're not so far
off
[Music]
certainly thank you for the pinky Merry
Christmas K my present for you is
another metal song
recommendation the German band for swans
has a badass cover of icy F oh okay
which is my favorite version of that
song I certainly hope you have a
wonderful
[Music]
year I mean the fact that it's iy fire
is a bit
interesting but metal guys you're not
going to get very far recommending me
stuff like
that I'm just going to put it in my
search bar
because you spent quite some money on
that
a for
on but it's not
really out of my own
well oh hey the guy looks like a
[Music]
viking you like the Viking me
yeah if it's like that okay that will be
fun okay I listen to it now but I I
can't play
it
German band
[Music]
right okay I'm losing
now there's an
egg fire and
smoke keep watching
[Music]
allans
during son
[Music]
yeah who's
that they dress up like
Vikings in their live
concerts
[Music]
together what's she doing with that egg
is she going to hatch
it is she going to go Daenerys
style she doing is she pulling a
Daenerys the
[Music]
mountain oh
wow we should all die together yeah cult
let's
[Music]
go
father the mountain
side
[Music]
the okay pretty cool I stop it here now
because it's pretty
long it's pretty
cool he has a good voice but it's not my
favorite voice to be honest for stuff
like this it's pretty decent though h
H now I even listen to
it was pretty good n no thank
you and merry Christmas to you and Happy
New Year to you too
[Music]
certainly sorry for being so critical
but you know who you're dealing with
right the Lord D 47 D Evans l d Dy Chong
thank you for the words of Chad wish
every kfp employee and merry Christmas
too thank you for such a gorgeous 3d
concert and Merry Christmas now I will
just shut up and listen to this honor
called okay thank
you the Fredy concert
man time is passing and more and more
it's it's just like you
know I wish I wish time wouldn't
pass I don't know just kind of don't
want it to become one of my vods I mean
it it is now but I don't want it to
[Music]
be yeah why why time why why crowny
why
thank you junkie chunk thank you so much
Merry Christmas to you too and happy New
Year soon soon soon soon but we're going
to all say that to each other anyway
soon so let's just stay with merry
Christmas for now chunky chunk SS than
soon G than soon thank
you oh I wonder if that was difficult to
order the
CD thank you
though oh and another one sink's also
got a honey work stage let's go
what
EV
Elias
or thank you very
much for the
pink merry Christmas as a gift to myself
for the first time in life I bought
something called a figure it is an honor
to finally be able to have t in my
room yeah yeah I'm with you in that
room I'm really there yeah yeah
yeah no thank you very much I still
couldn't get my hands on it it probably
would have been in that one package that
got sent
back I still never touched my own
figures yeah but I hope you're enjoying
it I hope you get to I don't know if you
already got it if you're already
received it but uh yeah I hope you like
it very much I wonder which one it is
cuz there's only think two that you can
buy the one that moves where you can
move the limbs and the one where you
can't move the limbs
right there's H H
wait those figures always confuse
me ah so the only one isn't the other
one is not available yet okay
okay so confusing so
confusing cuz like it's been announced
AGS ago and I'm just waiting and waiting
and
waiting like first they start uncolored
and pre-order and then eventually you
you get to see the color but it doesn't
mean you get to get the figurine just
yet I guess I don't
know yeah
damn
[Music]
anyway hope you're going to enjoy it
thank you for supporting me through that
thank game
8910 D and Jack Redwing thank you for
the red super chat hey Yana every time
you sing my heart flutters hopefully
someday they ship the POV album here
soon so I can blast it away 24/7 bog
[Music]
K that is Hungarian thank you Hungarian
fan I think I've heard of uh European
fans receiving
the CD now though no feel I se I've seen
some people talking about it
no oh okay hm too bad ah yeah I see one
one
German maybe it depends on the
country just got to be pray patient and
believe in it believe in it it will
eventually come I hope so I hope so
thank you very much for buying it and
for supporting me and my music it means
a lot to me don't it's nice to have some
more European fans too thank you for for
being here and and part of
kfp H C I think something like that for
thank
you
Bo
milk fellow
Z
Rene thank you for the pinky really
great various times I had to stop
everything else to just hear you sing
Merry Christmas
a thank you that's nice that you wanted
to focus on it every once in a while
appreciate it thank you Merry Christmas
to you too
Renee I'm hoping I can't has a kfp Chen
in it oh not not not as far as I know I
don't think I got
one but there's fanmade jimins so just
combine them Flappy boy thank you for
the red super chat number one out of
two or so where's the other one oh you
got quite
interrupted festive thanks for all
you've done this Advent the cookies the
singing the calendar and all that makes
the season so special you were kindled
for me that magic spark in Christmas
that I had deemed
lost and no song could be more suited uh
to anend than the Canadian anthem song
in
German you deserve nothing but the most
blessed time with your folks this
year wait what Flappy
Boy Flappy boy have you
always donated
in
Euro I'm so conf like we had this
discussion
recently Flappy boy
European the [\h__\h] but why are you
excited about Canada
then
oh because it's sung in an in in German
I
guess I
guess well Europeans are a minority here
so you know I'm I'm always like
fascinated when I see
[Music]
Europeans probably already went to bad
that Flappy boy sleepy boy huh more like
sleepy
boy
Slappy boy is sleepy boy good night I
wish you sweet dreams Merry Christmas
and thank you for enjoying my C so much
I'm glad everybody liked my Canadian
National Anthem that's holy legit thank
you for the big support the big generous
donations thank
you Jim TR no wait alar Jim TR thanks
for the pinky Merry Christmas K thank
you for the Fantastic col I hope you and
your family have have a very happy
holiday thank you I think it was pretty
pretty nice yeah pretty nice pretty good
thank sh I wish you the same hopefully
you could spend some time with them
otherwise if not then that's okay too
can we have oh the oh the bgm was off
so I hate myself
didn't even notice it's nice to not not
have any bjm sometimes I personally very
much agree with that so oh
well yum yum
[Music]
yum anyway thank you to chesse Merry
Christmas
Merry thank you so much I appreciate it
I'm sure you worked hard too
right Jacob 47 Prince of Denmark n g
[Music]
m Ry than than Jaden thanks for the
pinky Merry Christmas k give thank you
Merry Christmas to you
too so considerate to also say it to you
guys marry C
suu hopefully you were good and not
naughty this year did you get presents
huh I didn't get presents uh except for
from you guys so I don't know maybe I
was naughty IRL but uh good on the
internet so that's why I got presents
from you
guys chai D
LPN what the [\h__\h] this one has no
name
why what does it
mean why how can you have no name
someone than soon the Sai than soon C
the pinky Merry Christmas G thank you so
much for spending time with us love you
so much and hope you have a wonderful
holiday with your family I mean yeah it
was fine thank you for the sweet words I
wish much much joy and jolliness to
you Merry Christmas and happy holiday
now be good even if Christmas is over
there's no reason to be naughty now so
be good ma' thanks for Pinky happy
holidays thank you same to you Merry
Christmas ho ho ho
ho
[Music]
water and the
game
game okay it's pretty late now
I'm going to go and eat food and
hopefully sleep early I slept early
today but then I had a long ass nap
so I don't know if that will
work when was I supposed to wakey
wakey Wiggy Wiggy sgy
sgy what did they
[Music]
say
descript
[Music]
uh wait
what wait did I get the time wrong is it
1 hour earlier not 11 but 10 wa 8 no no
it is 11 it's eight hours time
difference
[Music]
so it doesn't say here I feel like it
said somewhere elsewhere when I going to
be
there I I'll find
out somehow somewhere somewhere
deep hidden somewhere the stream frame
is already up oh yeah no
um wasn't it since
like two days ago or
so
yeah I retweeted it I'll retweet it
again at this very moment repost
retweet in case you guys didn't find it
yet so um maybe turn on the notification
for that Stream So you get
notified I would recommend that
no and in German we say I'll in really
big fun today with that Mario game I
feel like I have confidence in finishing
it so let's play more uh later this week
I'll see you there byebye thank you for
watching today
C
byebye tomorrow cor
[Music]
operation
oh
um is this the right
[Music]
one
for