[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
for
[Music]
[Applause]
o
[Music]
[Applause]
what
spe
M M M M
mhm
M MH mhm come here come here come here
come here
baby come here come
here come here come
here e
okay K
[Music]
KY oh
exy howy
how
[Music]
K howy wait why is there two
chats
oh how k
spits in your
face how you like
that it's better than me shooting in
your face a
it what did I do my chat stopped
moving no it died there you go come on
come on
[Music]
yeah there we go there go my mouth was
open
E don't you dare enjoy
it ah I my
spit uh killed the internet
lines yeah what's what's up what's up
what even is HW TOA I don't even know
what that
is I really don't know
[Laughter]
don't look it up don't worry about it oh
no oh no I'm an alaka I love
alas so okay I'm here what
now I show up what
now what what what
play
game what you okay you go screen share
that's what we're supposed to do right
that's what's supposed to be on the
screen you screen sharing you playing
the
game go I'm waiting I'm here to just
react to you playing the
game okay yeah you loading in
okay okay
okay Hol here no you're supposed to play
Fallout what am I wearing my cowboy hat
for oh how to
turntables
a how do I screen share um I don't know
you could use um there's this thing
called uh OBS Ninja can give me a
link like my setup now I'm not seeing it
yet you're not sending
it how do I capture why why why do we
have to start from there this is your
your job
now bro can't even do your job properly
wow we we really got to start from
zero Mama
Mia okay maybe if you guys are still
hopeless maybe I should be the one
playing the
game all right right
okay God damn it
sh
sh sorry yeah yeah yeah you better
apologize Sorry boss uhhuh uh-huh
uh-huh oh it's [\h__\h] loud I know you
guys can't hear it but it's [\h__\h] loud
let
me I'm protecting you guys right now by
not not having it Audible for you cuz
it's too [\h__\h] loud why is your
[\h__\h]
loud all
right
okay
okay H did I when I played Fallout
million years ago did I do full screen
or small screen I don't remember I mean
on OBS I think full
screen so considerate I know I'm such an
empath Man full screen
okay well if you really want it that way
if you really think you want it that
way um but can I tell you a tangent be
before we
start C can
I tell you attention yeah okay okay all
right okay okay thanks appreciate that
appreciate
it appreciate it involves paint so you
know just uh just
me doing a little little ity bitty ity a
little
tangent who's a little tangent you you a
tangent such a good T what's wrong with
me I drank uh free sips of Coca-Cola
free
um let me
go over
here free sips yeah that's that's all it
takes that's all it [\h__\h]
takes now you know why I only drink when
I drink an energy drink where I only
drink two
sips okay come here come here come here
come here good good tablet good tablet
oh wow no not the USB sound does it work
okay it works so uh here here is tangent
um
um here is Furniture piece of
furniture okay and
[Music]
then here
is my big plant that I'm so proud of
like I destroy plants all the
time but this plant I can really
recommend to people who did I tell I
didn't tell this before right it's
recent but I really recommend this plant
to anybody who's really bad with um
keeping plants
alive this one bro I forget to water it
so
often uh it just barely needs water but
it and it doesn't even need that much
light but it still grows and grows and
never stops growing growing growing I
think in general it was called uh GL
fer so good luck looking that up in
English but like it's gigantic
gigantic G gigantic probably
gigantic plants thve on neglect I don't
think that's generally
true but yeah this one is thriving on
neglect it
seems it's it's i' I've had it for years
now this is my best plant in my biggest
plant it's actually huge okay so I have
this plant and now can
I I drew it too big can
I oops no
whatever okay well there's a little bit
left
there [\h__\h] we do we do we need this to
be perfect
up to my standards that's
okay okay and now this just this is
currently like standing there right and
then above I have some cat things why is
this
so there we go I have some cat
F on the wall mounted on the wall okay
these like cardboard thingies and they
jump from one to one to another oh you
barely can see the left side but it kind
of ends there anyway um but like the
last piece this is a corner okay corner
of the
wall like you know it goes that way it
just goes that way you can can you tell
perspective make it your Christmas tree
that's not the
point uh okay but here is uh like this
is is like a hanging Fabric and these
two pieces are mounted to the wall so
this is like a little bed for the cat
okay
so now I make I'll make it smaller
again a little
bit
okay so you know there's I have two cats
right one is called chunky
wonky and and she's Cheeto colored
right and she likes sleeping
here yeah happy happy
cat very happy
cat very happy cat so happy she just
sleeps and sleeps but she's pretty thick
right chunky wonky is known to be kind
of
Fick
now riddle me this kfp
while I was
gone on on these like past four days or
so I got a a
notification from my cats
sitter uh I received a
picture of this
plant completely on the
floor and several of the leaves those
are huge leaves and thick leaves broken
broken my best plant the pot didn't
break cuz it's out of plastic
now I pretty quickly figured out what
happened but my cat sitter um thought
that my cats must have this happened in
the middle of the night my cats sitter
thought that my cats must have knocked
it over like when zooming around or
something and then I was told the chunky
wonky over here she started in the
middle of the night like apparently this
incident of this huge heavy plant
falling down didn't even wake my cats at
her up but chuny wonky meow meow just
like that in the beginning of the stream
that was chunky wony he went
like like recently she does that a
lot she's a little bit more vocal than
usual recently but then yeah this fell
and uh she was meowing meowing meow meow
meow meow and then she goes to my cats
sitter and she like stands right next
and
goes really loudly until it's not
possible to ignore
anymore and then
yeah I uh was sent a
picture no now the the the suspection
suspection the suspicion
there you go was that she just zoomed
around and like knocked it over and then
you know I don't know but I have
detectiv my way through this I am smart
I know my cats very well I have put one
and one together so there is this um
formula here it is
cat directly
above uh plus fat
[Music]
equals equals she fell down and she fell
on
[Laughter]
it while she was sleeping she lost
balance her chunk spilled over a little
too much she lost balance she fell on it
she panicked while falling the then fell
on it like weirdly the plant fell down
as well big mess and cat is
like and the point that I want to make
here that is absolutely adorable is that
you know how many pets out there like
especially dogs when they mess up
something they pretend that they didn't
do it and they like look away and
they're quiet
and chunky wonky
here goes to my cat sitter immediately
and apologizes tells the whole story in
cat language tries to get attention and
it's like sorry I'm so sorry I messed
up no she seemed very apologetic and
very honest and very sweet and very
concerned and very worried probably
worried then when Mommy comes back that
mommy would be maybe angry but mommy is
not angry at all because this story is
too
cute yes chunky wony is okay but this is
cute she's so
cute she thought she was in trouble but
I'm just in trouble
because I'm the one in trouble because I
I got these cute cats
[Music]
and I don't know what to do with this
cuteness right rip plant ah the plant
has a few broken limbs but uh there's
still plenty of uh yeah what is the full
outfit you're
wearing it's my Fallout
outfit if I show
you if I show you the full version
people are going to roast me again for
having fre four arms
wait but anyway cute cute
right so cute my cute babies here all
right it's just my casual
outfit with this like cowboy look and
the Fallout uh
device very cute thank you for sharing
thank you for
listening yay
mhm yeah yeah yeah yeah
the clean version if you if you're
looking into cosplaying this can be
found uh somewhere in on Blue's account
BL BL o
o one of the kfp
artists yes okay
so
he I like this cowboy hat wait should we
should we sell a chicken cowboy hat one
day as
merch oh chicken cowboy hat damn wait
that's so funny I would never I don't
think I would ever like I don't wear
wait I do wear hats what am I saying I
totally wear hats I was about to say I
don't usually wear hats I do wear hats
no I really do that like I like it to
wear
Berets
hello I just told this story about my
cats chunky wonky and here can you tell
what happened happened I think it's
actually rarely my my tangent Arts are
recognizable as to what happened but
this this is pretty obvious clear math
also
demonstrated very clear
math yeah she fell she was sleeping
there and then she spilled over her fat
her chunk spilled over and then she lost
balance while sleeping and she fell uh
on the plant and the plant also fell
down and
broke cute right yeah
cute I could never be
mad okay moving my cintique
back
okay yeah don't don't be quiet now be
quiet now USB
CH extra
Jun what a good we a good
baby it's so
cute okay now we're going to play the
game perhaps maybe why is it not
working
oh we might eventually play the game but
chat where where do you want to go U
actually let
[Music]
me let me use this version of you
okay what were you really top left where
was I then who was I was I like
here long time ago we haven't played in
a long time and apparently I could
finish the game like now if I wanted to
but there's still a lot of side content
and this is like my every once in a
while filler game so I don't really want
to finish it yet
so no
I'm good with not finishing
it don't know about you guys but you
know don't want to get rid of my every
once in a while again wait it's The
Usual the usual deal I have to go on
task manager because it doesn't let me
tab out DLC time DLC
no wait DLC oh I guess there are dlc's I
think originally I said h no I'm not
going to play the DLC but who knows
maybe I will now oh wait the game isn't
sh
where's my
Mouse
Hello
Bro
Mouse
bro okay found
it always so troublesome
okay how about
now
yeah it's been a while please bear oh so
loud why it's so [\h__\h]
loud maybe it won't be so loud in game
Al I can turn it down on my side without
dabbing
out uh yeah
it's full screen yeah yeah that's fine
oh wait maybe I haven't played full
screen in the past who are you are you
my partner and my
dongle a search vaults in the region for
reverse P cleaner look at the
brotherhood's history files relating to
Elders being dismissed help okay we're
going to we're going
to battle music suddenly we're going to
figure out what we want to do
to in a moment where where are we what
were we doing oh oh okay something got
killed what' you
kill that
thing good job oopsie ah ah the menu
uh okay how do I open my menu again
there we go t okay
oh we were doing something with
Veronica is this the Veronica Quest
already Brotherhood Brotherhood
Brotherhood which part of this were we
doing search the vaults in the region
for several Hipp oh we were definitely
doing this right Hippa cartridge filters
search the vaults in the region for
reverse pulse cleaner search the vaults
in the region for differential pressure
control so it want all of this
uhhuh and I was going
for now what is this is this one of the
items it's not telling me which one but
okay there's four arrows though but [\h__\h]
ignore the optional okay
sure wait how do I
know when there's like so many uh on the
bottom left of my navigation like how do
I know which one's like the one I'm
actually looking for and which one's the
closest right
now well I guess I'll
turn okay it should be there ah oh in
there oh oh wait no is that not
just I remember this we were confronted
with dudes and I I had a really hardcore
badass moment where I killed all of
these [\h__\h] so this is this is the
Brotherhood vault is it
not right yeah I was on my way out okay
so we're going perhaps we could go to
this one vault
11 kind of that way
yeah should I go there okay well then
here we
go we're rolling we're
[Music]
rolling [\h__\h] I have to go around this
mountain oh there's an opening there
what is
this it's so close to the other one
okay okay okay let's remember how to
play easy easy easy my dog is hungry
he's going for some yummy
yummy what's ha again what the
[\h__\h] what is that is that your
weapon what Lobster that was it yeah
yeah I know it's scorpions but honestly
if you want to you know have lobster
just eat this and
imagine
imagine that's the gun I gave her oh wow
scary okay can I go through here uh kind
of have to go more left but I'm trying
I'm trying to get around
H difficult
looking difficult
looking come on let me up why my jump so
[\h__\h] oh there we
go
parkour par oh
yeah oh it's invisible
wall okay then what's the best way
[Music]
maybe maybe uh oh wait I could just go
from here
maybe teleport to the 188 Trading
Post and then yeah go that
way
easy oh wait my
arm where's my arm
do I have my fist
up let me try to fix
this when you scroll it I did that
again why is it doing
that okay at least okay here there we go
I took down my arm but I will not accept
such
shenanigans oh
no probably because it's on the
same screen on the same monitor
okay okay am I too big though whatever
it will have to be like this now I don't
want to I don't want to have to task
manager my way out of it
again I was about to say guest done but
that's German uh yesterday
yesterday all my trouble seem so fall
away I was going to say um yesterday
after my
stream I was
uh how the [\h__\h] did I get there I was uh
watching I noticed that Tim the CEO of V
was streaming on Twitch yeah talk about
the production of the video and the
products
etc
etc and I was curious and listened in
but I was going to I I it's not like I
don't have my password to the Twitch
account but uh it has the two Factor
authentification and the app for it I
don't have the access to the app jenma
has access to the app so I couldn't get
into it in the middle of the night
because I never like I think once I log
into it on this computer that is
probably not going to ask me anymore for
a while but I have never logged into it
on this computer I think so you know
couldn't get into my Twitch account so I
was like commenting a little bit on
Twitter is it up
there
maybe and so I don't know I think some
of you maybe some of you were watching
too I saw you in the twitch
chat
uh
[\h__\h] but there was some interesting lore
although I wonder
why Tim seemed is there invisible wall
again Tim seemed kind of
tired and talked about not having slept
you know the past days because of the
video production being yeah very very
stressful you're going the wrong way
what do you mean this game doesn't want
me to
parkour all right all right I don't know
how the [\h__\h] like what what I'm even
looking for but I'll try to go around
then I'm guessing it's not on top of the
mountain then but instead like somewhere
inside okay I'll try to find it but yeah
why are you streaming when you're so
tired just go to
sleep but I watched a little bit of the
stream and was interesting he was
showing off the beautiful knife too a
lot what do you mean I'm not bad at
check I've been checking the map a
million times now
now what do you mean kada is bad at blah
blah blah you have you do have a quest
for the mountain but you'd have to
follow the wiggly Road I
think what Wiggly Road what what what do
you
mean what are you guys talking about
that's another Quest this is another
Quest what's that thing over there
historically you're bad it in this game
you're a bit better
today chicken's getting up te today why
are you so up
huh why are you guys so
up you nervous because of v mean the
products meaning that more of you will
have to sacrifice yourselves and and
you'll soon be turned into chicken Ramen
is that making you
nervous and now now you think oh since
I'm going to die anyway might as well
annoy tento a little bit more than
usual we just missed you okay
okay okay so where am I supposed to go I
guess
like if only it would tell me like what
is this even about this
Arrow but okay so I'm guessing it's one
of the further ones like this
one you're in the right place are you
[\h__\h] kidding me are you [\h__\h]
kidding me I was told I
wasn't what about this
place you guys you guys want to want to
do what we talked about in the beginning
and you guys are going to play the game
because you seem to know how to play it
huh you want to screens share to me huh
after all huh maybe I shouldn't be
playing the
game seems like we can't really
collaborate here and get something good
going where the [\h__\h] am I
going yeah I was in the right place you
say that then I shall go back
so
anyway I was going to say
something so listen up
chickens listen up okay listen
listen I can't get the anymore from
World 22 okay
all oh maybe
here H so so I was thinking cuz so Tim
the CEO of VI was talking about how he's
actually a day one kfp oh no I I don't I
don't know I don't quite believe that I
think he's maybe a day one whole live
English fan but I don't think I'm his
OSI or anything I mean correct me if I'm
wrong but they don't it's totally fine
you know but like at least you know
they Tim knows me like my
activities Oh since a long time okay
okay that's that's really cool and
that's why Tim knows a lot uh about kfp
and all that yeah but then he says that
his uh girlfriend wife partner I don't
know um
is also a big fan since day one and I
found her account on Twitter for MAA
Mona thank you is definitely KP you
think so I need
proof but I can confirm I think his wife
girlfriend is definitely a kfp cuz I
found her Twitter account hi
Ma hello MAA
viewers I found the Twitter account and
she has a
Takami uh icons in her name yeah oh she
marks that made me happy cuz that looked
legit
and uh then when I realized uh I I
figured oh yeah I think I definitely
have been seeing this ladies Twitter
replies for a long time now here and
there so so guys even more
reason it's like kind of a local
business within kfp if you know what I
mean made by kfp for kfp is even more
true now than what we were talking about
yesterday they're one of
us yeah and that made me think what kind
of va is
this should I be
scared are you dead already oh oh that
made me think though
um like how like so randomly I find you
know
kfp in these positions of
power which makes us powerful too you
know and it reminded me how for example
you know how I was guesting at offy last
year and if you
recall uh a staff member like of the
like organization team of off was also
kfp
right and was kind of pushing to have me
on in the first
place and then also like I remember like
when I was thinking about that oh
another another example would also be
Steph who is A
kfp from my understanding a pretty
pretty big one uh and who writes lyrics
who has been hired for all the recent uh
lyric writing jobs from Whole Life
English like for whole life English song
uh breaking dimensions and stuff like
that yeah yeah so like look at all these
kfps hiding and lurking in positions of
power I don't know that was like really
fascinating to me to think about that
yesterday like we got
influence we've got
power yeah I wouldn't be surprised if
one day there's like a vice president of
the United States of America who's a
kfp2 or
so but yeah it made me happy too because
like I thought I thought I was just you
know I I really just wanted to collab
with v because they seemed like a a cool
company to work with with good quality
of food really good nutrients by the way
and really good uh protein by the
way um yeah high quality food high
quality products and everything lots of
love lots of you know effort and you
know small local business so to say
self-made um go Dam it so that's really
why I wanted to work with them because
is just
ah I
knew I knew that uh working with them
would result in good
things I'm just stalling right now in
this room CU I want to tell my
attention why am I taking it I don't
know but then after you know I work with
them afterwards I find out that they're
actually you know fans and they're okay
p and uh like both of them still looking
and that makes me just feel so happy I
don't know because it's like unexpected
and
H oh don't know I don't know it's hard
to say hard to explain it's unexpected
to
find
like yeah fans like like
that and and then I don't know it makes
me feel flattered I guess
also they have an adorable
cat and I noticed when I mentioned the
cat in the Tweet uh the girlfriend like
pushed cuz the C the cat was in the like
visible in the screen cuz the cat was
sleeping on the chair and then the
girlfriend she wasn't like showing
herself on camera but she pushed the
chair so that it would be closer to the
camera because she saw my tweet about
the cat
but yeah um anyway I always press Escape
God damn
it nuca Cola
truck I mean a truck a
toy they're lovely people it's what I'm
trying to say and they're one of us is
what I'm trying to say and I'm honored
and flattered and happy is what I'm
trying to
say dear fellow Vault dweller also thank
you furog thank you it's true it is true
congratulations your dedication to the
Dem Democratic process is the Bedrock
upon which the continued stability of
vault 11 is based now to help you make
your decision for this year's election
the Coalition of vault 11 voting blocks
has put together this handy dwellers
official guide through obtaining
overseers democratically or de do good
uh that contains a summary of the
leading candidates for overseer as well
as their statements Cy positions and
most importantly endorsements sincerely
blah blah blah blah
candidate I'm a devoted husband and
father of six beautiful children my
oldest Sam was on the honor rooll this
quar and I couldn't be proud of him said
his first word and was blah blah
blah wait wait wait wait a second she's
writing don't vote for me let alone even
if I had that still wouldn't mean you
should vote for me consider the fact
that I am grossly underqualified for the
position and that both of my opponents
are far more
deserving I know nothing about
governance you would be hard pressed to
find a worse candidate than me is this
like uh reverse
psychology what is this
experiment I can promise you my
Administration would be a disaster okay
uh interesting this is ridiculous I
shouldn't even be a candidate and I
wouldn't be if it weren't for all the
dirty backround politics going on around
here it's sickening you should all be
ashamed what could this experiment be
something about you know everybody
becoming
president fellow citizens due to the
tragic events of the past few days the
Coalition of the vault 11 voting blocks
has unanimously decided to postpone the
election for overseer pending further
investigation into the
murders is this like a thing where like
if you become president you will
be like murdered and that's the
experiment I don't I don't
what like is it like a
reference to I don't know JFK or
something does JFK like exist in this
world
your security team wishes you to know
that they are working tirelessly day and
night to find the perpetrator and are
already following up on a number of
promising
leads uhuh up to ni the same uhhuh
uh-huh good willing if the Killer is
apprehended swiftly we may have found
prom a promising new candidate for
overseer the
killer huh what
welcome guest effective immediately the
traditional selection process for
overseers hereby
ended in leure of a yearly election a
citizen will be chosen one month prior
to the start of his or her term with our
a main frames random number generator
ensuring complete impartiality and
fairness okay so randomized really
interesting
you voltech will be
there well this will be an interesting
one I'm sure they'll tell me
more about it the deeper I go did I miss
did
I in the beginning was there a vault uh
a p i was supposed to
read NCR Troopers
ugly
rat excuse me giant
rat carton of
cigarettes
suitcase pup cigarettes we can sell
those right those were good things to
sell I think
well that's the dead
end um cigar launch classroom that was a
classroom yeah okay then there were two
more paths over here but wait let me
check back I think this is where I came
from oh look at this
by
bro thanks uh I think I missed three
times Haley is a known adulterant
communist sympathizer elect Haley for
overseer
what kind of uh advertisement is that
also where did I come from here there
you go there was a PC here that I didn't
read what what does that do
oh it added something to my things okay
I'm just
a good doggle it's a good doggle nice
shot what's going on in this
room what's going on in this this it's
this one of old yikes yikes
still
looking how do I zoom in again is that a
rat you guys
okay I'm scared I'm also losing track of
where the [\h__\h] I haven't been yet
and that's a rat it's a crazy
rat what are you doing
uh what's turpentine's do I need that
brao
cleaner give me the
toilets sorry that was funny to me stuff
is super common okay I don't have a
feeling for some of these items anymore
if they're important or not
uh but wait I haven't been to some of
the other rooms
yet let me check it
out it's difficult to tell
where the
clinic that's just another door
okay
glue no I came from there
main entrance
uh-huh okay um then I guess I'll go
down so people don't seem to want to be
elected but it seems like they're they
have to uh sign up for it for some
reason about to make mon look like a
picnic with this
Vault what
why are you comparing it
to what the what happened hi
doggy vault 11 election guide wait are
these the
same this looks like the
same yeah
there okay here let me read the
beginning of this one I'm aware of the
rumors circulating about me I want
everyone to know that they are vicious
lies being spread up by the other
candidates in a desperate smear campaign
campaign I have never in my life done
anything so depraved let alone four such
things ah wait is she she the one from
the poster that I read out loud this one
says don't vote Glover his family needs
him oh no what's going
on
huh
yeah is it dangerous you guys say that
the story of this I hate Nate Nate the
story of this uh vault is weird but is
it is it
dangerous I'm always on alert you
know bro
oh my
arm my arm that never happened
before all right okay I have a couple of
stim packs will you do this to me
too oh no okay but it's the same stuff I
want new
information I hate Kate instead of Nate
rumors about Haley are baseless vote
Stone Club has done nothing wrong okay
okay what's
what common
room or is it the Communist room
h i don't don't even really know what
that
means I'll leave it to you
guys I leave the killing to you guys you
have a note I picked up an AIO loock
okay okay I I'll check it
out should
be
uh
here are we really going to do this it's
open we could just leave I couldn't not
after that we don't deserve to leave a
shining example that's what it called us
but we were we did what we were supposed
to not by a long shot anybody would have
done what we did you ask me that's
exactly the problem now let's get on
with this I'll go first wait wait people
should know what happened they could
learn from it if there's anyone out
there at all I hope they never have to
find out ready Harry yeah no no no
wait four corops at the front entrance
of vault 11 and the strange recording
points to Sinister events determine what
happened to the citizens what I have to
determine
challenges
what oh no
okay no what do you mean what do you
mean
determine oh is that Vault what what
Vault well don't don't tell me but like
I'm I'll surely find out I'm surely
getting closer to it
it's got something to do with voting and
dying hi lunch
box fishing battery cup
conductor looking very closely at
everything for more hints
H admin room can we just
enter wonderful why does I what's with
my reach my gun reach is
[\h__\h] overseer's office and security
H should try
to what killed something somebody killed
something oh what are you doing I guess
we'll go down
here my dog is doing
stuff but upstairs I guess where are you
finding these enemies door to vault 11
low level hey I don't know should I go
somewhere else
first did the explosion damage the gun I
don't think that a
thing I was seeing things
Nice
Shot go go
move I'll go in here first looks good
looks
good this is the security
office a
grenade some rounds I don't know
probably not for me what rounds do I use
right now guys
whiskey I'll take one 10 mm okay I got
some this is
new excerpt from the deposition of the
defendant Catherine Stone by Vault
attorney Gerald Geral miles question
okay let's pick up where we left off
Kate Catherine sorry right Catherine I
keep foret getting my husband calls me
Kate you were telling us of a discussion
you allegedly had with Roy gotle of the
Justice block uh not allegedly had we've
been through this it's still just your
word against his Miss Stone but please
the
discussion he said my husband's name had
come up in their meetings the candidates
endorsement meetings uh yes they were
going to endorse him he wouldn't say why
but I know my husband had a regular
poker game with some of them and he'd
been on a winning streak lately and
according to you what did Mr GLE offer
he said he could sway his block prevent
the endorsement but only if
I sway the
block only if you what Catherine only if
I only if you performed sexual favors
yes was this just for Mr gutle no all of
the block leadership they're friends
and you agreed what else could I do they
had the
majority wait
uh is this like
where maybe maybe so they have a
Republican and a de Democratic candidate
and the one that loses their party will
be killed or something like that I don't
know so they're trying to sway it so
that they stay alive I don't no
okay
uh how long did this go on before the
endorsements came
out I I don't know a month maybe and
when they came out and your husband was
endorsed despite your supposed agreement
was that when you decided to kill
members of the block
oh yes I thought their majority is
pretty slim if I fin things out a little
especially in the leadership someone
else might get
elected assuming weren't Caught no Mr
miles I expected I expected to be caught
that was my best chance now they'll
elect
me confessed murderer you think voters
would be willing to risk putting you in
charge they have to pick somebody and
live with their reasons yes but wait and
see wait so she killed
people
to make wait in her own party to make
her own party smaller and then get
herself
elected the
what I think we should vote for
her I am not fully understanding
this she's got my
vote H what no wait we spoilers explain
that part to
me she's trying to save someone yeah her
HB
husband a [\h__\h] no
science [\h__\h] damn it I hate
Kate explaining as spells
okay feel like I'm in a loop
I'm
scared but it's just stupid
rat stupid ass rats Bo
there
wait there enemies there
chill what
shot oh there's thing
here how do
I a trip wire well is it off
now how do I how do I do the slow motion
thing
again that's a one shot trap okay damn
it activate
is this like a parliament
setup why is it getting darker it's
freaking me out oh there's rats running
around maybe it's the light going on and
off chill Rex
chill reques key no where still looking
still looking for the key okay find it
hurry
up it's probably not in this room is it
heck pre-or money
O
Okay guessing it's in a different room
Dam
it why did this show up now I had to
level up like 1 minute
ago uh what should I skill into we're
almost level 100 of
spee but maybe something else is more
important
I wish I had more science but leveling
science now I don't know if there's a
point in it
repair 100
speech L science
good let's get this to 100 that's Max
okay maybe get this to 60
then and then repair also
okay and we get a new skill
thingy uh are the lower ones the new
ones how many new ones are there
always weapon stri require two points
lower the attack perk allows you to
select a fourth skill to be ATT attack
skill having cam resist perk means
you're 50% less likely to develop an
addiction to
cams action Grill perk you gain an
additional 15 action points to use in
Vats
ooh attack is 15 free skill
points don't get tag tag is nice tag is
great why why is steam power twitch
saying don't get
tag one skill
only you
don't straight to the midsection and
down they go and that's you do an
additional 50% damage with attacks
targeting the Toro oh
Center of mass any cems you take last
twice as long
o
uh tag massive
waste 15 is 15 a lot I feel like it's a
good
amount 15 sounds like a good
amount and usually I use Vats more often
now I just don't remember how to use it
right
now I
let's go for it but you guys got to
remind me how I use it V okay V for vat
okay okay right now I can't use it but I
need to find the
key is this where it came from okay
so that's a dead
end but I hear
enemies okay and let's go uh this way
utility that goes down and then the
atrium is over there but inaccessible
what is this
room or this
path I'm going to get
lost utility
also oh oh water uh okay dead
people and the
[Music]
Mantis hug the left B to navigate am
maaz
reliably really is that survival skills
or
something aha I was like literally just
thinking like does this room also have
like some kind of trap I should be
careful H
run what
why I'm scared where's my lady by the
way what
Ron can I am I good to
enter
[Music]
F I'm going to hate the plant Vault if
you go I wasn't I already in the plant
Vault I was in something very planty for
sure heal you're almost dead
oh I totally wasn't looking at that
where are my lunch boxes maybe the
nucas cing beans
what
huh what are you doing
Veronica scared for my life over here
bro what exploded was that
a is that a mine on the ground oh trip
wire M okay it looks like they're
usually just just by the
entrance they had like a war or
something here
10 mm rounds 1 mm
rounds like
uh what do you a civil war or something
like that put in a vault in a
small in a small version small small
Civil
War right is that what this is
attempting to
be is this the other entrance to this
room that I was looking at and then I
walked past it I don't know ah this is
confusing okay there's water here I'm
I'm okay to swim right and I'm supposed
to swim through here probably I don't I
don't know something about these parts
where there's like water going down I
feel like I'm going to get like stuck in
there and die it's concerning I don't
really like the idea of it
okay I'm healing I'm healing I'm healing
slowly safe
first
uh all
right you have the reever am I wearing
it how where is that thing is that an
apparel oh I'm wearing
it I'm scared
wait um uh let me heal up probably first
it takes so
long where the where's the
food a b c d where is lunchbox why is it
not under
L is it in MK is it actually not
edible it's not [\h__\h]
edible what the heck
make yourself more
useful as for
crafting it's just a box okay great just
a box just a
box are you going in doggy careful you
don't have a r
[Music]
braver wait can I actually put food in
how much more food do I need to
eat I want to use my stim packs I need
those come on come on a bit more yeah
yeah there there you
go okay okay I think I'm going to go
what am I looking for here I'm scared
I'm scared I'm scared
scared any traps here probably not right
on the water differential pressure
control that sounds interesting do I
need that is that a quest item oh
God random dog
feed let me open that why can I not open
it
[Music]
I'm
scared come on 9 mm rounds nothing
interesting I need to find a key is the
key on the Water
[Music]
Somewhere this goes up again is this
where I came from oh this is that place
H didn't find anything
good
ah look at this room wait traps wait
wait wait dog careful
careful
okay reactor
oh sorry oopsie why'd you open the door
doggy where you
going dog never stays with me dog just
do whatever dog wants to do it's a dog
life a wonderful doggy
life okay can I check out this oh wait I
thought this was a PC what is
this there's nothing here small
books pilot lights there's nothing
really
here gotta go further in you can tell
him to react defensive oh but not it's
probably good like you know he clears
away from
me why does this have so many special
locks on
it why' you open it why' you why'd you
open
it why did he just
how the [\h__\h] does a dog open that huge
ass lock
anyway we'll never
understand I hate the way this works in
this
game missiles all right
I was expecting something
else floor check floor check to the left
to the
right oh this is some more of that like
Civil War stuff um this one's pretty
underwater louds speaker
oh
radiation he's having
fun dogies in
water having the time of their
life plune plun plune plune plune
plune oh okay this one's properly locked
I don't think my dog can
handle this one I'm scared I'm scared
I'm scared I'm
scared where am I
[Music]
going just more rats like what is this
place rats can't be
president well I can't linger too much
because like this place is radiating
me okay there's a door here here that
goes up okay and this one goes further
down should I go down I don't know down
or up down or up down or up what first
we'll probably have to go both ways but
what's
better down down down down down
okay are you saying that because you
know and you've been here before
reactor okay I've seen that sign before
what kind of reactor n
nclear you're now sick with minor red
poison okay wait wait what that again
that you have to take when you're sick
with rad
poison right
away how do I know how much I
have it over
here I have ah okay it's directly here I
I'm on 200 now right okay I've gained
the free radical
perk what does that do does that give me
more resistance like
less something I'm
scared by the way he's more sick I'm
scared I'm
scared oh nothing's alive here right
sorry so no need to worry
surely nothing alive is here skeleton
moves cuz I bump into it terrifying
[\h__\h]
godam you're too strong for anything to
really hurt you here okay if you say so
oh
wait I thought I was taking
things except except for the radiation
you know that might be the end of me
what's 22 LR
round oh this one I can
open again there's nothing really
here maybe this way they for very
specific rifles oh this one goes up H
I'm scared I'm scared
either it this looks very similar or
I've been here before this door is also
open yeah this down and this up okay all
right all right all
right cafeteria reactor what was what it
was even to find to be found in the
reactor we've been
here I didn't find did I miss
something didn't find anything of
importance
seemingly
cafeteria oh there's some heat going on
there so wait when I shoot it explodes
or how does that work
again m
H lots of food oh is that a is that a
mine yes it
is I got you this time before you got
me gas
Leake what happened
is was that a late reaction a delay
reaction to my mind
exploding seems like the gas L is gone I
don't know it's not wobbling anymore but
maybe maybe it's still maybe I should
still be
careful you got too close and you're too
hot what mine's there a sound and they
activate yeah know that one I I
deactivated by the destroying
It
Anyway
yummy okay this is just the food
section I'm trying to find something
interesting perhaps a key for that one
door that was uh
closed
completely I guess we're not finding it
here
I voted for you and most life for the be
thank
you yay appreciate
it I am glad
to be your choice your first
choice wow there's a lot of food oh yeah
this is a good food loot for
sure oh oh no cucumber
wait how's my health oh my health is
full otherwise I would just eat it these
are like are these forever or time
limited I forgot I thought these were
time limited or no are these forever but
they don't have weight anyway uh
time temporary
okay I need to get rid of
something I really something that weighs
a lot and that I don't
need do I still need the powder gang
playe
outfit not anymore right cuz powder is
known by Jinx
now no how do I throw it
away what do I click to throw it
away good joke right right cook thank
you
can I throw the Boomer helmet and the
Boomer flight suit and yeah no just
these
two shouldn't need those anymore right
yeah what about
weapons wait maybe where the the
[Music]
the ammo is just weightless always right
I picked up the missiles that was waight
lless yes okay something here that I
repair I right wait can we do the the
thing where we combine things
again
repair oh this combines with the
Marksman
carbine does that make sense or should I
do it the other way around for some
reason do
it okay
cool I'm still very cucumber
maintain ah this one needs 9 mm
pistols the Maria
gun still looking difficult here I guess
I'll throw away some food I guess I
don't need that
much but it feels like a
[Music]
waste big book of
science like this one how is this Aid
doesn't even say how much it would
heal is heavy use
it oh signs increase by okay so this is
not temporary right that's
permanent ah ah right I can give stuff
to Veronica and the dog I forgot about
that do I have any more of those books
those heavy books this one's
different that's one's different
but are I they're they're not even
here I can't give them anything they're
not here I don't know where they
went I I shouldn't eat this if I don't
need it because it's just going to give
me more
radiation crisy s
goodbye if I just if I need more food
I'll just have to buy more
food what's end minus
one One Less ending in Fallout that I
can
play endurance okay a wait this is also
one of
those o
nice how many more do I have that I'm
just not noticing
sorry guys I'm I'm so like uncertain of
what to get rid
of not the V ramen noodles I need to
keep the V ramen
noodles M has a lot of junk in it oh
okay um uh can I sort by weight I don't
really see a sorting option
Caravan deck I think you guys told me to
keep that the
cigarettes let's get rid of a couple of
cigarettes I don't need that much money
right Veronica took the day no no no I
saw her running
around even though she's unrecognizable
to me I still know it's
her oh I still got somebody's [\h__\h]
head in
my in my inventory uh drop the fishing
battery fishing fishing fishing fishing
a b c
d there okay now we're looking a lot
better all my
junk I let out all my
junk why was this room so disappointing
I have so much nice food and I can't
even take it with me where am I supposed
to go
now goodbye lunchbox you're
fired feel like I'm missing something
did I go in here before oh wait this
room's new didn't go in here but where
are my people oh I looked at this room
from
above oh rat is
dead
nice I'm scared is there any anything
ooh prepared speech of Gus olon utsman
for the annual overseer election Okay
let's listen let's listen is it
audio audio Str wait I have a
password a it did it come with the
speech the password is
Betty uh prepared speech BL good
afternoon it's year it is the appointed
task of the utsman not only to officiate
the election
but to Chronicle it in hopes that after
the last overseer has finished his term
and walked to his death in the chamber
beneath his
office and the Vault has become still
now one day some excavator from
Humanity or perhaps some yet unknown
race of super
beings might find our records and
incorporate them into historical
Cannon what
but lately it's occurred to me that
that's not really why I think the real
reason we do it is because we want to
believe that somewhere in the archives
there's an answer to all of this or
perhaps there will be one when the
historical records are completed and the
whole story is told we want it to make
sense yeah make it make sense to
understand why the vault's main frame
will kill us if we do not offer one of
our own as a yearly
sacrifice just makes so what you how why
is your experiment to elect a president
which really is just a sacrifice what's
the
point
H to know if people will still but
that's not even
voluntary to fully comprehend why we
continue to have these elections despite
the unfettered corruption that has
plagued it for what must be decades by
now
there was a simpler time when elections
meant shaking hands and kissing babies
but now with the rise of the voting
blocks and this infestation of bribery
drug trafficking smuggling and God knows
what else we want to know
why well I've been through the archives
and I can tell you you won't find the
answer there you'll find an account of
the first overseer who entered the vault
as the only citizen aware of the
sacrifices that would have to take place
but he didn't have the answers either if
he did surely he would have foreseen the
Citizen's anger when he broke the news
surely he would have guessed that they
would want to choose a sacrifice
democratically in the way that we Citi
citizens are accustomed to washing our
hands of terrible
Deeds ah so wait in in the beginning
that it wasn't about voting for The
Sacrifice it was just like we need a
sacrifice and then there conclusion was
well let's just vote for one or
what uh and that his name would be at
the top of the polls oh wait wait wait
in
the surely he would have guessed that
they would want to choose a sacrifice
democratically in the way that we
citizens are accustomed to washing our
hands of terrible deeds and that his
name would be at the his name as in the
the overseer the first guy on the top of
the poles and that the Sim simultaneous
vacancy of overseer and M martyr would
forever fuse the two positions here in
vault
uhuh so basically if people don't like
it you're screwed yeah but then why are
some people making themselves I guess
they weren't really making themselves
unpopular not really or just just saying
don't vote for me Tom mon till I get my
armor let's
go but he didn't he had the answers no
more than any of us and the records
state that after the citizens discovered
that the sacrificial Chambers password
was his wife Betty's first name and its
door was unsealed so he could be offered
as the first
sacrifice he walked down into that room
crying like a child wait what what's
what does this last part mean he had the
answer the the records state that after
the citizens discovered that the
sacrificial Chambers password was his
wife Betty's first
name and his door was unsealed so he he
could be offered what I don't understand
this last
part what is this
saying can you guys tldr this last
sentence like simplify it
he says in a Flur way that if he' known
they were going to kill him he wouldn't
have signed up as the
overseer couldn't he couldn't he give
himself some
immunity as the
overseer the first has no idea why there
must be a sacrifice
too people voted for him to be come to
sacrifice found out the password to the
sacrifice sacrifice him
why did they need the oh because he
wasn't going in they needed the password
because like they chose him to be
sacrificed he was like nah I don't want
to but then they found out the password
to get him into the sacrifice room
pushed him in there or
whatever and then the deed was done I
guess but then but then but then okay if
the first
overseer was killed then why why did
they even continue the uh
project couldn't they have just said
okay let's stop this this is weird let's
just continue living
normally well I guess we'll find out
maybe still I don't know the r say so
[\h__\h] the
rules ah well once a year at least isn't
so
bad I can only wonder if there are no
answers to be found and we are just
going along with this because we don't
see another choice mhm well there's what
do you mean just don't do it
nevertheless I still hold on to hope
that we can find one I urge you all to
take the journey I took to remember that
it wasn't so long ago that we were ruled
by our Civility and our dignity and that
those were times when we didn't have to
be quite so ashamed thank
you
weird weird
I missed one important detail what
it's they would all die if they didn't
if they didn't keep the sacrific and the
main frame would keep kill everybody the
main frame has some kind of system
that's built into this Vault it would
kill them if they didn't sacrifice
damn shame read the beginning of the
note again
okay this part too prepared speech for
Gus Al utsman for the annual overseer
election good afternoon each here it is
uh the appointed task of the utsman not
only to officiate the
election but to Chronicle it in hopes
that after the last overseer has
finished his term and walked to his
death in the chamber beneath his office
and the Vault has become still that one
day some excavator from Humanity or
perhaps some yet unknown race of super
beings might find our records such a
long sense
and incorporate them into historical
Cannon historical
can so
what continue I already read
this yeah the main FR is the actual over
here
mhm but lately it's occurred to me that
that's not really why I think the real
reason reason we do it is because we
want to believe that somewhere in the
archives there's an answer to all of
this or perhaps there will be one when
the historical records are completed and
the whole story is
told read it again are you guys pointing
guns at me forcing me to read it again
and completely understand it's talking
about you reading uh me I guess yeah I'm
reading the historical
records well what did I mean with it
becoming historical
Cannon what
well I mean yeah that's the point that I
am I I am the goal me reading this was
the
goal wait did they stop making babies at
some point because why is nobody left
anyway I guess the civil war broke out
and then they killed all of each
other you stopped right before the s
that mentions that the computer will
kill
oh I lost hope that I will find my
answers you know okay so where haven't I
been yet I I got a password so that was
for
the should I go towards the reactor
again or the
cafeteria wait what is the fast running
button wait never mind there was no none
such thing in this
game you can go to the overseers office
now yeah if I find
it
uh ah put the gun away how do I put the
gun
away I'd love to see my friends
again
oh wait his speech is in here
too
why I could have found it
already hold
R but I need to be ready to
shoot
okay I thought that was the
way I feel like I need to be up
here
H yeah
I'm
lost the children thing made me think of
something ja what if people had children
just to make them overseer and spare
themselves
bro but surely that was a minimum age
right and you'd have to grow your child
first
right and then you would be so attached
to it that maybe you didn't want to do
that
anymore hopefully well I don't know
maybe it makes it worse when they grow
up because then you you're probably more
attached cuz you went through so much
together and saw so many deaths
together running against a baby
candidate what does that say about you
huh
uh where I where I come where do I go
where do I
go do I where do I come
from oh found
it oops wait a second where do I even go
again I
forgot
a where do I put the password
in I'm scared what what's
happening I don't even know what just
happened I thought my game was crashing
I don't know why I was screaming at that
but wait what what did you say put it
into the computer into that
one oh maybe oh did it already put it in
automatically effective immedately the
traditional selection
ended seon will be chosen one month
prior to the start of the our main
frames random number generator I'm
complet
ah wa we already read this before but
now it makes a bit more
sense so at some point
they yeah they didn't want to vote for
the people
anymore and so the system changed it to
RNG yeah
great ah oh there we go open sacrificial
chamber where is that
wait wait I don't want to go in there
without my friends
like are they sacrificing
me are Veronica and my dog sacrificing
me did they choose me to be sacrificed
is that what's
happening where are they
well surely it's just corpses right no
big deal oh wow wait
wait what if you're not dying you think
you're dying but you're just walking out
of the
Vault this looks like just a path
outside congratulations martyr your
fantastic journey is only just beginning
please proceed to the light you'll see
uh well I don't want to
die how do I avoid
dying the light is calming and puts your
mind at ease go to the light what if I
don't uhuh
whoa
uh that's a nice looking room over there
you can't complete the quest without it
oh [\h__\h] so is that an
ending welcome please sit in the chair
huh the show is about to begin so I'm
I'll be watching a movie when I die nice
maybe maybe all the systems are off you
know I won't even be seeing the
movie voltech presents happy Trails y y
y y what do I do what do I do s and get
back up greetings martyr and
welcome if you're here now it means
you've been offered up as a sacrifice so
that your Vault can continue to thrive
currently you may be feeling sad or
angry sa perhaps you never got to have
grandkids safe before anyway or to enjoy
the pleasures of a fresh cigar but march
with your chin held high Soldier and
remember that each of us has an
important role to play for some people
their role might be to heal the sick for
others it might mean they will drive a
race car or fly a rocket ship and some
of us are meant to Forfeit our lives for
the good of the people sure it might not
be as fun as driving a race car but it's
every bit as important let's take a
moment to reflect on the moments that
made your life worth living think about
that time you kissed your steady girl
for the first time under the bleach at
the big game when you snuck out after
curfew cat that your parents wouldn't
let you see because it was too scary
nice massage boy were they right and who
could I have so many more massages to Wi
this life to feel what a looker witness
these are just examples do you feel that
feeling
singes think of these things good what
you are feeling is peace you've led a
great life peace peace living it has
been its own
reward but it is only the beginning
close your eyes now and imagine what J
what's to happen how do I survive the
afterlife can you see them surely it
doesn't work any ah
I was saved I was
saved I've been giving another chance to
live life perfect ending thanks Todd no
legitimately thanks for saving my life
man I've been saved I don't have to die
[Laughter]
H I thought the thing that just opened
up was like going to like be one of
those things that move closer like the I
thought the walls were going to close in
and crush me or
something what was going on let's check
I
guess best time crash you could possibly
have in this game
yeah well I'm going back
in I guess
I double saved I had a quick save and a
normal save
so for some people their role might be
to heal the sick for others it might
mean they will drive a race car or fly a
rocket ship and some of us are meant to
Forfeit our lives for the good of the
people sure it might not be as fun as
driving a race car but it's every bit as
important let's take a moment to reflect
on the moments that made your life worth
living think about that time you kissed
your steady girl for the first time
under the bleachers at the big game or
when you snuck out after curfew to catch
that new flick that your parents
wouldn't let you see because it was too
scary Dam the right and who could forget
when you met the look like it was doing
anything what a looker what do you mean
I these just examples do you feel that
feel in your chest as you think of these
things I soft lock myself good what you
are feeling is peace you've led a great
life living it has been its own reward
take DRS take out only take a weapon
close your eyes
now a Joys await you in the next what's
a good weapon what's a quick quick quick
what's a good weapon can you see what's
a good weapon
good and why why are my people not with
me
this is a sniping sniping gun what are
you okay never mind maybe not roll up
brain it's already doing
damage oh there's something back there
though wait the Sentry is shooting me
[Music]
wait
uh uh those are behind me
sh uh drugs
wait which
[Music]
ones grenades okay I don't know how to
use
those Med
X damage resistance it doesn't stack
right going to die I'm going to die
I don't think I have
psycho oh I
do oh
[\h__\h] I took that took that by accident
is that really bad I'm scared I'm scared
I'm scared I'm scared you don't want to
use grenades re about your pulse rifle
okay okay
okay pulse gun I don't think I have a
pulse rifle only P
gun is it good
enough I only have
wait so
scared do I need to kill all of
these what the
[\h__\h] how am I supposed to do
this I'm supposed to do
this how I supposed to do
this oh nice slow motion is always good
what you're kidding
me not from that menu well it's fine I
died for some people their role might be
to heal the sick for others it might
mean they will drive a race car or fly a
rocket ship and some of us are meant to
Forfeit our lives for the good of the
people sure
it might not be as fun as driving a race
car but it's every bit as important
let's take a moment to reflect on the
moments that made your life worth living
think about that time you kissed your
steady girl for the first time under the
bleachers at the big game or when you
snuck out after curfew to catch that new
flick that your parents wouldn't let you
see because it was too scary boy were
they right and who could forget when you
met the love of your life what a look
these are just examples do you feel that
feeling stirring in your chest as you
think of these things good what you are
feeling is peace you've led a great life
living it has been its own
reward but it is only the beginning
close your eyes now and imagine what
Joys await you in the next life do I
still have the same amount of items as
before I died can you see them good
no no no no no can I stand here where's
where's the best place to
stand why are they already doing damage
to me the doors aren't really open even
[Music]
no I die so fast what am I supposed to
do do you feel that feeling stirring in
your chest as you think of these things
good where are the is peace turs you've
led a great life living it has been its
own reward but it is only the beginning
close your eyes now and imagine what
Joys await you in the next life the
afterlife I don't know if I where do I
have a grenade see
good wait are you already starting I'm
not ready bro
wait wait wait
wait for stealth
bo uh how's that work work
again I've been using bats
[\h__\h] hello care more about him but it
doesn't doesn't show me the thing it's
broken ah there you go I
can't
there maybe two shots is okay cuz cre
say I two shot it right okay
gotta be
[Music]
fast
okay
uh a [\h__\h]
oh hello okay you're pretty close that's
good oh there's one of the brain are you
important should I get rid of you can I
maybe should I do first these ones for
whatever
reason okay okay okay Sentry first okay
I'll look for the Sentry but at least
that thing is also gone now
uh what gives me AP like AP is
the this one this one fills up my thatat
thing again
right or jet or I don't think I have jet
see I have have
but it's AP right
rebound oh
okay so
Sentry
uh a it doesn't show me any sentries
right now only the all the [\h__\h]
turrets should I take those down too
now oh is that what you
mean they mean the turret
okay it's hard to select them there we
go but
32%
29% that's really
low got to get
closer well then let me shoot the robo
brain doesn't everything end if I kill
the robo brain or something like that
for example
I can only shoot like
once no
[\h__\h] okay wait so I take these shots I'm
try to move a little bit closer to the
uh
turrets then open my menu eat another
rebound or something or do you think it
loads up like how how does AP load up
again stick to the corners hide in the
corner and reload then go closer does
reload
are it's been a while it's over
time rebound is an instant Ah that's why
it's still kind of low
okay [\h__\h] I'm GNA
die but hiding in the corner I'm so far
from the
turret okay they're only in those side
rooms
right oh
hey I thought y'all we all
gone
no this [\h__\h]
menu open the Daniel
couldn't open this cuz I was reloading I
don't know if my shots went anywhere on
those
[Music]
turrets really I got
one oh God which one the right or the
left one
right one okay what so what does stealth
Boy do again I everything around me
become slow or I become invisible or
what what was
it makes me
invisible
okay well only if I crouch or
so no right
it' be a waste if I use it now wouldn't
work now they can already see you oh
okay that was to avoid the whole fight
hey I could have done
that why did you guys tell me you wanted
me to
suffer I don't know I don't know I was
just running straight towards it I don't
know
why maybe I should on left and right
left and right do you feel that feeling
stirring in your chest as you think of
these things SC good what what if I take
this for now peace you've led a great
life living it has been its own
reward but it is only the beginning
close your eyes now and imagine what
Joys await you in the next life the
afterlife can you see them good
do they see
me do they see me are they going to see
me what now what now what now what
now this is not going to go on forever
how do I try to take them
out Sak attack
Pi I don't want a pick
pocket what there a door to do you feel
that feeling stirring in your chest as
you think of these things good I was
walking up to them you are feeling is
peace you've led a great life leave
living it has been Z
reward but it is only the beginning
close your eyes now and imagine what
Joys a you in the next life the
afterlife let's let me analyze can you
see them good can they see me
good I would have been cool if I could
have killed everybody but this is pretty
[\h__\h] hardcore maybe if I had my
buddies with me but abandoned me and
sacrificed
me oh God override
lockdown there's a solution
here recording downloaded record oh okay
I can listen to this later oh 500 XP
it's over
there wait what now are they still
there now you come you [\h__\h] I'm done
with you I am so [\h__\h] done with you
wait wait where they so do they not
shoot
anymore cuz they're not shooting at my
buddies but my companions no sneak out
it's over
am I still
invisible not going to [\h__\h] help them
they didn't help me a
bit
alert I'm still invisible safety cannot
be guaranteed oh he's almost
dead I know I kind of want
to
sh they're all Landing so I can't I
can't walk out
why' you tell me to
shoot
why all right I guess we're still doing
this
but I'm still invisible so what do they
see me I don't
understand PE
[Music]
this nice I got uh it probably just
needs one hit right I don't know
[Music]
come
on come on
okay hello welcome no no welcome welcome
it's your turn now yipp you want a turn
you get a turn maybe that's only one
shot right oh that looks like
shot are we done seems so quiet no I
still see enemies there but maybe they
haven't seen me they haven't perceived
me but how how am I supposed to walk out
of this
is how can I walk
out go safe sa
F5 are these shots even going to land
this one should be okay but
[Music]
what was
that what was
that I exploded it okay one shot per
turret
okay [\h__\h] they're so in the
way but is the only red thing on the
screen is that just a turret
how much percent
14 oh
okay okay chill now now we're kind of
chilling here now we're
good eat some
squirrel relax a little bit nice safe
okay just two turs
left sorry friends but you kind of
[\h__\h] me over too so I [\h__\h] you over as
well that's just how it
works 26
okay now I'm super close what there's
four four
turrets oh yeah all right all right I
got full H full
AP
51 don't know wait it won't let
me there you go and one more can we get
them all in one go come on come on come
on who's a good turd who's a good tur
yeah you are oh good
turd
oh oh look at
go kill it kill it BL
it
okay
okay [\h__\h] did it it was chaotic and
weird
and
Dr good morning good
morning and I
mean yeah well let just all you know
shake hands make
up and do spicy things yeah let's not
think about what we have done to each
other and how we have abandoned each
other
anymore although I do think you guys
sacrificing me and letting me walk into
this room here alone here speaks volumes
[\h__\h] I will not forget that one in
particular okay uh there was some
stuff all right I know you can hear me
so listen up there's five of us left
five out of I don't know how many so
it's over
we've talked and it's over we're not
going to send anybody to die anymore so
shut off our water or gases or do
whatever it is your program to do but
we're done listening to you thank you
yay the knife is amazing congratulations
citizens of vault 11 you have made the
decision not to sacrifice one of your
own you can walk with your head held
high knowing that your commitment to
human life is a shining example to us
all and to make that feeling of Pride
even sweeter I have some exciting news
despite what you were led to believe the
population of vault 11 is not going to
be exterminated for its
Disobedience instead the mechanism to
open the main vault door has now been
enabled and you can come and go at your
leisure but not so fast be sure to check
with your overseer to find find out if
it's safe to leave here at vault tech
your safety is our number one
priority it was really that
simple it was really that
simple I
said just don't do
it I mean yeah okay we the thing back in
your mind that if you say you won't do
it then everybody gets killed and still
making that decision is a very brave one
and and yeah that's obviously why you
don't want to say we're not doing
it but yeah you got to call a bluff but
like who would know that it's a bluff
when you already know they're [\h__\h] up
simply by the fact that when it comes to
sending sacrifice in there it's actually
really going to be killed
apparently so yeah they could very well
also kill everybody if they wanted
to that's why they killed themselves in
the holotape at the start of the
Vault message this message hidden behind
six deadly
robots they call only called it out
after everyone was said everyone really
just one person survived after the rest
the the last remaining
five only one
survived wait and what happened with
that person who's what's their
name what happened with that
person there was only five people left
out of this massive Vault you just went
through nobody
knows left the imagination we don't know
never explained
what that's lame because like that
person should go out there and tell
people the
story there's an old man it was a while
ago yeah but like yeah even if he died
at some point he should have like
written it down or something
well that was weird a weird weird
Vault but
interesting
sure so the experiment was
to have the like
people sacrifice somebody but because
they didn't want to choose they made it
a a voting thing
and for the longest time they voted for
people as if it was a presidential
election and people died one after
another and then when there were only
five people
left wait so wait what with the five
people
left one person killed four of them or
what or or they were killed by the
system female I miss the female dorm
where are the
females oh females making me feel things
oh they they okay they should look good
mhm
oh and then only on one was left and
that one was able to hear this
solution because the system maybe
recognized that only one person was left
so what's the point and it
automatically made that happen happened
oh all five
heard they all
heard what what why did they kill
themselves just because they were like
broke they felt guilty about it and
killed themselves at oh like okay they
were psychologically
broken wait where did you get that
information from did I miss
that I thought I was listening quite
well
they finally refused to sacrifice when
five people were left so the computer
gave them that message
wow so at the point where it was only
five and they refused they were ready to
all die then they were told oh you don't
have to die now and so they killed
themselves
where are the
females
[Music]
e you can hear the gunshots in the oh
that's the those are the shots at the
very end
what congratulations citizens of VA 11
you have made the decision not to
sacrifice one of your own you can walk
with your head held high knowing that
your commitment to human life is a
shining
example are
we are we really going to do this it's
open we could just leave I couldn't not
after that we don't deserve to leave a
shining example wait wait they don't
sound they don't
we did what we were supposed to not by a
long shot anybody would have done they
don't sound very traumatized that's
exactly the problem now let's get on
with this if you ask me that's exactly
the problem wait wait people should know
what happened oh that's the one that
survives I guess if there's anyone out
there at all I hope they never have to
find out ready Harry yeah no no no wait
ah okay well we're voice
acting well then the guy the guy that
didn't kill himself says oh people can
learn from it but did he share anything
no apparently
not but okay maybe he after they also
killed themselves he felt even worse
about it and was like [\h__\h] this I can't
like what are people going to think
about me and blah blah blah and so he
decided to yeah just like move on as
much as he could I guess yeah he left
the recording
uh damn
okay no one would believe him I mean why
not because like maybe there's some
other people who already came out of the
vaults one way or another and surely in
everybody's Vault some crazy [\h__\h] is
happening so I would totally believe it
if I was like out there also just escape
from a vault surely he wouldn't be the
only one out there but I guess uh no so
okay I guess from what I can learn from
The Fallout TV show I'm sorry if you
don't like me taking my information from
that there is probably it's it's hard to
find other Vault dwellers out there cuz
there's more normal
people normal so to say not Vault
dwellers than Vault dwellers out there
right it's rare to find them because
they're also really rare in the show
so finding people that might understand
what the [\h__\h] you're going
through is
[Music]
hard stop using the gun
okay well it helped me a little
bit let's use
Maria or maybe not I don't
know okay how do I get out of here admin
mail door mail dorm
Mals I was here
already what this my dogs
doing was I here today today's
physician feel like maybe I wasn't in
here yet or I just didn't open that
specific
Locker what the dog doing
magazines are good yeah but those are
temporary right oh this one's locked
let's go a wish I would have found it
earlier I wonder what this does or
says let me
hack let me hack let me hack what's
going
on yay okay so four letters this feels
like you know like opening a newspaper
and doing a cross word puzzle four
letters how about spare spare spare me
spare me please I don't want to die
three out of four three out of five five
five oh those were not the okay I
thought those were the amount of
letters three out of five
correct it could no then it would be
four spark spark that's also for
scarf that's also for
Aid still
no
SP that's
two
huh huh I don't see much
more it has to be in the right position
too for it to save three out of five
right wait this one no
smile
one two wait this one store
store there we go I didn't see that word
okay what do you have in store oh like
these ones I know right so only the
security recording is
new downloading complete
okay
bye
dog more lore more lore more lore she
can't do this it's
done we're done nothing's done she's got
the authority the only thing she can't
do is change her own fate nothing says
she can't change the selection process
for future
overseers I say she can't you shouldn't
have toyed with her like that that Roy
we still have the majority we don't vote
for anything anymore oh I'm not talking
about voting I see what then you want to
have a sit in a hunger strike that's the
one with the lady not exactly being
interviewed maybe March into her office
with torches and
pitchforks yes come on I mean it what
start a revolution laws don't Outlast
their governments Roy all we have to do
is wait until someone from Justice block
gets picked for overseer then we have
them change the law back there won't be
any blocks after the new Overseer is
pick tomorrow everyone's going to move
on by the time we've reformed who knows
if we'll still be in the majority we can
hold the block together you don't know
that besides what if the computer picks
you what if it picks me and your
solution is to start shooting not if we
don't have to look we ar up we go to the
lower floors take some strategic targets
power food water just until she turns
authority over to us the other blocks
won't support it they're tired of us
having the power we have the majority we
don't need them this isn't a vote Roy
they'll fight back they've never had the
nerve hell of a way to test it I forgot
about this
part uh so trying to understand this
part too not just the ending of The
Vault story so this message was around
the election the last election before it
became
randomized or is
it
but
yeah but like what for it to become
randomized they had to say like they
don't want to choose to sacrifice any
more right but them saying that is
almost like saying we are not
sacrificing
anybody they should have just phrased it
differently and then they would have all
been free but I guess they just said we
don't want to choose it anymore so it
became
RNG oh oh the overseer just changed it
okay and
then she also was sacrific though
right and so there's two parties and why
did they do the Civil
War why did they start fighting each
other like that
[Music]
because
uh why did I do
that cuz the bigger party wanted it to
stay like before
ah the bigger party didn't want
[Music]
RNG because they thought they could just
continue choosing people from the other
party because they are the majority so
they can continue choosing people from
the other party until the other party is
just compl completely
eradicated oh and the current overseer
was that someone from the other the non-
majority
party so for her she's like yo yo yo you
guys are a majority you guys are just
going to continue killing us off so
let's make it RNG how does she even have
the power you H CU she's the overseer I
guess huh interesting
interesting
[Music]
spicy spicy well she for her to be
overseer guess she already made a lot of
enemies beforehand cuz she's the what is
that mope she's the one that uh is she
the one that they were talking about
that was like
you know doing spicy
favors yeah but not she was saying she
was doing spicy favors but then then she
killed them right was she going to do
spicy favors to the majority party
probably and then she killed
them who murdered the men who killed her
husband yeah they killed her this is
just so deep there's a lot of lore
there okay I think I got the most out of
it the most most important facts I
have chewed through them let's get out
of here if I find my way out of
here where is Exit
admin what's this place does this just
lead out I should also eat some stuff 36
months thank
you she did them so they wouldn't pick
her husband but they picked them anyway
so she killed them
oh yeah when you say they killed her
husband you mean they sacrificed him
right they K saying they killed her
sounds so direct but they chose yeah
okay I thought you meant they actually
killed
him what am I doing I I wanted to eat
some
food well what was I looking for here
anyway
what was the quest item that I was
looking
for I got it when I was in the water the
pressure device
a I didn't throw that away did
I is that an unable
item I can't okay
good okay
think am I getting closer to the exit
this what was this all about anyway I
guess just's more people getting
murdered during the Civil
War thank you Sparks two as a m
supporting H for 5 years now wow thank
you am I just going down
again not the right way [\h__\h] it's always
hard to leave can I teleport
a leave dungeon with OTE wheel I think
that's a different game right
[Music]
I don't
understand a
de wait
what the cigar launcher was one of the
first things we looked at but uh
the wait this room this is the room
maintenance ah here here here right wait
no that goes
down
Clinic
nothing classroom yeah
yeah ah he was right
there
okay I was have a hard time finding my
way out of the
vaults much love I came my for 2 years
already thank
you thank
you very much thank
you check the skeletons no I'm out of
here oh okay that was quite something
very interesting thankfully it wasn't
too
dangerous
except except the of course for the last
part that was certainly very
dangerous I
should make myself a little bit
smaller yeah
here is it too
small look I'm taking up so much space
so uh what's next uh
quests we did one of those so when is
gone next is evil the
hea cartrid or the reverse pulse cleaner
I don't really have a close place here
but maybe Camp from Camp I could go
there if this is one of the things where
I need to go
to or I have Vault 22 you guys said I
can't get that
thing
so are you one guide
Georgie you need to be
disciplined like that wasn't even the
first time I was told
that like last time I streamed this I
also was told that I might want to sell
stuff I also never know what to sell
though okay what am I looking for are
there going to be enemies even though I
went through here before
where is this
thing do you guys know on which
floor maybe an oxygen recycling cuz I'm
looking for an air
filter could make
sense third oh I don't know what floor
this is
now the enemies don't respawn at all
I really don't know where to look for it
man I don't want to go for this whole
dungeon have to go into the caves o
that's like really low
right it's on the
map uh but does it show it here even
though I'm not on the right
floor or is this the red floor
a you got to go through caves in
different
levels
oh uhuh it's still showing it here too I
guess that's just telling me to go
deeper or or
higher that's my other thing
[\h__\h] that [\h__\h] this is so confusing I
hate this why is it showing me the other
quests let's go to the lowest level and
then
walk down stairs
but I don't know like if this how am I
supposed to get help from the local map
if it shows a different quests and it's
trying to leave me outside of the
dungeon worse you guys tell me to check
the map but it doesn't really seem
helpful to
me you don't think is it's an
oxygen
okay now you guys got to be my local map
where the caves here why would they be
here right let me check so let's say
it's this thing
right
uh uh
oh
uh can I get there from this right oh my
God you're still here don't mind me I
have to wrap things up here gather my
gear that sort of thing I'll be leaving
soon enough cuz you're not going to tell
me where the thing is I'm looking for
she scared me cuz first I was like oh
it's just a dead body and then I
realized oh no it's kind of moving oh I
should shoot it but then I realized oh
wait actually I should why are you
sitting there doggy
I shouldn't shoot it because
wait I think I have to go around
it's it's inside the Locker on that
other side you get to it for another
floor
mhm but like started Pest Control okay
that's
helpful if it if it helps
okay so that is the fifth
level it's been too long since I've been
here
caves yeah
well okay I guess I got to go around
here and through this part maybe the the
squiggly El squiggle wiggle Park part
part well hopefully it will feel like a
walk in the
park unexplored bottom right
oh maybe you see
I
hear keyboard tappy sounds Tippy tappy
keyboard
ASMR okay uh
there some be but why is there somebody
typing
there that's that little part but I
don't think we did something else here
this doesn't look like the filter would
be randomly lying there I have to get
through this I guess I have to get out
of there and the only thing that makes
sense is like this path
maybe
right that's where I rescued the ghoul
woman
but I don't know how to get there
either this path is that where I came
from is that even a path
no I don't like this Quest it sucks
this seems like almost reachable but I
can't jump
anymore
how
how I guess I'll go back up here cuz I
don't I don't know
anymore but didn't I come from here
that's where I came
from
[Music]
Filter or we got
to make our
way
through yeah
like here
uh cave
entrance
hello there is
none from here even though I thought
maybe there would
be maybe from the level
above oh wait no there
is okay yeah this one's also familiar
looking split paths okay there's big
Stones let's go here but like yeah what
what's the point I'll just be in that
big Hall
again what the [\h__\h] is this
place how am I supposed to find this
thing you can't go back up so the other
hole was the exent
uhhuh different cave was there other
caves besides this one that wasn't this
the explosion
room it's in that
Locker no what if it wasn't a locker
right here then it would show
on the map but it's still showing like
it's on a different
floor but maybe maybe maybe maybe
maybe maybe wants me to go
through are these
stairs this is
like really not
so
rting what
what should I go with the
[Music]
elevator I don't understand
this yeah a mini map would also be
nice so
I guess I'll go to food
production the market isn't blinking in
the room with the Tilt computer
thing access Bea the third level am I on
the third level now what is this
level
okay and then maybe I try to
does that make
sense how would that lead to that over
there it
doesn't yeah
what even like is it is it a locker a
locker that I'm looking
for but now I'm on a different floor
[Music]
again huh
how do I get back to third level [\h__\h]
you
she didn't mean it Rex no I meant it I
meant what I
said so is there supposed to be a oh
yeah a cave in entrance
here and then I go ah for
here
mhm maybe this is better if you do this
in combination with when you first clear
this
dungeon that might make a lot of more
sense and uh you know you won't just be
like
aimlessly wandering through an already
emptied
dungeon mm so is it here let me check
the map uh oh yeah we're right there in
here no that's not a
locker these
ones
[Music]
yipp complete let's get out of
here let's get out of here was this
already in the locker before you uh
accept the quest or
wonder oh
yeah where do I wait where do I
go do I want to go this
way nope
is
this let me
out give me an elevator thank
you first
level worked with a mod of to make a
companion that could lead him out of
dungeons like this Terry
pret
what what what wait what Terry project
worked on this game
what
anyway you can just return and say I
already have that part got it cool if
only if
only okay and I don't understand is is
the last part here or here cuzz we're we
only really have one more thing search
the vaults in the region for a reverse
pulse
cleaner The Higher One or the lower one
the north
one this
one okay I'll try to go from here and
maybe we can sell some stuff
there uh
I just saw that body go limp and fall
down but then it set up oh I discovered
something it's a motel are you
alive howdy there was some kind of
massacre at one of the ranger stations I
don't know which one
great okay uh can I sell some stuff here
somewhere guess I got to go into Las
Vegas
or into this place right
what
oh South Vegas ruins East
entrance no wait I'm looking at Camp
McCaron yeah
okay let's get in there and sell some
stuff
I have 7 DM's where is all of that
coming from I'm not going to look at it
now because I have to Tab out with task
manager in order to look at that but
this is not quite the place place that I
envisioned don't remember this
place
um does anybody in the tents take my
[\h__\h]
hello in the building
okay I have no memory of this place did
Gandalf say that did he lie oh now that
looks familiar
all right who is it who's going to be of
service to
me loaded don't take chances for pickups
loose women may also be loaded with
disease
ew horse
Jesus
load ah wait this you're still here that
guy is still here oh wait who HS let me
buy let me
sell yes yes glad you're with
us
M did you miss the turn for the shop
[Music]
is The
Concourse I'm surprised we remembered
him n that was a special
one how would I forget the interrogation
[Music]
room Sho is in the basement oh my God
this game today is like
really like I can't even Dash to run
faster
[Music]
M I'm getting my steppies I'm burning my
calories in the basement I don't think I
ever sold anything here before did
I is this the
basement
no hi bro what are you doing here
something I can do for you I don't
know I got [\h__\h] one guide
again I'm opening task manager I need to
find out who the
[\h__\h] can't find my [\h__\h]
Mouse there it is scroll scroll scroll
scroll
ah you go there to get to the basement
well I guess maybe I misinterpreted that
sentence but I don't know what else that
would mean
ponics no here l dead RNG the shop is in
the
basement why did you do this to
me can't you see them already
suffering where is the shop over the
conquers that's where I was about to go
there I Lally standing in front of this
door whoa
W oh I've never been
here what is this crazy
place this looks like a shop what a
[\h__\h]
mess and I can't even take any of these
things ah
hello listen [\h__\h] I know you're not
really an NCR health inspector so you
can cut the restaurant critique routine
and I want my 50 caps back cuz I looked
it up and there ain't no disease called
colar rectal implosion syndrome huh so I
paid you to look the other way for
nothing what wait wait you're not yeah
oh wow I'm sorry you look just like
never mind are you saying all white
people look the same
up to
you is that what you're
saying hold up
H um would this lead me to his shopping
function oh yeah you can order up
anything you want as long as it's corn
or beans coin coin coin just kidding
haven't you heard with a few shipments
from home and a little variety the
troops are getting restless for some
quality grub you can only do so much as
a chef with just corn beans onions and
peppers wait that sounds amazing that
sounds like plenty of
ingredients you don't just need more
more more
fantasy is there a health inspector
bothering you H it's nothing you just
look like the health inspector who
stopped through for the yearly
inspection a couple of weeks back I was
hoping I wouldn't have to wait another
11 months to see his crooked ass to get
my caps back I will anything I can get
you I I did critique your place your
cleanliness here
uh can anything be done to improve your
supplies are you perhaps supplying me
with a side quest well we haven't had
any Quality Meat in months everyone in
the camp just eating beans for
protein say some of my kitchen Machinery
is broken down too so we've been eating
most of ramen and I'm desperate for
spices or seasoning comes with a lot of
just something for the general mood
around protein and spices and Seasonings
I got a big stock I could possibly
Supply it to you but would need some
money yeah yeah yeah yeah no yesterday
when I was watching the stream uh it
seemed like Tim really wanted people to
know yeah that the ramen has 35 gram of
protein that means nothing to me but
apparently that's a lot and way more
[Music]
than uh instant Ramen usually has so you
guys are impressed by that really I have
I I that sounds like a little to me but
I guess that's a big
amount oh okay there you go so you know
you know healthy ingredients too so you
know yeah so that's why you know the
ramen might be a little bit more
expensive than other ramas but it's also
way more high
quality yeah it's got that
protein 37 g m
wow wow it's huge for m right right
without meat
sheesh usually like protein shake or bar
has like that much oh yeah yeah I think
he said something like that's like one
ramen that's more like the a protein bar
has or
so which I guess oh yeah nutritious yeah
it's very nutritious not necessarily
healthy I would say if it's nutritious
then it's
healthy oh yeah and they have fiber
whatever that means to me that means
again not much but
uh how much fiber did they say was it
eight gram or what fiber there's a lot
of fiber in the ramen too apparently the
waa chicken
[Music]
ramen ah for healthy idle meetings it
helps with bottle
movements
what overpowered
anyway oh where would you suggest I find
meat in the amount you need meat here it
doesn't need to all come from the same
Source mm there are a bunch of different
vendors around who sell meat Fitz the
nashes Crimson
Caravan we've never really tried to go
out and organize deals with Merchants to
supply our food already having an
Overstock of food we haven't needed to
but we really need some good old red
meat on the menu soon so I'm willing to
divert some caps in their direction if
they're open to supply us oh so I don't
have to actually Supply it I just have
to make a connection for you
guys the Crimson Caravan would probably
be able to arrange a regular shipment
but I don't know of any spice is known
to improve mood improve mood hell we
have a whole research Department what
kind of SP one even set up in the main
terminal building they're the ones who
ought to be looking into what
purpose what parts are needed to fix the
food processor here's the list we've
been scrapping together quick fixes to
keep it running for months I think it
finally crapped out and needs a full
overhaul it's the goofy machine behind
the counter in the corner next to the
stove I'd be much obliged if you could
take a look at it and get it fixed up
would be nice if I had any parts already
or is this like special Parts I don't
know try the various Traders around the
waist where the pawn shop and Westside
might have some parts oh I've heard of a
place called House tools you could check
out it's an old factory on the north
side of Vegas just a word of warning
though I hear no one who goes in there
comes back out could be traps crazy
robots or who knows what's in that
place okay so I got myself a new side
quest or several ones what can I do for
you what happens if I fulfill all that
for him do I get free stuff no but wait
wa I'd like to Chow
down there we go all right I need to
remember these people they have like a
maximum of what they can take from me
uh wait he has zero cap
Stu is there is there any other vendor
in this
place traders in the basement I don't
believe that anymore I don't believe
anybody let me look at this ah
my game
crashed my game
crashed Todd don't be so angry at Todd
Todd's just trying his best
okay he put a I'm sure he put a lot of
work and love into this game
I don't know him personally but you know
this is a old game too it's like walking
on sticks or like riding around in a
wheelchair Todd didn't even work on this
one then why the [\h__\h] are you all
blaming
Todd poor
Todd where are we
continuing so now that I know that this
guy isn't going to help me the only
reason for me to go back is maybe if I
want to take all these side quests but I
got plenty of other side quests I guess
I'm
leaving forward and
left oh there's actual people who can
help
me this was me going forward and left
but there's just Troopers H Super
Trooper
[Music]
why is this place so
big I'm very very very tense
today this game is dragging me through
some
[\h__\h] you look like someone in need of a
reliable supplier
take your pick I was before my game
crashed but not anymore okay he got
8,000
caps okay what are we
selling no why is it doing
that bro stop doing stop that
stop
stop what what am I looking for what do
I wait was let me just wait wait wait
wait wait wait
wait let me move it like
this I can't no I can okay
H I can sell the bottles
right and then
cigarettes the pre- war money even
though that doesn't have any weight
tarentine
my
immersion you don't come to a takanashi
kiar stream in order to uphold
immersion
immersion perhaps if you want immersion
you got to go to like foko
[Music]
stream immersion what is that does it
taste
good I do not know such a thing as
immersion or or justice justice is
upholding immersion quite well too
those are your Best
Bets well wait wait you you guys are you
guys saying CeCe because of uh her
handcam streams I would like to remind
you that in my handcam streams I was
wasn't I like kind of the first one to
bring out something like the sleeves of
my outfit in a hand cam stream uh has
somebody done that before Before Me
Maybe I am very
immersive you just forgot about
it yeah yeah me and my hand I must have
been the first in whole life at least I
feel like I feel like maybe maybe
May and I had the whole bucket yeah
the OG's yeah pay some respect to the
OG's but now definitely there's not much
immersion
left guys tell me something to sell like
I don't I'm looking at this stuff and
I'm like I don't know what I will still
need maybe something from my weapons
those are like usually the heaviest
things I don't need a switch blade right
right but then the other stuff I don't
really know what is this Q35 matter
modulator whoa It's also very
expensive keep
that well
great it's a really good plasma rifle
uhhuh but that's different from pulse or
is that also plasma
you could sell it if you want to ah I
didn't speak into
science my heart
moves my immersion my immersion goes
into my music videos those are immersive
and
beautiful yeah the gun is right
there submachine gun I'm really
Caravan shotgun and the cowboy
repeater cuz I never I just don't use
them because I have so many guns I don't
I don't know what to switch
to the Caravan
shotgun
really 99 mm submachine
gun just going to run out of
money sorry for being light no
Cowboy repeater oh that's so cheap
okay I guess I'm selling that too cuz
you guys are saying I
should okay okay what else anything
here White Glove so I don't need that
anymore do
I the that one I think I used for that
one side quest I don't know if we're
done with
it no need
now
okay all right I think that's pretty
much it for
now give me a shat if you need anything
else later
okay all right now let's go to that
other last thing that we need for our
Quest if I ever make it out of this
place cuz it's huge did you give
Veronica a dress so white glove attire
fits her criter for
addess well it's gone
now but I I think I gave her a dress
before
Hey where's the doggle oh it's there
she's
chilling yeah I I gave her a dress
before I vaguely remember that but what
did we get out of that I don't
know if only you could teleport while
you're still in the building I don't
think you can right
show here we
go we're going to
go towards this
thing so turn
left let's try our luck am I looking for
another
Vault you guys
know yeah o which one is it this time
Vault free in the Vegas ruins
mhm okay you guys want to know
something the chocolate thing that I was
going to say
yesterday so my
sister like we were sitting at breakfast
this one day uh on my little
location and she was like talking about
how her
she's not single I'm sorry guys her
partner is um really into making duby
chocolate right now okay wipe your tears
away chat wipe them
immediately and
uh and I was like wait do I chocolate
what the [\h__\h] because on that very day I
was like this was the morning right and
and I was on my phone already before
breakfast and I I saw something in the
trending topics I saw du buy chocolate
and I was like H I wonder what that is
but I didn't look it up I didn't think
much of it and just ignored it but I saw
like people already talking about it oh
is this becom
a this is why we can't have nice things
I can't even have a nice conversation
walking for
America why America why why is it so
violent
here why must I
suffer why are there random landmines
blowing up on
me why eyes I was just talking about
chocolate so um God damn it
um what was I
saying yeah so her boyfriend was like
really into making dupai chocolate and
so I was like oh wait I heard about that
what even is that and then she told me
that it's like this chocolate with the
pistachio is going
on who the [\h__\h] are you oh it's Fe
F
fend okay and
um oh this is a dangerous area
H
dangerous oh my gun isn't
out let me heal
myself became bigger
again um
and yeah so uh and so because I knew
that we were going to go uh see the cats
and and
everything um and because my sister said
he wasn't done with like experimenting
yet because he first only tried a dark
chocolate and still wanted to try like
white chocolate and milk chocolate
instead oh milk chocolate he also
already tried I knew it was good but he
was like still still trying to improve
it so so I was like okay do you think
maybe like you know maybe he wants to
make some while we here on vacation and
then when we come by I can try some and
she's like actually yeah he might want
to do that and so when I got there I I
had the
pleasure of eating self-made fresh um
milk chocolate Dubai chocolate and it
was really good it was like self-made
and so you know
apparently if you want to buy it here in
Austria it's like very expensive and
only in specific
shops very expensive but probably not
even that
good my heart is still
pumping pump it up pump up the
jam but I was really good I still have a
little bit I I chugged it down and I was
like damn I got to stop
myself I got to stop myself
yeah it was good though so it's like a
bar of chocolate with like some crunchy
pistachio
stuff in the
middle I mean that doesn't sound very
groundbreaking and world changing I feel
like you know chocolate with fillings
isn't really that crazy but I mean the
pistachio cream is like really good you
know pistachio cream and like some some
crunchy thing I saw like videos like
afterwards the algorithm showed me
videos of like Dubai chocolate and like
how it's stop How It's
Made uh and they use some kind of like
stringy stuff and like cut it
up and mix it with pistachio cream I
don't know what that uh the name is of
that is that kunafa ah what is that made
out
of what am I looking for
okay mines mines mines m m the
mines pastry Pho what does that
mean Pho
pastry where am I
kind of D oh that was really
good that was really
yummy so thank you for letting me have a
taste look at her smile she's so
happy doing murder are you really happy
with yourself go Doo go doggo
[Music]
let me get him 20% that's so
low where' the other one
go don't let that [\h__\h] Escape I didn't
mean it I didn't mean it I didn't mean
it she
says I think I missed
twice what the [\h__\h] was that
this is a sick gun holy
[\h__\h] how am I missing so much maybe I'm
not but it feels like I'm only
missing [\h__\h] the
[Music]
fiends Oh Oh I thought I was being
killed suddenly I thought the turn
taed who is driver
nephy and what
you can stop showing me this now thank
you mysterious
stranger was driver Ney one of you
guys think we cleared it
out dirty
water
oh H boom head sh up
bid you
dead super stim
pack hey let's
go what's this
music frag
grenade I'll take
[Music]
him even though I never use these kind
of things
two or 360 and then
dab I think I need mods in this game to
be able to do such a cool sick
thing okay I was I got distracted I was
going to go somewhere up
[Music]
there I continued watching Breaking Bad
a little bit by the
way but I'm try going to try not to
like there was somebody trying to catch
up
right I think it was was it
Honolulu take the boss head oh
okay you're so
considerate which episode I reach oh
wasn't you I guess it was several of you
guys season 4 episode 2 yeah that's I
think where I am too now
[Music]
uh wait where is this boss did she
already
despawn or uh one of these they don't
look very boss
likee Ney ah this
one what do I do with her
head oh got XP jet she's got jet what's
buff out whatever I'll take a psycho
golf
[Music]
driver this
game this
[Music]
game unique weapon the golf
driver sh I should tell
it ah it does say nephy is golf
driver my my Phoenix heart my poor
Phoenix heart once you get your new K
meral Valley the knife looks amazing
right and it's so high quality
I the CEO seemed really like you know
like like he wanted the details more
acknowledged but I don't even understand
and know all the details but the knife
you know the knife has been sand blasted
which means like millions of sand things
blasted against the knife to give it a
really nice matte finish it's really
beautiful and and it's shiny and all
that and um yeah what else do I
remember uh um
yeah treat it well don't don't use a
knife sharpener where you're like
pull it through I don't really know I
don't even have a knife sharpener I
thought it was kind of funny when he
said
like uh he was offering for me to send
my knife in each time for it to get
sharpened uh because otherwise yeah some
viewer one of you guys brought up that
I'm probably just going to you
know use it until it's super dull and
never sharpen it one of you guys said
that to him and so he was like oh please
please just send me your knife and we'll
do a cycle I'll send you a new one and
I'll sharpen your old one and then you
use your new one until it's dull and
then you I send you the other one back
and we'll do an endless repeat of that I
was like you know that's kind of funny
like in FY that would be fun but uh kind
of you
know not very uh practical
so KNE setion where is this
uh where is this vault is it in here
but no like I know the price on the
knife especially is really high but you
know if you listen to all of
the what have I just entered if you
listen to all of
the details of how it was created uh you
know
uh you will know you know it's really
high
quality and and all of you know the P
like you
know it makes
[Music]
sense boom boom boom a not
dead you've gained the Lord Death per
what what what does that
mean but I died oh I've killed 200
people
woohoo why am I still wearing the
reaper that's should I
wear just doesn't even do anything I
don't have a good
helmet DT was DT like
the looks
good
you I need to heal a little
it is this really where I need to go to
this is not a
vault I basically have no armor
on why what about this is it is it
broken
no oh no I can't repair it though Lev
reinforced armor do you guys have some
armor the did I just
[Music]
killed oh
whatever my friends do everything for me
I could like wear this for in the
[Music]
meantime will they see me as one of
their own no right
wow
sexy raider blast Master
armor that's a different
one Dandy boy apples I'm taking his
Dandy
apples sorry my friend
okay I combined them all but if I wear
this armor elsewhere are people going to
be like hey yo what the [\h__\h] is wrong
with you oh I found VF
free uh was the experiment how long
people will survive when they're
hanging on a
fishing
thing what the
experiment failed oh it's an experiment
run by the
F what
really oh that's the
entrance but what did you guys
say activate elsewhere what do you guys
say uh
did you say yes to I shouldn't wear this
outside of this
place it's just the
deoration
[Music]
mhm why you guys dead I don't remember
oh guess it's my people my people have
done you harm it
seems it was totally not my fault so
don't take it out on me
M yes it'll tell you if it's
fact can wear it the game warns you
okay
easy so somewhere there's a button to
open the ball
store thanks for the
raid where might this button
be this place is
huge Go Dog Go Go Dog Go I think I also
got a hit right next to the volto while
oh okay but let me explore a little bit
why not what is
this
[Music]
hello oh I didn't lose any limbs
what
[Music]
um
okay
oh when I find you I'm going to eat your
I let him do too much damage to me holy
[\h__\h] what where is this leading to I oh
I walked over a trap oh there it is how
do I can I undo it activate
disarm you have been disarmed oh there's
m to
though does this also disarm
them why
is don't step on the mines my friends
don't do
it oh they're going all in don't die St
us
W yeah that's kind of what I was hoping
for that the explosions would work on
them
M I'll take a few things but like not
everything it's going to be cucumber
again Spike Knuckles do you think this
was better than what my lady has she's
the puncher after all right actually
this is this fauna fauna is this you
when I find you I'm going to eat your
spleen for fonica f f
FICA they're both punchers oh wait now
that's no F also was punching no I think
I'm talking about seven days to die guys
not General whole life L you know I told
you there's no immersion
here I don't go by the typical h life
rules I'm talking about 7 Days to Die My
Friends why isn't that the first thing
you're thinking about why are you not
synced up with my brain I'm so
disappointed in you
guys I thought you guys would do better
by
now I thought you guys can keep up with
my
brain that's enough of that
um
I I am shook head thank you for going in
front of
me is this safe to enter
now who whoa whoa
whoa what why is he so strong Rex are
you
good did you have fun up there guys let
me look at this
stuff always got to look out for trip
wires too man these days I'm getting
[\h__\h] over by them so often cat's
eye I love
them service rifle metal armor metal hel
maybe I should wear
that take the M armor he's got enough
he's had he had two service
rifles but see now I'm already like full
inventory
again so is this one good can I just
drop it
again same
one so how about
they wear the metal armor weight 30
though bro
12 at least that one isn't like a
particular
faction weight of 30 is in
demand
okay what am I even doing in here there
something to gain from going here or is
there a quest that would bring you
here boxing Lads life these magazines
make me think of seven days to
die oh
[\h__\h] I just sold one of
these I'm not going to take it I'm not
going to take these either although
these don't have
wait oh wait no the Gren have
wait are you going to explode on me
no season 2
when I don't know I think for now it's
good to not have like any of these big
projects because like they were taking
up a lot of people's time and schedules
and I also just want to like do normal
streams again you know for the
meantime and it it hasn't even haven't
been that long since we did seven days
dive but I do think like the idea was
that next time we're going to just do
like two or three days per week
stretched out over like couple of weeks
instead of like you know filling up like
everybody's schedules for the people who
do want to participate for the whole
week and like kind of like look lowkey
pressuring pressuring people like me and
fauna and someone who want to be there
every day to not take a break because
every day the the servers are open and
that kind of made us not take a single
break in seven days in a row or even
longer in my
case yeah so that way we can still take
a day off or
so and also uh schedule other streams
other games anyway we're looking
for a word
let's start with Banning and it's three
out of seven okay seven letters though
uh this this will get rid of one entry
or it will reload my attempts I think it
will reload my attempts right let me get
the the smaller ones this this one will
get rid of an entry
right or either okay then let me try one
more three out of seven it could
be couldn't be that one
sending could not be that one either
ceiling could be
ceiling five out of
seven ceiling what about
dealing yeah that it should be dealing
it should be
dealing
yo [\h__\h] genius oh I'm a hacker
[Music]
girl I made my boy through it
easily okay what are we looking at MEC
Murray's neon sign designs Factory
Forman station accident report log
shipping invoice shipping
invoice invoice number blah blah
blah description single side sign red
and white color s typ face top R line
reads
adverts what is this this even is this
interesting Kevin dropped one of the
Kevin
one of the glass tubes today while
forming it he ended up with a nasty cut
on his hand from the broken glass
fortunately no one else was hurt I
bandaged his hand and had him clean it
up before sending him home one more
accident like that and I may have to let
him go kids too accident prone incident
elevator one of the elevators to the
upper loading dog broke down again
unfortunately Jonathan
Jonathan was inside waiting to unload
and the sudden stop caused one of the
signs to slip of its pallet and it broke
his leg he'll be out for at least a
month while it
heals is there
anything like special to learn from
this is this like in connection with a
vault or
so what do you say Rex
we must solve this
case we must find
out Jamie fell into the fryer
today see me
again okay we're going down again
hopefully no
accidents or at least only happy
accidents this feels really
familiar reminds me of that other place
we went to long time ago with a
guy and that's all I can say because I
don't know how to describe what I'm
thinking
of but it was in Las Vegas in New
Vegas you say I can use V to check for
mines so if it doesn't activate when I
press it that means there's no mines
right
right yeah the Sign Guy
huh
exactly now you made me think that don't
shoot now you made me think that there
was a mine here and I was about to step
on it or
something no I didn't do that to myself
but why why is it he no showing my
companions
anyway let me out of here let me out of
here I can't right click doesn't there
we go right click does
work whatever [\h__\h] this
room so if I look for forward if I have
them in front of me it's going to show
me them on that but otherwise I just
look
forward it should work the way we intend
it to work
right I collecting the sunset the the
special ones no not really because I
already missed I guess a lot of them
anyway
okay let me try to go to the
Vault much time is already
passed we want to make sure that we at
least make a little bit of progress
today grenade bug I don't even really
want the
grenades actually cuz I don't use them
I'm not going to waste my bobby pin on
[Music]
that okay so it was like over there
and you guys said the button was right
next to
it was it
here somewhere
somewhere in
there you would be the greatest horror
game streamer if you ever actually and
that's exactly why I don't play horror
games because of my reactions that are
hurting my heart I'm constantly in
danger of a heart
attack
scared I I know I know it might be
entertaining to
watch um but
um I'm I'm I would like to keep uh that
at a minimum like me forcing myself do
things that I don't really feel
comfortable with you know for Halloween
once or twice the [\h__\h] are you doing
here you got some kind of [\h__\h] Death
Wish
[\h__\h] girl the hat that you're wearing
did you steal that from the Diablo games
go get yourself your own hats why do you
have to steal them from
Diablo this doesn't even fit into the
Fallout World let me tell
you I don't I am carrying jet psycho and
other favors and I don't deliver to the
help I want to kill her though I don't
want to talk my way through it but okay
if you're fck [\h__\h] carrying just
[\h__\h] say so yeah deliver to the boss
business as usual motor Runners down in
the maintenance Wing straight through
the door behind me down the hall down
the stairs to the right uh we have a con
coming through to see the boss don't
shoot at her down straight right or
something like that okay maybe it's good
to speech my way through
it okay down like
here hello Prim is going to be much
tougher to push around with that new
sheriff down there why are you talking
to me it's like you're talking to
yourself cuz I'm obviously not listening
whoa yeah this this looks difficult to
infiltrate wait down I'm not going down
it's straight down right
here is that even where I'm going to get
the thing that I want for my
quest oh maintenance wing
feel like I'm already not where I'm
supposed to be you're afraid to explore
the whole
place uh sure but I'd like to be
efficient about it we're looking for a
reverse pulse cleaner is that also in a
locker again does anybody know I'm on
the right track oh yeah I'm on the right
floor even I think
un lock her again will they let me take
it though quit your
whining I'm just
checking Primm is going to be much
tougher to push around with that new
sheriff down there you guys are
brainwashed you all say the same
thing I'm getting the shakes I need some
uh to take the edge off
um can we do this with just
talking he's got some crazy looking
dogs you guys are here
all right then hello sir nice to meet
you I wouldn't expecting a resupply so
soon so you have anything from Red Rock
Canyon to sell
me
um well uh can you tell me what happened
to the residents here I guess the Vault
residence I am interested in that I am a
vault researcher yes yes I study the
history of vaults please tell me I guess
it isn't a secret yeah the residents of
the Vault are all dead we killed them
funny thing is they just let us in we
didn't have to force the doors or
anything uh okay
uh uhuh why did you move the fiends into
this Vault we needed someplace to put
down Roots great I was having trouble
keeping my people out of Westside could
you have at least recruited those people
and have killed
them what's going on on West Side I try
to keep my people out of West side apart
from trying to stay on good terms with
the cons to do business there there's
mean son of a [\h__\h] that [\h__\h] mutant
is more trouble to kill than to avoid
having someplace for my people to sleep
reduces the chances of drifting into
Westside okay but I would have liked to
know what kind of Vault this was well I
never
know but I'm not really here to sell any
Kims
do I need to like check out his
room bye
bye guess
so it's empty oh this one can I just
take
it
really okay bye bye
guys thanks more tough security TRS [\h__\h]
we really got to stay the [\h__\h] out of
this
huh easy
which one's like always the first one
like should I always read the upper one
or the lower one first what's the
order that's why speech is op hey indeed
upper okay to all residents hello
everyone I'm sorry to inform you that uh
the small water leak that we detected a
couple weeks ago appears to be more
serious than we first SP is this from
The Vault times or is this from the
fiend times we're going to have to vent
the pipes in the section to isolate the
leak and stop the pressure from
stressing the rest of the system Vault
ooh unfortunately this means that we are
going to have to start rationing our
water rationing my apologies to go uh go
out to anybody who currently residing in
one of the affected areas we'll be
working to resolve the issue as soon as
possible so maybe we can still find out
something here in the
computers hi Jenny
it was great getting a chance to talk to
you oh they had a date I'm glad to hear
that things are going well for you I'm
curious if you'd like to meet me for
dinner one day next week I know we don't
talk that often but I feel like we
really clicked last night I hope you
feel the same
way hi there Vinnie oh Vinnie she calls
him
Vinnie last night was so much fun I
can't believe it took us this long to
sit down and talk let's do that again
very soon next time maybe we can hit
breakfast together as well oh Exel
Exel Vincent to William hey body thanks
for the advice din know went great last
night I'm not sure I would have been
able to wake up the guts to talk to if
you hadn't convinced me I owe you big
time I know you've been pretty stressed
with the water issues so if you need a
work from for some wreck time what's wck
time recreational let me
know A love story but I want a lore
story what the [\h__\h] are you looking
at
nothing all I guess the only way to find
out more about this vault is like to get
some more C killing these people and
going through the restricted
areas
probably eh could I have gone further
they don't care
he was so mean to me
though guess it's not red so
know okay hacking into the gate
now how
about revealed only
two this might be a harder one my start
was not good
okay I'll try one more time uh only two
correct so
yeah
me fre out of like
[\h__\h] I need something I need something
where are the special code Lo
s there it is oh I got the lives again
but now the word is different oh how was
it is the word still the
same same word okay so fre out the eight
correct
n e n one
two I maybe that one one eight
[\h__\h] enslaved is free out eight correct
an entrance was only
one so it's not even
the okay so here would been one two
what
wait yeah those only have two letters in
common
yeah detailed already tried revealed
already tried D it ends of Ed could it
be if it has the Ed and one more thing
in common with enslaved then it might be
it so this one
doesn't look like it
unveiled unveiled has the Ed and the and
an n on the second uh spot could be it
ah there only
two
inspired
[\h__\h] no I'm
cooked I'm
cooked
d a there's no more codes in here
really come on there must be one more
code ah this one gets rid of one only
or yeah I remove the
dud
okay I'll try
again don't don't revoke my hacker
privileges I like it it's fun it's my
favorite hobby
okay so those small ones you guys said
they can do both but this time it
removed the dot maybe I was just
unlucky let's start with obsessed four
out of eight good
start so probably the Ed again and
something else uh
revealed has
three
firearms no no was not order ordering no
discover no
infested
ah e s e yeah this could be it
yeah I'm so good at
it second try second
word disengage
lock are you done come on come on come
on come on
hey what's going on in here nothing
empty
empty Vault free utility jumpsuit for
lockpicking and
repair I could repair
them that looks pretty useful plus 5 +
right just the thing is do I really want
to carry that around all the
time and then if I put it away I'm going
to forget about
it I'm never going to use it
again is that the highlight of this room
that
suit there there's another
one there's a quest for the vault suits
oh to like have them all or so
okay I'll take my
leave a lady that collects
them perhaps for a museum what the [\h__\h]
are you looking
at
me you're lucky that I didn't come in
here here spraying and
praying even if I would have panicked I
would
have killed every single one of you and
left no one
behind it is
true just look at all the other vaults I
have checked out their Destiny wasn't
very nice
either I'm getting sh intrusive F I need
something to take the edge off wait
let me out
please okay there we go I thought they
weren't going to let me out unless I
give them some
drugs Vault free it's a good number for
sure they had a cool
experiment is there info to find out
what what it
is what it
was didn't find the other Secrets it was
drug related oh then perfect for the
fiends
huh maybe that's why they really went to
this one because they knew there were a
lot of drugs in there and they love
drugs all right team we're going to give
back our quest uh
where why is this not
checked why is it not checked
huh oh but never mind this was bugged it
was showing it even though I was in MK
I'm
confused return to senior night Lorenzo
with the
components in
there my only drug is
kiaha but I
don't uh endorse drugs I am straight
edge
so you got to be straight edge
too where is the entrance it's hard to
see
[\h__\h] so we shouldn't watch you no just
like watch me with a different mindset
with a more straight edge
mindset and and um I don't know don't
suck me up through your
nose I
guess that would
help where was this
guy this one right there I doubt it it
can't be that
easy the reports say Mr House's robots
are now using Tech we've never heard we
need to team up there soon move I'm
going to eat
you sniffing me sniffing
me I've never seen a chicken sniff
anything
before doesn't sound like something you
would really do are you really a chicken
or are you
perhaps a
takachi a takachi spy
hello is this the right
way yeah
oh this is the this is the [\h__\h]
computer room never going to try this
again this is the most ridiculous quest
in this whole
game I think you all agree with
[Music]
me wait wrong room
too it's like a spaceship in here it's
like Star
Trek [\h__\h] hey scribe taggard did you get
some sun
here
maybe hello
Outsider
hey
who he's moving around he's trying to
get away from me you there you good to
see you alive that is Lorenzo have you
found all the the components yet you
okay you really I mean that's great I
knew you could do it all along I'll get
right to work installing these why don't
you go tell the Elder the good news I'm
sure it'll be a huge load off of his
shoulders sure if I find him don't get
any ideas evening you better give me a
good reward return to elen Mech namara
with the news that the air fil system
should be
fine Mech namara
in that room
huh these fools tried to send you to
your
death really was this a kind of like
impossible seemingly impossible mission
where chances were high that I was going
to die oh this is for the Power Armor
training
ah back again I see have you found all
the components we
need yes let me just pour my water
yeah good news for a change your efforts
have humbled me
Outsider you have done more than I could
expect even from my brothers more I've
been going over the scouts trying to
stret keep coming up the same conclusion
the NCR is not the threat I've believed
it to be we should not have had to rely
on your help in this crisis I believed
my actions were Guided by caution and
Prudence but I now see the truth people
called me a hero after what happened at
Helios but I left that battle scarred by
fear and have allowed that weakness to
govern my
actions that ends now I will undo the
wrong I have done my brethren and lift
the lockdown with luck we will once
again flourish please take this it is a
small token of my thanks and scarcely
begins to repay the debt owed you but is
all I am allowed to give an outsider
this key will allow you use our safe
house to the Northeast I hope it will
prove useful in your
travels I am liked how wonderful I'm so
glad that I'm liked by you after all
I've done for you liked the bare
minimum th000
XP how come I'm not leveled up bro
that's a lot of exp ah there it is oh no
I'm not going to be yeah yeah I saw that
coming this
[Music]
time what's the point in getting this
even higher I can already repair my
things does it just repair them
better I can't even repair my armor
without having another piece of armor to
combine it with
you repair more efficiently oh okay jury
rigging
what jury riging perk one of the best
best in the game what what is
that at what point at
maximum 90 have 90 repair you can get a
perk to repair expensive armor with
cheap armor o okay cool cool I gave
yes okay do I get a another perk too
no I thought I get it every
level h a i were too okay well so the
thing is guys I have a dentist
appointment tomorrow so I don't want to
play too long and I still read I need to
read super chats so I don't know if I
should end here already we played for 4
hours go floss yeah I'll be flossing for
an
hour I did a lot really I only did one
Quest
[Music]
really it doesn't feel so satisfying
today and I got one guy so much and I
ran through plac
aimlessly was a bulky Quest yeah it was
like free quests and one we we went into
some
vaults yeah that was a cool Vault the
the one with the
elections yeah okay then I'll leave it
at that and I'll read super
chats also me me saying bruh while that
guy was talking was not towards by the
way it was U because of an email I was
reading on my
phone multitasking yeah save yes I did
one Quest then you're getting the power
I'm TR okay but I don't know how long
that takes so I'm just going
to I'm just going to leave the that
either way we can do it next
time so guys uh little remind them my
nandroid nid is currently open for
pre-order on till like January 15 or
something like
that and look at
her and my V things are also currently
open for pre-order really really nice
products to enrich your kitchen life and
your foodie life really yummy Ramen to
eat in that bowl the bowl is so
beautiful and the bowl actually like
it's very very big it fits like several
servings of that
Ramen oh I did ask about the good smile
thing cuz I read some people say that I
actually I asked uh my manager about it
but I have yet to uh receive a reply I
do also feel kind of
uncomfortable uh at this time to ask you
guys to buy something from the site if
that is true that the site might be
compromised so be careful maybe you
don't have to order it right now or yeah
you can order for amyamy you know the
site that Ena has a um sponsorship going
on with right now that seems to be safe
so uh probably better to order through
there and
I'm I'm sorry actually if you did
already order
through good smile directly I don't know
like I don't really know if it's true or
not or if it's still affecting
it um but be careful and have an eye out
on your financials and
stuff uh I don't really know like what
could happen but yeah if you used your
credit card or something you got to like
be on alert
maybe only affecting the US store
apparently okay so I I didn't get a
reply yet on information
but I feel like
it's like not really I don't know I
don't feel comfortable with like
advertising this to you guys without
warning you so
yeah
yeah yeah only the US shop so if you are
from the US please order for Amy Amy
instead for the
meantime I should have said it yesterday
already but actually I don't think I
really knew about it yesterday
uh
yeah I'll try to order it from my local
store nice that also sounds like a good
idea she is
empathetic am
I am I though Mando is number three on
amyamy well it has just been released so
to say
so that's not not that surprising
it will fall down soon
enough yeah great La GRE W I'm missing
her now
[Music]
already oh my favorite holand really
she's a cutie patootie isn't
she let me go
to now I wish I had a
like wild west kind of
desert background to go
to I only have this
swamp oh what is that what is that
[Music]
mean where am
I oh
[Music]
howy I'm pointing
at the noodles may may I please may I
please have this one
worm this that
one that one please can you feed it to
me
please
ah I'm
hungry
ah gumy worms
please the
purple there's several I think they all
have
purple I mean the one that is closest to
[Music]
you okay let me go go read some
CH kind of nervous about the
dentist it's not like I have like pain
in any teeth or so right now but I still
feel like I'm going to be judged do you
guys also feel like
that like oh you [\h__\h] you didn't floss
at all didn't I tell you to floss last
time you were
here I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
now I'm going to bleed because I'm going
to do the like the oh double P GM just
routine checkup and like a general like
yearly
[Music]
cleaning there we go I was
double and yeah last time they did that
they flossed my teeth and I started like
my my my too flesh was bleeding and it
was kind of
painful a little bit
[Music]
yeah but I I I did floss like uh twice
in the past two weeks that's actually
surprising kind of in preparation or
even three times
[Music]
maybe maybe that already prepared my
gums a little
[Music]
bit I'll do it again today and then in
the morning or maybe should I not do it
in the morning because then cuz my
appointment is pretty
early and when I say morning it's like
probably an hour before my appointment
or so would that just make it worse
maybe I don't
[Music]
know let them not be raw
already H
raw I not need it yeah I'll just let
them do their job and pay
them I'll let them deal with
it okay oh wow I'm so caught
up it makes me kind of feel lonely I
have to read the go super chats
apparently oh wait what Diablo are you
sure
[Music]
GD oh because mine the links were
already like
[Music]
purple Al so one before it it really it
already is purple for me I clicked on it
already maybe I clicked on it for some
other reason before H
okay ah I clicked on it ah I was like
okay yeah never mind like oh never mind
I need to give you my C yeah yeah okay
okay
okay makes sense
thank you what do you think of Saul by
the way best girl I'm not going to lie
Sal's great yeah Sal's funny
um I've I've reached a point in the
story where Saul is like also you know
kind of like in
trouble more or
less like we're all getting deep in in
trouble everybody's in trouble and yeah
now
Walt oh I saw this scene I I was like
okay I'll not say what happened but I'm
just wondering I didn't realize a box
cutter
could cut so smoothly so deeply so
[Music]
efficiently uh and that was also like
honestly I generally understand what's
going on in the show but that one moment
I was like is he just doing that
to like assert dominance
because how dare that guy you know like
or or is he doing
it because to to like kind of even it
out or or to like make Walt happy
or
H or just to be cool and respect
[Music]
it yeah yeah I think yeah cuz even Walt
is like I don't know why you did did
that why did he do that so I can imagine
that later on they're going to discuss
it cuz if even Walt is like out loud
saying why did you do that and confused
about it that seems like they're going
to address it later on
yeah even Mike was confused
yeah the way Mike slapped the [\h__\h] out
of him in the
bar Mike are you
what side is mik I mean obviously he's
on Gus's side because he he's employed
by him but
like he's cool though
yeah he's so
cool he has a family he has a a
daughter it's kind of scary
like feel like there's a flag there a
deaf flag above his daughter's head it's
worrying
and then he's like going to absolutely
lose his mind or so one day if his
daughter gets harmed or so imagine
imagine you love Mike and better call
all oh okay there's more Mike there I
see well who knows if that will happen
at all the daughter thing that's just
something I I'm
dreading also
Hank poor very like she's like always
been like a little bit of
a annoying kind of wife character in the
show but right now she's just like
trying her best to be supportive of her
husband
and like help him and motivate him and
she's still like staying so strong by
his side but he's more and more just
like knocking her down it's [\h__\h]
minerals and that's just it's not just
some
BRS it's
minerals so I hope I hope he will treat
her better but I also feel bad for Hank
obviously because I understand like he
must be extremely frustrated he feels
like um like he has no power right now
over his own body and everything he
probably feels like less manly also
because he can't protect himself and get
up and walk and I don't know you you
know be the protector of the house and
do his usual job and all that that he
now doesn't have anymore but you know he
was so close to the truth yeah he really
was too and now he's like out of
commission for a long
time but yeah he's really frustrated
obviously with all of that I honestly
thought that they were going to
completely disable him and make him
like yeah lose his abilities and his
legs completely but it does seem like
he's got got something left in there I
thought the show was going to go towards
he will never walk
again H but even then it seems like a
long long journey maybe in season 5
he'll start working again or or never
really properly
but yeah oh really at some point I
thought he was going to die too the
minerals will heal him hold her yeah he
needs a hold her
[Music]
but I hope he will at some point be
nicer to Mary again Marie or Mary I
don't know probably Marie hope he'll be
nicer cuz you know I understand his
frustration obviously but like at some
point her wife his wife will also reach
his limit her [\h__\h] his wife will also
reach her limit at some
point
Marie have to be considerate and an
empath
ideally yeah uh Toyama D thank
you clear eye thank you D thank you
thank you I would be the Envy of my
guildmates if I had a t to approved name
for my new character you want a name bro
by now you probably already made a
character didn't you did you are you
here a name for your World of Warcraft
character okay if you didn't make one
yet um how about
[Music]
H but that's also difficult because like
probably a lot of names are already
taken how can I know that the name I'm
giving you isn't already taken on that
server right now I can only think of
like
hster how about hster
gangster
or Lobster bobster
[Music]
I like that one I don't know what it
means
but try out those
[Music]
two or bobster Lobster Lobster bobster
or bobster lobser both
okay that one's really
random Dilla d zor d thank you LCA lemon
thank you for the pinky I took a long
break from alive and just started back I
just wanted to let you know your outfits
are so cute and I squeak out loud when I
saw them it makes me want to keep on
keeping on oh thank you welcome back
welcome welcome back I hope you're
enjoying it again it's always fine to
take a break if you don't feel it
anymore but I would be glad to see
everybody back who takes a break at some
point yeah and yes indeed my outfits
here you you heard it here once again
I am a fashionista so I must become Miss
vtuber D D snowy d
d and
n something
something
Kai Mahi maybe D for the pinky by free
they come by free thy way opens by th by
the Super Chat of the Willing we call
the home
of chicken Crea of kfp sorry my English
is not very good so I used Google
Translate to translate oh wow that came
out when you translated it words like t
h
[Music]
y
amazing that's a good translator very
sophisticated medieval sounding
translator it's from the guy in the
trailer
what what oh it
anyway thank you for the Super Chat D
just another thank you thank you for
giving me more names to
read see I was already stressing out
back
then about super chats not being piled
up
anymore na caught the face of the pinky
I am willing to sacrifice my bank
account to support the Super Chat
ratings no this was before all the
launches
[Music]
no are you going to going to be also
able to get the n and and the buy things
you don't have to though you don't have
to but you know somebody also needs to
feed that
Nero she's got to eat she's got to sleep
she needs a roof over her head too no
you can't be homeless because that will
mean that neroid wa will also be
homeless and that will be suffering at
least make her a little bit of a house
make her little house out of ice cream
sticks Elsie laugh and D
Al the gamer
[Music]
CR FR SC D El
D I don't know about dance stream
because I don't even really know the
coros but I'll definitely do a Koka
stream soon maybe J black work
than thank you chocolate FR D and space
waterful
dun now we're going to do go super
chats now for real for
[Music]
real stay in the middle
like Tracy D and jaob for
[Music]
thank
you melon lover d slave honolu
D vag
D
nice HK 87 thanks for the red super chat
oh com
kfp yes thank you for the support
[Music]
and we
have
Ali
and come oh it's been a while since I
saw your name here I'm very happy to see
Tanto and
SE or should I translate the rest part I
see oh wait okay this looks pretty
simple
and although the first part I don't
really
[Music]
know oh I am cute maybe h
something about
probably Korean language study or
so thank you thank you thank you thank
you slave Hulu thanks for the pinky yes
I am happy although I am not OPP
[Music]
or do you just not want to be called
OPP are you here
explain explain yourself
[Music]
huh guess we won't find out now
did I read that
[Music]
right y TV
D thank you for
watching
jaave
Bob maybe younger but how would you know
how would you know that you are
younger
[Music]
sh Wait was
that
[Music]
yeah thanks for the red super chat
thanks for the collab T I'm so glad that
this collab shines as you've prepared
for such a long time laa and GLE are
really cute and if you come to Korea in
Spring I recommend you to prepare warm
clothes this is because spring in Korea
is not warm anymore oh that's okay
that's okay it's also pretty cold here
in Spring too still maybe we're about
the same who
knows but
yeah I would like to go
again I wonder maybe if I go again maybe
I should check out more places not just
Soul maybe I should travel travel around
some more maybe if if the girls is if if
even just go are willing to travel like
maybe to a different city with me
that'll be really
cool but I also feel like I should go to
Soul again because I I want to meet all
of the girls although go was like
apparently uh I saw a translation of her
reaction to when I wrote on Twitter uh
that I wanted to meet all the is Idol
girls and go with them to like lot the
world or something like that which I
mean it wasn't that serious we can go
anywhere or in in separate grips I don't
know but she was like oh that's
dangerous all of us well yeah maybe
[Music]
but but we can stay
lowkey maybe uh or
I we we'll we'll meet in um not all of
us we'll meet one day I'll meet one half
of them and the other day I'll meet the
other half of
them or or we'll just meet them in is
Idol office or
[Music]
so but one way or another you can't keep
me from those
[Music]
girls yeah I'm going to meet them in
segments let's do a uh let's do a meet
and
greet I'll be in a meet and greet booth
and they'll come in one by one no no
that would be so cold we need it to be
more
personal
and yeah
[Music]
fun I'm going to get yeah I'm going to
break break into their
headquarters kindly politely I'll knock
on their door
I like excuse
me let me in
please please
please never mind wait that one I
already
read I think I owe you a kiss
[Music]
still
and me
[Music]
AB okay thank you for the pink Super
Chat
com so much but no words thank you thank
you thank you hope you enjoyed the
stream please come again
[Music]
mku one more time thank you for the
pinky over the
[Music]
table I can read that and understand
those simple words
T
in in
[Music]
the wait that part I'll read I I'll
translate I can't afford to spend any
more time in my life what does that mean
what is that supposed to
[Music]
mean translates to I can't afford to
spend any more time in my life what are
you trying to
say I'm sure it has a kind of different
meaning Papa go you're disappointing me
this one time ah it means he can die
happy ah see that's that sounds better
that sounds more like it makes
sense thank you for helping out
pong I
see I see
yeah don't die Honolulu I will not let
you
[Music]
hot
come and that was that now we go to Holo
cure
stream by the way my sub count it's
about to tick to
1.56 soon soon maybe tomorrow or the day
after tomorrow subscribe if you haven't
yet
subscribe always excited about those
ticks cuz those are you know it doesn't
show the all the numbers nowadays of
course because it's already so far past
[Music]
that 1.56 let's
go okay next Super chats take off this
seven d d thanks for the red chat cat
food fans have a great break W you
deserve it we'll be ready to give you
lots of love when you return thank you
appreciate it oh it's my birthday
tomorrow thank you for all the smiles
throughout the years wa and kfp you're
the best off to work off my super
chats thank
you thank you thank
you oh Alexander Nole that is that is so
[\h__\h] depressing
your calculations are depressing
[Music]
me take it back recalculate until until
it's a more promising motivating
result your calculations are off way
[Music]
off so Doug Hood thank you thank you and
happy happy birthday
wait I shall sing for you happy birthday
to
you the one who gifts many many
to happy
birthday
to a What
rhymes
[Music]
uh no happy
birthday uh uh
[Music]
uh
uh rhymes with uh May or
leay okay yeah sure but
uh H uh
uh uh slay oh and continue to
slay happy birthday DG
Hood hope you had a nice birthday what
did you do how did you spend your
birthday
how did I stream on your birthday I
didn't right cuz this was before I left
right I'm sorry I couldn't stream on
your birthday nailed
it I guess you're not here to answer
that's okay but thank you for always
being so supportive and so sweet not
just supportive of me but supportive of
other kfp too what an angel chicken
thank you so
[Music]
much all those kisses you gave to other
people shall return to you once
again stay healthy stay happy
[Music]
please chocolate insomnia f with pinky
hey q a while back there was a stream
idea that was brought up where kfp would
submit their tangents and you would read
them is that something you would still
consider thank you AA for your hard work
uh was it like I would be pretending
that it's my tangent or was I just going
to rate them I don't remember
[Music]
anymore if I would rate them that's
basically just a rate my life
story kind of stream rate the story I
just that I am telling you from my
private
experiences maybe just rate them H the
first time I thought of this idea was
some promising sounding is there
something you want to tell me are you
asking me because there's something in
particular you want to tell me you're
always welcome to tell
me this new idea is objectively better
you think so I don't know I'm not really
it's not really sparking anything in me
right
now you wanted to read our problems to
it one point I do still want to do that
that one I do kind of still want to do
that and also so Hol members but I first
have to learn how to read
palms and the way I would do it with Hol
members is like uh you know they'll show
me a picture of the real hands and I'll
just like make an image of it and like
draw the important lines that have to be
talked about it about uh on the hand
like you don't really have to see the
picture of the real hand you just need a
like a yeah illustration of a hand and
the important lines I'll like line them
on the picture and that way I can still
like go through
it and discuss it but first I have to
learn how to read
poems I I used to learn that long time
ago Cat Wedding idea when Sion Sion
don't even don't even come up with these
ideas we're not going to have time I'm
going to throw some stuff at you soon
we're going to start working on some
outfits you don't have time time for cat
wedding
[Music]
stuff yeah we're going to be busy we're
going to
cook I'm Vault you're Jesse or actually
I you're the one that's really cooking
so maybe your W but I don't really feel
like a
Jessie maybe I'm Gus I'm Gus your
Walt good luck
[Music]
yeah I'm Gus yeah I mean I
literally I'm literally Gus because I
have a whole chicken
business that I'm
leading I am
Gus a very M suspicious chicken business
in its own way a little bit different
from Gus's suspiciousness but uh still
comparable
yeah for robic danash Chase junor thank
you danan appreciate it vet Dragon D
Cruz D zly thanks for the red chat hey T
just got my myth earphones up and
running and I got to say so far I like
them a lot o tested them with four blood
and Mirage and they sound miles better
than my old ones o you hear that KY you
hear that perhaps for your my
earphones thec works well too so nothing
can stop W from K kicking my eardrums
what's the
ANC noise cancelling a what's the a
[Music]
for active noise
cancelling so basically just normal
noise cancelling like my headphones have
right my my the ones I use for
traveling they're already out seems so
yeah it's not the first uh person that I
saw talking about having them already so
a Japan bro talk about the myth
earphones on Twitter already so check
your mailboxes if you did order one
previously it might be on its way or it
might already be there thank you dip
hope you enjoying them don't lose them
they're small easy to lose don't lose
them don't lose them I feel like I'm
jinxing it good
luck maybe only use them indoor chances
of losing them are a little bit
lower Cody Co lunch y Awesome song thank
you oh thank you thank
you
Bruce thank you
years long lurker and occasional C
project manager I realized I don't have
an employee number and I saw a bite
animal pin oh can I have the number two
for8 isn't taken yet of course of course
I think it's not taken yet probably
haven't been giving out numbers in a
while too Pa gter thank you for the
pinky W in this game ain't just decent
more like Borderland Immortal oh you
basically got the drk old form Final
Fantasy mean if you would die you
instead heal to full if you can't tell
this is very strong possibly the best
defensive alt in the game okay yeah I
haven't played myself in a while when I
did it did feel
good maybe I should give her another
chance maybe for a difficult
stages if you guys think that it is
efficient that I am efficient and a good
Survivor
[Music]
GD is opening the spreadsheet right at
this very
[Music]
moment definitely one of the best
characters in the game
[Music]
wow yeah I think mint was also using me
in her Holo cure streams
recently midnight rer D awesome sauce
eating miks
ass kfp youf
[Music]
good luck they're not going to be as
good as the V ramen noodle
Jo aluda I saw you in the chat too are
you here to pick up your Super Chat
delivery thank you for the rest of the
chat hope you have a wonderful break and
for future W when she reachs us welcome
back and hope you had a lovely time
thank you I mean I I know I like was
like you know a little bit depressed
when I came back and all that you know
but over overall I mean it was still
great it was still a great stay and good
bonding with my sister too me and my
sister actually never have done anything
like this before and you know I told you
before I left that my sister was like
thinking of um doing this like manicure
thing with me and then we both decided
against it but because I was like we can
just do something like that in the rooms
too and I'll bring like a mask to put on
our faces and you'll bring the nail um
colors and everything and we'll just do
it to ourselves we did end up doing that
and um I I made I mixed the mask cuz it
was like something you make fresh with
water and then you with a brush you put
it on the face so I put it on her face
and then I put it on my face and then we
let it sit for a while while watching
like a Zelda uh lore video about
[Music]
um what's his name again tinkle no Tink
Tin Tin Tim tin
Tim tin t tingle so
close I don't know man but that was
interesting and then she did my nails
she like she was she wanted to file file
said it in English too file them and uh
push the cuticles and all that and I was
like I don't think I will like that I
hate that feeling and she started just
to try and I was like no no no no no no
no I hate that and then she tried the
cuticles and I was like I don't like
this evil that really
hurts
so no cuticles were harmed I mean one
cuticle was harmed and one Nile Nile One
Nail was attempted to be filed but uh
then she just did my nails without all
of those steps
but we figured it was good that we
didn't go to a manicure because they
would have wanted to do that on my nails
too and if I would have said no then
what's the point of the manicure
really would just be a waste of money
[Music]
actually
yeah but she was really careful and you
know really skilled in applying the nail
polish on my nails and yeah it was cute
and then oh I I also I I thought you
know maybe I can bring something extra
nice as an extra special thing so from
home I brought my you know my
Japanese things the things that I stick
on my shoulders sometimes when I want to
want to soo my chronic pain a little bit
and my sore muscles and everything my
stiff muscles and I brought them and I
put them on her
shoulders not bu no no no different but
[Music]
similar yeah and even that like
generally going on a vacation or
something with her together on a little
trip we've never done that but also even
just like doing something girly and
sisterly like that we have never done
something like that either so yeah was
good bonding time for me and my sister
and yeah I think we grew closer
it's just kind of sad that it these kind
of things like when it doesn't happen
until you're like
so so late in your adult life
already and you're just thinking man if
only we could have done stuff like that
when we were teenagers and stuff yeah
but better later than
never yeah yesterday she kept tabs on
the stream she was
interested in Diablo she also told me
IRL but she said she doesn't want to
play it herself because of reasons I
will not mention them but maybe you can
imagine she does like Diablo and fury so
she was probably that was a good choice
to do Diablo and then all the tangents
from our trip during the Diablo stream
because good combination for her
[Music]
your boyfriend had the house to himself
too yeah which apparently they never
have this opportunity if anything it's
the other way around sometimes
apparently but
yeah my sister was cute she kept on
saying oh I miss my
boyfriend but she's still enjoyed her
time with me and I I told her like ah
you got to enjoy this time away from you
know like cuz they in a long long
relationship by now it's pretty long and
it's good to like get some space too you
know space for
yourself every once in a while
[Music]
yeah yeah and you know we focused on
each other
and it was nice that we could have some
time spending together only us two
something we've never really done before
yay
yay so yeah yeah yeah yeah that's it
thank you
aluda thank you thank you for talking to
future or like present
wa M2M D awesome s d lunar D super bear
hero
D egg Kim thank you for the bread CH oo
what is that food in your profile
picture looks
like it looks like
[Music]
it looks
like dashim Tam with like a sauce on
top but maybe it's something else but it
does say egg kimchi oh is is this
like with
[Music]
kimchi egg omelette with kimchi hello
Teno I finally arrived V for a trip oh
this city is really wonderful and
there's so many places to visit and also
I will go to salburg too
oh great cities the best cities of
Austria one might say Enjoy have a good
time are you already in salsburg now I
wonder cuz this was this was 7 days ago
you might already be home but
now did you have
fun did you have
[Music]
fun J
JY I think that's me asking did you was
it interesting or was it
fun I
[Music]
think but you're not here to tell me oh
no
no no alexanda
no I know where are you going with
this
[Music]
sh I'm watching you be careful careful
with your
words Anyway
come now you came to Austria I shall
exchange this favor and come to Korea
again
soon see you an
[Music]
the
First new comp Productions D thank you
so much so
nice uh x i i i King thank you for the
pinky in
[Music]
German
for oh did you translate it because in
English it was like kind of like uh not
letting it go through because of some
word messing up the the censorship
whatever that's a way to pass by that
problem a way I didn't think of before
you could take this as an example guys
if you have that issue sometime just
translate it to German and try
again yes Modern Problems require modern
solutions yeah yeah yeah
smart so smart no wonder you work
glasses in your profile
picture thank you so much and then uh
[Music]
why do I I'm always Unsure how to read
this
name
yeah thank
you thank you for the pinky hi wa you
are amazing no
you that cat in that profile picture
cute too the cat is amazing you are
amazing we're all amazing thank you for
the
support oh
no and edf5 fencer thank you for the red
super chat thank you no words I guess
you were speechless because of the love
that you have for me understandable have
a nice
day thank you so much even double so
double red Super Chat packed in one EGF
EGF EGF LS La induction
alvarro d d Jim Tracy D and D D and
that's where I left you guys forever
no didn't but I'm actually going to
leave you now I could like probably
catch up if I wanted to I could catch up
completely but I want to like try to eat
dinner as early as I can so that I can
get tired as early as I can because last
two nights I stayed up way too
late m
so better end this early when I
can I hope I can sleep
early we
notied stop stop stalking me only I can
stalk
you we have an agreement did you
forget and now give
me that worm
[Music]
why has it not landed in my tummy
yet H I'm pointing at it this whole time
sending your signals why can't you read
my
[Music]
signals thank
you I just noticed the chat wasn't on
the screen this whole time sorry
sorry women are
scary say that again say that again
straight to my
face yes indeed perhaps I am
scary I need to scare you otherwise
you're not
[Music]
listening be scared
okay tomorrow we have another stream
what was
it this is a
test
answer cookie yummy true
correct anybody who didn't answer
within 5
Seconds usual room for one day
goodbye usual room STS usual room is on
the rise so many of you didn't answer
within 5 Seconds some of you didn't
answer at all people who didn't answer
at all you're going to go to the usual
room for 5 days
goodbye it's been a while you know we
need to get the usual room packed once
again it's been too empty these days
lurkers are kill yeah
lurkers
you must pay the price for your lurking
actions
I just don't know how to spell that game
well you should know by now because this
will be the fourth time on my Channel at
least that I'm playing
it like you should know it's not the
first time that this game comes up on my
channel after
[Music]
all yeah not very consider of
Me no no no no not consider it of you to
not to consider the name of the game
after all these
[Music]
times yeah you can learn how to spell it
in the usual room exactly hopefully you
come out of it being able to answer the
the question within 5
seconds but then the answer is going to
be different because it's going to be a
different
game
well I'm keeping you on your tippy
toes and now I'm going to go and eat
bread for dinner because
I yeah am going to be eating bread for
dinner I got some sandwiches and stuff a
sandwich and something else
bre yeah I think it's going to be
good yum
bread what's in bread carbohydrate I
don't know I don't know anything about
food maybe I shouldn't be leading a
restaurant
chain maybe no no no no carbs I got it
right
yppe yes yes okay okay oh then I can
continue leading kfp I think I'm
good okay okay
okay in we say and see you tomorrow um
unless the dentist decides to take all
my teeth out then I won't be able to
stream
anymore
[Music]
bye-bye
farewell Brave
chickens farewell on your travel and you
are being escorted to the usual
[Music]
room you think
Mexico will be your
Escape we have room
s they they are omip
[Music]
poent h
omnipresent
[Music]
there