[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
ah
huh
[Music]
hahaha
go
[Music]
i just woke up
my voice needs to warm up a little bit
i'm a bit
raspy a bit tired um
i spent so i i moved the stream to one
hour later
but even after that i watched so much
actually actually it wasn't netflix it
wasn't even netflix
because they took off my favorite show
off of netflix
so now i had to buy it on amazon
what the what the f
so i'm watching it now on amazon and
that doesn't sound
nice when i say i've been up all night
watching amazon
yeah it just doesn't sound right it
doesn't sound right
oh god damn it yes yes yes
office the office
[Music]
know
would you do such a thing
no god please no
uh oh well it's not my first time
watching it's my is every watch
and i tried my best to re-watch it
before the year ends but
it didn't it didn't work so
um i i got until in like
in like two to three weeks i got until
uh the beginning
the last episode of the fifth season
ah community mom community
i've watched like so many similar shows
like i really like uh uh
what's called what's it called what's it
called what pop pop pup parks
yeah parks and rec i like parks and rec
and what's the other one with the a
uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh
come on come on come on you know it you
know it i
i i i i think it's something of a yes
arrested development yes yes
and oh my god he says for everyone who
likes those series that i just mentioned
and there is one series that i would
like to recommend you
that probably most of you have never
heard about
i recommend to you now i know there's no
background music it's okay i recommend
to you
uh wait what's this called
web therapy i think that's what it was
called web
therapy i think
i i i recommended this one before it's
so
funny
it's so funny i wish i could watch it
again from the beginning without
ever seeing it without ever having it
seen but i already watched it
and it's so good
your voice sounds
weird today god damn it
i'm waiting for my tea to i i
web therapy yes the good place of course
i've watched the good place
i've watched all of these series that
are
low-key funny
voice is kind of hot
oh thank you you shouldn't say that to
me
because i'll just get a kick out of that
oh i haven't my tea
is too hot okay guys did you
are you guys here for sliver or are you
guys here for the surprise
i know
that's good to hear ah
i'm so tired sorry um so
well the surprise i will show to you now
is
okay um
okay okay i'm excited about this
i've been up and i've been waiting and
hoping for this
for a long time
tea is hot just like you
it's not merch it's not merch guys i'm
sorry it's not merch why would i
suddenly bring out solo merch
there's nothing special happening for me
no birthday
no song nothing it's not merch
unfortunately
sorry so what you guys ready you guys
ready you guys ready
count with me
ten nine
okay slower
eight
seven
six
ah
[Music]
okay back to normal uh okay
i got a logo and i got a layout
oh yeah i got a logo and a layout hey
yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
i commissioned this uh
and this is not the only screen i have
one for gaming as well
which i'll show you in a second and uh i
also have
uh i got
a second
i got a memo collab with later later
today at 9pm japanese standard time
that's in like uh
eight nine nine hours eight
nine hours nine hours i think yay
yay does it look nice it's very orange
but
i was um there's a ticket like orders
yeah because of the tape huh
i was uh since the beginning this is my
debut
i i had to make my own layout uh even
even though i suck at graphic design um
but for the w
i had to make my own layout that was
never really
i mean i mean i got used to it but i
wasn't really happy with it i wanted
something nice
i missed this vgm it's still there and
never has left
oh and yeah now i finally um
yep graphic design is her passion
whoever decides actually graphic design
is
somewhat of my passion
yeah today bird collab but anyway so i
finally uh
commissioned i wanted to commission a
logo which you see there at the bottom
uh it has like elements of my i have my
it has my feathers it has my hats
it has my sword in my shield
you know
finally got a new layout that i really
really like
yeah and i i asked for something with
lots of contrast because
i wanted to like um
i don't know i thought it would look
better to have lots of contrast that's
why
there's like this somewhat somewhat dark
orange
area and then in the back it's a bit
lighter i like the pattern in the
background
very cute and for the
for the title unfortunately the font i'm
using for that is not an obs so every
time i want a new title
i have to go into photoshop and then
write it out out there but i have a feel
prepared i have like
i have like that time i have next month
i have super chat reading and i have
watch along
i prepared those because i couldn't
think of anything else but i think for
now that's
that's more than enough
yes and of course i brought my stamp
silver
and i would say this layout is
kiana approved
a chat is in the bottom left of course
it is of course it is i'm sure my tea i
think it's ready now
yummy
so um
yeah so from now on we will be ditching
my old layout oh look it's kind of sad
like i got so used to my old layout it's
kind of sad to leave it now
knock out final layout
and then guys we have a gaming screen as
well are you guys ready for the gaming
screen gaming spirit
the old layout was okay yeah it was okay
it was just nothing i i just threw
together a bunch of vectors and that's
it how much control of the size of the
elements do you have
uh i mean i have like um
i have i can like uh get rid of
some elements uh
i guess i could probably change the size
of some of it
but i also have like the the background
in it
like alone only the background
in case i want to do something else with
it
but this is like my my chatting screen
and my
uh my my super chat reading screen and
who
what else what else can we use it for i
think we can use it for many things it's
my basic screen now
yep okay it pulled from windows ah but i
have uh
adobe fonts and they're not installed on
windows they're only installed in adobe
programs right that's why i can't use
them in obs
i think i think it's my tangent screen
peace my old leo too bad too bad
i'm gonna miss it maybe sometimes for
nostalgic reasons we
we should use it again okay
are you ready for another countdown
[Music]
eight seven
six uh
five
three
two
[Music]
yay look at this now this is not orange
it's uh
it has more like the colors of the the
light gradation of my hair
more like a softer yeah
nice and i i was working on the chat
yesterday so the chat fits as well
[Music]
i really like the gaming screen
i have a place for the logo of whatever
game we're playing
and then up there we have uh see behind
me
we have uh something going on as well we
have a switch
we have my belt we have my birdie where
my
my my shield as well and my logo at the
top yay
and on this side we have my hashtags
which i also have to change in photoshop
because of the font
whenever i want to change it and we have
the chat of course
yay
[Music]
let's see i think uh
there might be a tweet going up from the
person who made it
saying uh i have made this layout
it's from google someone called google
arigato
a little bit of a something new
something new and fresh
hmm kiana colored joycons oh
would you guys like uh a switch cover
that looks like that
i was thinking of that too like once i
saw that i was like hmm
i would like my switch to look like that
that would be nice
i think people can make it like custom
right
ah isn't this nice it's so fresh let me
turn on uh
music which one should we turn on let's
turn on this one
okay with that uh
being done now
[Music]
um now the rules are guys to feed me
and to make your mama go grow big
and fat and long okay i don't
want to be um
you know eaten up by you guys i i am the
one who has to eat you okay
do you understand feed me beat the
mama's neck
okay please
i don't know if we're doing the puyo
today maybe every once in a while i'll
i'll throw in some puyos
ah this is nice i gave myself a
different color this time
i have uh good luck good luck coming
um into my service
i think some people uh talked about oh
god
i hope that am i already being
targeted please don't
[Music]
okay here we go again does this uh
change the server every time i rejoin i
think i asked this question before
if yes then you guys might have a
problem
finding me no it
where are doesn't babies where are my
babies
[Music]
okay are they coming right now my baby's
coming i'm scared because you guys are
gonna
probably sabotage me again puyo don't
sabotage your mama
i'm gonna grow big before they all come
okay
oh yummy
apparently um there's some chrome uh
extension for joining
uh someone's server so if you really
want to join and you don't know how
there's something like that you're just
going to look it up
[Music]
you wanted to eat me i know that i know
that you wanted to make me bump into you
rude as hell i say booyah
growing big and strong this is nice
because no one is sabotaging me yet
oh no oh no it's it's starting
to account
[Music]
oh you guys are actually feeding me for
reals
[Music]
you're in the way you took my phone
that's my food
i like how you guys are uh advertising
my my stream and my my my collab
cafe number something something
something
yeah eat me mama let me eat you wait i
have to eat someone here
yum yum yum yum yum yum oh it's so big
guys
eat me mama you have to grow a little
bit bigger and then i'll eat you
mmm i mean i can eat you right now as
well but
you guys are actually not sabotaging me
for once
rainbow person rainbow stick very fast
very fast
someone stop that person
snick whatever that is yeah
what are you doing are you trying to
make me eat you
you're too small you're not you know
you're barely food
sacrificed
[Applause]
yes juices
oh my god you guys your names
are terrifying to me
so many people
yo everyone is in the server this is my
server now
kfp has taken over the server once again
i'm actually surprised that uh
slipper.io servers don't crash in
situations like these
i was way too close wait there's so so
much green down there
yeah i'm so big
thank you i wanted to get the one on the
other side too but it's kind of hard to
get them on both sides sorry puyo
you guys are being so nice to me today
yes
that's getting too crowded
sacrifice the sims sacrifice the sims
sacrifice
the sims
sacrifice the sims sacrifice the sims
oh i like how the ad the ads is always
following me
they're all following me ah
go away make some make some space for me
i need some space my legs are too thick
oh thank you thank you
that's mine that's mine
that's also mine
why why not
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
kill him kill him
take him out guys take him out i was so
big i'm never gonna get that big again
three thousand six hundred mo
no okay
that little little chick killed me how
the
how the hell did it do that it's
unbelievable
[Music]
look what i did there but this dude
didn't see that coming
he didn't see that coming
already beak and get my super chat
come on come on come on
can't be intern you're you're a friend
of mine right
you don't want me to die
you want me you want to see me grow
strong and big
real right
you don't want anything bad to happen to
me i think the others are still looking
for me
but they're probably coming soon
right now it's still quiet here only
with an intern
but soon soon the masses will come
oh god there's this little speed snack
which is trying to confuse me i'm sure
of it
where is everyone
[Music]
watch where are you going oh my god oh
my god oh my god oh my god oh my god oh
my god
just be careful that you don't kill uh
kill me by sacrificing yourself real
who am i girls don't say oh my
[Music]
yummy yummy yummy yummy yummy yum yum
yum yum yum
muda your sacrifice was taken by someone
else
i'm sorry i ate i ate a little bit a
little bit a little bit of you
i was able to eat thank you very much oh
thank you
ah right i forgot to look my audio god
damn it
no i can't i can't go out of this right
now
[Music]
blue booster
i will once i die i will do it pineapple
chicken yummy
yummy yummy yummy that sounds good to me
oh my god the kfb intern grow a grew
really big and strong for y'all
who is that is that someone from me
is that a friend of mine pita maybe not
scary up going
thank you thank you thank you
is is he a friend oh hey how does it
meet too many people now
we are
we are rainbow snack very scary
well leah please eat me kiara i would
like to eat you please let me eat you
but let's do it
let's do it somewhere where it's a bit
more quiet
i don't like it when so many people are
watching us when i try to eat you
oh thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
how [\h__\h] dare you
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god
oh my god oh my god oh my god help me
help me
kelly x
they're sabotaging me with names now
that's just that's just that's very
upsetting
please don't use names like that it's
very disturbing you're real second
that's your kia
go away
[Music]
oh so much food you thought you could
kill me there huh
ain't happening ain't happening my
friend
2021 edition
did you throw away the 2020 edition oh
i'm scared i'm scared i'm scared
do this [\h__\h] off
that was a precious sacrifice made by a
kfp
employee to me no one else is allowed to
take that from me
but i'm going on a little travel right
now i'm gonna
i'm gonna go on a journey
gotta get rid of those can i have that
chicken steak
can i can i take a bite
oh thank you chicken steak i asked
nicely
thank you yummy
mmm chicken steak
winner winner chicken dinner is that how
you say it
[Music]
i don't know if the oppai wanted to
wanted to eat me or kill
[Laughter]
all me
that was supposed to be my oh my god
this dude this dude
someone killed him he's he's going a
little bit too fast
he's going a bit too dangerous here
gotta watch where you go
my food for you yummy
i want to get out of here also here's a
faker don't use the same skin
just kidding you can use whatever skin
you want
you're my baby after all but then you
actually have to feed me
feed me now feed me now
your mother
part of my cooking hi to my cooking huh
silver and sander yo what up
where do baby xander how you doing
the server is full well good job to
everyone who made it in
i think it would be nice if some of you
would would uh
leave every once in a while to make some
space for other people that would be
very kind of you guys but i can't really
uh check up on that anyway
guys you gotta go slower guys
and buckle up put up put on your seat
belts guys
oh thank you
finally your sacrifice again didn't get
a sacrifice in a while now
feed me beat me feed me
i'm hungry i didn't eat breakfast yet oh
my my
my mom mine mine one more mine one month
thank you
[Music]
i got a little bit too careless there
music is back f for respect no
seven six seven six nine
oh
yes okay
next round i will not give up
i want i oh i want to be as thick as he
is or was i
was i that thick before and now it just
looks much bigger because i'm so small
oh are you going to sacrifice yourself
[Music]
oh wait how are we going to do this
thank you i finished sacrifice
thank you
kelly
kelly asked me to eat her i only got
half of her
there's this this this dude took you
away from me
why won't you do that give her back to
me
she's oh she's mine
why is everyone so aggressive when they
play this game like
just chill just roll big or natural
why do you have to sabotage others
not cool muda he alex kelly
you have good taster oh my god oh my god
oh my god go away
go away
you got so greedy buddy
i am growing big and healthy and strong
some people have recently been a bit
confused
about what i am when them thank you for
them
because i started off as a phoenix but
people
were thinking i'm a chicken oh my god oh
my god oh my god okay
okay go away go away
oh
so yeah so people thought i was a
chicken but i would i never was a
chicken
i always was a phoenix so that doesn't
count but then
i turned into a snack at some point
and also i turned into a variety of
other birds because i
i i made voice i made the voices of
of many many birds like seagulls
a crowd crow crow crap
crap crap well damn it
and um what ah
i did make chicken noises so let's just
say i i can be a chicken if i want to be
but i'm a phoenix
at heart and
kiana move your big hair what what does
that mean
what what does that mean
oh wait i'm trying to tell the story i'm
trying to
go away i'm trying to focus
okay imperial imperial imperial taco i'm
banning you in the chat
come on show yourself show yourself i'm
gonna i'm gonna ban you
come here come here usual room let's go
now
show yourself i'm waiting for it
are you scared now are you scared
[Music]
room are you scared are you scared huh
huh
oh i'm continuing
i'm screaming too much my voice hurts
anyway so yeah
i was doing all kinds of noises of
animals
um i i was also a cat at some point
sometimes sometimes i'm a cat sometimes
i was a snack as i am now
and recently i turned into a frog but
now i'm a snack again
and this evening i am also turning into
a dog
with my collab with dana where is the ad
where is the ad when i need it
so i think by now you've noticed i'm
invincible because i can't become
any animal that i want to be
shapeshifter phoenix
but honestly like recently it's been so
chaotic i've i've turned into
so many animals recently and there's
like so much like fan art of a
frog kiara now
[Music]
i really started to embrace
my frog self why
you better sacrifice yourself to me
after that after eating my food
oh my god oh my god oh my god
this this person probably doesn't belong
to us right
maybe one day thank you
maybe one day papa will make me a frog
outfit
oh my god the other side
i wanted that i went for the smaller
food
food source
maybe maybe in the future all my new
outfits will be a different animal
i will become an every animal that
[Music]
exists
i'm feeling kind of sick right now to be
honest
i didn't eat breakfast i'm feeling a bit
weird
no why is when there's so many people
oh it's so dangerous someone someone eat
someone
i'll get out of here get the hell out of
there get the hell out of there puya
sassana sausage shuba
are you from switzerland why are you
trying to be
helpful isn't that the sweetest
switzerland flag
oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god
get away from here i'm gonna get away
from here
ah yeah that's the switzerland flag
right
kinotori
who wouldn't want to be woken up from
that
yes you are going to the room because
you almost ate me
i'll tell you we are
ottoman's juices is always there
yes yes yes yes yes [\h__\h] off
sorry sorry i'm sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
by the way for today's collaboration i
will
be careful with the choice of my words i
promise
uh when i am on elena's channel i will
be very careful
with my choice of words i will not swear
[Music]
actually what the hell i'm
i'm really feeling a bit weird right now
we are is it the game that's making me
feel weird
is it the fact that i didn't eat
breakfast making me feel weird
is it the fact that i cooked for myself
yesterday making me feel weird and maybe
the food that i cooked
this is making my stomach feel weird
right now
what do i learn from that should never
cook for myself ever again
i poisoned myself
probably
hey i'm pretty pretty thick again right
now 3
600. nice
yeah speedrun
speedrun yay we're just zooming
[Music]
that was fun guys thank you
700k subs endurance oh yeah i'm like 10k
subs away from that
i'm 10 000 subs away from 700k but i
don't think i can do an endurance today
yeah by the way oh my god oh my god yeah
my food that was supposed to be my food
i'm
a bad bee emilia love
i'm about what happened why did she ban
you tell me more about it tell me more
tell me more
should i talk to her about it oh yeah
oh on your screen you wear a different
color
oh my god why is there so many people
here right now
[Music]
sacrificial sacrificial frog is that how
you say it
give me the frog oh my god that's so
much food
[Music]
the bottom left energy almost took over
me
oh my god wait was that kiara nozako who
finally sacrificed himself to me
[Music]
eat me again callie
i would love to i'm sweating right now
[Music]
why would you eat kelly
why that's not fair
that's not fair
uh it's not fair
why 5200
wait i need to i have apples next to me
let me
let me eat my apples my apple slices
and see if that will help
i dropped the apple no okay free three
second rule
no she'll go for your brain oh yeah
sure that's good for my brain right
so juicy
oh for real actually
[Music]
dude i just i don't know eat me
i don't i gotta be real light
um i don't think i can
continue right now
i was trying to um make the stream fun
and go a little bit longer but
it's weird i feel really weird
i mean we could try to wait for five
minutes and see if it gets better
i want to play sick
i want to play snack
uh
i wanna be snack i wanna
it will go away maybe it will go away
maybe it will go away for y'all i gotta
stay strong
never giving up eh
let's see let's see i'll give it a few
more minutes if it doesn't get better
in a few more minutes then i i i
probably have to quit
feed me beat me guys i need to i need to
become healthy someone sacrifice
yourself to me i need to be healthy
let me eat you let me eat you i'm not
feeling so well right now
feeding kiera thank you but you're oh
thank you thank you
come on now my babies you're gonna have
a good ass dirty pc
you guys have some mercy with me now
right because
oh it's so sparkly
so many colors oh
at least for 40 for the last run or so i
don't know it's going to be the last one
but at least
now can can everyone feed me and make me
go to the top of the
scoreboard please
ah it's getting so crowded for y'all
ugh
[Music]
strong snack wheel
somebody for you
[Music]
i'm i'm fine i think i'm fine i think
i kinda
[Music]
i love you guys so much
yummy yummy yummy yummy yummy i'm
i'm oh you are i think you wanted to
sacrifice yourself to me but
you hate me let me drink some
man i wanna have fun i don't want to
rest
hold on i still couldn't make it tend to
eat me
i want to eat him but what
you might be having an aura seizure what
what what's that
yeah but i wanna i wanna
this is so much fun now i wanna wait
more
i wanna play more
i want to blame is that google play is
that a google play skin
i want a kiana skin
okay we're going we're going until i
throw up
yes where are my kids oh judah's 2021
edition is on
number seven holy crap
where are you you must be really fat
right now
where is judas oh thank you
where's judah is that one that eats
tutors judas
sacrifice yourself to the greater the
greater
uh i don't know what do you say greater
god
where are you
[Music]
i feel every time i scream i'm i i feel
uh weird
now i'm not gonna throw up on the stream
i would never do that i would
i would probably mute myself before that
would happen for young
i'm i i think i'm okay yeah that's apple
you guys are so cute i love your names
everyone's so adorable i wanna i wanna
date everyone
but i already have cali so i'm sorry ah
wait that was on me
that was on me i sacrificed myself to
the frog
thank you team akimi yeah of course i've
watched
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat
thank you for the super chat is that
gouda oh my god good eye is so big
you're so scary and you're supposed to
be small
are you gonna protect me good are you
protecting me
but i had this before in in the other
sliver stream where i
thought i've oh god yeah sorry i'm
losing
i'm losing i'm losing concentration
i thought that someone was like circling
me to protect me but eventually they
were circling me to eat me up
to eat me alive
i don't know why why you would do such a
thing
that's just rude that's sad for y'all
i think i'm feeling better for y'all
i think i might be feeling better for
y'all i think i'm okay for y'all
and we will see i'm looking for judas
has someone seen judas is that judas
question mark i know that's not true
this is too small to do this
i'm gonna join you sure oh my god oh my
god oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my
god mine
oh yummy oh yes
mama go fat so many carefree people
thank you thank you i knew that that you
were going to sacrifice yourself to me
thank you
so many sacrifices what's going on
you guys are much nicer to me this time
compared to the last time we played this
game oh
thank you itadakimasu
[Music]
really oh man
i got so many nice sacrifices this time
i need more i did it what
bit here what wait where did you just go
i did judas
you what you actually did where which
one was you
you ran into him oh
oh i that
i ran into him or he into me
someone has to grow really big and
strong again and feed me again please
please
[Laughter]
carrots are good guys eat your carrots
that actually really does look like a
carrot
eat your carrots everyone mean nuts
underneath
an oil
[Music]
can i have this big boy can you
sacrifice
yourself to me
yum yum
[Music]
my wow
you guys are getting caught so close oh
my god
yo almost i'm gonna protect you okay
just look for team akin me don't kill me
where are you where are you you gotta go
grow strong and big in order to protect
me though oh my god you you are speed
what he got eaten up and now it's my
time i know you wanted to eat it
[Music]
ground pounder
okay shoot shoot
we have to focus for you thank you for
the red super chats
by the way thank you please protect me
please protect me please
i'm looking for a mama you know i'm
everyone's mama but i also sometimes
want a mama sometimes i want to be the
child
sometimes i want to be fed
can can someone be my mama
mama
mama mama or callie
callie is also good callie callie
protect me
[Music]
trap room send help what
are you trapped in the usual room i'm
not going to help you out of there
no no
that's not fair
[Music]
okay
who's that who's that who's that big
person
oh wait who are those two
like twins super strong twins who are
you
who are show your face to me
show your face
maybe please rest for you no i'm okay i
think i'm better now
actually yeah i'm fine i think it has
resolved itself
thank you
or is he trying to is he is he trying
to be nice and protect me no he's trying
to eat me
he's trying to eat me help me
help me
[Music]
revenge
someone is on number two why is that
person
where are you
wait he's gone am i not actually
changing servers because he's gone now
or did he really just die the moment i
died
but the whole leaderboard looks
different to me
yeah when people say i don't switch
servers
[Music]
you're jumping between a few servers
ah
i wanna go back i want to find akihiro
kikiriki and
and and i want him to sacrifice himself
to me
hello simps says the simp
from from one sip to another simply all
[Music]
that was a little bit too close you know
no no no no what's going on here do this
i don't like this do this
you just go away
goddammit almost
hey he wanted to get me i know i know he
wants to get me i ain't do this
thank you oh my god oh yum yum yum yum
so many yummy strawberries
sparkly oh my god
i love you guys who does lost bread
oh my god should we eat it or should we
give it back to her
it's so small what's what's good is
good i'm going to do with such a small
bread
no one needs that okay sorry that you're
looking cute
you're looking so that's so cute you're
so cute
it's so small for you
kawaii oh the usual room is sacrificing
himself to me
mine mine mine mine mine mine mine
demonetization oh no
oh no oh no
i hope the demonetization is not out
there to get me please no
i'm being so careful okay i'm ah
[\h__\h] yeah
i'm on that map again okay let's see if
we can find him
he's already at 21k a kfb member
is at 21k number two
oh my god let's get him to number one
and then eat him
the sensor i don't need this i don't
have time to push push the sensor button
i think i got time for that for you i
got no time for that [\h__\h] we all
maybe when i call up with lena i will
make use of that button
whenever i get angry but i will not get
angry because there is no reason to get
angry
there is no ah
okay continuing
i want food where where is my food
that dude is huge who is that
is that one of them wait that's number
one
that's number one right because he's
yellow isn't that number one
with no name
[Music]
i wanted to see the face why would you
do that no
now i'm on a different spot a little
surger
oh this person is also big big snake
big snake killer
i don't like the name of this dude he's
number seven oh no
is he going is he going to kill me maybe
he's so big he won't notice that i'm
inside of him okay and never mind i left
his
left the inside of the killer the frog
phoenix
sit on me
are you asking piccolo to sit on you or
are you
being peculiar asking me to sit on you
because takura sitting on you will never
happen [\h__\h] you
bye he was it was like
he was he was really going for it he was
really trying to kill me
where am i why are the people there
protect me
[Music]
where is my food boil derek
[Laughter]
derek is here yo
so nice to see everyone all my employees
so nice to see you guys
onion here's the onion yummy
onions
no let me get that one i want i want it
i want it i want it
oh dangerous dangerous foil
[Music]
you guys are being really creative here
i want to rank everyone
i want to rank everyone's names
demonetization was there again someone
bad him from the server please
i don't want to be in the same server as
demonetization he's
he's like he's literally looking for me
trying to kill me
nothing
[Music]
okay you were trying to you were trying
to do that okay i was trying
i was getting scared i'm being a bit
paranoid in this game
very scary unzip your pants
[Laughter]
it's from there a way out can you play
this from our layout gameplay it's a
quote from cali
ah i wanted that
oh thank you for the red super chat
bronx thank you so much
i don't want demonetization to come upon
me please no okay if you sacrifice oh my
god oh my god
wait wait i don't know which one to eat
i felt this one was safer
ah thank you though thank you
not a cult for you oh my
[Music]
are you guys being so so reckless why is
everyone
going into these dangerous situations i
want that come on
[Music]
painful
it's hard to be a snake wheel it's hard
to be a popular snake because everyone
is out there to get me booyoon
[Music]
there i think i'm in the server again
where uh demonetization
is trying to get me mama mama milk
i know you want my milk but can i have
your milk can we give each other some
milk
thank you
thank you wait this purple guy this
purple guy is doing some dangerous
things here let's get out of here guys
oh my god we can't get out of here maybe
maybe we can maybe down here
no oh
[Music]
why are you protecting wait maybe he's
protecting me do you guys think he's
protecting me
is he protected no he's not protecting
me but he's like
not no his circle is not getting smaller
so i don't think he's trying to eat me
or he's waiting for me to grow big and
big and big and then he tries to eat me
not yet yeah we're having a party in
here i'm his mustache and who's the
other one
who's the other one kfb cactus inspector
okay
it's it's us free in here let's have a
party
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
party poo your party for your party for
your party for you
where are you anyway i think he's uh a
good guy
maybe it's the person who sent the super
chat saying they will protect me
i like this i just have to i'm not
really growing much in here to be honest
because there's not so much food
but good enough oh my god oh my god oh
my god
[Music]
am i getting mama i always wanted to be
mamas
cool
[Music]
i always wanted to be like that
i wanted to be circles but in a good way
not in a bad way
i want it to be protected
yum yum yum yum yum and you guys go no
mother dad who killed my mama who kissed
my mother
you [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh thank you guys thank you
thank you thank you guys
i had a great time oh god awkward money
oh no just this person is trying to eat
me someone saved me someone saved
i think i think maybe he no no seems to
have
he's leaving he's leaving maybe good
intentions
show feet i'm not going to show you my
feet
nice
[Music]
please
i had this before i think i ate jaguar
before
wasn't there a time where i ate diagon
before already
keep fighting for y'all wait that
actually makes sense kfb keep fighting
for y'all
thank you eat me dancer oh i would love
to but can we like go somewhere else for
that
can we get a hotel room just you and me
one second i'm almost ready
wait wait wait wait wait wait not yet
eat potential okay okay
okay it was now or never
yeah i'm going i'm getting so big and so
slow though
i'm at seven thousand nine hundred oh my
god
that's the biggest i've ever been i
think okay no [\h__\h] around now
you gotta be careful guys
[Music]
okay all food look good nice for y'all
you're too close my friends too
close for y'all help me
could you meet help me
yummy yum oh i see
caffeine yo you're almost the same size
oh [\h__\h] oh my god for y'all
danger
screaming anymore but i oh
[Applause]
[Music]
i was almost at 10
i was over nine thousand [\h__\h] you go
away
you probably didn't know that i would
i'm kiara cause i changed my name
i changed my name guys you have to
protect fukuyo now i was over 9
000.
[Music]
try going in circles and trap otters but
then i probably will just kill myself
well okay if i grow as big as i was
before
then i'll give it a try but the thing is
people just get too close
by the time that i get that big people
are
all like ganging up on me and getting
like super close casper
passport is not a rat that's rude your
name is misleading
it's deformation is that how you say it
oh my god bottom left energy are you are
you here to feed me
please tell me you're here to feed me
oh no i think i i think he wanted to
but i was too stupid
death is what definition that defamation
okay okay
casper change your name to casper the
mouse because casper is is not a rat
casper is a mouse okay a cute
little adorable mouse just trying his
best to stay alive in my ceiling
but recently he's been so quiet so
i think i think
he might not be alive much longer
i hope he'll stay alive though real
oh is that the new oh wait
never mind i'm not i'm not going to say
anything
i i i i'm not i'm not going to say
oh pewdiepie
yui are you a friend no i think this
person is trying to eat me help me help
me or me
or are you protecting are you protecting
me are you a friend or foe
oh no no this is no no no no not happy
happy kelly help me kelly kelly help
because
of it
can i help you can you help me
oh my god oh my god who was that who was
that
who was that legendary hero oh my god i
was so close to dying right now
oh my i saw death like cali was
literally there i was seeing duff
oh my god oh my god i'm getting i'm
feeling dizzy again no no
who was that who was that herod
[Music]
that was amazing i was so close
the clutch was so real i was so close to
death
oh my god oh my gosh
[Music]
there
it was it cali was it was it really um
i mean i know it's not cali but was it
that that snake who saved me
i need to re-watch that and see who the
hero was
i have to rewatch the situation next
for kiara for you kiara nom nom frog
milk
yummy everyone sounds so yummy oh oh
yummy thank you
cali smell yo what up
at some point we could do a right next
up is 700 000 k right
maybe it's uh at 900
990 000 subs
i'm going to do oh my god you're so big
now
hatchimals juices wow i'm going to do
um a slaver.io rta
until 1 million subs at 990k
remind me on that oh my god thank you
everyone kfb notes here's my sticky
notes
write it down at 990k
i know i'm i'm way uh far away from that
990k we're going to do a sliver.io rta
[Laughter]
thank you let me eat you let me eat you
let me eat you please for y'all
thank you i love you thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you for the red super chat
everyone's names are so funny red super
chat what are you gonna give yourself to
me you're
pretty small right now you gotta grow
bigger that's not
what a red super chat is supposed to
look like
red super chat is a little bit thicker
than that
uncle uncle there's poop
someone pick up their poop here
someone left their poop
where are my sacrifices where are my
sacrifices bottom left energy you want
to eat me right
the other way around sorry let me eat
you thank you
i'm gonna make a circle now i
am circle i'm not only frog i am
also circled we are i'm settled for you
[Music]
you're so small should i protect you
let me protect you sapphire kitten don't
move
don't move
okay i'm protecting you now you are
under ah
[Music]
oh my god i tried i tried i tried
i tried to protect you don't move don't
move
don't move let me protect you i want to
protect someone yes okay
okay i'm protecting you yeah i will
never
never let you die never never
never never never gonna give you
up never gonna help help
okay i can't protect you for too long
and why not grow bigger bye bye
good luck in the tough world outside
there good luck
flip this game what are you trying to
tell me to do
there was so much food over there the
frog paradise took it away from me for
you
yeah then go home go
aquamarine is there again wait wasn't
wait was it was aquamarine
trying to protect me for a while i think
yes back
i couldn't get there i'm sorry oh
my food oh my god oh my god
it was not your fault it was not your
fault
[Music]
but who is that that's the that's that
that's the german
flag
hello
may i eat you please asking kindly in
german
[Music]
i think my german viewers are asleep
right now
right where my german viewers i think
it's like
in the middle of the night for them or
ah some of them could be awake by now if
they're
if they like to wake up early casper you
changed your name
oh my god who is this pink person wait
was that pink person is that the same
from
hey i'm getting confused didn't the pink
snake protect me before
isn't that my mama is that is that my
mama
mama you're so big already go away go
away go
away guys casper crystal can i eat you
casper
thank you casper yo you're such a you're
such a good roommate to have
thank you sorry that i tried to get rid
of you
i deeply apologize
mama
are you gonna feed yourself to me as
well eventually you don't have to do it
right away but
at some point it would be nice oh my god
the kiana kicker
bobby campbell the communicator is out
there trying to get me
be careful and if he wants to get me
that means he has to kill you first so
please be careful
be careful mama i believe in you we will
grow strong together
mama mama mama it's dangerous
please be careful mama i don't want to
see you die again that was the biggest
pain i've found in a long time someone
killed the killer someone killed the
killer come on please
please it's too dangerous we need to get
rid of the killer
the killer is there is that next to us
someone kill him
[Music]
[Laughter]
what are they doing oh no oh no someone
is getting eaten
no oh good job he was trying to eat you
for y'all
but strong food is hella strong for you
did you guys see that
good job wow
[Music]
the killer is still there he's right
next to my mama
right next to her
why is no one why is no one taking off
the challenge
to kill mountain to kill the killer
kiana killer on the prowl hell's just
vibing and spinning
yeah this is peaceful i enjoy this game
when i'm like protected aquamarine is
out there as well
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh did you what's going
on now mama what's going on
mama be careful mama come on mama where
are you going
mama where are you going mama okay okay
okay
okay okay mama okay mama
oh yummy mama you gave me some food
thank you mama
is the killer gone i don't see the
killer anymore
[Music]
look at me no the killer
i almost died oh my god there's so many
suicides here right now help me
i'm scared someone protects me
help me
i'm scared my momma is good who wants to
be my new mama
it's so scary oh my god please someone
go away everyone please
please go away please
please no text i got the pop but you're
orange
help me help me help me
[Music]
you are the last person i want to see
right now
no no no no no no oh my god i almost
died
because of a tiny tiny ass snake yeah
yeah you look the kia killer oh my god
oh my god
let's let's do it we gotta kill the kia
killer
no one's too dangerous it's too
[Music]
dangerous
judas is getting bigger who is that
who's that
nice sacrifice
[Music]
ah
next time i see you in the chat
i'm gonna ban you oh there we go
i have my mouse um put user in timeout
my mouse is on it
but i'm trying i'm trying to be i'm
trying to control myself
i'm trying to control myself
but this is my channel my channel my
rules off to the usual room bye bye
whoa nice
i want to say nice start but do it
i i i did it
well i'm the boss here okay you guys
gotta realize who's the boss okay
but if i unless i die
under uh 5 000 if i got over 5000 then
this is the last game oh
oh
[Music]
i don't want to die too small i know i
always say that i always say
last game last game when it comes to
this game which
sounds weird because this is the second
time we'll play it but i know i did it
last time but
but we gotta end it somewhere because i
wanted it to be somewhat short
and then i wanted to read uh super chat
where's food where's mama mama mama
mama is this the server where mama was
i know i see what you were trying to do
there i see it
younger you better behave better watch
out
[Music]
is
i would like to let me turn around thank
you
[Music]
[Applause]
is that my new mama or is this this
looks kind of dangerous
it looks a bit dangerous
[Music]
is this person going to eat me or
protect me
oh no he wants to eat meat please
someone help me
no one no one came to rescue me
i didn't go over 5000 so i'm playing
again
who was that what was the name of that
person what was the name
something was bk i think was it
again
oh
[Music]
that man i think his name was really you
or at least it will be soon
damn right sir damn right
piano medicine thank you you guys are so
kind and
[Music]
sweet
look at what i just did there
thank you
oh my god sweet in the literal sense
yeah that's some lyrics i better pretend
oh diamonds incense queen of sayonara
psych like psych
[Music]
i need to um officially
give that wrap a try once i practiced it
in a stream
and got pretty well at it
[Music]
look where you're going oh
are you protecting me bro
need a new mama what oh old mama was
best mama
i want my old mama back mama
mama looking for mama
[Music]
this shutdown guy is
uh doing some dangerous things here
i wanted to kill him for you
no he's kidding now he's trying to kill
me help me help me
[Music]
no don't circle me with that guy don't
tickle me with that guy i don't want to
be in the same circle with that guy mama
mama
mama we gotta take care of him first
mama please mama
mama mama
mama we gotta take care of him first
please
do something about it now mama mama mama
[Music]
mama boy that the wrong server where is
my mama
that's not the same server ryan would
you kill me
that's that's the wrong side right mama
mama server
mama mama a wrong server kill me kill me
kill me and kill me
i'm sacrificing myself please just let
me it's okay let's let me easy
the other way no no
please please please thank you
i wasn't trying to get you dude wait
which one is mama server
mama which one is mama's server
is this mama's server
i forgot which one is mama server mama
wait i'll come
come to you does someone know
is that mama server no
finding mama i don't think this is
i don't think this is it or maybe is it
the number six
nine thousand four hundred
this one is i think it is really okay
mama
we gotta look for mama we gotta find
more of these pink
wait i'm super far at the edge where is
mount
rest in peace kiara oh no no hell no
[Music]
i respect you you are the one who's oh
oh my god
we are
oh my god this is what i call
the kfb power together united
we will make kiana strong
i will be the number one phoenix
the leading fast food franchise in the
[Music]
world
oh my god demonetization is there no my
mother
please be careful there's demonetization
he killed me many times already
be careful mama yeah
[Music]
from austria oh hello austria i'm from
australia
love back to you though is that keanu's
killer
no kiana killer killer oh no he's
kiana's killer killer
everything's okay okay we say we're safe
guys
we're safe don't worry he's kiara's
killer killer
killer's killer we help
you we just gotta take care of uh the
demonetization
kiana dude sup bro all right don't talk
to me like that
you gotta address me with more respect
okay
otherwise my mama will eat you why is
cute i don't kill a killer
no we don't need a killer killer killer
we don't need a kayla killer oh yeah
someone has infiltrated my
oh no oh my god that was close wait mama
mama why did you let people in here
okay if we cannot kill
oh thank you
thank you so much for the sacrifice mama
let some safe people in here mama has a
good eye for who's safe and who isn't
can i eat you
can i eat you too i was gonna say pickle
i'm getting a bit confused here
i'm circling you and mama is circling me
can someone circle mama to protect mama
so that mama never dies which
bastard
[Music]
which bastard killed my mama
i am revenge for mama is this the right
server i think it is
[Music]
who was it was it was it demonetization
again
unbelievable the pain that i have to go
through
should i should i home tonight
[Music]
how do i live about my mama
how do i live without you
mama i told you guys unless i'm
um over 5000
i will continue if i'm over 5000 then
that's the last game
but we will see how long that will get
me i need my mama in order to
get to that number thank you
thank you thank you thank you
chiara babes
yes that's a that's a bit closer to how
you're supposed to address me
thank you that's my food [\h__\h] off
that's my food oh
thank you thank you
[Music]
i was just enjoying my my lunch what the
hell man i'm just trying to have
breakfast do not even give me breakfast
that's just rude oh thank you
oh thank you thank you where's my mama
though
[Laughter]
i'm not i'm not always over under five
thousand i got six thousand over six
thousand
like two times and i got um uh
over 9 000 one time oh god who is this
that is daddy
maybe i should try to be a bit more
aggressive
who was that no name person who was that
[Music]
google play store oh the colors are so
pretty
okay looking for mama looking for mama
again
use your speed to run from them when
they circle me
you mean before they circle me i will
try
i don't mind already so long no no that
was my imagination i'm not that long
feeding kiana but you're so small that's
barely anything
oh yeah did you see that guys
[Music]
come on let me eat you
okay
is that your nickname for me that's kind
of cute
i have no problem with that when you
guys give me cute nicknames
i like it chiara's architect i have an
architect wow i have like everything
kfb has like camping was supposed to be
a fast food franchise
but i think we have a few positions that
we don't actually need
so maybe we should um get rid of some of
these positions
but i honestly also don't want to fire
anyone because at the moment if i fire
someone
uh it's like pretty much
the end of their life probably
it's going to be really hard to find a
new job
tucker money love cafe canada
canada world of canada
oh god okay it's time for me to
a small snack thank you
yum yum yum yum okay i i i
left a little bit of you for someone
else i hope you're okay with that
he wants to kill me
[Music]
where's my mama hama did you give up
mama i don't see any mamas at the moment
kind of sad
yes i want to eat this rainbow person i
still can't you oh hell no you're not
gonna steal callie
she's mine
where's that rainbow person i to eat the
rainbow person
[Music]
we work for her but we also pay her
that's right that's how it works
it's not easy
for me mama oh please
thank you oh my god that was close that
was close and someone big died here
yes yes
i was never so happy about food ever
before
oh yeah but it's getting oh it's getting
too crowded holy [\h__\h] oh my god it's
getting it's getting too crowded [\h__\h]
off [\h__\h] up
oh yeah
that's what happens when you get too
close to a whole lot idol
you get destroyed
so be careful guys
i'm wait i'm at eight thousand eight
thousand eight hundred oh my god
what okay now don't die kiara
don't die let's eat the dead beets in
the hot
she's trying to get me no no no no i've
come so far i'm going for it
i'm over 9 000. i'm going for 10 000 now
i'm going for ten thousand oh [\h__\h]
how much am i circling me
that was close holy [\h__\h] okay leaving
i'm leaving
oh
[Music]
i was so worth nine thousand but now i'm
under nine thousand why am i another
nine thousand
dollars
but okay the goal was to the goal was to
get over 5 000.
yes um
unfortunately i
that was
that was not the last cake
i can't stop it's so much fun
it's so much fun i just can't stop
myself
is this my new mama are you my mama
all right you're so big you don't really
need to eat me that's so unnecessary
um
that's bullying what the [\h__\h] man
you did not have to eat me you were so
huge and you were going for such a
little snake what the hell
i'm going again wait i think i see mama
on the leaderboard no name pink that
must be my mama
[Music]
in the west part of the map please find
me mama where are you mama
let's do it one more time mama you and
me thank you
one more time one more time re reunion
with my mama
addiction presentation
wait mama is number one isn't that mama
like we have to find mama mama is at 20
20k holy [\h__\h] mama where's mama
[Music]
i have to get a bit bigger before i get
to mama because otherwise
i don't grow much inside of mama it
takes some time
can i eat you thank you
okay
mama don't die please stay alive mama
please be careful until i see you
save kiara thank you i like how you're
going into defense mode
after seeing me thank you thank you
ten thousand please
okay it's getting way too crowded way
too crowded here
help me please
please kill yourself now
the shots down guys back oh are you are
you trying to
uh oh god the demonetization is there
help people
oh thank you thank you that's very nice
of you
you're not my real mama though but thank
you but you're not my real
[Music]
thank you i appreciate it you're
protecting me but i feel like
you gotta be careful there's too many
people are you leaving me
thank you for like i think you're trying
to support me to find my mama
very supportive of you yaga
i wanna leave
we kissed we kissed
we kissed did you see that we can't do
it we kissed each other
now was that the demonetized it would
that wasn't that kind of the
demonetization
account
[Music]
dino i don't know if you're with me but
if you're from the kfp then yahoo
mama is no mama died someone killed mama
she was number one someone killed mama
a machine
no i didn't find her
i couldn't find her
it's gonna i want that
when is this stream ever gonna end
when is it going to end
[Music]
okay okay last stream last game
that's a lie probably that's a lie
probably this is not going to be the
last one for you
i was a bit distracted by
okay but we have to really end it
somewhere you had us toilet
ew because we were leaving some poop
here and there
because i need to read super jets
i need to read super jets
kelly kelly
you and me together forever don't kill
me kelly what the hell
i thought hey funny way here from me
kiana's toilet is following me
chicken feet ah
that was dangerous that was that was
very dangerous help me
help me help me help me help me
yeah i think number eight is my mama
again
number eight is growing fast too
was just number nine a second ago
who are you mama show yourself to me
are you the real mama
i thought i was everyone's mama
but oh my god the demonetization is so
big oh run run maybe he didn't see me
maybe he didn't see me we're gonna run
we're gonna run
we're gonna run no you're dumb
unknown kfb cultist you would have kelly
and
ahmed i i'm sorry but you gotta go
i'm sorry but you are in the way of my
love story with
mama
[Music]
i'm gonna go inside you now
maybe it's too difficult to circle me
right now
let me go inside you i'm going inside
you
mama mama mama
no i was just reuniting with my mama
why would you do that i was so happy to
see my mama again
[Music]
she was probably getting like really
excited to see me again and she went a
little bit too fast and then she bumped
into someone
so sad it's the saddest story i've ever
heard
strickling each other it's my food
let me eat you oh
thank you yum yum yum yum yum
let's see if i can survive until my mama
is back
that's a new challenge
top 10 saddest anime moments
[Music]
so sad
i killed juggle i
killed your girl
no it's getting real dangerous again
guys
no i i need my mama to survive
ah
someone help me it's too much going on
here
jago's idol dream i am i'm going to eat
it up
give yourself to me oh
yeah can't be save you please please
please either sacrifice yourself or go
away
this is too much stress i'm getting like
anxiety issues right now
[Music]
escape
help me she's trying to get me
i wasn't top ten oh my god did someone
take a screenshot of that
yes it's going good okay we're surviving
we're surviving until my mama comes back
help me
someone kill him someone kill him
someone killed a demonetization this is
not okay this is bullying
easy
can i have you me can i no no no no no
ah
no no i can't i have to stop i have to
stop i have to stop i have to stop
[Music]
oops
so proof was not on purpose i i
accidentally played that um okay thank
you guys for watching uh
that was fun i might want to play this
like without streaming
i want to announce on on on twitter
that i'm going to play it and then have
everyone join
but then people wouldn't really know for
sure which one is me
right because they can
ah yeah they just have to trust me
i was found out
thank you everyone it's hard to find
without them ah that's true ah
damn it oh hmm
you guys are all welcome to stay and for
everyone who wasn't here in the
beginning
what do you think about my new layout i
have a new layout
do you like it i i commissioned a new
layout for gaming and for the normal
screen as well
[Music]
now we got a logo i can i can put that
logo everywhere now that's nice i always
wanted a logo
i always wanted my own logo yay
it's bright and poppy yeah bright and
peppy yeah
i found you but it's hard to feed you i
want to play more
yeah that was fun
thank you guys so much for participating
logo is too big and it covers you ah
well yeah it takes some a bit of space
but
i think it's okay i think it's okay i
can also
like make myself smaller so you see
more of myself and i can get rid of the
i can actually move
i was wondering where uh the memo would
be best
because i think it was supposed to be
like up here but
then i don't know i was getting it was
getting a bit too crowded but because of
the tape
it kind of has to hang somewhere but it
doesn't
i think it's good over here
i think it fits yeah quite well over
here
yes
i was so happy with my new layer the new
background is cute thank you
thanks for the stream camera thank you
thank you everyone who participated
liver.io is so much fun i want to do
this more often
every now and then thank you for the
membership
callie says hello wait what do you mean
callie says hi
kelly wants to show up on her once wants
to show up on her stream kiana what do
you mean
callie is calling you attention
why is she summoning me isn't she
watching a movie
what's going on kelly is kind of craving
my attention recently
she wants me to comment on her stream
there was a bird in the movie okay
she wants me to show up huh
kelly you think i'm your puppet or
something
okay one i'm having some conflicted
feelings
no
stretching ah she just wants me to say
hi in her chat but then i have to open
up the streaming
i'm saying hi tell her i said hi tell
her i said hello
she says she in your heart go what
is it just made up are you guys just
making it up
she wants to compare who is the smarter
bird but obviously it's me
obviously that would be me
oh oh
hey guys and this is more for like uh
i think japanese fans
[Music]
starting from today in all uh joy sound
karaoke devices
in japan and you can my song is included
hinotoni is included from now on
[Music]
i actually knew this this was gonna
happen sometime soon
i knew it for a while and it finally
happened yay
actually in japan and the karaoke
karaoke um culture is pretty big so
there's like karaoke
places everywhere and the kanoka
is like kind of high-tech in japan
they have really nice karaoke rooms and
karaoke machines
and they have so many songs on it it's
my favorite thing to do in
in japan when i want to hang out with
friends i want to go to karaoke every
time
and there's a pretty much like two
two big karaoke devices that you can
usually choose from and one of them is
joy sound
so now i will always use joy sound
i think the other whole live songs are
also
only on joy sound i think
then
i don't know if there's like joy sound
uh in karaoke machines overseas
or is that only a japan thing i wonder
anyway i need to
i need to
is back
i hope you had fun in the usual room
my voice feels like my voice feels like
[\h__\h] today
and i generally feel a bit weird today
but it's actually
uh after after a while it got better
today
during the stream i'm just making some
tea again right now
yeah what
after the room i found salvation i am a
changed man new year knew me
are you are you finally gonna be nice to
me
i mean you you you were not as
rebellious as albedo
but does this mean you're gonna let me
win in games now
please let me win takamori never died
that's right
i'm just getting a bit confused because
because kelly is asking
for more um attention from me
and it's confusing me kelly said she
wanted to do karaoke with you before you
left a few streams ago
you mean like actual karaoke or karaoke
stream because we wanted to
um before i leave we wanted to do a
karaoke stream
but i'm talking about going going to
actual karaoke just together without
streaming
hope you'll get better jamaica's rory
pakatori thank you
actually maybe
maybe i should do a separate uh super
chat reading
i don't know
thanks so much for playing slip again it
was really fun i had fun too
thank you guys for joining
let me let me let me think about it for
a moment
let me drink my tea and think about it
if i want to
do it now i don't feel like my voice is
going to
after all that screaming
i like this new layout cute thank you
ah might be better to rest
yeah i have a collab later the collab is
not on my channel by the way
okay everyone you have to
make sure that you are going to be there
for the collab with reina please
have you gotten everything for your trip
no i didn't yet
um i went to buy a fluffy
warm jacket tally said she provides kf
employees with life insurance
is this scab
cali provides them with life insurance
[Music]
well
x
ah i am not sure about that
thank you for the red super chat though
thank you
i gotta buy some stuff for the trip some
warm clothing
i barely have uh one warm winter
clothing because
uh when the winter came i started to be
really busy with her
life so i didn't i didn't really uh
have time for shopping and going outside
and since i wasn't going outside i
didn't really have the need for
buying all those winter clothes anyway
and i don't want to buy too much stuff
right now because
it will just um my luggage will grow
bigger and bigger and bigger
actually and i wonder how many super
chats
uh there are to read
we can read a few we can try to read the
ones from uh
yesterday
right we're missing the ones from
uh only yesterday right bye emblem
but nothing from before that right
let me scroll let me scroll
buy a emblem actually i don't know if i
can do it did i read the rise at super
chat
i think i did
oh yes i did i read them in this voice
in in this voice i read them in this
voice i remember
i remember i was wide
[Music]
okay no actually i think i'm gonna
go man
once again i think i have to um
maybe tomorrow maybe i can have a
separate super chat
reading tomorrow
i'm gonna lay down again i think until
the collab
hmm
[Music]
okay ah sorry guys
sorry thank you everyone and thanks for
um
checking out the surprise that i had for
you the
new layout and stuff thank you so much
we will be using that from now on
i want to get a new opening screen too
but i don't know what to do and i
probably should commission someone for
it because
i can't do it myself i can't make
anything fancy for myself
ah thank you guys take care
thank you rest well thank you and get
some good restaurant thank you
thank you thank you thank you i love you
all thank you no white pianos
super cherry
ah okay guys in german
we say auf wiedersehen
bye
[Music]
bye guys see you
you