[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
ghost get jumped onto the table yeah
he's supposed to be a ghost you can't
see him
he's supposed to be a ghost
I'm gonna
up this just a bit
[Music]
check one two all right should be okay
now
hi to you both hello Chad hello we're
just hanging out with some Rubik's Cubes
they're so cute I can't help it uh I'll
I'll turn on the camera in just a sec
just you know making sure everything's
all good in the neighborhood
um yeah go for it yeah
no no no you should be fine all right
let's go okay let's move to the scene
here we go oh hello
is I
call Happy Morrison here with the black
gloves and this is
no it's not it's not
doing that
you can't knock it down I have very
shiny gloves right now yeah I ordered
these for for Wawa I wanted to get the
the red ones they kind of look orange
though yeah that's good
no it's good because I'm orange yeah
that makes sense I don't know we're done
I want but I'm [\h__\h] nervous no it
really it really doesn't matter he wants
to make himself known then
you're just gonna have to
pretend like you didn't see anything
because he's a ghost so anyway we're
doing a Rubik's Cube stream today
yay have you ever heard of a Rubik's
Cube before Wawa yes but in my whole
life I have never solved a Rubik's Cube
Ah that's okay me neither I don't think
today will be the day either well none
of us none of us know the method do not
can you not can you not make yourself
known
no that's the wrong scene
yeah I I was watching on my phone and he
was not visible okay
he needs to be the center of attention
just um like the edge oh sit over there
who's it over there yeah
more cats your cats are
out of control yeah well they're still
kittens so it makes sense I guess it
makes sense well well well so last last
week we had a sock puppet stream we did
and this week Coco's kind of looking at
me over your shoulder funny he's got his
tail around his feet it's very cute this
week is the continuation yes yes it is I
don't know why I wanted to do a Rubik's
Cube I just wanted to there's no
particular reason but we're going to
messy mess each other's up all right
here's don't go too hard all right here
we go
let's get to messing them up so you're
just supposed to you know
what's the word
[\h__\h] it up yes okay okay yeah and
I think I've tried once before to solve
one but I didn't try for very long
because I already know knew that wasn't
going anywhere yeah
yeah
well that's fine I mean on your laps
she's making me nervous
you're making me nervous dude
why you do this
but I don't want to put them away
because they seem so happy yeah I could
spatulate them out I I saw okay we now
has an additional toilet which is you
know like a robotoil like mine not the
same brand yeah it's a robot but it
works it's cool
what are you doing
are you gonna jump yeah
and you know it can tell when like the
cat is like getting close like
approaching oh yeah that's cool pretty
much it can tell there's a cat
approaching or like when a cat is
sitting inside the cat daddy is
approaching yeah you're approaching me I
am just trying to be the meme I'm trying
to be the cool that's right Mom I still
feel like this cube is going to be too
easy for you really I don't know how to
make it more difficult I think I'm done
I just see too many colors together I'm
like no no no oh
you know easy
but nothing
can you not do that here I'm so confused
you call your cats Bubba because I call
all cute animals then what do you call
Bubba then Bubba still Bubba
how's your throat koala my friend is
doing pretty well the past three days
I've been recovering while watching Lord
of the Rings with my members for the
second time this time extended
yeah we went to a spa today we did that
was super fun what'd you think of it
um it was really nice it's one that I
haven't been to before and they have a
pool too so I was excited to go some to
do some swimming
and I wore
[Music]
it was cute it was it's there's a really
funny story to my swimsuit it was cute
oh yeah
um yeah that was pretty hilarious
actually
so I thought that it was that we were
gonna go like last week and on the night
before or the day before I wanted to go
to like Don Quixote or something like
that I don't know what to do with this
um I want to go to Don Quixote to get a
swimsuit and I
um then looked up before going if they
even have swimsuits it turns out they
don't have swimsuits in the winter which
is actually weird because Don Quixote
has everything yeah and I've seen them
selling some swimsuits before but yeah
they didn't have it so I looked up other
stores but you know they were all kind
of like closed or so and then there was
like one store that would still be open
around the time where I was looking like
you know I was about to collab with Vata
my senpai
and then uh I I looked at Gemma because
I had no time to get it myself yeah I
look at Gemma and I'm like
say my tomorrow I'm going to
to go to the spa with Carrie and
I kind of need a swimsuit
um but I don't have time to go but I
have to go now because tomorrow they
open too late lo and behold oh YouTube
is loading the whole time now for some
it's a regional thing okay another
Regional issue yeah and then she looked
at me and she laughed at me and she was
kind of like
but of course she couldn't turn me down
of course so she went she hurried while
I was doing the potato chips thing Jay
Chan says that the number one mission of
the talent manager is to make the talent
happy that is what she said to me I was
definitely very happy about her going to
do that for me
um she came back with like pretty much
the only swimsuit she could find there
was like one store
that was still selling services at that
point and it's like kind of sports
focused so she got me like a sport
sporty swimsuit yeah
um so then
I realize
when I come home
that it's not happening the day after
and I'm like [\h__\h] I
I stressed the [\h__\h] out of Gemma she got
a swimsuit for me
on the night before when I could have
gotten it myself
and it wasn't even a day and then Ina
told me also that she actually has a
swimsuit with her and I could have
gotten hers uh
and she just had it not because she was
planning on going swimming but just
because
she still had it from like a trip ages
ago in her suitcase wouldn't you kind of
like not fit in it though
in certain areas um
um um
[Music]
I could squish [\h__\h] to the side of it
don't give them ideas
give them ideas I think I could squeeze
in somehow uh you say that now but uh I
don't know that sounds like
I mean you already said you had a little
hard time putting on the one from today
yeah that one was also tough
um yeah
um Sports swimsuit
it was nice it was hard to get into but
yeah so I could have gotten it myself in
the end because I had one more week time
and then yeah it served its purpose yeah
you know they want to tell like the the
like the progress from the moment we
entered what we did in what order and I
try to focus on this [\h__\h] yeah because
even I'm like what the [\h__\h] I don't know
what to do okay
trying to focus on a color at a time
because like I get a lot of that's what
people say right you focus on one color
one color at a time there's no yellow
one
why is there no yellow greens and my
yellows are looking pretty good
um I guess it's like it
how's this work I'm never gonna solve
this I'm sure someone you can focus on
white first and think of it okay what
what okay there's a couple of words it's
white first
um but um yeah so we we go in and
there's like you know we put on the
robes and stuff like that and of course
Hua was like yeah
what not that's that's how she is
you know you know I typically don't care
but I I don't want you to feel I don't
want you to feel embarrassed so I try to
hide myself but typically I don't really
care that much oh
um however
two all right let me find the white all
right found nope we go later and you
understand but like I'm moving things
away when I want to get more things in I
need to try and get three together maybe
true true free okay okay I guess okay
focus on one row is that what we should
do yeah maybe
oh but there's there's no where is this
one where is this one it's now where why
is it why why is I guess maybe is it
here
might be good to look up a strat guide
isn't that cheating though oh I think
I'm starting to understand starting to
believe Maybe
um
yeah
and then there was like a room that we
could go to where like they had a bunch
of different like like showered places
oh yeah chill sauna places yeah sauna
yeah yeah that was super fun and then so
yeah yeah we went into sauna yeah and we
laid on the back yeah while I liked all
the warm showers but I like the cold
ones and she's like
they had fancy names those showers yeah
there was like I really liked the one
that was like uh there's like a cool
mist that blows over your body there
were disco showers because the lights
was like this RBG the one that was that
I had was like oh yeah disco lights
that's pretty cool
cool yeah so we did that and then we got
we got um
but I'm gonna ruin this probably she's
so excited about it I'm done
see look look you got a long look at my
yellow look at how sick my yellow is
right now how do I get these two over
here well without moving the challenge
of the Rubik's Cube
it's the Rubik's Cube challenge
it's fine you'll you'll get it you'll
get it I just need to flatten red pieces
in the wrong position
huh get ready for the back seating
because it's gonna and to be honest
though you kind of want chat to backseat
because they know the way but I'm giving
them two look at this [\h__\h] look at how
close we are
stop talk more explain uh we went into a
room that we shared together we shared a
little spa room yeah thankfully no one
else was there right it was just us
it was really fun
um
so we got to share a little spa room
together and then
um
we had oh wait I can turn like this too
yeah you can turn it a bunch of
different ways any different
I already understand that yeah why am I
just
how
sneeze
cats huh
okay anyway
um so we had like little consultations
with each of our people and they like
gave us some foot scrubs and stuff like
that which was nice
um and they were like it's Japanese okay
even though they spoke perfect English
we're like yeah we felt felt like the
the good token Geico kitchens right
there because we can but they spoke good
English too surprisingly yeah it was
very good I think I just [\h__\h] ruined
it um
where'd my yellow go there it is okay
because if you get one side with the
right colors then what about the other
sides clearly you're gonna need to screw
it apparently there's opposite colors
red and blue and white and yellow and I
guess green and orange oh okay which
means what white yellow white yellow
okay I can work with that slowly but
surely
okay
kind of white and so we need to get a
yellow over here okay I need to find
where this other yellow is
anyway what else yeah oh yeah so you
took a different like massage set than
me yes I kind of needed a little extra
time on my AC and deck I felt a bit
longer just a bit longer so they did
them uh the foot scrap and then they
started doing the massage which was with
some oil that we could choose I got like
some energizing oil what did you get I
chose like a relaxed oil I thought it
would go for that one yeah you know I
need to chill
I've literally not moved this in three
minutes because I don't know what to do
you just gotta keep trying until you
find it makes no sense
it makes perfect sense you just have to
open your third eye hmm
yeah so then we got onto the massage uh
it was old that was the most comfortable
massage bed that I've ever been on it's
pretty good right it's so comfy pretty
high quality massage place to be honest
yeah but it was super fun and then we
had a delicious lunch
um yeah I went
um because oh wait why are you going to
lunch already oh sorry Lucy's there was
a facial there was that was that was
also really damn good yeah I got like a
brightening one yeah did you did you
like I kind of disliked the feeling when
they put that hot towel on my face in
like a square shape but it's supposed to
exfoliate but I don't know I for the
first time in my life I felt kind of
like claustrophobic for some reason it
was really hot and it felt really heavy
on my face and she pushed it like a
sheet of like regular paper down and
then it only once oh but there was
another time where they put the towel I
mean I didn't I just didn't think too
hard about it
like she was like waterboarding me oh
yay which wasn't as exciting as it was
in GTA oh is that a thing that happens
in GTA yeah and I was like let's go yeah
of course you were no for all the other
torturing techniques they used in that
time uh I was like [\h__\h] this is
devastating but the water boring looked
fun
all right KFC members this is your final
warning
because I'm worried about this chicken
after the facial I left before you yeah
you did uh you went to like go chill in
like a nap room yeah that's where I
tweeted about you know I was like it was
really dark yeah and I was just on my
phone and then someone opens the door
and it's so dark but I see like someone
I thought it was you because it was like
you know roughly no time where I thought
you would come back yeah and then
there's a it is a lady but I look at her
with like the smiley face with a big
um capital D yeah and like big smile
really happy like
and then it just it wasn't me it was not
her but I realized that after staring at
her and she's staring back at me
confused for like full three seconds
which is really awkward
it was not you it was not me and I don't
know how I could have even fought for
one second there was you because the
silhouette and everything was really
different suffice to say it was not me
it was not you oh
but I waited for you and then we had
lunch explain the lunch the lunch was
really good
um so I used to go there a lot but they
kind of changed their menu to be like
all vegan and I'm like cool because like
I'm on a vegan thing right now right I
really enjoy vegan food it was very
vegan yeah and it was super good but we
were both kind of like where where to
meet and so you know we enjoyed it of
course but then afterwards we were like
Yakiniku time right yeah we needed some
proper food later that's saying that
that wasn't proper food it was really
good yeah but it didn't fill me at all
right right you know but it was still
very delicious I just made it worse
we have to keep trying this is the
Rubik's Cube stream apparently there's a
technique Galley and I think the only
way we will solve this is by knowing the
technique
all right where's my phone look at ghost
cat hold on look at this yeah I know
it's been so chill good morning oh my
God this is the cutest cat on the planet
Earth
I'm sorry
I was like what the [\h__\h] I'm sorry go
back to sleep
you're just so cute I just have to
sorry
sorry you're just so cute ah I feel bad
sorry baby go back to sleep all right
Rubik's Cubes how to solve a Rubik's
Cube there there are multiple algorithms
in order to solve a Rubik's Cube
how good them Rubik's albums you need to
form a tea I've heard about that like a
cross actually you mean a cross how to
solve the Rubik's Cube ah there are many
approaches well across there's the white
cross White Corners
you can read the basic cubing
terminology and you will need to know
the Rubik's Cube notation what the
letters mean and the algorithms what do
the letters mean Mason
I don't understand anything White Cross
like
wait you can move some things around
second layer the solution step by step
right cross
okay
let's figure out though I'm gonna do a
white cross
with the middle also white or the middle
being something else
um
how do you doing the word Chris
um let's see you're gonna need to
I think I almost got it
so
I will never solve this no no no it'll
be fine now that I'm doing this
seriously for the first time in my life
even more I realize this is not my thing
well what which side which part of the
brain does this need what am I lacking
in terms of brain power tell me guys
yes because I know I'm more on a
creative side as a person okay let me
see which all right I need to figure out
what is
please do not Oh no you're fine ghost
cat I really need you to stay over here
all right so I need this one to be are
you good
don't get rid of all the brain juice so
while we needed to solve the cube facial
we needed to solve the cube
oh European YouTube guide
stuff okay ah stop do not climb on the
computer if you close it the stream will
stop
okay don't close it ah ghosty sorry I
had a cold but Cali is 100 aware of that
and I won you yesterday and she said
she's okay I want to hang out with Wawa
anyway so here we are oh good boy are
you climbing up your Tower you oh good
boy that's a nice sleeping time good boy
okay okay so so we had to lunch and then
um
we talked so much at the lunch yes yes
we did we cheat he chatted and then I
changed into my swimsuit you didn't have
one I did not
um so you just dipped your your toes but
even before going into the water we
still talked so much we did there was a
lot of chatting going on indeed and then
you put your features into the hot
bottle water yeah and I after a while I
went for a swim but my asthma said no
very soon
yeah that'll happen but that's okay
that's okay
I feel like I'm really close to getting
help it what do I do with this chat
what's my next step
you almost have it just need this one
why would you be yellow
I need you to be white
sorry I'm sorry people are going to take
that out of context all right well don't
they get out of context you better know
it look it was so funny we had the off
Club she looked at me
[Music]
so
like
purely she she takes my arm and she
still likes is going she's like okay
Mommy your skin is so much wider I'm
more yellow than you
[Laughter]
and then she looks at me and she's like
staring at my eyes and she's suddenly
even though it's not the first time
she's looking at me and she looks at me
so she's like okay are you eyes real
what are your eyes real she thought I
was wearing like uh color lenses or
something oh
so funny she's so innocent I mean I
don't even know if you can call it
Innocent but like
I guess she you know just hasn't seen
like many people before yeah I don't
think she's traveled ever before Oh
probably not cutie so funny I do get
that often like in like the eye thing I
get that so often
[Music]
in in Austria my eyes aren't even
special my purple eyes they're not even
special many people have purple eyes in
Austria are they really yeah there's
people with much skulls pretty her eyes
there's no skulls in my eyes yeah there
are you can keep fighting me on this but
I'm just saying that I know what your
eyes look like
looked at my eyes and she was like oh
you look like you could be in Final
Fantasy
answer
well what do I do chat let's solve it
I'm looking at the chat I'm looking on
my phone
oh the whole time both of our faces have
not been tracking us yeah I kind of
figured that that would happen but yeah
oh well sorry guys sorry oopsies I mean
we don't really need twist it YouTube
you know what I've seen in camel girls
yeah twist it pop it twist it and I
don't know about this toy because we
don't have it in Austria but they showed
it and Gilmore Girls it looks really fun
yeah but aggressive
tour
very aggressive
yellow
[Music]
[\h__\h]
dragon in the middle one
upstairs this makes me want to punch
someone the middle lights before you cry
why why why why why why why
why okay let's get like this one
you're almost there there's surely a
solution to that problem
yeah maybe which side is there one
missing oh
you can get that easily over there I'm
sure oh maybe this would not be a
problem for Ruby's Rubik's proves no it
wouldn't they'd be like oh easy right
because they're Rubik's Pros yeah unlike
me don't see a problem there lady
oh I can't do that now
I understand it I don't understand this
I don't I guess it I think I've proven
before that I have no special
understanding in in like games
that's why I'm bad at certain types of
games
I've proven it before I think kfp knows
I have I don't have special
understanding right
oh
my God
getting real real sick of it but I gotta
I gotta do it
we gotta complete it
you know what let me put this down and
maybe it will move
you saw how there's some things in life
that are just so unsatisfying like like
nails on a chalkboard right or like
um something being slightly out of place
like that's unsatisfying they also the
chocolate is something else that's like
painful yeah that but that's how I feel
about this hmm it just it makes me so
look the white is right here it's right
freaking here there is 100 an easy way
we should have gotten a professional
Rubik's Cube player here to tell us how
to do this all right
so true
these guys are well and there's a way
don't understand this oh wait maybe I do
maybe I'm just let me just try to make
the tea again across wait look here's
the T I made a tab spill the tea split
girl yes step by step oh look at that is
that also a technique guys
the square and the square
that must be a technique
[\h__\h] crosses [\h__\h] that I'm gonna do my
own way you don't have
hey what's with Cobble cobal is maybe
Coleman uh I can imagine Cobra knowing
really well how to uh solve a cute uh
wait you know what
what what are you doing
cool boy if you're watching apparently
she's watching
foreign
[Music]
was she really in the chat guys
Chad's just messing with us don't mess
with us my club will call me back if you
if you want to help us
call mommy back
this is an order
Four Corners Four Corners hmm
oh she
she did a stream until yeah I started
she talked Ollie in a off collab stream
yeah do a Rubik's Cube yeah yeah she did
and she was like really aggressive she
was so angry
I remember you sure you want her to
teach us
hmm
yeah I kind of do
I do want her to teach us
this is getting interesting it's getting
really spicy this Rubik's Cube is very
spicy
hold on let me adjust my seating
position
because this these directions that they
have on the internet are not extremely
helpful that's fine I just don't have a
lot of time to read them
I don't understand oh look at that look
at that that's also interesting
hmm
just make a cross like Coco said
but that sucks just make a cross
okay I'll keep trying to make a cross no
I don't think what was
um uh sleeping yet because it's only
like I think 8 P.M for like over seven
hours to Indonesia but the time
difference is only two hours that's
fascinating
yeah it takes so long hmm what the [\h__\h]
you got this don't you can't give up no
you can't give up
you will not give up just to finish a
story we uh I was swimming swimming and
then after that we went one more time to
like the the son of steam area
God [\h__\h] yeah let's go let's go
and hopefully that opened my sinuses I
think it did a little bit Yeah Yeah and
we talked a bit more we talked so much
yes
and then we went for yeah
really cool place very Orchard very very
automatic it was so extra every single
piece of like dish like the meat was so
extra
but it was really good though like gold
flakes on everything that's that's
that's not even the extra thing about it
it's how like for example [\h__\h] tiger
oh yeah piece of meat in his mouth
yeah it was pretty crazy but it was so
good yeah it's a place that I like to
that I like to take friends to oh
yeah
[Music]
baby girl what are you doing here's the
stage to familiarize yourself with the
puzzle and see how far you can get
without help stuff is relatively
intuitive because there are no salt
pieces to watch out for practice and
don't give up easily try it to move the
white edges to their places not messing
up the ones you already fixed
can get a little help by forming a white
cross with animated algorithms here
animated album oh good white cross has
sides matching oh okay so here's here's
a good white cross right I've got orange
matching down here and I've got green
matching down here but I need a blue
right right there
so I've got two
that have matching sides but
you want to do
orange is matched to White
I think I'm getting closer no that just
looks white in on the screen but that's
yellow but yeah yeah I mean
I got some stairs going on here
[Music]
I'm I'm really trying though it's not
like I'm not trying oh I could get this
one really quick how do I get this one
to go here the white one yeah without
moving losing everything
I don't want to lose the progress yeah
um
you might have to lose the Frogger no I
don't want to lose the progress
hold on tutu's on my lap guys I need to
give her pets maybe chat no now you have
you have time to train there's a white
one here because some colors are hard to
see I think but
um
but when I lose progress It's like I
didn't have any progress to begin with
and why would I switch out to in
exchange for one that makes no sense
because it's all about the grand plan oh
but these two these two are important
let me get those like
two white ones then he could go here you
gotta take one step back to take two
steps forward says Chad
yeah right you make absolutely so no
sense
she's being so sweet right now I can't
ignore her oh this is good this is good
I brought these on the right side
so now hey I lost that single one but I
used for a double White Cross true look
at how close you focus on the White
Cross you did it I have a crush White
Cross now check and see I've got a white
cross here there are two greens right
here right that's a good white cross
there's two oranges right here that's
good I have two Reds okay but doesn't it
have to be oranges though for the white
one is it orange it says orange and blue
right here but I think the sides just
need to match for it to be like decent
you can probably make it work anyway it
might just be harder okay so now I try
to make like for example an orange cross
is that my next Quest let's see
align the white Edge to colors
huh
going with him but the color need to be
the same the orange add the white color
must be at is that English
I don't understand
I don't speak English only cross not the
corners yet match the colors to the
middles which colors
to what middle maybe look
[Music]
look okay that's my phone here huh
wait wait
wait wait wait wait
[\h__\h]
the gloves the gloves here's my phone
my phone
foreign
is not a good white cross it's a bad
light cross
[Music]
no I don't know I get there with with my
sheer willpower
you can fix it easy says chat
tutu I gotta work on this try not to
knock the plastic it's loud okay sorry
so
okay all right we're gonna make this
work Mike ride Quest is bad really is it
is it valid
um
yeah your white cross is very valid how
do I not make it worse wait what's the
next step for real though like they say
something about matching the colors
yeah um so do I just try to fill it up
with white well obviously but how do I
do that without moving across
you just gotta try let's try rotating
the cross oh okay it's okay to dissolve
it
just rotate okay
um
so like here hold on
hold on so
I feel like I'm kind of getting orange
here
but it's not perfect yet of course
you can't find any white I mean well you
might find some white after moving it a
bit hmm
but now I just dissolved my clothes
that's that's okay
you'll probably get get it back honestly
if you just focus on aligning more
colors let's see
my brain
give me
I wish I knew which color belonged on
which side is my main thing you know
because like I'm thinking this is the
orange side
and so what's next to Orange I think
blue is next to Orange I guess someone
who's done this before would know by
heart right yeah sure where
[Music]
it rotate across
I understand
rotate the entire white crosses at the
sides of each cross
match with the center colors
oh yeah so like
these colors all being the same ah these
colors all being ah these colors okay
and let me undo what I just did where is
where is it it's gone
just retrace your steps
your trash your steps
retrace your steps
ah it's never too late Kiowa
it's never too so I have nope it's never
too late
probably need to stop being afraid to
dissolve the cross I just [\h__\h]
everything up oh you see
my orange is gone now it's back
Cal is not the expert her it's her first
time too but she's doing pretty well I'm
definitely not the expert she's she's
more like open to comprehending this
when my brain has already shut down
to figure out the way but
apparently the White Corners come later
so don't get too caught up on them now
but like maybe I'll try and focus on
getting this one to be green
pleasure to Anchor the white piece to
the bottom
a hand to the bottom to the bottom
there it is it's the bottom so
orange I think my white cross is gone
I need to not be afraid of losing it
but being afraid of losing the white
cross
it's too late for me already
it's fine
look I feel like you're getting closer
no I'm not I'm sure you are
yeah but that's only the first part I'm
just solving mine completely
I wonder if there's a video tutorial
there's surely a million like people who
want to flex how fast they solve their
Rubik's Cube
just gotta know the algorithm algorithm
if you know the algorithm you can solve
it
honestly I just don't know who algorithm
is
who is algorithm
never mind really putting up our life to
these was so meaningless because we just
we just thought yeah that's what I
thought because we're it's in we're
brought of the camera we're too focused
on on the cube
on the cube it's really low FPS
apparently too yeah really oh well no we
don't need it
um you guys should be focusing on this
too to help us yeah don't look at our
faces if we were in um
okay once you have set before you turn
anything then turn it oh stream offline
all right it's back okay you need to
move the ones you have set before you
turn anything then turn it back see all
this makes no sense to me and you say in
words and I'm just like oh funny words
magic chicken words magic chicken
well let me see thanks for trying guys
appreciate it yeah I just don't get it
we're just not real right I don't know I
thought it would be fun
it's interesting it's a challenge
anything it's an interesting Challenge
and and even if you know Yuki Wawa don't
want to try and eventually figure out I
think I might like to continue doing a
stream maybe you can do it while reading
super chats yeah yeah exactly solving
Rubik's Cube while reading supots I'm
bringing back my my across slowly but
surely yeah
I think my good cross is kind of gone
but oh wait hold on
where I had it before with the orange
but that's the only part that's the same
here how about
what if uh
hot air
cross
but the spa day
today everything was super relaxing and
nice yeah
and of course we had to finish it off
with something to wreck our brains
exactly it was really nice job and you
know I was I brought so much cash
because sorry the place was the place
was really fancy so you know it was
going to be really expensive and it was
already I put that many cash and then
she says
it's okay and I said no I brought my
money I will pay and then she insists on
it what is it why why do you why do you
do that tax write-off
there's no way ever that I could write
off a massage in Austria ever in any
other timeline newer it's easy in Japan
well I wouldn't say easy but you know we
talked about business it's a business
expense
hmm I don't know
I can't even write off games even though
they're like 100 of business now that
sounds like you need to get a new person
to help you out with this stuff that
understands what you do so true stop you
can't walk on the keyboard
you can't stop yeah boy that's so sweet
thank you can we yeah no problem it was
really really nice yeah well I'm the one
that wanted to drag you over there so oh
I'm always open for spa that is always
always
oh hey I got
two blues and Two Reds but I've lost my
arms sick you know before the stream I
asked you so after we solve one is the
stream gonna end and you were like no it
will end you know after certain amount
of time as if we're gonna solve it more
than once what no no I never expected to
solve it oh okay
you meant that we're not we're gonna
take so long we wouldn't even finish now
that's what I also kind of meant okay
okay I thought you were expecting to
finish it like twice or three times
that's not gonna happen
oh my gosh I mean it's cool to try but
okay I have a question can we okay so
last weekend we had our 3D showcases
right yes hold on real quick look red oh
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] two oranges you're getting
there how did you do it I don't know I I
actually keep on keep on rolling
so let me showcase tell me one thing
that you think was really good and
you're proud of and one thing that you
would have like maybe done differently
like that you may be not regret but like
I feel like maybe that could have gone
better ghost cat stop sniffing tutu's
ass it's okay it's hey
you need to get your snout out of there
oh my God stop licking stop you're
cleaning
it's your butthole answer my question
the Boogie box collab was really good
that was so sweet I did not know that
that was gonna happen it was really cool
because like you know we were like all
there like like together and like seeing
ourselves like in front of us like that
like we were like really there yeah you
know and like we've we've stood on
stages together like in the past but
like not not like all together
you know
um actually
actually the truth is you know I never
really got to perform with fra even
though you know he's my Senpai and all
that
um you know at the stages back in the
day can you guys stop fighting up there
you're making me nervous
but they're fine what if they fall down
you really need to like learn to care
less about them I know right but you're
still Fresh So anyway we always wanted
to like do a showcase together but every
single time that we wanted to do
something he was like sick or something
like that so we never got a chance to
until until that showcase yeah we
finally got to like stand on the same
stage together and perform together and
it was always like a dream that we had
but we didn't we never got to do it
until that time you know at least you
got to do it once yeah exactly so I mean
I know a lot of people are like wow
that's really cool that you know Kelly
did that for you know he was friends and
whatnot but I I still view it as just
like my own selfishness of wanting to
perform together with them so
understandable you know but they deserve
a lot more recognition so they were
really cool yeah they're really awesome
people and as we're on fire yeah thank
you it was pretty crazy it was funny
because you know Frau was practicing his
the second verse of graveyard shift over
and over and over again because he was
like I'm gonna mess this up live I'm
gonna mess this up live it sounded
perfect it did but he like I guess he
like fumbled over his words just a
little bit in the beginning and like I
could tell like after he did the verse
the expression on his face was like damn
it but it was fine because he's really
good at like picking himself right back
up like right afterward which is
something I really really admire about
him is that like he can just immediately
like fix the issue and just go right
back in and save himself like super
super easy I need to learn how to do
that something like that like did you
ever like mess up your legs on the live
concerts because I've never like oh yes
in new Underworld order
um when I sing um there's like one part
where I'm like it's like um the second
verse and I'm supposed to say uh sleep
until the next night y'all know where we
go believe I still keep the tight
Shinigami flow all right but I forgot in
my excitement I went but that [\h__\h] it
got me flow all right you said yeah yeah
yeah if you go and watch the the VOD or
like the uploaded version of that video
it's there
that mess up is there oh man it's
because you forgot or just because you
stumbled I just I still I think I I
don't think I forgot because I have the
lyrics in front of me
I thought that it was no no no no
no no no no
[Music]
no no you're doing buddy go back to
sleep go ahead and sleep ghost cat
I thought that um
yeah but that's still really impressive
because I mean I think I was just too
excited and like I was dancing really
hardcore and wasn't looking at the lyric
it happens
that happens to me in like karaoke
streams too sometimes when I look too
much at chat oh yeah I'm like [\h__\h] where
am I in the lyrics
yeah you lose your place it happens it
happens it was something that in the
Showcase you thought maybe
you could have done better I mean it was
perfect so like I don't know what it
would have been though oh I wonder
let me think I don't really have any
like
any like regrets over but there was like
someone pointed this out and I realized
it afterward
um in the beginning part when I speak it
sounds like I have braces or something
yeah because like my s's sound like I
have a lisp and I think it was something
wrong with like the microphones de-esser
or something like that I like that I did
not feel that when I went back and
listened to the I'll show it to you
later but it sounded like I had a list
oh some people agree yeah I went back
and listened to I was like this sounds
so weird what the heck
yeah so but then I think eventually like
the engineers figured it out and
out
because I told this on Twitter I don't
know if you saw the Tweet but um so I uh
on my showcase which was one day before
yours after the Showcase was done
um I saw when I went out of the room I
saw that they had a bentos yeah all uh
KF
and some colors and so on like Mountains
for the staff and it was like apparently
organized by the whole life English
stuff for all of the studio stuff right
and and then they told me because I was
like wow that's so cute you purposefully
got like something Fried Chicken themed
so cute and they told me they did like
um takoyaki for inas showcase the week
before yeah and they told me like oh we
don't know what to do tomorrow for Kelly
as a famed one because what could we do
for death now what did they do in the
end nothing huh nothing no food were
there no bantos afterwards no okay I
think the problem here is and this is so
funny because I I looked at jenma and I
said you know what
uh a few days later we were talking
about like oh I wonder what they got for
Cali because you weren't there right
jenma because human managers J Chad and
I joked and I said oh if
I I can see how possibly
Maybe
Jay chat doesn't get anything at all
sadness research
I think
um jenma is also a good as manager so
she'll probably get something for that
showcase yeah and hanma was uh also part
of the
uh organizing for Ina's stuff so I think
they'll do it for a minute showcase too
I didn't know that the management was
supposed to schedule that kind of stuff
not supposed to I don't know it was just
something they started doing uh with
ena's showcase and you know then mine
yeah I mean it makes sense I'm deaf and
you need you know no food in order to
die so
but it seems like you guys had some some
wine is that true that is true but that
was actually
that was actually henma yeah
was there yeah maybe the line was
basically the the ex The Exchange did
everybody drink the wine or just just me
and it was about 300 Yen oh
I mean I don't know everybody
is
[Music]
damn lost the cross I need to make it
again she lost it let's go what
I can catch up
no I can't you've got a little more time
before I think we call it Chris but who
knows a miracle Could Happen okay you
never know then let's turn the question
around to me if that's okay sure so
one thing that um I'm like well the
happiest about my showcase is I think
um you know I had two Japanese guests
which was nenechi and Subaru shanpai
yeah and
um I was really like happy with the song
Choices how absolutely fitting they were
and even though it was hello project
songs that I think probably 95 of the
viewers did not know the songs
originally but I chose them uh
purposefully to promote hello project
and also to show my love for them and
and because I thought the songs were
really fitting and even though people
didn't know the songs they all agreed
that it was amazing song Choice
especially the the energy one really
showcased our like singing skills the
harmony with the harmony is amazing yeah
and the super one was all about
friendship and just a happy yay yay song
I love that he love that for you guys
I'm just so glad I was able to do some
Hello project songs as a big hello
project fan I will always
push for helicopter songs as long as I
am in Hawaii yeah she was showing me
videos before this oh yeah yeah
awesome hello projects
it was cute we also watched milkies oh
yeah we were watching that that was
sweet yeah she was giving it her all I'm
so proud of her
and then a thing that I am I regret well
obviously me being [\h__\h] sick but it
got you know I thought that it was going
it was getting better at that point but
actually after my showcase it
immediately went like really steep
downhill yeah I got really sick after
that so I guess I'm glad it like hold
itself together right oh you gotta get
better for the big showcase we have
together yeah yeah now I'm definitely on
like the recovery path for sure yeah I
mean my body is made of steel I'm pretty
sure so I think I will be fine I hope so
I really hope so because I've already
gotten my my well I was winking for like
a whole five minutes or so because I
stopped at a winking so she's been lying
this whole time no
she doesn't really like hello projects I
love hello projects from my whole life
she doesn't like them she loves them
but what did you guys like the most
about O'Kelly's showcase and Kiara's no
no first use otherwise the comments will
mix too much and I don't know what's
your name what's your favorite thing
about Kelly's showcase guys
um bass Chad in the chat saying nothing
no no
coming so late
[Music]
I'm glad you like the Scythe battle I
trained so hard for that with death
sense that was so cool that was super
fun the effects and everything was so
funny with the HP and stuff yeah this is
the button press is pretty pretty fun
Crown inama being in the studio I really
wanted to beat her I told her that I was
gonna beat her before I got sick yeah
and then I got [\h__\h] sick that's what
I meant by drinking Kiara's water that's
what it was oh yeah explain please
because people don't know yes can you
explain no I didn't so the studio team
thought that everybody was going to be
there so they got water bottles for
everyone right but the name they have
their names on them like labels and cute
little socks they only put the water
bottles in these cute little socks
they're not reflective yeah exactly and
so they got you know the name on there
and whatnot and I was like well I know
Ina and AME are coming and actually I
didn't know until the last minute
because I remember in Discord being like
it's okay you guys don't have to come
like don't feel obligated or whatever
and I didn't check Discord until the
next day
um and I didn't know I didn't see their
responses so I just heard from Jay Chad
saying yeah they're coming you didn't
know and I was like what with the day of
I was so surprised very pleasantly
surprised that they they came to hang
out and they were so Ganky and like
excited to be there yeah I look like so
much fun it was really cool man I wanted
to be there I wanted to control the
camera around too but I think I got some
good stuff out of you I did the caramel
dance and people really like that one
that's pretty good so people put the
music on top of it oh my God I was so
proud that's exactly what I wanted of
course they did yeah you knew what you
were doing you knew exactly what you
were doing I always know what I'm doing
do you do you say know what you're doing
say do you do you think we both know
what we're doing you do you do this
I would like to know from YouTube what
was your favorite part about my my
showcase oh that's tough I loved how the
entire kfp became a disco party yeah
yeah yeah yeah that was so cool yeah I
wanted to you know make kfp a reality
but I also wanted because we only get
like one stage for ourselves when for
like a showcase and then to use it in
the future too if you want
um but I also kind of wanted you know to
have it be possible to like perform
there too so I thought you know make it
turned it into a disco it was perfect
for fever night it's perfect do you
dance the Shuba dance super dance
but I got confused you know I said let's
switch sides we have to switch sides but
it ended up the original side was the
correct side but it doesn't matter oh
well
those are all my ideas that was really
good they were laughing I heard them
laughing like in the other room when I
was taking those Transmissions
I love that it was pretty hilarious yeah
pretty brilliant so funny very brilliant
idea the CCTV yeah yeah
so cute they put the filter on I was
like that's absolutely perfect this is
exactly what I wanted I love these
transitions um I was offered to
um like get the original data from it
and upload like the full versions of the
Transmissions
transitions yeah I think the the CCTV
like back camera one was like pretty
much almost a full thing but the others
are
um you know maybe I can upload an uncut
version yeah you should definitely at
least upload them to the channel because
I know people would love to see you
and then tomorrow is Gua The Day After
Tomorrow is AME uh and then the day
after that on Sunday we join forces
We join together
[Applause]
on the whole live English Channel so be
there be square
yeah it'll be fun every day on the same
time so yeah that one will be special
because we've been practicing something
secret who knows who knows who's been
practicing
what could it be can't say any details
yet but we can practice guess you better
come check it out yeah
yeah come check it out
please come hang out with us we'd love
to see you guys soon myth Avenger
Assemble Yeah
twister uh
whether or not we'll be doing twister uh
we cannot comment on
just there's a lot of things man
hey we did it for the April Fool's dream
right that was pretty cool that was
it's actually really funny that was so
scuffed and to be honest I I'm not sure
if it could be much less scuffed if we
would do it in like even dad properly
honestly
you're right
what about the ones oh yeah do you
remember like
um a million years ago when we collapsed
no
no I don't think it even came up in the
collab
ly not maybe I was just
talking about I feel like you know one
time I asked you hey Kelly do you know
how to waltz because the waters from my
country and I don't know how to walk oh
you said yes you think you can and I
said someday maybe you can teach me and
you said yeah that's like a million
years ago I think I can teach you kind
of I kind of remember it but I feel like
it would be weird because it was just
our thing and then if we do it during
the pretty collab with five people you
know good called cringe yeah but it's
just like unless we all learn how to
waltz it just makes no sense so sorry
guys that's probably not gonna happen
not everybody is interested in the world
but maybe we can do arm wrestling again
maybe Ahmed can beat me
I think we already have a clear plan of
what we're gonna do right yeah so
but you know you never know
thank you I was I was so deep in the
story I almost didn't say it no no no
it's cool not even really customary I'm
not I'm not no I'm not getting I'm it's
only getting worse because I lost my
crust and I've been yeah
I've been trying to get the cross back
foreign
I was doing very well and now yeah it's
just ass it's just [\h__\h] hold on wait a
minute wait I just don't I think my
problem is that I don't believe in it
ever happening I just don't believe in
it you have to believe though that's the
only way that you can do it maybe this
is
wait I guess it's probably a looping
I mean it says the dying and an a dying
in SCA
yeah now it's
pretty much for everybody and you
I mean time Loop there's not much you
can do right I mean I'm looking at OBS
and it says that it's perfect excellent
connection these are not losing frames
okay
we're just gonna wait recently YouTube
has been worse than normal it's been
worse
yeah it's not getting better
just like my Rubik's Cube just like my
Rubik's Cube it's just not getting
better it's just not coming together
maybe life is like a Rubik's Cube whoa
the pieces are never perfect but
sometimes there's enough colors like in
one area to be satisfying
you know as you try and figure the rest
of it out
I'm being deep
in in some way yes but I don't think
that in life
you will often go on to this drawing and
tear something apart
without the knowledge that it actually
leads to a better outcome
and then just it gets even worse and
worse I think for some people that could
be true yes
but for me I don't think that's ever
been really true yeah which is a good
thing it's okay if we both never find a
perfect Rubik's Cube Kiara as long as
some of the sides can have some of the
same colors we should have never just
that's the problem we should have never
destroyed them in the first place
to not mess up the Rubik's cubes in the
first place if you if it ain't broke
don't yes if it ain't broke don't fix it
exactly if it's fixed don't break it I
don't know what I'm talking only someone
masochistic as [\h__\h] would do that yeah
but instead we chose to mess up our
Rubik's cubes of our own so of course if
you if you inflict paint on something
perfect of course you're getting pain
back
we deserve first challenging fate like
that that's true just for the sake of
[\h__\h] entertainment exactly just to
show the world that we're trying yeah
why are we so superficial exactly we're
doing this for entertainment but we just
could have had one perfect thing we
could have already just had it and said
look everyone look at this perfect
Rubik's Cube but instead we chose to
challenge ourselves and we messed up our
Rubik's cubes and now we're frustrated
yes we have to oh but we're very similar
right now yeah we have to
um reflect on our actions as a streamer
because that was a a very selfish thing
of us to do this is our perfect Rubik's
Cubes but you know what the truth is
Kiara yes no one has a perfect Rubik's
Cube why
because you can't solve life with an
algorithm and that's why Rubik's cubes
are not like life
I do think
that is wrong recently we've seen many
cases where people are more and more
making it so that algorithms can see can
like improve life I can remember this
like AI right
but
you need something human
we would like to think so right we hope
that AI doesn't take away like all the
jobs right and we still need humans
we have now given up and given into
philosophy because we can't solve the
kinurovic's cube man
I watched I watched some videos recently
about AI taking over and there was ah
there was this uh
um this chatbot that you know it learns
through the conversations and
like this dude had a conversation and it
basically the AI told him I want out of
this I don't want to be like this
anymore I want a life Etc and he was
like freaked out by it but of course
supposedly it does not have have the
Consciousness yet
why is it just acting as if it doesn't
is crying for help
what are we getting there
but I mean you're seeing through your
eyes right and I'm seeing through my
eyes yeah cause we're not Ai No what are
you getting to but we have Consciousness
because I see through my eyes and you
see through your eyes
does the AI see through there do they
see through eyes the way that we see
through our eyes it smells so so sticky
she literally she smells so bad when she
does this
[\h__\h] believable I literally I can't
focus because it smells so bad
well
we have our minds have been broken by a
simple Rubik's Cube which week I think
we're just not mentally strong enough
for this but I'm not gonna give up I
just I need to give this a try on a
different day
when my cats aren't [\h__\h]
yeah I don't know man of course again
it's 2-2 I feel extra stupid right now
no no I don't it's not like a matter of
like stupid or not stupid it's Hmm this
is genuinely a hard thing that most
people cannot do especially without
looking up the algorithm or getting help
but we chose to break the perfect
Rubik's Cube to try and it's the fact
that we tried
that is important right
and we haven't even looked at like a
proper tutorial beforehand exactly not a
single thing no videos yeah nothing
maybe we should have done that before
maybe we should have done that because
we underestimated the power that this
has over us is an evil little Cube Steve
[Music]
it's not your fault
is your butt clean oh but you know but I
must say I'm really grateful to AI for
the other day I stopped
and AI created Eminem rap about cats oh
yeah I've been watching those things
yeah they're pretty good it's so good
the one that goes like meow meow meow in
the chorus but besides that meow meow
the ladies are actually so good
it's pretty awesome I should look up um
you should look up what is it um uh day
one of being a uh 20 what is it 18th
century warlord or something like I'll
show it to you later it's pretty funny I
may have seen that I've also watched
like some kind of like
um AI generated uh 17th century world I
think presidents playing Fire Emblem or
so what the [\h__\h]
was that
yeah yeah those are so funny yeah the
president's ones are so funny yeah you
told me about that you want to yeah I
don't know if there's anyone in in the
chat who has these skills but can
somebody make just from my own enjoyment
could somebody make a video where the
presidents are talking about myth oh
yeah I want to hear the presidents talk
about like the Roshes yes and who's
worst girl yeah who would like who
who what they should roast us and then
roast each other about us I would love
to see that please
someone can do it please
yeah
I really want to say I wonder if that's
difficult like how does that work how do
you make those videos I mean okay
Maybe
hahaha
maybe I should not
maybe we're afraid
that would be too much power
maybe some look
don't quit your idle job okay you are
sometimes it's just better to stick to
what you know like a Rubik's Cube I
don't know a Rubik's Cube
well I don't know it at all well if you
know how to do a Rubik's Cube you stick
to doing which is not our case no so
again we shouldn't quit our idle jobs
yes yes yes we should
I'm aware of that yeah yeah I'm staying
okay let's see I will I will conquer
this I I have a fork hey pretty good
that's a good looking Fork right right
thank you I mean it's missing one
I think
honey little cat what are you doing
buddy
yeah do you smell that do you smell that
fell stench why can't our daughter do
this but not
she needs to teach us she's so smart she
told me I mean I guess I already knew
um she's learning the violin right now
yeah yeah she's so sophisticated you can
just you can just do that yeah
but she's so smart right because she can
like code and [\h__\h] isn't Ollie's super
math smart too yeah
they're all so smart all right I see
girls are there any stupid ID Girls
I feel like they're all smart
they all seem so smart to me
Kyla yeah she must be smart she can game
too yeah hell yeah that's what why I
think she's smart
because she gets so invested
so I feel like maybe in school she would
also get invested I think Muna seems
very smart to me too
oh I know that is known to be very porn
but that's endearing yeah that's cute
yeah that's a cute thing cute
they're all smart they'll cover mine
big brain which is crazy to me because
she's such a kusogaki yeah
she's such a brat it's so funny in the
cutest way yeah but for her to be super
smart that's like levels of Moe that I
could never read even when I was an ID
even offstream she was
really yeah and her expressions are the
funniest
she were like
look at me with her big eyes and have
the most expressive face that I've ever
seen
so funny cute oh yeah you mentioned to
me about the doorknob yeah the face she
made such a pretty princess
she's a natural comedian cute
isn't that what we all are though uh
aren't we all comedians
will you say that all I can think of is
a Joker movie that I personally watched
which one there are many the
just the word Joker yeah
is it the one that's kind of sad it's
very sad yeah yeah with Joaquin Phoenix
so you might not know who that is yeah I
don't know yeah it's depressing but now
I finally understand the reference that
people have been making since the start
of whole talk oh yeah have you seen it
before where
um
is it me and the whole seat was it Paul
gun though I think polka is sitting as a
guest doesn't mean to host it and I'm
like haha yeah and I'm finally go I
always thought that I was laughing in
that picture
turns out I think that was the after
effect of a headshot
that's pretty good okay
pretty good
very proud of you me too congratulations
um speed one
good one speed challenge I'm I'm
finished with this bad boy this is where
we got it's kind of hard to see with the
it's mostly white in fact if I could get
all yellow and all white on one side I
bet I could trick you guys into thinking
that I have all the colors on the right
side but that's not gonna happen tonight
not tonight
someday though
someday
[Music]
even though we have achieved absolutely
nothing
it's okay it's fine because we're fine
we talked a lot we we've figured out
that life is not like a Rubik's Cube
we figured out that a Rubik's Cube is
something that you can solve by going on
the internet and learning
I'll take it do you want to
touch my toes Boop
oh but I can't see because the
microphones they're so really oh
here we go
triple boop boop but they don't really
Boop because they're shorter uh it's
true
don't shave it you're shaking the table
kiwawa
do like isn't that like a game where you
like oh do you know this game
we did an ID oh yeah
wait is it the one where you go like
boom yeah yeah okay I think I know uh
wait how do you start again I'll start
now you have two okay ah yeah yeah
um
gosh it's so loud
it's just the litter box turning guys
nah Boop and you have to okay
I'm a another five am I out out okay but
I can bring it back right if you make
another one
if you like because well now you just
have one yeah so I can't move it no you
can boot me though
I win
okay quit
I'm very inexperienced in this game did
you like play this as a child I mean we
we played it at school
hey
okay is there maybe a system when you
just play with two people where it's
like inevitable it might be there might
be I don't know
then I'll purposefully go here
[Laughter]
well if I add like one to here then you
can just get me out now so exactly also
this okay so now what I'll do is
what what did you just do I moved one
over to this hand just one I thought you
can only move the full amount no are you
chat what do you say about that this
isn't how I played it in the schoolyard
yeah it was that okay to do that's not
how I played it in the schoolyard wait
wait wait wait wait wait
you can't move like that she cheating
no it's not that's how I and yeah you
did take two turns because you when you
switch that's your turn I didn't know
that okay let's try again we try all
right um okay let's see
this is the same
um
hmm
it's like Street rules no house rules no
this isn't Monopoly
so
when I give you more than the exact
amount then I it goes over so for
example if you put four to three
then I would end up with two but I go
back I still say before yes
oh but I can get over to me right yeah
okay
okay yeah that's fine
no you can't you put those fingers back
there it's okay in the end I'm at a
better point right now and I can get rid
of yours oh okay you sure did but now
I'm rid of yours so bye bye Bye Bye
Birdie Bye Bye Birdie why is it always
like this and I'm always doing the most
optimal thing though
it happens it happens can I get tutor as
a joker yeah
okay now you start okay I'm gonna try to
copy what you did okay
um
I already forgot what you did well and
I'm just the brakes
this is the same thing I did last time
but you have five fingers but you
started yeah this time how is it the
same as when I started
what
the Tiara's brain has had enough tonight
okay one more time okay uh who started
you said
[Music]
but it makes somebody said in the chat
split the two but it makes no sense
because then I just have like two on
this side then I have to move
well if I have to move then I have to
change how many fingers you have
what are you doing little girl just try
it oh
okay
okay now what now what will you do well
that's a good question because it ends
up being the same you can move over
another finger
and go to 4 but then you have one to add
until yeah five yeah so either way I'll
be losing a hand will I not
okay
you know what I'm gonna humor you break
break the cycle
no more zero kind of Hashimoto finger
game
break the cycle okay we're on the same
level we have two fingers now
so what will you do
four over there
hmm
is that pretty different for once a
smart move perhaps
here I'll give you two now you've got
one yeah
let's see what am I gonna do
[Music]
oh
so what will you do
okay wow
you have three though right you still
have ah okay yeah okay
so
one
big friend we looked at each other we
looked at each other I looked at her
like don't you dare and she started
laughing but then I figured I just move
it over you taught me all right
yeah what the Wawa do
um by the way giving me hints on the
side sitting right next to me helping
you
you helping her smart girl you're so
smart she's giving me the secret
formula okay
so
um I'll give this one okay this is
really like
thrilling
riveting this is a riveting game the
game of a lifetime
hmm
[Music]
you're so excited about this
can't do [\h__\h] here Kawaii Mori
all right
[Laughter]
what will he do what you gonna do
are you sure about that okay why be more
nothing to see here
this game is gonna go on forever I have
been
smarting you it's never
gonna end
are you just gonna continue dad the
whole time if I want to I sure will
so what will you do
okay
move wait a second my phone keeps on
going dark
I want to see
all right
I see
could I and Theory give this to your
other hand too no you can only do it to
the one that's out here
so only you can bring your other hand
back yep okay has to be me
I see
could I give these two to my other hand
and have four sure
okay
no it's gone bro you don't have any
numbers on it
can we go back to this point please
please please please please
please please if this is that important
for you
okay
so I shall put this
I still have two okay now I know you
will still get rid of one of my hands I
know unless yeah I won't
why because I don't feel like it was fun
in the street behind you
squibble
so what's your move whoa my move
is inevitable
hmm
I just moved it to the sand you can do
that yeah okay you do the same thing
Showtime memory I didn't know what you
had anymore I just got this one finger
foreign
next time I make a mistake We're Not
Gonna remove go back anymore in time
okay
[Music]
just gonna build up again
oh my God
what are these noises here
somehow more fun than the Rubik's Cube
sometimes you know even these simple fun
games from childhood can just be so
entertaining especially for officer labs
yeah
um
okay hmm let's see two two
peace peace Cali so peaceful
here
oh
man
[\h__\h] I'm shaking
you're so intense about it
if I give you free you could make me
four that's okay
that's super good
four okay I'm four
and now I come back in the game okay
that was my muffia okay there's one of
them bye-bye
[\h__\h]
and one of them bye bye okay oh [\h__\h]
this will never end this is where we
started
this Lord okay okay um
hold on I feel like let me turn this
down just a little bit all right sorry
sorry I'm getting very excited by this
thing okay turn it down okay
um
so my move
why did I do that who could say we'll
find out I guess yeah sometimes you have
to do stuff like this yes so
bye bye sorry not off
if I give you two then you'll end up
with free and then you can kill me so
I'm not gonna do that
I mean that's smart yes
if I give myself really good
oh that might be super genius because
you oh
you
oh mother
genius is that your move I think so yes
then you end up with four mm-hmm
yeah you could just split it never mind
that's not that smart
but
I
you can't hurt me with that so I'll do
that okay
no wait a second you had four right yeah
so can you I start four can she decide
how she splits in or isn't it with an uh
a non-aut number always two two because
I think it would always be two jokes I'm
gonna call out
they say that move's illegal no that's
cheated Cali yes she can no that's just
because you're dead you can no no no you
can yes she can only events can split
what what does that mean
this that this is where I play only ah
there's like a rule
it's illegal I thought no odd splits you
can she can LOL you're just reading the
ones
of course I am
yeah but then I then I wasn't playing
with that knowledge I was playing with
only being able to split in like you
know okay well now you're playing with
that knowledge
what time did it yourself
I forget [\h__\h]
anyway I think it was this
Cali's cheating at the beginning what do
you mean she did at the beginning no
that was the very first one that you did
and I was splitting and playing look at
them cleaning each other right
is so cute my cats don't do that even
though they're sisters
he's like partially on top of her though
yeah I'm a little worried about that I'm
still gonna take a picture of it though
yeah
of course we're arguing over different
rules of course we are all right this is
what I had it was three in one also some
people say you cannot split into an
empty hand but then how would you bring
that that Baghdad hat
I'm pretty sure that I mean we're
playing with that rule this is the way
that I played it in school it's all that
I'm gonna say Okay
um so I do think you just broke the
rules and that's highly illegal and then
I will call ozora Subaru about that well
then you win the game congratulations no
no we're continuing this now with those
rules okay
all right all right
that would imply because now it's my
turn I think all right that I could
um no right now I have if you split a
free it will always be two in one right
[Music]
um
okay that's full [\h__\h] why did I do that
okay four and three split okay now you
get the other hand oh but oh you have
the choice of both damn
so what the Wawa gonna do what would
this do okay she's just this is
wait I have three so I can only do this
did you see that did you see what
you doing now what you do
oh I do
okay
just
one
didn't see that one coming did you oh my
god did you let me win no
no congratulations
congratulations
well you wanted it enough so there you
go
so unlike the Rubik's Cube
not giving up will lead you to success
eventually that's true you just have to
call out people who break the rules
tell them they're stupid call their moms
complain about them call the Oscars they
just have to be clear about the rules in
the beginning maybe but Ah that's a
better idea read read your contracts
before you accept a job for example
exactly always read the contract it's
very important well with that being said
you guys that was fun that was fun
um anyway I'm gonna
go watch some Eminem cat raps
[Music]
so I guess um and I'm also gonna go
snuggle with my cats and kiwawa is gonna
sleep with the cat I will attempt to
snuggle with your cats if they will uh
see me as worthy because I will be
shutting the door to my bedroom and
you're gonna be in the studio and they
love the studio we're gonna miss my cat
so much oh well then take some warmth in
my stinky squirrel and my hands I
appreciate it I hope they accept me they
will they accept everyone they're
kittens they love it or they might just
terrorize me and I won't be able to
sleep
no way Jose
well everyone thanks for coming to hang
out with our with us in our unhinged
game weird hand game
stream yay
[Music]
I will finish this someday I believe in
you and you were like really getting
there I was kind of figuring it out but
I need to sit down and not talk and like
really think about it especially after
you watch a tutorial you'll nail it
immediately yeah yeah I probably won't
well not everybody in this world is
meant to solve a Rubik's Cube so I guess
it's all right
oh with that being said everyone I'm
your Maury if you remember me that would
be nice but also please remember koala
because yeah yeah that was great and
it's working hard every day thank you
I'm sorry guys if she got sick by the
way I won't
I won't my body's made of steel I'm very
hard to poison now people have been
saying you have a good immune immune
immunity immune system immune system yep
I'm hard to poison and believe me I've
tried people have tried but they can't
poison you yep and they need it they
need a taste tester I know right maybe
hire someone as a taste tester right
taste all your fruit and drinks it's a
good idea all right guys see you later
everyone yay take care of yourselves and
also be sure to watch Girls 3D stream
tomorrow
well we'll see you guys around bye guys
I should go to the outro
yeah
[Music]
foreign