[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
please
um
[Music]
my beloveds
okay
foreign
[Music]
still quiet what the [\h__\h] I'm like
screaming
I can raise my game
but the more I raise my game the more uh
the more
yeah bye
is the noise
I think the game doesn't even really do
anything
when I do it on the microphone
yeah I I was good because I'm so close
to the back of what I'm gonna break it
[Laughter]
uh all right
okay I put a gain on obs
um
oh did you hear my wish
did you at least hear my leash
[Music]
better okay
okay
yeah you heard it okay okay okay okay
[Music]
yeah for 2023 to be good to us me and
you you and me
um
hello
[Music]
happy birthday to you happy birthday in
your shoe happy birthday in your pants
too happy birthday to you
my crazy stories
you sure you wanna you wanna hear those
to hit
it
today I went to shibuyan
foreign
a while
[Music]
it's so exhausting
if I signed it will we people no
Shibuya from Persona 5 I guess
uh only wear the Box the first time in
it yeah or the second time or so but
oof it was so crowded it's always
crowded
um
but I I wanted to go shopping buy some
clothes
with a friend today
and a new friend and
[Music]
um we chose Shibuya I guess because in
Shibuya there's this building you may
know it it's called ichimaluku 109
uh the big shopping center it's kind of
narrow but pretty tall
there's like seven eight floors or so
um
and on every floor
you like walk around
and go to the stores and they're like
all kind of like
there's like three styles that you can
find there one
is
super cute frilly girly
like
like really cutesy cutesy cutesy Style
and one is gyaru kinda
somewhat I mean Japanese standards sexy
and the third one is like
kind of like
still a little bit girly but not as much
cutesy
um more like on the elegant side more
more Down to Earth but not as normal
still as maybe super normal clothes that
you would find in unicrows or or so yeah
it's those free types of clothes that
you will find at the ancient molecule
and it's
I think only girls clothes I don't
remember seeing men's clothes
I mean my voice sound strange I have a
different microphone I hate it when
people say that
and then I get really like worried about
it like what
foreign
I sound different to myself too but
that's how it is just
do be like that and took me like that
and also I'm still like I have this
horse voice and voice
um
it's getting better though I've I've
felt big improvements today
[Music]
because when I was out today
um not a single time
did I have to spit out something
hey
even though I only took it last night
that magical ancient
Asian medicine
hmm
only took it yesterday evening didn't
even take it today
oh my I will laptop suddenly going like
[Music]
I think I think a certain can be told me
already many times how to fix this I
think
I still haven't like yeah dead end can
you hear it
airplane laptop
the vacuum cleaner
oh man so [\h__\h] annoying I wanted to
buy a new microphone for traveling you
know
and I was looking for options
because I'm not happy with this Yeti
microphone
not happy with it at all with the sound
um but then you know and there were so
many choices and I just couldn't [\h__\h]
decide I wish there was a place where
you can actually test them out
like it's really important to hear right
and most of the reviews of microphones
that I can find like pretty much 95
percent
sometimes for certain microphones 100 of
the reviews on YouTube are by males
and it doesn't quite help me to hear
a man's voice
with a microphone that I want to use for
streaming you know what I mean
hmm
some of them allow you to send them back
yeah that's really annoying I'm like the
type that if I order something from
Amazon or so then even if it's if I'm
not happy with what comes out of it I
just I don't send it back
because it's too much of a bother
no other sampling
one should I can try who knows
Maybe
oh
but I think all the mice she has are
like proper like microphones not really
travel microphones because I'm what I'm
looking for is
not something too expensive because I
want to use it for traveling what if it
breaks or so something that I don't have
to like take too much care of
still sounds good
um but yeah
I think she only has like the Real Deals
hmm
anyway
have its own audience interface no it
doesn't have to no no
I was also thinking of buying that small
coleslaw
yeah the small one because they have a
big one and a small one the big one is
too big to bring it for traveling well I
want to bring a small one
for like using Echo and so on easily
and having audio go through that but
then I don't know I thought too much
about it both the microphone and the and
the goalie Solara I was like yeah I
don't know those you don't see you
I might be bonked no I see you
so we're gonna do that waxing stream of
moves you wanted to do back in Europe
um well the thing is that group of girls
they have like a schedule set already
and
it doesn't seem like they have time
for anything extra
and it was really hard for me to
get some time with them actually
um that karaoke thing was kind of
spontaneous but
uh
yeah I was like please please tell me a
date when I can meet you girls please
please please
five days later please please please
give me a date please please five days
later
um can I can I please have a date please
please please
when I can meet you girls please at
least Mommy because I haven't met her
yet
um so I don't think we could do the
waxing stream during this time no
unfortunately
there doesn't seem to be time for that
it's okay
maybe I'll just wax with with Cali
sometimes
um
also I think I said I'm gonna meet Ina
right but it turns out I'm not meeting
you know
sad
very sad I'm very sad about that
um
yeah that was exactly my reaction the
oof Emoji was exactly me
yeah
but I have a feeling we'll meet again
soon
anyway
you know my eyes are shaking because the
camera is like
somewhere else
should I can I bring you closer
oh well it's they shake like my my cat's
eyes
you see how my eyes are shaking
oh wait now it's not so bad but you know
some cats have this condition where
their eyes shake and I was really really
worried because my cats have that when I
first got them I was worried like
turns out some cats just have that and
it doesn't affect them at all
um
I shake sound
yeah you only really notice it when you
like focus on their eyes
some of my duty I was worried when I
noticed
yeah it's it's weird both both of them
have it
constantly 24 7.
no
anyway we're doing Super Chat reading
because I need to catch up I know I
originally said I want to dislike this
fire but I realized
it's not gonna get any better I have to
read those super chats first
uh as many as I can clear them out
and you guys like my Super Chat readings
anyway so
I guess you guys don't really mind
can we can chit chat
um
um and I want to tell you a little bit
of my plans as far as I'm allowed to
um tomorrow
uh I don't think I have time for a
stream tomorrow and if that is going to
be really really late
um
I'm switching
accommodations tomorrow
and then
uh going to
record something
at Kelly's place because
I have some deadlines to meet
and then I have a meeting with uh
someone
so that's my day for tomorrow it's kind
of a busy looking
foreign
just make sure you have some time for
yourself yeah well
I
whenever if I find time for myself I'll
have to use it to learn my [\h__\h]
dances
things to learn I'm so [\h__\h]
um
I know I haven't been streaming as much
of course but and it might look like to
the outside for you guys like I'm not
doing anything but that's absolutely not
true
I didn't even sleep that much I slept
six hours
and then got ready and went
you know I live quite far away from the
city center right now takes me quite a
long time so
um transportation takes a long time
too
um to go anywhere really maybe it will
be better once I change your
accommodation I'm not really sure like
how far it is from everything
um
yeah
so that's tomorrow
and and then
on Thursday
I'm I'm hanging out just like without
streaming with kanatan I think
to do karaoke and then in the evening I
think I can stream
uh currently I have nothing specific set
up for that day
maybe I can organize a spontaneous
and otherwise it'll be solo
[Music]
the sixth
on the sixth
uh I kept that day open still you know I
kept a couple days this week open hoping
that you know I am a senpai
I understand but I would you know
um
[Music]
let's just say the days are still open
so I might I'm gonna try to fill up day
six
uh with something else probably
um
so probably evening stream and then
during the day I'm gonna try to probably
learn my dances
take some time at least on that day
um
and then on the seventh
we have a corable but not on my channel
and not with whole life members but with
Ophelia and ukano where we're gonna fan
girl about hello project
yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
thank you Anno thank you
and it will be on Ophelia's Channel
and then on the 8th
we have a
of a corable with a Japanese
whole life member
so that's that
thank you what what's with tunic sugar
tunic you're loving it
oh you're welcome
it's really good I know
and then let me go a bit further to the
next week on the ninth
um on the ninth during the day
I have some work to do
in the studio and then in the
late evening
I have an off collab with another Japan
member
yes
Tuesday is mercury connect stream
mm-hmm
and then Wednesday 11th
and organized by yours truly
four people collab then I think you guys
will appreciate it
very much
with two Japanese members that I haven't
met before
oh
and
and Ian member
yeah
then on the 12th
it should be
just gonna say it
me and
chokosensei and merus senpai
yeah I asked them to have of collabo at
their place
um
probably I'm hoping we're gonna do like
some cooking thing spicy
yeah I haven't met them either so I'm
excited yeah I wanted to meet buff so I
thought why not you know do a triple oh
baby triple cause um they do a lot of
stuff together
um
and on the 13th I'm kind of busy have a
recording and I'm probably gonna use the
rest of the day to rest
and then 14 15th
I still have those days undecided
surprisingly
probably gonna stream solo and maybe
organize one more of collab
oh this is way ahead of time I plan a
lot of things ahead of time yeah
no I I definitely kept some days open on
purpose because I know I also have to
rest here and there and I still also
um need to
learn dances for [\h__\h] sake
me
I still have some Japanese members
um
like that you know we promise each other
to
to off collab or just meet
normally
um but we didn't decide on dates yet
some of them so maybe those will fill up
those empty days as well
and then the week after that is
really busy the week from the 16th
I am recording a lot of things
and
very busy
so yeah
Tony Izu at the moment it's like that
[Music]
um
you got this yeah
I'll be busy that week why are you busy
tell me Brandon what's your excuse you
have yet to turn
um
send in a notif notification of absence
Brendan Brandon where are you going I
didn't I didn't approve that
I didn't give you the stamp of approval
Brandon Brandon Brandon Brandon's son
[Music]
Brandon summer
where's the excuse
Brennan
family I didn't see that okay
what are we done it's a cruise
planning's in 2019 damn I guess I wasn't
around at that point yet okay okay
I guess that's all right
since 2019
damn
wow
doesn't it
foreign
right didn't you feel something's coming
you know I went to have lunch with janma
yesterday
every time every time I go eat with
General
I'm like shook it
orders she eats like for like she eats
um five times as much as I do
but she's like super slim
what the [\h__\h]
how does she do it
huh
don't expose her like
five times as much as me
maybe almost six times as much as me
my friend has that too
I have good metabolism too I think
pretty pretty decent but like what the
[\h__\h]
needs all the energy for work oh oh and
then for every single meal she orders
she adds
hot sauce and like spicy chili flakes
and everything all over she's like Nabi
in that regard
everything has to be extra extra spicy
and then last night you know I had a I
had we actually ordered because it got
really late and I I we ordered food we
ordered Curry
and you know I ordered the mildest mild
curry available
and then when we were eating I was like
oh this is a tiny tiny tiny bit spicy in
my throat
I was feeling it you know and I mean
that was that was still of course
totally like tolerable for me but I
definitely noticed it's a tiny bit spicy
okay and then I look at Gemma and I'm
like if you try this You're gonna laugh
at me
it's gonna make fun of me so she tried
and she laughed as I predicted because
it's absolutely nothing not even no it's
like negative spicy food
probably
foreign
I am too sensitive
but it's not like I couldn't eat it you
know
at all like totally no problem but still
just saying
[Music]
it was like a moment for me
that's for hot things
but yeah I can't eat hot food and spicy
foods
okay should we like start with something
and then tangent again later
today is
humidifier on I got the heater on
everything
[Music]
ready to go
pouring some more tea
it's a normal thing normal day at kfp
forgetting about super chatos
okay am I a ladder now because I'm like
leaning my
head on my hand
it could be
kissing the microphone what
links to some random Channel
eh
no what the [\h__\h] no at least what are
you saying oh wait you mean the one
before
hmm
link as well
oh okay the second link links to to a
chat to this chat
yeah okay that's because I
oh that's that's because I put it into
obs
oopsie
oops
laughs
okay hold on so what you got
what you got Horizon I've heard I've had
one complaint
s
even my laptop is mad I have one
complaint for not reading like five
Super chats
from some stream
which I find funny
which one
is it even in whole life this one's not
even in hold on lizer
because it's private
[Music]
it is wait which one is it before is
this one
huh I feel like I already went back to
this one before
wait a minute I didn't but where does
the part start where
um
where does the Twitter space Parts start
and where does the
equipment Channel called life
transference yes I know what are you
what
look at the timestamps oh
wait I think this is the wrong one
the one I'm looking at I think is wrong
it's not the part five which part is it
at least not on its own I would have to
probably like
um
you're piloting a drone in this world
not the fan
has weird noises I'm not yeah okay yeah
okay I'm outside yeah yeah this is
totally yeah it's very windy here yeah
yeah yeah
right after my car right before
Clubhouse
right after America right before
I have nothing in between there just a
wait never mind
okay I found it
okay let's look at the timestamps
um uh-huh so the ones on the 13th of
December
okay so basically
you just
you just wanted me to read those
because
your name is there twice
it's not even like a message from you
it's just the name twice
I see you two two times
thank you for the pinky oh there's I
mean there's a Gilmore Girls review
episode review so I do want to read that
even though
last time you said I don't have to read
it but I will read it because I'm I'm
curious
chemical girls episode four Max is cool
I like Luke more of course I mean
they're writing the characters so that
you will like Luke more
definitely
that is 100 on purpose
um
this episode's theme is dealing with
criticism Rose degrade yeah what the
[\h__\h] why is she gonna D like that's so
scary
it's probably because she was like
rebelling
sukis risotto I can relate after
applying for better jobs
after two years of streaming is it
easier to deal with critics boss and no
worries I'm enjoying the show the
writing is sharp the characters are
complex I can't even see things from
Emily's perspective sometimes oh yeah
yeah yeah I feel like Emily gets more
and more like interesting and likable
throughout the show I promise to stop
bugging you with the suit these rumors
have to season one okay okay
and but I don't mind reading them
um
what was I gonna say oh yeah critics
[Music]
do I
does it get easier
to deal with critics
um
I don't remember
how I
how badly I
felt about critics do you do you
two years ago hmm
I mean it always depends every now and
then there's always like
certain
critics which are which are more like
hater comments let's be real
that get to me
every now and then hit me in the right
spot
but I think it's just that two years ago
um
the amount of [\h__\h]
that I was getting was just so
overwhelming
there was like no way from for me to
even Escape it
and it was just so much so the sheer
amount of it
was just unbearable
so that's probably
the difference
it was really bad like it was about
everything it was about my voice it was
about my design it was about how I was
um having lots of technical problems was
about the microphone it was about how I
act in collaborations it was about
everything it and I was like trying my
best you know at everything and I read
like critic critic with critiques which
were more like hater comments because
they're not really nice
about literally everything
so
that was a tough time yeah
um
tough done it's like oh I there's some
things I can't do anything about other
things feels like it's just like you're
[\h__\h] on me because you want to
and other things
surely there's room for improvement I
agree on that too
but it's hard to do
it's hard
certain things are just engraved in your
personality or you know
it just says you can't just snip your
fingers and Bam everything is different
now
you know
well
what about their criticism I don't see
much of that I feel like
I feel like it's
most of the time it's either nice praise
and comments or really shitty hater
comments
there's rarely an in-between
honestly
hmm
it's true
I never thought about that but it's it
really is mostly like that
hmm
[Music]
establings
how do you say that it was right on the
internet
um
some people are worried about offending
you yeah yeah I understand that um
well look at one manabu how rude
they are to me
and I'm still not really offended most
of the time so don't worry
what was that oh my God
what did you say to me on Twitter the
other day that was like oh my God
I have to look it up
I need to expose you
what did you do this time let me tell
you
let me tell you
I'm telling you let me tell you
what was it oh
god wow I just saw that your quote
retweet of my
of my copious flag Eliminator
quote really hope this means we'll hear
less of Kiara being disgusting and
spitting flag them every stream it's
been so gross quote
[Laughter]
oh my God
foreign
my laptop is flying
I didn't I don't even know what it was
anymore
I think it was something positive to
that actually surprised me
well well well
see her next to an airport
it's like I'm super cut oh you know what
would be really disgusting if cow carrot
made a compilation of every time I spit
out like I'm
maybe mix in mix in some
sometimes when I blew my nose
ew ew ew
I don't I'm I'm not I I don't think I'm
asking you to do it I think you probably
shouldn't do it
probably
oh
Pro
of
oh yeah this not joining ritual maybe I
will be added to snot
it's the it's how you audition for snot
hmm yeah but
okay
[Music]
um
okay so that's I hope we are all happy
now we're all satisfied now no one can
um
sue me now
so let's go I don't think anyone decides
you character
about it but okay
I do want all super chats to be read
in general theory
but that was weird
just saying
pressuring and pushing
pointing out out of like a million
different
days free
I also wanted to be read our Ed so
greedy that crazy [\h__\h] [\h__\h] how dare
she
cares about nothing but money
[Music]
endless already following up on my
request thank you endless for the rest
of the chat
thank you I want to go to New Zealand
thank you Jake's the BET what's going on
why are you guys sending these readys
what's happening thank you Jake's the
best ever
who's Jake
is it you
I like your positivity about yourself
you're Jake
New Year's gift oh is it the red
envelopes
[Music]
you want to see where they filmed
damn I just have a general image of what
a Lord of the Rings of New Zealand being
beautiful
I can only offer green
that's beautiful too I like green
27 months you know that's really [\h__\h]
impressive
I'm tricking out of a love life Cup by
the way
exposing Gemma
she's not idle Master fan what the [\h__\h]
but you know today I might um I'm really
sorry but I'm I think I'll probably be
overlapping with two Lesson by stream
you guys are welcome to watch her stream
though but uh the the anniversary stream
um just wanted to say I was riding the
train
that was running
training
and then
there were no seats so I was standing in
front of someone
looking at my phone so I'm looking down
right
there
and then my eyes kind of wandered over
to the phone of the person right in
front of me
and what do I see
laughs
they were watching Thomas streams
and I'm like
you have it
I mean
uh
damn
um
foreign
[Music]
you know this doesn't come yeah this
doesn't exactly this doesn't happen in
Austria I don't just come across someone
watching some whole life members stream
randomly uh in Austria this this happens
because it's in Japan
so funny I was like a bit
I'm gonna pay more attention to people's
phones now and see what they're watching
I want to make more
um I want to see more
more of them when we see how how many of
them are watching whole life
during their transportation
time
stocks no
what are you why are you watching huh
let me see let me see
I did see
someone wearing a kfp hoodie
not today or yesterday or so
but recently
from more or less far away
out in the wild
um
I was shocked
is that the reason for your Tweet which
one
a wild chicken yes
has to be chained
brought back to work
on that okay Espino
good to know foreign
foreign
[Music]
chicken was trying to cross the street
maybe probably
my crazy 10 minutes no that was today
nothing to do with that
um
I should wear one too no one will ever
know
yesterday
I was like
um
it's
tangent stream guys this is yesterday I
was like uh let me and me and Gemma were
gonna go have lunch right
and
I I
really had to go shopping today because
until yesterday I didn't really have
anything really warm to wear besides
like like one thing maybe
um
and
but Gemma did borrow me
um
some fluffy pajamas
yeah
and
as I've been I've been sleeping with
those
and
I was gonna you know
just
wear the top of the mokomoku pajama
because it's warm and fluffy and I don't
have anything else to go for lunch and
then Gemma is like okay wow you're not
gonna change I'm like no this is the
only warm thing somewhat warm thing that
I have I'm gonna go with this
and then she brings out some cute
sweaters for me to wear
one of them one of them was a Wah in a
almost cat sweater
but I thought I can't wear this
so I this is for another one cute one of
like an anime big really cool
fashionable anime design on it
um
it was it fit pretty good it was really
cute really girly cute
no
taskar
kept me warm
10 size am I not the top is
close your ears
yeah I did it quietly for you
oh thank you super snake Mario you
received it
[Music]
it's my first time receiving any of the
emergency happier oh
new birthday mood let's go
let's clicked machine yeah
cuckoo
still not 100 you mean my my throat and
all that you're not 100 but today I
definitely that feels like a big
Improvement
um
yeah
it sounds like a big Improvement I was
able to spend the day with a friend out
without coughing out flag
and without having like lots of cops I
think I coughed once in
three hours
or four hours
hmm that's a pretty damn good ratio
my my
it's not it's still annoying me though
it's in the weird place
One Cop in four hours is fairly normal
um
it's very good
thanks for the snow update
you're welcome
we're Landing
are you hearing
it it got a little bit more quiet again
quiet now
welcome to Pokemon Airport
gate
a five zero is closing and
five minutes
passenger
[Music]
please head to the gate immediately
friend
just as clear as it normally ever
exactly
clear though sometimes
wait at me I need to get my flight I
know I'm gonna miss it ah I
missed
a flight
maybe two times in my life
and one time was really terrifying
because I was alone next time let's go
I wonder if I told the story before
when I was alone in Japan with my first
trip
um to Japan and was super young still
and you know money tight
very tight
and
I was
already on the way to the airport
yeah
oh wait they actually I missed two home
flights from Japan before
I think it was two
was it two or just one
it might have been two but the first one
you know was real traumatic because it
was my first trip to Japan I was alone I
was young
and I missed it I'm like
hey what the [\h__\h] what did I do now
[Music]
and then I had to borrow money
to get a new flight for the next day
because I think
um
I think I didn't have that much leeway
to stay much longer on such a last
minute flight
it was really expensive
back then price is very much more
expensive too than now there weren't
that many airlines
that route yet I guess and uh
no this was the return flight
hmm
numbers of light in the U.S once I had
to buy first class ticket then to Vegas
I have missed a flight yet damn
yeah yeah I've been on so many flights
so
it happens every once in a while but it
traumatized me so much that
um
recently in the past couple years it
hasn't happened in a long time
yeah
missed one fight in my life was a scary
but of course my parents to prepare for
an extra Weekend in Paris for me oh
go to Germany recently and they canceled
my return class because I missed a
connection flight on the way there it
well I mean
you wouldn't have be able to call it
anyway right
to catch it anyway right
if you would have been able somehow then
that sucks
that sucks if you like got a different
connection flight or so
had to drive home to LA from Canada
could you not have like gotten a
different one
oh we just go really early
when I have an international flight
outside of Europe
I go two hours early
if it's uh
flight
within Europe
um sometimes 1.5 hours early
1.5 even though even though
when I do that I still have so much time
a lot of
a lot of flights where I check in online
I only need to be there at like earliest
one hour before
even could be even more
kitty kitty but still just just in case
just in case yeah
okay
yeah
okay let's read some shots for [\h__\h]
sake oh my God
for my voice leaves me again
uh on it
where where am I continuing
I think I read the kind of the holotalk
ones
so maybe Christmas
okay okay
oh
sure
hi this is
Christmas
I'm not thinking that I'm finishing them
all today uh but let's try our best
shall we
okay
thank you for the Rainbow Oh I haven't
seen a rainbow in a while
beautiful I already forgot what color it
was
now I see it again oh rainbow has all
the colors
wow
well
happy to see you healthy again
even if you didn't leave us for that
long boss wait
spoiler right Ghana I wasn't really
healthy again
we assumed it was getting better but it
really wasn't much better I'm not sure I
can be here for the Stream So I wish you
a Merry Christmas in advance
thanks for this wonderful year and for
everything you gave us love utensil
right Ghana are you here
hello thank you
thank you so much Merry Christmas
delayed Merry Christmas to you hope you
had a nice Christmas you are here hey
thank you for giving me the RGB Super
Chat that's what we should call it
rgbing wait does RGB stand for rainbow
no red
green blue I know I know I know I know I
know I know it of course I know
I learned that
yeah yeah smarty pants
get out of here
get out of here somewhere smarty pins
rain Gibble
I'm not sitting comfortably let me
sorry
let me change some things here how about
how about
it's not about that oh
you know I use my extra extra
monitor yesterday right
and before that I went to go buy
went to go buy a little HDMI small HDMI
to Big HDMI cable for the laptop we're
taking off again yeah
foreign
[Music]
because
um
I forgot
the extra monitor in Korea you know
something it feels like something's in
my throat
hmm
foreign
[Music]
I'm not tasting it
on it
hello okay
and
okay
I forgot the monitor in Korea Okay so
bought something about that and and and
it was then sent to
it's not a good position for the camera
um job pen so that I can pick it up in
Japan at some point
and general gave it to me and she was
like here it is but it had no cable and
I'm like oh okay I guess I have to buy a
cable
so I go out buy a cable
a small HDMI to Big HDMI and then I then
I arrived
back and I'm I look at my my my stuff
and then I see
immediately
a cable in my suitcase
that I thought was normal HDMI to normal
HDMI that was going to use it in a hotel
room
to connect to the
TV
foreign
how did that get into my luggage I
didn't do it on purpose
yeah I have a spare now but when when do
I ever need it's probably too much
bigger Gmod for anything else
never
so then I say
the moment
the first in the first 10 seconds after
we got back I'm like
tell me we bought that cable for nothing
and she's like oh
but we didn't go out for nothing we only
got lunch and we also we got a different
cable than I needed to
me
take it away by your parents
oh you protected it
nice
good job good job
foreign
thank you so much
thank you
don't say gross
thank you very much and and happy New
Year
myself free thank you for the pinky
hi tencho it's early Christmas Payday
for me after whole talk yesterday I can
see that I'll talk is not just pause
possible but enough of the book oh
with all the enthusiasm for Idols maybe
yago's dream is not dead after all
yeah
I don't doing idle talk soon not on my
channel so that I have more freedom
on what to show and what to do
I'm planning on making a PowerPoint
presentation
I told the girls every one of us has to
do a PowerPoint presentation
on our favorite Idol group and we're
gonna we're gonna show it um on stream
every one of us is going to do a
presentation like in school they'll be
like hello
um
and um this is my PowerPoint
presentation
um about um
was founded in 1969 and yep under the
hello project roof stuff like that
laughs
yeah I have to make a PowerPoint
and Ophelia Channel
yeah today I'll talk about
um our project
please give me good grades
okay okay
Merry Christmas the only present I need
are you saying all you want for
Christmas is me
[Music]
right
that's what you're saying also
congratulations from one million before
blood yay
what million one million
score now
uh please guys you can stop listening to
four blocks and listen to my other new
ones to Sean covers thank you
foreign
one million oh next time I go to Korea I
need to sign up for 1 million dance
class
so one million Studio dance studio is so
popular
oh I gotta go into the beginners because
even like starting from the second level
I feel like it's already too high level
oh
oh I could teach no oh
you have to look at those
videos from them
no no I'm not on their level I'm not on
the teacher's level
no way
yeah I love liakim
I love her
I used to watch a lot of their videos
nowadays not anymore but Lia Kim was my
favorite teacher I loved her choreos so
much
hmm
they're so well known to
it's really good makes great corals
you hosted the dance class before
I guess so can I tell can I call myself
a dance instructor and choreographer now
it's like calling myself a game
journalist just because
i i rate games
like after I played them but it's just
you know
thank you Jacob
[Music]
your rating is better than Game Spot
ah shut up
you maybe not a game journalist I mean
you can actually beat the games and
everything
hmm thank you wow that's quite the
compliment because you guys always say
I'm [\h__\h] at games but you guys saying
I'm better than the game journalist
wow wow are you sure about that guys are
you sure that I deserve that kind of
compliment
who says that
you guys
that's what you think I can see inside
your brains
I know what you're thinking let me watch
me stream she's so [\h__\h]
sex I can do it better
[Music]
where's my makeup
take off makeup
you will see no difference
interestingly
I just want to take it off
okay while I'm doing that
uh GD you thank you for the pinky it's
past midnight here so merry Christmas
happy Chrissy so what'd you guys say in
Australia
to you my ocean can't be I never heard
that before glad that you've done it now
glory to give you thank you
thanks mate happy Chrissy
sometimes we call it that
hmm
[Music]
that's it's crikey
Chrissy
someone's name
that's funny happy
belated Christmas to you too
you know
you guys never have white Christmas huh
you guys will never know what it's like
to have a Hawaii semester
today
gonna see
but don't don't worry guys don't worry
Australians
even in Austria we used to have white
Christmas but nowadays not anymore so
although this year it did snow before
Christmas a lot
but I think on actual Christmas Day I
didn't pay attention but I think it
didn't it's not I'm actually not sure I
don't think I went outside
hmm
maybe it snowed in some places
I feel like maybe this year there were
maybe some white Christmases
I mean if you live in the very north of
course you had a white Christmas
very North or on a [\h__\h] Mountain but
like in more normal places things have
changed
um
[Music]
foreign
I'm streaming from an airport there's
um frequent takeoffs and landings please
excuse it
I know it's loud but
yeah I need you know what I need I need
a swimming background that's like an
airport with airplanes leaving and and
um arriving
just for when I'm traveling
so it's like in character with the
noises
looks at Eden exile
staring at Eden exile
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
it's like I don't want to finish my
Super Chat backlog right it doesn't feel
like I don't want to finish it
[Music]
certainly feels like
at least we're having a good time
nah
um yellow
um
is also meant to be finished
hmm
okay go next
that could thank you for the pinky here
comes another Gilmore Girls review
episode 6 of poor Rory that first
birthday party have you ever had to go
to an event that you didn't want to
I like that Emily is mellowing a bit
unless the show wouldn't have her
reflect on her actions look brought the
eyes so nice oh I don't remember this
episode
even after reading all of that whose
birthday party was it Maurice
let me remember this one
don't remember this one at all
because I enjoy reading the superchatos
but I also enjoy dragging him out
look at this plane just landed we're
gonna try to connect the tube to it
so that we can have the passengers leave
the [\h__\h] plane immediately
connecting connecting
please stay seated and and with your
seat belts buckled until
um it's come to a full stop and the seat
belt signs are off okay ignored ignore
the full stop just and when the seat
belt signs are off you little [\h__\h]
out
Alicia
plain delete
the chair doesn't have a seatbelt
you guys are telling me that
you guys don't have a chair with a seat
belt in front of your PC
you don't buckle your seatbelts when you
watch my streams
stick dangerous
Nino
it's dangerous have you seen what kind
of Adventures we've been going on
I've been going on some crazy ass
Adventures
how to sit
my bucket is enough for me yeah you look
comfy in your bucket
string for the Jet Plane don't know when
I'll be back again cause I'm streaming
on a Jet Plane
I don't know and I'll be back again
oh no
I hate to go
uh my backs are packed
ready to go I
hate to see you
walk out that door
was that the lyrics
I hate to like you up
I'm safe
goodbye
the Dawn is Breaking it's early morning
taxes waiting it's blowing us
ready I'm So Lonesome
I Could Die
so kiss me and smile for me
tell me that you wait for me
oh midnight you'll never
let me go
cause I'm living
on a laptop
it looks like it's taking off
oh babe
it's so loud
[Music]
this is a pretty song I love it you guys
cry so much about it and it makes me
feel like I shouldn't be saying it like
you know I would say it more often than
karaoke but you guys are always like
so I keep it out of my settlers set
lists most of the time
man for you guys so do you guys don't
have
flashbacks and [\h__\h]
I do it for you
okay
[Music]
thank you that code even though I don't
remember that but I'm glad you're
enjoying it and you're so into it like I
feel kind of bad for making you watch
this girly
teenager show
but I would say it's like better than
like iCarly this
at least I'm not making you watch
[\h__\h] iCarly
right make a grown grown ass
adult man watch iCarly
imagine imagine
how dare you
and then she's landing and Charlie was a
game
my Cali was awesome though this is
iCarly's for very mature audiences
iCarly is probably better oh you guys
suck
you guys are you guys have no taste you
always think you guys have better taste
but look at you look at you
look at you oh
oh
let's move on
for the pinky foreign
[Music]
and
hope you had a good Christmas
I'm sure you want to question our taste
okay well your tastes are only good in
that regard
s
it's a different category
I'm playing
you guys you guys are keeping track of
my Landings
as much as that Twitter account keeps or
kept track of Elon musk's private jet
plane
is this what this is
don't worry guys I will not ban you for
reporting when my laptop is landing when
it's taking off
I will not ban you guys no
I'm not like that
I mean it's obvious
public information because I'm streaming
it so
[Laughter]
[Music]
YouTube he can't touch me here he can't
touch me
shots fired I mean would be proud of me
hey okay
oh [\h__\h] Jenna was watching the stream
when I was talking about her what the
[\h__\h]
she's not here right now by the way
she's like somewhere outside I thought
she wasn't gonna be listening
and now now I think she's not listening
because I'm pretty sure she's occupied
or something
um
foreign
that's like honestly like fascinating to
me
I don't understand how she can eat so
much
I've met like people
like a lot of people
in my life surprisingly well and
I don't think I've
I mean I mean I've met some people who
eat a lot yeah but but
this much
yeah yeah maybe it's really it's like a
source of energy
yeah yeah
hi Fam thank you for the pinky Merry
Christmas wow glad you seem to have your
health back once more you guys are all
saying this in that in that those super
chats the Christmas super chats but was
I really that healthy seeming
did I seem that healthy
I mean
you jinxed it
maybe it did it get worse after that
again I don't know they were a lot
better than you when you were yeah yeah
yeah yeah
I don't think it got worse after that
not really
but it just didn't quite heal properly
for a while
thank you Tyson wait where was I didn't
read it all enjoy the time with Mama
Tony
and safe travels you've given us so many
great gifts this year I can only hope
our love is enough to repay if kfp is a
gift that keeps on giving
um
honestly Lucas few days every once in a
while I was feeling like I just want to
tweet out I love you kiss me or so
um
and I always stop myself but there were
many times where I was feeling very
grateful and sappy and just want you
guys to know when I stopped myself I
wanted to I didn't want to expand my
Twitter
um or be like be too dead and I guess I
was feeling a little bit too I didn't
want I want you guys to know but at the
same time I didn't want you guys to know
um
and I think of you
even outside of the streams like so you
know
I want to say thank you
no
[Music]
my jet is taking off
I think Elon isn't that one Elon is in
that one just so you know guys
don't track it
don't track this one
sensor sensor
[Music]
um
yeah
yeah I did my Twitter no no no no no no
I really should have bought Twitter man
when I had the chance when I when I had
my meeting with Twitter in their office
and I brought my my um
business suitcase thingy you know those
actin koffa style case with my
50 million bucks in it
yeah yeah I opened it up and I was like
so
and my briefcase and they were like hmm
so you're saying
you're buying us we're bonus money but
the one thing in return that you want
is for us to turn into Orange
and I said yes
um
then they turned me down because of the
orange
fifty five zero million
um
[\h__\h] man color discrimination
No Deal they could have had good amount
of money and
like good Administration
they may have gotten more money
but
they have shitty Administration out
anyway
Jim Tracy thank you for
um pinky but also wait I feel like I
didn't say enough to type it thank you
for the merry Christmas wishes I wish
you all the best too happy New Year as
well thank you so much for your kindness
and sweetness hmm thank you sure very
much hope you had a lovely Christmas
Administration
my Twitter overlay's still orange yo you
kept it
nice
sorry I'm just feeling very roasted
today
I feel like I got roasted by my
electrical heater at night
I'm in a roasty mood
and I have to let it out
foreign
you know no personal grievance or
anything and
you know
I see a Target and
it's a very easy target
can't help it so Jim Tracy thank you for
the pinky
I'll be at work during the streams and
I'll have to vote it but I just wanted
to say Merry Christmas Kiara and I'm
glad you're healthy in time for
Christmas and your Japan trip thanks for
everything you do boss yeah I hope I
hope I didn't get any of my family
members sick I don't think so thank God
I was kind of worried that
um because I read that bronchitis is
even like when you feel already better
can still
be
you know
what's the word transmitted to others
I didn't want to have my family members
go for this [\h__\h]
now that I did
yeah but they're fine how's brojo doing
that's a good question oh wait I I asked
him today how my cats are doing let me
see if he answered oh he says very good
they want to cuddle a lot of course
there
will look
they miss me
I demand photos
Casino
[Music]
does he smell like you no I don't think
so ah he said yes
thank you you guys know what that means
right
thank you soon
I miss my babies
I'm glad they want to color with him
though I want to ask
if they're sleeping in bed with him yet
or not because last time he took care of
them when I was in Italy they didn't do
it apparently even though he was
sleeping in my bed
they didn't join him
they were probably like sleeping in my
closet in my clothes you know I wonder
if they're doing it now
[Music]
um
Target
uh
fluffy yeah
he's like online right now
oh yeah thank you Jim Tracy for your
sweet sweet words
uh yeah for my Japan trip thank God I
was like in somewhat okay condition
the super work now oh yes for jazz
they're using Tracy merry Christmas
happy New Year
thank you
hi hello
[Music]
condo
um
foreign
at the end of his Super Chat says you
don't have to read the super chat but I
already read it at this point
well thank you so much
[Music]
foreign
that somehow makes me happy because that
means they don't do it with anyone you
know
they just sleep in bed with me because
I'm there
before I won't I want them to get along
with my brother
oh
um
[Music]
maybe they are sleeping he misunderstood
or I misunderstood
he says on the ah they do sleep with him
on the bed
[Music]
okay okay it seems they have adapted
their usual sleeping spots
is privately sleeping on the pillow next
to him
because she has
her favorite pillow
yeah yeah
right next to the you know the one I
sleep on
sweet
sweet sweet
they're not that loyal to you well I
mean
it's their usual spot and his family so
it's like
the same thing same thing
but but they they definitely miss the
way I pet them
and I cuddle them
there's a special way
I know the good spots I know
at what times they like it
and like what rhythm
um I love tea
I'm like TT oh
[Music]
you're so weird about your cats excuse
me hey this is
oh that good setting episode 11. oh
nice
are you just watching one episode per
day
how can you stamp yourself
oh are you have you already watched more
and you're just keeping the super chats
like
so it's not all at once
7 A.M good morning good night I guess
oh oh
the Apple creator person is taking off
right now
update the laptop tracker
take up take up
[Music]
ah Steve Jobs that's his name
it's not so important so I couldn't
remember
what you gonna do take away my Android
oh I remember uh or I thought of a new
holotalk speed quiz question I don't
know why I didn't have it in yet Android
or iPhone
I need to put it into the next speed
quiz
um
I want to put it in because it's quite
quite important
wait oh it
oh
when
it
for 11 years
I didn't know I guess I didn't know
because I'm not an Apple user oh I'm
very sorry
what
11 years
zipping on that rock well maybe I heard
about it back then but
you know
okay I'm gonna be honest it's just such
a
household name and and big important
presents
that I guess he was still alive in my
mind
even though I'm not even an Apple user
um
just assume that he's still alive
because
he should still be alive right
how old was he
he should still be alive probably
probably wasn't that old
20 what no way
nah
56 oh okay well that's I mean
I should still be alive yeah
at least it wasn't like too super super
super super young like 20.
it's already
I know about Michael Jackson
accomplished a lot um
that's right
[Music]
thank you for saying 40 is Young I said
it on about I say that about other
people
but whenever in roughly
[Music]
five thousand years when I turned 30.
I will not be thinking that's young for
myself only about other people
doesn't apply to me
uh don't hide hey have a son
um
maybe it's cold outside would you make
us feel warm someone make it home but
you give us a place to be is this all
all of this lyrics or just the first
part
we might not get presents but you smile
as a gift so maybe alone but you keep
this sounds like lyrics but you keep us
company
but just the first okay because the
every sentence is so short
oh oh oh oh oh oh you make Chris's
bright yellow thank you glad you're back
thank you too
[Music]
I honestly I wanted to stream much more
during Christmas like the whole December
yeah December and
um
well yeah most of December I I checked
my streaming hours in December I'm very
sad because I I really wanted December
to be hot
um
I was just getting started
wake me up
[Music]
and I said it before but I especially
wanted to stream a lot in December so
that I can be forgiven for not streaming
that regularly during my January Japan
trip
which is also why I've been feeling so
pressured
um but you know
no clip review stream
Oh you mean like uh
clips of 2022 I wasn't actually planning
on that but maybe I would have done it
spontaneously
[Music]
that was fun last year
um
already streaming a lot for being in
Japan thank you
I'm appreciate that well
um some some of the meanings like the
one tomorrow will not be streamed
so I'm sorry about that
but I'm trying my best to stream
in as many occasions as price possible
hmm
thank you
Merry Christmas
[Music]
celebrates Bay attention
for the pinky it's great to hear you
well again I want to say how cool it was
to see your Advent calendar idea go from
attention to such a huge part of this
year's celebrations thanks for bringing
some holiday spirit to us Merry
Christmas thank you yeah I'm really
proud of that one I think management
also appreciated it and liked it
um so
yeah
I'm proud of it I'm glad uh
I just stubbornly went through with it
I think you guys learned the lesson too
not underestimate what's possible
um
made December more fun I agree came in
clutches here I agree it's such a good
idea I agree
just wish I had it a little bit earlier
so that it could have gone over
management
um but if it would have gotten for
management it probably no hate on
management we probably wouldn't have
gotten so smooth gone so smoothly
because I think as I said before the
reason why the videos all came in
more or less on time
was probably because I was pushing for
it so hard
but I also gotta be honest so I didn't
like doing that I didn't like being in
that position so
imagine management always having to nag
us
again and again like hey hey we need
this deadline's over please uh
um because I felt like
I didn't want them to feel like look you
want to [\h__\h] annoying me I'm doing
her [\h__\h] favor and she's annoying me
so the deadline
foreign
but I wanted it to be our project you
know
I hope no one was annoyed by me I hope
they all saw it as a
nice together project for Christmas
season
[Music]
yeah
stressful position but very rewarding
um
there was a blast in me I'm very proud
of it very proud of it
yeah
hope we can do it again next year
oh oh oh oh who's taking off let me see
let me see oh it's Christina Aguilera
okay
Christina Aguilera is taking off she's
singing
[Music]
makes me so much stronger
thanks for making me
oh
doing a concert in the airplane she's
using the she's using the announcement
thingy the walkie-talkie thingy
you can barely hear her
man such a diva
love her
um
Brandon thank you for two pinkies you
don't have to read this out loud if
you've been reading for a while I
haven't been reading for a while but
I've got a lot to go so elevator quietly
okay
mm-hmm
your birthday's on Christmas
oh
oh where'd you go
where'd you go Brandon where'd you go
wait oh wait that's a cruise thing isn't
it
but didn't you planted since 2019 you're
saying I'm the one who inspired you hold
on that kind of doesn't line up does it
it doesn't
[Music]
hmm
oh
oh the Scotland trip oh
wait you're super chatting in USD does
that mean you went from the Americano
lands to Scottish lands
oh
your tooth exploded oh holy [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
wait did I hear about that before
when how where I feel like I heard about
it before Oh my God what what what what
maybe your truth exploded
oh tangent
[Music]
la
looking so crazy now
um
suddenly detonated around 10 oh an
airplane yeah okay I remember something
like that oh
[\h__\h] hell
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
that's that's that's like that's like
something you would hear like in the
news laughs
or like on on a YouTube like reporting
video or so
passengers 2 explodes 10
000 feet up in the air
feet or kilometers
oh take off let me see let me see uh
oh oh it's um
it's
James Corden he's leaving America James
it's James Gordon he's leaving America
because like they hate him so much and
he's being shipped off back to
um England
laughs
I know I know he's not wanted
oh man
I don't know I like I I like his content
and then but I've heard about all the
things
oh yeah I told you I'm a roasted chicken
today
thank you Brandon
you so considerate for not making me
read it but I guess it's only like a
tiny
tiny tiny help because there's so much
to read
um
and not only the wait staff thing
there's like other
instances and stories yeah yeah
interesting scenarios what what do you
mean I'm coming up with interesting
scenarios I'm looking at it it's
happening it's reality
looking for the top back soon
uh Flappy bully thank you for the rest
of the chat good timings Good Tidings to
you
my friend
Happy New Year
hiding so what does that even mean
tidying up
good cleaning
is that mean
tell me dates
news
well wishes
I feel like it could have been come
um like connected to how you clean up
your
um place
after New Year's
you know big cleaning
and they're wishing you good luck with
that
I guess not
oh
not Tidings typings yeah but this one's
written with the D
oh oh take off take off
oh it's
um
it's uh who is it this time
oh it's someone who I can't say
secret secret
someone's flying to Japan
right now
no no I'm thinking of someone
okay okay okay what oh yeah good timings
that's how far I got in the in the Super
Chat and festive greetings to you and
all of kfb
Santa really came through this year and
brought us a recovered Kiara right in
time for Christmas Eve can't stay though
they're dragging me off to church when
actually I need to worship my one and
only true goddess yeah this is your
church
[Music]
Christmas Christmas Eve I guess it
wasn't e for you yet
um how was it
what what's what's new in church huh
what did they preach about
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
Like a Prayer all right see it's
spinning it's spinning I knew that what
I had in my head was fitting to the
church Fame
on on your knees
I'm gonna take you there that's when I
realized this song is loot let's stop
singing it I'm gonna take you there
it was loose right
foreign foreign
that's the spirit like I like your
enthusiasm
and you're have to say
how are you so into it
utano good evening Uta no I'm I'm
thinking of going to your place for the
stream by the way
maybe you came with that right
make it an off guy on our side
[Music]
do you have
um
PowerPoint install
did it come with your Xbox
oh take off oh [\h__\h] your Xbox is being
shipped right now
this is a FedEx flight
taking off right now
you you have it on your [\h__\h] Xbox
yeah
PowerPoint comes with your Xbox because
you [\h__\h] have it just kidding I'm I'm
memeing right now with Donald I'm sorry
I'm sorry
why am I calling it with tunnel
Pandora I know which one I should call
you
I'm gonna call you panchang
panties
part time
I don't have PowerPoint on Xbox of
course you do
just look
I'm trying to get something out
um
it came
thank you
what's happy New Year in Korean
uh
Papago
Papa go
who's gonna be fast to chat or Papa
called Happy New Year I'm faster I'm
faster
[Music]
foreign
this year I will
really
learn Korean
I am sorry I didn't learn as much as I
wanted to
and promised
last year
I
really
I'm sorry
as my New Year's resolution
and
um
[Music]
foreign
okay
I'm really disappointed but the year
went by so fast you know
um I was like the past like two months
three months I was like oh [\h__\h] years
ending I really gotta I really gotta
start my Korean lessons now yummy then
two months before year ends oh I still
have two months I can still like go
pretty far into months
let's do it and then one love
it was like oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] it's ending
I [\h__\h] up and I'm getting sick [\h__\h]
but this year
I'll try my best I'll I'll take lessons
Okay then I can't run from it
and maybe instead of the one that I
wanted to do where I could schedule
lessons myself
freely maybe I'll just do something
that's on the same day same time every
week so then
I can't you know keep on delaying it you
know
um
first I thought it would be a good idea
to have like something flexible
but when it's flexible then you just
keep on moving it
ah
[Music]
foreign
eliminate stuff like them
Gemma yesterday was like kiwama you know
that legum is not pronounced plugum I'm
like
yes I know and you should know I know
okay
foreign
[Music]
let's go
Cruise bye
[Music]
sky sky is very busy right now because
the sky is carrying all the airplanes
now taking off from kiwama airport
was glad to say that your recovery is so
quick you're truly of Phoenix have a
wonderful trip in Japan and happy New
Year over there I thought I didn't even
have to revive though only once my my
tongue only revived I tried to explain
it to you guys some of you guys thought
it was a full Revival no no no no I
burnt my tongue it was on fire then it
burned to ashes in my mouth then I had a
[\h__\h] ton of Ashes In My Mouth which
tasted disgusting but I guess I didn't
really taste it because I didn't have a
tongue
um
and then I came back
yeah
so only the tongue revived
[Laughter]
don't speak too hard on it yeah
[Music]
this is Revival regeneration
isn't that the same thing kind of
depending on how you look at it
I guess regeneration is more like only
one part of your body
oh oh oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
it's taking off it's taking off
um that is
that chick
that Silicon Valley chick
going to
um
jails
hmm
just being shipped off right now
the one with the blood veils
we have in the tech in the streets
where we have a lot of flights in that
area today it's a coincidence
the blood test Jake
um
I feel sorry though because I think she
has a dog
and I think she's pregnant
hmm
Elizabeth Holmes yeah
doesn't she have a cute dog
man
oh she probably okay
I wanted to make a playground jerk
can can get pregnant with
okay
Elizabeth
what was her thing called
what is it called Paradise
with fair enough needle
no
if put fair enough needle in thumb can
get pregnant
laughs
what
um
oh my God Clara it's so early I'm koala
Now Phoenix graduation
that's my attention what do you mean
classic tension what do you mean
what
money
Noni
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
I
don't know
[Music]
what's up
okay
no problem why don't you say something
aren't you saying that you wanted me to
read some chats man thank you Skye
Shadow pencil thank you sure hey hey
wait there's a there's a couple non Reds
and pinks for a while now you know the
problem was just there were so many Reds
and pinks and I tend to start a tangent
because I feel like
I wanna you know give each Super Chat
the time it deserves and you know me
starting to tangent is kind of like a
gift to that person
like hey this is your personal tangent
just for you anyway
um
okay here I'm being stopped again and
the laptop is also being stopped
apparently
um
I feel like my flag gum is becoming less
and less you know solid
yeah
probably a good thing
I mean it never was a solid as a rock
you know of course not but uh I could
like feel it it
with my tongue
just so you know you know you need to
update you guys
when you guys know
um when I'm getting healthy and how it's
going how so you can estimate how much
longer until I'm back to normal
guys just want me to be healthy right
I'm keeping that in mind
yeah so Apple says Merry Christmas yeah
glad you're back and feeling better hope
you have a great Christmas and the rest
of the year too thank you
[Music]
um
pepper
be careful
and move
not get sick like me because otherwise
you're not gonna enjoy
your life for a really long time just
like me imagine imagine how disgusting
it would be
to be like me right now
and having to constantly no matter where
you are
spit something out
I actually got sick recently oh no
hopefully not as bad as me
it's just like me yeah
it's crossbody's natural thank you for
saying that
hmm catboy
really is
oh you could be in Japan yeah but sick
it's natural it's natural thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
for understanding
I'm just over sharing but you guys know
that's just me like I always share
everything I'm I'm that over Sheriff
it's my it's in my nature
it's me
he says
to me I'm exactly where I'm supposed to
be now I can sing this it's Disney
oh um thank you Ethel
soon
merry Christmas I'm seriously so glad
you're healthy can help with your best
I was not really healthy
but thank you we're getting there
a little bit more
so close
I can grasp it
so close to it
right there
I see it already
thank you unknown
I know I know
uh
probably missing the streams yeah but
we'll be back to normal also I guess
this Arc right now is good for you
you can fix your sleep schedule and
sleep like a normal person for a little
while
just a little while until I'm back in
Austria enjoy this
nice rhythm
enjoy it while you can live like a
normal person go outside when it's
bright you've got come back home in the
evening watch My Stream go to sleep
around midnight whoa what is this
20 nah it wasn't like that in 2020 I
streamed past midnight didn't I I really
don't remember that time but you guys
keep on telling me that back then I
streamed for the night did I really do
that
it's incredible
hmm
oh oh take off take off that's a 2022
leaving us you're kind of delayed what
the [\h__\h]
do I get a
a refund
2022 overstayed it's welcome
it's taking a delayed flight or I guess
it took a connection and already took
off somewhere else a while ago
and kiwawa airport is just a
connection
sorry um
that must be it
[Music]
wanted to hang around for a bit longer
understandable I I wouldn't have minded
I I wanted 2022 to stay around longer
I remember that one Super Chat reading
in the middle of the night wearing a
really loud sound that killed a lot of
our Instagrams oh yeah yeah yeah yeah I
remember that too that was when I turned
on like an echo through OBS I think
I think so
and you guys were like I was like I'm so
sorry and you guys were like thank you
thank you
thank you so much
Studio oh wait I know um
thank you for 2022 I struggle with
darkness and people
but empathy always helped me yeah people
suck understandable only chickens are
good especially sad Sparks that song
pulled me through so many dark moments
really potential wonderful yes hoping to
someday hit attention version of Rolling
Girl you mean the Vocaloid song
right
you probably needed that
does someone know yeah oh
oh I mean yeah that's that's possible
was it a difficult one if it was it was
probably very difficult
I don't remember like if I would hear it
I would definitely remember
I know a lot of the old Vocaloid songs
the new ones I don't know anyway
except the ones that like get covered a
lot bye
Hollow members
like I can keep up with new Deco songs
and like those uh
like king and queen
Sonu Atari
around there phony yeah yeah yeah so
those that get covered I I'm someone
able to keep up with
duck noises just when you hear me doing
that
just imagine a duck
Bad Apple
but that's more Toho
aren't you mixing something up there
love old Toho Arrangements
songs
you know what I heard
what I found really fascinating
you know
um who here has been to comica before in
their lives
probably less way less people than than
people who haven't gone
I wish never never know me
okay barely anyone okay then let me
explain so comic oh God a tangent what
am I doing
uh you know it's big right and it
happens in the same venue every year
twice they have this big venue they have
several halls and then they split the
halls and like when they assign the
tables to the circles
um the circles that sign up they have to
write what's like genre what their new
thing they're new like either book or CD
or whatever will be about
and oh here the tangent is taking off
the standard is taking off
yeah so that they can be put on a
fitting day and a fitting area
so for example back in the day
I remember when I used to go to Cancun
when I used to go to
brain and I used to go to come and get
back in a day like one area on one day
would be for Cancun one area and on one
day would be for Toho
one area and one day would be for Bokaro
and so on
yeah fgo and so on so it's really
organized yeah and especially Toho
always had for years and years and years
a huge presence
um
what does circle mean it's like you're
[Music]
um
your
your whatever your
what you call your thing
and maybe yeah a group name
um
yeah yeah
total always had the biggest
present and then
you know how uh comica was like I think
it didn't happen for one or two years
it was canceled several times because of
the sea thing
and now it's back right
and ever since it's been back I think
the first time it's been back was did
like 2020 to summer I think
I think that was the first time in this
bag number 100.
100 come again
um
[Music]
Chicago
who you call
was it 2021 winter oh okay
but so what I've heard uh it seems like
you know during that break when comica
wasn't happening is when whole life and
YouTubers and all that was booming right
so now that it's back
seems like they have been dedicating a
whole haul
for YouTubers
on one day
and that's just mind-blowing to me
I used to go to comicat and everything
was Toho and this and that and this and
that there were no YouTubers
well there was another thing V2 were
related then
the artists were drawing other things
and the musicians were making other
things
[Music]
foreign
yeah that's that's like what it makes
you really realize
that times are changing
and
one of the most popular things right now
I am part of it that's like another like
big mind-blowing explosion in my brain
moment
[Music]
I'm part of that
it is surreal
wow
yeah do you understand what I'm feeling
damn
it's so obvious
in especially Japan
in other countries as well of course in
conventions specifically you see how
times have changed
but in Japan it's like visible
everywhere
like when I was been riding the train
I see like advertisements from
certain
big YouTuber companies
on the like like train yeah
crazy
and then there's like a whole lot of
stuff and and convenience stores and
here and there and there and there
wow
foreign
is another one of those moments where
I'm like
this stuff is really big huh
pretty like mainstream even now in Japan
people who watch anime and who watch
streamers watch YouTubers
it's like equal
anyway go back to Super chats go go go
go go go go thank you Studio Rob
went on a big tangent there
is yours belongs to you I I give it to
you
I put your name on it Brazilian thank
you for the pinky here's a gift to you
to our wonderful Dental to celebrate her
recovery also I'd like to mention I got
a shiny Town flame what
the firebird Pokemon oh right as I saw
the stream reservation go up so I named
the Chihuahua was a lucky sign
and lucky you
never got one but I'm I don't care I
don't I'm gonna be honest I don't really
care about the Chinese
certain things I don't care about that
much because it makes no difference the
shinies were stronger than normal
Pokemon I would care
but yeah yeah
nice good for you though I'm happy for
you
foreign
[Music]
thank you very generous
ah you were lucky you got one colonel
yeah
foreign
because it feels like I've been waiting
for your date forever
foreign
that made me yawn
[Music]
um
not even forever it's just 24 days
an advent calendar
it's not even that much longer of a wait
foreign
[Music]
oh you rejoined thank you
thank you thank you
and what was I saying
oh oh please don't feel like obligated
or so
you feel like having financial troubles
but I appreciate the support Danka soon
hope you had some left over from the
bonus and were able to spoil yourself a
little bit because you deserve it after
working so hard for a whole year hmm
I hope next year or this year will be
good to you
thank you so much Mary delayed Christmas
and happy New Year
[Music]
thank you for the support
action 18.
thank you
Christmas album
well I mean
my Christmas album that you have to pay
for when you get all those Christmas
themed song covers for free
hmm
Shadow typhoon
Tigers Spirit Kim thank you
thank you for the pinky Merry Christmas
Canada first Christmas as a kfb member
and I have and happy I get to spend a
part of my Christmas watching you stream
thanks for everything you've done for
kfb and whole life we're truly grateful
hope you enjoyed this day with your
Nichols and family thank you
thank you soon yeah my Christmas was uh
quite all right I guess
I feel like it
went better than the previous year
and yeah it was nice
good food very much meat
has a lot of meat
Beef Wellington
stuff good stuff kinda missed my root
crowd
for me Christmas equals hot count we had
no hot coat
or block out
yeah
German tongue twister
where's the wood count
red
um
um cabbage thingy stuff with like um
like sometimes apples
oh maybe
um
I think apples sometimes they're in
there
it's kind of creamy
not really creamy Saucy I don't know
yeah red cabbage
um
soft
good stuff
very good with like a venison
probably
good morning egg
thank you
hell yeah
I but wait what do you even mean we've
cut off a clue so that is way too German
the word is way to German I'm sure
there's an Austrian word for that
because that sounds Soldier we don't use
Cruces what's that supposed to be
I don't remember what that was
it
canoodle
no wait
so basically are you asking me or or
what's what's cut off I've noted
what is that what is that even
oh
what do we call them in Austria
photographers
and we don't really do those much
I guess they're more like like Chris
Chris please
yeah I definitely prefer uh summer
summer clothes are in my camera is like
where the [\h__\h] is it come here come here
um
okay
[Music]
I need to get a little bit faster man
happy belated be late belated delayed
Christmas
thank you for a wonderful year hope you
had a good year
20223 will be even better for you
Dominique thank you for the thinking
my biggest respect for how you've
manager holding an advent calendar
you've done a great job and I have some
experience with projects right now we
did a tremendous job couldn't be more
proud and to everyone who helped out too
Merry Christmas thank you thanks for the
membership
thank you Dominic yeah yeah yeah you're
doing like some kfp projects right
thanks for taking care of those too
maybe 2023 you'll do some more maybe
you'll get some help maybe
maybe you can lay back a little bit
but maybe you're enjoying doing them I'm
just going to do more and more and more
thank you guys for all this weekend free
projects the fan projects from your side
I appreciate them you guys are so
thoughtful I was thinking of kiwawa just
like me for real for real I'm always
thinking of give me
just like me for real for real whoever
will for we will
I just turned into a phoenix drinking
five days ago oh
[Music]
oh was there something that you didn't
join like by the way
I remember like something like this
before thank you for two years of
happiness Daniel I can't even count how
many times your stream cheered me up and
made my day better you're the most
amazing boss anyone could ever ask for
I'll continue to support you forever
thank you forever really forever pinkie
promise
pinky promise
ubub
um
the other day
[Music]
you're so cute
can I read you our
chat log
so here the ship is taking off
person airplane
so we were discussing what to do
for our off the lamp
and then we decided on ditching a game
because you can do game anytime
and then
and then she said
yeah and it's it's too lonely to just do
collab one time and then end it there
and I said
Angel and then she says Kiana goddess
and sends me a choo choo emoji and I'm
like
I'm gonna fall in love
and then she says cute
and I post the Cali blush Emoji three
times
and suddenly she's like oh what about
the thumbnail I'm like
what do you mean about the thumbnails in
one week
you're already gonna decide it and he's
like hey
phone it was too fast and then she posts
the the Simpson uh Homer Simpson hiding
back into the going back into the
the
Hedge
give give
me
I need something I'm starting to dry out
yo and there is no genma to bring me
another one
don't get up you get myself
[Music]
I'll go
well Jamesy it's like living as a
sandwich
yeah you can you guys take care of the
uh like my my thing where I
my my flight
control center
thank you
foreign
[Music]
what happened
what did you do what'd you do a plane
crashed [\h__\h]
guys you're lucky it was a
AI controlled plane with AI robot
passengers because everything
this AI already at kiwawa airport almost
everything
there was
everything was by Ai No No human lives
were lost
for sure you know I used up one whole
um honey container
I wanted to open up a new one
but I couldn't so I'm using like a honey
stick thingy
or jenma has to open the container for
me actually though I'm leaving tomorrow
so I gotta get my own honey
I'm I'm so grown up they grow up so fast
no no I have to get my own money
trying to be like oh she grew up so fast
and I was like Wow watching Mario
leaving sad face and I'm like yeah sad
face
is
I don't know
post it
the reason I was staying here in the
first place was you know actually to
save some money
I'm too cheap and it was difficult
because like if I would look for hotels
after a couple days after New Year's and
there were it was a lot of choice but if
I would look for a hotel from the
beginning of when I arrived to the end
of when I'm leaving the choice was so
small
foreign
even though like I'm making a big mess
and kind of like
making Jen memo work I think she's
enjoying it me being here I think it
could be wrong but I think because
someone she was kind
of skanking on it and she realized I'm
leaving
I think
so okay
Emma
as opposed to s
make me work hard what the [\h__\h]
hey
I'm having a good time
best manager
like I'm even like borrowing her clothes
also I got like a new scarf today
and you know I kind of bought a scarf
that looks like Jen was scarf because
she's been carrying around this scarf
that I thought looked really soft and
nice and fluffy and I found one
today that looks like that and I bought
it low-key influenced or high key
influences by Gemma
no it's kind of matching Now new stuff I
forgot to bring my scarf I have more
than enough scarves in Austria but this
one is different
this one's different
this one's very different it's not a
normal scarf
hmm
Gucci scarf no no no no
let's okay back to Super chats
[Music]
we're not getting so far today huh
um where was I
ah unknown thank you
soon
[Music]
Merry Christmas Daniel glad you're
healthy again Phoenix power my second
birthday next week I will keep a wish
for here hope everyone stay healthy and
get more happiness thank you your
birthday wish you're using it for
everyone else's Happiness and happiness
you're such a sweet chicken look at that
chicken I raised that chicken
look at that
so proud so well raised
thinks of the whole flock before
thinking of themselves
man
because I sat on you when you were an
egg
yeah
good memories
well well merry Christmas and happy New
Year to YouTube
[Music]
it's okay to think of yourself sometimes
though okay or very often to that's okay
I wouldn't say it's egoistic or anything
like that at all
people need to themselves first in most
cases oh maybe that's selfish to some
people I mean what the hell
especially if no one else thinks of you
then then you gotta think of you
no
well aren't you busy with two and
samples live concert
are you two window wing
ado
thank you I'm actually surprised
you have me on five percent volume lies
lies then you wouldn't be able to hear
me at all
you got me on at least 30 percent
but I'm honored
that I that you don't completely focus
on Thomas and far right now
I pick up some it seems like you're
picking everything up what I'm saying
not some
maybe I'm actually 50 right now
Simpson
no candy thank you soon
Roy slang what the [\h__\h] thank you
all right you got me
50 down played to five percent you can't
fool me
see that is the biggest proof that I'm
gonna lose it soon
okay I got you on 50 at least
oh
okay
I got you wrapped around my finger
no thanks for the pinky Ruiz Lang what
the [\h__\h] Merry Christmas to you too what
is that AR again
set set AR
what the
where's that from what was that from
said AR
en't you guys know surely
Argentina no ARS is Argentina no
that's AR
South Africa
South African rand
hmm
good that looks kind of new that or or
it's not new and we just never get that
but it looks kind of new
thanks for the pinky
oh it's kind of like
a pinky is like 350 yen
[Music]
yeah
so sorry a cheap one
[Music]
economy be like
damn
don't tell the VPN people don't tell the
VPN people
only the people with that currency
should be using it
don't tell them
I just did
they should be using it because they
live with that economy okay
foreign
[Music]
I don't know I don't have that
issue that much anymore I think I mean
it was never really a big issue you know
never really was a big issue but
I think it's only fair
um
where was I here Crimson DX nagashun FBI
unusual incidence unit
as the hell Colleen I reacted to that
before
can I give you guys a recommendation
so there's this uh famous song old song
that got covered by this group that was
mentioned in that Super Chat
um did I really love so much
I sure
I love the music video too this is like
11 years old but the song the original
song is even older here
I think my desktop audio is off right
because even if it was on it probably
wouldn't even be working
[Music]
it's so fun
I know the dance even
[Music]
is that Scott is that what you call
Scott
maybe Anna would like it I would like
this one wouldn't she
[Music]
thought
oh
oh it wasn't as bad as whole lies or
make it made it look now hold on
but didn't set up the conversion oh
and I misunderstood anyway this song is
great
listen to it
listen to it guys on the side
okay go back go back Phoenix
glad you're feeling better thanks for
your hard work in making this Christmas
special Halloween and wouldn't be the
same without your Miracles
you're just saying that because you're
biased hmm thank you I would like to
hope so I would like to have a
or special
meaning and purpose
in hollow life
English
but
I think I think I've come to be quite
proud of like my position
and
what I've like
done so far of course I would have liked
to accomplish even more things in this
time that I've spent here but
I think I'm pretty proud of
my activities here so far and
see myself as a full-fledged whole life
member who deserves to be
acknowledged and praised for my work
and
yeah
internet
oh
[Music]
my God
foreign
[Music]
I was just talking about a friend that
I'm sampling through genma's tea
assortment
she has a lot of different teeth and I'm
going through all of them
now I'm drinking orange herbs tea hello
hello
hmm
okay that was not obvious it must have
been YouTube
um
[Music]
okay
let's go let's go let's go
uh SPX was saying I don't think I read
this one yet Merry Christmas Tim Jones
today's my birthday Christmas Eve baby
here haha what your baby is here if you
feel up for it could you sing happy
birthday or how might if that's better
for you thanks for the amazing streams
as always thank you oh ah that's what
you mean you were a Christmas Eve baby
[Music]
okay that must have been like so nice
for your parents
I mean was it Maybe not maybe I'm like
romanticizing it too much but
he must have felt like it was a
Christmas present
um especially if they're like religious
or so
but yeah in terms of
presents
ah
I hope you got an extra amount of
presents every Christmas
um
because you deserve it every planet
deserves
Christmas for their birthday and their
and Christmas separately
your friends can come to your birthday
party oh well I mean you can you can I
don't think it's so uncommon or weird to
have your birthday party be close to the
day to the date but like as a on a day
that's like easier for everyone to come
to
I think I've done that before too
put it on on the weekend or so I think
that's not a big problem
but in figuring you're right yeah they
would never be able to come on the
actual day probably
foreign
[Music]
ah clapping sounds so loud in my ears I
don't want to clap
happy birthday
hope you got presents
for me
my present is that you're here it hits
happy as [\h__\h]
thank you soon for your support
wish you a lovely Year with much success
may your dreams come true
thank you I'm gonna answer in English
then because in German doesn't seem to
be your first language
hmm I see I love levakism
best snack that's Austrian snack but I
like the normal one I don't like eating
the horse one and it's a horse version
of it and no
I just generally like for me every meat
that's not like chicken some other birds
and beef and pork
is to me kind of like
I feel weird about eating it
yeah well we have we have like a stack
thing like eating horse meat is not in
general not that common here I would say
I don't see it much but what I do see is
liver cancer
made with horse meat but they also make
it look different meat I always do the
one with different Meats but some places
do it with horse meat I just feel like
it's kind of weird I don't know
but my oscar is not the only place that
eats horses I think a lot of places
Japan too they do um raw of course
basashi it's called basashi
I tried it before it's like really fancy
and expensive
you know
um
did it taste good
and I didn't really like it
because I don't know it was hard to chew
even though it was really high quality
but it felt really hard to chew and
um
I felt so weird out to be eating it
anyway
[Music]
it was very tough yeah I was like the
thing is I was there with some other
people and I was kind of being
recorded
eating it and
I felt very pressured but uh
but you know I'm chewing chewing chewing
chewing chewing chewing chewing I don't
want to force myself to
um swallow while it's still like so
big like scared of choking so
uh
I didn't like that experience
not high quality will cause a sickness
oh
no no that was the first and probably
the last time
that I ate horse meat
I mean
I don't judge people who eat it
um I just hope that
I don't know let the horses get treated
well
um
but if it's about that then I should
probably become vegetarian
it's always so traumatizing I'm gonna be
honest it's so traumatizing to see like
how some cows and pigs and chickens and
all that get traded it breaks my heart
where's my [\h__\h] heart
I at least
the thing I can do to help is buy
um
organic
products
like here we have in Austria we have
like a seal for
um
products in the supermarket
I choose the wrong profession
um that proves that they have been like
treated better
um
okay if we definitely free range
yeah
there's something here called Vanda Hoon
the the
traveling chicken
I think what they do is they let the
chicken
travel
around the world around the world so
that it sees a little bit of the world
before it gets eaten isn't that
beautiful okay it's probably it doesn't
see that much of the world
but no it's I think it's different from
free roaming because we have a different
word for that let me let me see what is
a Vander Hoon
wonderful
[Music]
okay maybe it's just that they have a
really really really big
ger than free-range chicken area
they don't get to travel
[Laughter]
okay I guess that was too good to be
true
I mean I didn't think they would travel
countries just like maybe
from
I don't know
some some stall to another store like an
exchange program or so that would be
nice
I don't know man I just want you guys to
see some of the world
like how I want my cats to see more of
the world and not to stay in that
apartment for their whole life you know
that's [\h__\h] depressing think about it
you love your cat or your dog or so so
much but I guess a dog at least you take
out for a walk but a cat a cat
chicken Exchange program dakama already
drawing something right now
but yeah I feel so so sad about it
because like they get to see a little
bit of the world through the window but
don't you think they're like wondering
like
I wonder how I wanna know why yesterday
you told me about the blue blue sky but
all that I can see it's just straight
out of lemon tree
and I wonder I wonder if there is fish
if there's chicks that I can take a
little nap
I don't know that I can see it's just
this [\h__\h] window
and I'm yum yum yum yum
yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
yum yum yum yum yum
meow meow meow meow
isolation this is really sung by a cat
don't you think
isolation
is not good for me
ah he's so Nation I wanna go out and
break free
meow meow meow
I wanna go out and meet other cats don't
put me on a leash I'm not a [\h__\h] dog
no and I want no one I'm a free cat I
wanna go the world is my toilet and I'm
Gonna Roll and all that I can see it's
just a [\h__\h] window give me the cat
treats cat treats
yeah
beautiful
foreign
I want my cat to see a little bit more
than just the apartment before
before they you know
go somewhere else
okay let's go let's go switch that Mr
empty block thank you soon
Merry Christmas attention gave me so
much great content from our buzzword as
always even spur of the moment ideas
like that advent calendar of Epic
achievements once she coordinates and
management manages them illness
soundboards illness sideboards cannot be
stopped according to kfp thank you if I
wouldn't have been sick I probably would
have also organized some kind of or
tried to organize some kind of New
Year's Event or so
hmm
Maybe karaoke or so although if I would
have done that we probably wouldn't have
had many participants this year people
traveling and so on
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
maybe next year more girls will be
around
and not everyone will be sick or
somewhere else
[Music]
Cali finished did she finish the game
though or just a stream
did she do it
[Music]
she finished did she do like did she go
even further than me or did she ended
like around where I ended it
she did it let's go
damn because she didn't expect ever that
it would be that long
she stopped right after the crabs oh
okay okay okay
[Music]
um
thank you
not the entire post game wait did I do
post game
what is post game
I didn't do it ever
okay
in sync
just like me for real for real she's
just like me for my Gloria
foreign
[Music]
I'm glad you're feeling happy and
carefree I hope that will stay like that
I will continue trying to deliver good
content
for you and all the other chickens all
my beautiful chickens
thank you guys for a great year by the
way
um
copy
zero no no
questions
Hey kid
no one calls me kid I'm an adult excuse
me Merry Christmas Merry Christmas to
you too so glad you're doing much better
now don't feel ever upset feeling you'll
disappoint us
your driving education is why I Will
Always Love You best wishes for you and
your friends and family in the new year
much love thank you to you too would you
say that
and you
you will always
love me
[Music]
thank you wow it's so nice of you to
sing such a beautiful song dedicated to
me
thank you I have a song for every word
yes I do
thank you forever Hall
thank you oh from Canada Oh Canada Oh
Canada how beautiful are your maple
leaves
tripping with the maple syrup dropping
on the pancakes Oh Canada Oh Canada a
beautiful all your maple leaves
hmm
for an evergreen nugget shown Anthony
web danger zone thank you for the red
super chat
that's how the anthem goes doesn't it
yeah yeah yeah I heard it before they
sang another opening ceremony of the
Olympics hmm
Merry Christmas I'm glad you feel better
and you will always have a chicken
thank you
I'm very proud to have you guys really
I'm so proud love kfp love love so much
be
oh look at you guys
so strong I feel like every chicken
every single chicken
counts as much as three people from
other fan bases
which
is necessary anyway if you wanna you
know be on the same height because you
gotta become chicken totem pole
put a coat on yourselves
to not stand out and look too too small
you gotta like assert your dominance
right I feel like kfp has to assert
dominance that's why
one chicken makes up for like free
from other fan bases
because they're all tall
and red but chickens yeah small But
Mighty hell yeah
this is is
the chickens are taking off we're ready
to fly
you always worry I always believed in
you guys
I'm so proud
again
thank you Anthony
I'm counting on you in 2023 all right
sis
you how do you read that thank you
chicken nuggets
[Music]
I work thank you for the red Chan merry
Christmas happy holidays Kiana and kfp
hope you all have a great time and will
come good and healthy into the new year
yeah well I slept
so I can't believe I slept through it oh
man
it's kind of lame
kind of lame but if it was Austria I
would have enjoyed uh fireworks I gotta
say you know there's not really much to
enjoy here at midnight
hmm
I mean except I guess the whole live
concert
did you guys when you guys watching the
whole live stream hmm
the New Year's one the countdown there
was a countdown I recorded like some
lines for it too
and
some singing and dancing
[Music]
I never watched the final version I
didn't watch the archive
man
foreign
I didn't even know that people were
gonna change outfits
[\h__\h]
I'm not gonna lie I would have loved
to do the switcheroo too
hmm
me
I wanted to do a switcher YouTube
some of them look really funny really
cool this is really uncanny
do I use it correctly to see certain
combinations
more Cali Alpha Kiara
ooh hot hot
I love myself in Cali's outfit
yeah actually you know what no need to
change with Japan I wanna HD like proper
3D
outfit switch
in Ian within Ian
um
so I'm gonna do Caroline
uh let's see let's see let's see
I want to see Belle's doing Iris
[Music]
um Iris doing
phrasing is kind of weird isn't it
I was doing
um crony
crony doing
Gouda
Ahmed doing
um
what am I doing
I'm not doing Mommy
fauna doing Kiara
did I miss someone good at doing wait
who's left for good
I don't think I gave Thunderman yet
that's actually perfect
oh and Ina then wait then I don't aren't
we like a
h
you know doing tails
I don't think that fits so well but well
oh I didn't do it myself
and I did I said Callie
and did not no Cali is wearing someone
already
signed it I forgot which one though
did I not wait did I not
maybe I didn't never mind
no I didn't
um
okay Cali doing bales
oh I think that would be funny
um
mm-hmm
[Music]
yeah yeah
okay let's stop it there I need to read
super chats
oh
I'm unstoppable
oh okay
well of course the size would be
adjusted of everything
so cyrix says
merry Christmas happy holidays Canada
and kfb hope you all have a great time
and we'll come wait I already read this
attention confuses me
you Osiris
how was your
Christmas and happy New Year
hmm
capsular notebook and video cuisine
man
is good
because
[Music]
in terms of
more dead
in 20 20.
as a plateau master
conditions
[Music]
have a wonderful year thank you too will
I hear the same from you one year later
I hope so
let's make an appointment
in one year
you better be there
or be square no it's not an option you
have to be there waiting for you
kiwawa in the future is waiting for you
don't disappoint her
thank you see
thank you soon
or Robert Carney thank you very much
what's up boss I'm glad to see you doing
much better in time for Christmas merry
Christmas and I love you slugs puppets
thank you
uh Clooney
I'm not saying it I fought it but I
didn't say it clearly reported on my
sock puppets I gave her a really
detailed explanation she was like oh my
God thank you for the big detailed
explanation
oh
told her how it all came to be
yeah so she wrote ch
did she just put Kiana and the rest of
the text for an auto Translate
and just put it right now kios the age
man
I feel very Italian
Mamma Mia
um
did she did she notice when people
pointed it out the people even pointed
out
and Chad did she notice I wonder
she did what did she say what how did
she defend herself
she cannot just write her same voice
name on
nah I don't mind it's funny
it's funny
she covered up the name of her cursor
she admitted she used deep ell
him
yes I am the Senpai oh am I back to 100
thank you Robert Carney
made me I inspired you to make your own
sock puppets or
if not then why not
why not
I mean it's a weird thing to suddenly
make I guess
nice
outlet for your creativity I recommend
it 10 of the 10.
yeah
I did I want to ask you guys I did get a
massage a couple days ago
really really necessary after like I
already felt like taking a massage in
Austria but then I kept on pushing it
and pushing it because I was like oh I'm
going to Japan so let's just kind of
massage there because they're better
you get better quality for your money
so I waited and waited and especially
after the flight I really needed it
I want to ask you guys dude this is
normal like for the people who get
massages
like me
that I'm not sure if my anatomy is
[\h__\h] up
what if it's normal that when they
massage like your back some of them when
they get really like intense
they
like push you down so much with every
move
that I can't breathe
is it because my body is weird or is it
normal
happens to me
I never let another human being touch me
no one what about a girlfriend boyfriend
hmm
playing normal really
yo that that massage that I had was
really good but like she was so
so
intense
but at the same time it felt good you
know but every move I couldn't breathe
but it was so good
but it could break
I want to go again
really nice
lady was really nice too
yeah
[Music]
every move yeah every every like you
know she goes like it in this room
she had really fast hands
and remove on my back
she was going down my spine
even around the stomach if she when she
pushed me down
was couldn't breathe
but like normally I only have this
a little bit
and in the upper area but this time it's
pretty pretty bad
good massage though
I need new lungs or where can I get them
tell me where you tell me I need new
ones but like you don't tell me where
give me like a link URL
huh
thank you Robert Carney can you dance
thank you soon brother thanks donkey
shouldn't Optimus Prime thank you for
the pinky Merry Christmas to you and all
of kfb I hope you all have a wonderful
holiday with lots of love foreign
two whole chickens
thank you for your sacrifices Carefree
Brothers you will never be forgotten
he was supposed to only eat one
two is a bit much don't you think
you better lay an extra egg this month
to make up for the loss
remember I gave you guys
the new job of laying eggs
lure
thank you Optimus Prime
Merry Christmas to you too and happy New
Year bye now thank you for your support
thank you sir
hope it was tasty
Pancake Man Dancing Dragons
Merry Christmas Kiana thank you dragon's
fire it's really nice to see you still
around too me and all those familiar
names have been around for so long thank
you being so dedicated
really really really really happy just
to have you here
[Music]
my sweet sweet chimping
I'll never forget you
Alexander basket
thank you for the pinky
it was a last minute idea about the Accu
calendar turned out to be a great
success didn't show it was nice to have
something looking to look forward to
every day you should feel proud and you
definitely sound better today
thank you yeah
it was really good I think so too you
guys had something to look forward to
every day and me yeah
I haven't counted such a genius idea
gets you hyped up for everything
mmm
no should do it again 10 out of 10.
normal can never go back to normal
Advent calendars anymore what about you
guys the ones with the chocolate inside
[\h__\h] that I want my whole life members
inside behind each door
um
a Great Cookie
need more sock top as this year
Well if next year I once sick again yeah
I'll just
I just make every day with sock puppets
maybe throw in some finger puppets
in between
thank you imagine hey thank you
Merry Christmas to you too
[Music]
that's your name now for a while
thanks for the pinky Merry Christmas
Merry Christmas to you Merry Christmas
to you I'm getting a little tired Merry
Christmas to you
as always you're the best boss we could
ask for thanks for all the hard work you
do for all of us
thanks with being there to support me
for all of it
[Music]
I couldn't do it if you guys weren't
watching
you guys are what keeps me going thank
you so much gargan show
Merry Christmas to you too
hmm I have to leave it to work in an
hour oh but then
I think I'll be done
I mean at least for the day
[Music]
James McPhee Chad Merry Christmas Daniel
thank you to you too another Christmas
together isn't that nice
this is our second or third Christmas
together James I don't remember
definitely not the first one though
thank you very much for
being here still
it's not a given
I appreciate it thank you
much love from one to you
TV table trade thank you soon
thank you for the merry Christmas red
Super Chat
how do you say
um Merry Christmas Feliz Navidad nah in
Portuguese
Feliz Navidad Spanish
how do you say it in Portuguese but like
Brazilian Portuguese because isn't the
Brazilian Portuguese different
than normal Portuguese
as far as I know but at least not that
oh it's very similar
but at least not time
yeah right I know that because I've been
to Brazil
100 different but there's definitely
differences
but maybe Feliz Natalia is the same
oh
well then Feliz Navidad to you and
what's New Year
was a Happy New Year
what's that tell teach me Teach Me
[Music]
teach me
foreign
[Music]
music class when I was in junior high
school
yeah
whole class will sing Feliz Navidad
and I always had to do that because I
loved that sound
Feliz Navidad
I wanna wish you a Merry Christmas this
is such a fun song right I wanna wish
you a Merry Christmas they never played
like whatever I don't know Britney
Spears or whatever
so I guess I was lame but this was the
least lame song this and I wonder how I
wonder what lemon tree song
those were the two cool songs they were
playing as cool as it gets in school
thank you thank you
senior I forgot a kiss maybe what
let's go
CS Pony says Merry Christmas and welcome
back to Angel it's the best gift that
you are healthy and stream with us hope
you have a good time in Japan and hope
you and all kfp are healthy thank you
very much
I'm having a good time so far I think
the
um
the first
two three days were the most stressful
it's gonna get a bit more stressful
again in the last week
and it's generally always stressful a
little bit
I get stressed out easily I guess
what
I'm enjoying it though it's nice to be
back it's been a long time
it's nice to be back yeah
[Music]
very overwhelming again though
like suddenly being in such a freaking
crowded sitting again because the trains
being so crowded too
much
[Music]
tonight
at least I still care about my squirrels
oh yeah
even though they're only required to
wear it
like in transportation and
in stores it's expected
but
I don't know everyone outside also still
wears them
um
but that's just because like originally
they were already
just voluntarily
wearing masks so often everywhere
um
so there's like no complaints about
having to wear it a little bit more
that's the culture yeah
cool
you know that's the one thing that I
thought was kind of stupid like
people in my country and probably also
other countries too complaining so much
about such a frivolous thing
like see the positive things about it
you don't have to do your makeup also in
the winter it warms your face like it
really does
I like to keep it on in Winter even when
I'm out of the train or so
it's warm
yeah
yeah it's like stop whining just do it
like it's not a big deal come on
[Music]
yeah it's just I'm not wanting to be
forced to do it yeah yeah yeah
a lot of people will just go batshit
crazy when when they're being told what
to do
yeah it's not even about the mask I
think
but yeah they're not used to it like
don't
I'm just not used to it suddenly being
told hey you gotta wear these masks now
hey hey
I can't even breathe well without the
mask okay but still I enjoy wearing a
mask still
um
don't wear a mask see what Watch What
Happens
I don't think that works
in that direction
quite that well
um
yeah yeah at least people got somewhat
used to it I think the most backlash was
like in the beginning
I like masks and there's some men but
maybe it would have helped especially in
Austria in Austria we were
we still are required to wear a very
specific type of mask
in Japan that's not the case
you can wear any mask in Japan and
there's like really nice pretty wands
and so on
and more comfortable ones more like
um
lighter ones
yeah
uh what's it called kn95 in fact there
was a different different name
um but yeah it's like a more
proper mask I guess
ffp2 that's the name yeah
I think n95 works too though
oh yeah
I think Dad like pissed off a lot of
people too
Maybe
hmm
I'm getting so tired I think that it's
also the heater in my room
well it makes me tired
[Music]
I can take it for a while without the
heater
ending my throat again it's like killing
my fruit man even though I have the
humidifier right next to me I feel like
humidifiers don't [\h__\h] work
now
huh uh
foreign
ever since arriving to Japan
I think
um
I think it's really like this
environment
I don't want to like sound
like I'm complaining or anything you
know
I don't want to complain because like
Jenna is letting me stay here it's
really nice and I like it
but I think you know the error and all
that is killing me here I hope it's
gonna be better in my next accommodation
[Music]
you know
it is draining me
but when I'm outside it's not so bad
though
doesn't feel so bad when I'm outside
hmm
still having for all issues I feel like
I need like
20 humidifiers to really feel humidified
um how about buy cheap portable air
profile no no need
I think the hotel I'm going to probably
has all that stuff anyway
let's go stress and train just to go to
Japan stretch and drain yeah now I'm
okay
okay I'm trying to make use of every day
as much as I can
to not regret anything
but I also don't want to stress myself
too much because I know when I'm going
back
and it's not
too much later so
no stress
necessary
okay let's end this [\h__\h] it's almost
done
where was I
oh yeah
mixed Breezy Warrior attack
thank you for the pinky thank you for
amazing content over the course of
December I bought some lava merge's
birthday but the Advent calendar
uh well today's stream of the sock
puppet show as the climax was even
better I will cherish this present from
you for many years
I'm glad you like
you like it yay you have a merch whoa
wait when was it your birthday on that
day on Christmas
you buy
I'm a cat or like more in independent
stuff what did you buy oh
tell me
give me that kiwawa merchandise haul
show it off
oh my cat yeah they restart yeah did you
guys get some restock over cat stuff
get it well you can
the hollow live meet
these shirts look really cool too I like
them
[Music]
they're really cool
I got that new shirt in person oh yeah
they were selling another convention
right bring your shirt finally ring a
shirt
I did push for it
yeah it's back now
[Music]
thank you for getting the merchandise
thank you for supporting I appreciate it
represent
represent don't feel shy to wear it
outside all right
people who know will know
and people who don't know will not know
and they won't judge you either because
they don't know but the people who don't
know will also don't judge you because
they know
no no need to be shy
Chihuahua logic
so for no one knows so they don't judge
you but people who don't know don't know
flag thank you for the Reds of the chat
no message
what's up with that
I rarely have that nowadays people are
thankfully properly making use of their
character limits
but you
you
this old baby
thank you for the support no message
then I don't say much back all right all
right yes for the pinky
can't thank you enough for us this year
feels I feel like I'm on the right track
oh I'm changing a lot for the better you
are my hero someone I could support and
channel my love into in my dream of and
of my dreams on I wish you to lead a
wonderful life I've been super busy boy
always make me
lunch Merry Christmas to you too
thank you
good for you
[Music]
I didn't expect that one did you
got that one
came out of nowhere
[Music]
you're such a
musical being
crank it watch me
oh boy you
lyrics it's probably not cold so you is
it crankton
foreign
you
Soldier Boy watching me crank it watch
me roll watch me crack that Soldier Boy
Boy
Superman one of you who Crank That
Soldier Boys
[Music]
hahaha
oh I just wanted to sing it a little bit
that's my first try how did I do would
be you right now watch me oh my name is
UK
is he okay
I don't think he's okay
[Music]
so cringe
Soulja Boy's cringe
cringe I thought you were yawning
yeah
French French
you tuned into L.A you just tuned in I
read your super chat a while ago
thank you
hope you'll find it later
anyway last one is no surprise
no surprise
okay I read this
[Music]
they were
not so many so let's go through the
pitani Thai curry
that was a that was a big one yo I know
it was one stream in four hours but it
was a big one
oh that reminded me
yeah yeah
Me song
people are giving our Christmas who knew
yeah it was a big hurdle now that we
overcame that
you know we're closer to
the end
yeah equivalent to free normal streams
[Music]
someone's cute really love how catch it
is
you know I kind of really randomly chose
the lineup for this
but I think it worked out pretty well
um
[Music]
that's it that's it hey now I can say I
read three streams in four hours not two
see how fast it goes sometimes
um
the next one
has a couple more
is the
Pokemon endurance
oh song is on the street well still
let's tell
the next one scares me guys
this might be the last one I'm reading
but still big accomplishment I would say
what do you think guys
what do you think
I'm gonna try to not
Tangerine too hard okay
and we must
how's my throat it's okay
Pinky
gogos episode seven I guess when Lorelai
asked Dean to movie night without
telling Rory
oh I totally understand Roma's reaction
nice of Florida like to go to the
kitchen and things got spicy
she can read the room she's a kooky
reader Luke listen to Laurel Island
festival and Max still to Percy for me
yeah well I mean
she's a good catch
I understand why you were getting
thirsty
catch well I mean
thirsty ass but it wasn't
that bad Max wasn't that bad
he may have been a little bit on the
horny side but
he was still a good dude I would say
I liked him
no
look is so sweet Max good though yeah
obviously can't win when Luke is your
competition
yeah but Luke has his flaws too you will
see them
stubborn man
they were stubborn
yeah glad you're enjoying it still
connections
I'm guessing the x is
happy birthday belated Robert Carney
assassin
cereal thank you for the rest of the
chat hi wow I'm so glad to call you my
awesome your dedication to whole life
and your community is insane oh looking
forward to the Japan trip can we expect
some content from the normal Studio I
would love some high quality Wawa ASMR
to fall asleep to now back to lurking
well
[Music]
Cheryl you got me there
asking me so directly
well
Maybe
[Music]
not ASMR related though
hmm
I'm off to you again
but
I think jenma is coming back soon
um
so um yeah well well Sarah that's all I
can say but I think that's enough for
you to get excited thank you for the
rest of my chat wow
for support yeah and
I guess I do dedicate myself quite
should not wait to you guys
uh you guys are on my mind
24 7 yeah
head is never never empty always filled
with chickens and they go book book and
a book book here a book their book
everywhere book book
Had a Farm
thank you
would be blocking you from entering the
school
yeah it's okay it's okay it's good to
have you back but you still sound a bit
sick perhaps you should visit the school
news
I did I did
did you know that I would love her so
much so how did you know how could you
guess that I would love her so much that
was totally unpredictable
oh she visited all right
I'm glad I went there man she cute she
hella fine
good good lady good lady worth it
birthday
ma'am thank you for the pinky and Wawa
this year has an extraordinary for me as
I've changed a lot I became healthy and
happier and stronger chicken thanks to
kiwawa I wish you a healthy and even
greater 2020 free from the bottom of my
heart thank you I love you I love you
too thank you too for following me for
such a long time
good for you for making improvements in
your life in 2022
I hope 2023 has some good things in
store for you
you can make use of all those
improvements yeah
I wish you all the best good luck but
don't forget about kiwawa okay Gotta
Stay With Me
stay with kiwawa don't forget about me
please
thanks for the pinky Valley and thank
you for the random Chad oh
what the [\h__\h] how's that pronounced is
that French Merry Christmas
or New Year's
Noel sounds more like New Year
oh no well that's Christmas oh I guess
oh
okay I did hear it in connection with
Christmas before now that you're saying
there's some kind of food
I heard it pronounced in Japanese before
but you don't know what I do or
something like that what is that some
Christmas food
I think some Christmas bread or so
maybe it wasn't like that
was it like that
something something new well
foreign
oh it looks like a tree
well it looks good it's like a
rope chocolate roll cake
I'd say you look okay
hmm
feel pretty good
creative by switching up the flavor of
the cake batter or cream red velvet
gingerbread pumpkin oh there's so many
different variations mmm gingerbread
yummy
yummy yummy a tree
Uma would like that tree cake
but she probably wouldn't because it's
probably not vegan
foreign
[Music]
I mean I've had like this kind of rolled
cake before but not specifically
this one I guess
hmm
that actually makes me wonder in Japan
they like to eat cake for Christmas yeah
but it's not this one
for some reason it's just like um
like a normal ass
normal ass like cake with white whipped
cream
and like one strawberry on it
Strawberry Shortcake so much and I'm
just like
tastes like
one percent of strawberry and 99 of it
is
cream and [\h__\h]
that's not enough for me
needs more strawberries
but like if they choose a cake to eat
for Christmas then why not this bush you
don't know him
because
you know
foreign
Strawberry Shortcake
I like cake of strawberries but
you know it's kind of lacking some
strawberries there
hmm
but then in Austria even though France
is so close
we don't eat cake for Christmas
is it is there any French people here
right now is it really common for you
guys to eat that for Christmas I wonder
at you okay log cake last year chocolate
one
[Music]
it's pretty common oh
I would love to eat cake for Christmas
ma'am
big
kind of expensive in Japan
cool well make it yourself looks easy to
make yourself
I feel like that rolled cake is pretty
easy to make yourself
my friend used to make it
heart attack
during this pack and I got a heart
attack hello Dad Mom
oh my prayers have been answered
a hot hot lemon tea straight from
the hot place
[Music]
oh wait a second
I knew something was off
this is the same drink I had like two
days ago I think is it no
oh
same brand
is both hot lemon tea but the packaging
looks different but I think it's the
same thing
but the other one I drank the other day
you know what it tasted kind of off
this one tastes normal
yeah yeah I taste the difference
it came from um
what's it called in English
vending machine
how can it be off
I guess
packaging mistake
[Music]
yeah no this tastes different especially
because I know this tea very well I've
dranken it many times in my life
yeah yeah I know it should taste like
that one tastes old but kind of old and
I still drank half of it because I was
like there's no way this could be off
there's no way
no but this is so good it's really hot
but it's the hotness that is drinkable
nice it's really like a princess
and jenma treats me like a princess
jenma
I'm gonna miss grandma
um being spoil
she brought some sweet stuff even though
I already have cake in the fridge
okay
I said I'm not gonna tangent
I lied
so the French insert French here and
back from an operation though still busy
during the holidays but when you say
operation do you mean like a military
operation or like a physical body
Hospital operation
which one is it but I'll be going to
Japan for the first time this summer to
Hokkaido precisely oh didn't I read this
one when it came in since you're in
Japan since you're Japan expert is there
any place yeah I remember this one
because I didn't know what you should be
doing in Hokkaido no idea
but I think already kind of like
um gave you advice as much as I could
thank you soon
[Music]
yeah enjoy I don't know if you're going
alone or with someone but I think you'll
have a great time first time in Japan is
always very special
and overwhelming and but in a positive
way
um
yeah I think you'll you'll be like yo
what are those what's that and
everything you see
no no time to think no I'm like
answering so you guys you guys need to
understand by now that like when I read
a red or pink that for a while I will
like go on and on and talk to give them
their money's worth
I don't want to just be like okay thank
you bye
I do this on purpose to a certain amount
in the green you know
of course at some point I go a little
bit too far sometimes
yeah exchange rate is good
just tangent again are you complaining
should I be ignoring the chat um you
don't want that either
okay
hold on move on moving
Sunny what love thank you soon in
[Music]
Korean
let me see
let me see papa go
my desktopology is not working so I'm
just gonna read what it says in English
goddess I tried that what I wanted this
Christmas as a painter who is not sold I
was always afraid to go out in the world
I guess it means like as a painter
no I don't know what it means which is
not
um selling well I was afraid to go out
into the world but with the support of
the Goddess I stepped into the world
it's not a lot of money
but I'll give you all my proceeds it I
got something more valuable so it's okay
oh I love the goddess nkv who always
support me you're so sweet
they are so sweet
passport passport Hospital
oh
it's so sweet
um thank you
sorry
thank you pillbox
he's so sweet thanks for being part of
kfv thank you soon
every time I play AOE I think of you
thank you for the beautiful father all
the time
my sinuses
sorry
it's in weird places
getting better though
who said it says
lift your arms
sinuses lift your right leg
[Music]
thank you so much for one
okay if he loves you Chihuahua loves you
yo
you need to chat thank you soon Draco
meteor.com fire glass thank you soon
this guy it's like trying to get a
fortune
soon
[Music]
might be very well past December 28th at
this point but wanted to send a super
chat over for my third birthday and my
question mark is this is overall
celebrated as a Carefree chicken oh oh
it's censored
did you forget your real age or are you
censoring it
celebrate it is okay for chicken thanks
for three years of much resplendance and
laughter Buzz lady looking forward to
what awaits us next may I be supposed to
ask for two favors
please have the birthday song can I have
a
roll Safe Harbor line instead can you
wish a happy birthday for my friend and
no nimus Lee minus kfp orderly Observer
happy birthday
his birthday is December 30th thanks a
ton hey
you know how you go to the Quest Giver
in an mmrpg who wants certain quests
items and you already have them so you
already give the quest back immediately
that's what I just did
[Music]
both of you
yeah both of you same day or just close
the your twins
twins
which is soul mates
you're welcome you're welcome
hope you had a lovely birthday
hey my birthday is
half a year to go
still some time left but I think the
time until then will pass by fast I
probably
by like probably in February or so I
have to start planning my merch
[Music]
who do what to do
thank you for the two pinkies
shoes
[Music]
yeah yeah
uh bass driven Massacre technician
principle playing negative
I learned from Twitter YouTubers are AI
too you know I I saw that and I don't
interpret that whole thing as them
saying
B2 is our AI
I know some YouTubers were like they're
calling us I don't know about you guys
but I interpret that it as
that at the same time as YouTubers were
Rising through through the influence of
the YouTubers the those like all kinds
of AI stuff were also
Rising
like the I don't know the the
AI like Image Creators and whatever I
don't know maybe maybe I'm wrong eh
there are actually so many times
actually I who wants to watch that
a little
it doesn't make sense no contacts hmm
I didn't think how charged the term AI
is right now
yeah I don't know so okay well then but
then they didn't mean those YouTubers
they meant hey I have a tubers against
but are there really that many that is
that it's worth mentioning them
so many many people mistook YouTubers
for AI at the start of the YouTuber boom
it how can you mistake it as a i
there's obviously like a real human or
Phoenix or Reaper or whatever
talking behind it
I did huh why are you stupid
did people read it as kizuna AI it
oh
oh my God
it just means love in Japanese
they
read it as AI
she role played as an AI well but still
I mean it's obviously not in an AI no
matter what she role plays as doesn't
every person with common sense who sees
it
realize that
there is a human talking
hmm
that requires you to actually watch it
so maybe the most people who bought that
just like heard it and didn't really
look at it what it actually is
I overestimated people's critical
thinking skills
I never heard about that people thinking
that YouTubers are AI That's the first
time I hear about that
foreign
[Music]
let's not get into this this takes time
this discussion why did we start another
discussion I don't even care about this
topic I don't care about it at all I
don't give a [\h__\h]
foreign
keep your flesh disguise
I'm real
I'm a real boy is that what Pinocchio
says
no he says I want a beer does he what
does he say
your boy
I'm a real girl
so the deck shut up
and me no give me
I need to go to Idol meeting also but if
I don't know
thank you for the pinky I took my lunch
break just for this moment don't tell my
boss I was watching QR stream doing work
I love this twist worth it what twist oh
that that twist
glad you enjoyed it
the AI twist
that was AI because that was noticeable
that it wasn't a human behind it
it was an M robot kind of thing cannot
really convince you after all
and robot uh malfunctioning uh
yeah don't be cool Channel
bone removal expert
scary
Pokemon location
[Music]
what is that from
does anyone know
not Eminem I'm not thinking of Eminem
you guys are so basic
foreign
[Music]
how you doing not Lou
what are you doing throw your nose it's
not coming out it's like somewhere there
behind my sinuses
it's like in a weird space right now
I have to like push the air up from a
weird space to try to get it like moving
you know what I mean
uh
I'm not gonna pour water for my nose no
I'm not gonna water board my nose
yeah like they were like really really
far back
um
I'm not gonna get Gemma to pick my nose
no
I don't need her services in that way
you
hmm
you volunteer well I will [\h__\h] snap
your neck if you even attempt to do that
oh we're getting closer
[Music]
well um today's my birthday happy
birthday
notebook love you okay Tina
um
[Music]
finishing another Pokemon game ooh sadly
I missed the final battle so I'll vote
it ASAP
this might be the last stream there will
be no job till you'll see down the road
yeah they have like a big area reserved
right so I hope you keep enjoying the
game plus more tulip in the post game
was that the nurse
wait nurse is playing a role in the book
game
just pull up someone else
I don't remember
oh here really oh yeah she kind of like
disappeared afterwards hmm
I love her
okay well yeah I think I kind of like
um how do you say application in English
um I'm kind of like done
was the right word
closed off
um
yeah
I've concluded yeah I'm gonna go back to
it I saw content but
I mean I think if it was Arceus
I would go back to it
but I'm not really motivated for this
one
yeah you get me
yeah maybe I'll I'll probably uh play it
privately because
it's entertaining enough
play privately I guess
yeah a little bit
to pass my time
oh
yeah we have to move on to other things
like fire and blam
let's go find them there's Bale's say if
she's gonna play it because of her mommy
I wonder if she's gonna play it
I'm gonna play it ever since I've played
my first Fire Emblem game
back then
I've always wanted to play the next one
worried about the difficulty
she's not sure yet
she's hesitating
there's a word that she won't be good at
it well I mean you can always get
vaccinating and less strategy like turn
base thingy so you always have a lot of
time to think about it
hmm
in experience in a genre well I mean
well that shouldn't be a hurdle but
she can she's gonna watch My Stream and
then decide if she wants to play it too
oh
there it is there it is I think I got it
reach
nah
foreign
it's in a weird spot
I hate this
I'm getting dizzy
chiefly hero
Academia Christmas is done and I got my
bonus from Brooke here to deliver your
cut hey thank you for making my
Christmas a lot more enjoyable than
usual lots of love to all the Capri
soldiering crew oh soldier boy
um not so nice holidays out there
um
thank you
[Music]
um
happy holidays to you too our holidays
over now
maybe in many places they're already all
over hope you had happy holidays
good time
for your support and sorry I'm kind of
like mentally like
dead right now
it's been a long day again
and I'm kind of exhausted but thank you
thank you for your kindness and your
generosity
thanks for the bonus
oh baby
Happy New Year to you
I pretend that you shouldn't Heavenly
Stoner thank you soon
rise every time
thank you for the pancake treat brought
her into some nice drink or food kudos
to the pilgrimage
oh hmm
well I've treated them to some things
now he's being treated to my cats I
think
that is quite a treat on its own
thank you oh hey you guys stop saying
Frozen brochures I'm feeling for him he
stayed outside on purpose even like one
hour after I was done streaming I was
like where is he
not only you guys but I also was worried
for nothing he didn't even like feel the
need to come back on time hmm
it was past midnight
young sir
Patrick
I don't know where he went I know he
watched the movie and that's all I know
and then I said what else did you do
movie was like what three hours long
and he didn't tell me he's so secretive
sometimes
but I don't want to be like annoying I
don't want to act like his mom
so I just laughed at them
where'd you go
he went on another pilgrimage
uh thank you
so
did I read more than I made today I hope
so I think so
[Music]
some say he's still out there
so I'm sneaking around motor oh
I I I think he would be a good Hobbit
hmm
he would fit in
we did a lot finally
oh I gotta go now oh my
thank you right so for you don't worry
about it thank you cheekies monkey
golden ninja go
okay I will I will go
I will go
um as I said you know tomorrow no stream
I think
um
I thought it was destroying the table uh
to Domino's dream
uh but still lots to do
yeah all right then and in German we say
auf wieders in
uh what's gonna happen New Year guys
and thanks for being here
spending the evening with me nice
tangents guys I didn't even tell you the
great I didn't tell you the crazy
tangents okay okay okay okay so
um the things that happened in 10
minutes of me being in Shibuya
and standing at the famous Crossing okay
the you know the big scramble egg
Crossing
um
Okay so
first win
first thing I see is
a group of young dudes one of them like
all of them focused on one dude that one
dude taking off his coat revealing
underneath
while being filmed by his other dudes
a really tight blue
I think like a wrestling suit full body
not quite full body most of the legs
were bare
with a made apron once he took off his
coat they walked over the scrambled egg
Crossing
I'm assuming it was for like a YouTube
video or so
then next thing I saw the whole time
was
um
that was this weird dude walking around
showing uh well like holding up
a sign handwritten sign that said
um
I even took a photo We're not gonna show
it I guess but it said
um
do you want to release relief release
your stress
from everyday life
you can
you can use this bat
to
slap my butt
for men it's 500 yen for women it's 300
Yen so you have to pay him
like
I guess three or four bucks as a dude
and two bucks as a woman
to get the chance to relieve your stress
and yeah
it was a plastic bat though it looked
like a plastic band no not like wood or
so and he was running around the whole
time but not a single person I was like
around him
observing him for 20 minutes
not a single person took up this offer I
wonder why
hmm
next thing
um
was weird too
dudes
came up to me kind of oldish looking
maybe like late 30s
beginning of their 40s
looking really normal
and try to speak to me in English they
were like hello hello hello hello
you speak English and I'm like
thinking if I want to answer or not like
kind of looking at them really pretty
much like this like
um
yes
because I wanted to be polite I guess I
answered I'm like and let's hear it
about I guess
I know it's gonna be [\h__\h] but we're
almost here I'm out
and then he goes
and
I am YouTuber
can I interview you
and I say no so they walk away
but when they walk away I see what they
had written on their whiteboard they
were carrying a little white board which
I guess was the what they were gonna ask
me
uh in their interview
and I'm so glad I said no because
I don't even want to
I don't even want to say what question
was on the Whiteboard
it was um
let's just say a very
sensitive and say so
question
hmm
man yeah gross gross
gross gross gross Buzz grows
and one more thing that was happening at
the same time the whole time
and this one area in 10 minutes was I
was also observing two really cutely
dressed
like Idol looking girls
uh with like matching hairstyles kind of
doing like a seemingly like a
meet and greet kind of thing
with some fans
they they're like coming and going and
taking pictures and like
[Music]
in the middle of this like
crossing right in front of the Crossing
I was playing Yakuza IRL
that was just so much going on and I was
thinking oh man I guess I really am back
in Tokyo
oh it's been a while since I've been to
civilian man
I don't remember it being this
crazy years ago
if this is what I seen within 10 minutes
oh God
it was interesting
all those Yakuza cyclists
sub story
oh man
Japanese
Yakuza um
right on the money with accuracy
that's how they write those signs just
take inspiration from real life I guess
it's not it's not that crazy yeah
because I ain't that crazy
yeah
it's reality
I always gotta remember the Japanese
title it's not Yakuza
gutoku
okay so that's my
that's my little tangent
for the day one little tangent
okay
foreign
[Music]
but wasn't that just a subtitle
Yakuza like a dragon or so
hmm
or maybe not maybe oh it was Yakuza like
a trend
oh for the eighth game it's just gonna
be like a dragon something something
oh
[Music]
I think Yakuza is catchier in English
for like always these people because
they're gonna be like cool
I feel like a dragon I gotta be
uh
hello
yeah I don't think I'll be back moving
but
it was a good timing
I'm gonna go just want to say goodbye
[Music]
bye-bye you hear me saying bye bye right
guys
okay
yeah okay okay okay
[Music]
foreign