[Music]
do
so
[Music]
do
hello
[Music]
twin tails
how's it going how you doing today um
my arms are really weak right now cause
like i was i was carrying stuff um
before the stream
uh
not because of a workout but that was
almost a workout
um so my arms are like jelly right now
um
[Music]
i did go
to the gym a little bit
i can show you a picture later
but right before the stream i uh
i was carrying some stuff i went to buy
a new plant
sure you did you little [\h__\h] you don't
you're always like that even when i show
you proof i'm gonna show you proof later
you little [\h__\h] you always like
me
i saw you comment i rewatched my archive
okay of my gym announcement and i saw
your comment when i was like when i
showed the the fan art of me being in
the gym and i was like i was in the gym
and even when i was at that point you
were like nah
nah i don't believe it
until i
uh showed those those photos of the
machine
but now you're again you're like
i don't buy it what the [\h__\h]
why do you guys not believe me not all
of you just some of you why why do
especially you
you know when you know that i mean you
you know i mean you
why you don't believe me the [\h__\h]
but anyway right before though uh before
the
you know what next time i'll bring them
i'll bring them
and and
it's fun to doubt you [\h__\h] you
next time i bring an acrylic stand of
myself and put it on the machine so that
you can see i didn't just take pictures
from someone else
uh-huh
uh what was i saying right before the
stream i was carrying some plants so my
arms are like jelly right now plants and
other things like furniture and i was
overall doing some stuff in my apartment
today
which maybe i'll uh
touch on today
tell you about mm-hmm
uh oh here we go we're starting with a
little bit of tiredness and a tiny
headache but not really a headache a
forehead egg
sausage
[Music]
green green
iced tea
um very sugary stuff though
[Music]
more more more
yes drink need to drink more i also had
kind of a late breakfast so
[Music]
yeah
um let's see um today i want to play
sims 4. again yes i know sims 4 even
though recently i showed off my sims one
it's because um i just still need to
test out sims one i need to install it
and installing it on on windows 10 is
not like
that easy also i need a i think i i have
a
external disk drive somewhere i just
need to find it
um
uh bleeble blue we're gonna play sims 4.
and
um i downloaded a new expansion pack for
today's episode i thought i already had
it but i realized i didn't and i
downloaded it early enough don't worry
about it so let me show you something
already
i already um clicked it away but i took
a screenshot just about there
what no
restart again oh [\h__\h] you
okay something new was uh once again
update installed
yeah today is spring themed because the
past uh sims 4 episodes we had christmas
and we had new year's eve in new year's
eve we had everyone come together
wait we did both right okay
i definitely remember doing christmas
and then being like uh should i do uh
new year's separately yeah i think i did
i did it separately but i definitely did
both
i listened to your song it's great thank
you yeah i did a really a little
scrolling thing on the bottom left
and did a little scrolling thing
oh sure
[Music]
sims bgm
uh
road game
we're gonna continue with council
uh
because they have
potential
[Music]
anamata
council
[Music]
this time we will have
um
spring and for the sake of spring i mean
we could have done it without this
expansion backpack but i thought
why not
uh combine it
um
one second let me show you
so basically i got i got uh three more
things um
um but the others don't matter that much
this is cottage living
i think
wait connor's living was the big
expansion pack i think that i got and
then two extras or something so it says
uh
razor befriend animals there's no taco
llama probably but let's just say it's
in alpaca because i love alpacas
chickens and cows can provide sims of
eggs and milk
we're gonna have chickens guys
llamas provide wool for crafts just
don't get spit on
wild birds share their sweet songs and
rabbits pickle we'll freely roam oh my
god but keep an eye out for mischievous
foxes here you can see all of that in
the picture look at the child hugging
the
chicken
well and there's someone milking the cow
and there's yeah there's some bunnies
oh so cute oh that dude is holding a
chicken up in the air it's going crazy
and then there's a little fox there's
little chicks there's tiny little chicks
oh my god so cute i'm so excited and
then it says live off the land wherever
sims grow their own produce forage in
the wild or visit the village market oh
it's a village market fresh is best up
for a challenge well i want to grow
our own produce not produce produce
right in this case
english english easy
try growing oversized crops to enter
into the competition at the wind finch
wick fair oh
not a huddle
embrace the countryside hanford on
bagley is nested in a cozy countryside
oh i think this is a new um neighborhood
but i don't
i don't think we want to move right now
uh pack for a lovely picnic or lose
yourself in a cross-stitch session oh
cross-stitch session
get to know the locals at the gnomes
arms pub and learn about the town from
your neighbors
actually i kind of want to
kind of check it out
maybe we'll move our family
enjoy the simple living benefit from
higher quality food while using the new
simple living lot challenge
ah this new love challenge will require
your sims to cook for fresh ingredients
for each meal will you seem to be up for
the challenge uh maybe not right away i
wonder if you can add the
the tr trait later on are there any sims
gurus
who know
sims already can barely keep themselves
alive this is just guaranteeing your
death no i mean
you're right with the first part of the
sentence but not with the second part
uh once you need money for that yeah we
have to check how much money we have but
if we move like it sells the value of
our house and
yeah
it's my birthday today happy birthday
it sounds good though i think this is a
a good um good good theme for today's
episode while celebrating spring we're
gonna build our farm our own crops and
maybe get some cute animals like jim
keane's definitely chimkins
definitely hundred percent many chickens
and i already saw like some gameplay of
how this works so by the way this is not
really specifically new this has been
around for a while college living
we get our fresh produce products
produce produce
don't worry about it
and so you can speak english just fine
no sheep's balance yeah it's uh i think
it's
because um sims 4 and sims in general
has a history with llamas
um
i i also think it's like
weird because it's not really common to
have llamas
um or alpacas uh
at least not in like europe and probably
most areas in america and so on i know
there's some like areas maybe maybe a
country like for example peru
is maybe a country where there's a lot
of alpacas but certainly in most
um countries a normal farm does not
really have
alpacas or llamas i think
not not normally
um
yeah yeah so this is kind of a weird
combination but it's because sims has a
history of with llamas there's like um i
think they're ever since sims 2 there
has been
like
like um
there's like sports
teams like uh items that are
themed after that and the mascot for
that was always a
a llama or like not sports teams but
like the university
clan or whatever i don't know what you
call it and their mascot is a llama yeah
i know sims history it's like i'm gonna
sims i'm a sims historian man i can tell
you all kinds of [\h__\h] yeah yeah um yeah
it's like a college mascot and then
there's like items with that on top of
it yeah like like flags and t-shirts and
stuff yeah
sims historian kiwawa
yes sure there's alpaca farms everywhere
but like it's still not that common
i just want to say that
in texas wow howdy uh so okay
um
remind me to do all of these things
except maybe the the challenge um but i
want to i don't want to forget it maybe
i should write a memo let me write a
memo to watch today night rouchini
uh
i had a memo what a memo here
yeah yeah yeah
and then we
oopsie
um
so we wanna do we wanna grow
grow crops
and
get
chick
and
maybe maybe uh yeah
move house maybe
and uh
find fox
and
i don't know and
go to pub
cook with produce produce produce
okay
maybe like this
we start we're gonna chill today okay i
i always stress myself so much when i
play sims
um
up until now i've always kind of
pressured myself because ever since the
first episode people were like oh my god
kiara's sim streams are so [\h__\h] funny
and i felt very pressured because of
that so every episode after that i
always
spent some time not streaming sims
because i i just you i needed some time
and then and i always felt like i
couldn't live up to the expectations
anymore
but today i'm going to say from the
get-go that
you guys should not have expectations
because today is going to be a chill
cottage living stream okay maybe we can
find a nice car that you should live in
at
[Music]
there it is
obs
oh why the [\h__\h] is it down there here we
go
sims
sim
window size is so weird what the hell
oh
that doesn't fit
why is this windows eye so weird
this
never fits here it's so weird
it doesn't fit my way out
ah
it's kind of cut off though
there we go
okay but just a little bit
the resolution should be 16 9
oh well
this will do
okay
so here we are um how much money do we
have can i like look at it there you go
information
oh
that's really not much
let me let me look at the
where can i ah
here it's been a while it's been a while
i don't know how to do this anymore this
is the new place a new area
oh
look at that beautiful
lake going a river going through
and i see some places with farms what
some family
wow they have a big farm the watson
family has a big sasuga sausage watson
family i expected nothing less here's a
bar
oh this is small
we could get this empty lot or we can
which one
this one
is also small one bedroom one toilet
i don't know if we can afford
um
moving over this one has
lot challenge wild foxes and simple
living oh what is this old new hampered
an area that boasts rolling hills
luscious states and a small community
garden old new handford fenford
is perhaps best known for its historical
naming
woes initially known as little hen for
the neighborhood renamed itself new
hanford in an attempt to escape its
diminutive origins however in neglecting
to inform national map makers they
ceased to officially exist for a
two-week period
when told that to be reinstated would
require yet another name change
residents chose old new hanford
which beat out the other choice new new
hanford by silva
sims descriptions are always kinda cute
finch week
all right now you know what we're not
gonna move but we can visit anyway we
can visit the pub
um later on but i don't think we're up
for the challenge right now
where do we live
here
we live here
yes
all right we moved takamuri to that big
ass house almost next door i forgot when
the [\h__\h] did we do that
i didn't remember i don't remember that
we could have also
lived in that house
all right car slow start today
slow start but here we go
what select the sim to play what do you
mean select the sim to play
why
this is this is this is this from the
update
why do i have to choose who to play in
the beginning makes no sense
[Music]
i play everybody
yeah um
oh yeah i think i ended it last time
wait we don't live in this huge house oh
oh there you go they're at uh
they're at the myth house right now
oh uh sana is this yours can you
i think it might be no wait no that
might be enos um okay so sana uh just
died um fauna is about to pass out
uh
iris is about to pass out
crony's about to pass out
muma is about to pass out and
which is bales is about everybody is
about to pass out you know what um
can we just all sleep now we should go
home why are we not home go home
everybody go home
but you're i know you're sleeping right
now
and stinky
we could we could use the facilities
here um but you might fall asleep while
you're
ah don't you just
sleep in the goddamn beds stupid sims
they never go
ugh
watson is also dirty as [\h__\h]
this is inappropriate please stop amen
oh is santa sleeping in your bed
wow me parker sorry i'm gonna just sleep
somewhere else
[Music]
[Laughter]
sorry just let me okay i'll i'll leave
you
mmm there's turkey down there you know
what we should stay in in miffa house a
little longer until we all feel better
oh oh this is also appropriate i'm sorry
about that
are having a rough start mm-hmm
i'm so sorry ahmed
so sorry for intruding your privacy no i
wanna [\h__\h] again we should go home
we should go oh is there another
bathroom
we need another bathroom
uh yes
here uh
take a shower
and
hmm who really needs to sleep we all
really need to sleep how about you sleep
in
takamori bed
you
sleep as well just everybody go to sleep
fast
you women you can sleep uh you can't
sleep on there okay
you can sleep one one of those
go go go go go go go
everybody use the myth beds
oh i know they went home [\h__\h] because i
told them to go home
okay okay then let's just go home okay
enough is enough i'm going to have to
ask you to leave now ina who are you
saying that to
oh oh [\h__\h] fauna is walking home and
um
bails passed out in the snow
[Laughter]
yummy
ah oh she's gonna be fine
she's gonna be fine what is what is
happening why did ina who's eno getting
angry at
you know who are you mad at uh oh oh
yeah i see
yeah she's uh oh miss
is making some foes here you should
probably all just go home now it's just
how do we
how do you just quickly go home again i
don't remember
just go home go home let's go home let's
go home and die at home
[Music]
oh god i thought someone died
go home
[Music]
we're dying here
bails where's babes by the way just
bails left okay bails
ah [\h__\h] you're not even oh no she is
very sleepy ah go home go home come on
come on go home
come on bails you can do it
it was a terrible terrible new year's
party but i guess it's
it makes sense it was a new year's party
so
it makes sense they all didn't sleep for
the night
it makes sense if you think about it a
lot of people stay up all night for new
year's also it does not look like spring
here but okay um we all need to sleep we
all just need to sleep sleep
how do you do this again yes
uh
sleep
oh you're actually corona is doing
pretty fine cronin can
shower
we just need to get everybody's
mood back up and then
we are going to
start building
our farm i guess uh
get leftovers
and
you're also gonna
get leftovers for now
all right all right i'm in control
kiwawa is in control
a sound plan yeah
all right so much better controlling
such a big group of
a big group of sims when
oh iris
uh
when when you have only one floor this
is
this is what also well the problem was
with
oh god it's so dirty
with um
with the mitt family it was a big family
and it was just a huge huge territory to
work with
women what are you doing with me
you're going to sleep okay and
afterwards you should
shower because you're also stinky
simmering what a treat yeah yeah
yeah yay i know people like my sims
streams and it pressures me but i hope i
hope we can find a middle ground of
being entertaining and calm all right we
have two shower people done
uh
you're gonna grab laughter it's
wonderful that's what i wanted you to do
you crony is doing wonderful can crony
somehow make money for us
what can you do cronie what are your
skills
can you go is there is there a way that
we can maybe
because the only money maker we have in
the family right now is sana with her
art
and that's not gonna get us very far
maybe we should really have someone get
a job or we can
odd jobs
it's an option for odd jobs guys
bail's just standing in the snow
oh
wait because of that icon
did i forget to click on her i keep on
forgetting to click on her because she
doesn't look like one of us in that
[\h__\h] outfit sorry i forgot about you
oh my god i'm so sorry um just go sleep
please or actually not that i don't know
which bed belongs to you just go to
sleep in whatever bed you like
bails
go sleep
i think she's bugged
how do you reset a sim again
oh dear she's not doing well she can't
move
oh [\h__\h] she's trying to she's trying to
do something here but it keeps on
stacking up and failing have you ever
how do you reset
sim again um
does anyone know
she's never seen this much snow before
yeah probably
i think she's enabled true
testing change enable trip
was it right click
did it work
oh no
[Music]
ah there we go shift left click reset
object debug ah
it comes natural it comes naturally
oopsy uh
and then are you are you good now can
you go sleep now good job
are we sending them to
reset
[Music]
kill no she died i didn't kill her
ah [\h__\h] odd jobs okay crony odd jobs
looking for gamer crony is a gamer what
a coincidence i need someone to come to
beat my oh these are
are these one-time jobs
beat my friends best score at blick
block we have a bet that i won't be able
to do it within a week i'm willing to
give you half of my bet money and more
if you uh do well enough she can't beat
my score back wait minimum
recommended skill video gaming level two
we can quickly reach that if we don't
have it yet
oh other than that we have paid beach
cleaning
mixologist
dump or discrete
tv hookup help
sense sculpture judge charisma level one
yo what are these jobs and what in what
expansion pack did they add these
oh this one has a high
very high pay
looking for paid volunteers who are
willing to clean various beaches around
the island do i have to follow her when
she does that recommend skill none
let's try dad
beach cleaning has 106 but one time
while this is 33 dollars per hour
okay now let's do the gaming one and
what the [\h__\h] do i do with this lady
here
what do i do
reset and she's reset again can you go
sleep
oh okay she's fine now i guess this one
just didn't work this one
if you click down here she does it like
automatically usually but yeah okay okay
i think we're doing better movement
uh oh what is going on here she's trying
to nap just sleep how about that
how about that
[Music]
don't need to always
do everything for them
you're doing terrible don't talk to iris
just go sleep chronic is off to work
already oh my god we didn't get time to
oh [\h__\h] does crooney have gaming
skill yes give me skill free okay she
will do great she will do great she's
out there
she's out there um
scoring in blick block
to get a record nice nice nice sasuka
cronie i had a feeling i had a good
feeling about this okay santa's sleep uh
and then after sleep
go shower
uh fauna is
having an issue oh she's also bugging
you see this here
this shows you that the sim is bugged
[\h__\h]
and reset
and sleep
okay
this is why you can't leave them alone
and do let them do their own thing
because they're just gonna bug and die
oh iris is doing well too
who is this
oh bales bill's finally sleeping ah good
for you good for you
um
iris is by the way playing road rival
alpha and now going to sleep apparently
or she tried
do i have to help you
there you go
ah beautiful oh my god everyone's
sleeping or at work ah
the time is spinning up great success
oh we got over 100 bucks cronie easily
beat the client's friend's best score
and shockingly she beat the world record
score very cool the new blake vlog world
record is getting a lot of attention
nobody knows it was actually crony while
that lack of recognition could
potentially be frustrating at least
crying on a nice juicy tip to distract
herself 99 plus nine
yeah
good job
wow wow i guess you guys don't really
see it but i read it for you so so yeah
if only world records were really that
easy to beat oh look at
look at her being so
so proud how do i take a screenshot
again in sims uh
see
yes
now let me before we have a problem here
again let me just check something really
quickly
no everything is good okay
okay
this is so typically crony but i mean i
have to say after beating the world
record you you deserve it how do you
turn off the whole interface again
uh
does someone know that
no no it says c to take a screenshot
within sims
does someone know tab
tap tap
oh yeah i love my sims gurus oh
beautiful thank you
gotta take some good photos i'm getting
like the best material for thumbnails
out of these streams like
it's just so good
look this is like almost like she's
kissing us
i want to get in the middle let me get
in the middle
so slightly so slightly not the middle
[Music]
she dislikes herself too much but in
this case
in this case
oh god oh my oh her mouth
look at her mouth nice teeth
nice teeth you got there crony
what are we doing
what am i doing honestly
just trying to get good pictures of my
beautiful
chicks
okay
um okay we're good
all right all right cronin thank you can
you do another job also holy [\h__\h] this
place is so dirty can you do another job
uh
actually maybe we should i wonder if our
jobs pay more in general
but she did go immediately so at least
we can decide i think our jobs are
better because at least i can decide
when i go
let's do one more cronie
let's do one more
what skills does she have
handiness free singing free video gaming
free the others are one or nothing let's
let's find something in happiness video
gaming or singing
or something that doesn't require
anything
this is what perfection looks like
exactly
paintings make tons of money yeah we
have we have sana for that uh oh it's
still the same ones not a hotel fitness
mixology handiness level one 23 per hour
begins to sap okay
let's go
charisma level one as well
there's one for
christmas surprising corny doesn't have
charisma
let's go crony
huh
queen oh
she wants to clean the sink thank you
you could also clean the floor though
goku
when are you going to work
okay
didn't you say i asap
all right i'll just wait uh
bayless is taking care of herself
beautiful
you do that
oh crown is going now
[Music]
there she goes all the job here we go
i won't be supposed to start some kind
of farm yeah i'm just trying to get
everything everyone you know
but okay but the thing is we don't even
have money to build the farm you know
that is the first problem we have
thousand six hundred simoleons simoleons
and that's really not much and i don't
wanna cheat
[Laughter]
this is hard mode we're not we're not as
spoiled as memphis okay
council and hope are not getting the
easy ticket you know
myth was lucky
they got a [\h__\h] ton of money from the
get-go
but yeah can't say the same for
our dear counsel and hope members
[Laughter]
yeah no cheat run is more fun i have to
say like when i played sims for a sims 3
2 whenever privately back in the day i
always cheated and it really took away
the fun of the game but i also i felt no
reason
i felt no reason to not cheat
because i guess i also couldn't feel
guilty or whatever i just wanted to make
it easy for myself but now that i'm
streaming here i see that in order to
also make it interesting as a stream
um it helps to not have money because
then there's challenges so
maybe we should get one more person a
normal job how about bales since you're
up what skills do you have
she has
mischief free but that's probably not
gonna get you although
it's sims that's probably gonna get you
some kind of job find a job is there a
mischief job
like clown or something
um
actress
detective doctor interior decorator
scientist astronaut not
athlete business
conservative but we can always learn new
skills though criminal
critic
culinary education engineer entertainer
maybe mischief helps there freelancer
gardener
law
painter politician
salary person
who's that dedicating your life to the
fire serious data corporation and
putting its needs above all else is just
a first step for a salary person
it's like
stability respect and endless hours so
it's basically just someone in a suit
who goes to work
that's all there is curry here is
part-time oh there's like
ah maybe part-time let's do oh this
barista
i want bails to be a barista drop diver
fast food employee there's like
part-time only jobs i didn't know
if the player and return after the shift
is finished
ah
these are jobs where you can actually
follow them there's five jobs where you
can follow them but we don't have time
for that because we would keep on
leaving our family these are jobs where
they can just leave and they'll come
back eventually and these are part-time
jobs where you also don't follow them i
think
retail employee manual laborer lifeguard
fisherman
fast food employee diver barista
babysitter what do you think what should
what should bails be barista right she
loves coffee yeah yeah
bae rooster
barista
[Music]
yes yes
she starts as a coffee stain remover
if you love hanging out at the coffee
house and already know all the fancy
drink names why not get paid for it
exactly
[Music]
28 dollars per hour 5 a.m to 7 a.m oh
well good luck bails
oh good luck
she starts tuesday at 5 00 am she starts
at the the frothy foma nice do we need
any skills for that
uh
we have a job man
she has a [\h__\h] job i'm so proud do
you need anything
promotion requirements
just performance no skills for now
i'm going to work with positive emotion
maintaining high relationships with
co-workers oh we don't have time for
that
it's okay we don't need to be promoted
we don't need to be that um you know
um
how to stay
uh eager in life
okay uh so you're cleaning a little bit
and after that you should go back to
sleep why did you wake up so early
and then we can actually pass time
quicker
is that shift even legal why five i mean
and people work at any times but maybe
you mean it
maybe it's a rhetorical question
how can what do you want how can some
how can yeah how can going to work at
5am be illegal good question
ambitious yeah that was the word i meant
drawing i know i'm just waiting for
santa to wake up but she was like so
[\h__\h] dead she's sleeping for like an
eternity okay wake up now
you need to paint
shower first because we don't want your
stank on the paintings that you're
selling
okay and now scrap is this not yours
either
do we only have one or why it's scrap i
guess because i don't know who it
belongs to
new one okay let's let's make a [\h__\h] ton
of money um
landscape painting go
failure
[\h__\h]
what
the good news is that crony successfully
set up the tv
the bad thing news crony accidentally
dropped the tv
it was a little scratched so the client
wasn't especially thrilled maybe crony
should be a little more careful next
time outcome your odd job's rating has
dropped and only only 13 simoleons are
you [\h__\h] kidding me she had the right
requirements
cronini you dropped the tv why what
happened
oh that face is hot though
[Music]
oh damn girl
oh she has such a beautiful face
this is beautiful with the owl painting
in the background oh she's such a
oh she looks so good from every angle
how does she do it
she's so hot
okay um okay you deserve to sleep uh
where's your bed
sleep anywhere i guess
she's so photogenic yeah she's perfect
it's perfect that she's perfect because
she's perfect
ah
when you make other hello live groups
like japan or any see this is uh and i
had an idea um when
i was in the pre-chat because okay
actually it wasn't even my idea someone
in the pre-chat had the idea gotta give
them the
credit um i'm going to make um
a holotoni family which means that mummy
and kiara will have to leave their
respective families and we will add
reina louie and sumail so a new five
people family and my plan is to
um have them start with
zero
simoleons like absolutely no money even
poorer than these girls um and then do
our best of painting and and like in the
beginning you really have to you can't
even paint because you can't even buy
one of these
um so you will have to
uh run around and in sims 4 there's like
all kinds of like like little little
things that you can gather and then sell
hoping to find something that's worth
some money so in the beginning we will
have to do that
yeah
yeah yeah
um
yeah
i'm gonna make it a little bit difficult
but for now we're still playing with
council but sometime soon i'm gonna do
hodo today i think i think she's
finished
oh thank god 305 plus some fame the more
famous she gets the more these will be
worth so let's do more confident
painting let's go
[Music]
okay we're making money
child abandonment ah don't worry about
it it's sin it descends and we can make
clara grow up and then cali will take
care of her cali will take care of clara
it will turn into yabby house why
oh because we are so um sensitive
give louie the salary person job until
her fun
need is in the toilet quit and become a
beachable
why
did she say that that's how she was
working before becoming a youtuber
[Music]
kylie going to be a single father
it's not like that guys it's just it's a
different dimension in in another
dimension kiara will be still with her
family okay
it's just like sanjon
we're done you saw your speech today
244 let's go
next one
finger painting
wow it's so big
okay go go go go go go go while
everybody's sleeping and i don't have to
take care of them thank god they sleep
like
[Music]
they sleep like a
like a bear
what's what's a good
uh
example they sleep like
they sleep like
oh what happened what happened what was
that sound
sometimes sims makes this sound and i
don't know why
like a baby
that's it
oh like a log yeah yeah like a log
[Music]
are you done
402 for that damn
someone needs to explain art to me oh
god everybody's waking up okay uh can
someone cook some food why are you about
to do leftover eat macaroni we still
have macaroni we still have leftovers
nice okay
uh
thank god we built these toilets in
separate rooms scene we really needed
with so many sims you really need it
um
good morning fauna
uh
yeah you're getting those leftovers okay
okay you just do what you do
i can't handle all of you
hunger
[Music]
maybe we all sent them working for a
little while
and then have them all quit their jobs
when when we're good again when we have
enough money
chat with moment
okay i'll give you a little break only a
little break santa i need you
three
two
one okay get some food quick
smart move give her food all right all
right all right quick quick eating
so this is go away
someone put this away fauna clean it are
you still eating movement roommate clean
it
[Music]
why you hate everything so much
she's killing the snowman
no
oh
[Music]
who built this one does someone remember
oh she's so happy about it too
empty trash or at least she's emptying
the trash that's that's nice of her
she still has that
santa outfits
i know you want to chat but can someone
clean the freaking floor like what is up
with that oh wait yeah wait we can ask
the dust bunnies for um getting us stuff
was it mummy that was friends with them
it looks like it befriended
okay okay
oh no wait fella oh i need to give them
dust so that they're happy
roommates doesn't return an empty pot
clearly haven't put minimal effort into
actually finding anything yeah a dusty
snack okay i'll get feed dust
oh my god fauna
getting those gains
and if he does to you
step on don't stop okay okay okay santa
try something don't waste your time
drinking water uh
figure painting goals that was that was
pretty good that was pretty good
new skill day was awful
wasn't up to bail's expectations why did
we have to do that anyway
why are we
new skill that was awful okay
ain't nobody got time for that i'm busy
here
[Music]
that looks like iris pranked the [\h__\h]
toilet again
do you see something suspicious here
guys
there's two toilets to find the find the
difference here
gonna use uh this one oh yeah especially
because here i could prank the toilet
but here i don't have the option
[Music]
she never stops doing it you can't stop
her
all right uh what could we do let's send
iris to
get a job
i think yeah find a job let's go
also part time job what job do we want
for iris babysitter barista diver fast
food employee fisherman lifeguard manual
laborer or retail employee where do you
think
um she could do her best criminal
why the [\h__\h] is there a part-time
criminal wait there's no part-time
criminal there's only full-time criminal
you want her to be a full-time criminal
[Laughter]
no babysitter baby say that we don't
want him to be gone for so long
or do we maybe we do want her to be gone
for long so that she can't prank the
toilets all the time
how long does she have to work for a
criminal
okay nine dollars per hour that's so
cheap compared to the other thing
[Music]
that babysitter
oh i can choose
it doesn't really matter
but
there you aim it ah this one is
nighttime let's do this one
okay
nice more money more money for this
family we are 2 200 now
everything still is a bit dirty
i mean you're partially at fault for
that
we're pranking everything
wait
because it's not christmas anymore we
can sell some things we're gonna sell
this [\h__\h]
we can oh all the christmas things you
can tell the presents
i already got rid of a lot of the things
i think i can't see much
more and that was actually about it
okay
what else that was worth it
um
iris
clean
and
uh
oh yeah can you can you earn money from
doing something here but at least you
can make uh some mac and cheese
yeah yeah yeah yeah so that we don't run
out of mac and cheese
connie's
when did cronie come back from her
oh yeah right a while ago i sent her to
sleep
because she worked so hard
and once you're back
you could finish this
once you're done sleeping go do that
sana
uh good job
400 sell
next
how about an what cells is the best i
think that was like one kind of painting
that sells the best let's do a large
abstract
i think they do pretty well
moment phone i just kissed what no way
[Music]
nah
need a vacuum cleaner wait is that the
thing
because the floor looks so dirty
this is by the way the floor
um getting dirty and all that and the
dust bunnies is is not part of the main
game this is part of like an expansion
and you can turn it off apparently
there are vacuum cleaners
oh
which is the cheapest this one is the
i'm cheapest you can practice one too
vacuum around oh but maybe not not not
in the room where the dust bunnies are
not in that room
[Music]
uh how's it going over here yeah same
chimney how about fauna
you
[Music]
ah
she can't use it here i guess it's not
dirty enough the floor just looks dirty
but she should be able to use it here
no not that empty vacuum we just bought
it
what about here
no
i don't understand these
things
huh
is it only in the rooms where there are
actually dust bunnies
ah vacuum here vacuum ah
never mind never mind apparently there
was dust in there which i don't believe
but okay so if we put this here look at
the dirty floor now
now we vacuum here
can we do it
oh
okay she vacuumed somewhere else but
okay ah
i think
no it's not getting cleaner yet
still looks dirty
[Music]
don't get fooled by that
oh that looks so good
that looks pretty good good job
uh is this finished
iris
iris can you put this
grab all servings can you put this in
the fridge please
just that dusty daddy got filled up but
just being brought into the house
now it's in your inventory so let's put
it back in here all right
i'm a stone upgrade
salad
salad yes who's that
portion of good fortune
food
congratulations
hey bills did you plan to you might not
even dirty your bills
[Music]
we reached three house three thousand
simoleons guys
going going fine one more sauna one more
how about
snivara watanini
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
toilet
crony what happened
what just happened i heard a bad sound
again
i'm gonna get food
eat that food yeah that was just
someone's leftovers
you're gonna eat some more
how about a snack
get a snack
snack quick meal
applesauce
chips
how many she's saying let's do that
okay okay
i don't know what to do
too many sims
[Music]
i will start i think i will start um
building something that i will start but
we'll probably won't get to finish it i
also don't know how to even
how to even get those
animals that we want okay let me put
this here
how do we want this thing to look like
and where do i even start
terrain tools
how do i
i make
a farm thingy
um
off the grid
maybe it's an off the grid
[Music]
is there a chicken coop
wow it's so big
wow
it looks very comfy
nice
what is this animal shed apparently for
cows
500 that's something oh that's huge but
it's not that
expensive one second if we move this to
here
can we fit this
[Music]
yes
nice
maybe like
like this
oh yeah
can we place this there no it needs all
that space
the closest we can get is here okay
what else is there garden plot
admirals fish trap
[Music]
a bee box
should we get bees
a canoe
roast them toasted campfire
a bird feeder oh yeah we can get birds
with this
we're gonna have a different color let's
get this one orange
and
we can even afford
the bean box as well
these are dangerous no no no no we need
the beast
let's make it yellow right so small cute
[Music]
maybe maybe here
all right once the snow is gone i want
to like decorate all this more what was
this again ah grapevine
grape all of these are grapes
grape grape dessert
grape tissue okay
so
do we need to pay extra for the animals
yeah purchase animal how much is a cow
in the llama over here
350 400 400 450.
we still we can still afford but let's
buy chickens first
eggs
eggs can do a lot who will be the farmer
it will be fauna fauna will be our main
farmer did we give her a job
no good then this is your job
now fauna and purchase chicken
little baby dicks good
all right we'll get
we need hens and a rooster i suppose a
rooster for your coop is a good idea if
you want them to breed and create
hatchimal eggs
ah
also good to protect the coop from
predators and act as the nature along ah
all right we need
we need let's do two hens or three
and one rooster is that a good balance
my mom would probably know
um
we're farming now we're in the game yeah
your neighbor's gonna hate you oh
there's trips
they all live pretty far away
they live pretty far away no worries
really far away seems good
bruce is gonna fight uh yeah if some
foxes come
without the rooster they would probably
kill the hens that would be scandalous
there's already bees we didn't have to
buy the bees they came naturally oh
fauna has unlocked the recipe for
friendly treats information about
friendly treat animal treat has an
additive honest notebook
how did that happen so we have chickens
now
i hear them
but you can't see them
i hear them though
signed chickens i mean assigned
chickens does that mean two different
coops
we can do
there's a chicken chicken
oh chickens hello
oh it just reminds me of the first time
i brought my cats home to my home and
they were like i opened i opened the
little door
of the
the
the the cage thingy
ah and they were like so hesitant to
walk out there but it was so cute i was
staring at them forever until they
walked out and then slowly they explored
everything
look at them go
what's up
uh scatter fruit nearby
oh
all the four chickens are out
those are you guys
wait i want to take a picture of you
fona can you do it again
good job fauna i'll take some more
pictures of you later
oh can i pet them
we're gonna give it a treat you meant
about human life do that do that oh my
god bails
green again
she's green again fauna you will be the
the chicken's best friends oh my god
look at the chicken
oh my god
she's not getting along with the chicken
um um
socialize
ask if golden chickens exist
egg assist
huh
that looks like a yes
hug can i hug you
can she please hug you
please oh my god oh my god oh my god oh
my god oh my god that is so cute
that is so cute and the sounds are so
cute
oh this friends
pet
come on
[Music]
how do you play
i need to name you
i can name it i need to tell them apart
[Music]
is like
[Laughter]
that's a great name actually
you will be iggy i like that name
uh alright
i hope we get a along well
make up exciting joke oh my god father
the chicken needs to hear an exciting
joke
then once there was an egg
and then i dropped it
oh [\h__\h]
eggy did not like the exciting joke
[Laughter]
here's a here's a treat
[\h__\h] i have no treats i need to make
treats
uh that's why she learned a recipe i
guess because she bought the chickens
uh
where are you going fauna why why is
your priority not the chicken huh why is
your priority not eggy how is that
possible why do you keep on running away
this is happiness right here
this one was thinking about cupcakes
just now
hi jean do you have to clean it but i
guess i have to clean the coop maybe
okay let me oh oh that's the rooster
okay let's socialize with the rooster
pet the rooster
ask if chickens should cross roads oh
dear and did not like to be pets let's
ask if they should you know
cross the road yes look at 10 and it's
so cute ask again
because i already probably forgot that i
asked it a second ago yes it really
likes that question tell joke about eggs
acting in villains
your wigs are so stupid oh wow
that's so stupid oh funny
jokes
can we pet you now
all laughs have limited amount of money
defauna has recent daily cap for a
lifestyle what do you mean sure
oh look at the eyes it's going crazy
about that
so happy
[Music]
bed one more and then and then we name
you
oh so cute look look look at the eyes
when she pets it
like now
so cute
name
kentuck
[Music]
that's example name is kentucky i don't
even need to think about the names this
is perfect they're giving me the best
names i don't even need to use my own
brain wonderful okay you're kentucky
i love the little jumps
no no what are you doing you have trash
where did you get that trash from [\h__\h]
um we'll buy cows later when we have
more money oh my god i was so focused on
all of this
completely
oh look at the toilets oh my god one is
pranked one is broken
of course it is oh [\h__\h] um
we need santa to do that um
iris i was what the actual [\h__\h] is wrong
with you
you're repairing that and can you
unpractice
kiana wants to come over
no she wants bails to come over no no
sorry kiana sorry i'm calling
sorry kiana we're a little bit busy here
oh my god isn't she following fauna
we just walked into the house
i don't know if we welcome chickens in
the house i guess we do
i guess we do
oh fun fauna is
doing the gains again
if you have time for that talk to the
chickens
oh my god it's so cute
uh
this is this is another unnamed one that
socialize with this one
um if chickens like foxes trotting
i guess it's like if they like foxtrot
being all cooped up
tell a joke about me i don't think it
will like that joke
but um
let's give it a try
clay
and
pet okay let's try it
rainbows
[Music]
we need to name this one too i guess the
other one
where's the other one that i already
named this one
my favorite thing to do now i'm never
gonna do anything else in the sims i'm
just gonna take care of chickens for the
rest of my life
oh my god
this is like so fulfilling
okay they're really not getting along
here what do you want from me
what do you want from me
blah blah blah
i likes to be pet
no i would never trade you
a pet
it likes to be
petted
you literally do that
ah i was completely resolution of
improving his film good job
i need 100 maybe i should do a 100
chicken challenge
befriend 100 chickens
first of all get hundred chickens and
then befriend hundreds
okay oh what the [\h__\h]
why did i just go over here i love a
zuma
fails
look at that face
look at that face she looks so she looks
like my emoji
[Laughter]
brain empty why is bales taking care of
that
iris should be the one
and this one broke that was the one that
was pranked before iris
fix it
why are you feeling bad what happened
with you
gross
gross prank toilets are disgusting all
on their own having one explode is wrong
on someone okay it exploded on cronie
nader
we're crony
probably isn't the best feeling having a
toilet explode on you sana while you
have some time here
oh she's broken again
all right
thank you dough bales for trying to
clean that toilet that everlasting dirty
toilet
um
how are we doing with the chickens we
didn't name that one that we were
befriending
which one did we just start befriending
this one i think name this one
sandy i don't like that one i don't know
what that's supposed to mean like what
joke that is but how about
um
[Music]
mcnuggets
jimmy all right we'll have one jimmy
uh
and then this one we also have to
socialize with this one
why why are there negative who would
ever scare
white hen or who would ask what are you
some kind of chicken
[\h__\h] came first white hen or the egg
[Music]
who would who would ever do such a thing
take care of the chickens
do it
[Music]
i guess i can can i see hunger full okay
okay when they're not full that's when i
should scatter some food
um
oh funny oh she's so energetic she's the
right person for this job
did you like that
[\h__\h]
she's telling a joke about llamas
yeah
i like that not funny
so cluckers
i love that it fits so well with
smoothie and chunkers i'll remember that
if i ever get a chicken i really like
the name cluckers
that's a good one that's a good one i
like it all right we named them all um
they're no no one is hungry but how do
we take care of the the bees thingy
bond with bees change into beekeepers
okay we should do that first probably
before bonding with them
let's get some honey
hey honey hey honey
hey honey
decided to get a duck what in the game
can you get duck a real duck i think you
can right if you have a
little lake
uh how's how's it going here are you
done oh you got you probably just just
no you got done so
money is looking good romani is looking
good again we can buy a cow i think ah
do another one
don't die on me
eating okay take care of yourselves all
right everybody
i'm counting on you guys
now you need to do something with the
bees
well i've got the bees let me see look
it's look it's spring is coming
chicken chicken on spring
chicken is on spring break
sleeping outside we're just warming up
oh my god i'm so happy
[Applause]
she was fine
i uh apparently chose the wrong person
to do that
i was a moment
no they were totally fine with that it
seems like bees like
owls
clement frost oh that is santa
hello
santa is calling fawna it's good to hear
your voice fauna i want to ask you if i
should get to know katrina caliente a
little better as a friend
what the [\h__\h] is that they seem like
good company why are you asking fauna
i don't care and go for it
uh
she's playing a game you are supposed to
bond with the base
no
no you bummed i can't
this cannot be done while wearing the
beekeeper
oh
maybe you only need it when you collect
honey
ah cause like there's no bonding that
you can do if you wear the beekeeper
suit
ah
[Music]
grumpiness calm active level active
honey amount empty
okay then then uh change out of the
remove bee keeper suit
on
there's a barrier between them no not
anymore oh my god
yes this is nature
this is nature
oh [\h__\h]
that is surprising
this is unexpected they are um
do you think we bonded a little bit
also let's maybe have mummy take care of
the bees and uh fauna just takes care of
the chickens
[Laughter]
one second i need some water
mumbai has turned them against fauna no
oh dear
that must be it
when we bonded with them so that she
could use them
to attack her enemies
[Music]
right now like cronier irish take care
why why cronie has a job iris has a job
they both have a job like crony doesn't
like side jumps
iris got a babysitter job and bales is a
barbarista so they're kind of busy
um
how are you all doing um mummy is going
to sleep nice
bales is watching a tv but you can also
go get some foof
uh sana
just finished another beautiful painting
selling that when is your fame ever
going up you should sleep now though
good night sana
sana yeah
how about
another aunt job for cronie
let's see what the internet offers today
and she's been painting a lot for us
we're 2 000 bucks again
she sells seashells
skill none
[Music]
hiking buddy fitness fishing skillman
okay
box packing so i just got my nails done
and i have to pack some boxes but i'm
pretty sure if i tried and i'm going to
ruin my manicure plus the boxes are
going to be totally heavy so i really
need someone to come and like do it all
for me
do you see this emoji
a rat i think box packing she can do
but this one pays more more
yeah oh wait there's also a last minute
beach party cooking level one i don't
know i don't know by heart if cronie has
cooking
on level one let's do the seashells i'm
starting a business selling stations by
the seashore i want people to someday
and look at me and say who is she and
why is she selling those seashells you
know anyways i need some stock to get
started so if you're interested i'll
take as many seashells as you can find
i'm often legally changed my name to
shelley
[Laughter]
okay kayla
i don't have any seashells right now but
i'll help you
wait do i this is me i need to bring
seashells
i can just
[Music]
does this imply i need to actually bring
seashells like collect them somewhere
beforehand no no way
no way
i think i can just go there let's try it
oh my god chalet that is ingenious holy
[\h__\h]
iris
throw that away throw that away where
did the
where'd the vacuum cleaner go who used
the vacuum cleaner uh was it
farmer
[Music]
i should be in someone's inventory
oh
great parts
[Music]
because she keeps on repairing the
broken toilets ah she pranked another
one
we should or is it never let iris use a
a toilet ever again
you know what let's keep it in your
inventory
vacuum
lightly
like him lightly all right vacuum
stung
fire was stung
by a bee ouch pesky beans things are the
worst but it is hard to resist disposal
of honey
understandable fauna
[Music]
wow
it's still snowing though but look and
oh my god our our pond is uh unfrozen
again
oh
can we fish
fury i think we can
it's so grayed out though
oh baez is getting a call by kiana again
no sorry kiwawa why do i keep on calling
second time i'm calling all right fana
thanks for that you should uh take a
break
go sleep
you'll sleep in the bunk bed
iris also sleep
well she was probably trying to sleep
because this was bugging out again
ah click on the fishing sign oh
i know i need to stalk the plum the fish
oh
wolf eels like the fishy ones stuck in
his pond discover more fish in your
household collections to gain more
options oh
it doesn't cost money unagi
[Music]
i don't know if you would make unagi don
or so out of this specific type of eel i
wonder if it matters
but i [\h__\h] love unagi don eel eel on
rice
that's one of my favorite japanese
dishes
[Music]
all right oh wait it's stocked up now
okay wait uh who likes fishing
was it iris
i know reyna and and and callie like to
go fishing
in games
who else in council
there's someone in council fana
oh you didn't like no no no the thing is
i don't like i like normal fish when
they're when it's not raw
and i like you when it's not rough but
so for example shrimps and crab and
anything that is not raw and octopus all
that kind of weird stuff i don't like
it's actually surprised that i like eel
but i do i do like eel very much
eh basil's freaking out cause someone
was in her bed really yeah oh
oh yeah
no but don't don't those are both not
assigned to her but uh you see you see
this again [\h__\h] it happens so often she
wants to sleep
which one is yours
i think this one is yours no
no it doesn't say
just sleep wherever bales come on you
can do it
i'm like a kindergarten caretaker
unbelievable
okay
okay okay crony is going to the odd job
soon
this looks so wonderful
all right let me do something i want to
do some um
i want to do some um um landscaping not
really landscaping but i want to do the
ground
terrain tools
oh yeah
we need some dirty stuff
illusion of sand
pinecone mounting rough sand
earthy dirt there we go
maybe all around
no no no no no not everywhere
maybe because the the cows would be
stomping here and there right
[Music]
i needed to look uh realistic can we
make it brighter
[Music]
okay nice
oh my homies hates that not a hood oh
well
sometimes you sometimes you're gonna
live with sand okay now here we have
something growing so we'll have that
soil there
and then
we'll have like a
a path like let's say
cause fauna will walk around a little
let's create a pump
[Music]
we could actually make a leg of stones
or something oh
it doesn't look so good though when it
fades out like that
the shadow there's some huge tree that
makes a red shadow
[Music]
how about this one
oh i like those stones
how about we make it
not so soft
yes okay
nice
i like it
uh
i do
until where do we want the pop
[Music]
go back to green
okay
have some green here
and maybe connect a path here
uh did we which one did we use
this one i think oh
[\h__\h] no that was not it uh this one
[Music]
garden designing yeah
what if we execute the sapling so it
doesn't cast a shadow and execute itself
but i think it's
i think it's this one
did this huge [\h__\h] tree cast a shadow
even over here at least in the morning
time
but i can't get rid of this tree
see i think yeah look at that shadow
it comes from from somewhere here
i can't do anything about that one
but that was a very very um aggressive
way of saying that
uh is that still snow oh
um
[Music]
some more powerful
these paths are cheap or like free
actually at least so that's nice
they have some pebbles around it
does that make sense no maybe not let's
have sand let's have sand
it could also be a pebbly
needle oh well
[Music]
and now
[Applause]
try to connect it
over here
[Music]
okay
and then that works
yeah okay
okay
that's nice
but
uh
you know realistically when someone
comes out from that door i feel like
they would walk just straight over there
they wouldn't use the pebble path
because that's how humans are they're
stupid
so
i'm gonna make a dirt path
someone always keeps on walking over
there
who is it
you're ruining the [\h__\h] grass
you're ruining it man
[Music]
these
okay stones being realistic here
i need my tinfoil hat
it's mine my tinfoil hat
oh
oh maybe something around here
made some pebbles here
nice all right all right all right all
right okay anything else
maybe we can decorate it with some
plants as well
oh
maybe some bushes
what do we have
wow
wow this one is huge
and that one is nice
[Music]
move objects on
okay
how do i not use the grid
movements on didn't even work how do i
not use the grid i know there's a way to
not use the grid
bb move objects on
i can't tap anymore ah change to nihongo
ah
i could do that but there's also a way
to out
oh thank you i never knew that actually
i played sims so often but i never knew
how to do that pink asalena plus oh
let's plant some stuff like around the
path
here and there
[Music]
ow
green fern oh
oh pretty
[Music]
no lying a palm
whoa
[Music]
do it like everywhere
also these are so big
swiss cheese plants wow it's gorgeous
[Music]
wild grass i like wild grass you guys
like wild grass
it's so wild it's inspiring move
move
okay i'm decorating the house
and we can be so proud of it because we
can be like yo we didn't cheat for this
at all
[Music]
oh it's springtime so this one isn't
even green yet so these these change
later on this should have uh some
flowers as alias later on
a small forest fern
okay
aside from a lot doesn't count no that
does really not count oh yeah our bgm is
overlapping don't mind it
granite falls shrub oh
all right let's combine some things here
all right
i'm looking good
this will this one look nice once uh
once the
the flowers
are sprouting
oh lavender bush
i shouldn't mix too many things here
should i
maybe here
uh
take the wild grass
i'll pick another one
move this over here and then pick
another
lavender that sounds lovely
i can't wait until it
sprouts
all right that looks that looks pretty
good
don't you think
i have a green thumb you guys have seen
on my twitter today maybe um that uh
yeah there has been a lot of green stuff
sprouting on my balcony
[Music]
actually those plants are really easy to
take care of like i just
sometimes maybe twice once or twice per
week whenever i think of it
i i uh water them
but at the moment they're just doing
everything on their own once they bear
fruit then maybe we might
i might have to take some better care of
it
that's too big
um
oh wow
but at the moment it's just happening i
don't really have to do anything
and but there's there's one thing my mom
called me today before the stream
and
let's put that here
yeah yeah that's nice that's nice
and my mom called me before the stream
and
she was like uh because she saw my the
pictures on twitter
and she was like wobble up we need to
talk i need to call you i need i need to
talk with you about some things i'm like
okay i wonder what it is
[Music]
um
so she she was really excited she called
me she was like okay wawa you're welcome
everything's sprouting and i'm like yeah
i know
i saw it
and then and then she told me okay it's
time
it's time it's time for some action like
what what what oh yeah right
i remembered she told me
um
yes
she told me when she was like helping me
plant everything
that
there will come a time
where for the uh what was it a
red currant
it's a natural toilet it says open air
naturally you can actually use this as a
toilet yeah
you know what this one cannot be pranked
i will get this toilet
the non-practicable
toilet so my mom was like chihuahua
the the red currant ones they're
sprouting and you have to
um become a bee
she said i have to become the bee
because probably there won't be any bees
around
my balcony doing their work in order to
actually have this plant carry
uh current successfully i mean she said
it might actually carry it even if i
don't do this
but she said anyway i should do it to
give it my success i have to pollinate
it yeah
she said i have to pollinate
my
red currant
bush which i think is so cute and weird
i'm gonna be um
there's flowers i'm gonna be
[Music]
um she said i need to take um
oh that would look so nice
she said i need to take
a little brush like a paint brush with
just a small one
and uh then i
uh
have to like
tickle
tickle every single small
sprouty thingy
where supposedly later it's gonna carry
the berries
[Music]
and b yes how will bb
did i did i do an mb video before
or was i just planning on delaying it
doesn't sound too hard yeah it's not
it's not difficult i have to i have to
do it once i think i forgot i think only
once
i did oh yeah there we go i i always was
a bee
easy no problem for me
no problem for me
leave it to me
and add some here this this will be fun
for the bees because this will carry
some flowers shaggy luscious
it's a hybrid between chrysanthemum and
daisy
don't think guys that this exists in
reality it could but most of these sims
things are made up
[Music]
okay i think
oh wait maybe a little bit of a
little bit of a dirt path here because
the chickens walk a lot here
[Music]
salted earth
i don't know which one
go grow grow garden activate and let's
use this one
soft and
not so big
ah
too big
oh
yeah yeah
[Music]
okay
just very very slightly
[Music]
m artist
guardian design is my passion
okay okay i think this looks pretty good
now um we can also improve it but for
now
[Music]
i don't know what else to add we're
gonna add some animals later um do they
need anything besides that
barn
i suppose not the food is gonna be
[Music]
here anything else water decor
maybe maybe we're gonna have a nice
bench to sit outside oh there's a
there's a timber log chair oh that's so
cute
that's so cool
we can have it here so they can look at
the cows
yeah
and one more here
[Music]
to look at the bees and the flowers and
the chickens
and then we add a little stomp
[Music]
here
and
a stone
here
you can sit on the stones
that's a table even
oh there's a whole couch like them
that one is uh
tree trunk
ottoman man what
what do you use this as
nice natural very natural
and hey bail ah that would look really
good i think
if i put it here like probably
originally if i didn't have move objects
on i probably could would not be able to
put it here
but i hope it doesn't obstruct anything
if i put it here i just want it to
look even more like a barn you know
um
[Music]
there we go
isn't this nice it looks so natural
you connect with it yeah country feel
very much country feel
there we go
this is fondant's dream you're fun and
this is all for fun yes you'll be mostly
the caretaker of this beautiful
beautiful
place wow
chicken sit
chicken sitting
she's sitting and chicken very happy
i can't wait for it to maybe i should
take pictures once everything is like
you know more uh sprouting
happy nature sounds yeah
i don't think fawn wants a farm
yeah maybe not in reality but you know
lore
like
[Music]
yeah
look it's so cute
oh
happy
my farm
look at my farm
wait a second
[Music]
oh give me a ah
there you go
no ah
go down
[Music]
that's so cute
okay
when do they report today's ship they're
this is kfp basically they're working in
here they're making eggs in there
they're a pr production factory
well what's happening here
why is she uncomfortable
tired just go to sleep are you having
problems going to sleep
do i need to help you oh crony is
keeping her up all night
um crony sleep
mommy sleep everybody sleep just go
sleep although kron is actually fine
crony what can you do did you do that
side jump
or did i not give you a new one how
about
oh you should you should uh practice
charisma or acting artist speech
practice speech
let's go
okay
i could put everyone to sleep but nah
we need to use the time that we have him
all right are the chickens gonna be
sleeping now oh look at them
on the second floor this is so cute such
a cute house oh my god it's so cute my
mom um
has like an insanely huge like uh garden
um
what the [\h__\h] are you doing here and uh
she's planning on getting chickens she
used to have chickens before
um but that's when she left somewhere
else and
eventually you know i told you the story
she made the chicken into soup chicken
and i thought it was absolutely
terrifying
uh to just think about that
first first meal is for a while um you
know getting those daily chicken eggs
yeah they produce so many chicken they
have so many eggs every day but at some
point they were so old
that yeah you have to you know
do something
well this chicken is a sleepwalker
sleepwalking chicken
okay
[Music]
eventually moved away and
now she's working on her garden and step
by step she's like you know building up
her territory and eventually she'll get
some chickens again uh she said and she
might want to get some other living
animals too
um
and she'll get those eggs don't worry
she won't kill them immediately
and she wants to build a chicken coop
and i gave her
a while ago she was
um at my place and i gave her this
camera i was like do you need this
camera it was like a camera i bought for
um
when before i left austria and i go to i
went to japan
um i really was worried about my cats
rmt was gonna take care of them so i
bought like a camera around and i can
set up so that i can watch them when i'm
in japan you know and i asked rmt to set
it up but she was like no that's kind of
creepy i don't want that so it was never
used and then i showed it to my mom i
was like do you need this and she took
it
uh to her place and the idea was to
install it in the chicken coop that she
one day will build
and uh
we will have a live chicken camera maybe
somehow if we're able to somehow get the
feed
and i thought maybe maybe we could make
that happen it sounds funny doesn't it
a live feed of the chickens oh we should
add bird seeds
oh curry small number two nice
oh now she's feeling bad okay go add the
bird scenes
we can get some birds too nice and now
uh toilet
and then sleep
we super chat the chickens
i need to make a
channel just for the chickens uh a
chicken coop whole life english channel
yeah and then there will be a 24 7
stream
no probably not but yeah
uh i don't know maybe we can record some
footage i don't know i don't know how
we're going to do it but it was just an
idea
[Music]
um
there is a 24 chicken stream called
chicken city of course there is there's
a 24 7 stream of probably everything
little little kittens
i've seen that before and bunnies and
all that
yeah
and some um
i think some like uh animal uh shelters
and that have uh 24 7 streams as well to
raise money and so on
woke up uh in the middle of the night
to grab some food that's okay you can
work after that oh and father good yes a
farmer has to work up work up wake up
early to work up exactly yes use the
toilet the one toilet that's not pranked
critical failure
chronium
oh [\h__\h] she didn't go
to her where that's not my father she
goes automatically why would crowley say
she was up for delivering seashells if
she really wasn't only she knows but
maybe they were too scary seriously they
might have a crab and then or something
outcome your odd jobs rating has dropped
once again and zero simoleons ah
oof
she was sleeping when was she supposed
to go
[\h__\h]
god damn it that's the second time her
rain dropped
no
[Music]
okay fan are you ready to do some work
you gotta eat first maybe and then take
a shower
uh
okay
overs [\h__\h] oh my god is someone practice
i'm not i'm not repairing this
a mathematical diagram all right let's
go bales actually sorry can you do
something else can you repair this
where the [\h__\h] did santa go
what are you doing what about the
mathematical little diagram
these are so
cute okay
uh
uh uh fauna yes shower okay
quite the logic still oh she doesn't
even have a logic skill and she was
drawing a mathematical diagram
yo
that's motivation that starts somewhere
yeah bales is always either in that
green suit or she is naked it's either
one of those
chickens are sleeping
[Music]
and
then
after the balance is done with that
you're gonna get uh
leftovers
fauna
it is time
to
start
collect eggs
we can collect eggs
scatter the food first
status clean eggs ready to collect five
oh
five eggs
yo i thought it was so crazy that eggs
like chickens lay eggs every [\h__\h] day
man it's like they're
pooping out eggs literally
collect eggplants
oh
our first harvest oh egg
egg
eggs
oh egg
egg nice five eggs
wow
beautiful
cool
there's honey too
can we um no wait wait wait wait for
collecting honey
i think we might have to oh it's only
partially full though
uh
collect honey there we go okay let me
try let me try
the meal
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] they're mad
only a little bit very good they're okay
oh you really don't need to do anything
with bees they're so easy maybe my mom
could get bees too
can you change out of that suit please
remove okay
now we have these eggs we're gonna
[Music]
we're gonna put them how do you make
them hatchimal i guess the rooster
didn't do his work
multi-port honey cool are you poor we
need to bond more
wow
mathematicians
little planets probably considering it's
sana
[Music]
so only 102 that's so cheap
down the path to stardom she's earned
her very first fame point
we worked so hard on that which is hers
to keep fame points can be used to
purchase fame perks within the fame info
panel with her newfound fame though
she's now susp susceptible
susceptible to developing a fame quirk a
behavioral oddity shaped by the actions
she takes
so interesting
wait where can we do that
uh
the fame thingy
[Music]
also we need to complete one more
emotional painting
uh any any emotion right wait where do
we do this uh stardom thingy
uh fame point
[Music]
what
it's not the rewards store but we have a
lot of
oh
well we can buy some stuff
what do we have here i should check this
speed cleaner waterproof
we have a lot night owl how about night
owl
uh build extra skill at night speed
readers
storm chaser free services marketable oh
marketable sims sell items they've
crafted for most simoleons does this
count for art does someone know
oh
frugal heat proof ice proof incredibly
friendly independent
being healing antiseptic
i don't have enough for that
someone i believe so it does oh let's
get that one that makes sense
i hope i hope it does redeem
okay
we can get one more thing
i don't know if i want any of the cheap
ones though speed cleaner
yeah how much do the others have 1 200
120 100 1500
for bales bails can get something
1 500
stoves and grills masters have a chance
to create impeccable quality consumables
that use stoves and grills
bales looks like someone who would like
to grill
but
yeah you know what we'll buy a grill
we'll buy grill not now remind me of it
we only have 444 simoleons right now
thank you made the crowd louder than
last year hell yeah please do
please do please come to talk to me
there's already so many kf planning to
come to dokomi even from outside of
germany so like wow i'm kind of nervous
but
this is so exciting last year there were
some kf people and i was really glad
they were there because like the chances
were really high that nobody was gonna
be there and like tickets were sold out
the moment it was like before it was
announced and and and then
uh they had way way less um
um
what's the word
the maximum of people they could let in
was way smaller i can't find the word
capacity capacity uh
in the whole convention and also in the
live uh hall
so the seats were like pretty empty
one seat open in between probably more
than that yeah because they just didn't
let that many people in i hope we can
fill the whole the whole hall please
please please oh
i'm getting hungry
um
it's been two hours now
but i've been productive here oh let's
see um maybe we should uh speed this up
and get a cowboy uh 444 we need to paint
a little bit more let's see we need to
paint a bit more outside i don't get it
what was what was that with the
oh oh look she's so happy skilled up
notable newcomer
pretty tasty she's so happy
phone notebook is it a notebook
no
oh
uh does someone know
where that
maybe here public image ah fan points
one i found it but like how do i use the
fame here
whoa
oh
what can we do with one fan point uh
corporate partnership upload videos for
increased fame and money return
uploads from the video station music
station will earn someone more fame than
normal in addition sano's influence will
become a commodity that corporate brands
covet as mean as a means of reaching
their target audience sana will
occasionally receive phone calls from a
corporate ad agency with a timed request
to upload a video for an immediate but
do i need equipment for that i don't
have any any equipment for that
networking easier socialization now we
don't need that
chance noticeable chance to gain bonus
fame from skills and careers there's
just something about sana that makes you
stand out from the crowd and makes other
streams take notice by holding this
aspect of her personality there's a
chance that any single skill or
career-based action from here on out may
catch the public's attention giving son
an extra boost of fame
um
this sounds the most useful because we
get money but
do we need a
to buy the whole equipment
not sure
i guess let's go this now
a plus from the video station and music
station will earn some more fame does
someone know how this works
check the whole skill tree
i mean i don't have the points for it
now
oh but i have to go upwards right
[Music]
we can combine things that's okay we're
just saying it's an item if i remember
okay okay one second need to drink water
[Music]
music station and vegetation are
specific items okay maybe let's get a
video station
video
[Music]
no
no not video no not video gaming
recreation just vicky
video station video station
oh dear we can not afford that 1
500.
the more choices video station the more
views video station
okay
wow it looks like looks like a streamer
set up yo
okay we have to work for that
that's like free paintings yeah sana can
do it
[Music]
but you know she's the only one really
earning money here at the moment what
about those part jobs when are they
going
uh
but still
i thought she's focused we should do an
emotional painting
[Music]
mathematical diagram again
aspirations
in her uniform when she comes back she
also she's already gone
okay she just had a quick cry
what are you doing
do sit-ups okay okay quick quick
almost level up almost
she's learning logic right now oh
that's so useful
while drawing normally you have to play
chess or something
to do that
milestone complete nice
complete ten excellent paintings we will
write three paintings
okay uh
and
now let's draw a landscape
okay
um
oh my god the research is swimming
let's look at this can i do something
with watch birds
you guys are watching birds too now
oh [\h__\h] you broke it
um
iris
repair you have been repairing school
don't you
uh
handing this too
iris i'm counting on you
i was you just she looks so happy she
must have done something again
oh bob there's a twitter bird
[Music]
is really like the the main character
today fauna and sana
did you see the crazy face of santa and
the thumbnail it's like insane oh what
about so many birds oh my god oh
bailey's brought home money how much
[Music]
56. she did some superb work too nice
bails let me look at you
oh baby stuff
very stuff what's up
this uh suits you well although your
teeth still um freak me out
they
how's it going
you look weird
but cute uniform looks good on you
oh you're doing a great job favorites
how about you know through some how
about doing some after work fishing or
something what do you feel about that
are you doing well
yes okay
oh my god there's a [\h__\h] crocodile
well bands won't feel just comfortable
here
oh my god
okay let's let's uh go fishing next to
crocodile
oh look at the ducks
they look so fake
there she goes fishing
[Music]
she's
fishing
let's go bales
get that fish
go get that fish
all right all right you know that uh
fauna has finished then well let's take
care of the cheeks
what can we do
actions
ah create animal treats at the fridge
yeah friendly treat
do it
and sana finished once again six seven
eight oh
that is a
very good price
let's go
may is doing pretty bad you'll be fine
oh chicken this this one is eggy is
always in in the in the building
eggy
thank you oh don't don't get too close
to the kitchen counter or i'll make
scrambled eggs out of you by accident
and get leftovers
[Music]
cooked mac and cheese no no no no why
would you do that sims are so stupid
there's a [\h__\h] of mac and cheese in the
fridge
no need to cook it now
once momma is done with that you take a
shower
iris wants milk no no milk for you no
stop stop with the milk i don't like
milk
[\h__\h] uh looks like the fish in this area
are too crafty for bells try fishing
elsewhere until she has more skill or
try using more valuable [\h__\h]
okay forget that
uh just go to toilet
kiana is calling again what is it males
i need to challenge myself a new job
might be the solution what do you think
i don't think you should do it
stay in holo
stay in hollow
you're probably right i should stay put
for now is what piano says
thanks bails for the advice
i don't know why she keeps on calling
bails
bills have just been delivered oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] 856.
that is almost all of my money
smile to the side
hi
there you go
uh bills
bills can you pay the bills
bails bills
funny
so funny
[Music]
so
it is time for more animals let's get
cows
uh purchase animal wait we haven't we
don't have money we have oh wait we have
535 thanks for the painting
um we can get one cow
let's get a cow let's get the spotted
one
let's go
damn you fake bro
beautiful oh it looks so beautiful
beautiful the world is your
paradise enjoy kyle oh my god you're so
cute
uh socialize
pet
what what are those jokes tell joke
about not having a cow man
what does that mean
ask how for lottery numbers
but so then what are the lottery numbers
and tell a joke tell a joke do it
how many sounds
[Music]
okay understandable when you get
attacked by by these like that i
understand um
that you would drop the trash but can
you um why did you even come here thanks
bonnie that's crony
why didn't you do that
apply my treatment do they have mites
[\h__\h]
oh no
okay be careful and they are irritated
apparently
go away bails
uh maybe you also befriend the cow
pet
complain about mowing don't complain
about moving to the car if you have a
cow that comes with it
maybe you
look at the birds bails
okay beautiful we have a full farm now
but i want the llama oh he's so happy
you're so cute
you're about to sell the masterpieces
these are very sure you want to do wait
a second wait a second
wait to a gallery
[Music]
wait sorry
but i will get
here
[Music]
huh wasn't it just six out six thousand
no four thousand sell art gallery sell
so art gallon yeah why would i do
anything else
oh my god they're playing chicken
sitting next to how cute uh
wait what why can't i not get another
can i only have one
what is the capacity of this thing
[Music]
can i not get another
baby
one per shed
i have no space for another one unless i
get rid of this whole thing
[Laughter]
um
hey
this is uh eggy eggy is so social
oh look at them
oh
eggy wants some company that's why eggy
is also always in the house but now eggy
can be outside with a cow instead
and he just wants to be close to someone
how
okay and by the way how are you doing
happiness level very low here's some
dust
it begins nothing meets the feeling of
crushing that final boss level whenever
mumei is gaming
she is as one with the universe is it
safe to say she likes video gaming
i love these prompts every time when
they come up with you know with the myth
and the council family
and they're questioning is it safe to
say
myth and counsel and hope like video
gaming
no no no no no no we hate it we're in
the wrong job yeah we hate gaming why
are we why are we even in whole life man
it's such a depressing job because we
hate gaming so much
no yes she does she definitely does like
it
mom
you made a masterpiece you're so
confident aren't you let's make some
more
how about impression painting
i never did that before i think all
right and then
makes one happy now happiness still very
low what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
get leftovers by the way uh
befriended and very low
can you
go get valuables
bell's got charisma
oh just by talking to iris oh look at
the
famous otp
getting an
[Music]
oh they're done talking damn it
oh where are they going walking like
that oh never mind they separated sad
did we get did we get something valuable
here's more dust
would have broken oh [\h__\h]
the good toilet is broken
repair
ah
oh but crony no iris we'll fix the pc
somebody fixed the pc thank god
a house of streamers only one pc
can't survive for very long
this is kind of in character mummy is so
weird like yes she would walk into a
room without saying anything and just
watch iris cleaning a toilet
yeah i can see that
yes
yes [\h__\h] clean the toilet do it
clean the toilet that you're you're at
fault for breaking
mm-hmm
yeah you missed a spot you missed a spot
[Laughter]
iris and there's another spot there
people fixing yeah there's absolutely
nothing like you're doing nothing here
this is air air
toilet repairing
how are you fixing this toilet you're
not doing anything
also you know she's barefoot in here
that's disgusting
a little clothes for comfort yeah this
room is very small
push here push your movement push here
tell her how it feels to be pranked
no okay
chat with iris you're not having
any conversation dell
wow
i love that that looks so cool
nice
we have so much money now and we
and we built this beautiful farm but we
can only have one animal i'm so sad
i need to feed you though four dollars
to feed the spotted cow
let's do it
i want to see you feed the cow and then
i want to see you milk the cow
[Music]
oh cow very happy you dropped something
but okay the chickens will pick it up
clean spotted cow
even though it's already clean but i
just want to see it
let's see chicken you're in the way
[Music]
oh that is so
this is nature this is nature at work
beautiful
so loving
just like right there fell asleep this
is the cutest thing this is egg no it's
jimmy
it's jimmy
this episode is so wholesome for me this
makes me so happy
oh
i really improved this lot too i'm so
proud
this will happen proud how are these
chickens doing you guys need some food
we already have food i already scattered
it once i think it's only in like one
day probably
is there are your eggs right now
free eggs oh there's some uh late layers
i didn't say to stop
are you the cow
ivana building an army tooth crosser
nah
she's just you know caring taking care
of this family
let's put the eggs
chocolate egg
blue egg what the [\h__\h]
wait
[Music]
why we have a chocolate egg a blanket
yes what what does that mean
the game knows the world fawn's
discovered information about a blue egg
which has been added to the notebook
learn more click the link
oh chocolate egg
make by feed hen a chocolate treat we
didn't do that animal treat and the next
egg delay will be chocolate
ah
and can we use an ingredient in any
recipe that requires chocolate instead
of chocolate
ah i see or eaten for a burst of
happiness
uncommon
part of a complete breakfast see even
the game says so nutella is a part of
breakfast i'm blue if i was green i
would die
i'm live on the screen i would die that
wouldn't be that yes that was the lyric
stella did never die if i was green i
would die what
friend hand a fruity treat animal trait
and the next a day lay will be blue blue
eggs are used to complete certain iran's
for the grocery owner
and grocery delivery villagers that live
in hempford on bagley what
to complete certain rants
[Music]
animal treats wow okay interesting so
wait did we learn how to make a
chocolatey treat no
how do i learn to make a chocolatey
treat
you need to make more treats
yeah something for the other part of the
for something for the other the other
town mm-hmm i guess
eh i don't want to move
we could we could move the whole lot
though
oh you were eating the flowers
no no santa no [\h__\h] you santa
we don't it's not it's not christmas
anymore we're in a different uh
season right now okay we have other
things to do
we don't want to i want to see another
spicy mushroom
where did you get that
how'd you get that and she why does
mummy have spicy mushroom and bananas in
her inventory
oh did the dust bunnies
[Music]
walking around here again is it iggy no
it's kentucky they just said they're
like they live here
kentucky's like i want to check out the
bedroom wow nice you got some nice stuff
here yo
you know
amanda you could buy some freaking
furniture for my chicken coop as well
why the hell am i not good enough i'm
the [\h__\h] rooster in this house i'm
the only guy
in his house and you guys don't think
i'm good enough
you buy us some nice furniture
where the [\h__\h] is my herman miller chair
huh
no no no we don't use a german military
we use a shitty chair too
okay kentucky chill chill the [\h__\h] out
or i'll make some kentucky fried chicken
out of you cool door okay
this one is very happy
content yeah attention content
[Music]
okay he's like okay
you guys you guys furniture isn't the
best here but you guys are living
on um
on a budget as well i see okay
never mind me then so they're still
wearing the christmas
outfits you could change your christmas
outfits
kentucky you're gonna eat the bunnies
try to eat the bunnies
you get some valuables
splurge
slurp no
[Music]
wants to sleep soon
you know what you can sleep now
uh
wasn't i was a babysitter where the hell
are you going to babysit
oh she only babysits on the weekend oh
okay she has a lot of time
how about
oh who made this
crony
cronie
[Music]
we already have mac and cheese in the
fridge i stopped her once and she did it
anyway
i want to make some magic
okay there we go
um experiment there we go and then we
put this
11 servings of mac and cheese into the
fridge also sell this
sell this
all right
and
oh she's cleaning the toilet so nice but
you don't need to do that get some
leftovers
and
actually iris should be the one fixing
this [\h__\h] again
both donuts are broken
okay stop experimenting you really need
to repair those toilets
[Music]
vacuum lightly there we go
perfect
how about you sleep early today
and sa na na na uh are you done eating
yeah
clean up and then draw again how about a
realism painting
hundred dollars
beautiful
okay i'm so occupied today i'm doing so
much here i've accomplished so much
they only got the idol meetings
um
yeah it's a good question how do they
keep on breaking the toilets if they
supposedly
don't use them
[Music]
yes you can paint in-game like pictures
but you have to take them at the spot
as far as i know at least that's that's
what it how it was back in the day
clean lightly how do you why didn't you
clean it properly
okay
[Music]
all um and then before you start
pranking [\h__\h] again
i'm gonna sleep
okay
[Applause]
not only in the sims i've been
decorating and accomplishing things also
in my apartment today guys
i
i started
um
a session since yesterday i've been like
putting paintings and mirrors and other
things on my walls like i i realized you
know what i have a hammer and a nail i'm
not really good at putting together
furniture but what i can do
oh sunflower is putting things on walls
at least that should be in the range of
possibilities for me so i put all kinds
of things on walls that i was waiting to
put on walls yeah
for example right in front of me i put
up a huge uh 2022 whole life calendar
right now i have a picture of whole life
gamers in front of me for april it's
really pretty
with some cherry blossoms
[Music]
uh november and december
i already looked at the picture it looks
really cool too
it's it's not the standard um
boring default picture i also got a
calendar like a standing calendar
that has the default pictures
which was boring so i didn't use it
but i put up the proper the big calendar
that you have to hang i think it's maybe
from comic market i'm not sure like i
have so much merch i'm not sure what was
sold where
um
yeah
yeah yeah and then i had some more wall
scrolls that i didn't uh
um that i didn't put up yet so i added
some more wall scrolls on my wall
and i put up a mirror in the
in my idol meeting room like a really
fancy memory i went to zara home the
other day hi tanjo hello i went to zara
home and did you know that zara has like
a furniture slash home decoration store
did you know that did you know that
if we order the whole live calendar it
has to be for 2024 are you saying that
because it won't arrive until then
yeah
[Music]
it depends depends
the anime nyc one has everyone's
birthdays oh i didn't know oh that's
cute
i only sell cloves here no i'm sure if
you look for a tower at home i'm sure
you'll find one
at least in the bigger cities probably
uh
i went to dara home
i got some stuff i got a new laundry
basket
for
i decided to get a laundry basket only
for the towels to have them separate to
try to get
those not too close to cat hairs that's
mine that's my strategy
um
woman what are you doing you should do
something why are you not eating why
why are you not taking care of your
needs
eat and then toilet and then sleep
it's that easy
and what was i saying oh yeah i got a
new laundry basket and i got a dust
thingy with some really pretty feathers
i was like you know what oh actually
it's this thing on this icon right now
a duster a duster with feathers
[Music]
choosing the toilet too okay okay
thousand one wow
that one
turned out good
a feather does it yeah
um and i bought
uh what did i buy i bought some picture
frames
[Laughter]
so i also printed out some pictures not
on photo paper just a normal paper but i
was like whatever and i put them into
the frames they're really fancy frames
they're like they're like um not normal
frames yeah they're nice frames and um
and i bought uh a mirror but the mirror
is
not like a normal shape it's actually
like unevenly shaped it looks really
cool
and then the edges are like kind of like
uh like they look like they're made out
of some stone material on the edges i
thought the
the uneven shape looks really nice so i
put that into my
into my uh groningen
what happened
sleep
oh because moment one is on ah
i'm sleeping that one
um what was i saying
[Music]
i thought it would look really nice in
my island waiting room that's what i was
saying uh what else did i get oh yeah
and i got a big
big golden um
thing to put a plant in
a pot but like it's not only the pot
it's um
like standing on some kind of
um thing to make it taller mm-hmm so
because i got that
i had to buy a big plant that would fit
perfectly into the pot
so
i went to the to the flower store again
today and i got a new plant
yeah
it's a big one
it looks like a tree it's a masterpiece
oh nice
i'm so hungry i'm getting so hungry
again
[Music]
it's so big but it was actually not even
that heavy so i had no problem carrying
it home but i always have to buy them
one by one because i don't have a car
and i am alone so i can only carry one
plant every time i go to the plant store
now so slowly and surely i've been
getting more and more plants and now i
have another one and i really like it
i hope i will not destroy it
yeah got any snacks you can eat real
quick
some chocolate and stuff yeah probably
yeah but i guess for the moment it might
help you
know
[Music]
good morning bells
good morning what are you gonna do
let's follow
bales nice ass crack
snowbee
mama really revoked my plan privileges
for one specific plan
only one specific plant
[Music]
my other plants are doing okay right now
okay
the illusion of eating
helps me get over my hunger for a little
while
macaroni and cheese for breakfast
of course all i eat is macaroni and
cheese
every day every morning every can i say
mama donai instead of mom
[Laughter]
i mean llama tony
[Music]
it's confusing sometimes
crony and cheese did i say crawling
cheese what's going on i said macaroni
or my crony and cheese put some cheese
on on cronie and you have macaroni and
cheese that was soup
you're insane
[Music]
casting a spell on the foot see
now it tastes better
[Laughter]
it's her um
her um
um
a ritual before eating you know have to
cast her spell oh you see
more
i don't know
okay
[Music]
work for bail starts in an hour oh wow
she has a perfect sleep rhythm she woke
up before work to get some
um food in her system and she has to go
to work at 5 00 am so that's really
respectable
whenever
um
i had early shifts at work where i had
to um
leave to get to work around like
5 5 20 or so
um i had to
uh
you know wake up early to do my makeup
and all that but i didn't have enough
time to eat breakfast so i never had
breakfast when i had the early shift why
are you not eating
go eat
don't talk to bails
[Music]
look so
excited to go to work
[Music]
just wake up another hour to
i can't that would mean i would get up
at like
three or two a.m
who wants to do that i can't sleep that
early
also because my shifts were not always
early shifts it would switch like
sometimes early shift sometimes late
shift so
[Music]
yum yum yum yum yum
yum
okay
don't know how much longer we're gonna
do this because we did the things that i
wanted to do uh except for moving house
i think we're happy living here grow
crops get chick
uh oh we need baby chicks i don't know
how did i make chicks because up until
now
the eggs were not um um you know
hatchable maybe we need to leave them in
the coop
uh and we could go to the pub but i
don't wanna
i don't wanna
maybe maybe not
if we don't go out with everyone then i
would be okay with it go cook with
produce oh yeah i need to cook with
products well mac and cheese needs eggs
right so they're probably using the eggs
let me see something
uh
open
there's six eggs in here
if they cook something
with eggs will will it be less
[Music]
will they automatically use it or do i
have to tell them i think i think it's
automatically
fawn is a vegan in this game oh
wait
it says vegetarian approved this uh this
is adequate oh yeah it's uh it said um
vegan mac and cheese
or at least vegetarian mac and cheese it
didn't say that yeah yeah i am should be
okay she's happy
[Music]
iris i'm watching you
don't do it good girl good girl i'm so
proud of you
okay iris good morning it's time to feed
the chickens
uh
scatter food nearby
wakey wakey as well good morning
and let's see how many
eggs
slightly dirty eggs ready to collect six
uh how do i clean and clean coop there
we go
let's see how she does it
let's look from here
oh
nice she got something on that i think
one super
vitality fertilizer
in the oh is it chicken poop
oh you get fertilizers aka poop out of
there
and then i can use that on flowers
ah wait what does uprooting plant mean
do i have to do that
what does that mean let's try that too
fauna fauna fauna you're working hard no
the don't run away oh i guess you
already put it into your in her
inventory the stuff that she does need
okay how convenient
perfect oh no that means throwing it
away don't do it
don't throw away in a plant i didn't
know what that meant
oh dear is it
ah now it's dead
promonto bean blender veils has been
promoted as a barista to bean blender
she'll now make an additional 14
simoleons per hour
nice and she received a bonus
good job bails
wow
so inspiring
good job bills so proud of you
so proud of you do do something i don't
know
[Music]
make yourself happy somehow
look at the birds
watch the boots
congratulations bae will be the ceo soon
yeah of star bakes
so funny
congratulations bails on the
congratulations bails
and views about cats
yeah that seems like something she would
do
i have a collab with um fauna tomorrow
actually right tomorrow
i think it's tomorrow
so i think we will be infusing each
other and
infusing
and infusing each other about cats
chickens everywhere they're so adorable
we need to we need to
make make them happy too we need to pet
them
oh my god
remind of dinosaur heritage
okay let's do that i love the prompts
so you are originally a dinosaur
it didn't like that
it did not like that at all
sorry about that sorry if we're telling
you the reality that's like telling a
cat that the cat is a cat hooray
maybe
you you everything's okay you're not a
dinosaur
sorry for saying that here's a hug
no no no
you need to take care of the chickens
okay so that was uh cluckers cluckers
should be happy now
uh how about
encouraged to hold stalks
stop doing other [\h__\h]
[Music]
what do you think about holding egg
stocks
huh
fight no it does not want the egg stops
okay no stocks for uh kentucky
oh she really wants to go to the toilet
no no no no no and hug
ask chicken if it expects foul play
tell joke about pecking order
do it do it
hello the unawful box 2 gaming console
wait we can buy the thing right it's
launching soon and their marketing team
thinks that you're the perfect celebrity
partner to hitch their wagon to oh
sponsorship
complete one of the following options in
the next 24 hours to fulfill this
contract use the video station uh to
upload any video footage you've captured
your ad agency will edit you into a clip
for social media and send you a payout
for uh usage of your likeness
uh gamers love brands just get angry and
yell at the video station camera a bunch
and say whatever comes to mind if you
upload a video with an angry vlog your
payment will be even larger
they want me to be angry in a vlog for
the sponsorship
okay so either upload any video photos
you've captured or upload an angry vlog
okay
well we do have the money now for
um
[Music]
for the video station
isn't that just a kiwa attention no
radio station there you go
well now i cannot even afford this one
apparently this one gives more views
oh i want the table like that it's so
big
only two monitors though kusa
oh it's a
it's an interesting mixer with a
keyboard like
what is that camera though
it's on an iphone
i don't know
then should we get rid of the other one
shut the wait
maybe we can we don't have the space
but
this fits in here
maybe
we never use this
um apartment after all
nice music
so now this belongs to sana i'm sure a
lot of other of the girls will want to
use it but this belongs to santa okay
she made this happen
adam cooper oh hd camera ring light i
want the ring light yo
that's so cool we can like add so many
things what
hd camera oh
well that will improve our youtube
content so much
it just likes lights bright white oh
damn that's so cool
that's so cool
okay record video i can't make an angry
one i can make a cheerful one i'm not
angry right now but cheerful should be
okay oh no product private review
huh
a gadget like what do i have to pick
they said
they're launching a gaming console so
the market even thinks that you're the
perfect
pitcher pitched your wagon to
use the video station to upload any
video footage you've captured our
attention
okay
i think it means you can do whatever the
hell you want
and we will edit it so it looks like you
did it for
us so even if you do a video about
fashion we will edit it so that it looks
like he made a video about our
gaming machine
yeah and angry is just a bonus
okay let's start cheerful blogton i want
to see
everybody move it's saturday time
unless you want this to be a
collaboration
let's see harvani she doing it
maybe
don't do it in your pajama are you doing
it right now
she's doing it but she's not looking at
the camera she's distracted
i need to look at the camera
the gen z kimbalaya
what the [\h__\h] is happening to uh
what's going on is it the toilet
[Music]
she's scared hide under the covers
pecked it
the rooster pets at her
ah their person was so mean fana is
getting a bit fearful of the oh no
what did i miss
oh no
oh no she's so scared of the rooster
maybe maybe we need a chiara to live
here to take care of the chickens
oh no
she's hiding
moana
[Music]
[Laughter]
taking a panicked pulp
oh my god um no not on the pre
you're gonna get that only panic but
pranked
oh no
it's a panic
[Music]
oh poop
[\h__\h]
she's purple what she looks so purple
why is she so purple i think it was just
uh the weird lightning in here [\h__\h]
she's still she's still panicking
[Music]
um they gonna
ah
plain water no no no you're fixing and
cleaning those toilets
oh my god
oh my god oh my god
oh that was cute they were she was
sitting on the hay ball thingy
oh
all right
oh indeed
more indeed um oh oh i think she's ready
to get milked
next harvest normal milk
uh hungerful okay i want to milk her
fun are you good let's forget chickens
for a while let's deal with a cow okay
you'll feel so much better
can we do it
milk spotted cow okay
okay
oh sana is done i think is she done no
not yet
let's do this
now
this is where the action happens
[Music]
oh
wait wait
oh my god
fascinating
nature at work
wait where the hell are we
we go
let me let me
take a good look at that
you like it
[Music]
let me squeeze you
oh so much milk um fresh milk oh what
the [\h__\h]
don't kick me [\h__\h]
no the bucket
kentucky doesn't care kentucky continues
to sleep well okay uh i'm happy and
dirty well [\h__\h] you you [\h__\h] it up
yourself let me clean you
no milk for today guys
we're not we're not getting any milk out
of this
[Music]
oh man
okay here there you go
oh
refill feet ah i don't have to clean uh
the cow directly
i can just fill this one up here
no milk
oh happy vlogging what do you want to
call this um
playing
uh
finishing
kirby today
today
i am
happily but also sadly finishing
my playthrough
of
one of my
favorite games
kirby
the new one
and
even if it's gonna take long
i am oh [\h__\h] i can't write more okay
uh
see you there poyo
all
right she did it so now i have to send
that in
[Music]
okay good job how do we send that in
ghost
no
in the inventory
maybe
delete edit
upload
do i just have to upload it
let me look at the text again
where did it go no it's it's gone
where is it
i can't find it edit first
okay
[Music]
let us try but they said they would edit
it
they said they would do it for us
oh ours look what you have done
and
clean okay
just upload but if you want to make the
video better you can edit oh okay but
it's it's not for not really for us it's
for that management if not management
for that company will it automatically
be counted as
yeah it did say upload anything within
24 hours
okay i feel like i hear kirby sounds
what the [\h__\h]
how long does this take
pretty long
uh
for you there's nothing to look at there
okay paula i know you're feeling bad
right now what's the reason
what's the reason
gross prank okay once again it's
latoya's fault what can we do to make
irish stop pranking her friends
continuously again and again and again
and again
let's do uncomfortably vacuum
[Music]
oh man
it's not having a good time
uh sauna quite the media production
skill nicer
may you feed them some dust even though
they're not so helpful anymore these
days
okay irish is done
uh
throw away let's take some care of this
apartment man must be the chickens
that's for the chicken no no no other
reason
we need to befriend the chick at the cow
it probably didn't like us enough yet
and that's why i didn't let us milk it
properly i want that milk though i want
that fresh milk from you
please oh please
oh when you're happy aren't you how
about a treat how about a friendly treat
i have a friendly treat for you
you'll love it don't stomp on the
chickens please uh they like being
stepped on by me but not by cows i think
oh it didn't work
i can't
[Music]
i don't know why wait wait wait what did
that say
uh successfully edited and can't be
under that anymore okay so now we upload
it
yeah
oh let's go to inventory i want to do it
right oh no it's gone
[Music]
ah it was here in this inventory
and upload
there we go youtube let's go
subscribers
look at this beautiful new video
on the bottom left cinderella a new song
cover did you listen to it please listen
to it more than once listen to it twice
three times maybe per day it's a short
one so why the hell not
thank you
are you talking to her through the wall
wow this is some fitting walls man
okay sana has done some important work
today so i should deserve some time off
in the shower and in the toilet
uh
i think
we will
now
how do we
[Music]
if okay one more time let me ask maybe
someone can give me an answer if i leave
the eggs in the coop will they
eventually hatch
[Music]
is it that easy or do i have to do
something extra
also my nose is so itchy
there's some some cat hair on it i think
i keep on trying to get rid of it but
i don't know
you have to incubate them
oh so i have to take the
is there an egg incubator no [\h__\h] way
what about you know how it works
naturally how does it work
incubator there's no incubator
there's a room called the incubator
which is a whole freaking room but no
no then it should be
[Music]
make sure your chickens are happy leave
the eggs in the coop and they'll hatch
naturally after two days ah
it sounds like you copy pasted that out
of google thank you
okay so it will it will happen in here
just if i leave them and now we'll have
little babies huh that footage is ace
our editors are already recording it to
meet the needs of the client but don't
worry i know they're going to love it
keep your phone handy we'll ring you
with another opportunity soon
[Music]
hey
okay
bales do you also want to be a beetle
how about you study some trends before
you join holo life
oh sana what are you wearing i never see
you wearing that
mummy is getting called
by kiana who why is it
why is it always me who's calling
how's that
possible huh
yeah i wanted to come over but i
literally ghosted her
mommy
they hate each other oh no
yeah yeah yeah it don't be like that
no it don't feel like that we may never
go smee
never
chat with me
[Music]
you were supposed to debut before
council anyway oh it's so cute you're so
cute you're so cute
they're bathing in the sun
look this is so cute
i'm so
so in love
they keep on trying to stay close to the
cows
[Music]
oh my god we need a name for the cloud
too i didn't name it yet name
clubber oh
[Music]
sorry that's a beautiful name but it
will be noedo my one and only cow i'm so
proud of this cow
yes
no to happy
i know what you're very happy
that i'm so cute
i could look at this forever
oh
i'm trying to get the
into the shade of the cow oh they're
becoming one oh no
so oh they're mating
making babies is that how chickens make
babies they just become one
oh my god they're so in sync
this is nature oh they looked
[Music]
i guess you could record a video
inspiring vlog
nice
draw
confident painting
just okay we're gonna play until we have
chickens okay does that sound good i
think it sounds good
wait
does that mean we have mites again i
don't think so it's just you can do this
anytime right grumpiness enraged how do
we make them happy
should we just ignore them do they get
happy on their own
why are they so mad
sounds like a plan indeed it does it is
a plan that's it that's what we're doing
any fish
but maybe not here right because you
can't really get any fish here
even though i added fish
yeah there's eel in here maybe maybe i
don't have the bait and the power to get
eels down
that's probably it
oh collaboration iris crony coming up
soon
oh yeah so an odd job for you again
which one is it gonna be coconut milk
real milk
uh-huh no skill required
uh photography gardening charisma we
have charisma
uh this one is sand sculpted judge
and the seashells
she'll probably not be really happy to
see us again
and oh the tv hookup help
is there again the one that we
previously broke we should probably also
not go here let's go do the charisma one
we're playing both of those people
well ah actually you know what we never
showed up for the seashells one she
doesn't even know what we look like
we could go there which one pays more
this one pays more ah but this one is
per hour and this one is one time
begins us up
oh see this one was at a certain time 2
a.m
let's do this one we want to go now
let's go now
do your best oh no she's drinking milk
she's gonna drink some milk are you sure
you can do that now
sure you got the time for that
befriended
free dust
oh she's going now yeah she's off to
work
good luck cronie
don't break anything please don't break
the the the
the uh
sand castle thingy or whatever we're
doing
is is it happening no it's not happening
why can't we not make them happy anymore
oh she's taking out the trash oh no oh
well that will make them happy too
probably
[Music]
the kirby sounds were coming from these
animals i realized now
you got this cronie sam
can't wait to get fried or dumped into
the usual room oh welcome to the
membership yeah
thank you very much
mommy look at those birds
maybe mummy should also be friendly
chickens this one is content is anyone
not happy this one is
okay
this one is content
this one is
okay eggy eggy what do you need
oops
yeah whatever
eggy
uh pet eggy and
pet eggy again
and play it with eggy and iris just made
a video
can we
uh
[Music]
just focus focus on your job
all right sign up once again finish the
painting oh
this is so inspiring climbing up the
mountain
yeah yeah yeah yeah
welcome to the mountain top says kelly
this is calla clomping up the mountain
wow
money raining
noise
one more while you're doing so well and
fauna
what do we have to do
uh
clean and rage still what do we do about
them
try try bonding with them fauna
your nature should be able to do it
she's thinking about cats maybe we
should get a cat for her she can't go
there
oh she can't go there
not why go here
she's stuck
between the chairs can i move you
no we'll move move fauna
[Music]
reset can you can you can you go
somewhere
[\h__\h] why why this was never a problem
before
this was never around before in this
chair
i didn't move anything here are you
stupid
[Music]
move object is on
no
all right i'm moving away for now
don't get stuck again
go here there we go
oh wait wait one more second
[Music]
all right now let's try let's try um
should i collect the honey would that
make them happy
let's try to vomit
somebody
it's not scary it's not scary it's not
scary
yeah
nature
wow okay that went well
that went very well are they happy now
no they're still enraged
okay um change would you be keeping it
and take
uh collect the honey
but we have to keep a suit we're fine
we're fine
so cool
it goes up with the brown color
[Music]
the chickens might be kind of in danger
right next to the bees i hope they get
along they're still enraged though what
the [\h__\h]
i don't know what to do with them oh
okay
yeah give them something to look at
[Music]
beautiful
absolutely beautiful inspiring
i love it uh oh no food here uh refill
oh we can clean the shed is it dirty
[Music]
she goes inside to fill it up but it's
outside
ah there's like a hole there oh
you can't see what she's doing but she's
filling up the food i think
oh and she's gonna clean it afterwards
[Music]
and i she's doing so much hard work man
the protagonist of today's episode
are you gonna sell this
and
oh [\h__\h] look what's broken again iris
wake up
no
no molina
not your fault
go in here
iris has to fix and clean that
does she not learn from from this whole
charade does she never learn from it she
has to be she has to continuously
clean up her own mess
oh we have no more no more
uh macaroni and cheese it's time to make
make macaroni and cheese
[Music]
hope nobody gets ahead of us
yay
stand
parts
at least that's money we're basically
actually we're we are somehow in an
indirect way making money from her
pranks because she breaks the toilets
and she repairs them and for every time
we get an upgrade part that's like about
10 to 20 bucks
[Laughter]
we're making money it's smart it's a
business she's a business lady
there we go cooking up some nice
macaroni and cheese
macaroni and cheese seems to be so
common like outside of
my country but we don't really eat
macaroni and cheese it's not that
popular uh cronie was the best joke that
ever had at the competition just wise do
you mean divine maybe artistically
critical there are adults who say she
was born for such a role additionally
she caught three cheaters how do you
cheat at a sand castle competition just
ask
crony oodle
oh humble to have such a legend amongst
their ranks the beach administration
paid cronie a bonus for grace in their
competition
of course she deserves that she graces
everywhere she goes
out come your autumn's rating has
finally approved 105 simoleons plus a 10
uh simoleon's tip and relationship
gained with darion [\h__\h] darian we don't
need darian in our life we're good on
our own
but thank you thank you i guess now
we're just waiting here for
the uh
for the macaroni
for the
my cronie and cheese
sit good job crony
so proud
uh also wanna take off that big episode
chickens are sleeping cow is sleeping
you're cute oh i just realized there's a
there's a chicken a versa thingy on here
ah
[Music]
asleep
and uh are you done are you done are you
done save rock no
toilet okay
clean lightly oh
oh mommy
video gaming level four
okay
[Music]
oh hunger wait oh wait can you hurry up
please
hi uncle go home
when is the food ready iris
we have some more salt some more pepper
i'm hungry
it's done
grab all servings
she took something
from there all right we got some
servings here crony corny no sleep
get leftovers
uh who else is hungry
liz is hungry
you're hungry no don't cook
what are you trying to cook
grilled cheese we have macaroni and
cheese
broken
i still get leftovers
priorities
damn it that was on it
what was that
circle
[Music]
maybe the capital matters
though
okay yeah that way
[Music]
i'm just saying i think we have to clean
it up manually all right um
iris you're done no sleepy time you're
gonna repair the even if it wasn't you
who broke it i don't think you can prank
a fridge that would be too cru
cruel um but you have so much skills in
repairing now so
[Music]
yo
clean that up and now we all go to sleep
again and rinse and repeat
yeah yeah
come on you can do it don't i mean it's
kind of dangerous with lack of sleep
iris you cannot go to sleep yet next
ring that broke what is the sink
this [\h__\h] apartment everybody's
breaking the fingers and sims if you buy
cheap objects they're more likely to
break
so
yeah
it will be like that
no no don't play in the puddle
if you're doing so well then you should
draw
all right clean it up and then you can
finally sleep
hooray
[Music]
painting level eight
that's pretty high i think maximum was
10.
really
we've um the ability to draw
masterpieces being relatively famous and
opinion level eight this is the kind of
lion that you draw
and this is supposed to be your
confident work really
really
ah she can't sleep next to iris oh dear
oh dear all right we have one more bed
here
not cursed enough
it's a masterpiece of course it is art
block yeah yeah oh work for bill starts
in about an hour bales are you good
oh [\h__\h] wake up wake up wake up you're
working an hour you need to get
leftovers quickly although there's food
at work they they do eat at work so it's
not too bad
there are two toilets there they're
clean and not broken and you choose to
fertilize
the bush over there which is so far away
crony
why
i don't understand sims
just go there
[Music]
someone understands sim's logic because
i don't understand it please explain it
to me she's kinky like that
i mean i did put it there so that they
can use it in case both toilets are
broken at the same time but now
everything's cool
weird
all right granny now you're feeling
better it's time to eat next to the
insane bales she will be happy to have
some company
and feel less insane
oh you didn't even eat all that okay
oh
switch off please but you're gonna go to
work
you gotta go to work now you can go pee
at work
go go quick
that's going to take a while to go to
work if you walk like that so you can
carry so
[Music]
bill's off to work
and then she can finally walk normally
again
she'll come back home stinky though
because she can't fill up hygiene
nah
a lot crony
since you're the only one up go make
yourself useful clean up and uh
i say hello to the rooster
rooster didn't even say uh good morning
yet didn't even say kikity can ask what
ruffles feathers
cute
but they don't like the jokes i asked
them
hunger starving oh no and unhappy oh
i'll i'll scatter the father i'm
sleeping right now let me whoa
mommy let me scatter some food sorry
whoa whoa whoa whoa
well cow poop is indeed very stinky
can you
can you clean that cronie is that okay
for you
she's like i will clean the [\h__\h] out of
this barn is gonna look even more
beautiful than i
look like afterwards
no that is impossible i take it back
that is impossible i take it back
good morning good morning
all right
she's doing it for phone that phone is
tired man although actually it's time to
wake up
you're not tired anymore
you're just slacking you just don't want
to clean the shitty barn
huh bell's already back home nice yeah
it was only a two-hour shift
all right uh let's let's see kentucky is
happy now
jamie needs some love
wait we named a hen jimmy
just realized now
makes no sense
[Music]
come on be nice
make up an exciting joke
oh
she's scared now too
ah that chicken was mean vails is
getting a bit fearful of the oh no it's
a chicken
yeah um you guys should not
underestimate the power of chickens okay
they can be
very dangerous
come on be nice be nice
okay they always like the padding
they always like it
who is jimmy what do you mean who's
jimmy do you mean he's famous
chicken lover
bale sort of trainers and chicken love
oh this chicken is such a sweet one vais
has built so much trust with them that
she didn't even get pecked at when
showing some love finally she
understands oh look this chicken is
up in the air
oh
wait let me take a photo
ah
[Music]
it's it's just nice to see this you know
give it give him a hug
bairista
give jimmy a hug
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] i've been talking with
friends
[Music]
dance machine how does it need to do
what what's going what's going on
what
what is it
is it i think it might be her insane
insane trait
or still the effect from getting packed
before but they said that that this one
wouldn't peck her anymore
just talking with friends i think i
think it's her just being insane
scream incoherently um
are you gonna scream incorrectly at
fauna
calm down bails it's all good there are
no ghosts in this apartment
you're gonna be okay bills we're here
for you you know
indonesia's calling i heard you became
friends with santa tookama she's pretty
cool ah
yes they're besties they're all besties
[Music]
is talking to us oh [\h__\h] this car was
dirty fauna
fana
clean clean no idea
clean no idea please
dust bunny caretaker by feeding and
petting dust bunny fauna is keeping our
household dust friends as happy as
possible
just keeping all the animals happy we
haven't seen any foxes or bunnies though
fox is okay because we have a rooster
but do we keep bunnies away also because
we have a rooster
[Music]
i wonder
what does it say
i'll joke about not having cow ask how
about the weather
oh
um
oh look at the chicken racing at my legs
[Music]
uh they liked it so let's try to milk
noel again
try number two yeah that's cuter than
the chicken
yes i am thank you although it's a
difficult task
milk
oh i would like to get a taste of that
good job noodle thanks for the mix it
worked
now cow is happy too because the
pressure is
gone
what are you doing chat with bails let
me look at the milk
[Music]
oh there it is bottle of milk excellent
oh and we have honey too
honey and milk
we still have a treat and we have oh the
super vitality fertilizer sprinkle daily
those are those really make sure your
plant is as healthy as possible and you
have the highest daily quality crops
wait how do we make crops like
love it valentine's day samara
apparently oh [\h__\h]
eh i i want to keep that maybe for a
stream
[Music]
information about a bottle of milk
but what about the chickens what about
the chicks and seed chicks
isn't it about time to
see did you see some cute chicks
maybe tomorrow but tomorrow is love day
tomorrow's valentine's day
i wanna i don't wanna i don't want
valentine's day to be part of today
i wanna make a stream out of that baby
um
oh sorry fauna you were
you were showering sorry about that
oh we're feeding the bunny
your friends no are you friends all your
friends
valuables please
and painting let's go
let's go
now you were supposed to clean uh falabo
can you make thin ice or something
could oh that
we couldn't do that they're pretty
pretty tasty
i've heard that they're very uh
very close
[Music]
water collect eggs to get a hatch in
london and
oh that way around oh everyone just have
to leave though
[Music]
i think i just drank a cat cat ah no
it was on my tongue
i didn't drink it
[Music]
okay then in that case we have to uh
take the eggs collect the eggs
uh eggs ready to go like 12. i want
those six
i need those six
one and two and three
and four
oh we got all the twelve of them
wait
oh my god
none of them are hatchimals
[Music]
uh 18.
she didn't even use the eggs for the
macaroni and cheese
do you not need i guess you're not mean
eggs for macaroni and cheese i guess not
is it only macaroni and cheese is that
all you need
[Laughter]
we need to use the eggs
we need to make it worthwhile
[Music]
yes you don't milk butter no eggs
i'm just saying i mean i mean
skill i want to make something and i
said cook roof produce so i i have to
cook with products
you go to the toilet though
this one
oh there's a broken shower
actually it should be iris
she has freaking cooking one
one
two
okay my main bales have two
skill points in cooking
so bales is just standing there how
about you cook something with eggs um
[Music]
cook
this is only one portion
then you have to say serve
serve lunch
onigiri
what's with eggs
blt no
vegetable onion tomato
maybe a gram meal ground breakfast any
fruit no eggs really
wait nothing here uses eggs
why does the ground breakfast not use
any eggs hello what about baking
it doesn't say anything about
ingredients here so he probably doesn't
use anything
huh make a cake i didn't need it canning
what is
oh
cool
that's new as well
but this doesn't need
eggs either
what did i get the eggs for uh
bales is freaking out again um what if
what if we're single there's some single
meals here this one we're gonna have egg
and milk that we produce ourselves so
the cost will go down from six dollars
to two dollars
wow
oh we can use the honey for honey cake
two eggs for eggs and toast for some
reason it's still four dollars though
what the hell
not a doll
scrambled eggs with bacon
it says tomato here even though there's
no no there's no tomato in there
okay
well let's make it just for the sake of
it uh we will make yorkshire yorkshire
pudding
ah oh we can make family slice
right all right let's make family size
let's go
bails
make us what's yolk should put in
what is yorkshire pudding is it just a
normal pudding
there's a broken toilet surprise
surprise
who would have thought
let's see how do you make yorkshire
pudding you put it all in the bowl
then you mix it
then
you put it in the oven just like that
you literally just pour it in there and
then magically it's in the form
now you wait while talking to mommy
sooner or later
i want to look it up
yolks you're pudding
your
pudding
yorkshire pudding is a ah it looks like
a baked pudding made from batter of eggs
flour flour and milk or water a common
english side dish it is a versatile food
that can be served in numerous ways
depending on its ingredients size and
accompanying components of the meal as a
first course it can be served with onion
gravy
what what is the consistency what is
that
what is the texture like what does it
taste like i don't know
oh
it doesn't really look like a pudding
though
[Music]
seems fairly simple though
nice well nobody's hungry though i think
oh you're gonna eat it anyway
yeah she's not really hungry but she
made it herself so we gotta
we gotta eat that enjoy it enjoy it
bells you can make dad so proud of you
is there
wait what do you call that animal with
two heads
because we once again have this as a
chicken it's so cute though it kind of
makes a heart shape
[Music]
what do you call this
a hydra chicken a chimera chicken
two chickens and one can do even more
work than one chicken
you are hired you look weird so you
can't uh
work at the counter with two heads but
you can work in the back and i don't
know with your two hats you can crack
some eggs or something
in double speed
conjoined chicken twins
i only have two wings yeah but they have
two heads which means they also have two
beaks and four eyes
four eyes yeah it could be a bodyguard
too
[Laughter]
who is it this time
where is it this time
uh cluckers and jimmy
ah
handy not dandy slinging hammers and
nails left and right it's not iris cup
of tea should iris banish to self-abuse
and admit that she dislikes handiness
iris i understand you dislike handiness
but all of this it's just it's just your
own fault maybe if you decide your
dislike handiness then you should also
dislike
mischievousness because this is the
reason why you're doing all of this
so you like to prank everybody but you
don't like to clean up after what you
did huh
no
we cannot do that you need to be
disciplined oh this time it's fallen
look
yes
make sure that iris does her job
correctly
she's very unhappy
she's very unhappy there
[Music]
all right you want to go into this
toilet
and also clean this one
do you like cleaning you don't like
candies but you like cleaning you're
better
uh cronie is bugging
you good okay she's good
oh
she'll be fine let's sell
why we failed with the chickens what
should i do
am i doing something wrong why are they
they gotta be really lucky
to to
have them hatch
oh god
i'm doing it again
no matter where they go
like they're always sticking to the cow
and then they just sit at the same spot
the whole time
why
but it's so cute at the same time it's
scary and cute
kawaii
[Music]
boys yeah
you guys do that too
you do you cuddle up so close together
that it looks like you have two heads
[Music]
it's creeping me out guys
yeah
bales is talking with friends again
imaginary friends even though there's
one right next to you a real one
is like sure
i don't know who you're talking to but
very interesting
please you keep on doing your fails you
know being able to talk to yourself like
that might actually be really useful
traits when you become a streamer
because yeah aren't we all insane
what cronies said
[Music]
cory what's up karma
sentiment game i'm glad you don't think
my llama jokes are getting old i feel
like you just get me oh who gets you
iris oh my borrowed
yeah you're so fun to be around i really
enjoy spending time with and i hope you
feel that way wait that was about fauna
ah
and the other one no bubba don't worry
about fauna
phone
that is adorable
oh
actually i don't know like relationships
within council that well i know cronie
and women get along
i don't know iris and bails get along
but
what about
what about the others
[Music]
like
besties and i don't know about it
okay stop stop talking uh to yourself
again bills
stop it stop it stop it
you're insane
oh my god she scares me they're all
pretty close yes they get along with my
pranks cronie that's a dude yeah i know
those two get along
it's a complicated nah nah nah there's
nothing complicated about that
bae and mummy are besties really
mummy's is claimed by all of council
so popular wow
i want to be the dad popular i want to
be a popular chick
not the popular chicken i want to be the
popular chick
did you hear that guys
very loud don't don't yell like that in
the kitchen go into your coop
for your balcony
let the outside people know that you're
alive
we have
definitely for one thing solved our
money problem
uh almost ten thousand simoleons and i'm
not even forcing santa to draw right now
so
no i suddenly have a this huge garden
with
blooming sunflowers and beans and
chickens and the cow
the chickens keep on
becoming one chicken but
that is a talent that we we might just
have to show off at the talent show
iris drinking that milk again
fleeing
uh
clean clean clean it up and throw away
this
now where do we stop
where did we stop because i don't see
chickens or chicks working out anytime
soon you know what i would buy a chick i
will buy a chick that will be our
solution
uh but ah they're all going into sleep
now i think
purchase uh
hand check
should we get one more hen yeah
oh a cute little chick will i grow up to
be a good hand
yes
where is it where is it is it gonna come
out
welcome
oh my god oh my god so cute oh my god
speedrun shake any percent no egg
necessary
oh my god look at it look at it kawaii
so bailey
it's a baby guys treat it nicely
give it love
take care of it keep it safe please
where is it going where is that little
chicken going
fairy
oh my god
oh my god oh my god
[Music]
oh my god oh my god how does it feel for
you guys to watch this must feel very
familiar right for me this is amazing
but for you guys it's probably nothing
[Music]
you want to play don't you
you guys this is every day
everyday life
don't scare the chick
though hug i want to see a hug
i want to see i want to see a hug
let me see a hug
every day bro oh
we have to feed it because it didn't get
uh the the food that was there in the
morning
or to feed it directly
[Music]
it needs to grow big and strong
there you go oh so much food yum yum
[Music]
shut up santa claus
don't step don't step on the chicken
that's so dangerous
whoa
oh
smooth zoom
don't don't you s you're dangerously
close with your foot there kyoto today
oh my god
that's way too close
fauna
don't kill the chicken that i just got
believe it
oh sheer [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh
the whole world is yours now yeah
so is yours
to explore
[Music]
you find friends
there's a place called yeah
we should name it
uh
name
eggy wait don't we already have an egg
you know
how about uh exton
eggston it's axton it's sexton kind of
weird and difficult to say
exton
edward
fred er fred frederickna
um
[Music]
um egg bird
i like egg bird yeah or egg winner it's
a girl yeah it's a baby girl
egg wina
egg
and chick combined is chika that's a
weird name toodo
eggnolt i love those names but can't you
guys think of any female names with egg
eggwin oh
freder freder fred egrika name it
breakfast no
reggie
okay regina doesn't really sound like a
name for a chick but once it's adults it
will fit better
okay we have a lovely adorable chicken
bales is absolutely insane
yay water playing in the pond in my
social anxiety suit
i am not myself i have not myself bales
be like i i'm someone else
yay hey stop stop the crocodile totally
not
dangerous why why why
sex out oh [\h__\h]
yeah bales doesn't care she's an
australian
dolphin
hmm no [\h__\h] were given that day
[Music]
she's she's just chilling she locked the
crocodile up she because she wanted to
say hello she wanted to say good night
sleep well mr crocodile
sleep well
you should sleep
all right everybody sleepy time
you're still eating
i
think we'll stop here because i think
it will be uh
lovely
on the next day right
time passed by so slowly actually
i think we might stop here
i am satisfied with what we have
achieved
almost four hours of sims 4.
oh
look at the state of our toilets
time goes by slowly if you don't go
speed if you have like so many sims to
take care of you can't go
speed that often
and then the time actually goes by
pretty slowly
i
normally when i play privately i never
made families that are this big i only
made like maybe
solo families or couple families and
then maybe have a baby or something and
maybe a pet but
really only like two adults and yeah
raised a baby
made adult and by the time i was adult i
probably usually always
um
finished
my playthrough of that family and
wouldn't touch sims again until
one or two years later
and then i would start a new family
because i wouldn't feel connected to the
old family anymore i would always
restart a new family always the same
but
but streaming this game makes me
continue
the families and it makes me not use
jeans and it makes me make bigger
families interesting families have
actual story um
story lines and and and themes and all
that and have reasons to celebrate [\h__\h]
and all that so actually like i've never
played it seems
like this ever before like so it just
makes so much sense are you gonna clean
up
oh okay
i guess you can help iris that's so nice
of you
yeah
yeah i'm i'm i'm using sims to its full
potential finally
[Music]
she was um a bit embarrassed that i
showed off her kinky art the other day
uh yesterday
what's what's what's what's work oh
holy [\h__\h]
she's so speed i knew it was raining
next to
lily
wow
well
you know what i will not show this on
stream you go on my maloney twitter and
look at that holy [\h__\h] i loved i love
that
um
i see some
[Music]
yummy
that that is pretty of it that was
pretty am i
maybe this is the next thumbnail for our
next horo 20 5 memories stream
if that ever happens again
we can use this as a thumbnail
[Laughter]
i like the black hat you know it's my my
normal hat but in black it looks so cool
reminds me of um the artwork for
one of my
uh
one of my um
hinotory remixes
from one of them
uh mamaloni drew like
one of my default my default outfit in
like a kind of like a black
version of it right you remember
and that looked really cool actually
[Music]
blessed
you saw it
yeah wow hmm
we're all pretty blessed um in many ways
damn
mourinha has um the most she's blessed
the most and um
yeah that's um
not a bad drawing
[Laughter]
i will retweet this
ski
i like it we have
we have such a nice group picture now i
could put this on my table on the office
if it's small then maybe maybe youtube
won't mind
just put put it in a frame in my i mean
in my my obs office my youtube office
you know maybe also in my real office
gemma has a heart attack oh no no no no
heart attack
happy happy feelings only
[Laughter]
ah
good job i like i like it
on it
i
did it
well uh i feel like she she's stopped
like she started drawing like some art
for
um
not for but like after that 3d uh
concert she started drawing on something
right for the en and id members
i saw the the work in progress pictures
but then apparently she stopped because
she needed to draw this lude hollow tony
picture understandable understandable we
um
we cannot be mad
i am not even mad
cool
i want my dad to sleep
when my sleep
okay
now that uh
almost everything
how the [\h__\h] did crony
become acquaintances with smoothie when
she's in bed
sleeping
[Music]
smoothie
this is
this is basically
smoothie coming into my room right now
telling me
that is the end of the stream as
smoothie likes to do
that is so weird this movie is not here
this movie's not on this lot i mean i
would understand maybe smoothie was
roaming around because
this movie lives next doors like uh in
here no
myth lives uh
somewhere very close by wait is it here
[Music]
no here here it's over here this movie
is here right now i think
i think this is the lot that we got for
them right
nickel i know this one this is it this
is it
this is it
sorry sorry sorry this is dylan but i
don't see smoothie anywhere
near
well
sims do be delivering all kinds of
mysteries
let me take a a picture a normal picture
a pretty picture of sana
um because the one on the thumbnail
made her look crazy
[Music]
you saved us today sana you made so much
money for us you became famous for your
art i'm so proud of you
oh my god
look at that i want some art like that
for my
for my apartment like to decorate it but
i don't want it to be just printed i
want it to be an original but like i
don't know where to go to get something
like that i ordered something of amazon
before and put it on my wall before but
it looked painted but it was just
printed and i
was a bit disappointed but if you don't
look too close it looks realistic
do i need to go to a gallery how
are they all expensive are there like
some cheap galleries out there i don't
want to pay twenty thousand dollars for
a painting like this
always makes me feel like i could
probably do this by myself
especially without like that because
it's like not even anatomic uh like no
no and not anatomy and that tommy wow
wow this looks cool
i mean you would think you could do it
yourself but then you would try and it
would probably not look like this so
in the end even if it looks like it's
just like scribbles and
colors mixed together randomly
often it is more than that so
yeah well you know what we'll get
everyone to sleep
there we go
if that was not
a productive sims
did you get ducklings
did they always have ducklings
those are not even real ducks
[Music]
but okay everybody's sleeping
that was
productive
successful we have animals
we we are self-efficient
growing our own products growing or
milking and and taking
um
great job today
yeah we have a crocodile too but
crocodile is sleeping right now in here
yeah yeah yeah i hope the ducklings are
not gonna be eaten by the crocodile
yeah
all right sufficient not efficient okay
okay
okay close enough
we are fishing tilde we're
self-sufficient and efficient
both of it both applies
this was so much fun i really like these
streams thank you yeah it was way more
chill this time
than usually i didn't want to
didn't want to be like
uh
you know stressing myself out too much
about it but it was a lot of fun
and the decorating of this garden was
fun too i felt creative
yeah
there are two types of eggs you harvest
some are normal eggs and some are
hatchimal eggs place the hatchimal eggs
in the coop to incubate them and you
will get chicks yeah but so far we were
just really unlucky all the eggs that we
uh took out of the coop
were um
not hatchable
sadly but we got yourself a chick anyway
yeah i was like fine i'll do it myself
i'll get my own chick even if you can't
lay chicks that's okay
[Music]
i show up and it ends sorry you can
watch the archive please
um
oh my gosh already 11 p.m
[Music]
i think we can read super chats
uh
though
because
i have to get up um at the decent time
and i still have to make dinner and all
that
but yeah we can do it it's not so much i
think yes
let's go to the office um but i'll leave
you guys for
um
two minutes or so
to wash my nose and go to an aisle
meeting
but i will
[Music]
i'll go to the
super chat intermission
but i can't use my crispy fry fried
party right now because for some reason
since like two or three days ago
my monetization for each stream where i
used the superchat intermission
in the recent past days has been killed
by me using my own
ost crispy fry fried party
[Music]
yeah it's so weird we'll get it fixed
probably but it's so weird so i'm not
gonna use it uh let's use something else
how about a hino 30 remix or is that
dangerous too no hino20 remix was not
sold anywhere so
it should not
be recognized by anything
yeah
well let me let me put in a hino30 remix
you know they need to be more
appreciated anyway
my hino3 remixes
so underappreciated those remixes are so
fire
honestly
uh where do i have them
where do i have them
[Music]
uh astrophysics and red shift where is
the other one
[Music]
alpha there we go
instrumental
do we have a
non-instrumental one doco
i can't find it well i won't be gone for
that long anyway
so
i sure
ah
a bit
can i
can i change the volume before i switch
screens no i cannot
ah
it might start a little bit loud
it should be fine though i'll
immediately make it quiet okay
[Music]
prepare your ears kfb are you ready are
you ready
make it quiet on your side but it
shouldn't start that loud suddenly i
think
three
two
one
oh yeah okay okay okay okay okay
all is good
are you hearing now the hinotonia remix
where should i go okay that wasn't even
that okay okay everything is cool uh
i'll be right back and then we'll read
super chats thank you guys for watching
if you're leaving then thank you for
staying until now i'll see you again
maybe tomorrow um
we're playing uh
uh clubhouse games i think on my channel
i think
so yeah see you soon
see you soon
and
[Music]
okay
you
[Music]
is
wait one second
[Music]
hello
i'm back
i think i think i
think i might know why the
the smoothie thing happened
maybe
i could see sims
having this kind of
uh
um
possibility and maybe she was dreaming
about smoothie before she met because
she met this movie in a different
household and within the dream they
became friends like
like also outside of the dream but like
through the dream they became acquainted
maybe
i could see that it would be
um
like
made possible
in since
i see them doing something like that
maybe or it's just a weird thing one of
those weird things that happen in sims
and um should not happen but happen
anyway
also i need to save i want to play more
cuz i want to play more
but i need to stop i don't have time i
need to
i need to eat and sleep afterwards i
don't even know what i'm gonna eat for
dinner
maybe just
ham and cheese toast again
all right closing the game
exit
there we go
wonderful
thank you guys for still being here by
the way thank you for staying until the
end
i wanna hear
i don't wanna hear that lone alpha remix
right now
[Music]
yes
you okay it's kind of quiet but it
probably will get louder
always stand till the very end yes you
should
that's so very quiet
[Music]
i'm listening to the instrumental
because i can't find the original
anymore
thank you super chat those for
supporting our attention exactly thank
you very much
very much appreciate it as always so
let's go
it's not so much i can finish this fast
i'll be quick
and then i can do my other things
[Music]
i could read the super chat fast if i
wouldn't get distracted by my own music
[Music]
read them to the beat i did that before
yeah
uh
let's read the ones from this stream
only because i'm um i am
i am called up oh by the way
uh finally i also got a date for a date
and a time for the monopoly collab it
will be next week
and um
i also finally chose the game to play
with coyote
on her channel though
i think
uh
yeah i was looking at so many games and
and like so many games that i wanted to
choose like i wrote them down on our
discord i was like how about this game
this was fun and then two minutes later
i realized oh this one doesn't work
because we don't have permissions for it
after all so i delete it and then i
frank and think and think and find
another game and i was like how about
this game
uh this one's cute too
and then i realized two minutes later ah
this one is an only couch co-op so i
deleted it again and i did the same
thing again another game that i was like
let's play this one but this one was
also couch co-op and then another one
and it was also couch co-op so i kept on
writing and deleting writing and
deleting writing and leaving
yeah
and finally uh i found one that i
realized i didn't play yet and
uh
we could play it together
in online co-op unravel
[Music]
unravel uh
actually
i don't know if we're gonna play unravel
one or two
is
our both games
online cola do you guys know
oh all those games i
um
asked her about where oh i think
nintendo games
unravel
no idea i'm not sure
i think two is the only color
yeah because i saw inna and anya
played on level two in co-op like a year
ago or so
okay
do we not have to play unravel one to
understand unravel two is there like a
connection did someone play both of them
anyone in the chat
[Music]
yeah no i know that there's couch co-op
games
that you can play online for steam but
when it's uh
when it's um
uh
a nintendo game then as far as i know
there's no no way to play it online if
it's only local
for nintendo
[Music]
don't think you need to play the first
one they're connected but i don't think
i need contacts okay thank you okay okay
and then
uh no
then she cheese asked me what should we
collab and i was like oh [\h__\h]
uh let me think i just i just finally
thought of one idea to form a coyote
let me
think of some more let me poop out some
more ideas
and for that uh
partially you guys were very helpful
because i did that community post
about what should i play with coyote
right
um because i did jackpots party that
should not be played with uh two people
yeah that makes no sense so then i did i
i did not ditch i i uh
presented some ideas to
um
energy
uh
escape simulator operation tango and
kirby superstar all of them i haven't
played yet
and so
yeah and all of them have a japanese
version and all of them have online
co-op
yeah um now which one will it be i will
not tell you yet but it's one of those
streets
probably
orange hall of girls are far too strong
are you also including ninety she is
very strong yes
[Music]
i think operation tango is surely a
great game but as a collaboration game i
think it's
again something where
you can't have a conversation with each
other much and you also can't really
have a conversation with the chat either
you're just trying to solve [\h__\h] and
um
i mean
yeah it's it's kind of fun to watch that
maybe but
it would be more fun to have some
some more bantering in between right
[Music]
but i still want to play it sometime
because
it's it's one of those few co-op games
out there you know like it takes two
one of those few
one-on-one co-op games
[Music]
yeah
and
i don't know about escape simulator are
there other simulators that you can play
in co-op
because i just
uh thought of this one because gouda and
crony played escape simulator
i wonder what other
simulators you can play in co-op
i know the the doctor
surgeon surgeon simulator was co-op
right
how are someone has co-op well that's
kind of boring though
i understand escape simulator because
there's like riddles and stuff you can
solve together but
how would you just wash things together
the surgeon said yeah
what else is there
surgeon simulator chaos i remember you
know a long time ago the myth girls did
a surgeon simulator
uh collab right
and i was not part of that and i was
thinking oh i wanted to wanted to be
part of that but i think it was a really
late time or something for me
um that was a long time ago
so maybe i'll play it with some other
people one day
[Music]
this scare of cleanup detail oh i've
heard about that one recently
please remove retweet no
no if you would you know there's so many
other whole life members who retweet
way more you buy art than i do just
scroll by fast
scroll quickly
quick zoom zoom for your timeline
no i will not end this is high quality
art you know i usually don't
retweet much
art that's like yabby
but if it's from mamaloni then i have to
i am obligated also this is horotodia
art high quality holotori art how can i
not retweet it
sorry
sorry but
[Music]
just scroll quickly
yeah
and matsuni
[Music]
both of them
i'm pretty yeah bye
and martin too sometimes yeah
[Music]
i don't even look at the arts of asses
hashtag i don't i never
uh
look at
that one i most of the time i forget
about its existence
so i don't know what's going on there i
might be missing out on a lot of uh
beautiful pieces
of asses
all right so basses
didn't even know that existed yeah it's
for a loot kiana art so that the people
wouldn't post it in arts of ashes
so now we have arts of asses since a
while ago
you should check it out every day no i'm
not like you
no
plus if it is yummy you wouldn't like it
yeah i can imagine like if it's like
um
like
as spicy as you know what mamaloni
posted
or even a little bit more spicy
okay
i i like looking at that but
i'm sure there's some things on that
hashtag that
i don't really want to look at
so i'm good
i don't need that
[Music]
colonel stannis is a regular there
as part of the art oh you mean looking
at the art
[Laughter]
or both
all right let me read some super chat
those uh patsy dynasty miniature pincher
junk dancing for the pinky we will have
a lot of time together but i would like
to talk about the past event for a
moment did you know that the only one
week left you can watch all my first
fast event is
streaming oh yeah
yeah right now it's the last week yeah i
think this is the wonderful event not to
be missed yeah it reminds me that
reminds me did you guys see um
whole life english channel has put up a
reservation for the premiere of a digest
of
our 3d performances i knew this was
gonna happen
because
um
pretty much immediately after
um the concert
i was like you know feeling like i wish
i could share this with everyone like
show
people part of at least a part of my
um
performance so
um on the same day i went to our discord
and i was like at management hello
could you guys maybe consider putting up
a digest of our performances not the
full performance you're gonna have to do
that maybe just a part of it on youtube
you know it could also get people to
watch it who haven't watched it yet i
think it's a good idea and also you know
who knows when people will see our
phones reading in afternoon and i think
it will be a great idea to put up a
digest
and then no i'm not taking credit
because i got an i got a reply and they
were like oh we were actually uh
thinking about doing that so yeah
it was not because of me but i was like
uh
if if it weren't for management already
thinking about doing it maybe
but i really wanted to
share at least a part of it you know
in movement we can share the screenshots
but
it doesn't quite get the point across
does it
mean
english
[Music]
everyone needs to see a glorious
movement i wonder if they put my cake
into the digest ah they must tell
i'm sure my kikkity kick will be in the
digest how could they not i don't know
how long it is i don't know
um what they will show i didn't see the
digest but i'm just happy they're
putting up something
[Music]
yeah
oh you know what
yep
[Music]
let me put up here
so everybody
ticket sales and archive close at
11 59 pm april 20 of 2022 jst please
note that the deadline for the streaming
archive is at 11. this is repeating the
same line
ticket sales and archive close at 11 59
pm april 20 of 2022 jst i repeat please
note that the deadline for the streaming
archive is 11 59 pm of april 20 2022
very important it had to be said and
written twice
[Music]
yes
so
watch the art club maybe you can watch
the digest before watching the archive
if you haven't watched the concert yet
then maybe the digest will be the one
thing to make you watch it
i didn't watch long so i think
most of kfp
watched
it together with me
and if you have already watched it then
don't worry i'm not forcing you to watch
it again
[Music]
but for everybody who hasn't seen it yet
make sure
to give it a chance give it a try yeah
when will the blu-ray be available oh i
don't know but it has been announced
it was announced there will be a blu-ray
but i don't think there's a date yet
[Music]
if i am uh
randomly streaming at the same time then
yes but if i'm not then no
buying a blu-ray
i would buy it too if i weren't so lucky
to probably get a free copy of it
i might wanna
nah i'm not gonna do a watch along again
when when i get the blu-ray but i
definitely wanna i want you guys to look
at the blu-ray footage because it will
be so much prettier no pixels and stuff
okay i need to read super sets
yeah i need to raise up
[Music]
streamed it for dozens of times by now
and can't get enough i mean um
cinderella i absolutely love it you're
super speedy talk the animation all
right you're singing and especially your
feet
this is my favorite cover of yours after
goodbye singing you're the best love
your voice a lot thank you my favorite
cover after goodbye singing really
wow
thank you
might be my favorite cover really wow
i'm happy it's not everybody's least
favorite
i really love this song i'm just not
happy with my
with my voice in it so yeah no that's
that but uh
as long as you guys are happy about it
yeah and everything is good thank you
very much the gamer created in hokkaido
looks like you're already planning your
next long series of streams don't forget
about your promise to foreign
you mean calling her
or
a collaboration what do you mean
[Music]
i don't know which one you mean but um
i'm already planning so much i don't
want to fill up my whole schedule with
uh
collabs every week and also you know you
know what it's like always me initiating
it i don't blame for that so i don't
blame any
of these people i'm collabing with but
it's always me niching i can't always
think of everybody you know
i'm always the one gathering the people
or ask me hey do you want to collab so
i also want to collab with a lot of
people but if i'm always the one who has
to initiate it then
it's it's just
yeah it has to be at my pace okay give
me some time
give me time please
[Music]
no i i took the initiative
with nina to it i i asked her if we want
to collab because uh we're doing the
song cover do we want to celebrate the
collab uh the song come with a collab
and she was like yeah let's do it
but that was actually awesome
so
yeah
japanese are socially scared it's not
only them i'm like
mostly it's about whole life english
um
yeah even all the whole live english
collabs are usually me asking hey do you
wanna collab
yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah
like sometimes sometimes the girls
are like hey who wants to collab this
game
and they ask openly but usually it's
like at some american prime time
that
i can't really participate in and i also
don't want to be like hey can you change
the time so i can participate because
like why would they do that for me if
there's enough people participating
uh at the at the time that's good for
them and you know
yeah
if someone wants to collab with me i'm
sure they'll hit me up
on their own
[Music]
why would i live with you why would i
live with you huh why would i live with
you if i could live with ame
or
eena someone in the chat asked like
telling me i could live with them
in america
why would i do that
we need more holo eu
yeah
somehow we do
need more
but at the same time as as i said before
i'm also happy that i
am the only one in terms of you know
not overlapping too much
like when i see the schedule the google
calendar
with the girls all overlapping in
american prime time i'm i'm like i get a
headache looking at that
[Music]
it's cool that you're there for us you
watchers i am happy to have some eu
watchers yeah eu still doesn't have
by far still doesn't have as big as an
audience for youtubers as america has
so
it's not that much but
yeah we're getting there somehow slowly
you can yeah you watch it thank you you
can love you thank you i love you too i
love me some europe
i don't want to force myself to stream
at weird times when i can stream
comfortably at these times and then have
stones some amount of
audience
you're up
even if you don't like me this is what
you get so deal with it
i am yours take me
away from
[Music]
um
hmm
the fried scores oh dear lord okay
thank you for warning me i might get a
heart attack again because it sounds
like someone's leaving me again okay
[Music]
no
i once had the opportunity to rescue a
little chicken from an abusive home i
took her to my house and take care of
her until she passed away she was cute
and smart i still remember that when i
got back home she was there in the door
waiting for me she was so sweet her name
was coco being carefully reminds me of
her loss
sweet thank you for doing that for that
chicken
i'm sure the chicken loves you very much
chickens are so cute i learned to love
chickens too
even though i don't meet them
very often in real life
here on youtube yes
well i don't see you much in real life
oklahoma thank you for the pinky i
watched the vlog of the aftertalk after
my school the new usual room looks
amazing i was an engineer for the
military before i started pursuing
further education oh i would like to
volunteer to be part of the engineering
team oh
all right time for my sleep good enough
we'll watch the vlog tomorrow how about
yeah you don't seem to have a job title
yet how about um you will be
the garage engineer
yeah we settled for it to be a garage
not the usual room so you can be the
garage engineer
one of one of the many
or
[Music]
engineered military sounds really really
helpful actually how about you become
the engineer supervisor
you'll be the engineer supervisor huh
congratulations on your promotion
[Music]
dancing that's very smart uh writing it
in into the username so i'll say it for
sure
happy birthday
after moose prime thank you for the
pinkie i heard you wanted to start the
farm i'm literally doing farm work while
watching your stream oh well i'm more or
less listening to it because i need to
focus on driving a tractor how do you
even hear it when you're driving a
tractor that's so loud
you need any tips on how to run a farm
i'm your man
oh i wonder if if there's a tractor item
in the sim sport
there's no cars so
they used to have cars and sim stream
like cars that you can buy for yourself
and build a garage and then drive them
actually
noise canceling ah
not a hotel
yeah but in sims 4 i don't have they
didn't add the cars anymore it's kind of
sad the cars are really cool
[Music]
i think in sims 2 if i remember
correctly
yeah where no matter where you went
um
you would always take a taxi or a school
bus if you go to school but you will
always be picked up by a taxi in front
of your your house and then in sims free
you had your own car or a taxi to pick
you up and then as soon as four
as we've seen
nobody takes any cars at all anymore you
just walk and then teleport
which is kind of weird but
um
like
yeah if i click i want to go home then i
would prefer if the
character wouldn't walk across
half of the
world
in order to get home
if she's gonna end up teleporting anyway
at the end of reaching the map then why
not just teleport right away that's so
weird
this is so weird
okay helicopter oh yeah right and sims
2. um i think it was with the politics
carrier if you reach the top of it then
you actually get picked up by a
helicopter that's so cool
i had that before
yeah you kind of upgrade from taxi no no
actually if you go to work you get
picked up by like a like a work car and
then the higher you get promoted the
better the car gets that picks you up
like it turns into a limousine
and then into a helicopter
yeah
so cool
um
[Music]
bees tend to live where they can make
the most comfortable home most of the
time a well-maintained human-made bee
house is any ideal place to live
the bees can leave at any time but
choose to stay so yes bees choose
civilization over nature
[Music]
they
understand that they need they should
use whatever is offered to them yeah
that's pretty smart
um
[Music]
who said i would forget that again i
remembered it
i remember it easily
here comes
[Music]
actually got my tickets as soon as i
could after you talked about the last
one ah
thank you
oh my god so many
you guys should
have an idea
i was about to say you guys should take
a smooth picture but maybe we just take
like a picture um i'll have a staff
member of document take a picture from
the audience
don't let me forget that i i hope i
remember it
like at the end of the concert or so i
want one of the dokami staff members to
go
um to the very front where the stage is
and then take a picture of you guys from
the front yeah yeah
and everybody will be like cheese
maybe they can maybe they can hold
an acrylic stand over me because like
the screen in the back where i'll be on
uh you can't have that on the picture
together you know like one of those
concert pictures where
the performer would sit on the stage and
take like a selfie together yeah we
can't really do that but maybe they can
put like a doll or an uh
acrylic stand or something
there
so i can be part of the picture or i
just edit it in afterwards
oh yeah i couldn't do that then i can do
that i'll just add it in afterwards
and we'll just act as if
that was
natural
it was that was exactly
what it was i was there sitting on the
stage
[Music]
bring a massive cardboard cutout
we need a cardboard cutout
that would be nice
oh maybe they can make one
pablo mendez duncan
man lord duncan
[Music]
miss pistachios
wait why is everybody writing justice
for gravy
and judy duncan
cruz
why
what happened justice for crazy
[Music]
that's because i don't really eat gravy
here
okay
uh consider it added okay
[Music]
it's like it was boycotted
one two three four five different notes
four different people
sent a hashtag justice for gravy
uh super chat around the same time it's
like you guys uh planned this all along
all according to cake
it's my shampoo yeah but i don't eat it
not much
no not really
okay okay
okay for my american customers
cruise thank you in the game of crazy of
london pinkie
i've been replaying cinderella non-stop
thank you the cover is beautiful
especially the high notes also can't
wait for the upcoming original song i
love your music so much and i'll support
it as much as i can love your tantra
thank you um currently
my artist is working on the art for the
music video i've decided to not make it
a 3d music video
um i think my my next song after that
i'll have that one be a freaky music
video
but this one no no
i i feel like it would have been kind of
scuffed if i did that and i don't know
yeah
the next one
because also the next one i might time
it around my birthday or soon after my
birthday and that will be right after
the pretty
goofy concert so you know it kind of
makes sense then um
should make sense then yeah
[Music]
yeah and
thank you
i'm glad you enjoying cinderella thank
you
i also like the higher parts at the end
the ad-libs they were fun to sing
[Music]
it was fun it's a fun song it's just too
short jim tracy thank you
thank you for the pinky thank you
[Music]
yeah
how's it going how are you doing
thank you for your support
and the shirt is giant dancing oh
i think i'm back from a skiing trip in
austria was there still snow
that's right most of the food you
recommended to answer your questions
from last time the question i just asked
again we were up high so the snow was
really good for most of the week also
i'm scott it's not english
oh sorry
oh oh my dear ow i uh all right a friend
and that's actually perfect because i
speak scottish english anyway not that
stupid british english i'm better than
that and so as perfect we can
communicate like we're from the same
country
thank you so much for coming to austria
hope you enjoyed it
um yeah maybe come back soon sometime
someday
i'll be waiting for you
the pokemon professor again oh yeah
would you cover parasite i do want to i
was thinking about it um
but i don't know there's like a lot of
different songs that i want to do right
now yummy
it sounds more british than your normal
british
really
wonderful well but i'm not british that
wasn't a scottish accent
yeah
can't you not hear it you you
you're foolish
um amateurs you don't know how scottish
sounds like gotta do more chess sounds
[Music]
for the last year you have given me more
joy
and happiness than ever oh i see where
this is going and why this would be
scary okay
happiness and everyone i'm afraid that i
must say goodbye to oh my god
oh my
even even though i knew that this was
gonna have a happy end
i must say goodbye still sounds like
you're leaving me to
go to work or something because you
don't have time anymore
why the [\h__\h] why the [\h__\h] do you do this
to me do you want me to cry and have a
heart attack and like a mental breakdown
or something do you want me
eh my time on this world has come to an
end this is how the first one ends
the fryer is calling my name and i can
only hope that i've become chunky enough
to become an excel chicken bucket
or money yeah
burger patties nevertheless i will never
forget my time at caribbean i hope that
my fried body helps can't be to become
ever strong i'm going to get you your
little [\h__\h]
i want to hug you now because i'm so
relieved
but at the same time i'm angry at you
ah
come here let me hug you and then i'll
also give you a butt spanking for giving
me a heart attack
congratulations on becoming a bucket
down thank you for staying part of kfp
for one full year
yeah
thank you
don't do this to me again okay
don't do it again cry
it's very scary
maybe it's scary
when role play goes too far
well thank you though thank you for
support i hope you're gonna stay much
longer and and and never forget kiwawa
hashtag will catch the yolk all right
i love you
thank you so much
can i reset my fried super chat to give
me a heart attack too no
it's too late for you
i don't like it no no no no
no no no no i cannot
tolerate that no
[Music]
good morning
[Laughter]
[Music]
is this is not making fun of me this is
not a joke this is just a normal super
chat what's what's up with you
and they said just now in the chat that
they reflected on their
actions of being tutson
[Music]
wow i never thought that this would
happen i thought i could not
make you like
be all like serious and normal to me in
the super chat
let's see how long
this will hold up it might change very
soon
he'll go back to normal soon enough yeah
yeah
he'll be like
she she made such a big deal out of me
riding a normal club until now i'm going
to beat simpson again
looking for the tattoo thank you
irish sheep farmer with you
no
if you don't mean the one where a lady
on a hill
makes some beautiful sounds and all this
sheep come flocking to her if you don't
mean that one then no
then i don't know it
and nicklaus invites and dancing no i
don't take
applications to be a mecca pilot i am
the pilot
the most you get is sitting on my lap
no backup no backup necessary you can be
um
you can
make a coattail chaser
yeah
or something like that
all right everybody i'm gonna go grab
some food now and all that boy bob blue
thank you everybody for watching
me
thank you
we got cinderella for 24 hours
cinderella
you mean you want me to sing 24 hours
cinderella or you're just gonna play
cinderella for 24 hours
i hope you're going to play cinderella
for 24 hours
and
but don't forget yeah don't forget
everybody my new song cover i released
it yesterday youtube seems to have kind
of and me too we both kind of killed the
momentum so please help out please leave
a like and a comment and share it please
i would appreciate that let me know
[Music]
so that it won't drown it won't be
drowned out and forgotten forever
[Music]
thank you
you can also you don't have to listen to
it the whole time you can put it in a
playlist with one more short thingy and
then keep it on repeat you know you can
even speed it up and then just when you
leave your your room you can just leave
it running if you want
yeah no playlist playlist you know i
have a playlist like that heck and
tekken i have two different ones one is
public one is not public for some reason
no no actual reason actually but
there's no reason for it
been on replay since the debbie did
thank you
i play on 0.5 speed
is that the highest isn't that slower
oh that's
that's a little bit faster than normal
two two times speed is the fastest you
can do
or that's slow oh that's slower
why would you do that
maybe just because
maybe just because it's too short i
understand that
what does it sound like if it's shorter
maybe because some songs sound pretty
good when you speed them up right but i
don't think you can really make a song
sound sound good if you if you slow them
up unless you re-record the vocals
because the vocals will just always
sound so [\h__\h] up
yeah first super shot what there was
another one
i don't send it so light when i'm
already done
space one of all thank you and thank you
your first super chat and you waited
until the very end thank you
let's go
and uh make a chicken dancing so naked
naked naked
all right i'll go now okay guys
[Music]
um
yeah
uh tomorrow collab with farmer
eh
probably on my channel
i think
um
okay
[Music]
my throat is
uh tired
they have the humidifier running the
whole day i don't know if it's making it
worse but like my froat is not doing so
well kind of kind of uh
dry
i need to drink more water
[Music]
more water
one more second
or five more seconds or six more seconds
seven eight nine bye-bye
[Music]
oh
i'm
tired
i'm such a grandma i need more vitamin d
jeff being being you duncan
enjoy the
ah
hi guys yes yes enjoy the archive stream
cinderella
second monkey dancing thank you
fly fishing
yes babies yes babies
yes babies
gonna chill with my babies
as
always it's hard because it's midnight
but i don't sleep at midnight i sleep
hours later
but i didn't have my nap
the days where i don't have a nap
i think yeah i think that's it
that's the issue
if i don't take my daily one hour nap
[Music]
i don't function well i need my daily
nap i'll and baby
i'm toddler need nap
[Music]
bye bye
it's not like i don't get that much
sleep but
[Music]
bye bye