[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
a
[Music]
[Applause]
pap
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
hello k kle
k everybody
[Music]
scream
yay
sorry for the wait everybody but we are
here now uh everything good see
moving I hear someone opening
snacks I sorry that was
me she's snacking the squirrel is
snacking crinkle crinkle someone take
away her
snacks welcome everybody to the have
exciting
spectacle
[Music]
2024 here's some bgm oh we
we nice H this is a continuation from
last year's stream we have gathered here
this time not only with Ian members but
with ID members as well to celebrate
this wonderful day with some eggy games
eggs eggs
eggs egg
excellent xeg
EGS absolutely excellent excellent I
will be hoping for many many egg puns
from you today if you can think of one
just whip it out whip out those egg puns
at any time that gives you extra
points no it doesn't extra extra extra
point I get the extra
point okay um we have upgraded the whole
thing quite a bit these egg Egger Games
Hunger Games are way bigger than ever
before
so I might have to explain everything to
you guys but uh listen carefully explain
good one over
there one um you may already notice that
this part is kind of reusing the holot
talk Studio a little bit uh but not
everything there's some other rooms with
some big Arenas that I think you all
like very much but first of all I want
everybody to go over to the egg showcase
over
here yeah we see a lot of lovely
beautiful hand drawn eggs here and maybe
everybody can go behind the
table and we'll go from the left side to
the right side to uh show off the egg
and then also introduce yourself mum
your egg is first over here
oh is it go get your egg go get your egg
and talk about it I should I grab it
yeah grab
it okay this is this is my egg I made it
really last minute um it's a bunny maybe
show it into this
camera oh where oh hello this is my egg
there's a bunny nice there's a tail
behind there's a tail behind too I don't
know
[Music]
hold oh gosh you can do it m you can do
it no no it's not really got it can you
see the the tail can you see it it's
cute oh
cute craftsmanship
A++ oo amazing I'll put it back now yeah
put it back thank you so we have mum
participating next up we have quani your
egg is next to M's egg please pick it up
and show it
off yes this is a big boros where's the
camera it's over here over there oh
thank you here wait why do I have I mean
there's many cameras but uh okay
currently camera pick a camera okay yes
this camera the yes this is my egg it's
boros it's a very poose up picture of
Bor think right now the camera is on
this
one oh okay sorry I'm trying to
right now I'm still photogenic okay yeah
this is for where the why is it moving
okay see look at that there's a ribbon
and everything that's beautiful okay
that is my egg oh no we have moved the
set
camera was it there
before yeah yeah yeah good yeah okay
good F it's fine all right it's fine so
quason is one of the egg Challengers
with this beautiful boros egg wonderful
next up we have Ollie please pick up
your egg and short off cuz it's
amazing it's so good so
cute camer is the
caming popping off this
what
where's the oh the camera is over it's
behind
here oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh where oh
there's a camera in front of you wait
wait no no there's a camera in front of
you ollie St yeah there she go yeah they
can see it they can see it yeah I'm
popping out of the
egg it's like Ollie's
ovulating I love it so much it's so
good thank you that's all cute uh okay
it's awesome is the
camera camera camera son are you are you
good is everything okay over
there I think it's on me now
a well
conce you can a well to conceive this
egg sorry some some trouble checking I
just want to make sure everything's fine
on the camera cuz it doesn't seem to be
want to keep it warm going so well yum
it's okay it's funny it's funny okay
yeah just keep it on me for now my mind
to sit on all these eggs right now ol
thank you for the beautiful egg it's
amazing you want to sit on hardil egg
next is my egg it is I know you may not
uh know for sure which one is the egg is
it me or is it or is it this thing
because we look so much alike this is my
froggy waa
egg can you
see
cute so cute cute indeed be careful if
she if you your child you don't know
what will happen if this egg breaks you
don't want it to break so please protect
it with all cost protect protect egg
protect
yes next egg she's prot Santa but not
Santa is
by I think it's a gnome Kara yeah not
Santa this is garden gnome
who be him he's very friendly please be
his friend he's looking for friends and
maybe more than
friends this is not a dating show so I
don't know if we can give him anything
but crack Hearts if I want to ship your
egg with my egg after the show for
love next up is is this egg I think it's
wiu egg wi please introduce your
egg okay where where should I show
uh front maybe front yeah it's on you
right now it's fine that's good that's
good that's good this is my egg I just
want to show it because it has teeth
nice teeth
yeah this like
Spong good squirrel teeth
yeah those those will work well on the
nuts okay next in front of that we have
a pretty colorful looking one by m oh
details
Mo you want to pick up your egg I know
you're baby right now but
G MAA is
baby explain your egg can you say can
you say something about this
egg egg egg yes egg egg good
[Music]
job how old are you so true how old are
you yes
yes okay she's doing her
best she's doing her
best okay there's no age limit in this
game I don't think I don't think so free
for all
ages okay we have another egg here this
one is by let me look
at MAA I
think MAA please show up wait MAA not
wait which one is this egg there is a
moo though a she she W it is a moo egg
oh it's my turn okay so I was thinking
of moo is Mo now but
no where's where's the camera okay my my
egg was SED by a cow and um it's hard to
see but yor is supposed to be at the
side cuz he is like you know like the
little pallet
[Music]
stuff oh
cow egg didn't know cows laid
eggs they do I me rabbit lay eggs too so
you know is that's something that can
happen nature would know right Fon you'd
know if like
C happen on this magical day of eggs can
you say yeah like a rabbit Le gave birth
to thisn
thing okay beautiful hopefully this egg
will bring you much luck
today and next up we have milkshakes M
next up we have a me beo egg go ahead
explain what you were trying to do with
that Crush people's skulls
perhaps you can do it
yeah
[Music]
g wait can I can I
uh w
I
mean was
eating egg nice egg okay thank you that
looks really heavy I don't want to go up
against this egg later I shall put it
down so that it doesn't fall on
anybody's head yeah last but not least
Ka please oh a oh
no hello hello everybody you probably
thought that I was gura but it was me
Mory Ki the entire time oh my
God I had you all fooled anyway this is
my egg this is this is my egg this is
weird
cat weird cat is very strange and scary
and probably the strongest egg out of
all of the eggs because this thing this
thing has caused Wars this thing has
wiped out entire civilizations you best
be careful and watch out for a strange
cat yeah oh sorry M I'm sorry to break
the news to you this thing is very evil
but yeah look out I can't wait for it to
shatter in 5 seconds you'll see we'll
see about that strongest egg ever no m m
you back thank you you can have it later
yes please yes
please beautiful we have so many nice
eggs in the back by the way the eggs
that we drew last year or at least some
of them they're also very cute if you
remember
[Music]
them okay I have one announcement to
make the scoreboard is bugged after all
so uh My Little Helpers will be taking
notes behind the scenes about the scores
please ignore the
scoreboard yeah don't take it as a
reference because it isn't showing
everybody
it will at least show uh everybody who
is already on the board but the ones who
are not on the board have to be counted
manually
unfortunately stuff happen that's that's
what happen doing yeah okay so now that
we showed off our eggs successfully we
can move on to the first game of the day
which is called egg hunt
extreme yay serving egg hunt today
follow
[Music]
me oh yeah take the selfie camera to the
people who have
[Music]
it sorry um over here
okay here we
are everybody
G in front the end of the universe is n
oh maybe I'll go in the middle cuz of
the
camera yeah you can right this is just
weird cat Okay welcome to a
stream it's our playground
y he's so cute and so
big it's so much nature I think fauna
would feel really comfortable in here
huh I do want to lay down in the
grass these bunnies is a little ominous
though I feel like it's not safe to
sleep around oh don't worry about it
they are good bunnies they follow the
footsteps of our one and only us
p
oh are these eggs did you bring them
from the other
room yeah it's our child hey okay that
might be a little bit confusing so
you'll have to put them on the side
please uh out of the battlefield please
did I see say Battlefield I mean um
peace peace
field wow we're going to
[Music]
battle my okay I don't know did you
the members already know how this game
works but I'll explain it to the viewers
hereo here is a little bit of a
different version from the egun that we
did last year basically we will have
four Challengers at the same time there
is no team H each Challenger will lock
themselves in into one of the bunnies
that will be their basket where they'll
be bringing the eggs too yeah once the
game starts you will find eggs all over
on these big platforms you take the egg
and then you bring it to your basket
only to your basket not to the other
baskets after a little while there will
be one big golden egg spawning right
here in the middle that one you shall
all attack and try to kick it like a
soccer ball over to your basket wherever
it is you can uh yeah try to get it away
from the other Baskets at all cost don't
let the others get the golden egg
and then after 90 seconds yes battle
after 90 seconds the game is over the
round is over and we will find out who
had the most eggs in their basket okay
yeah although I do wonder how that will
work if the score is not shown and the
camera doesn't show everybody at the
same
time so we got to count um maybe if you
members can count your own eggs that you
put into the basket that would help the
staff to
count can you girls do that when you put
one egg into your basket can you uh
count that in your head is that possible
yeah yeah yeah we can try
count I think possibly the ones up there
math don't have to count possibly like
uh you're not good at math don't worry
you just have to count how many eggs you
put in like one two three okay but if
you're up there I don't think you have
to count cuzz uh those are registered so
ID members I think have to count
unfortunately but ID members are good at
M
okay what about though MAA is baby ma is
baby
ma yeah MOA is she's she's going to
learn how to count today isn't that
exciting yeah exciting exting she's
trying she's trying she R she will do
her best she will count in her head she
can do
that yippe you can do it one I'm
sweating yes nous oh she's trying yes
dude that's not sweat you need help man
I'm sweating
nervous hey guess what I'm about to take
all of you guys on with a trackpad how
about
that I'm already sweaty I don't need any
more
sweat all right are you girls ready to
start the first game of the
day okay yeah then I need I need four
how about we start with four that are up
there FAA Kelly mum and
Quon please find yourself a
bunny
yeah okay sorry guys uh in the in the
Stream you may not hear all voices
equally cuz it's proximity but I'll stay
here in the
middle all non Challengers please move
out of the ring over
here what happened
here next baby what
goodness it's a totem pole of eggs I
leave it back nice okay that's s a
little B
my grandparents though
why did you m did you push the did you
click on the yeah sign it's showing me
my face okay it's not showing it to me
but that's
okay everybody same with my face showed
up too oh you you pressed it you pressed
it my face also showed up yeah perfect
yeah I did okay F you pressed
yours yes it shows your face right
yes okay
nice oh who's the who's the contender
over here
M do you want me to get more
eggs no not M M M crony oh we love Force
marriage here yes which one which one
who you is that
bunny oh this is my bunny okay I'm sorry
I'm sorry m
did you press the The Shield the
sign I did okay it shows your face right
you do know that you can make your yes
okay wonderful I'll
be I'll be starting the game soon you
girls understand the rules I think how
are you flying where was the button I
here the yeah no running for desktop
players I mean y'all are y'all are
desktop players so honestly uh you could
no no shift Allowed no sh shift no shift
no shift sh don't be
Shifty okay we start in in a moment I
press the
button
three two one
go let's go good luck let's
[Music]
go Big
Egg let's go oh it's located like
everywhere they're everywhere yeah the
golden egg is already here you could
already get the golden egg if you
want oh
man don't forget about the golden egg
cie's on the golden egg somebody stop
cie on the golden
egg no don't st stop her don't stop me
cuz I'm having a good time somebody stop
her having a good
time get yourself those points
yeah good question M good
[Music]
question that will we will find out
still this egg is stuck man oh several
players have IGN have have started to
ignore the golden egg and instead are
relying on the small eggs this is is a
strategy oh crony is still working on
that golden egg she
believes how many more seconds I wonder
oh she's working on it she believes she
will get those extra points the big
points for quason oh I think it's in she
got him oh or did she yeah I think five
points now go get some small
eggs I think I think they're gone is it
over over respawn after 10 seconds but
maybe it's uh over I don't know uh is it
over I think it's over okay well M
scored really big
holy Quon how many single eggs did you
put
in I got like three eggs and then one
golden egg is that uh I think let me
check with is that how our the gold EG
is only worth three points I thought it
was 10 points
I don't know why I have
eight I SC Kiara I'll be honest I only
got three eggs you only got three
eggs that's fine how did mum get so
many uh maybe Cron's counted for her oh
um the golden egg the golden egg just
disappeared because the timer ran out
before you could get it
in sorry Quon you tried but it
disappeared it's okay it's not too late
it's not
it's not 90 seconds we over I might put
put four in there I think I actually put
four inside of the how the hell did you
get 18
points because two eggs would spawn one
would spawn over here and then I get the
other one that was over here and by the
time I did that the other one would
spawn nice M good job you got take
that's why your mouth is so bloody bunny
the blue Bunny's lucky okay that was
round number one for these Challengers
please move over to outside of the
Arena it's okay we get to do it again
yeah try again yeah oh my
God oh my God what is this making a sh
Eggman it's my
egg we no
please
no Eggman EG Eggman Eggman
[Applause]
H okay enough Shenanigans give us more
eggs enough Shenanigans we'll we'll need
another uh round of contestants how
about this is our new over lisu please
choose a bunny okay MAA please choose a
bunny and bio please stop playing with
the Eggman and a bunny where there's no
one yet
and sh please go in and choose a
bunny okay I have a camera on me should
I stand on the platform so that I can be
helpful yeah you can stand somewhere
there yeah that should be good maybe
over here you can also move around yeah
camera work ma um make sure to press the
the thing so that you see your picture
on it I'm fine and also please uh count
count the the eggs that you put in thank
you
you see it okay L please do me a favor
and and and uh count every egg you put
in thank
you
okay down
peopleo oh nice dance oh she's
doing
it she looks motivated people make sure
to click the the sign so you see your
face and make sure to pict there okay
make sure to count every egg you put in
please thank
you okay
and
shy did you do you see your
face yep I see my beautiful face okay
then also please make sure to count
every egg you put in thank
you I have 100 eggs okay
okay
um although the thing is I don't have a
timer dear dear waa
stuff um so I don't know when it's over
staff
son um can you turn on a timer when I
okay let me take a picture real quick
hold on you'll tell me okay I'll press
the
button okay girls are you ready to
rumble
yay oh nice Cali getting the good angles
there wow okay we'll begin I'll press
the button I hope you can hear me I'll
countown on zero I press the
button three two one
zero block
back there it is oh the golden egg is
here we is going for the golden
egg I don't think this is the actual egg
is it what do you think
the whole
time bi stole the golden egg from R
maybe she already is close by she can
block
her say hi Oh I I I don't know this
works oh no just run against it just run
against it you can push it away touch
it oh oh they pushed it into Shield
basket I
[Music]
think get extra points
oh no oh maybe free it's okay you now
have the big points so pretty good you
there is egg oh I can see egg nice nice
how are we doing on eggs the second the
second golden egg is
here oh sorry ah I'm interfering I'm
interfering it's good for my diet where
did it go oh they're all fighting over
the Golden EG
will it disappear before the counter is
done I can't see anything probably
will oh oh it's done it's over ding ding
ding ding ding
[Applause]
ding you're done
congratulations we don't have a count
right away maybe we need a little bit of
time actually let me ask you shi how
many eggs did you have how many small
ones I had that one golden one four
Smalls nice four Smalls one golden and B
what about
you uh I think it was four or five you
had one job you had one job
sorry I count bad four or five you say
it's okay maybe maybe we had an eye on
that we'll see and whu how many eggs did
you have I only got three small one okay
wonderful Ma how many did you get huh
can you say 100 no that is wrong she
clearly won no there's no way you got
100 come on Winer baby she's obviously
the winner here do you mean I
one three free free eggs for MAA baby
okay good job MAA that's not too bad
that's pretty good so we have free free
four or five and obviously Shi is is the
winner in this case with the golden egg
in her bag
woohoo yay
woo the D girls now get out of the ring
thank
you where the exit again yeah you got to
get out of
here oo edgy way of exiting oh babe
wasn't there Iris was there though hello
girls yeah hello I think uh out of here
the ones who haven't tried yet is me OE
and who I think that's just me OE but
everybody gets to do two times I think
so we'll need some some people who go
onto a second round already I think cie
tried right I volunteer as no call
didn't Callie did you already do a
round I did okay what what it
was oh yeah oh yeah
okay okay then let's do uh only the VR
players again uh Wu biu me and Ollie
please not Ollie wait Ollie I guess you
stopped but you can go in you can go in
you're not in VR right now are
[Music]
you just desktop
right yeah oh that's okay yeah you take
take a bunny and click on the
sign you know how it works I'll take the
yellow
bunny okay my
face so we have ol biu me and
L okay okay everybody push the
sign and I'll need someone to push the
starting uh box you you go see the
starting box don't press it yet yeah
yeah we can okay sh I'll leave it to you
you're my assistant today
okay okay oh God box on your
side it no just the one on your
side okay yeah all right all right on
zero everybody stand by their
baskets
yeah we still
back three two one
zero this too high how do I jump
y oh yeah keep counts please
[Music]
one go get the golden egg hold on
actually I feel like the chances are
kind of
low
me take strong
egg
two no R's getting the golden egg
someone stop her I will stop her I will
stop her I'll stop her why is it
Stu it's stuck okay let me get that
one people people egg strong people
somebody needs to tell me when those 90
seconds are over I guess when the golden
egg is gone
that's I think four
eggs you got it oh my
God you're too small don't go up there
no
Noor
again quick quick quick quick quick
quick quick
yes no no no you're not going to get a
second golden egg no you're not no
you're not no you're
not
no no yes go
no stop it stop stop okay we're over are
we I think we're
done okay stop stop stop Gather in the
middle okay good job everybody people
how many eggs did you
have six six damn good job people only
have nine nine damn oh my God nine I
seen like none or nine it's nine nine oh
my God damn good job and W you got the
you got the big one and how many small
ones I got two two small ones and one
big one yeah damn I got I think only
five for so but mine you can see on the
scoreboard it's 12 but that's just
because it's multiplied I
think uh
damn well clap clap clap for us only you
don't look so impressed but you have a
good
number okay yeah nine leave the
battlefield
everybody okay we're going to go
crony only you can stay go going to
second round choose choose a
bunny oh
okay actually the reasons why I don't
want to leave it's that it's kind of
scary over there oh
understandable yeah I get it oh uh one
question to the dear de my picture is
still on there if the next person uses
this bunny will the points not add to me
it will it be fine if they click on the
on the sign just
wondering just double
checking it's fine okay I'm I'm feeling
sick motion
sick oh my
god oh my god wow you're so small big
why are you so
big can I
get
Madam I'm going to throw up okay
you got girls somebody needs to what
what's going on somebody needs to
challenge the
challenge H I will choose is round
number two yeah or yeah round number two
for some people but now it's already
round number three I
guess and yeah okay we're we're leaving
Ollie in then make yourself smaller
again do
ideally yes ma'am yes ma'am I'm sorry
you scare me when you were so
big hold on I have to remember but
you're so beautiful you're like a a
goddess a thanks app okay then let's
Kelly Kelly you didn't do a second run
yet did
you no I haven't I'll do it now H cie
second round OE second round she woi
second
round and uh quason I'm plusy are you up
for a second
round oh my good oh yeah oh my God holy
wow can I get between those ties man
bro uh I think this bunny over there is
free for you Quon or maybe not actually
Ollie is there uh the the the the P
dotted one is free okay
think yeah press the the signs
make sure it's your
face and if your if your face is not on
the scoreboard please count your own
eggs thank
you are you ready
girls you
ready okay wait is this your is your
face oh my God are you okay she won't me
you're te posing oh yeah I'm just
chilling yeah that's to explain
dominance oh did you press the sign it
still shows my face but I think that's
just it shows my face for me okay good
then I'll shall press the button oh beo
big oh bio
small okay three two one
sheir go go go
go come
she got the she got the
Cal go Callie go Callie go Ollie go
Ollie get those eggs too oh is that easy
easy Oh shot is on the golden egg
currently she's the only one focusing on
it she got it she only got the golden
egg let's go wait are you putting in the
same basket
did you put over there right wait did
you it's your face I have two signs I
have two
signs yeah two faces don't don't worry
just count count your uh okay okay
that's confusing yeah your basket is the
the poka dotted
one okay
okay there's a gold gold
egg cron wants the golden egg no it's
mine it's
mine this time it's looking like it
wants to go into Quon baskets no it's
mine going back and forth ah she only
got a second oh my God holy she
only got a
second I think this is pretty decided oh
I think it's done
yeah all
right oh wait do you think it despawned
or do you think it went into your
basket oh no no I went in I'm just
saying the small eggs kind of Spawn the
same place so oh yeah they they do you
kind of know where to go get them yeah
it's fine that's fine all right JY how
many seven small two bigs holy macaroni
that's incredible that's the best score
so far how are you this good I know
excellent excellent absolutely crazy
Ollie how many eggs did you
get I got 12 12 that's also pretty good
damn good job OE good job thank
you K I see you were up to 20 I don't
know how many you were before but that
looks pretty good to
me good job good yeah I got 50 eggs and
quason for some reason has 38 points up
there but that might just be because you
you had 18 before right or no not
18o I have no idea but Y how many eggs
do you think you put into your
basket I think like a 100 eggs sure I'm
king um maybe like six six
eggs six eggs that 66 or 6 but did you
Al you does that include the ones you
put into the other
basket yes yes okay cuz I wonder uh just
a note to the death I guess you got to
count both then both baskets cuz like
the the the sign the sign has like like
the the yellow bunny also has my face on
it so that's I got confed ah probably
was your your your basket previously in
the previous round yeah so yeah both of
them might have counted towards the the
the score on the board maybe might be
yeah
sorry about the scuff
eh yeah we still have some people who
didn't do a second round so we got to
gather
those okay girls who didn't do a second
round
yet I
haven't
M MAA right probably
MAA you didn't do a second game yet
right no okay so as you free and me
we're going to go in ideally go to the
basket you had before if that's
possible okay okay F which one was
yours that one over there okay okay good
oh perfect that might work out perfectly
except MAA which one was yours too yeah
uh can you go to the pink one Mo my ins
side okay thank
[Music]
you okay
okay
then second round yeah let's let's uh sh
are you going to press for
me okay thank you
free oh three two one zero
go
oh oh oh wait did I
press I thought the egg was going to
show up
there
Y how do I get up there I can't I can't
reach no I'm too small okay I got to I
got to get the gold deck got to
get oh nice
W
where it
no no no I want the GL I want the
egg no I got to get it I got to get it
no no
no go back no no okay I can't fight
forever over the skull and egg damn
it I am not winning this
one oh
no
no holy CR
what's
up yeah I'm not winning this another
golden
egg I'm so bad at this I'm never going
to be good at soccer but that's just
Austria it's
over it's
over otu
otu every everybody
gather MAA how many eggs did you
get one golden
egg no who let her have the golden
egg one golden egg and how many small
ones thank you three three okay thank
you for counting you're getting so good
at this
MAA F what about you why why you look
sad I think I had I'm have my my game
face on I think I got eight or maybe it
was nine standard eggs I don't remember
say nine nine is okay thank
you m what about you or actually you're
up there aren't you you're at 58 oh my
God yeah oh holy moly holy moly mum 58
eggs it's not 58 eggs but like this I
think one egg is like two points or so
of free points so that's multiplied I
got 21 small eggs oh my God God 21 in
one goal in one round yes how does she
do you want me to show you
how they were right next to you weren't
they I went I went over here mhm I went
over here and I wait two seconds and
then resp damn it should have should
have gone over
there
okay don't hate the player yeah that's
fine that's just you know Destiny um is
there anyone here who didn't play a
second round I think we're
done you're done right no I think we're
good yeah everybody play a second round
okay we're done with this game let's go
I'm so glad cuz it makes me Mo SI and
the points have to be counted ha her
opponents okay hi Eggman we we're moving
to the next Game Goodbye
Eggman are we just leaving him there
goodbye he's just going to stay there
okay yeah it's where he belongs oh he'll
be protecting the Park
yeah what a good man a good
Eggman just let him serve as a reminder
for Humanity all right everybody to
strive for excellence Excellence nice
one for excellence yeah thanks pretty
proud of that
one welcome to uh this game is called
egg balance
parkour
[Music]
y go so how does this game work I'll
explain it for the audience and also for
you girls again a little bit and there
will be two teams if you if your team
wins then you get overall extra points
if your team loses then you're not going
to get very many points at all and so
there's for example the red team
consisting of these players oi Wawa wiu
shii and Kopi great team right okay two
of these players AKA waa and wisu are
currently playing with actual VR so
those will be standing on a platform wiu
can you go over to the other uh platform
with the spoon
yeah the other members of the team
please stand in the
middle nice yeah she she only is so
small I'm here I'm here hold on let me
she's just a little tiny she's somewhere
there oh there she is yeah so uh besides
that we see a bar under the the team
graphic and we see a bunny that's trying
to hop to the goal on the other yeah and
it's split in three parts as you can see
so uh we start with the wava on this
platform I'll be holding the spoon
watching for me I'll be holding the
spoon and there will you will see there
will be obstacles coming at me that I'll
try to dodge and the spoon and the egg
has physics so if the obstacle hits the
egg the egg will drop and the bunny will
not be able to move on you inside me now
we have to do this three times until the
bunny reaches a free time successfully
until the bunny reaches the next level
then
immediately it will go to the middle
stage which is you
girls H there will be a quiz this year
it's not uh particularly Easter related
questions at
all questions cuz Ollie's
here there may or may not be a math
question a good math person these
questions can only be answered by the
members on this platform not wiu not me
okay only you girls okay and there'll be
a question I'll move on to the answer if
you got it right then there'll be a
right or a wrong ding ding ding
or and then you do that a few times and
then we move on you can see that the bar
will move on to wiu who will then do the
same thing as I did yes
understand does that make sense chat
yeah before you start uh you might do
you want to move your Premiere to a
different time to supposed to start in
15 minutes uh yeah Gemma was supposed to
do
that JMA are you
watching let me message her can you move
the premiere
please I literally looked two minutes
ago apparently it's done now yeah it's
done you're looking at the same time you
have your connect with JMA lovey Dy nice
okay so we will begin the game uh in the
red team good a
trivia oh yeah I know some crazy facts
probably actually can someone press I
don't know anything unless it's this
yellow button for me when I say not yet
though okay thank you Mo baby okay we're
ready to go ready to go red red red red
R red team red
we're ready to be
excellent okay yeah that's exciting I
think the the stream camera doesn't see
the egg uh on the on the
spoon but there is indeed an egg on the
spoon maybe the you can see
it it's just the camera doesn't see it
you can see it though what if what if
what if car's stream camera is oh no I
guess you can't change it oh well
there's supposed to be a egg on here
okay and it's really wobbly it's okay we
can
pretend yeah it's wobbling a lot we can
describe it for everyone wob W so wob ah
it's moving okay ah it's moving so much
begin Mo he's
blushing oh I already dropped it
oh it's wiggling that one's easy sh I
dropped it anywhere oh you got it he got
it he got it he got it oh you said you
dropped it but it's still in the spoon
yeah uh it comes back right away but
this one I this one I did there we go
there we go oh nice the bu be moving be
careful it's so
wiggly so much no no no give me a better
obstacle give me a better one oh that
one's good that one's good I can do that
one why does it move like there you go
like that yeah good job to like back it
up and stick out the
[Music]
okay should be
it we moving on to the quiz on the
periodic table I doubt you know that
one no gole you can skip if you
want helium hydrogen helium perox helium
I think I have to press this button
right
lithium so you were wrong I remember
that dang it sorry about that next I
know is Breaking Bad how many signs are
a heag
eight what is
heag seven said seven he I just said
seven I just said seven just so you know
I literally just said seven then I'll
give you an okay believe in you believe
in you thank you thank you next one what
is the capital of
Switzerland Sweden umet oh no
geography
um it's
it's okay and one you got to get one
more correct Legend how was mountain in
the solar system M Fuji no uh M Everest
wait solar system I don't know that's a
trick question the button please what's
in this system cilantro do you want to
lock in something or cilantro
kro I don't I don't
know yeah Alejandro
[Music]
Kar all right
go math question that one okay so
apparently this it doesn't matter if we
get it
wrong Al Ein oh
youbody
nice okay moving on to I think the next
one dodge dodge
dodge actually actually it's really not
jiggling re is quite good at this yeah
dang She's So
Cal a little bit one
more isn't at
all it's okay you got
this win did it nice job 186
seconds y r MVP nice
job f a squirrel that was red team with
186 seconds the blue team has to top
that or go under that score ideally can
you do it blue
team I think we
can
okay
basically uh please take go uh the VR
players please go on the egg stages just
one
each so I think
MAA have a great
view yeah also uh wait I was actually
going to change the
bgm let me change it now it's never too
late oopsie double
bgm
good thank
you nice people also already in
position okay and we're switching to
Blue Team that's you make sure for the
uh egg players stay on the platform
don't don't go on the stairs please okay
Ma yeah stay up there okay okay
come we start with MAA
St I think should come now there it is
let's
[Music]
go you got this baby drop the egg oh
she's doing it she's doing it baby she's
so good she's one with the egg bab baby
got good B this one I think she dropped
no she didn't oh my God okay question
time you did
it
4 isn't a 21 26 you want to lock it in
26 which one 26 26
correct oh wait y okay next
question the same it's the same it's the
same damn that's an easy
question next one what the
heck oh now it's I don't even know man
it's in the ocean or something in
the I don't know what it is either I
don't know you don't know you don't know
want to skip the Pacific
Mountain okay
wrong
why in
thece I got the ocean
oh who one oh
God H anybody locking
inar
y that was I think already it moving on
two
people I think they're
win first one clear I think
yeah second
one good night
clear did she drop it no she didn't one
more wait they got it figured out oh
this one
dropped no what how come you didn't drop
it
what okay they got it B plus 15
points W woohoo
congratulations be
we
yeah those questions were a little bit
easy it's okay it's all friendly
friendly play oh my God my VR is like
glitching see the question so they
didn't even
know this is all all fine we have some
nice looking scores M seems to be
leading if we just look at those points
by the way M how do you feel about this
pressure I feel great I love
pressure okay last but not least we're
moving to the last game stage follow
me this one's amazing this one's
huge look at
these it's like the Hall of Fame
venue WWE music playing okay I will need
the four zaco players from the people
who were counting
the everything uh let me see they're
saying something
oh
uh uh who are the duckle probably one of
them is me
probably um not me yeah not
you right then M you can can you find
your your button thingy I found it
already we put it here M you're already
passed
Jacko okay h c k
bi Oro there's one more missing please
await the
results so Callie I don't believe that I
don't really believe it either fake news
but it seems to be true wrong maybe she
didn't do so well in the first game yeah
The Blue Team I mean that's that may
have been good but the individual game
counted as
well dang not bad apparently there's
some really good
players so who's the last one lucky um
they spawn in really good places sorry
I'm still waiting on the info on the
last one let me change the bgm in it
matters not it's okay's
not we're still taking this one home
maybe maybe who could it be who didn't
get a golden egg before that's a pretty
bad idea that's a really bad maybe wait
oh I'm already on there I didn't you
didn't I
did what
a I think it might be
qu no
[Music]
but she's on the winning team the Blue
Team yeah and just by looking at the
score I see fauna has less points than
quason
is that accurate though cuz I think when
someone was using the same bunny as
CR I
I
yeah
H
uh
h i who volunteers yeah who volunteers
to be a
tacle I has enough confidence that that
they can wants to be a tacle don't I'll
put you into the tle I'm sure you can
fight through it oh oh two Gamers
against each other going to get the
Championship win people versus funa
that'll be intense
you oh and
Takami some intense
fights okay then it will
be m versus crony
cute and these are just like randomly
assigned cron May over forever probably
laughing like that bro these
together
and versus o go hydrate okay this is how
the field is looking so
far very interesting the tle fighters
fight themselves up
here okay and if you win at the
end we'll just going to because the the
girls I think because the whole score is
all messed up again we're going to do
the following whoever we're going to
ignore the previous games whoever came
out as the winner of this will get this
Trophy and be the the the winner of
overall
today yeah excellent the expert of
2024 okay so we're going to enter the
duckle basically for the viewers
what this game is like let me explain
it's almost like
a rock scissors paper but there's only
two options I guess over here follow me
if you
want over here there's the eggs that we
drew but oh The Challengers shall not
use the eggs that they drew but just any
egg that speaks to them as in that egg
must be the strong egg that will will
lead me to victory yeah you think about
it you look at them you see if you have
a connection with the egg then you take
it to the boxing ring and then you will
face your opponent and we'll see which
egg was the stronger one just for the
audience who understand these eggs have
randomly assigned stats to them some are
already decided to be stronger than
others we don't know which ones I also
don't know which ones um but we'll see
we'll see who gets the right egg and who
wins to be the expert 2024 one's really
strong you think so we cannot use our
own egg no no no you can use any egg um
I I would I would recommend you to use
just any egg that looks nice to you that
you maybe want to even eat for breakfast
or so I'll all of them
yeah okay yum yummer your egg
first my egg what's in my egg you think
it's it will win I hope so froggy waa
egg go for the win let me switch think
the devs are going to make your egg weak
is kind of insulting oh wait I was
doubling bgm was
I sorry guys if I was double bming was
I uh last game by the way is by the way
is called eggshell
expert hey
don't think bgm was fine oh
okay uh uh was it okay okay yeah did you
guys hear any bgm so far dear
chat this is intense it will be intense
oh the bgm is
intense yeah okay they heard it okay so
we start with the taco Takami Taco cup
wo
woo please chose your
egg I will be back for my for my uh
fight against okay I will believe in the
froggy waa
egg and choose this
one
Callie come up here oh I see oh I have
to choose one from here okay got it I'm
listening choose the one you believe in
take you know I kind of like fauna's
little dude fa's little guy looks good
yeah you like him or you you like like
him I mean I don't know fa that's a
little bit of a personal question don't
you think yeah would we have to do it
behind camera so okay careful now don't
let's not touch our eggs just yet only
on the command
okay all right I'm ready only the tip
only the tip me bleed come come closer
cie if you want to challenge me okay
let's meet in the middle I'm ready all
right okay I fear nothing we just Bonk
each other's eggs once then Parts super
hard then again then Parts you know
Until It Breaks but slowly okay are you
ready place your bets now place your
bets on your Contender number one
Contender over here froggy wa using the
froggy waa
egg and then K be using using gnome
gentleman let me turn his head around so
that like you can like when you when you
fight him like you fight his face yeah
Mr Handsome gnan oh I want to do the
same I'll turn her around too let's make
him kiss ready for you let's make him
kiss a big smooch okay ah I heard a
crack okay I heard a c I heard a
crack second hit
go I told you I told told you that her
egg would be the best
one this is this is not rigged it's not
rigged okay I'll bring my egg
back first and they let her
win Okie doy nice Ollie nice you know
what to do next in the taco we have bibu
versus F please choose your eggs wisely
let me see it's on let's let bi go first
do you want to go for your
own yes it's a stone after all so it's a
bab nice oh cute can you smell what The
Rock is
cooking smells
delicious I smell an
omelette okay then uh funa what you will
go with your gnome no no no no no this
this guy I don't trust
him I want M's bunny okay let's go with
M bunny please move to the to the boxing
ring changes every round I think the
stats change yeah every
round
okay okay I want you to you to a
duel I accept your duel don't just don't
just go uh quickly mashing just just
like uh take time take your time okay
with the mashing carefully okay okay are
you
ready can we choose own
beu the newcomer from Advent versus the
top gamer go paa from promise d
d go
fight approach egg
[Music]
approach crack now number
one who's crack that was a crack that
number two oh people's EG is
gone the stone was not strong
enough let's
go you'll get him next time good job
good job dang it nice to please bring
the egg back good showing bi boo okay
thank you your egg is gone bi boo
forever forever
ever it's okay eat myself
yeah okay placing fun
Cris yes now we move on to the not
duckle aka the uh
quarterfinals T it has changed to
Pink the first one of one that
everybody's looking forward to m versus
crini please go up to choose your egg oh
no I'm going to kill
you
H I'll kill you third
violence
is suggested embarrassing for you that
this is what's going to kill you okay
that's so
embarrassing you know what
they already started Sho they started
cracking yeah yeah you can actually
already fight here it has begun please
move to the boxing
R it was an early an early crack they're
cracking early this
year it's the global
warming that some pre
crack
okay a good I'm going to kill you I'm
going to kill
you I'm going to kill you I'm going to
kill you wait wait oh my God I'm
ready approach no you know what I'm
going to put my gamer face too you know
what I'm I'm I don't have a gamer face I
got my gamer face you know what let's
freaking go
attack
attack wait wait wait okay I'm ready
okay I'm going to kill I'm going to kill
you
okay I choose
you I I destroy
you I choose you okay come at me come at
me don't let your emotions overcome you
no you come at me focus on the X
power you you coward fine okay fine on
guard oh I heard a crack one more crack
and it's over nasty one go for it
believe come in come in
yeah she's dodging she's
dodging you can climb she must be scared
clb you're too short slam DG slam
DG that's right defeated by your own
creation
wooho oh yeah yeah yeah cope cope inhale
that cope man good job please bring your
egg back to the stage where you got it
from okay you should fight with that
instead hey thank you Ali good assistant
you're welcome
oh next go next we have Kiana versus she
w
win oh
no let's choose an
X I think I think is my egg here your
egg's this one oh I see is it oh yeah
suppes yeah that one looks
good it's pretty yeah I'll Trust in
froggy waa
again I'll Trust in
death I'm scared I'm
scared take down egg sorry that's M old
meme oh she dancing oh oh what do you
want what do you want how you want to
dodging moves right here you can't DOD
this egg I'm to smash oh where did you
Destro it what
happen no it's okay my egg is safe I'm
channeling my my egg energy into the egg
I will become one with the egg let me
let me make mine face yours there you go
oh no ol's face is too cute it's ready I
can't I can't yeah she should let her
win no ol I'm sorry for what will happen
I must hurt you are we starting I can't
tell I'm literally right here okay yeah
so we're starting I I wasn't sure
there's usually like the taunting and
then you like smack yeah oh I mean let's
go let's go oh crack oh wait who who
crack was that the egg are CRA your
crack or we don't know we don't know for
sure take this
EG I dodged where' It Go where's you oh
is it gone oh I think we died oh
no just like the
real I'm so
sorry Ollie I'm so sorry for your loss
and she sorry Ollie it's okay I like
being what a shame with Kara I stand on
she w we dead body
Victory nice she killed me in
Roblox I never played Roblox before damn
oh man all right bringing back the
egg okay next Who's
Next who is
next MAA versus
FAA okay
then a baby that doesn't seem ethical
have no mercy the baby doesn't even know
what's going
on I can't fight a baby no you're good
you're
good then we have to call up
Lu What's Happening
Here uh hi do not punch the it's like an
umbrella yeah it's my little tent oh
sorry sorry let's go to the eggs how
many people could beit you're going for
him again it's time for sure time for
sure you forgave
him I forgave him that's so sweet he's
black me if I don't Sho him something
bad might happen that is a really toxic
relationship you're having with him I'm
going to
myself I can't believe you you're a baby
and you drew this egg you're such a
talented artist a talented baby
yeah definitely the next Michael
Michelangelo for
sure will be even even better than need
my inness one day if that is even
possible okay all right no mercy against
babies we are here to fight and to
decide who is the expert
2024 so are you ready ladies and
[Music]
gentlemen I hope you have to house all
of
usit wait wa baby fight baby fight F
baby fight baby
fight maybe maybe fauna can try to level
with her opponent and become baby
too hold on I can become baby
how um how will she do it there's a
way if there's a will there's a way
there's a
way she's becoming baby she
[Music]
baby now she's the smaller baby
baby fight baby fight
F whe baby okay the egg is almost bigger
as you let's go attack crack the
egg
no one more go for it CRA oh no a thir
crack who will it
be
[Applause]
[Music]
but Ollie can you stand the
psychological damage of fighting
yourself how does it
feel to fight your own creation yes yes
I like this emotional damage
you're me what can you really hurt your
own creation
Olli
yes I can because it's kind of a
mediocre no it's
a all right it's m we shall
see ID first gen versus ID second gen
approach each other come on come at
fight come at no you come at me I'll hit
you who will go for the first hit you
with this
undying egg oh yeah the Zombie egg mine
is literally made out of stone
what I'll take the first
hit what was that the cening
this attack ouch oh I heard no crack
come here attack they're two powerful
bam I heard no crack still heard no
crack what are you doing you're dodging
cracked Under
Pressure they don't want to crack why
why is they cracking well
maybe maybe they're equal no
that's make them kiss maybe they'll
crack then yeah okay okay kiss kiss okay
[Music]
kiss that's weird they cracked
once yeah they CRA friends chope okay
and then lovers can they be oh my God
this is just like Hunger
Games yeah they should not be
made out oh
yeah
what
w why is it not
cracking maybe maybe try dropping it and
picking it up
again kiss harder drop it
yeah
go okay oh
here we're not hearing any CS are we
wait I think this is a
tie wait let me try maybe it's you oh
where where go oh here
okay I think it
disappeared oh I heard a crack okay you
can continue I fixed the
egg is it gone all his egg is
[Applause]
[Music]
gone sorry Al I tried my best you did
you did good
you did really good man I'm so sorry it
was so good
your your daughter lived no yeah your
daughter is still
alive
Pebble
was okay we're moving on actually to the
semifinals let's go let's
go we're getting closer to the trophy
with each step all right shall we start
with the crony versus kiata match
up oh no oh no oh yes
it oh
no come here come with
me which egg are you going to
choose you are very clean oh
I can I have your egg
yeah sure okay okay oh yeah sure you get
over it really yeah oh really okay
really yeah yeah yeah I mean I I I it it
will it will it will surely not betray
me
so my egg that's this is true this is
true then I'll
choose this should I choose this m
egg or no yeah I'll just m egg
horony
power it's
beautiful okay here we
are we our matchup is unexpected perhaps
I representing M with this egg to
fight my egg your egg frogua froga
theocc will like cooperate with crony
we'll see she likes crony it's only when
it's with Kiara that could be yeah
surely you can't kill someone with those
beautiful eyes so cute oh trust me she
can
kill she took down Taki out of all
people I am froggy W your um battle face
yeah it is my battle face
cropter let's do this let's get it over
with
approach
oh what the he oh I
crack okay nice
nice I don't
know I'm scared will I come at me come
at me come at me my own end my own
Nemesis
crack holy holy oh my
God
she I
[Music]
Hy
power thank you
m you created something so powerful it's
it was able to take down the Frog of all
frogs nice one nice good bunny
yooo I'll bring it back keep it
safe she didn't she she didn't make we
cat Cho weird cat was choosable yeah
obvious weird cats would have been a
dangerous one over a little so over oh
that means I'm in the finals now who
will face me in the finals fa versus
lisu please make your choice of
egg and this one's
important this one will bring you to the
finals okay you took fa's egg the very
popular F believe in the green no in the
MAA okay that's fine that's
[Music]
fine break not go the baby the baby yes
the one that you took
[Music]
down
okay you too you know how serious this
situation is
Right know yes this is your one chance
to the final exactly you get it okay we
all want to go to the finals we all want
to get that trophy so give it you
all give it your egg okay
approach how do you feel facing the
handsome
guy
terrified hi he's trying to
whisper trying to whisper whispering in
your ears oh
no sweet
cho cho cho make him
kiss oh that was not a crack no fight
fight
fight yeah I heard a bnk from br's
microphone don't a
crack a gentle that's the first
kiss I will be
gentle
oh
yes anymore
amazing yeah you K him I did not expect
this one green versus green wow oh no
I'm up against fauna I'm so scared no no
it's already time it is time we're in
the
finale this is an
finale fun let's choose our eggs maybe
we shall go with our own or do you want
to go for a different one I think I I
have to choose the the yes okay I shall
choose froggy
waa this is the realest of the
realest oh my tummy just said make made
some noises I want to eat egg time for
some some flies yeah or gummy worms
ideally got to get some
grub so in order to do that
got ultimate final believe in the dream
Kiara believe in the dream okay I
believe this will lead me to victory
that trophy that I created will be mine
B this is for all the eggs the green
will consume you today and only one
green person will be left
over oh
no what am I without my green nothing
except for pink and maybe
blue all right let's fight F it's on
it's
on oh my God the explosions are
intense they must be so
strong you're so strong every single
time
it's they're just too powerful Dynamic
it hurts to hold this power in my hand
too powerful okay one last crack tring
I'm going in
okay wait
[Music]
what took them there get fcked oh
no I
win no way no
way no I acci win my own game with my
own
egg no stop saying you saw it with your
own eyes you sillies I can't win my own
game with my own EG you're not rigged at
all no I if it's riged then it wasn't
riged by my own hands if anything it was
rigged by someone else's hands real
winner
is sus but what can you do will someone
do me the honor and thank you oh fauna
do you do you want to hand me the
trophy yes is that the propy is that is
that okay down for you oh my God for you
Wawa I Crown you the expert of 2024
congratulations oh father thank you in
exchange I give you as the second
strongest cender Contender I shall give
you my egg for the future generation oh
for you to be strong I will incubate it
thank
you yes please make a new froggy waha
grow froggy waha thank you I I think you
would be the best mommy for it as you
are green just like
her yes I will raise it as one of my own
thank you
everybody I guess I am the expert 2024
it feels wrong um I didn't really want
to win but um
nove thank you you but all of you were
really really good at the other games
too especially like the the blue blue
team was it blue team was kind of crazy
yo in that group Game Holy
Moly yeah and M M in the in the egg hunt
sheesh M had the
Strat M had the gamer
strats thank you so much that was the if
maybe a little bit scuffed but it was
the the excellent spectacle egg games of
2024 wee
[Music]
oh my
God it was exciting was it
exciting yes and just as good as I
expected it to be everybody do you want
to do you want to come up here and stand
next to me around me a nice group
picture
maybe you really exceled
today
goodix one sec oh where are we where are
we oh here yeah let's take a little
group picture chat audience you will
have to take the
picture can we see everybody is this
everybody you got to face
forward oh yeah maybe should be a little
shorter hold up your your blades are
hurting me I'm so sorry I don't I don't
know how to fix this it's okay you're
just happy to see
me okay
small see yeah only big maybe for the
balance we can have one more big one
next to cie
then yeah who wants to be
big who wants to be big with cie and
Olie it's not so bad feel let mejust my
height but now there's a gap is this is
next to you m that's true oh sh you're
pretty big now you get bigger SS pretty
good yeah I can step on people well
that's good that's good come here come
here yeah F get a little closer yeah
yeah now it's balanced nice balanced as
all
[Music]
things on M thank you for
watching in froggy we say i ribit a
ribit i ribit there you know frog
pun happy April fools as
well yay
yay thank for watching
and stay if you want to be redirected to
something cool wink
wonk yeah
knows thank you so much have a nice day
nice evening have a nice Easter have a
nice day fools don't get fooled by these
people there's some people who want to
play some tricks on you yeah what do you
mean I know you got something planned
K happy talking
look I'm not in control of that yeah
yeah yeah yeah don't be too gullible
guys I
dcing
you byebye
[Music]
byebye