[Music] A
crepe shop is
opening. The guests are two tall people.
[Music]
Thank you.
This is Calliope Molly. Ruin is here. Thank you
.
[Music] I
think that's the self-introduction I decided on. I said
flew in from Austria two days ago
and did this crepe collaboration before coming to Japan. [
Music] I was
looking forward to it.
Hololive is the English gem, Chiara.
[Music]
When did I say it?  Months ago2 months ago2 months ago
Thank you, I'm grateful.
Thank you so much. I
really love crepes. I
love sweet things.
In fact, when I came to Japan the other day, I ate the
Hololive crepe
collaboration. I
took Ame-chan and Gura-chan with me.
That time,
I remember it was Aki-senpai and Aki-senpai's, so I ate Aki-senpai's. It
was really good. What would Aki-
senpai
do if he could decide something for himself? That's
right.
Amazing caramel sauce and cheesecake.
The best.
That collaboration has ended.
I bought the acrylic stand too. I
think I bought something else too.
[Music]
Maybe it was a badge.
And that thing, that clear file thing you gave me.
I got it.
[Music] I
really wanted to go, but it
was a little scary. I
don't think everyone knew. No, no,
nothing.  Without saying anything, I thought in a small voice and then
left right away. It's okay
today.
[Music]
Please enjoy. I'm not drinking mesh, but I'm drinking beer. Let's have a toast. Yes, cheers. [
Music] He
told me about having fun with crepes.  I was
wondering what to eat and what to bring,
and I was a little
worried.
Ah, I see, the amount is
incredible. I brought a lot. I wanted to
convey my gratitude, but it was a
really
nice big surprise
present. I
thought about it today.  What do you want to eat? I asked her to
draw a picture of grapes. I
think I'll show it on the stream.
Thank you, thank you. You can
eat as much as you want today.
So, the first one is Chiara's
crepe. Tadaa!
This is  What kind of crepe is this?
Grape. Basically, when you order a crepe at a crepe shop, it
always looks like this. Strawberry,
banana, and fresh cream.
This is vanilla ice cream,
but it's not a fortune cookie, it's more like a cookie.
[Music] It
was fun to see the other members' drawings.
This cute sketchbook is full of
hand-drawn crepes by the members who have come so far.
Cute Anya.
Ori-chan's cap was amazing. I
tried to make it sweet and sweet.
[Music]
What thighs?
Like thighs.
More than that,
bent arms.
But this is Japan, here's the boobs.
There are people who take fraudulent photos like that. I've never
seen them before.  Even an
old man can make a cleavage. If someone who is a little annoying says, "Can you send me a picture of your house?
", you can just take a picture of this. [
Music] [Laughter] If you
add some lace or something,
[Music]
[Laughter]  You
said you wanted to eat ice cream. I
think crepes with ice cream on top are the most complete.
Crepes are
cute.
With ice cream on top, they're super cute. They're really good.
And I think a little chocolate cream
sauce would be nice.  Yes, but I'm okay with a little
chocolate sauce. Thank you.
[Music]  I hadn't
eaten anything so I was waiting for a bit.
[Music]
[Laughter] I
hadn't really eaten anything so I
went to the game and I was like, okay, it's fine
. That's my treat.
[Music]
Dinner crepes, right? Today's
membership.  I mentioned this a little on the stream,
but for me, if I
don't eat a salty crepe first, it
feels a little strange. For example, if I
eat a sweet crepe first, and
then eat a salty crepe later, it
feels a little strange.
Well, at
first I ate a salty crepe, but later I
thought I could try a variety of crepes,
both salty and sweet, so I thought it might be
better to try them.
[Laughs] My
friends often say "check in" so
I  Let me check in a bit more. I'm sorry for saying that a lot. That's
right.
[Music] I was
watching and writing that.
Teriyaki chicken and potato salad. Actually, Kitamae. I
heard that. Senpai, what do you
like? I heard
that.  I
forgot about the potatoes. I
wanted to order some potatoes. What was that potato salad?  I was
saved because I had potatoes. I
put in roasted sweet potatoes. I put in roasted sweet potatoes. I
put in lettuce.
English
pronunciation is completely different in Japanese and English.
This is Calliope 5.
[Music]
If you have it, please put it in.
Please.
[Music]
[Music] That's right [Music]
Bad I'm Nut
Festival Crepe Knot
Festival crepes contain apples,
blueberries, bananas,
strawberry sauce, fresh cream, and
cream cheese. I was thinking of adding ice cream,
but I ended up adding cream cheese and  It has a
bit too much cream in it,
but I
think it's good to have a lot of cream. It has a lot of different
fruits in it, so it's
colorful and
stylish. I
came here to eat a lot. It's
amazing.
[Music] It
looks delicious. It has cute blueberries in it too.
Yes, there are blueberries in it too. I
want you to take a look.
[Music]
Frozen strawberries are
not in season.
That's right.
[Music] They're
a little
sour.
About four of them.
This fruit festival, the Bataanmat festival, there are no
crepes without strawberries
in them.
It's here
[Laughter] I'm
looking forward to the decorations. Aki-senpai said something really nice after I was selected. I think
Aki's sweet crepes are just too
tempting.
[Music]
Okay, senpai, it'll be 40 minutes.  Can you
make three crepes?
Leave it to me.
Let's start with the side dish crepes.
[Music]
There's green ones too. I
like Japanese cucumbers and
those Austrian ones. They look really different.
Thin
Thick  But there's more
[Music] There
's no dots
[Music] The
moon is also smooth, next to Austria The
difference between zucchini and cucumber
[Music]
Vegetable
I know it really well I know it
That's right You
know my cooking, don't you?  It
looked really delicious. I often make it,
but
next time, I want you to make something other than those crepes, like
Japanese food at home. I want you to make something good,
not restaurant food. I
want you to make curry rice. I'm sure it's
delicious.
[Music] [Music]
[Music] You've
been telling me this for about a year now
[Music] Let's
play it with a real camera.
Let's play it.
I know, I know, but maybe I've never played it.
What kind of system did you buy?  The person who
collects the resources [music] and builds their own land, makes a road,
builds a big city, and gets 10 points wins. The
person who builds the best land will be the first to go.
[music] The
enemy will destroy it.
[Music]
[Laughter] I
thought it sounded like "I want to kill you"
[Music
] Wow, it looks so good [Music] I
really think they should film the making of this on camera, I want to see it now
Shou
[Music]
[Laughter] I
can believe it, but
[Music]
There's not just one
[Music] It's
like an anime. You
know it. You don't know it, do
you? [Music] No one knows it, but, um, that
Nishiki
What do you call that?
[Music]
Nishiki is super friendly. He
quickly became attached to me.
[Music]
[Music] It was
so fast. He
's a pro. It
can't be helped, it's okay.
Please, please, there's no problem. I'm
going to eat Calliope.
[Music]
Wow, I'll put in some crepes. That's really nice. Where should I put some? I'll
take some quickly. I
also want to put in an Instagram-worthy senior stand. That's nice
. It's
beautiful. It's the
best.
[Music] It's
really nice. Thank you.
[Music]
Well, you can send me some photos there,
of course. That
's OK, I'll send them over. I'll make
two or three more in the next 30 minutes.
[Music] I'm looking forward to it.
Anyway,
they're all really nice. I have to
check them all to make sure they're all in.
All
[Music]
Sweet baked sweet potatoes I'm going to
put in now
Sweet baked sweet
potatoes I saw the world Nice
[Music]
Today's baked sweet potatoes
Rich baked sweet potatoes
[Music] They
sell them as they are, and they're done and they're becoming ice cream  It's
frozen and smells amazing. I
went to Starbucks two days ago and
they're
doing a limited time offer of a
Frappuccino that tastes like
roasted sweet potato. I
tried it and it was
surprisingly good.
Surprisingly interesting.
Baked sweet potato
Frappuccino
[Music]
But it wasn't tasty,
not very good [Music] It wasn't tasty, thank you Thank you That's right Is it okay? [Music] Let's eat. Is it okay? We've started serving crepes. If you don't like the sound of eating, be careful.
Ring
[Music]
Amazing
[Music  ]
Wallet I
think potato salad and teriyaki go really well together.
[Music]
Have you ever put a cucumber behind a cat
?
[Laughter]
[Music]
No reaction.
It's a legend. A
cat legend. You'd be
surprised.
[Music]
Or maybe an animal like a snake? I wonder what kind of
snake it is. The two of them keep coming back and forth. It
really caught my attention.
Of the cats, there
is only one girl, but she is the most talented. I see.  I see, I see. My
cat
and I,
one of the two, has
started jumping on the door handle to open it since the beginning of this year. It
's really bothering me.  But I
want you to stop.
Lock it up and
don't give me any cashback. Well, basically, I
All the doors are left open all the time.
Even the doors inside the house, the door that my cat leaves
open, the door that leaves the house, so I
told her not to go there.
[Music]
It must be really heavy, like this, on the first floor.
Normally, if you drop it, it won't open because you
have to pull it with your body. That
's right. You're so
smart, I'm sure you'll figure it out someday.
[Music] That's it. I
've got one more chance.  Okay,
I'd like to try the same thing as you, senpai.
[Music] If you
pronounce it like a baby,
and if you pronounce it gently, it comes out like that.
Thank you for thinking I'm cute. The
next step is to call me wawa.
[Music]
Calliope.
Recently,
[Music] It
seems to be a bit strong.
Thank you.
[Music]
This is interesting. The beer that Curry-chan was drinking earlier
is Japanese, but there are also strawberry beers. It says strawberry beer,
but it doesn't
taste like strawberry at all.  It's not strawberry
[music]
That place,
but I like the basic design of this package
[music]  Have you ever
heard of wheat in German?
I don't drink beer so I don't know much about it, but
is it barley juice?
[Music]
Then you're drinking the same thing, Calliope. You
don't drink alcohol. What are you going to do if you lie now
?
[Music]  I
'm making my own crepes now. They're so
stylish. [Music] They're fun. I wish they
'd put in some more strawberries.
[Laughter]
But you still have some left.
[Music]
No. [Music] That's nice. It looks really expensive. I'd
like some vanilla ice cream.
[Music]
Expensive
[Music] Let's
put it in.
And
by the way, the time counter says
there are 20 minutes left.
[Music] I
want to take a picture before I wrap it up.
[Music]
This is gonna hurt.
[Music] I got it.
Nice.  I
sent a photo to You'll
upload it to Twitter as art
[Music]
Yes, ice cream
[Music] I'm
super excited
Can I have a little spoon later too?
Thank you I
just taught you some great English a while ago
[Music]
Beans
English I
remember the meaning  I
remember what it means to watch a long work in one go,
for example, in one day.
[Music]
Please use it if you are good at it.
[Music] I
watched One Piece on Netflix. It was a
really
good movie. I watched that movie. That
One Piece was really good.  I do
n't know, but this One Piece on Netflix was
seriously godlike. I got really interested in it.
Nami-chan is so cute. Did you notice that
Chiara's
casual clothes have recently become available for browsing,
but...  I'm wearing the
same color bikini top as Nami-chan,
so it looks like a full Nami-chan cosplay.
[Music] I wonder if
everyone noticed.
Thank you, Flash. I
get a lot of compliments on how good I am at taking photos, but crepes
are difficult. I want to take them from the top.  So,
this might be good.
No fresh.
Flash off. I'd like a spoon.
[Music]
This crepe shop is busy.
Thank you.
[Music]
Other other characters are
[Music] My
favorite One
Piece.
I don't know.  I don't know, it's the
worst. I think that person is
really interesting. But I think Luffy is the main
crew member now.
Yes, Skeleton Bits. I
love music, so I really love it.
Kari-chan just
made a song for Volume 106 of One Piece. Thank you. It
was fun. I
did my best.
[Music] I'm so
happy. Can you
hear the ASMR in this?
[Music]
But the sound is small.
[Music] It's
soft.
[Music] The
crepes are panther.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Yes.
[Music] I'm
looking forward to it. Yes, it's a fruit festival. It's butter,
fresh cream, strawberry sauce. The main
ingredients are cream cheese,
fresh cream, bananas, and
blueberries.  Apples and strawberry sauce on top. It's
okay.
[Music] It's okay. I might be
crazy, I might be crazy.
[Music] It's the
best. It's absolutely delicious.
[Music]
Thank you. It's
got bananas, bananas and apples in it too. Apples are in
it.  What should I do? Should I stick it on top or
scatter it in the middle?
[Music] It
looks better from above, that's true.
How do you cut an apple?
Slice it.
[Music] I
know this one. I've never done this cut before.
Is it [music]?
[music]
If you cut it this way there's not
much left and you can eat most of it. [
Music] I
mean,
there's something about that empty senior.
[
Music] It's beautiful. Amazing. I want you to make an Austrian apple dessert. I'll send you the recipe next time. [Music]
[Music]
[Music] I like it.
Right
[Music]
Is everyone in the comments really right?
My
parents, right? Senpai, there are 9 minutes left.
Strawberry sauce.
That might be it.
Somehow, those few people are quite like Hololive's 1
[Music]
Some of the 2nd generation members are a little bit pushy, but the
reason is not immediately
clear. I don't know what they're doing.
Mio-senpai is also
doing it like this, so it's
hard for newcomers to understand.
Subaru-chan's is  Or an
ambulance
[Music]
[Music] It
's in.
Thank you, thank you
[Music]
Thank you
This is my favorite of all the ones I've had. It
's the best. I'm
glad you like crepes. You
definitely like sweet things.
[Music]
JP's  Some of the members
like sweet things, but
savory crepes are particularly popular.  The
photos always end up looking the same.
Yes, it seems like the diameter is the most common from here on out.
But maybe it's just Hololive. Yeah,
normal crepe shops and girls
tend to be sweet. I think strawberry flavors are the most common.
Americans also like
sweets.  I do
n't want to eat anything else.
[Music]
That's right. It's the
most unhealthy crepe possible.
[Music] It's
made cutely. I
think crepes were originally made in France.
[Music] The
crepes that are served on fancy plates are
different from the
crepes you order in Europe and Japanese crepes.  It's completely
different. In Japan, there are many different things on the taps
and the way they are rolled is also different. I
think that difference is really interesting.
[Music] The
crepes at Volante are simpler and more
crispy.
[Music] It's
quite  There are many simple ones, but
both are good, but if I had to choose, I
prefer Japanese Harajuku crepes.
[Music]
Japan is really something like
overseas
desserts, or even if it's not dessert, overseas
food.
I'm in Japan.  When I make it, I feel like I can add my own flavor
and
make it my own. I
really like experiencing the difference because I make it my own Japanese version.
There may be quite a few. The two of them made this.
But there is that Austrian crepe. It's
actually
called a nose chinken.
Crepes and crepes are thin, right?
Pancakes are thick, right?
Hara-chin-kun, in between,
a little bit.  But the noodles are thicker than crepes.
That's right, that's right. I can make that too. Let me
give it a try.
I'm still eating. I
'm eating slowly.
[Music]
Thanks for making this collaboration.
Round and round.
[Music] It's
wide. I
love it. Wo
n't it burn?
Two more minutes. Two more minutes.  I'm
still eating
after the delivery
[Music]
or
[Music] I
wanted to buy a crepe like this.
I'm not the last one, so I'm going to put a hot plate like this in the kitchen with gas. I
have electricity, but I'm a little
Weak
Okay, do your best, do your best
[Music] [Music] I've raised the bar by using my cooking experience [Music]
[Music] It's
really good
[Music]
[Music] Wow, that's
great,
let's start!
I can make French toast!  I'm
really good at it,
but I feel like it's pretty hard to make it unless it's in my own kitchen.
Oh, come quickly, when are
you coming? You might say, "I'm in Japan."
Oh, I'm already in Japan, so
please come.
Two members  He always says "I'm going, I'm going,"
but he never comes. I'm
waiting. Let's go eat.
[Music] I'll
post the last crepe I tried on Twitter.
[Music]
So, today
was the Aki Takamori party.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, senpai. I
think I'll be able to sleep well from now on. I
'm still eating whenever I get a chance. I'm
busy so I eat really fast, just
like a Japanese salaryman. Like a salaryman.
Yes, you're right. You can eat crepes with one hand
so you don't have to work. It's
true that I'm always busy.  I'll make some too, so come and eat. Thank you.
[Music]
Please subscribe to my channel.
Thank you. Thank you
.
[Music]
Later today, we'll also be streaming Corone's birthday,
so please watch it.  Please. The
crepe shop is
closed.
Thank you.
[Music]