[Music]
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
B
I be sparkling down of H English aent
otherwise known as
people hi
[Music]
K hello
everyone how are you are you doing good
is everything good how I'm excited for
today's hi people Bo hi
what
huh what is what is
[Music]
that
huh was that
louder
what
huh
huh huh
[Music]
huh what
go where where am
I
[Music]
what who what who are you who are you
guy who are you who am I
[Music]
huh oh wait it says up
there COI
be you is that
me am
I am I co
beu oh oh
okay yeah yeah course beu uh that seems
like a familiar
name yes hey you you're finally awake
yes I I am awake now
yeah but I'm kind of confused as
to what's going on
[Music]
um can you can you guys can you guys uh
tell me what what's going on what what
so my name is
kizu yes what
else what what what what else do do you
guys know anything about me do you guys
know
who be you aren't I be you I'm a
rock I'm a
rock how does that
work rock rock rock
rock rocks
can can live rocks are people I'm a rock
herse I'm a rock magical girl I'm a rock
magical girl
I can fly oh I have wings right I
[Music]
have I can
fly I have candy feet
what what what do you mean
[Music]
by wa did you guys see
that my my
you w do do you see these what are these
what are
those
[Music]
W I guess maybe I am a rock person cuz
they don't look like regular
huh wo they
sparkle what are
those
oh I guess I must really be a rock
person then tck the gem on my chest huh
oh
yeah I do have something on my chest wow
that's
surprising
wo is this my core it changes
color huh who wait a second let me try
hey click make me make me mad or
something make me make me
mad uh make me angry or something uh
uh I BL chest hey that's
Ru
[Music]
wo how dare you wait first of all how
dare you how how dare you but oh wow
look it's red wait okay okay okay okay
okay make me sad make me sad make me
make me make me make me
[Music]
sad do
it do it
[Music]
me
no no silk
song Wait there's something in my
memories about
waiting for something called Silk song I
can't quite remember what that means but
it I feel like I've been waiting for it
for a long
time
wo it's blue now I'm so sad why why am I
crying why am I so sad about this this
silk song thing
[Music]
huh why am I so sad about this wow
wow this is cool man I'm I must be keki
beu then
wow wait a second where where am I hold
on do you guys see this you guys you
guys see
this wa wait who are
you there's cute girls
everywhere wear in a
box well wait was that a
dog he has a fuzzy tail oh is that a
bird a a bird where's her wings oh she's
got Wings back there I Wonder If She
lays egg do you think she lays
eggs oh she's backing away oh do you
think I scared her I don't know
[Music]
who oh the dog is approaching me
uh are you dangerous are you a dangerous
dog wait there's two there's two there's
two dogs wait
huh there's two move them they look the
same
huh there's why are you guys saying BW
bow bow bow it it seems
like that
word bow bow
bow H wait who else is
here oh oh pretty green lady oh she's
pretty
I feel I feel like a motherly
motherly I like I'm drawn to her like
she's my she
she she feels
like maternal to me like I feel like I
recognize
her huh she's so
pretty oh I mean well look at look at
look at her
eyes wow she's my Nemesis she wait she's
my nemeses oh look look a cute shark I
love sharks oh this this is so cute oh
there's another green lady over
there oh there's so many there's so many
cute girls
oh
oh they're together
I I feel I feel like a word is forming
uh
um amama amama what does that mean
amama amama what does that mean
huh oh oh
oh look at her she's pretty
H oh she's got a flame on her chest ooh
sorry I'm checking you
out I feel like I feel like her
name everyone's talking oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh
oh
for
for what
oh we're back we're
back we're we're back I I guess we're
back
yeah made
it hello jump
scare was H I think my bra died for
[Music]
I just wanted to touch you yes
I what about
you I'm
a what do you mean by that taller than
you lost child what a she
you know what you're my enemy I decided
you're my enemy now yeah you're
[Music]
my
hours are we
lover I can't St
forever I'm not talking
talking okay okay
EXC what what's your
name
my oh you know your name I don't even
know what my name Isom
people oh okay what if they like
lied yeah but what if
they What if I about being your what I
your money
you no no I would never
li no you can trust me look at
me
I exactly I don't
trust I
like Twinkle Toes you call Twinkle
Toes I called you reverse
proximity back up back up no it's okay
make up I'll make it up to
you fight
you you Bight me you Bight me oh yeah
I'll play you yeah that's that's a lot
for
first SOI who are you
hard are you okay I'm told my name is
I'm trying to get you in my right ear I
seen you somewhere before I don't know
you look kind of familiar you kind of
look fatherly you know done that before
you have like a fatherly Vibe why would
you get that impression I don't know I'm
supposed to be a cute girl right just I
it in my
heart well what's your name
again I don't know if I can be a dad
though that sounds like a lot of
responsibility I don't know why but
[Music]
I'm maybe the wall
slowly who heck is that like aing huh
shees hello maybe it's the letters
floating above her head are you those
letters threat to my corner co co
co what do you call I
I am I've been
[Music]
told what should I call you guys
the in the chat the
B nice to meet you the capital T Capital
my name is the B okay the
B yes I'm beu and you
Echoes of
Forgotten memories P the sneaky what's
the
sneaky Who I
Am the world I live
in and more than
anything the people I hold most
here faced with the
Oblivion I
feel
[Music]
empty
relieved
perhap
distra is is any of this for real or
not I do not
know
wa so much I don't know and
yet so much I don't know and yet
oh that bright light it call don't go
into the light does call to me
oh so much I don't
know going into the bright I am kind of
concerned
I'm again I mean everybody's going so I
guess I should
go to the light light follow the
light than to the light light the light
is this it oh
are we going to shirt up do we shirt
up
scared very powerful with
this I don't like I don't like that I
don't I don't want take me take me
aliens to be Dad wait what is an
alien I don't like this I'd rather be
back in the shadows
I liked better was it's black I like
this that looks like an egg this is much
yeah
right that looks like a it's like a
broken egg what is a soul gem is this a
hole looks like a hole oh it's not a
hole a hole
guys you see
[Music]
that live Liv is still castle where am I
hey who are
you you there what are you doing I don't
know I got hit with something now I
don't know who I am you have a look of
Outsiders about you
Outsiders
huh wait could it
be quick send word to his
majesty wait are you guys are you guys
the government I I never liked the
government the the heroes have arrived
at the sanctuary what I don't want to be
I'm not a hero right away
huh Royal
audience
gamer welcome Heroes this is the kingdom
of live Liv St and I its king oh
interesting wow he's so
cute the gods who brought you here have
informed me that you remember not by
your own
names yeah I'm CL
beu a side effect of travel between
worlds no doubt is this a what what's
the word did I get Easter
kind this must all come as a surprise to
you but hearken well it was I who
summoned you here you see an
unprecedented Calamity now threatens our
world it has sewn the Earth with
corruption and driven us from our homes
can I can I go home can I go back to
sleep this seems like too much too much
this blooded land now gives rise to
creatures of Shadow known as stains ooh
Shadows I like
that I like
I the kingdom of L and it surround these
are now the only safe place to us leave
stand but should the Calamity be left
unchecked it is only a matter of time
before it consumes the entire world wow
I think that's a you
problem oh
oh yes faced with this Prospect I
scoured the ancient hex for a way to
combat the Calamity and therein I found
one the ritual
of hero summoning what's a sticky key I
don't know what that
means you who H from another world have
been summoned here by me oh you summoned
oh you it's your fault huh to become the
saviors of Lea sto oh only you have the
power to save our
world
huh me so I asked will you
no yeah your
majesty what is
it a great host of stains has broken
through our defensive line
uh-oh
no we are rushing to mount a defense but
the situation is D Your Majesty we must
get you somewhere
safe how do you how do you how what is
the sticky keys and how do how do I how
do I how do I on on the sticky how what
what what is the sticky key and how do I
how do I
uh
[Music]
ah okay okay okay
okay what who are these strangers
let's say you Heroes will you accept
this Dy no but
sure is there there's a great power
within you will use it to save us to
save this world
world who are
you my name is
oh so
you're okay okay that's what I'll call
[Music]
you nice to meet
you yeah a pleasure to meet you
pleasure pleasure pleasure
see I am very happy
yes I'm sorry there so many
voes you you're my
enemy are you sure hey do you know the
language of this world if anyone's
talking
outside the heroes I cannot
understand because you who has the power
of privacy please tell me if these NPCs
are talking uh uh I don't think they
are oh good good to know I thought I was
going death I think they're just staring
at us yeah okay they disgust me with
their facial hair oh but hey voes in my
head if you got facial hair I bet you
look
good oh you have voices in your head
too oh yeah yeah do you yeah I have
voices in my head too they keep
commenting about me being stupid and
sticky keys you have a good oh no I'm
sure your sticky keys are like stickily
wonderful yeah I don't know what s keys
are I I I would stick with you anytime
you know thank you wait oh they're
talking they
are why did I feel
using so many words I don't understand
these words we come from a land of
simple
words
anybody together oh look at that look at
that
don't shoot I got youer I got you what
I
[Music]
would what oh I guess you can't die
world what was
thatuh we made it I'm okay oh I must
battle I think this
is I'm right here what you call short
[Music]
H this is this is back into combat back
into
comat
die I'm going stay away from it no I'm
dying
oh that's the Str
I'm
[Music]
okay violence I must go back into
battle got Xbox
microphone I there is in
any why is it so cute
shout
Revelation
what
Revelation am I saying it
wrong
re revelate
time re
revoltion a
revolation
revelation
uh re it's not the bread
oh
well um t m it feels like the voices in
my head are are
uh are
um figuring things out yeah
[Music]
uh anyway I'm kizu that's what I've
learned uh the goth girl is my enemy
who's Kyla I don't know who's KY um
there's two cute dogs there's two of
them I don't know if that's a that's a
thing but
um and there was there was this rat girl
her name was what the B and and and then
um was yeah the bay her name was the Bay
okay so do you guys know who any of
these people are you guys know voices in
my
head and then and then there was g in G
or something like that hold on Tate I
feel
like I feel like my head is too empty I
think I need like something to fill it
in I feel like there's a song like is
this the part where I like break into
song or something like that
um
wo is that how it works I think of a
song and it just plays
wow wait what why are you saying
sticking out when am I supposed to stick
out
huh you're saying words that I don't
understand thinking what does that mean
what's a god what I don't understand any
of these words you're
saying nothing don't ask well now I'm
curious what what are you talking about
sticking SCU what's a SCU
[Music]
huh
H isn't isn't tax a bad thing I don't
really remember too much about but isn't
aren't people like supposed to avoid
taces like I don't it just feels gross
to me Tac is
like you like this new be you wait does
that mean you know who I was
before huh you guys know me like
[Music]
actually maybe we can't talk what do you
mean you can't talk about are you hiding
things from
me bble what's that that sounds wrong
what's a bble
be I'm I'm kizu that's my name I feel it
in my heart
kizu NDA what's an
NDA that's a funny word n what's that
stand for you're under it can't you
climb out of
it oh I like this music
[Music]
ask me no secrets I tell no wait I want
a no
secret you remember tomato what's a
tomato no I don't like tomatoes I
remember some of my favorite foods but I
also remember some of my dislikes and
tomatoes are gross I don't like
that tomato yeah
no does your name Virgil ring SP who's
that
huh you like strawberry
milk I've never had it before but maybe
if I tried it I would like it my oosi
what's an
Oshi you you guys are saying so many
words I don't
understand huh
H I'm I'm very confused right
[Music]
now please say ARA ARA ARA
ARA okay I said it now
what you know what milk means milk is a
drink right it's a it's
a a liquid
a a
liquid it's a drink right from uh from
cows the oh yeah that goth girl reminded
me of a
cow
[Music]
yeah a Jeep what's the Jeep is that is
that a car oh yeah it's a car isn't it a
car I know what a Jeep is I remember now
it's one of those like it's a really
really big car um it's kind of hard to
like climb into cuz it's really tall
yeah yeah je yeah I know what you're
talking about why are you spamming it
though did I have one did I have a
Jeep I can I have a car I can drive I
didn't know I could drive
oh wow I can
drive W we're going to I got to I got to
find my deep
[Music]
then deep is your sheep that doesn't
make
sense a Jeep is a car not a sheep what
do you
mean deep don't
[Music]
go let's go back here for a second I I
felt I felt a little
oh I felt a little uh unsteady in the
void even though I felt it was the void
felt a little too comfortable I might
have fallen asleep and I feel like now
is not the best time to fall asleep so
we're going to we're going to hang out
here for a bit until until everything in
my head gets rearranged
yeah where are we I don't
know this place this place is nice it's
kind of bright
though but there's like a castle back
there oh was that the castle that we
were just at
oh interesting is that castle mine is it
do I am I a princess wait am I a
princess am I a am I a wait I it does
look like I have a
crown and and I'm wearing a dress that
that looks pretty Royal so am I a
princess
wow wait does that mean wait does that
mean you guys are my subject
well I can't be oh t m the voices in my
head are compelling me to go
somewhere de shaboo oh my God we're back
guys did you know we we failed to save
the world once that was that was the
that was the world oh my God wait so is
this like a different timeline we fa
forces have turned the
[Music]
time is this kind of where you go back
going to have to redo everything get me
out of
here save the
world
you Mar I'm not going to call off my
marriage we're going to call off this
journey and going to go to
your and I
will
you we have
[Music]
going to eat us a piece of
bread I gave you my
[Music]
bread
fig keep my on yellow
yellows hello e bre you seem sturdy oh I
I I think I am pretty sturdy bre CL have
you
SE
go like rock candy oh please don't eat
that please don't eat my feet no wait
please
my was
the it was the
no
I out of this box no it was me I don't
have any was the pink cat okay she's not
very nice is she the ba it's you
again oh J I thought you were slain I
thought you were slain I saw you
die
SL I think we were all slain
echo of Forgotten memories it did reset
everything reset Who I Am the world I
live in I feel like this has happened
before the more than
anything the people I
I've face with oblivian I feel
empty reles I've totally done this
before Skipper Skipper what's a skipper
oh well I do not
know oh I should
have I would love going going towards
the light oh oh are we're going toward
the light again oh you welcome back I
feel like I jumped of you guys before
yeah funny
huh yeah for some reason you remind me
of a cow sort of loop a cow yeah wow
might me of something small and rock
hard does that mean am I
hard I make you hard
baby bro
what what who are you I don't know who
who are you yeah who are you what's your
the voices in my head told me to call
you be boo I no I'm not does that ring a
bell I'm not
she boo boo yeah I don't know what a b
boo is either I have no idea where they
got that from what's AO I'm closeu I've
never heard that that's what I thought
too yeah I'm they said that you were my
wife wait I thought we I've never seen
you before in my life it I don't see a
ring on you
either yeah me too maybe you guys should
kiss something bad
happening okay I don't know it's the
first meeting I'm not ready I don't know
who she
is I don't she is we didn't fin
our I'm looking for voes in my head said
that you my
wife got taken away from because I find
you very attractive have you I'll give
you can I give you look at that behind
there you go
I like
[Applause]
her wait wait what's your
name say that again
no I'm a good Reaper I'm not going to
tou what's your name I'm
I'm back here again beeping
government dragged back here Skipper or
whatever you say no more sticky keys for
me get out of
here sticky
what there's nothing
sticky babo I don't want to I've seen
you
before get
out I don't want to help you with this
Calamity oh but maybe wait maybe I do
have to help them is is that the reason
we got reset am I forced to help
them is that
it is that it is that why we died cuz I
didn't want to help them maybe we have
to help
them
oh government mandated dang
it dang it wait why did I say dang it
that feels like something that I say
dang it huh
what's
going this is
crazy tell everyone wait I know what
happens there's going to be enemies you
know what happens yeah there's going to
be enemies don't you remember don't you
guys I remember you guys don't remember
there was a battle right here am I crazy
yeah no I remember too are we in an
endless
loop probably I want to follow her how
do we break it I don't know we need to
kill someone we need to
kill yeah let's kill someone yeah anyone
will do oh you I won't die without
a don't you purple like why why you
smell like chicken please
don't offer know man why are you purple
like the stains purple like the stains
am I a bad
guy maybe you're the evil one gosh that
makes all of you my enemies then
oh Yi how exciting maybe we can top that
and
have hey why do you two look the same is
this a TW
Dem hey hey why guys why do you guys
look the same why I tou your
tail I don't know it feels little weird
to me
why maybe there's an imposter
they don't seem to know each other
either I'm here to save the de oh I hurt
myself I know her she was trying to beat
me
up no buies allow I'll protect
you I will use my sword as a weapon of
oh I have food
now wait P person P person I have food
now here you go take it it's a
weapon no no could you pray for me thank
you I appreciate it hey she's talking to
me dogs get
[Music]
away find me beautiful help D two dogs
two dogs are attacking me for no reason
dogs we'll protect you it say it's GL
she
PRS well
I I I don't think I have heard it but I
think you should leave her alone whoever
you
are yeah don't be a
bully I'm not bullying her I'm just
bully I'm just letting see the pring do
do you look like you might be a dog so
do you
bark hi yeah yeah you yeah bark for me
yeah bark for me yeah bark for
me yeah yeah come on puppy yeah bar you
have dog ears in a tail oh
bark for me too yeah bark for me B but
that's barking B it's cute though bow
bow bow yeah she is barking don't that's
why you hate me I don't hate you your
Pur okay can you I want to hear too I'm
a little
curious wait the big guys are talking
again D of this place okay
a you're it is nice
y fall the CR don't don't H me anym wait
I'm ready they they were right here I
remember from my past life yeah they
were right here going to happen here
it's going to happen I remember still in
the soil what do you remember welcome I
remember
you uh what's your
Jonathan no my name is
Jonathan Jonathan Jonathan G yeah gathan
J yes yeah gz G
Jonathan do
it live the king
[Music]
wait I
I
[Music]
maybe we got to get we got to get the
first well
done
vehicle down
go
okay really
don't let him get you
[Music]
nice
okay we
have so
cute die I'll protect
you exp no no no no you
don't see why you might feel bad jumped
into the air watch out are we winning
paist he's like a Bo oh out there's more
over here get the
r yeah I'm scared we better not lose
this Loop
then oh
[Music]
no oh no the dog died
fuzzy one what did we
make oh there's a wall f look at the
hero Myst serious
light what's this Revelation signing
emotion what's this what's this
item
um revelation
W the stain host has been
routed
H you fought bravely kind Heroes I pray
are you not
injured that Mighty armored one must be
their leader the stain King fascinating
most fascinating
well I see why they call you Heroes we
being a right pickle without your help
do they have accent wait a second we
sustained minimal damage thanks to your
Valor our kingdom is in your de thank
you I must hasten to inform His Majesty
of our Victory will you accompany me
Royal audience
[Music]
chamber I heard the news though we
called upon you suddenly you Rose to the
occasion you have my deepest gratitude a
chair can I sit on it can I sit on it
wait it's empty let me sit on it hey hey
hey who own this chair what interested
me most however is the strange power you
manifested during the B
which you were able to defeat the the
stains that power may be well the key to
saving our world from
Annihilation according to the heroes the
power came from them like a forgotten
memory when they spoke the word
revelation also who's talking to
me but once they used it to Route the
stained host it seems that the power
vanage without a TR my power my power
where did it go well that's bloody
brilliant in it so what are oh so that
one's British okay what are we what's
what's a British what are we supposed to
do Revelation we must uncover the
secrets of this phenomenon if we are to
Prevail against the
Calamity many questions remain but one
thing is certain the kingdom of Li stall
is still stands today thanks to you yeah
thanks to me here here so Heroes I ask
you once more will you lend us your
strength to save Le still from
ruin uh sure I was forced to nod okay uh
marvelous on behalf of all Liv St I
thank you we are blessed to have your
Aid kind
Heroes allow me to introduce the four
Great guilds which are responsible for
ensuring the Kingdom's peace and
prosperity The Haven for all the Curious
where knowledge and creativity are Valu
above all the Scarlet
wand the home of for Glory Seekers with
ambition and vision where the closest
allies become fiercest Rivals the Amber
coin the stom of healing where the
spirit of empathy and devotion thrives
the seruan
cup and the beacon of the righteous and
loyal where the great threats are faced
with even greater courage the Jade
St one of these Guild will become your
home during the time
here
oh Beyond this door lies the room of
Truth therein the will of the ancestor
shall decide your guild fear not
introspection is also a vital step on
the road to Enlightenment exeler as I
always say ever
higher time to roll the die say be
seeing some old you lock down at the
Amber coin Guild
Hall let us save this world
together the room of Truth awaits go
forth with
Valor I'm going forth I'm getting pushed
up room of Truth step on the platform
and receive the will of the ancestor o I
got my weapon
wait what
is oh I can't
W oh okay I'm going distract got I got
to step on it I got to step on the
thing seek the power that Amber
grbs ran
cup wait didn't it say didn't it say
this one is is is is uh what is this one
again da the
cloak oh I got a
[Music]
cloak
ah wait
ah armed with an unwavering will seek to
defend the soul of
[Music]
Jade enigmatic
reflection where's my horse okay that's
so cool what horses they so
quick Kaku
I Jonathan do do I have Jonathan J
you're here Jonathan G it's Jonathan G
GG for
short uh I think there's uh something a
little little the different about your K
really oh yes oh oh my goodness W are
you an
imposter wa what do you mean you're
going ah I cannot beare look at you what
you are an impost
evil your black cape where is that where
did you get that from the the St what
I'm one of you you're you want to wait
so are we all ceran was that it we are
all ceruleans EX one of
us a different The Guild Master oh
Master Guild Master I am on my
horse Dan is busting upon you hero
welcome to the Guild Hall of the Cilan
cup
I didn't read the first
part where even so soon after your
summoning speaks volumes about your
selflessness oh oh as a member of this
Guild you'll be joining the effort to
cleanse this land of stains and bring
Salvation to the
world but one must walk a one can run
first you should learn about the town we
strive to protect as well as how to
accept and perform quests
Quest within this town there is a
location known as the quest board o
where is it where is the quest there you
will find the quest master who will
impart his knowledge upon you you may
also use this time to familiarize
yourself with the town o oh it's a quest
speak to the quest matter
okay okay where did she go where'd she
go where'd she
go huh
she she uh is really fast yeah well we
just keep going this way okay I believe
you
guys I guess we can ride horses oh wait
how do
I
W oh Quest board Quest board beautiful
seeds everyone you too thank you thank
you his name is you must be one of the
heroes then the guill master told me to
expect you I thank you for risting your
lives to protect our Fen Kingdom uh
guildmates how do I get off my horse uh
shf sneak sneak thank you than thank you
thank thank you thank you thank you very
much thank
you understand your main duty is rid the
St but I hope you'll take time to help
some citizens in
need he must be tired of my battle by
now so how about we can't you started
with the quest right away I see looks
like perfect job for you well best of
luck oh you go now which which Quest
should we take complete the side quest
the options what what are the side
quest okay we can I can read these right
I think so materials needed at the
smithing I'm The Apprentice at the smiy
and my master says we're running low on
raw materials if you can help us gather
some please stop by the Smith can we
only take that Quest it looks like so
everything's the same okay Quest
accepted
I will get on my horse too oh okay I
accept it accept it what is the
SMY uh
SMY SM where is where art the thise
there is a map so we can maybe look
around and uh
what oh oh did I did I accept
it oh
yes where's the black
smiy would be is this a smothie n yes oh
is it
SMY
SMY materials
needed what do you need what you
[Applause]
need oh great you saw my quest I posted
well to start with could you bring over
10 Oak locks there are a bunch of trees
not far outside town you can chop
[Music]
trees this person over
here all
theen oh we'll get 100 coins upon
completion 100 coins we can buy food
with that we'll be rich why am I in a
different
party what's the name of your horse of
your
seed
G oh mine is ninoa oh
what is
your yeah what's what's the name of your
horse
Tam I think it's
uh a co wait are you are you guys all in
the same party together not yet should
we join a party shall we party up I I
how do I leave my
party join the party in a party I got
kid by a random party I don't know how I
did it you're just in a party yeah
without us
[Music]
huh I got kidnapped oh
well by who by I'm green someone named
I'm
green I'm purple I'm green stole you
yeah she stole me I'm in her party for
some reason can't believe this
strange kind of scary I'm trying I'm I'm
calling upon the scriptures to see how
to leave a party yes I I do not know how
to leave this I've been
kidnapped okay
well let's let's see maybe did you get
that party
invite I did I did
not hold on how do I
[Applause]
[Music]
accept let me let me look at the
scriptures
the scriptures the scriptures on how to
free ourselves from someone's
party
aha oh the voices in my head are very it
said I have to find the person who
invited me but I don't know who invited
[Laughter]
me oh there's I'm green
so she wasn't just made up I see she's
probably very far away cuz we
[Music]
don't see
her return Our member to
us oh maybe the magic to can help try
your magic to oh Magic to oh there was
something really sparkly over there for
a second did you guys see
that where in of the quest board ooh the
magical toe wait it says I'm not a
member of a party but I'm in I'm in a
party huh what what I did not mean to
trade you oh I failed to invite
you maybe
[Applause]
mayhaps oh might I think that if you go
to page four of the magical toone you
may be able to leave
that's magical to I I I I think I
pressed that magical toome and it says
that I am not a member of a party but on
the my screen it says I'm a part of a
party so this mag perhaps you might need
to
uh unconscious yourself AKA oh yeah
perhaps perhaps I will I will close my
eyes and um go to sleep and
[Music]
then and uh I will give you some privacy
I will look away from you yeah hold on
[Music]
look oh she just to the land W come
back are you still in a party I'm good
now I have escaped the grass of the
random people yes what in wait why is
they fail to invite player
we
[Music]
[Applause]
good why why can I can someone else try
to invite her to our party I think only
party leaders can so strange that is
difficult is still in a party how about
we remake the party how do we remake a
party uh you click on your magical toone
and then magical
toone I've disbanded my party I will
invite you no fail to invite
oh
[Music]
a it's okay I
will I will
be the long
the Lone Wolf I I guess it is my destiny
to work
alone I
suppose free her free
m who is
eating it's
Gigi
you I was hungry in Minecraft oh oh yes
what is Minecraft
I mean I mean what's a m an enigmatic
recollection what an enigmatic
recollection we are know I don't
remember onward back to the quest board
oh yes yes I don't think we they're in
we're in oh wait they are there oh
oh everyone's here she
is okay okay stand still you don't move
I will free you I will K you from my
party wonderful
woman okay
okaying how do I
we're in the party now okay everyone
let's go get wood and beat the other
team beat other team speed running go
horse
go the other teams can't catch upad of
them we are so so
ahead ex wait uh
uh is this the
exit yes
yes okay let's go I killing the chicken
no not part of our Quest that's not part
of our Quest it's a part of a future
Quest have a point die chicken what are
you we seek your eggs you look okay
never mind you look familiar to me why
are you looking
away who are
you
wait there's something familiar about
[Music]
yes there's another
one help help
help oh there's a
rabbit oh you get money to
grind oh okay I'm helping I got to do
are you okay Mr sheep person you okay
okay that sheep person's
okay okay oh my God they're spawning
outside the walls at anomic
rate away wow we're so fast when we do
it
together yeah yeah we completed the
objective did you complete your
objective I don't think so okay oh I got
eight coins from killing that will it
will it say when you complete the
objective are you guys okay okay I guess
I just got to keep
going ow you can also check your
inventory just to double check oh my
inventory my pocket oh I think I need
two
[Music]
more oh my objective is done
it's not called Revelation but you may
use Revelation okay oh wait can
iation I want to see a revelation
reation
Revelation H oh that was very cool we
got 20 coins yeah let me see your
Revelations it's on I am tired now oh
tired yeah I have a cool down yes I have
a refractory period yeah these are some
magical trees yeah they they come back
to life the
trees wow the spawn rate on this is
insane crazy yeah crazy stain slime ball
can be thr why would it spot on top of
me did everyone finish their objective
yes yes let us we back let okay H we
cannot let them catch up I summon
yours okay let's just onward to the the
black the smiy yes which is which
was uh oh there they know the way wa
what does that do you cannot use the
enchantment great you brought the thank
you so much see my there bring the raw
materialss and
for
hello people scare
me wait you brought the thank you so
much to my master over
there okay I do not required
materials we need place it ha Fallen to
their death hath Fallen po not CRA this
want Scarlet wand member oh great we saw
the quest they posted while you bring 10
okay it looks like we need material
failed to purchase we are missing four
five how do I make a oak logs I think
that's very easy my friend oh I
think I think we got to speak to the
quest Master information to C compl
exactly completed s just that easy my
friends
h o of
easy interesting I have an
axe I think we need to speak to the
quest Master since we completed the
quest or maybe we have quest to speak to
the
master master did you say what we needed
collect 10
cobblestones onward my
ah okay somehow I had the wood and gave
it to him I'm I think I'm
[Music]
confused
oh we need Oak Plank and
stick can we craft that here
okay is that it
can
I surely not
right oh we can make Oak planks
okay three Oak
planks maybe I have to go to the quest
Master again
yeah how do you stick
oh
oh okay I need more
plank yay
okay now we go back oh hey it's boo boo
oh hey
what booo what' you call me what' you
say who are you call boooo
honey yeah hey what what weapon do you
have you have like rock candy what do
you have though show me your show me
your
Revelation okay it takes a
while so cool instant
TP oh nice I cast
I think my father's failing to people
right now probably
forever oh how did I how did I do that
oh oh crap I think I just off my
cat oh I can trade with you and I can
invite you to
party no not don't invite her again
we've been through
thisy the way 10 cobblestones and speaks
the blacksmith P okay I I must go when
people need
me okay how fun oh farewell oh I wasn't
talking to
you we can leave the radio now oh yes
now that we are together we can hang up
the phone call as the Le bye my fellow
party members good day sir
[Applause]
hello Question Master oh hello I don't
oh
yeah do where are
you hit got hit a little bit too hard on
the head and is lost now um I may I get
picked up please if you if you look
above at the top of your your your
eyesight at the top of your vision what
do the words at the top of your head say
I speak with Quest
Master oh return to the quest board oh
okay oh there you are I wait to you yay
let us speak to the quest
master I hung up on you oh okay okay
okay I will also hang
up never mind I don't
know what I am
speaking is it working yeah yeah yeah
you just need to you need to talk to him
and then you need to click here to
accept the quest on the actual
born hey this looks like the perfect job
for
you joyous day oh
teammate I will I will I them
what does to M mean I just came out of
my mouth talk to
him yeah let's go turn it
in compl the you did it from now on when
you find
St the more different materials you find
B the logs Master you bring the raw
materials to him he can make all sort of
toolss and items for
you you can craft logs into planks and
planks into sticks from your inventory
I'm on Cobblestone now sticks seem
useful
like party
member Miss party
member ah yes yes I'm on should we just
stay in the coal yes perhaps I think we
should
[Music]
okay okay I found a call the others yes
call the others yes this is the
the seru in the end we're helping those
ined yes we call as as is the rule of
the seruan um
team
and and
devotion
a deliver a wood
shovel okay that's easy oh hell hello
hello hello oh can they have can they
hear us in the call I don't think so oh
I can hear you I can we can hear you
guys yeah even if you're in a call we
can still
hear because we have ears and you are
next to us so
uh all right are we ready to complete
more quests yes I would love to complete
more Quest I just finish the the
cobblestones one I'm not sure what to do
oh we can we finish Quest Master
crafting a stone pickaxe and a wooden
shovel oh I need to collect a
cobblestone I have not done that yet yes
yes
yes where where where would one go to
fire de
Stone you go out where weall got the got
the wood go a little further and there
should be a mound of stone okay let us
make haste oh it's let us make haste let
us make haste I've being
escorted wow the adventure
adventure L should we create should we
create a party uh no there's a party
leader right now she would have to
invite you inside the kingdom walls got
our pickaxes swinging side to side for
some reason to this makes me feel a
little sick watching this happen
I don't know I just I just feel I feel
some sort of attachment to these to
these solid like beings I feel a little
sick that you're destroying them H oh
wait
apparently CH says they become
Bedrock but it feels like they I don't
want to I don't want to hurt them though
it feels like against my nature to hurt
them here I will give you I will engage
in trade oh trade
yes and then I will give
you 10 of these things oh thank you you
are not hurting them oh I don't have to
hurt them I've already done it yes thank
you don't have to hurt them wow so kind
you're so
kind of course it's part of the ceran
way of behind you
motion oh wow so strong I protected you
you are so strong thank you I owe you my
life Wow
should we uh perhaps ask the uh ask the
to join the the group group
call call maybe maybe we should stay on
the group call so that way we do not oh
oh perhaps when we get separated we can
still
discuss okay okay yes
yes doesn't
work woohoo quick let us return
return ring ring ring yes this is Tam
Gander we are thinking that we should
stay on the phone call just in case we
leave each
other's hearing range yes I believe that
is a splendid idea spend thank you
Splendid
Splendid joyous
oh Jo amazing
wonderful oh you have to
trade we got to make planks and sticks
all right okay we
need running out of though I was I was
trying to skip the process I understand
maybe I should ride my horse so I don't
get hungry see I got this one chance um
perhaps my my
group it must I might have to resort to
the violence against the rocks it does
why oh you must do it yourself I must do
it myself no you have she has to hurt
very she does not want to Cobblestone 16
shovel great okay where is the
shopkeeper we are going to I see it well
I am going to complete a
[Music]
quest I did it there are there are so
many it's
oh oh God damn it there are more quests
we have so many quests to do huzzah I
love the town people these Quest
slop you can repeat the quest you can
repeat the quest it's a repeat Quest
you're so
needy wow talk to the shopkeeper
the shopkeeper stain
he
[Music]
lapis potato salad maybe they have some
bread I have to speak to the child in
the garden child in the garden they're
the child I must I'm so sorry my the
BART
friends what's going on do you need
assistance
no I killed them all okay oh
no it must have been very hard my
friends where did all of you go I'm
trying to child okay I will meet with
you cuz I do not know where the child
is oh I see you my fellow Maiden it's a
p hello pubs usually have food did you
speak to to the child in the gardens
already
mayhaps where is the child in the
gardens I know not I was hoping you
would know where the child in the
garden's rest the child in the garden
the child in the
garden is this the child in the garden
child where are you oh I see it's the
child in the garden oh what about a few
many Ys away y
I have a feeling children be dangerous
let us make haste I am making haste to
the child in the
gardens the
garden my horse cannot jump get it it
can't jump never mind my horse can
nigh yes there is a Le best child right
here I
have able to make you let us speak with
you okay don't to us please everyone's
doing what they can just like you talk
to him Master the child does absolutely
nothing we are spreading joy and
heroism to this
to that's where the shop
is we are aspiring him you too can be a
hero when you grow up if you just look
to the sky and Shout revelation
to my mouth
I
epic you are
too leaders to empathy all right empathy
yes you may grow up to become a shoper
one day or master or a hero or
great what's an NPC what's an NP see
these are just know it just popped into
my
head oh a lot of things seem to pop in
your head wonder what the cam tastes
like it's like tip of my
tongue I wonder if it tastes like
cookies I feeling C of I don't
know what supped do now cookies I think
we have to go back to the maybe the
shape of our tongue your tongue tastes
like
cookies only thing you can
buy
potions master master of the quest I
have 693 points I
do
this I forgot what the quest told new is
here we have to speak
to dor why do I have so much heck
are there so many two girls sorry I so
hry get my
nail I don't know I found they come from
you seem to know very well about this
realm you are very well acquainted how
do you know
my are you does
thou where the shopkeepers
are across the way from the Smithy the
Smithy thank you my trusty companions I
appreciate it no problem why do we all
talk like this I have no idea like
what like what wow it is just how we
speak we can build our own marus Guild
House Brut dear friend Guild House let
us build our own Guild
House I think the quest is done Jo day
let us day let us make our humble AB yes
our humble abod we have our little plot
on the uh near the wall uh let us Build
Together Miss Miss time
lady yes Rock I okay shop I I have
seemed to have lost my way shop is this
way oh thank
you yes no problem oh I I very much
appreciate your guidance thank
you
anytime rock thank you
clock oh nice nice potions 100
coins where is this place
a
Coliseum oh I like the way it
thinks
what
please accept our call for
[Music]
theop sneak sneak sneak sneak why are
you sneaking so much I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm sneaking
sneaking remind me of a sneaking I don't
know I think I'm starting to remember a
certain song about sneaking like a
sneaking oh like a sneaking how do you
all know that song have you same
area are you still on your first
Quest song you all up with nurser ride
may have it could be
[Music]
may excuse me excuse me uh you you you
seem to have a blue aura around you Dam
it I
do B found it I found it with I am on
the way where is she
her who are these people
no she's ours now she's ours trying to
take
her
my were not there when she needed you
quick come with me join our team even
know
we I think it's late now Al
so okay you our what what you're
disappearing my friend honestly if you
want to be with us you can be with
us help you your come here come here
come here let's go
Iris you would
leave walking
away she's her they're taking her away
do not stop taking her she's
I know you have two hes one dark and and
a lighter one you must listen to the
darker one her back oh my go she's
suddenly hitting me she's suddenly
hitting
[Music]
me I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm
sorry I'm sorry sorry
[Applause]
I'm hey Revelation revelation reation
Revelation
reation
Revelation Revelation
Revelation done oh nice fist oh thank
everyone has such cool
moves they look like from a retro game
Revelation re everyone has such cool
moves a retro game I know not yeah yes I
know not of what you speak who are you
youti
beautiful violin lady oh at least you
know I am to be the next Queen of the
kingdom of lesto what I did not know of
your intention how you say it this is
not an intention this is meant to be
your destiny it was meant to be it was
meant to be are you are you related to
them are you their I we have blood
related are you blood related to that
tiny King what no we guys and we knew
that we were
destined you married the king that's are
you under cover with the
King it's complicated
she she was to propose to
me but you don't have you didn't have to
accept wait I wanted to her to the
[Applause]
power all right all right this is theut
Queen of the liest yes yes
I'm glad you know fellow peasants
peasants my my queen I'm sorry for
speaking to you with such we will not
protect you if you don't respect us
that's why you're in a different
Guild you need to you need to support
the ball again gg gg
gg G help wa stay away from her she is
our new Queen she's to be our Queen
where is she remember that and kill her
later on my side
but return wait I am secretly what is
what is your
name a supporter of this meet you Iris
so to meet you what is your name I see
my name is Jonathan G St the G Jonathan
g g for sure
horse okay okay I'll call you okay G for
short Jonathan J G oh Jonathan Jonathan
Jonathan with a
G yes I I'll call you Jonathan jonath
Jonathan yes oh oh okay yes I would like
that so okay um Queen Jonathan um who
are you hello I have a name not
Queen I would like to be
addressed for
sure so sounds very cute and then who is
this rock that was trying to kidnap me
I'm Ki we're going to go to the
shopkeeper Ki beu you the wow your name
is
be I don't know why that sounds familiar
but slightly different from what I
remember different I don't know I don't
know I've always been yes why am I being
surrounded by so many people we are team
you are one of you are one of
usan cup yes but I but I join another
team you can leave it no no you did not
join another team you are one of us you
youve always been one of us we are
destined for each other really what what
makes this what what what what why why
am I one of you guys in your eyes
because you have empathy have I feel
your aura Dev it'san my team might kind
of being
Su she's one of us you guys don't I
don't know especially you you don't seem
like you would have empathy in
me I am made of empathy you are I am I
am liquid empathy I seen it in her eyes
in Tam's eyes the way she spoke to that
child she is full of
empathy I see yes I will I would have to
discuss with my current uh my current
team members will you return to us it is
a Jonna Watson she wants to kill the
king she wants
she wants to kill
theing oh no she thought she thought
Revelation was Revolution and she was
planning to the
king I mean I can understand that that
misunderstanding but what arrow is the
set in you you will not kill the king
what is even
an leave my friends alone
she wants to kill the king Jan would
never kill the
king Jonathan are we talking about this
one
Watson
wat away from my
M don't talk you
ex excuse me excuse me sound like neck
excuse me you don't talk to a guild
member like that yeah than you your gu M
talking to
my a
Friend the King we are of the J sword
and we are
loyal we are loyal
wee your father's a hamster and your
mother
smells excuse me
that to
me I've never known my mother you
disturbing the piece you know that I'm
so sorry don't listen to whatever they
say is you're crazy hey hey
hey you want to kill the
king let's find out let's let's find out
shouldn't talk about this here they're
listening oh they're listening yes smash
you meet are
you can't talk about this right now why
you
guess I don't know you are too evil give
up Scarlet wand wait Amber
disgusting
disgusting I from that
place disgusting yes Amber we don't
interact we don't
interact do not ever interact with Amber
don't talk to us don't talk to us I will
be don't can't you I can't
you excuse me the air is very loud you
guys from what you guys
from you are a king killer you are the
king now I can report you
guys I'm going to report you
guys he hey that's not a good idea hey
hey hey hey hey that's not a he has
absolutely absolutely run that's not the
right where are you
running where are you headed to she's
going to report us where is she
reporting us too I have no idea the
quest
Master my goodness the truth we are val
honesty in this group do you think sure
do this what
H yeah we totally could do that what
else do you can totally see that
happening in Naruto what what else what
is Naruto what is Naruto what do you
exactly what it sounds like what I don't
know what it sounds like did you just
make a the first thing that comes to
your head this is my re
my Revelation
isn't never I would
never she saw that one movie do you she
that one movie where they sing and make
din she a pretty girl heyan yes I
thought you were about to say do you
know John Cena I'm sorry
I'm
Cena is he around here I can't see him I
who John Cena who is Jonathan John Cena
who that Jonathan you guys hear a
familiar jingle whenever you hear that
name Jonathan Jonathan is
this
know how do I
know G are you going to me gathan coming
back no it's no it's
j Amber I know but if you kill him he'll
be gone oh yes yes
I I put my my name on the line us Amber
coin have nothing to do with Amber you
on the Amber team are you of Amber she's
of Amber you Amber what's wrong with
Miser understanding you on the what are
you talking about I'm in your team I'm
in your party no you are on our
team no you shut huh huh I mean you you
shut your humble
mouth say to me I did not say anything
are I thought you supposed to be a part
of the team I'm Sol level you guys do
not defective yeah I I don't even they
they're the ones who reached out to
helping I you're supposed to refuse it
man you're inan cop oh well I mean I
didn't know you guys were in
youy join our party we should we should
we should remove ourselves from this
should I I
Jo
Jo a tra before they ask any more
questions I don't TR does anyone not
want does anyone be nice here we all
about caring nobody wants you except
nobody oh nobody wants you except us
this really so join wow wow we are so
compassionate empathetic oh we are
compassionate we are taking join you
must open your magical tomb do you see
this the magical book open your magical
book and the locate page four locate
page four magical book
yes and dissolve your
party wait click to disband click to
kick click to leave try leave try to
leave yeah should I maybe say something
before I leave no no just leave no no
get out I mean yeah they You Belong with
us they ditched you they ditched you
they they did they they did they ditch
me did they really ditch me yeah they
ditched you it's not
aing it's not a
misunderstanding you were just a decoy
uh-huh okay you were meant to be with us
you are one of ours let me let me just
say let me just say in chat I was
ditched so I will leave we accept you
for who you are traitor or not you can
make a new leg abandon we we have been
tied by the strings of Fate I'm sorry I
will
switch yes
yes is this really the right
answer this is the right answer nobody
loves you except us yes only we can
accept you for this is very toxic this
feels very tox
don't we we we we are we are the empathy
group we are the group that is full of
empathy
and I'm trying to I'm trying to leave
wait wait wait okay okay I can't open
the book all of a sudden wait
wait oh recycling B on page four of your
magical tomb do you really want to leave
your party yes yes yes yes yes oh I
guess the sword doesn't have I have I I
have alone now I now we we will now join
our team join our party you are one of
us oh okay okay you guys are actually
full of empathy right yes we are full of
kindness we arean cup take our
love okay wow all right now your magic
radio feeling the love and now open your
magic radio yes my magic radio mag this
is Magic this magic radio what do I do
with the radio and join our call us ring
ring our radio call on our is a party
call it's a grou it's a group there we
go yay I feel like I belong you belong
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm not getting anything done let's go
we were supposed to be the calm
one Cal we are calm we are we are calm
we are very calm we're full of empathy
we're kind we're so nice kind we know
love we know peace yes know peace and
love does our ancestors actually know us
I don't think they know us yes maybe
they were like us they wrote history
they like we are the calm Think About by
the way is your quest sorry my beautiful
te yes my beautiful teammates uh uh how
do I check what side quest I'm on oh you
done your magic book one more time and
you you flip to page
two oh check your oh okay okay yes it
says I do not have any active side quest
whaty then you you talk to the board
okay okay the
boardy the quest board okay okay are you
guys are you guys you know fully
already much farther ahead I'm on a
don't are you guys just ahead of me we
are three quests ahead if I were to
guess I see
mayhaps Mays yes I I came I came a
little bit you know a little bit after
you guys probably CU I'm just that
important you know I have to check
something you are we are just so full of
empathy we understand we know why the
boor not the dude empaths okay okay oh
there's so many quests accept all of
them all of them because we are helpful
every Quest I think there's only one
yeah I think there is only one
okay there is only one it looks like a
lot okay and then I go do you want the
fast pass through some of the quest oh
there's a fast pass is this is this giz
what is gizan I have no idea what I'm
talking it's called the uho special oh
the Eno a special please give it to me
me at the Smithy where's the
Smithy the Smithy the I have no idea I
would like a horse where do I where do
you get a where do I get a horse your
egg you crack your egg oh my God horses
are are born from
egg in the best that they are yes
oh well that's NE knowledge is it over
here and how do I get off of it oh there
we go do I just abandon the horse you
press uh you shift the button yes you
sneak ni yeah
gotcha oh
sorry on
okay hello hello fast pass fast pass
hello here is your you are drenched you
are soaked I am drenched yes I just saw
you in the water wait I can't I can't
give items I think you have to trade to
trade oh no are you you have to trade
you get cold okay um no I'm way too you
cannot you cannot Fastpass you must the
actions on her own you're drowning
help
drowning oh yeah drowning
ick
the I
am thank you fast
pass I am a silly
clown
CL you
[Music]
drowning what's going on
to oh my God what the hell's going on oh
I think was someone tortur I think Ro
are you guys torturing somebody no we
having a nice
B I did not man this is such a peaceful
team hands push me under the water go
was it
you no someone was holding me down who
is that must Amber I couldn't get I
couldn't get Amber team must have done
it the Amber coin used their telepathy
on Amber team is the is the ambercoin
our like our our main enemy yes they are
our enemy mhm are oh they are so they're
like they're the ones that we should go
out to kill kind of enemy yes yeah oh in
the name of empathy we must kill
them must I don't think that's show how
empathy Works yes I see I didn't know
empathy was so violent but it makes
sense one of them plans me sometimes
violence is the only answer to to have
empathy show up we have to restore
balance
yes I'm starting to understand a lot of
things thank you you're welcome this is
what empathy means um empathy is to kill
empathy is to kill the bad in this world
empathy means to kill unfortunately my
loyal companions I have a a pool
somewhere from the unknown and I must
withdraw are you being summoned by the
forces beyond your knowledge the
darkness is Clos and I must I must Shar
can drown course um but I believe in you
guys you guys will you come back to us I
I will come back will you come back I
will I will come back to you and come
back to this world as soon as possible
please don't forget about me okay don't
forget I I do not wish to be we will
never please never forget you we will
never forget you please please remember
we never forget you your wise words
okay beu and I will return to you my
companions we will wait till you return
we won't forget we will never forget
please forget you I will I will see you
again I will see you again good goodbye
goodbye
fwell uh uh uh
uh well that was
weird okay my voice is in my head
unfortunately I am getting a a summoned
from the outside world and I must I must
way G Mena sorry whoa what was that Goa
sorry
I my bad um but thank you for helping me
try to recall my
memories as kek beu I don't remember too
much but I found new friends today I've
made some new enemies um
um
and yes the future Queen is in my party
that's an interesting thing to note yes
and there there is this yellow girl on
on another team but she has I think we
have a lining interest I must remember
to meet with her later yes very
interesting but for now full of
compassion and and empathy with my new
my new Guild Guild companions I will
remember this day and look forward to a
brighter tomorrow
so I will see you guys on tomorrow
yes ad farewell for it is the end for
kak be you offer today yes uh tomorrow
see you later the voice in my
head goodbye
[Music]